Leave them here.
- That should go in the back seat.
- Yes, sir.
If you bribe someone like this,
you'll be caught right away.
I guess you could call this a bribe.
Today is your future
father-in-law's birthday.
What?
I'm grateful enough that you came
to wish me a happy birthday.
You really didn't
have to bring anything.
Soo Ryeon, get over here.
Mr. Hwang sent us
this precious gift.
A gift? What gift?
And his son brought it
all the way here in person.
We must expel...
all government-funded professors,
who have lived as parasites...
of the Yushin dictatorship
from our sacred campus!
You must be surprised
that I showed up unannounced,
Soo Ryeon.
Why are you standing around?
Come have a seat.
Guys, come have a seat.
Well, I should get going.
Why? Stay and eat with us.
No, you have a guest.
Oh, are you uncomfortable?
No, I'm fine.
But Soo Ryeon's friend can do
as she wishes.
- I'll get going, then.
- Myeong Hee!
Where are you going?
Stay and eat with us.
No, I should get going.
Come on. I bought a cake.
Just stay and eat with us.
Who might this be?
Oh, Soo Chan.
This is Mr. Hwang's son,
who I told you about the other day.
Oh, the guy
Soo Ryeon has been seeing?
I'm Hwang Hee Tae.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lee Soo Chan,
Soo Ryeon's brother.
(Episode 3, Your One Month)
- Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday.
- Eat up.
- Thank you.
Let's eat. Eat up.
Goodness.
I'm sorry that all we did was put
an extra spoon on the table.
I would've gotten a hen
had you told us you were coming.
A hen? Please, Dad.
If you cooked a hen on top of this,
the table would collapse.
It's a humble spread
but eat as much as you want.
Will do.
By the way, Hee Tae.
Soo Ryeon is such a tomboy.
What do you like about her?
Don't say that you like everything
about her.
That's such a cliche.
Why do you like her?
Well...
This place isn't open
to just anyone.
Can we trust you?
She left a strong first impression
on me.
Right away,
she said we should go print...
some anti-government flyers.
My gosh, you're really something.
Soo Ryeon, what about you?
What do you like about him?
Are you losing your mind?
Why must you ask such a question?
I'm curious too.
I want to know
how you've felt about me until now.
The thing is...
Whatever, never mind.
Let's just eat.
My gosh.
It seems like
you really should get married soon.
I've never seen you get so shy.
I told you!
It's really not like that.
Goodness, you and your temper.
Myeong Hee, you know them well,
don't you?
What?
Oh, the rice cake place.
You said you're a regular.
I should order some rice cakes
for the grand opening.
Will they take good care of me
if I go alone?
Why don't I go there
and place the order for you?
It's very close to my house,
you know.
Let's just go together then.
How about we meet there
before your shift tomorrow?
All right, then. Come on.
Dad, shall I tell them
to come back inside?
No, leave them alone.
Don't ruin the mood.
I'll drop the honorifics
since we're the same age.
What kind of scheme brings you here?
Me?
I'm here to figure out your scheme.
What was your purpose
behind starting this ruse?
And what do you plan to do
going forward?
My purpose and plan? It's simple.
I don't want to marry you.
Go ahead and reject me.
You need to gauge
the situation better.
I'm the one who has leverage
over you.
Reject you? Why would I?
It'll be such a hassle.
All I need to do is
tell our parents what you did.
Go ahead then!
Why bother playing along?
I don't want to get Myeong Hee
into trouble.
Why are you bringing her up
all of a sudden?
She has nothing to do with you.
I like her, that's why.
What? Who?
You like Myeong Hee?
Yes, I like Myeong Hee.
Got a problem with that?
Hey, I sent Myeong Hee there...
to be rejected in my place.
Right.
If getting rejected was your goal,
you should've come yourself.
Why did you have to send Myeong Hee
as your stand-in...
and complicate things?
You're being ridiculous.
I think you got the wrong idea.
Don't you dare hit on her.
Myeong Hee has
no feelings for you whatsoever.
In fact, she can't stand you.
Well...
I have a hard time believing you.
You don't seem all that interested
in other people's feelings.
Money is the reason
she's been seeing you.
What?
Myeong Hee has been forcing herself
to see you to earn money.
Why?
Did you actually think
that she had feelings for you?
Yes.
What's with her suddenly?
Did you two have
a lover's quarrel or what?
Thank you so much for today.
And happy birthday, sir.
Thanks.
Gosh, I almost forgot.
I almost sent you home empty-handed.
Oh, right.
We packed some food for you.
Wait right here.
Oh, it's okay...
Is your leg okay?
It's true that I missed you,
but I didn't expect to see you here.
Hee Tae...
Then I'll see you again next time,
Myeong Hee.
Hee Tae, here.
Gosh, there was no need.
It's nothing much,
so no need to feel uncomfortable.
Okay, thank you.
- Drop by again next time.
- Sure.
Anyhow, I'm afraid
we'll have to maintain...
this situation for the time being.
What? Do you mean you'll keep lying?
What do you mean? It's not a lie.
What I mean is,
we'll just continue
to not tell the truth for a while.
Whenever I tell my dad
I'm going to meet him,
he's totally okay with it
whether it's day or night.
If he's going to find out anyway,
why don't we get
what we need out of it...
and worry about the aftermath later?
My goodness, you're totally crazy!
What if things get out of hand?
What will you do then?
Gosh, I don't know.
Anyway, let's stop talking
about that.
The thing is...
Myeong Hee, can I ask you something?
What?
Well...
Do you...
like Hwang Hee Tae?
What are you talking about?
No way!
Right?
Okay, I'm glad to hear that.
I made it quite certain...
that he won't hit on you anymore.
What did you say to him?
I told him you're meeting him
to make money...
and you have
no feelings for him whatsoever.
What... Did you really say that?
Yes. Why?
It's the truth, isn't it?
You won't see him again anyway.
Are you seeing him again?
No.
(Tonight at 7 p.m.,
Music Cafe Hee Hee Nak Rak)
What is it?
Is something wrong?
You look like an antsy dog.
The thing is...
A friend of mine wants to see me.
But my best friend...
hates that friend so much.
And she said
she won't hang out with us anymore.
Then don't meet that friend.
What if that friend keeps waiting,
thinking I'll show up?
Then meet secretly.
Then I'll be lying
to my best friend.
Don't meet the first friend then.
- But...
- Man, whatever.
If you want to go, just go.
If you don't, don't.
What's gotten into you?
The DJ at this place
is kind of ugly,
but he plays some amazing songs...
Hey, two o'clock, look.
Two o'clock?
He's gorgeous, isn't he?
- Hey, give me some lipstick.
- Lipstick?
What for?
Are you going to go talk to him?
Are you insane?
Only a woman with courage
gets the hot guy.
I'll go fix my makeup
and go right over.
Myeong Hee.
It'll taste bad
if you keep stirring it like that.
That's how I like it.
Why did you ask to meet me?
I promised to play my song for you.
Were you waiting for me
all this time for that?
What about you then?
Why did you come?
I came to apologize.
I'm sorry for deceiving you
all this time.
Why are you apologizing?
You never deceived me.
Why didn't you say anything
when you knew?
If I said something,
we wouldn't be able to meet.
I wanted to keep seeing you,
and I still do.
You want to keep meeting me?
Yes, I do.
I'm not the person you think I am.
I'm not the daughter
of Changhwa Industrial either.
I know.
The cheeky nurse from the ER, right?
I'm the eldest daughter
of a penniless family,
and I dropped out of high school
and took the GED.
I was born out of wedlock.
My mom used to sing at nightclubs.
But what's the problem with that?
Thanks to our pasts,
we turned out to be...
strong and interesting people.
The truth is,
next month, I'm...
Hey!
Wait, lady!
That blouse looks very familiar.
Right, I know that face too.
But that person should be studying
in the library right now.
Myeong Hee,
please don't tell Dad about this...
Oh, dear.
Do you know Myeong Hee?
Yes.
(Reliable Communication and Finance)
It's my first time actually seeing
someone who goes to SNU.
May I hold your hand?
What are you doing?
Behave yourself.
Myeong Hee,
what's your relationship with Jin A?
We live together.
My dad owns some real estate.
It's just a boarding house.
Oh, a boarding house.
Jin A, do you have a pen?
Shall I give you my pencil case?
If it's okay with you,
can you write down your number?
I'll write it
with a permanent marker.
- What are you doing?
- What?
I just want to
talk about music with her someday,
since we're both music fanatics.
By the way,
how do you and Myeong Hee
know each other?
Well...
Myeong Hee and I...
Our bus is here. Get up.
Hello?
Oh, it's you, Hee Tae.
Soo Ryeon? You haven't met her?
I see.
So she said she had a date with me.
No. We do have a date.
All right. Have a great time.
Soo Chan. Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to order rice cakes
for the opening ceremony.
I'm running late.
I'll see you later.
- Have you been well?
- Hey, it's been a while.
Hold on.
Are you here to order
rice cakes for your wedding?
Our wedding? It's not like that.
What are you talking about?
It's for his opening ceremony.
Can you prepare them
by tomorrow morning?
Tomorrow morning?
We're a bit backlogged here.
I don't think we can.
Come on.
You should never miss a customer
who's having an opening ceremony.
I brought him here
so he'd become your regular.
Have them ready
by tomorrow morning, okay?
What are you going to order, anyway?
- First, some red-bean rice cakes.
- Red-bean rice cakes.
Hold on. These red beans
look a bit old.
Do you have any newer batches?
They were delivered this morning.
What are you talking about?
Also, rice cakes made with old beans
taste better.
Don't use these.
Use the ones
that you hid in the back.
They're all the same.
- Can we get a discount?
- Of course.
Soo Chan,
do you want to have them delivered?
What? Yes, that sounds good.
If I'd come here alone,
my guests would've had...
just one bite of rice cake each.
It's better to have too much.
It's a celebration.
Hold on.
Shouldn't you eat before work?
What do you want to eat?
Don't worry.
I'll eat at the hospital.
Come on.
Let me buy you something nice.
Are there any good places
around here?
(Watch repair)
You don't want ribs, do you?
- Let's go eat somewhere else.
- Should we do that?
What? Marriage?
It seems like
the parents are talking about it.
Hasn't Soo Ryeon told you?
But they only just met...
Hey.
You can't believe...
the mighty Lee Soo Ryeon
is getting married, can you?
I can't either.
I'm also worried
that they're rushing things a bit.
It doesn't feel right.
There also seem to be
rumors going around about the guy.
I wish Soo Ryeon would be
more careful.
What kind of rumors?
They're nothing serious,
but I would've preferred a guy
who grew up in a happy family.
I'm probably just being nosy.
Goodness. Like I said,
I'm just being nosy.
As long as they like each other,
who cares?
Don't you think the two of them
are quite similar?
A couple like that may quibble,
but they live happy lives.
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Resign!
Yushin remnants must resign!
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Resign!
My dear student democracy activists.
We should not be
onlookers or bystanders.
We should be
the leaders of the university...
and the democracy movement!
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Resign!
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Lee Soo Ryeon.
- Resign!
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Lee Soo Ryeon.
- Resign!
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Hey!
- Resign!
What's this?
What are you doing here?
What else? You and I have a date.
They have a date.
We'll talk later.
I don't have time
to deal with you right now.
Do you really have the right...
to criticize
government-funded professors?
What?
You want to reap the benefits...
while avoiding the responsibilities?
Do they know
that you're playing a hero...
using the son of the Head
of Anti-communist Investigation?
- What's he saying?
- I'm not sure.
Get lost while I'm still being nice.
Gosh, seriously...
Hey, Hee Tae.
What are you doing here?
So?
Do you want to be humiliated
in front of everyone?
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Resign!
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Resign!
- Gosh!
- Oh, no.
- Myeong Hee.
What happened?
You have a concussion?
I'm totally fine,
but this jerk still dragged me here.
She fell while fooling around
on the railing of the rooftop.
Hey, I only fell
because you grabbed me.
Be quiet, both of you.
So? Did you get a CT scan?
Yes. Everything seems fine,
except for some minor symptoms
of a concussion.
Myeong Hee,
please make sure I can leave soon.
The protest must be at its height
right now.
Gosh, do you still want to play
a hero?
Hey, no one will even notice
you're not there.
- What did you just say?
- Stop it.
Stop it, you two!
I'll go and ask if you can leave.
Wait here.
- Okay.
- You little...
Will you...
- Don't fight, okay?
- Okay.
Come on. Seriously.
Behave, okay?
Gosh.
- Stop it. I said, stop it.
- Let go.
Gosh!
- This is so dusty.
- Did you just hit me?
What? No, I didn't.
Don't you think the two of them
are quite similar?
A couple like that may quibble,
but they live happy lives.
- You really need to stop.
- Whatever.
- Hey.
- What?
- My patience has a limit.
- What did you say?
(Emergency room)
Myeong Hee.
Well, so...
I wasn't going to wait for you.
I just had some business
at the hospital and the timing...
Where's Soo Ryeon?
I don't know. She went somewhere.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Let's go get something to eat first.
Then I'll sing you that song
I wrote like I promised.
I don't want that.
What do you mean?
You're going to tell me
we should stop seeing each other.
I don't want that.
Did you know
that your fathers are discussing...
your marriage?
Both you and Soo Ryeon have
complicated problems to solve.
I don't want to make things
any worse for you guys.
Forget me and Soo Ryeon.
What about you?
Tell me how you feel,
and I'll make everything simple.
I'm going abroad to study.
What?
That's what I was trying
to tell you yesterday.
I'm leaving in a month.
I only went on that blind date
with you...
to earn my airfare.
When... When will you come back?
My plan is to move there...
permanently.
So let's not do anything
we'll regret later on.
Let's end this here...
so we can only remember
the good things.
Wait, Myeong Hee.
I'm glad to have met you.
I really mean it.
A month?
At this point,
even that's pretty optimistic.
Her recovery is slow.
I can't say for sure
how long she'll hold out.
Can't she...
still be transferred?
That's beside the point.
She's unconscious.
To her, it'll make no difference
whether she's in Seoul or Gwangju.
Don't you think it's selfish...
to make her take this risk?
Hey.
You seem to have many secrets
these days.
What was that earlier?
What's going on
between you and Soo Ryeon?
Why do you want to know that?
I barely know her.
It didn't seem that way though.
Do you like her?
Is it even allowed to develop
romantic feelings for a comrade?
Nonsense. Stop being absurd.
Can you play something else already?
You've been playing
the same thing over and over.
This is plain torture!
My gosh. What is it now?
Why doesn't anything ever go my way?
Hey, be honest now.
Is everything really okay?
Think about this.
Let's say you just met
the woman of your dreams,
but she's going away for good
in a month.
What would you do?
- Is Soo Ryeon going somewhere?
- I'm not talking about her!
The woman of my dreams
who's going away for good?
I'd give up immediately.
- Why?
- I'd rather live with regrets...
than miss her
for the rest of my life.
I hate heartaches.
Just continue to live the way
you always have.
Isn't it your philosophy of life
to live lightheartedly?
That's when it's only about my life.
It's totally different...
once another person's life
is involved.
Goodness. You've come a long way.
You care about another person now?
If you have a headache,
why not try the solution
from our high school days?
Here.
Goodness. You startled me.
You're home late.
Since when do you smoke?
Well, this is...
Go to bed early.
We have somewhere to be tomorrow.
Father. Your lighter.
Keep it.
Make sure you carry it at all times.
So, Father is going to bring
more clothes to the camp?
Yes, on the next market day.
Why don't you put on
the new shoes instead?
The shoelaces are a hassle.
They keep getting tangled
if I tie them.
You wear worn-out shoes
because shoelaces are a hassle?
Put these on instead.
Come on.
I don't want to. I don't!
Little bear.
It's all over. I messed up.
All the kids are annoying.
I got on the wrong side
of the coach.
When something is tangled,
just untangle it.
Untangle it carefully
and tie it nicely again.
If you leave it tangled,
it's your loss.
Whether it's your shoelaces
or training.
Isn't running fast
the most important thing to you?
Jung Tae,
are you angry you're not allowed
to stay at the camp?
You know how Father is.
He barely gave permission
about you missing school to train...
No, it's not like that.
I'll get going.
I'll come pick you up
before Father gets off work.
Don't come to the camp.
Meet me here instead.
Guys, don't run.
- Ju Bin, you're in Room One.
- Yes, coach.
Kyung Jae, Room One.
- Gun Woo, Room One.
- Yes, coach.
Digestive Drink, Room Four.
Work hard.
Yes, coach.
- Attention.
- Attention!
I can't hear you. Attention!
You have just three minutes.
Go to your rooms and unpack.
Change into training clothes
and get back here.
Ready.
Too slow. Hurry up!
Yes, coach!
Jung Tae, are you in Room Four too?
Just my luck.
Move.
You have one minute left!
There will be a penalty
for the one who comes last.
Guys, hurry.
Hey, Digestive Drink!
What?
Take it off. It's mine.
We all have the same uniform.
Why must you be so fussy?
Hand it over.
Hey, let go!
- Hand it over.
- I said, let go!
- This is mine.
- Hey, let go!
- Stay focused.
Hey, I can barely hear you.
Do you want to do ten more laps?
Stay focused. Stay focused.
If you leave it tangled,
it's your loss.
Stay focused.
- Stay focused.
Stay focused. Stay focused.
My gosh, Gyeongju Gas sent one too.
I know. There's limited space,
so it'd be better
to leave them here.
- Yes, let's do that.
- That's right.
- Perfect.
- Soo Chan. Everyone's here, right?
I'll get going then.
You brat! Where do you need to go?
You must stay until the end
as a member of the family!
Hey, Auntie is right.
What's going on?
Do you have another date?
What? You have a date?
Why didn't you tell us?
My gosh, Mr. Kim! You made it!
- Thank you for coming.
- Hello.
Gosh, Mr. Hwang!
I'm sorry we're a little late.
Congratulations, Soo Chan.
Gosh, thank you.
Can you take this?
Aren't you guys going on a date?
I guess you came to see her
because you couldn't wait.
Right.
My goodness.
You keep showering me
with such precious gifts.
My gosh.
You gave my son permission
to marry your daughter,
your dearest treasure.
- Myeong Hee.
- What?
- My gosh.
I didn't know
there would be so many guests.
I had no idea.
My goodness,
you didn't have to bring anything.
Soo Chan.
- Show Mr. Hwang around.
- Right.
I'll be right back. Wait here, okay?
Mr. Hwang,
I'll give you a little tour.
This way, please.
Gosh, Soo Ryeon.
Your husband-to-be is here.
Why are you standing around?
Go make some coffee for him.
Auntie, don't call him like that.
I'll make coffee.
Take a seat.
Yes, take a seat.
Enjoy the food, everyone.
Yes, thank you for coming.
(Changhwa Pharmaceuticals
Aerial View)
You'll buy patented medicines
from other countries...
and manufacture them?
Will this be more profitable
than just importing them?
Yes, of course.
Being able to supply
such medicines on our own...
without having
to rely on importing them...
will help strengthen our country.
You have such an admirable son.
Gosh, he has grand plans...
but has a long way to go.
We underestimated
building a pharmaceutical factory.
It costs a fortune.
One of my in-laws is looking
for a good company to invest in.
Shall I introduce you to him?
Pardon me?
We'd be grateful,
but you don't have to.
This isn't some stranger's business.
We're a family now.
You're the brother
of my future daughter-in-law.
Oh, make two cups of coffee for me.
- No sugar, please.
- Sure.
Hey.
Is that the guy?
Soo Chan's future brother-in-law.
The one born out of wedlock.
He wasn't just born out of wedlock.
His mother was a courtesan.
My gosh,
what is Soo Chan's family thinking?
I understand their daughter
is a troublemaker,
but how could they marry her off
to someone's illegitimate son?
Come on. I heard he's a med student.
And he's good-looking.
He'd better be.
His mother was a courtesan
after all.
Keep it down. He'll hear you.
I was born out of wedlock.
But what's the problem with that?
Thanks to our pasts,
we turned out to be...
strong and interesting people.
My goodness.
If you let this year go by,
it'll be too late.
There's a right time for everything.
You won't be
an eligible bachelorette forever.
Why would you put it off?
- Here's your coffee.
- Thank you.
- Stop it.
- Miss, are you a bookkeeper?
No, I'm Soo Ryeon's friend.
My gosh.
You kept making coffee over there,
so I thought you worked
at a coffee shop.
Don't get me wrong.
It's because you're pretty.
- Did you go to college together?
- Listen to me.
Do you have a boyfriend?
She's my guest.
Really?
Myeong Hee, let's go.
I'll take you home.
Come on.
Enjoy the coffee.
I'm off.
We should get going too, ma'am.
- Shall we?
- Oh, okay.
- See you.
- Okay, see you.
You should never force yourself
to do what you're not used to.
If I keep forcing myself like this,
I may actually fall ill.
Let's end this here.
What?
Hey, you're also...
I'll give you three days.
Whether you tell the truth
or another lie,
do what it takes
to deal with your family.
If we take this further,
we can't get out of it.
What if I say no?
Then I'll do whatever I want.
What? Med school?
Myeong Hee, I'm so impressed.
It's nothing impressive.
The med schools here only admit
those who will become doctors,
whereas everyone gets admitted
in Germany,
but few survive.
I have to do a good job
once I start school.
People who are overly modest
can be annoying, you see.
So when do you leave?
In a month. That's the plan now.
What? In a month?
It all depends on the situation,
so it might change,
but that's the plan for now.
That's too soon...
I mean, that's soon.
A month will fly by.
What? You have a gray hair.
What? I do?
Hold on. Let me pluck it.
Let's go, shall we?
Myeong Hee...
Hold him down.
You idiots.
I told you to interrogate him,
not butcher him.
Who will take responsibility
if things go south...
in this day and age?
We're sorry, sir.
Sir, please spare me.
Don't kill me!
Sit up!
Please, sir...
I really didn't do anything wrong.
Hey.
I really didn't do anything wrong!
I did nothing wrong!
Dad.
Please believe me! I didn't...
- I'm sorry, sir. We'll quickly...
- Forget it.
Have someone tail him.
The student council executive?
We're already on it.
No.
My son.
(Gwangju Pyeonghwa Hospital,
Emergency Room)
My goodness,
I'm in the main sector again.
It's already May.
Time really flies.
(I'll pass the exam this year
no matter what!)
Goodness.
Darn, a year has passed already...
but I can still smell
my brother's stink.
Dad!
- Dad!
- What?
- Dad.
- What is it? I'm busy.
Can you give me
some of those mothballs?
I need to get rid of that
horrible stink.
I already put mothballs
in that room a long time ago.
- Seriously.
- Come on.
- I'm so busy. Goodness.
- Come on. Hurry.
Yes?
Yes, who is it?
Hee Tae?
How did you find where I live?
I mean, why are you here?
Oh, Myeong Hee. I...
Excuse me. Where is...
Are you crazy?
What do you think you're doing?
There are people in there.
I'm glad.
I wanted to say hi to them.
Wait, Hee Tae.
Do you not remember what I said?
How can you...
Gosh, can you let go of me?
- Is he already here?
- Come on...
Oh, hello.
No!
Hee Tae!
Mr. Hwang!
Oh, dear.
Have you lost your mind?
What did you do to our tutor?
What? Tutor?
Hee Tae is going to be my tutor
starting today.
Don't worry about it.
Wow, the taste is perfect.
Wait.
This belongs to my brother,
but it's all out of tune.
Do you want to tune it for me?
Later.
There we go.
First of all,
let's take a look at this.
(Report Card, Lee Jin A)
Let's see.
Ethics, D, History, C,
Math, F.
Jin A, what is your dream?
What?
My dream is to become
a radio producer.
I want to produce a music show
like "Forgotten Nights."
Oh, I see.
But Jin A, you know what?
I have to be good at math
to be a producer?
No.
You're already destined
to be good at math.
- I am?
- Yes.
Listen. Pythagoras,
who is known for his famous theorem,
was the first to create a scale.
And the father of music, Bach,
composed songs
based on mathematical calculations.
Do you know what that means?
It means that math is music.
And music is math.
But the thing is,
you are a music fanatic.
You've unknowingly mastered
the nature of numbers already,
and you're destined
to be good at math.
Like me.
So?
Are you prepared
to accept your destiny?
- Yes.
- Good.
- Get in there already.
- Why should I...
Go give Mr. Hwang some apples.
Oh, my. What is this?
An apple?
I was mistaken earlier.
Why didn't you tell me
you were her tutor?
Is this really an apple?
I'm sorry.
I've washed your shirt,
so don't worry.
It really is an apple.
Yes?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Mr. Hwang, can you stay for dinner
after today's lesson?
Oh, dinner?
I'd be happy to.
Here we go.
Do you drink?
I was waiting to open this...
when my son gets discharged
from the army.
Wait.
Gosh, then you shouldn't open
such a precious thing.
I'll go out and get some makgeolli.
No need. Come on.
It's because you're like my son.
In that case,
I'll have just one glass, sir.
Do you even know
what that's made of?
This is really...
Medicine. It's medicine.
- Mr. Hwang.
- Yes, thank you.
Let's clink glasses.
Cheers.
Do you know what I did for my wife?
I left my home
and started living with my in-laws.
Can you stop talking about that?
This is the third time already.
This story doesn't get old
even if I tell it ten times.
You can't listen to it
without shedding tears.
Get your handkerchief ready.
You know, I used to be quite popular
in my old neighborhood.
But you know what? After...
- Hee Tae, you should go now.
- I came here...
If he gets more drunk,
you'll never get out of here.
- It's okay.
- Stop being stubborn.
- I'll be fine.
- Myeong Hee.
Can't you see I'm having
a talk with my son?
What are you whispering
to my new son?
He should get going now.
It's almost time for the curfew.
Curfew?
You can spend the night here.
- What?
- We'll spread out a blanket...
in the living room...
- and sprawl out!
- But...
- I'd love that.
- Really?
My shirt isn't dry yet anyway.
- It isn't dry yet!
- Right!
It isn't dry yet!
- Son!
- Father!
- Let's have another drink.
- Give me another glass.
Sure thing. Here you go.
Are you drunk?
Why are you playing the guitar
in the middle of the night?
I'm not drunk.
I'm just parched...
from all that soy sauce earlier.
That's all.
Well, then...
Should I get you some honey tea
or something?
Don't bother.
Suit yourself.
I don't need any honey tea, but...
Can you sit with me for a moment?
I'm sorry.
For what?
I feel like I'm being selfish...
and causing you trouble
again and again.
You didn't cause too much trouble.
After what you told me,
I thought hard
about the remaining month.
And I realized,
it's not the month we have
that I'm afraid of,
but how much I'll be hurt
after that month is gone.
I like you, Myeong Hee,
and I'll only continue to like you
more and more.
Goodness, you and your cheesy words.
I look forward to May every year.
On a May night,
even if you sing badly,
the grasshoppers help you out.
The grasshoppers?
Yes.
Let's see here.
(Madonna Fashion)
Whenever I think of you, Myeong Hee,
I can't help but sing.
Goodness.
There you go again
with those cheesy words.
Myeong Hee.
Do you want to go out with me...
just until the end of May?
(Youth of May)
What's your relationship
with Ms. Jang Seok Chul?
We're offender and victim.
- Come along now.
- Leave right now!
Do you have time tomorrow?
- I have somewhere to be.
- I'll come with you.
- You don't even know where.
- It doesn't matter.
Keep an eye on your daughter.
She's not a kid anymore.
I won't go easy.
Have you been spying on me?
Let's just say I'm interested
in my future daughter-in-law.
I have no interest
in getting married.
He's going to invest
in our business.
My father's factory will be finished
in a month.
Let's keep this up until then.
We shouldn't cross the line
just to save ourselves for now.