COURT
Kang Sol.
You're not curious.
You're not curious at all.
Was her name Kang Sol?
-Kang Dan's twin sister.
-Subrogation rights.
A KNOU graduate who served time in juvie.
How did she manage to get into Hankuk Law?
She's really getting on my nerves.
She got in through the special screening
for low-income applicants.
Don't worry, sir.
It's not like she can do anything.
Oh, right. Yang Jong-hoon
was the prosecutor who sent her to juvie.
He was told to send her to jail,
but he ignored it.
Yang Jong-hoon, that moron.
How dare he try to bait me?
He's baiting you?
You must lock him up.
You'll lose that moron
if you let your guard down.
I won't let that happen.
I have a secret weapon ready,
so he won't be able to get out of it.
That's what I like to hear.
Defendant.
You stated you were in your office
at the presumed time of his death,
between 14:25 and 14:55, correct?
Yes. You're right.
JUDGE
I was in my office.
You should've come early.
It got very interesting.
Any other questions for the witness?
I do have one more question.
Did you mention the possibility of this
being a suicide?
Yes, I asked if that possibility
was completely ruled out.
Why?
When I saw Professor Seo, he was already
under the influence of the drug.
My head…
I feel like it's splitting in half.
VOICE MEMO 004
SAVE
YU SEUNG-JAE
Had it been a murder,
he would've mentioned the killer's name.
That's right.
And with that handwritten note…
LET ME LEAVE THIS HELL
Your Honor.
When the detective who found the note
suspected suicide,
the defendant firmly told him
it was not the case.
-Am I wrong?
-That was--
You're right.
I did say it wasn't a suicide case.
And I still stand behind that.
He mistook the witness
for Han Joon-hwi, his nephew,
which means he was in no condition
to explain his situation.
That is a good point.
Darn it.
No further questions.
Defendant, do you realize
that statement could be used against you?
Yes.
I can't turn a murder into a suicide
just to get out of this.
Okay.
Witness, thank you.
JUDGE
But you see, if I killed him…
I'd be happy if the detectives thought
it was a suicide.
Why would I want to say
that it wasn't a suicide?
-What?
-Good point.
-That's true.
-My gosh.
Is he really the killer?
I'm not sure.
People are beginning to doubt it,
and reasonably so.
"An obligee may exercise the rights
belonging to the obligor."
The Civil Code, Article…
Article… 404. Article 404.
In order to exercise the rights--
-Hello.
-Oh, hello.
-What brings you here?
-My case is going to trial.
Suspension of indictment is like pleading
guilty. So I'll prove my innocence.
If it's because of what I said…
No, you were right.
No, it wasn't my place to say that.
Professor Kim Eun-suk agrees.
What was his name? Mr. Han Joon-hwi?
He helped me a lot.
I see.
Everyone knew but me?
I wanted to tell you but was worried
it'd distract you from studying.
Because of me,
you were even told to repeat the year.
No. I won't fail and retake it
just because I was told to.
Ace the exam, for my sake.
Yes, I should.
I can do it.
I should do my very best.
Where was I?
I'm the one who wrote the opinion,
and I even had a nosebleed because of it.
I can't believe Joon-hwi didn't tell me.
I should just blame my bad grades.
It's all my fault.
You can't sleep if you drink coffee now.
You must be exhausted. You should rest up.
It's evidence.
Witness.
Are you aware
that the defendant told the police
you're probably the one
who killed the victim?
Yes.
I'm an evil criminal, you know.
He probably thought it'd be perfect
to just dump it all on me.
Why did you go to Hankuk Law School
on the day of the incident?
I was Mr. Seo Byung-ju's personal driver
at the time.
I always drove him to the school
when he had a lecture.
That day,
I left as soon as I parked the car.
So you weren't on campus
at the time of the incident?
-No, I definitely was not.
-How can we trust you?
How do we trust the words
of an evil criminal?
WITNESS
-What's he doing?
-You can trust this ankle monitor.
I see. Because of this,
we can track your every move.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
We have checked and verified
that you were near Mr. Seo's law office
between 14:20 and 14:55,
the estimated time of death.
Thank goodness I had this on.
Your Honor.
That day, the defendant
was also wearing an ankle monitor
to experience what it's like.
JUDGE
Why couldn't we retrace his steps?
He claims that,
by pure coincidence…
DEFENSE COUNSEL, ACCUSED
…it was out of battery.
Dead battery means it's not trackable.
-Does the monitoring center let it happen?
-No, never.
The Ministry of Justice isn't a joke.
That's because he's not a criminal.
He did it just to experience it.
Is that so?
I'm actually wearing one now.
So I know they strictly abide
by the protocols.
DEFENSE COUNSEL, ACCUSED
At the moment,
the battery is at around 25 percent.
And the monitoring center…
MONITORING CENTER
…is calling.
LEE MAN-HO'S ROUTES
If you don't answer…
JUDGE
MONITORING CENTER
…they keep calling until you pick up.
May I answer this call?
They'll send a probation officer
if I don't pick up.
JUDGE
Sure, go ahead.
Hello?
Yes, I'll charge it right away.
DEFENSE COUNSEL, ACCUSED
Why did he ignore this call
and decide not to charge it right away?
It was because
you didn't want your location
to be tracked.
Because it'd prove
that you were at the scene
at the time of the incident,
not in your office.
It didn't look like
Prosecutor Jin felt guilty at all.
So what if he feels guilty at this point?
But still, he leaked it out,
not Seo Byung-ju.
I told you to be quiet!
It didn't look like
Prosecutor Jin felt guilty at all.
How did you find out?
Kim Hyeon-jae and Choi Jung-hyeok
were the first reporters to cover the case
and Prof. Yang's charges, in depth.
CHOI JUNG-HYEOK
They wrote the articles based on the info
leaked by Prosecutor Jin.
And they covered your father's case
before any other reporters did.
-It could be a coincidence--
-Naturally, it seems fishy.
I need to look into this.
Statute of limitations, five years.
It'll expire soon.
You must be very careful if you want
to get Prosecutor Jin indicted.
This was recorded in secret,
which means it was unlawfully obtained.
What have I been doing all this time?
You were barking up the wrong tree.
But it helped me discover this.
Counsel,
you may cross-examine the witness.
DEFENSE COUNSEL, ACCUSED
No questions, Your Honor.
Witness, you may return to your seat.
If there are no further questions,
we will wrap up here.
Your Honor.
I'd like to bring in another witness.
-Who is it?
-I found an eyewitness
who saw the defendant kill Seo Byung-ju.
-What?
-Seriously?
I'd like to keep the witness' identity
confidential until the next trial.
This is unacceptable.
Who is this witness?
You can't spring it on us like this.
The witness is terrified
that the defendant
would retaliate if any info
were to be revealed in advance.
The witness
couldn't come forward sooner
for fear of ending up like the victim--
If the info is kept confidential,
what about Mr. Yang's right of defense?
Well, the right should be guaranteed.
So, on the condition that
the defendant won't try to contact
the witness under any circumstances,
-please disclose--
-Then I'll probably contact the witness,
so let him have his way.
-What?
-Professor Yang!
-Why did he say that?
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
There he is.
Who is this new witness?
Why come forward now?
Will this witness be the smoking gun?
I must protect the witness,
so I can't say anything now.
See you at the next trial.
-Mr. Jin!
-Just a comment!
-Tell us.
-Just a comment, please
Say a few words as a prosecutor.
-Prosecutor.
-Tell us.
Please, just a comment.
Say a few words.
Wait, Mr. Jin.
Gosh.
He said this new witness
saw you murder the victim.
This will be the smoking gun.
Once he brings in this witness,
it's game over.
How could you say that to the judge?
How can we not know about the witness?
It is ridiculous, isn't it?
I agree that your client
is a total nutcase.
I have to say, this must be tough for you.
How are we going to prepare
for the cross-examination?
He means you don't need to prepare for it.
What do you mean?
He said this person witnessed the murder.
That'd only matter
if Prof. Yang murdered the victim.
He's bringing in a false witness?
Right, he must be pissed off.
Prof. Yang publicly humiliated him
that he'd be
the first prosecutor to be indicted
for publicizing an alleged crime.
Why did you have to provoke
the prosecutor?
Who did he bribe?
DEFENSE COUNSEL, ACCUSED
There you are.
Spare us a moment.
-Why should I?
-He wants to talk to you.
They seem busy, so keep it brief.
I'm sure you know who my father is.
I'm going to sue Prosecutor Jin Hyeong-u
for publicizing an alleged crime.
Thanks to you, I discovered
that I had been barking up the wrong tree.
Is this real?
The son of TOYGOODTOY's CEO is
-Yang's student?
-What's this?
-You recorded this?
-I got chills.
He thinks Seo Byung-ju disclosed
his dad's accusation.
So, that's why his nephew came to see me.
I hope he didn't do this
to get his father's revenge.
Be quiet. Man, I can't believe this mess.
It didn't look like
Prosecutor Jin felt guilty at all.
So what if he feels guilty at this point?
But, still, he leaked it out,
not Seo Byung-ju.
I told you to be quiet!
You recorded this secretly?
I wanted him to know that my uncle
wasn't the one who leaked the info.
Who knew it was Prosecutor Jin?
I told you to keep your mouth shut.
-The cat's out of the bag.
-Once he's indicted,
I'd like you to be my witnesses.
What?
Even if Jin actually leaked all the info,
he won't be indicted.
Even your professor couldn't do it.
We can do better. We, as his students,
ought to make it happen.
I'll make it happen.
With this recording?
Are you guys really law students?
Secret recordings of others are considered
unlawful evidence.
They're inadmissible in court.
I know.
I should've partaken in this conversation.
Then you wouldn't have had
to come out in the open with this.
I recorded my conversation
with the two of you this time,
so it's no longer considered unlawful.
PROSECUTION
This courtroom of all places.
JUDGE
Prosecution.
Arraign the accused.
He's innocent.
DEFENSE COUNSEL, ACCUSED
Did you just say
the defendant is innocent?
Then why did you indict him
in the first place?
Had I refused to do it, they would have
replaced me with another prosecutor.
DEFENSE COUNSEL
The defendant did not embezzle
the company fund.
Some higher-ups in the prosecution
has the CEO's back.
He followed the CEO's orders
and took the fall.
Therefore, the defendant is not guilty.
DEFENSE COUNSEL, ACCUSED
You became famous after that trial.
PROSECUTION
I didn't want you to quit.
I hoped you'd never leave
the Prosecutors' Office.
You left before I did.
That's true.
Gosh, I thought I had no regrets.
But it feels weird to be sitting here now.
What will you do now?
You couldn't prove your alibi,
and there's a new witness now.
I'll look for a witness.
A real witness
who can help me prove my alibi.
You didn't have to come.
What would the doctor think?
I spoke with the school.
You'll take Prof. Moon's
Constitutional Law course.
What?
-The semester is almost over.
-Okay.
What are you talking about?
Why would you switch courses now?
It's better than not being able
to use my laptop in class.
Don't even bring it up.
Aren't you sick of it?
Seung-jae, you went to the trial too?
-Yeah.
-Why?
If you switch to that class,
everyone will find out
-that you're my daughter.
-I have to go.
Prof. Moon's exam questions
are from his books that are out of print.
Then get me those books
as soon as you can.
Okay, I'll search the entire country
if I have to.
KANG SOL B
Give me some time.
I'm not sure whether I should tell you,
-or--
-I'll give you some time.
But don't tell anyone else
before you answer my question.
That ring…
Are you going to keep wearing it?
Here's your coffee.
This and Kang Sol B's laptop were switched
in the cart because
they're the same model?
Then who put your laptop in there?
The person who took my laptop, obviously.
The TA said Kang Sol B's
was returned to her.
It's this guy here.
-But I have no idea who it is.
-Yeah, it's hard to tell.
With the cap and the mask,
all I can see is that it's a guy.
Oh, hold on.
I think I know who this is.
What did you just say?
What do you mean I'm the witness
the prosecutor mentioned?
You're the witness.
You couldn't tell the police
when they interviewed you.
That day, you saw that prick
slip something into Seo's coffee.
It was meth, not sugar.
What's with you?
I'm telling you that you saw it.
You're insane.
You're insane!
You've completely lost your mind!
And the spy camera too.
Why are you doing this to me?
What do you mean?
You're hurting my feelings here.
Yeong-chang.
We'll get married soon.
I set up the camera in your room
to keep you safe
because I love you.
You think that's love?
Of course.
Let's get married next year.
As soon as I get into law school.
But to do that, we must make Yang
pay for what he did.
-Didn't you see him mess with my dad?
-Don't let a personal grudge--
That bastard killed Seo
because of a personal grudge.
But he hasn't been convicted yet.
Presumption of innocence?
You're a law student after all.
Out of the people that left shoeprints
at the scene,
who else could be the culprit, then?
Ye-seul.
Why don't you get it?
It's not like I'm trying to frame
an innocent man.
That sly murderer is trying to get away
with a murder using his legal knowledge.
Let's teach him a lesson.
What?
What are you saying?
-A recording?
-You took it off already?
I'll call you back.
You know why I quit being a prosecutor.
Want to know why I became a law professor?
To make sure there are
no more scumbag prosecutors like you.
Remember that.
To win back your position
and teach again--
I must clear my name,
so I'll have no more of your antics.
Do you think you'll get your way?
We shall see.
Hey, Ye-seul.
Hey! What's wrong? Are you all right?
MY HUBBY
That was a great cross-examination.
You were awesome.
Really?
I'm pretty awesome.
You believe
that Professor Yang
didn't kill him, right?
No.
I don't believe anyone.
I've been burned by someone
who had my absolute trust,
and it broke me, you know.
It still hurts.
Then on the witness stand, why did you--
I just told the truth, that's all.
I can't commit perjury
when I want to work in law.
Does it mean there's a possibility
that he actually killed him?
It can't be completely ruled out,
if the new witness is telling the truth.
You keep this.
KO YEONG-CHANG
I WILL NEVER HIT JEON YE-SEUL AGAIN
MY HUBBY
1 VIDEO FILE
Don't forget
this long night we had.
You knew it was Prosecutor Jin?
Unfortunately, what you sent to Ji-ho
is unlawfully obtained evidence.
Which is why Ji-ho recorded this himself.
You want Ji-ho
to sue Prosecutor Jin, don't you?
You were right.
One of my uncle's belongings is missing.
His glucometer.
They returned everything else but that.
It must be his next card
after the fake witness.
The president would like you
to apologize to Assemblyman Ko.
Me?
You humiliated him
in front of the students.
I just wanted to check.
It wasn't the right place for it.
The students were forced to be there.
-So you won't apologize?
-I suppose he won't sue me?
Sue you?
I'm hoping Assemblyman Ko
will sue me for defamation.
I take it that you want to call
the election law violation
into question again.
Yes.
I told the president
that we'd be violating
freedom of conscience
if we forced you to apologize.
I'm sorry.
For putting you through all this.
If you want to apologize to me,
just make sure you get acquitted.
The president
will fire you
the moment you get a guilty verdict.
You know that, right?
Seriously?
You won't attend his trials?
You, for real?
NOT EVEN CURIOUS
I'm sure you're curious.
It was like Pandora's box.
NOT EVEN CURIOUS
I got another warning from the vice dean.
He said I'd even have to return
the scholarship money.
Mr. Sung.
For Constitutional Law,
I just need to study my lecture notes now.
But as for Prof. Kim's Civil Code course,
I'm missing the notes
on subrogation rights,
the most difficult part.
I bet someone
already photocopied the notes.
Tell me who it is.
That person asked me not to tell anyone.
Don't be curious.
Can't you help me out for once?
Speak of the devil.
What?
-I don't want to talk to you.
-Why not?
"Why not"?
Forget it.
Hey, I'm asking you. What's wrong?
I feel so betrayed.
I heard you knew about Bad FaMa's lawsuit.
I was trying to be considerate.
If you knew, you'd be all distracted
because you're so nosy.
Still, I can't believe
everyone knew but me.
I really wanted to see her clear her name.
-I know.
-You know?
I felt like an idiot when I ran into her
at the court.
She was worried about my exam--
Ace it so you won't have to retake--
Obviously, I don't want that.
I want to ace the exam too.
-I really do.
-Then just--
Just do it? Don't you dare.
The smartest kids in the country
go to this school.
No matter how hard I study,
I just can't do it.
Those who give me false hope that I can…
Forget it.
I'm so desperate I wish
I was the vice dean's daughter.
Kang Sol.
That's my name, Kang Sol "A."
I was hoping that "A" would bring me luck
and help me get an A.
Like a lucky charm.
That's why I wanted to be Kang Sol "A."
Do you know what I was thinking?
I even thought it'd be nice
to steal the exam papers.
You passed the second-round judicial exam,
so you'd never understand.
So? You don't need my help?
This must be heavy.
I do need your help. Put it on my back.
Let's go, Mr. Genius.
Article 18 and 19 go together.
These are important.
The amount to be refunded…
Make sure you go over the third precedent.
-The third one.
-Okay.
This case is…
WILL NOT FAIL
Gosh…
Provide an explanation…
Come in.
Hi, I'm writing exam questions now.
Hold on.
SLEEP, SHUT DOWN, RESTART
All done.
What's with that jealous stare?
I am jealous.
Of course you are.
You wrote exam questions
even while being detained.
I really want to write the questions
for the exams next year.
Will I be able to?
ALL RIGHTS RESERVED
KIM EUN-SUK
Who do you think the witness is?
The sunglasses.
DOCUMENTS
EXAM QUESTIONS
How did you know from Ye-seul's sunglasses
that she was in an abusive relationship?
The kids don't want to get called on,
so they try not to be noticed.
Who'd wear such huge sunglasses
just because of a sty?
Her boyfriend, Ko Yeong-chang,
is Assemblyman Ko's only child.
I heard he had set up a spy camera
in her room.
It's just my hunch.
Love you.
We can go to school together next year.
If he's using her to get back at you
for what you did to his dad…
OKAY
When it comes to relationships,
you never know what could happen.
LAW SCHOOL ENVIRONMENTAL LAW
If Ye-seul can't break it off with him,
you may not be able
to write the exams next year.
It'd be risky to provoke Ko Yeong-chang
without solid evidence.
Your future depends on this.
You can't just rely
on Ye-seul's conscience.
Why don't you talk to her?
And threaten her not to lie?
Right, she's under a lot of stress
because of her boyfriend's threats.
Assemblyman Ko has a lot to lose.
Why don't you mention it to him?
He won't even take my bait.
Right, that's true.
You know
that finding a witness
who can prove my alibi is the only way.
All right.
CIVIL CODE (2020)
Just for ten minutes.
TIMER
10 MINUTES
START
CIVIL CODE (2020)
KANG SOL
Have some.
You seem weary these days.
Are you worried about something?
Oh, no.
My wife and I are trying to have a baby,
but she's been on edge.
I see.
I guess it's not so easy even for OB-GYNs.
Where is your ring?
Did you take it off
because of Professor Yang's laptop?
Thank you, Professor.
Please let her know.
I'll talk to you soon.
2:25 P.M., OCTOBER 5, 2020,
THE DAY OF THE INCIDENT
Yang Jong-hoon speaking.
PROFESSOR KIM EUN-SUK
See if he had a missed call
from Seo Ji-ho around 2:30 p.m.
Professor Yang suspects that
you were the one who took his laptop.
Would you say…
his suspicion is reasonable?
2:20 P.M., OCTOBER 5, 2020,
THE DAY OF THE INCIDENT
Did you have a missed call from Ji-ho
around 2:30 p.m…
SEO JI-HO
…that day?
Seung-jae, what happened to you that day?
It's your fault.
Ten minutes isn't up yet.
CIVIL CODE (2020)
KANG SOL
TIMER
Subrogation rights…
It's so hard.
TIMER
I won't
fail the course.
Please take back what you said.
I'm studying very hard
and trying not to ask you about Dan
so I won't fail.
I never take back what I said.
The Bad FaMa case client took my advice
and is taking it to court…
-Your advice?
-Professor Kim agrees with me.
You think you're on Professor Kim's level?
Pardon me?
Korea Law Review published
her paper about subrogation rights.
She's such a seasoned law professor,
whereas you don't even understand
what subrogation rights mean.
Are you at her level?
If she said going to trial would be better
than suspension of indictment,
then I'd agree too.
Even if you won't take back what you said,
I'll make sure it won't happen!
Korea Law Review published
her paper about subrogation rights.
Korea Law Review published…
She's a seasoned…
"Korea Law Review"?
Korea Law Review…
Kim Eun-suk.
ON CRIMINAL LAW
ON SUBROGATION RIGHTS
KIM EUN-SUK
I'm going through
the legal principles.
Let's emphasize the structural causes.
Judges make decisions based on evidence,
so proving your innocence
won't be that easy.
The legal principles discussed in court
are not always
in agreement with public sentiment,
so it's hard to tell.
28 POLICE OFFICERS VS 8 PROSECUTORS
DIGITAL PRISON
Have a seat.
NAME CHANGE APPLICATION
It's late. Can you drink coffee now?
You like weak coffee, with ice.
Don't worry.
I didn't slip anything into your coffee.
As you know,
I'm not allowed to go out at night.
If I left the house now,
my phone would ring nonstop.
PRESS HOME TO UNLOCK
This is my son,
whom I left in the orphanage.
Anyway, what did you want to talk about?
If it's because I testified…
You said you were looking for Dan.
Kang Dan…
volunteered at the orphanage
and mentored my son.
According to the director there,
she was the only person
my son confided in.
I heard they stayed in touch.
She was the reason
I moved to this neighborhood.
Has she really gone missing?
I haven't seen her at all.
Of course, she's in the US now.
How do you know?
I'm looking for her as well.
I did manage to get hold of her.
Yang Jong-hoon speaking.
It's me, Kang Dan.
Kang Dan?
It's been a long time.
I heard you were looking for me.
Kang Dan?
Who is this?
Text me your number.
-But that number--
-If you want it, let's make a deal.
You hate Prosecutor Jin.
-Who put you up to--
-No one! I told you.
I'd never cut such a deal with anyone
because I'm a chicken!
Okay? What happened was,
those two reporters kept nagging me
to do an interview--
"They had no choice but to pass
the Lee Man-ho Act to make sure
such evil criminals
would never be set free.
Choi Jung-hyeok."
I'd never agree to be interviewed
by a reporter
who wrote an article like this about me.
I'll give you some time to think it over.
Oh, right.
The person who met Assemblyman Ko
and told him to propose the bill
was Kang Dan.
LUCKY YOU!
SHARE EXAM QUESTIONS
YOUR DADDY HELPED YOU?
CIVIL CODE (2020)
KANG SOL
My gosh, she wrote down
every single thing.
And it's well organized.
Her notes were the reason
she could join our study group.
Why do you think
Sol B and Ji-ho let her join?
Maybe they knew who her father was.
No, I'm telling you.
It makes no sense that she got a warning
with these notes
and got a 29 on her test
when her dad is the vice dean, you know?
Right, it makes no sense.
Oh, dear. You guys will practice law
and earn a living?
Are you sure she's his daughter?
Did you even check?
Did you ask her?
Well, based on the photo
and the situation…
He has a point.
Then she should've aced
the Constitutional Law test.
I know.
CRIMINAL CODE 1
CRIMINAL CODE 1, 2ND SEMESTER FINAL EXAM
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Hey!
I'm okay.
-You should go see a doctor.
-No.
I have to take this exam.
You're not well enough.
I'm fine.
I can do this.
-I have to…
-Sol.
LEGAL COUNSELING
Gosh, how inconsiderate.
She has no shame.
I would've preferred not to know.
Why switch to our class now?
Our grades will drop even more
because of her.
We wouldn't be worried about that at all
if it was actually Kang Sol A.
Sol's smarter than you.
It's always stupid losers
who bad-mouth others.
-Hey!
-Hey.
Study hard
so you won't have to worry about it.
Geez.
-Seung-jae.
-Hey, you woke up.
Did I not finish my exam?
You did.
You fainted after you finished it.
Gosh, thank God.
I'm sure you aced it.
What can I do
to write such perfect answers?
It's as if you can read
the professors' minds.
You're dehydrated from too much caffeine.
You pushed yourself too hard.
You've been doing other things
on top of studying so hard.
The client wants a jury trial,
like you suggested.
REPLY TO YOUR LEGAL INQUIRY
You practically wrote an essay
explaining why you think
a jury trial would be better.
-This must've taken hours.
-Seung-jae.
Don't I need to get some rest now?
Sol! Are you all right?
You're not dying, right?
I knew one of us would fall ill
because of these exams.
Why did you come here?
It's not even a big deal.
I'm fine.
Hey, let's go.
Since you want a jury trial,
it will be reassigned
to a panel-judge court
from the single-judge court.
Okay, let me know.
Is this Professor Kim's paper
on subrogation rights?
My gosh!
This is the info I was looking for.
Her final exam from last year
was based on this.
Yeah, it mentions one of the cases
she covered in class.
She'll probably tweak this a little
for the exam.
Yeah, totally.
Sol, you rock.
-You don't just take good notes.
-That's right.
By the way, you really don't want to know
who the witness is?
There was nothing to "witness"
because Prof. Yang didn't kill him.
So, there's no witness.
So they're bringing in a false witness?
But if someone witnessed it,
it must've been near the mock court
or the media room.
If it was the media room,
one of the professors…
No.
The witness…
It's me.
Is it really you? You saw it?
-Yes.
-It makes no sense.
How could you be the witness?
If she saw it, that makes her a witness.
She says she saw it.
It's your problem
that you trust Prof. Yang too much
to believe her.
What?
I think he's capable of saying
he put sugar in Prof. Seo's coffee
when he actually slipped a drug in it.
MY HUBBY
Hey, babe.
Hankuk Law professor Yang Jong-hoon's
third trial will begin shortly.
With the new witness
who claims to have seen him in the act,
many expect that
the trial may take a new turn.
You can do it, okay?
Just say what we practiced.
COMPLAINT
PLAINTIFF SEO JI-HO
I'll make sure
he gets a guilty verdict
and pays for all the damage.
SEO GI-YEOL
I'll show you
how capable your son is, Dad.
Dad, I will…
make you regret
not being here to see it.
If you do a good job today,
you no longer need to feel bad
about getting into Hankuk Law.
We meet again.
It's nerve-racking
to be on the witness stand.
Good luck.
Don't worry.
Today, the whole world will see
who killed your uncle.
I'm going to the restroom.
Does this guy know
-you ripped up the pledge?
-Of course.
That's why I gave it to her.
We have to stop her
before the trial begins.
If Prof. Yang can't stop Ye-seul,
you should…
She made this choice,
and he wants to respect her choice.
Knowing that
she's about to commit perjury?
I understand you're worried about him
because of Ye-seul.
No, it's not that.
I never suspected Prof. Yang,
but now that Ye-seul is saying
she saw him do it,
I'm thinking maybe it's true.
It feels awful to see myself
beginning to suspect him.
PROFESSOR YANG JONG-HOON'S THIRD TRIAL
Witness.
I'm too nervous right now.
WITNESS
May I take some calming pills?
JUDGE
Yes, you may.
What are you doing?
ACCUSED
Eye contact with me will make her
uncomfortable. Please understand.
Witness, did you see the defendant
slip a drug
into the victim's coffee? It wasn't sugar?
Correct.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
-Gosh.
-See? I told you.
How could he do that?
The defendant's life depends on this.
Are you sure
it wasn't this?
It was this?
Yes.
-My gosh.
-Seriously?
WITNESS
Why didn't you come forward sooner?
"Why didn't you come forward sooner?"
If he asks you that…
I couldn't.
That's it.
Why not?
-That's…
-Before you answer,
glance over at Yang Jong-hoon again.
With fearful eyes.
Then the prosecutor will say,
"You took the oath."
Just state the truth.
Professor Yang said,
"You didn't see anything.
Take it to the grave, or…"
Or what?
He said he'd make me suffer.
-What?
-My gosh.
-Seriously?
-I can't believe this.
How could he say that?
"He said he'd make me suffer."
You have to look like you're about to cry.
Good. Yes, that's perfect.
That's it.
You don't need to actually cry.
No further questions.
Counsel,
you may cross-examine the witness.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
Witness.
Please calm down.
Hold on. Don't ask me anything.
-Please.
-What?
Gosh.
I can't do this.
You little…
I can't do this as someone
who's studying law.
I really can't do this
because I want to work in law.
Witness.
I'm sorry, Your Honor.
I wasn't in my right mind.
-Hey!
-Order!
What's going on?
Witness.
Are you saying you lied?
Yes.
Witness.
You're changing your word
as you fear the defendant would retaliate.
Right?
What I feared
was the video from the spy camera.
Do as I say.
He threatened me
he'd disseminate our sex video.
DO AS I SAY
It terrified me.
-Damn it.
-My gosh.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
I don't know whether Prof. Yang
put a drug or sugar in the coffee
because I never saw it.
I'm sorry.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
-Jeez.
-Unbelievable.
I'm sorry.
Damn it.
Shit!
There he is!
-Excuse me!
-Wait!
Excuse me! Just a moment!
-Just a moment!
-No! He's leaving!
-Wait, just a second!
-Wait!
-Just a moment!
-Is it all true?
-Wait!
Excuse me!
-Hey!
-Hold on.
Follow him.
Wait!
Ye-seul.
Ye-seul, are you here?
Sol.
What do I do now?
LAW SCHOOL, AUDITORIUM
Don't think about anything. Just sleep.
I'll sleep here, so think I'm not here.
It's okay, Sol.
I'll get my blanket.
Oh, turn off your phone.
RESTROOM
I suppose you're keenly interested
in my trial.
Yes, especially…
today's trial, I must say.
Can I say something too?
If my student has to wear sunglasses
in my class again because of you,
you'll end up having to wear sunglasses
for the rest of your life.
CRIMINAL CODE
PRECEDENTS
MY HUBBY
Yes, I'll sleep beside her tonight.
I'll call you if anything happens.
On your knees.
Are you deaf? I said, on your knees.
Don't do this.
"Don't do this"?
Fine.
Then tell me.
Who told you to do that?
Me.
You?
-You arrogant--
-That's not why.
You little…
That is why.
Otherwise, you can't stab me
in the back like this.
I'll pull out the knife
you thrusted into my back
and stab your arrogant heart with it.
No.
Yeong-chang, no! Please!
-Don't do this. Please.
-Let go!
No, I can do this.
Ye-seul.
People will forget what I did.
Actually, I'll become a hero.
For disseminating a sex video
featuring a hottie like you.
You're studying law, so I'm sure you know.
A fine, at the most?
Probation?
Poor you.
You, on the other hand…
Your life will be destroyed.
The video will go viral
if I say it features a Hankuk Law student.
I know I'm the perpetrator in the case,
but you're the one who's screwed.
GALLERY
How…
How can you do this if you love me?
You're the one
who betrayed my love.
CONTACTS
Does your father know about this?
What?
You shouldn't do this
for your father's sake.
My gosh, you dared to bring up my dad?
Ye-seul, how dare you?
You've become awfully arrogant
since getting into Hankuk Law.
You need a lesson.
Let go.
Damn it.
Yeong-chang. Hey.
Yeong-chang.
Yeong-chang, no…
SOL A
Professor Yang.
Something happened to Ye-seul.
-Son…
-Ms. Jeon, let me take you to the station.
If she gets interrogated,
there'll be a lot of damage to you too.
I know it's tough, but you have
to look straight at your situation.
Are you saying he may never wake up?
Why didn't you bring him in as a witness?
Prof. Yang seems to be so disadvantaged.
I want to believe the blank paper
you handed in means your courage.
He knows that.
As he didn't appear in this courtroom,
it is dismissed.
-I bet something happened to him.
-I think Seung-jae…
Isn't this Yu Seung-jae's phone?
Riverside?
PROFESSOR KIM EUN-SUK
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs