Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
FAVORITES
SOL-I
The receiver cannot be reached…
CHA HEON
"Thank you for enjoying…
A Love So Beautiful."
I'm done!
CHA HEON
MISSED CALL
Heon.
When did you get here?
About an hour ago.
I'm sleepy.
Go back to sleep.
You're so handsome.
Thank you.
TO YANG HYEON-A
ALWAYS BE HAPPY!
Here you go.
-Thank you!
-Thank you.
-Hi, Dae-sung.
-Hello.
-What's your name?
-I'm A-yeong.
-I'm a huge fan. Always be happy.
-Thank you. You too.
Hi, there. What's your name?
Seo Ji-su.
TO SEO
-Sorry?
-It's Seo Ji-su.
It's you, right? The hospital.
Hi.
It's good to see you.
Me too. Thank you.
You look different
without your doctor's gown.
Thank you.
No way!
JEONG JIN-HWAN'S FUN SINGING CLASS
"I'M STILL YOUNG"
Ladies, show me that smile. Smile!
-Real, real, real, real, the real deal
-It's the real deal
-The real deal is right here
-Real, real, real, real, the real deal
-It's the real deal
-I'll love you with all my heart
You're supposed to dance
with your partner!
Okay!
Thank you.
Heon, I'm here. When will you be here?
Can you wait there for a second?
Sure.
-Here.
Thanks.
-Let's go over there.
Heon.
What's all this?
WILL YOU MARRY ME?
Are you asking me to marry you?
Yes.
Ta-da.
Sol-i.
My life has no meaning without you
because I'm nothing without you.
So…
let me be by your side forever.
That's cheesy!
Are those song lyrics?
No.
What is it?
Did Jin-hwan coach you?
No.
Will you marry me?
Sure.
-Congratulations!
Thank you. Thank you so much.
-I wish you happiness.
-Thanks.
-Be happy.
-Congratulations!
-Congratulations.
Congratulations!
Thanks, Heon.
-Congratulations.
-Be happy!
-Congratulations!
-I envy you!
Heon, look at this. Isn't it stunning?
I bought that ring for you.
That's why it's more beautiful.
It's sparkling. So pretty.
Heon.
Let me pinch my cheek.
That really hurts.
Sol-i, you're not a puppy.
Sorry.
Heon, wait for me. I won't bite you again!
Heon, get back here.
Don't.
Give me a hug.
Go home now.
Tomorrow's my day off.
-What are you doing?
-Taking a nap.
MOM
-Mom?
-Shin Sol-i!
Why didn't you pick up the phone?
Mom, I must have fallen asleep.
What's the matter?
Do you remember Jin-su whom I mentioned?
-Who?
-My friend's son. Sun-nam's son.
-I turned down that blind date, Mom.
-Don't be shy.
I got a look at him.
He's really tall and quite handsome.
Also, he's a general manager
at a big company.
Sun-nam and I checked your compatibility
and you guys are a match made in heaven.
Why did you check that already?
I said I'm not interested!
Hi, Ms. Lee. This is Cha Heon.
What? Heon?
Yes, Sol-i and I got back together.
I'll pay a visit soon
and greet you properly.
Here. She has something to say.
Yes, Mom.
Hey, Sol-i! You just said you were asleep.
Mom, I think
my phone's running out of battery.
I can't hear you. Can you hear me?
I can't hear you.
You should go home now.
What's that sound?
Upstairs.
A newlywed couple moved in recently.
Got it. Good night.
Heon.
I can't sleep.
Close your eyes.
I'll be here with you
until you fall asleep.
Heon.
I was touched by your proposal today.
I guess you really like me, though,
seeing that you proposed to me.
Sol-i.
Yes?
Why do you always forget that I love you?
I love you.
I love you too.
Wake up. Have some breakfast.
I want to sleep some more. I'm tired.
You slept enough.
I was exhausted last night.
-Heon.
-Yes?
You're blushing.
You too.
Last night, you…
Hold on.
Is that the delivery man?
Sol-i, it's me. Open the door!
Hey! Open the door!
-I'm doomed. Darn it.
-It's your dad.
-What's going on?
-Goodness.
-What is she up to?
-Heon, hide!
-Sol-i!
-Hey, Sol-i.
Sol-i, I never thought
you'd be home with Heon today as well.
Oh, he left after the call last night,
but he came back this morning.
Oh, is that so?
Yes.
I hear you and Sol-i are back together.
Yes, sir.
Do you drink?
Let me pour you a glass.
-Sure.
-Thank you, Mr. Shin.
-You're welcome--
-Honey!
-Let me pour you a glass too.
-Sure.
Thanks.
All right. Let's drink.
-Father.
-Yes?
-Please marry me.
-All right.
When should we have the wedding?
What are you talking about?
Come back to your senses, both of you!
You'll marry each other?
Instead of saying,
"Father, please marry me,"
you should say
"I'd like to marry your daughter."
Honey, are you all right?
Honey, I'm not drunk.
Sol-i, I'm perfectly fine.
All you can manage
is half a bottle of soju.
Why would you test how much he can drink?
Heon, you had enough too.
Heon, are you all right?
Of course.
-Honey.
-Yes?
Sol-i, I should take your dad home.
-I…
-Take care of Heon, okay?
-Come on.
-I'll stand up on my own.
-Seriously?
-Gosh.
Heon, I love you.
-What? "I love you"?
-I love you too.
Sure.
EDITOR
Ms. Shin, a date's been set
for your autograph event.
Guys, I'm holding an autograph event!
-Oh! Brother, that's great!
-I knew you'd make it.
-Congratulations, Sol-i.
-I'm proud of you, my friend.
Congratulations, Sol-i.
Gwanghwamun Kyopung Book Centre,
next week at 3 p.m.
Will you guys be there?
Darn it! I'll be training
rookie pop band trainees all day.
I have a car commercial
lined up at the crack of dawn.
I'm afraid I have a meeting
with my professor that day.
Sorry. I have a seminar
out of town that day.
Does that mean none of you can come?
-Thank you.
Thanks.
AUTHOR SHIN SOL-I'S AUTOGRAPH EVENT
A LOVE SO BEAUTIFUL
I'm a huge fan.
Guys!
Hey, Sol-i.
I think we're the only ones here.
No. Others already came by and left.
Jin-hwan, can you please stop teasing her?
Incredible, Brother. I'm so proud of you.
-I'd like an autograph.
-Sure.
-What's your name?
-It's Cha Heon.
What a pretty name.
A LOVE SO BEAUTIFUL, BY SHIN SOL-I
CHA HEON
Your hands.
Hi, Sol-i.
It's me, Heon.
So when did I start to like you?
Heon, what are you up to?
Nothing.
-Let's go.
-What? Already?
Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Subtitle translation by: Hye-lim Park