♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 22=
Qingqing.
Can I please not wear this dress?
It’s hard for me to walk in it.
No.
You look so beautiful in it.
Come on. Let’s practice the etiquette.
No, I won’t.
My general.
Come on. Hurry.
Like this.
Place your hands like this.
Head up. Chest out.
Smile.
Bend over.
General.
Be gentle. You’re a lady.
Chin up.
Straighten your neck.
Smile.
Come on. Nod.
Be gentle.
Come. Walk.
Slow down.
Smile.
Come on.
Smile again.
Like me.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
Am I pretty?
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
So pretty.
Anyone? Catch the assassins.
-Where are the assassins?
-Where are they?
Fall back.
Catch them.
Don’t let them get away.
Hurry.
Their moves suggest that
they’re assassins from the underworld.
But...
But when they attacked me,
they didn’t aim for my throat or heart.
Instead, they aimed for my face.
What’s their goal?
Maybe... They want to disfigure you.
What?
The dress is ruined.
It’s made by Wind City’s
best embroidery store.
What should we do?
We’ll go to the Empress’s tea feast
this afternoon.
It’s fine.
Just find a waistband to cover it.
Waist...?
General, my wrist was twisted just now.
I think I need some treatment.
Long Yan, please.
Come. Help me get dressed.
General.
Is this one okay with you?
You can decide it.
Why is my chief guard
blushing?
General.
I think this is the one.
Maybe... They want to disfigure you.
Disfigure me?
Who would want to disfigure a general?
But those blades
were really aiming for my face.
They want to stab my eyes.
(Xu’s Mansion)
Empress, I heard that His Majesty
intends to make Feng Chenyue
his consort.
Nonsense.
General Feng is the general
who guards the frontier.
How can His Majesty
make her a consort?
Your Grace.
I heard the same rumors.
Seems that His Majesty wants to
reinforce the loyalty of the army.
Here comes Great Lady General.
Greetings from Chenyue of Feng Family.
Seems that the Empress is
not so kind to me.
Rise.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Here comes the Emperor.
Greetings, His Majesty.
Rise.
Thank you, His Majesty.
I have just finished dealing
with imperial court’s affairs.
I heard that Empress and Consort Rui
are attending a tea feast at
Prime Minister’s Mansion.
So I came to have a look.
Don’t feel restricted.
This...?
This is Chenyue.
Your Majesty.
When you’re in a lady’s dress,
I can’t even recognize you.
You’re so pretty in this dress.
Come.
Sit next to me.
His Majesty really wants to
make Feng Chenyue his consort?
Feng Chenyue in a lady’s dress...?
It’s unexpected that
she’s not less beautiful
than any of my consorts.
He wants to make me his consort?
Thank you, Your Majesty.
This wine seems to be good.
Good wine.
Your Majesty,
do you want to have a taste?
General Feng, how can you just
give yours to His Majesty?
Your Majesty, General Feng lived with
the unrefined rustic women
at the frontier.
She doesn’t know the manners.
Your Majesty, my action is
punishable by death.
Please punish me.
You lived at the frontier.
It’s normal that
you don’t know Wind City’s courtesies.
You’re pardoned.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You’re indeed a good warrior.
But you need to learn more about
Wind City’s etiquette.
I...
I misbehaved again?
Okay.
I need to check on the east market.
I’ll accompany you no more.
-Safe trip, Your Majesty.
Please.
Bye, Your Majesty.
Do you know that
you just committed a crime?
You were so rude to His Majesty.
You’re still alive
because of your Feng Family’s grace.
Your Grace, you’re right.
My father always said I’m a wild girl.
He was afraid that my manners
will get me killed.
That’s why he kept me at the frontier.
Now, I’m in Wind City,
I need to learn from
all of you.
You have a correct understanding
of yourself.
Feng Chenyue is different from
the person described in the rumors.
This must be Consort Rui.
You must be Consort Rui?
Dongluo’s ladies are like
Dongluo’s mountains and rivers.
So pure and fresh.
Really?
Like Dongluo’s landscape?
You’re complimenting my beauty, right?
Consort Rui is still like a child.
His Majesty likes her character.
Consort Rui shows
her emotions so easily.
She’s not a sophisticated person.
So who on earth
sent those assassins to harm me?
(General’s Mansion)
I heard from the assassins that
Guo Mansion’s chief manager paid them.
Is Guo Family an enemy to Feng Family?
Lor...
Xue Qianxun.
What are you here for?
Little rabbits.
So adorable.
Rabbit-shaped desserts
handmade by Goddess of Moon.
I brought some for you to try.
Then, I’ll make myself at home.
It’s so delicious.
Have some too.
Otherwise, I’ll eat them all.
It’s all yours.
You’re so nice.
Wait.
Why did Goddess of Moon
give you her hand-made desserts?
She likes you?
I don’t know.
I don’t care about
what she thinks.
I’m not an easy bird.
No.
Who is she?
Who is the person
that’s in my head?
I have something to attend to.
I’ll go now.
This meteor mark
is really so hideous?
He said he’d pursue me.
Now he regrets it once he sees the mark.
He claimed that he likes me.
Liar.
Liar. Liar. Liar.
Well.
You touched my whole body.
I’m not an easy bird.
Who is she?
What does she have to do with Qingqing?
General Feng.
(Xu’s Mansion)
You promised to hang out with me.
You mustn’t break the promise.
Sure.
Let’s not go back for now.
Let’s go somewhere else first.
Where?
Prime Minister’s wife said that
there are fireworks tonight.
We can watch fireworks everywhere.
Why would we come to
the city wall purposefully?
I once saw
the most beautiful fireworks here.
Yuchi.
I like you.
How about you?
Did you also see
the most beautiful fireworks
at this place?
I’ve never been here before.
I don’t like watching fireworks, either.
No.
He’s not my Dragon King.
I’m wrong again?
Feng Chenyue, wake up.
But I only watched fireworks
when I was a kid.
I don’t like it now since I’m grown up.
Feng Chenyue.
You’re so stupid.
You got the wrong person again?
Stop being silly.
For all these days,
I was flirting with
my chief guard.
Gosh. This is so embarrassing.
You’re finally home.
I’ll prepare bath water for you.
Move out of the main yard.
Don’t come in without my permission.
Yes.
What’s going on?
What happened?
Why is Chenyue being mean to you?
Quiet.
What’s going on?
Who’s the bad guy
that wrote this script?
My Dragon King.
Who are you?
(General’s Mansion)
Move out of the main yard.
Don’t come in without my permission.
Yes.
I knew that you’d forget me.
Why am I still so sad?
(General’s Mansion)
General.
General. General.
You came back late last night.
There’s something
I didn’t have time to tell you.
What is it?
Yesterday, I went to the market.
And I met the underworld assassins
who came to the mansion
to kill you that day.
They hadn’t left Wind City.
You happened to find them?
So I said I’m born lucky.
Anyway, I heard from the assassins that
the person who paid them
was the chief manager of Guo’s Mansion.
Mr. Guo, from Ministry of Justice?
That’s him.
What’s his history with Feng Family?
Whether there’s history or not,
ask Wind City’s prefectural magistrate
to capture the chief manager of
Guo’s Mansion and interrogate him.
Ministry of Justice is in charge
of all criminal cases.
Capture Mr. Guo’s chief manager
just because of a few words
from underworld assassins.
Do you think that’s possible?
Then what should we do?
Stay still before the enemies
make a move.
Authentic Dongluo desserts.
Buy one, get one free.
Come take a look.
Guest, there you’re.
Where’s the dessert I ordered?
I’ve packed it for you.
Goodbye.
Master.
Chestnuts. Roasted chestnuts with sugar.
Move.
Lady.
Master.
You’re smart.
Lady, seems that
you’re from Dongluo.
Lady, slow down.
Have some fun with me.
You’re so pretty.
It hurts. Ouch.
Master. Master.
How dare you run away
after beating our master?
Run away?
Why are you still standing there?
Beat her.
Don’t come closer.
I’m the son of Marquis Guangping.
I won’t spare you if you harm me.
Don’t come close.
She is...
Jin.
Chenyue.
Why are you in Wind City?
It’s a long story.
Why did you stop me
from beating that pervert?
He’s the son of Marquis Guangping.
It’s hard to get over this episode
if you harm him.
If you want revenge,
there are many chances.
Come. Let’s find a place to chat.
(Puer tea)
Just now,
you dodged it fast.
So I said your skills
aren’t sharp enough.
After all these years,
your aim is still so bad.
Seems that
you’re not doing so well
in the underworld.
My aim is bad?
You might be the only person
who dares to say that
in the four nations.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪