♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 21=
I’m going back to Wind City.
How about you be my Chief Guard?
Thank you, General.
But, I think you don’t need
a soldier like me in Wind City.
You don’t have to answer me now.
We’ll set off tomorrow
and you can decide it then.
Chenyue.
I knew you were here.
Zheng.
Mr. Lu.
I have something to tell General.
Excuse me.
I didn’t finish my word just now.
Actually,
I got a secret letter from my father,
saying that some ministers
are discontented with your achievement.
He asked me to…
Keep your nose clean
and stay away from me?
Of course I’m not afraid of the gossip.
But, Chenyue,
you have to be careful in Wind City.
As the Military Supervisor,
I’m afraid I can’t go back with you.
Returning to Wind City is more
dangerous than a war?
Without people around to help,
you have to be more cautious.
I got it.
Thank you, Zheng.
General.
Tomorrow, you’ll return to Wind City.
You must be well-prepared.
Long Yan.
General.
I’ll return to Wind City with you.
His eyes.
So familiar.
Yuchi.
Dragon King.
Long Yan.
Take a look.
Is this the Five Horses Painting
that you want?
Yes, it is.
You can get this painting
from the Emperor.
No wonder you’re the seventh princess
of Dongluo.
It’s nothing.
But I do have an important thing that
I wish you to help me out with.
I really can’t assemble
this Magic Cube Lock.
Jin, please teach me.
Okay.
Look. It should be assembled like this.
(Yue)
This should go in here.
And put it here. That’s it.
It took me over an hour.
But I still couldn’t put it together.
How could you assemble it so fast?
This is the Luban Lock my dad taught me.
Of course, I can assemble it.
I even gave it a new name.
Magic Cube Lock.
It’s a better name than Luban Lock.
Here. This is your birthday present.
It’s for you.
Your name “Jin” was carved in it.
(Jin)
Thank you, Jin.
I’ll forever cherish this.
I’m afraid you’re too stupid to use it.
No, I’m not.
Look. It’s done.
You assembled it in less than a quarter.
Jin, you’re so smart.
Can I borrow this for a few more days?
Okay.
I wonder
where’s Chenyue?
Guest, here’s your tea.
General.
This is the third pot of tea.
(Tea)
Four desserts, two sunflower seeds.
We’ve had enough food and drinks.
We have traveled for nine days.
Let’s hurry now.
And we can reach Wind City by dawn.
Then we can freshen ourselves up
and greet His Majesty tomorrow morning.
No.
(Tea)
Why not return to Wind City for rest?
Long Yan.
Talk some sense into General.
Long Yan, how do you think of it?
General believes that
if His Majesty knows that
we can get back to Wind City
in nine days.
Then the next time,
he will order us
to return in eight days.
So, I’m on General’s side.
We just need to return in ten days.
You think so much...
You think so much about everything.
I’m totally defeated.
But, General, at least,
we need to find a place
to clean ourselves
before we greet His Majesty
in the palace.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Long live, Your Majesty.
Dongluo is now trembling with fear.
There’s no need to worry about it.
My beloved General, please rise.
-Though Feng Chenyue is young,
-Thank you, Your Majesty.
It has been a tiring trip.
she knows how to act soft and
show weakness before His Majesty.
-She’s indeed smarter than her father.
-I’ll reward you thousand taels of gold.
And I’ll confer you the title
of Great Lady General.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
General Feng.
What’s going on?
General Feng, please stay.
Empress summoned you
to Fengxi Palace.
Okay.
Come with me.
Eunuch Qi.
This is General Feng?
Yes, Empress asked me to
bring General Feng to greet her.
It’s a misunderstanding.
Empress hasn’t had good sleep recently.
General Feng has fierce spirits
because she has killed many enemies.
So she wants General Feng
to guard at the door
since it’s the noon nap time right now.
So it is.
But is it appropriate to
ask General Feng to be the guard?
It’s fine.
Then,
thank you, General Feng.
Dragon King, there you’re again.
This is the palace.
I just want to take a look.
If you insist on stopping me,
then fight me.
Dragon King, no one wants to fight you.
Finally, you’ve been behaving
for a decade.
Why are you here again?
Just tell us. Which imperial concubine
do you wish to meet?
And what is your gift for her?
We can give it to her for you.
I want to meet General Feng Chenyue.
Fine. I’ll take a look for you.
Why do you help me?
Recently, Lord of Luofeng Pavilion
let out the word that
any Heavenly General who’s able to
stop Dragon King
from entering the palace
does not have to drink the Lethe Tea
if he needs to go through trials
in the earthly realm.
Lord of Luofeng Pavilion
has always been so harsh.
He doesn’t give anyone free passes.
Dragon King, we have to
thank you after all.
Xue Qianxun really loves to poke his nose
in other people’s business.
She’s fine.
Empress asked Feng Chenyue to
guard outside Fengxi Palace.
General Feng.
Empress just started to get sleepy.
Please, General.
It’s fine.
Empress is so poor.
She’s so young but already
suffers from insomnia.
Imperial Kitchen’s eight treasure
ginseng chick soup
is so nice.
After drinking it,
I feel that my hands, feet,
and even my heart are warmed up.
That’s indeed.
His Majesty said
the weather is cold recently.
He asked Consort Rui to
take care of your health.
This rain is so sudden and strong.
This is the heaven’s will.
Empress asked Feng Chenyue
to guard outside Fengxi Palace
amid this rain.
Great!
What Great Lady General?
Just let her get soaked in the rain.
May I be excused?
Jin,
we’ve humiliated her.
Why are you still unhappy?
She fought in the battle
and harmed His Highness.
We can kill her or humiliate her.
But those who’re on her side
should not treat her like that.
But His Highness
has warned me that she’s the enemy.
When I bully her,
I should show her no mercy.
When you grow up,
you’ll understand that
some enemies are worthy of our respect.
Why is the place I’m standing at
not raining?
But everywhere else is?
Yuchi.
Yuchi, is that you?
Immortal of Fate,
this is not how you drink the tea.
Then how should I drink it?
You should let the heat
disperse on your face.
It can keep your skin soft and dewy.
Immortal of Rain.
Hurry.
Why is Dragon King flying
in the raining area?
Dragon King is flying
in his dragon form?
What does he want?
I’m just asking.
I’m not sure.
I brought my disciples
and observed him for a while.
He just sat in the air
in his huge dragon form.
He’s so impulsive.
I’ve told him that
using his power to
change into his true form
will harm his body.
I guess
he must have evil intentions.
He tries to stop my rain.
Immortal of Rain, don’t worry.
If Dragon King wants to
disrupt your rain,
he might have directly
knocked on your door.
He wouldn’t do
what he’s doing right now.
But he won’t just
fly up in the air
for no reason.
He must have a purpose.
If I’m not mistaken,
he’s sheltering someone from the rain.
Sheltering someone from the rain?
Fine. I’ll make the downpour stronger.
He’s not afraid of water anyway.
It’s useless to make it rain heavier.
Then,
I’ll add thunder to the rain.
Yours is the earth’s thunder,
not the heaven’s thunder.
You’re just scratching his back for him.
Considering your health,
you can’t even take the earth’s thunder.
I remember that you once told me
you want to see Star Halo the most.
Was that you?
Don’t wait for me in the rain next time.
Our General’s Mansion
has plenty of umbrellas.
If you use your power at will
in 49 days,
your power will bite back and harm you.
Dragon King.
Why is your power so weak?
You abused your power
and was hurt again?
Be quiet.
Dragon King.
Don’t abuse your power again.
I’ll watch over Chenyue.
Look at yourself.
This...
This is the authentic piece of
Han Xiaozi’s Five Horses.
Thousands of taels
can’t buy this painting.
You kept your promise and deployed
the female general back to Wind City,
the Empress will reward you.
I need to ask Mr. Guo for a favor.
Back then, your beloved son
wanted to accumulate experience
at Feng Army.
So he could return to Wind City
and get promoted.
-But Feng Se discovered his embezzlement.
-Once in Feng Army, forever a part of it.
-and expelled him from Feng Army.
-Once expelled from Feng Army,
there’s no return.
That’s Feng Army’s rules.
Once he’s expelled from Feng Army,
there’s no turning back.
General Feng.
-You even begged the Emperor for mercy.
-General Feng.
Please have some mercy.
-But Feng Se...
-Please have some mercy.
The military order is final.
No one can change it.
Expel him.
-Yes.
-General Feng.
-Dad.
-Jun.
-Your son was so defeated.
-Dad.
He indulged himself in
drinking and riding.
He fell down from the horse
and broke a leg.
Now, you managed to
get Feng Se’s daughter,
Feng Chenyue, back to Wind City.
Don’t you want to teach her a lesson
and revenge your son?
But Feng Chenyue
has made no mistakes.
I can do nothing to her
even though I’m in charge of
the Ministry of Justice.
We’ll
take her eyes.
Here.
Thanks.
(General’s Mansion)
This place offers
good foods and drinks.
But it’s so boring.
At the frontier,
I drink to the mountain views.
I ride and shoot. It brings so much joy.
Here. This is tasty.
Roasted chestnuts with sugar.
It’s still warm.
Come on.
I can’t be mistaken this time.
Last time when I asked Zheng,
I scared him a lot.
If I’m wrong this time,
I might be seen as a maniac.
Why are you
feeding me chestnuts?
Chestnuts are hot
because they were just bought.
So I peeled it for you.
Really?
It’s not that hot.
Let’s peel chestnuts together.
It’s delicious.
Sit down.
Why did you buy chestnuts for me?
I heard that you’re drinking
on an empty stomach.
I’m afraid it might harm your health.
So I bought you your favorite food.
How do you know
this is my favorite?
This is
my responsibility.
It’s my job to care for general.
My chief guard
even cares about what I eat?
I...
♪Wind blows the skirt’s hemline
You’re in the shadow of the tree♪
Oops.
I feel I’m flirting with
an innocent lady.
♪The leaves rustling Not too loud♪
Wait.
Where are you going?
♪The heart beats fast and deafening♪
I’m General’s guard.
General shouldn’t peel chestnuts for me.
May I be excused?
♪Embrace the warm wind♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
♪Like a thick wine flows into the sea♪
♪And into your heart♪
(General’s Mansion)
♪Thousands kinds♪
Have a try.
♪Of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
♪Like a thick wine flows into the sea♪
Chenyue has taken the Lethe Tea.
Why is she like Ayu?
♪And into your heart♪
Your Highness.
Why did you do this?
I almost forgot tonight is
the full moon’s night.
Can’t you just remind me?
Do you have to suffer it on your own?
Knowing that my heart aches for you
makes you happy?
Your Highness,
I will never forget your benevolence
for the rest of my life.
Stand up.
I want her to suffer a prolonged death.
Spare Feng Chenyue’s
miserable life for now.
Take her eyes first.
Your dad
sacrificed for the nation.
Are you saying that my dad died?
Your dad was ambushed by
the enemies at Tiger’s Howl Valley.
No one survived.
This is the oldest prince.
When he took us there,
(Feng)
this was all we found.
Why would they kill my dad?
Imperial doctor said that your meridians
are harmed because of shock.
You feel that there are insects
biting your body.
I asked my men to search relentlessly
and found this prescription
to make Life-saving Pill.
Taking it along with alcohol
can stop your pain.
I’ll one day
revenge for
all the dead Dongluo warriors.
Now, you don’t have
a mother or a father.
If you wish,
you can stay at my mansion.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Your world is filled with hatred.
Never forget the hatred.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪