[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 15]
It's getting late. I have to go.
Wait a minute.
It's so cute.
Haven't you been waiting all night?
All night?
Didn't you?
No.
Who told you?
I... I wasn't waiting for anything.
Really?
Pure and naive.
Physically strong.
Passionate.
Senior,
when are you going to stop pretending?
Are you sure you're okay, Ding?
I'm fine.
Then stay safe.
Give me Liang Chen's address.
What's wrong? Is her house on fire?
Yes, it's on fire. I'm in a rush
to put out the fire.
I'm going to put out the fire too.
Wait, let me change
into a suit and tie first.
Just give me the address.
I don't need you to put out the fire.
I'm not the kind of person
who betrays his friend.
You want the address?
What's your offer?
I wonder who begged me
to bring girls over?
Nature Emerald Suites.
Building 8, number 1601.
Thanks, buddy.
Are you going to put out a fire
or start a fire?
What a scare.
[Sun Bin Yu]
Hello, what's up?
[Orange, where are you?]
I'm at home.
Great.
The fresh meat set meal that I ordered
for you is on the way.
What?
[It should be]
almost there by now.
No need to thank me.
Taro,
didn't you take your medicine?
Hello,
I'm Lu Lu Xiu.
Do we know each other?
Why do you come to my house?
What are you doing here?
I'd like to know you all over again,
senior.
What are you talking about?
I don't understand.
All right, when did you find out?
Do you really want to know?
Forget it. I don't want to know.
Senior,
when I knew you were Little Box,
I was really happy.
Because
I've liked you for a long time.
Senior, I haven't finished talking.
What else do you want to say?
Get some rest. I'm going home.
What, is that it?
Why? What else do you want me to say?
Nothing.
Good night, Little Box.
Why don't I
walk you downstairs?
All right.
Don't you have a coat?
Hold on a second.
Go back.
Okay.
Go.
Let's head back.
All right.
You're back.
Did you see her?
You're asking the obvious.
That's not right.
According to the normal script,
you should be the second male lead
who got defeated.
Have you been cast as anything
more than a third male lead?
No.
What's the exact situation
between you two now?
Do you like her?
Of course.
Despite my skill level, I still
team up with her every day.
If it weren't for love,
what else could it be? Charity?
Many people like her, okay?
What gave you the right to start the fire?
Aren't you afraid of
setting yourself on fire?
Do you see it?
What?
The halo of a male lead.
Halo, my foot!
You...
Lu Jing! Lu Jing!
Lu Jing, I haven't finished yet.
Lu Jing, what's the exact situation
between you two now?
Lu Jing! Lu Jing!
Open the...
My snail rice noodle.
[Supreme Master]
Hello?
Senior?
You're back.
Are you happy?
This is the local specialty
that I brought for you.
A box of lemons.
Thank you.
Did you have fun?
Don't remind me. Just thinking about it
makes me depressed.
If I knew I could see Herman,
I wouldn't have taken a vacation
even if I was tired to death.
It's nothing. We only did a live broadcast
and had a meal together.
I'll introduce him to you
if there's a chance.
You guys even had a meal together.
How was it? Is Herman handsome?
So so, I guess.
Good.
Now I'm not so depressed.
I'll just let him live in
my imagination forever.
He looks like Liu Mao Yan.
That's not handsome to you?
And you actually can keep up with him
and it worked out so well.
I'm so envious.
I'm not that good.
We had an innate chemistry, that's all.
Grab the ball.
Block him.
Da Ming, defend him.
Block his shot.
Stop him from boxing out.
Don't let him box out.
Defend him, defend him.
Grab the ball.
You play very well today.
I feel a bit restless recently.
Forgive me.
Restless.
Restless, restless.
Go on.
Defend him, defend him. Grab the ball.
They can't make it without me.
You're very good.
Why don't you join the game?
What are you doing?
Just dance a few more times.
I'm still not familiar with it.
Just finished class?
Qi Qi, we'll practise first.
Don't take too long.
Bye-bye.
Is your hand feeling better?
It's still pretty bad.
I can't move it.
When will your hand recover?
When can we
go on a mission again?
No rush.
Even though we can't go on missions,
we can still listen to music,
go to art exhibitions,
and enjoy the finer things in life.
That will do too.
Senior,
you're here too?
Didn't you say you couldn't
move your hand?
My hand hurts.
Feels like it's getting worse.
It's your hand that's injured,
not your leg.
What are you squatting for?
Every part of the body is connected.
I almost gave myself away.
That rascal must have done it on purpose.
Then again, this charade is getting stale.
What else should I come up with?
Why is the water so cold today?
I'm freezing.
Why is the water ice cold?
Be glad you're still alive.
[What are you doing?]
I'm watching a video.
Liu Mao Yan is quite handsome.
Why?
[Supreme Master]
Hello.
[Are you upset?]
You replied to me so late
and praised others for being handsome.
How can I not be upset?
[My junior is such a jealous person.]
Then what do you want?
A crawfish meal will do nicely.
Isn't it supposed to be your treat?
You still remember?
[Yes, of course.]
All right, it's my treat.
[How about tomorrow? ]
Tomorrow?
[Can't make it?]
How about today?
Today?
Right, I'm downstairs at your house.
Downstairs at my house?
He's downstairs at my house.
[I'm just kidding.]
You're just kidding me?
About today, tomorrow or being downstairs?
See you tomorrow.
Here you go!
Good, put it here.
-Have some dumplings.
-And dumplings too?
Great!
What a spread.
Here, taste it.
Okay.
-I'll put this here.
-Quite nice.
-Not bad. Good flavour.
-Come and eat with us.
Bao Bei hasn't eaten yet.
Jing,
-did you buy all this?
-Yes. Just now.
-Here, have a tea egg.
-Thanks.
Your grandpa knows that I like tea eggs.
He's better than you at cutting fruit.
Right, it looks decent.
I learned it from Grandma.
He's becoming so caring.
Good improvement.
I'll enjoy the blessing of
my grandson from now on.
Chef Lu!
It's really good.
[I just remembered that]
[it's winter now.
There's no more crayfish.]
[I knew that.]
But I want to see you.
[The first snow is the perfect time
to take a walk with a lover.]
[They say you meet the guy of your dreams
during the first snow.]
[So where are you?]
[The first snow is here. It's the season
for confessions.]
A woman's idea of romance
is so ridiculous.
What can be better than
having hot pot on a snowy day?
[Having hot pot on a snowy day]
[is the least one can do
to honour winter time.]
[I'm having a hot pot party
at my house today.]
[No one is allowed to be absent.]
[Reply if you received this message.]
Shan Shan.
Shan Shan,
the snowman is here.
Where is it?
It's all melted.
I'll make another one for you.
You're serious?
I'll be right back.
Shan Shan, the snowman is here again.
Are you a fool?
You actually took me seriously
and made another one?
Are you cold?
No.
Not cold?
My foot.
Your ears are frozen red.
[Having hot pot on a snowy day]
[is the least one can do
to honour winter time.]
[I'm having a hot pot party
at my house today.]
[No one is allowed to be absent.]
[Reply if you received this message.]
[Having hot pot on a snowy day]
[is the least one can do
to honour winter time.]
[I'm having a hot pot party
at my house today.]
[No one is allowed to be absent.]
[Reply if you received this message.]
Senior.
Here.
It's additive free.
Drink more. It'll replenish
your nutrients.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Do you know how to put on ice skates?
I'll help you later
so you won't get your hands hurt.
I've put them on.
All done.
Be careful.
You should sit down.
Can you skate?
I can't.
The why do you come here?
Today is a working day.
There are less people on the rink.
You can be more relaxed.
Besides, it doesn't matter
if I know how to skate or not.
What matters is you do.
What if I don't know either?
Then,
let's stumble together.
Why don't I give you
a demonstration first?
Slightly bend your knee
and lean forward.
And slide your left foot out,
followed by the right.
Watch me.
Come over. I'll catch you.
Don't be afraid.
Senior, catch me!
Be careful!
Do you want to skate together?
I don't dare to.
Then let me show you once more.
Come over.
Senior,
you have to catch me then.
You lied to me. You obviously can skate.
It's not funny.
[Okay. Congratulations to Madam Ma]
[on winning the title]
[of Snarky King of our
first Silver Tongue Cup.]
[Next, let's give a big
round of applause to]
[Madam Ma!]
Why don't we eat first?
I think we should use clear soup.
Can you show
some respect to the hot pot?
Didn't you invite Liang Chen over?
She doesn't eat spicy food.
Orange hasn't even replied
to me on WeChat.
I'm not sure if she will come.
Fine, clear soup.
Then there are the others.
All of them stood me up.
Typical case of romance over friendship.
It's only a snow day.
What's with all the display of affection?
One might think it is snowing rose petals.
Can't they be more considerate
of us single guys?
All right, three.
We're having hot pot.
What about him?
He'll have dog food.
[A beautiful, slim, and generous me.]
[I should also thank my father.]
[Without my father,]
my mother alone
as you know,
could not have birthed me.
I learned
pretty quickly, didn't I?
Very quick. Awesome.
It's because of you.
You're a good teacher.
I think you're trying to make up
for your terrible acting
with sweet talk.
Is it sweet?
Senior, are you upset?
Enjoy yourself.
I want to play with you.
Didn't you have enough fun toying with me?
You can toy with me too.
Come on.
Come on. I'll show you
something really fun.
Senior,
are you free tomorrow?
I have work tomorrow.
How about the day after tomorrow?
Work.
Why?
I'm wondering
how long will it be until we meet again?
Aren't we together right now?
But I'm already thinking
about when we'll meet next.
I think they're here.
I'll open the door.
Stop waiting.
They are not coming.
Eat something.
Just eat.
Here.
Forget it. I'm not eating either.
It's fine.
Ding,
I have nothing to do later anyway.
I'll do the dishes with you.
Here we are.
Liang Chen.
Where are your manners?
Call me senior.
Liang Chen.
Chen Chen.
Then just call me Liang Chen.