♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
=The Blessed Girl=
=Episode 1=
I’m Linglong,
surnamed Huotu,
born into the Fire Tribe.
My father said
every life in our tribe
is a gift from ancestors,
but other tribesmen said
I was only born
because my father
broke ancestors’ rules.
By the way, his name is Huotu Xin.
He can bake meat pies,
but
the dough can be hard
and the meat stuffing salty.
His fresh ground soybean milk
always contains dregs.
He can cook everything
including all that you’ve eaten
or not.
Over the past 16 years,
he’s done all the cooking.
I’m the luckiest girl
to be able to enjoy the food he makes.
Linglong,
rise and shine, sleepyhead.
Today is your big day.
Linglong.
Linglong!
Father.
Father!
I didn’t mean to
sneak out behind your back.
You stayed up late last night.
I didn’t want to wake you up.
Would you rather
see me worrying?
I know, I know.
You’re
quite fragile.
I must protect
your feelings,
right?
You little troublemaker!
I knew
you went to the Glory Rock,
didn’t you?
I’m a big girl now.
You can stop worrying too much.
I can take care of myself.
Really?
Even adults wouldn’t go uphill
before dawn.
It’s slippery and dangerous,
you know?
Could you protect yourself?
Look,
I was there to pick
the first Dormant Lotus
blooming towards the sun
on the Glory Rock.
Isn’t it beautiful?
It is.
I’m giving it to Mother.
This is my first time
seeing her.
Linglong.
Father!
Stop there.
-Catch me if you can.
-Stop!
Come here.
(Beloved Wife Jin’er)
Mother,
wait for me.
I’ll see you later.
Don’t be so sure.
Only if you pass the test
will you be on the Mountain Team
and go to the Flame Chilling Wall.
Don’t let your mother down.
Of course I won’t!
Ever since the Earth Fire Test was held,
no one has passed with flying colors.
That’s because I haven’t taken it.
That’s my girl.
Moon Grass!
You found it!
Seeing the rain
last night, I thought
there’d be some this morning.
Look at you!
You also went uphill before dawn.
Alright. Enough.
Eat it while it’s hot.
What do you think?
Is it good?
Just relax.
Focus on the Test.
Don’t feel pressured.
You don’t need a clean sweep
to be on the Mountain Team.
If I didn’t make it,
you’d be the one to blame
for being a bad teacher.
I’m a bad teacher?
You know what?
When I was
in the team,
I was the best firefighter.
Or your mother wouldn’t have
fallen for me at first sight.
Didn’t you say
that was because you were handsome?
I can be both.
Father,
why did Mother
go there?
Others all say...
What do they know?
They’re a bunch of green-eyed bumpkins
because I married your mother.
Your mother gave birth to you.
That’s all you need to know.
I’m no longer a kid
and I deserve the truth.
I made this for you.
It’s beautiful and useful.
You’ll be invincible in it.
Take it.
Father.
Put it on,
pass the test
and see for yourself.
If you find your mother,
ask her for me
why she went there that day.
By that day,
he meant the day I was born.
The place my mother went
is called Flame Chilling Wall
built by our ancestors.
Behind that wall
is the Earth Fire
that once destroyed everything.
It’s
the most terrifying place in the world
and it’s off-limits.
Only the bravest ones
chosen by the Mountain Team
have access to it.
Of course my father was one of them
while my mother
wasn’t even born here.
That day,
Father broke the rules
by going through the Wall with Mother
and stepping into the Earth Fire.
500 years ago,
the Earth Fire
turned our tribe into hell.
By going through the Wall,
we could go back to that day
and witness
that apocalypse as if
the world had stopped 500 years ago.
No one knows the origin of that fire
or my mother’s background.
That day,
only Father and I came back.
Tribesmen never gave their blessings
to my parents’ marriage
or my birth.
My father was the bravest man here
who had taken the Mountain Team
to extinguish countless fires.
But ever since that day,
he hasn’t been near
the Flame Chilling Wall again
as if he abandoned his duty
to guard the Wall and fight fires
and forgot my mother.
But not me.
I’ve waited for 16 years,
for this very day
to be on the Mountain Team
so that I can put out
the Earth Fire behind the Wall
and find out everything about my mother.
Today is the day.
I’ll pass the Earth Fire Test.
The Huotus will come back
as heroes of the Mountain Team
and leave our names
on the Glory Rock.
Fire never dies!
Do you recognize this?
Flammable Stone!
Such stones with inexhaustible energy
used to be our treasure
and laid the foundation
of our former glory
but they can destroy us as well
as they keep the Earth Fire on
for 500 years.
Flammable Stones
are right under our feet
in the mountains.
Such mines
are all over our tribe.
We can live
to this day
because our ancestors
built the Flame Chilling Wall
at the cost of their lives
to cut off the mines underground
and seal the Earth Fire
in the Wall.
As their descendants,
we cannot hide
outside the Wall they built
just to make ourselves safe.
Make it stop!
To quench the Earth Fire,
we must find every Flammable Stone mine,
cut them off one by one
until
the last Flammable Stone
is dug out.
Then
the Earth Fire
will be gone forever.
That’s
the mission we’re born with.
-Fire never dies!
You should know
this is the most dangerous job.
-Also the most glorious one.
Has she no shame
signing up for the Test?
Well,
I won’t lose
to that oddball.
Linglong,
we trust you
and we have nothing to worry about,
right?
Yes.
Alright.
Prove yourself
in the Test.
Remember,
there are no rules
in the Test.
Don’t get killed
and put out the Earth Fire.
That’s it.
But
every judgment,
decision
and move you make
will determine
if you’re qualified to
be on the Mountain Team,
go to the Flame Chilling Wall
and carry on the great mission
our ancestors left undone.
Get yourselves ready.
Follow me.
Prove yourselves.
-Come on!
-You can do it!
Pass the Test! Make us proud!
You must win!
Linglong,
the result doesn’t matter.
I’ll cook your favorite food
and wait for you at home.
I’ll pass the Test.
I know. Go ahead.
You’ll pass it!
I’ll only say this once
because the Earth Fire
won’t give you a second chance.
Centered around the Hawkeye Peak,
within the 2.5-kilometer radius,
at the long and narrow valley corridor,
there’s simulated Earth Fire
made with fire powder everywhere.
Your task
is to identify the fire route,
block the Earth Fire
and destroy the center of it.
If the fire powder has covered
half of your body,
you’ll be deemed as burned
and eliminated immediately.
Come on!
Come. Why did you stop?
Are you sure we should follow her?
What if we catch bad luck?
Nonsense!
Be careful!
You’re welcome.
Linglong, you Huotus
are as good as they say.
I heard a lot from my father
that when your father
was on the Mountain Team,
he put out 18 fires in a row
without losing a hair.
What else did your old man say?
He also said,
“what a shame”.
Focus.
This isn’t over yet.
Look over there.
Every fire
points to that direction.
The center must be there.
This could be our chance to win.
Didn’t your father say
the Huotus
are born to win?
The three of us will
destroy the center and be winners.
Xia Ling’s team
has put out another fire.
Most fires on the east side
of the Hawkeye Peak are out.
No one on the two teams is burned.
All of them
have great potential.
No one caught the fire?
They’re swift,
especially Linglong and her members.
They’ve done it
quickly and accurately.
Maybe they’ll all survive.
Since when
was the Earth Fire so nice to people?
Change of plan.
Activate the Burning Ring.
Something is wrong.
What’s up?
If the two fires join each other,
we’ll be trapped inside.
Run!
Go!
Go on!
Hurry up and go!
Luckily, you took the precaution
by using two Stone Freezing Balls.
Goodness!
That was close.
According to my father,
that’s the Burning Ring.
If we got trapped,
we’d be dead for sure.
My father has never said that.
Safety matters the most.
We’ve put out tons of fires.
Destroying the center
is almost impossible.
Anyway,
no one has ever won.
All we need
is a spot on the Mountain Team.
No.
I must win.
More are coming
our way, I think.
There are no rules in the Test.
No rules?
Listen,
hide yourselves.
Don’t go anywhere
near the fire.
Protect yourselves first.
We’ll win.
Fine.
What if Xia Ling
puts out more fires
than us?
That’s not going to happen
because I’m here.
Where are you going?
To fight fires.
Linglong,
shouldn’t you be with your team members?
What are you doing here?
To extinct the Earth Fire.
What’s your plan?
You’re the real source
of the Earth Fire.
Once I get you,
the Fire will die out.
Let’s see.
Why did you do that?
You said
there are no rules in the Test.
The same goes for the real Earth Fire.
All we need to do
is to put it out.
But you’ve
got burned.
If there’s a chance
to quench
all the fires within the Wall,
won’t you risk your life?
That’s what
a qualified Mountain Team member
should do,
am I right?
Linglong.
Congratulations!
You’re the first one ever
to have put out the Fire completely.
Unfortunately,
you can’t be
on the Mountain Team.
She’s never allowed
to go to the Flame Chilling Wall?
After discussion,
the Elders and I
have reached that decision
and notified Chi Fang.
Even if
she passed the Earth Fire Test?
She won’t.
You...
Huotu Xin, what are you doing?
Do you know
how much this means to her?
I do.
This is for the sake
of you and our tribe.
Back then,
you disregarded the rules
and married an outsider,
leading to a huge mess.
We cannot afford another risk.
The past is the past.
Can’t you let it go?
Linglong
carries the blood of a foreign tribe.
Once she went there
and offended the ancestors,
there could be dire consequences.
How could she offend them?
Tell me about it!
What’s her surname?
It’s Huotu!
Ancestors couldn’t be
happier seeing her.
The Huotus
inherit that surname from
the great Founding Father
of our tribe, Huotu Ke.
Shut up!
I won’t!
I’m surprised that you still remember
Huotu is our Founding Father’s surname.
But look at you!
What’s wrong with me?
You abdicated your responsibility
for a foreign woman,
and left the Mountain Team
to babysit
your daughter at home.
Are you still a Huotu?
I won’t change my decision.
Period!
Huotu Xin.
Leader.
Is Linglong back yet?
Linglong?
What happened?
She was upset
because she didn’t make the cut
and she quarreled with Xia Ling.
I’m worried...
If anything happens to her,
I’ll make all of you pay!
Huotu Xin!
What did you tell him?
I said
Linglong
put out all the fires alone.
Did you activate the Burning Ring?
Yes,
I did.
How did she succeed?
Father.
Will your name
be carved on the Glory Stone?
Me?
I can’t care less about that.
But I care.
Ever since the first time
you took me here
and told me stories
about those ancestors on the Rock,
this place
has become my favorite.
I have tons of
other stories.
We can go to the White Forest next time.
I’ll tell you a story
about the Deer Hunter.
Did they cast me out
because of
what happened to Mother?
Of course not.
You’re a terrible liar.
Do you really think
you’ve grasped the gist
of the Earth Fire
just because you found a loophole?
Hadn’t I done that,
no one would’ve won.
That’s why
no one did.
Because it’s never
about winning or losing.
It’s about life.
When the Earth Fire was blazing,
tens of thousands of our ancestors
sacrificed their lives
to build the Flame Chilling Wall.
Why?
That wasn’t
to seal the Fire
or put their names
on the Glory Rock.
They did that
to protect those
outside the Wall.
Even the wisest ancestor
didn’t know
when the Earth Fire would stop.
If everyone
threw themselves
into the fire like you
only to win,
what would happen?
There’d be no one left
to fill the cracks
on the Flame Chilling Wall.
The Earth Fire would burst out someday
and set not only our tribe
but also the entire Suchuan on fire.
That
would be a real catastrophe.
This test
is lesson one of the Mountain Team.
It teaches you
that life is more important
than putting out the Earth Fire.
That’s ancestors’ teaching.
So
it’s fair that you lost.
Don’t blame others for it.
But
that’s
different
from what Chi Fang said.
What does he know?
Were I still on the Team,
he wouldn’t
become the team leader.
I don’t believe you.
I swear
to all the ancestors on the Rock
that everything
I said
is nothing but the truth.
You know, your mother
isn’t behind the Flame Chilling Wall.
She’s in your heart
keeping you company.
I understand, Father.
I’d like to hang out here for a while.
Just go home without me.
It’s... It’s getting dark.
Please!
Fine, alright.
Just a little while.
I’m leaving.
Come home
before it’s dark.
Fine.
-Or the food will get cold.
-I know.
No sign of her.
I looked everywhere but didn’t see her.
Don’t panic.
Our village is small.
She must be somewhere nearby.
Where are you going?
To find my daughter.
Do you know where she is?
We’ve got so many men looking for her.
You won’t help me.
What’s that supposed to mean?
Aren’t we helping you now?
No one wants her to get hurt.
She must’ve
gone to the Flame Chilling Wall.
What?
What are you waiting for?
Go there now!
Follow me!
Leader,
you aren’t mad at her?
Not now.
We’ve got more important things to do.
Shizi,
hey,
when can we stop doing this?
Stop whining.
There’s no one down there.
Go down and stand guard.
It’s late.
Who’d go through the Wall?
Do you still have liquor?
Let’s drink.
Danzi!
Look.
Anyone?
Leader.
What...? What brings you here this late?
Did Linglong go inside?
Has anyone got in?
I don’t think so.
You don’t think so?
I don’t know.
Even if she’s inside,
the fires there are unpredictable.
Without our fire map,
she won’t get to the Palace of Flames.
Have you forgotten about the Test?
Huotu Xin!
You came faster than I thought.
Perfect timing. Let’s go.
It’s dark.
We can come again next time.
You’re lying again.
Linglong!
Father.
I don’t get to
come here again, do I?
I’ve promised Mother.
I just want to see
the place where she passed away.
I’m always eager...
To see for myself.
Do you know
your mother
once looked at me in the same way?
She begged me to bring her here.
Although we weren’t together
for too long,
every moment we shared
is the most precious memory
to me.
It’s irreplaceable.
But that one is the only exception.
I regret it a million times
and I’ll never
forgive myself for it.
I wish I could
undo what I did.
Linglong,
you’re
everything I have now.
I cannot
have another regret.
Well then,
stay close to me.
Linglong!
Stop!
Linglong, where are you?
Linglong!
Come back!
It’s dangerous!
Linglong!
Linglong, watch out!
Father!
Hang in there!
Linglong.
Everything will be fine.
I’m here.
Come, Linglong.
Linglong.
Leader, what’s that?
Does that come from
the Palace of Flames?
What...?
What’s that, Leader?
Is that ancestors’ warning?
What should we do, Leader?
Say something, Leader!
Be careful!
What’s that?
No idea.
What is that thing?
Leader, what’s that?
Should we attack?
Is it the Fire Demon?
A monster!
Be careful. Watch out.
Kill her.
Stop!
Run!
Linglong, it’s me!
I’m your father, Linglong!
Wake up!
Stop!
Don’t hurt her.
Relax.
I won’t.
She won’t hurt others either.
Do you recognize me?
He’s your father.
You shouldn’t have hit him.
You can cure him,
right?
Linglong,
is it you?
Cover her.
Linglong.
You’re fine. Everything is fine.
Where’s that monster?
Be careful.
That’s not a monster.
Don’t be scared
or try to hurt her.
You should be in awe of her
because
she’s your Goddess.
It’s true that Goddess
has never left.
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪