♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 27=
Is he the Grand Hao Tian Master?
My name is Shi Nian,
a teacher from Cang Hui School.
Where is the Grand Hao Tian Master?
Why do you want to see him?
I should verify your words
as to consider our collaboration.
As long as you could enter
the final of Soul Master School Contest,
you would get to see him.
Why?
Only when you succeed to enter the final
could you be of our help.
Tang San.
I hope you don't misunderstand
Cang Hui School.
In fact,
we can be friends.
What do you say?
You're right. We're friends.
Friends should help each other.
Are you willing to enter the final
and fulfill a small wish
for us?
Of course, what's your wish?
You'll know
when the time comes.
Sure.
As friends,
it's also crucial to be honest
with each other.
You're right.
Friends should be honest
with each other.
Did you meet Du Gu Bo?
Yes.
Why doesn't he come here?
Du Gu Bo has been poisoned
and he doesn't dare to approach
Cang Hui School.
I came here to snoop for him
the means of removing the toxin.
Please tell him that
whether he wants to remove his own toxin
or Du Gu Yan's,
I advise him to see me in person.
I am not in a hurry.
I can wait for him till
he has tried every means
and met the deadlock,
I'll wait for him at Cang Hui School.
There's only one condition
for removing the toxin,
ask him
to be our friends too.
Sure. Let him be our friends.
You may go.
Looking forward to our good cooperation.
See you in the final.
See you there, my good friend.
Watch your steps.
What are you smiling about?
What on earth are you smiling about?
Tang San.
What happened to me just now?
You keep giggling after coming back
and your facial expression changed
suddenly.
Shi Nian
is a teacher of Cang Hui School.
I felt that he's kind
once I met him.
Whatever he said,
I'd totally agree with him.
Does he have Spirit Branch Martial Soul?
I think so.
He tried to control me.
How did you get rid of it?
I have no idea.
I heard someone calling me
in my mind.
The voice can leave a shield
deep inside your mind.
Do you know any other
Grand Soul Land Masters?
No. It's a woman's voice.
I don't know her.
There're lots of secrets
in you little brat
with just Triple Soul Rings.
Your Highness,
Prince Xue Xing has sparked
a dispute between the Imperial School
and Shi Lan Ke School.
They're going to fight tonight.
Under such a situation,
I'm afraid that only you
could stop them.
I'm busy.
I don't have time for trivial matters.
Don't you remember that
it was you who introduce
Shi Lan Ke School to here?
Regarding Shi Lan Ke School,
ask them to settle by themselves.
I did say that I'm preoccupied.
Don't disturb me again.
I've stayed for long at Shi Lan Ke School before,
I would rather not meet them.
If they found something fishy,
it would be troublesome.
What do you say?
Get out of here.
I have a way to remove the toxin.
Have you gone berserk?
Please promise me two conditions.
I can't even handle this poison,
do you think you can?
Anyway,
you have no other methods.
Why don't you trust me again?
How to do it?
Listen to my conditions first.
Speak out.
Firstly,
we need 2000 Gold Soul Coins
to participate in
Soul Master School Contest.
Sure.
Secondly,
I doubt that the Grand Hao Tian Master
behind Cang Hui School
was controlled by
Spirit Branch Martial Soul
of Shi Nian.
Please help me to capture him,
I'll wake him.
Sure.
Now, tell me.
How to remove the toxin?
My Martial Soul makes me impregnable
to any toxins.
But it doesn't mean that
you can remove the toxin.
The toxin is combined with her blood.
Yes.
I've approached it before
but I didn't get poisoned.
This means that my blood
is able to resist the poison.
What rubbish are you talking about?
What if I transfuse my blood
to her?
Both of you are the same in nature.
It may work.
Let's start now.
Hold on.
Have you thought about
how much blood should I transfuse to her?
Replace all her blood, of course.
Then my blood will be drained out.
Of course.
I'll die.
It's your honour
to save my granddaughter.
Lie down.
How about the toxin inside you?
As long as she's saved,
I could die together with you. I'm okay with that.
But I don't want to.
You have no choice, though.
Elder,
we can interchange.
What do you mean?
Transfuse my blood to her
and transfuse her blood to me.
Her blood is poisonous.
But I'm immune to poisons.
I can remove the toxin myself.
By interchanging our blood,
neither our blood
nor our life will lose.
How to do it?
It's impossible.
My Martial Soul is Blue Silver Plant.
Who cares
what your Martial Soul is?
The veins of the plant are hollow.
Use Blue Silver Plant for transfusion?
We may have a try.
Start now.
Let me return to my school first.
Why?
I've been missing for some time.
I should inform Wu and the others.
Not necessary.
My Martial Soul is also poisonous.
I may do something
during the transfusion.
How dare you!
I want to go back first.
We're almost there.
It was originally Lanba School.
And now it belongs to
Shi Lan Ke School.
I'm totally not interested
in your topic.
Hurry up and settle your things
and go back to do the transfusion.
Elder.
I think you don't have any friends,
right?
How do you know?
I could tell
from your attitude.
What do you mean? Are you scolding me?
Can't you guess it?
Elder.
Do you
rarely communicate with others?
I used to focus on researching toxins.
I've got no time for others.
No hanging out?
Why do I need it?
Well, now I get it.
What?
Nothing.
Our school...
They're not from our school.
What does it matter?
Hurry up.
Tiao Dou Imperial School has a task
inside.
No interruptions.
What task is it?
Are you from Shi Lan Ke School?
Yes.
Capture him.
Elder.
Did you kill them all?
They just fainted by my poison.
I won't kill those
from Tian Dou Imperial School.
Why?
Because the royals of Tian Dou
provide me with resources
that helped me through
to advance to Nine Soul Rings.
So, are you
the secret weapon of
Tian Dou Imperial School?
Why do you have so many questions?
Elder, I'll go in and check it out.
Why are Yu Tian Heng and
Brother Dai fighting?
Mr. Lander,
you're aware of the battling rules
between schools.
If no one wins over Yu Tian Heng,
you have to hand the girl over.
I'm not defeated yet.
Brother Dai...
According to the underlying rules
in Tian Dou City,
students are responsible to resolve
the schools' disputes by battling.
That brat
is quite strong among those
with Quadruple Soul Rings.
While the tiger,
he only has Three Soul Rings.
He can't win.
Who will be handed over to them?
How do I know?
You can't win over him.
Do you have any methods?
Since you're willing to do the transfusion,
give me your right hand.
It's done.
You can release your fist
with full force.
Thank you so much.
Who will be handed over to them?
Tang San?
Tang San, where have you been?
Tell me what's happening now first.
Sister Wu broke into
Tian Dou Imperial School.
She was knocked out by Yu Tian Heng.
They want to hang her
at the school gate.
Wu was knocked out?
Yes.
Headmaster has brought her back.
Don't worry.
But once we're back,
they've reached here,
saying that if we lose
in the Soul Battle,
we have to hand Wu over to them.
We were planning to do a tag match,
but
Yu Tian Heng is too powerful.
Brother Dai.
Let me do it.
He's strong.
Be careful.
No worries.
I have a secret weapon.
Are you all right?
Is it you who knocked out Wu?
She has gone berserk
and broke into our place
to search for you.
It's impossible.
That's amazing.
Yu Tian Heng is impossible to lose.
You must have hidden tricks.
Only students could involve
in the Soul Battle between schools.
This is what you said just now.
You said that
as long as someone from our school
could defeat him,
you will forget about Wu's matter.
Your Highness,
you won't go back your words
before us, right?
If you don't pay up for the contest,
you're not allowed to participate in it.
Tang San.
What's wrong
with your fist just now?
Where is Wu?
In the room.
She is just in a temporary coma,
it's nothing serious.
Why did Wu
break into Tian Dou Imperial School?
It was because of you.
Me?
After you went missing,
she was scared out of her mind.
We suspected Tian Dou royals,
so she broke into their place.
Wu.
You're back.
Are you alright?
I went to look for you.
I even...
fought with them.
By the way,
Tian Yu Heng is indeed strong.
I've knocked him out.
Really?
Because he has bullied you.
It's not all his fault, though.
It's me who broke into
their place first.
He shouldn't attack you.
But
where did you go that day?
It's me who brought him away.
That Grand Soul Land Master?
Have you done talking?
Can we leave now?
Where are you going?
Wu,
do you remember that
we were finding Du Gu Yan
in Star Forest?
She has been poisoned.
I want to go and help her
to remove the toxin.
Why is it you?
Let's go.
No one
could ever take my student away
before me.
Even if you have Nine Soul Rings.
Want a fight?
Headmaster.
Please listen to me.
I'm willing to go.
Please don't fight.
Please.
Don't worry.
I'll come back once it's done.
How do you remove the toxin?
Interchange his blood with Yan Yan's.
Isn't that more dangerous?
That's why I let him come
to see you.
I have confidence.
Wu, release my hand.
No way.
You have vowed
that you'll always stay by my side.
Well.
Let's go together.
It'll be alright.
I couldn't be disturbed
during the transfusion.
Wu, wait for me outside.
I want to stay.
I won't talk nor move.
It's better to let her go out.
She's my sister.
Let her stay here then.
It's not necessary.
If you failed,
I'll poison her.
But it has nothing to do with her.
I don't care.
I just want to save Yan Yan.
Let's start.
This is for blood drawing.
This is for blood transfusing.
That's how the interchange works.
Initiate the Martial Soul
to remove the toxin yourself.
I did think of blood interchanging
before.
But I don't have blood
that can remove toxins
nor tools like Blue Silver Plant.
Now, I can only
depend on Tang San.
Hang in there.
The toxin will be removed
if her blood is all changed.
I know.
He is captured by
that Grand Soul Land Master?
They mentioned about
removing the toxin by changing blood.
With Tang San's blood?
He said that Tang San is
immune to toxins.
This method will surely fail.
Why?
Tang San is immune to poisons
because of the self-purification
of his Martial Soul.
When changing the blood,
the toxins will enter into his body
continuously
and his Martial Soul
would have to keep functioning.
With his current ability,
he just can't stand for a long time
as his Soul Power will drain up soon.
What's the consequence?
Both of them will die.
Oh gosh.
It was because of
Tian Dou Imperial School.
If they didn't stop us,
we'd have come back earlier.
It's the same even if you're back.
Our rival has Nine Soul Rings.
How do you know we'll lose
since we haven't fought him?
The point is they left so fast,
I have no idea where they've gone to.
They just left?
Their scent should still linger.
Come out, Luo San Pao.
Smell around this room.
Tell me, where have they gone?
It has got it.
Let's go now. Stop dawdling.
Headmaster.
Don't fight him head-on,
just save Tang San and Wu.
After so many years,
three of us are collaborating again.
Run your Martial Soul.
Keep your Martial Soul running.
You'll die if you can't persist.
I know.
Good.
Very good.
It's working now.
Just hang in there.
Good.
I know.
What's wrong with him?
He's running out of Soul Power now.
He can't afford to function
with full force.
What will happen to him?
If he failed,
both Yan Yan and he will die.
Stop him right now.
No way.
Your granddaughter will die too.
Everything will turn futile
if he stops now.
Yan Yan will die too.
Let's put a bet.
Let's bet that this brat can persist.
Hang in there.
Tang San can't persist anymore.
Don't touch him.
I want to help him.
No one can help him.
I can.
I can transfer my Soul Power
to him
to make him continue
the removing process.
Soul Power is different from blood,
I've never heard that
it can be transferred.
I can do it.
If this keeps going on,
Tang San wouldn't be able to continue
supporting Blue Silver Plant,
and both of them will die.
Let me try.
How come Soul Power can be transferred?
Will this work?
Right ahead of us.
It seems like the invincible
with Nine Soul Rings
doesn't live a great life though.
He lives in a cave.
Let's go in
and check it out.
Very good.
Just hold on for a while.
If you continue
to transfer your Soul Power to him,
you'll be done.
Last time,
when I was locked in a cage,
Tang San forsook his Martial Soul
to save me.
He said that he'll protect me.
However, he doesn't know that
deep in my heart,
I have the same thought.
I'll protect Tang San too.
I'll keep him safe.
So, I'm not afraid.
I don't care whether you are afraid.
I just want you to keep it going.
At least
until Yan Yan's treated.
Keep on.
Why are they seeking trouble now?
Keep going on. I'll go out for a while.
Brother,
for the sake of you,
I'll persist.
Building a house within the cave?
He has found us.
How did you find it?
Dog?
No.
It's a Soul Skill.
Tang San who you brought away
is my disciple.
So what?
I'm here to bring him back.
I offer you a chance now.
Leave now and I won't fight you.
Return Tang San and Wu to us,
and we'll leave immediately.
Aren't you aware of
your current situation?
I know.
You're the invincible
with Nine Soul Rings.
Sorry.
Because of Lander and my students,
you're involved again.
Once again we collaborate,
I feel the time has rewound.
I feel like I'm superfluous.
Two with Seven Soul Rings.
Double Soul Rings?
You're just inferior to your disciple.
It's great that disciple surpasses me.
How dare you fight me
with such a weak team?
What Soul Skill is it?
Nothing will change.
That dog?
This is the Martial Soul Fusion Skill
of Golden Iron Triangle,
Sacred Dragon.
Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
I've never thought this secret skill
would exist.
We only want
Tang San and Wu.
Are you threatening me?
Go, Luo San Pao!
It's almost done.
Everything will be all right.
He is really robust,
it seems we can't stand him anymore.
We can lose,
but we can't retreat.
She's right.
Golden Iron Triangle
should not be defeated by fear.
Let's fight till the end.
Watch out!
Stop!
Tang San?
How is it?
Her toxin is removed.
Tang San.
Headmaster, Sir.
No worries. Please listen to me.
Tang San, are you okay?
Where is Wu?
I'm fine.
Wu
is taking care of Du Gu Yan inside.
She is too daring.
Ask her to come out.
Let's leave here.
Sir, Headmaster.
Can you leave first?
Truth be told,
the toxin of Du Gu Yan and Du Gu Bo
was caused by me.
I should treat them before leaving.
No way, Du Gu Bo is so terrible.
I nearly freaked out just now.
Yes.
Both of you must leave here.
Am I right?
Are you kidding?
Is this enough to scare you?
Actually...
Actually, Mr. Du Gu is quite nice.
He's just nervous
to save his granddaughter.
Are we leaving like this?
He has his own thoughts
and responsibility.
Since Tang San and Wu let us leave.
We should respect them.
Why did you stand in front of me?
Did I?
Yes.
Perhaps I was freaked out
and went the wrong way.
You wanted to protect me?
How can I with Double Soul Rings
protect you who has Seven Soul Rings?
Isn't that too arrogant?
Am I right, Lander?
I've seen it.
You were protecting her just now.
True feelings only reveal
in crucial moments of life and death.
See? Just admit it.
You...
The toxin is removed.
She will awake soon.
What happened to her?
Something is special about this girl.
Special?
Soul Power
belongs to the power of Soul Master.
It can't be transferred
to other Soul Masters.
It's a basic rule of Martial Soul.
But, she breaks it.
During the transfusion,
you had to run Martial Soul all time.
However, your Soul Power
was insufficient.
When the process is going to fail,
it was this girl
who transferred her Soul Power to you.
Her action
had violated the common cognition
of Soul Masters.
Aren't you shocked?
I just want to know
whether she is okay now.
I'm afraid that
she has given you all her Soul Power.
When I left here,
two of her Soul Rings had been crushed.
What does it mean?
Perhaps she will become
a common person.
Is it life-threatening?
I don't think so.
Could I
return the Soul Power to her?
Didn't I say that
Soul Power can't be transferred?
This is the rule.
Wu, are you awake?
Are you all right?
Yes.
Is the toxin removal done?
It is done.
Everything is over. No worries.
Then I'll take some
Soul Power back.
What's wrong?
My Soul Rings have been crushed.
I can't be a Soul Master anymore.
That's why I want to return
all your Soul Power.
I can't form the Soul Ring.
So I can't
absorb Soul Power.
No, there must be a way.
Teach me. I'll return it to you.
I'm afraid you can't.
No one can do it.
It's fine, Wu.
Regarding Soul Power,
I'll accompany you to practice
from scratch.
It won't take long.
Wait for me then.
Don't advance too fast.
Don't worry. I'll wait for you.
Elder.
Please come.
I have something to tell you.
Is she able to recover?
It's impossible.
My Martial Soul was injured back then.
But it had recovered
after absorbing a Soul Beast.
It's different. You were just injured,
but your Martial Soul was still reserved.
But, she has given you
all her Soul Power.
There must be a way.
Well, it's your turn now.
My turn? What do you want?
Remove your toxin.
I've promised both of you.
It's your turn now.
I don't need it.
What do you mean?
There are a lot of toxins in my blood.
With your Soul Power,
you're incapable to do that.
It's fine.
It's enough that
my granddaughter is saved.
How about you?
I'm not afraid of dying.
I thought you would want to try.
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪