♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 26=
Oh yes.
I want to know one more thing.
Golden Iron Triangle
is considered iron or gold?
You're stupid. It's just a name.
Your name is Ma Hong Jun.
You're Hong or Jun?
Don't bother with him, Headmaster.
Carry on.
You have your point.
Do the headmistress and Master
have any secrets
that they never tell?
Yeah.
Her name is Liu Er Long.
She and Master are from the same tribe.
To be honest,
she has fallen in love with Master.
I knew it.
Fallen in love.
Have they
got together?
Later, Master had a relationship
with the chief of Martial Soul Hall,
Bi Bi Dong.
Er Long was so upset.
Then the Golden Iron Triangle
disbanded.
Bi Bi Dong?
Master is really something!
Now it seems like the headmistress
hasn't forgotten about Master.
Am I right?
Yeah.
This...
This is good news.
At least she can help all of you
to join the contest.
What is that?
Think about it.
Headmistress Liu fell for Master.
Master and the chief
also had a relationship before.
Why is there nothing about you?
This... You don't understand.
When Master was still young,
my personality was
far better than his.
No. Then no one liked you
because you were ugly?
Go to clean up your room!
I... I was wrong about it.
You...
Let's go.
After that, we were kicked out
of Tian Dou Imperial School.
Yu Tian Heng brought us
to this place.
I never expected that you're
the headmistress.
That's what has happened
over the years.
You and Bi Bi Dong
never met again?
That was something in the past.
I don't mind helping you to sign up for the contest.
I can change the name of Lanba
to Shi Lan Ke.
I think it's inappropriate.
Why?
It is
an abandoned school anyway.
And I will let you
take over my place as the headmaster.
No. No!
I... I'm just an ordinary teacher.
Okay. I will give my place to Lander
and become an ordinary teacher with you.
But...
It's settled.
We will register tomorrow morning.
You said that your name is Hu Lie Na.
The direct disciple of Bi Bi Dong.
I told someone to check it.
Hu Lie Na
died two years ago.
You're not Hu Lie Na.
So, who are you?
Only you
can know the truth.
You guys go out.
Release your Martial Soul.
Your Highness, we will be waiting at the door.
You can tell me now.
Hu Lie Na is dead.
I just borrowed her identity.
You can even find this out.
Nothing can be hidden from you.
So who are you exactly?
My name is Qian Ren Xue.
Bi Bi Dong's daughter?
Princess of Martial Soul Hall?
I'm no princess.
Why did you go
to Shi Lan Ke School?
I have my mission.
What mission?
Replace Dai Mu Bai.
He is the Prince of Xing Luo Empire.
And he is alone in Shi Lan Ke.
This is a great opportunity
to replace him.
How to replace?
Just like this.
Your Highness, is everything all right?
I'm fine. Just stay outside.
My mother
lent me this power.
A Tool Soul with Six Soul Rings
can't restrict me.
You've seen that.
Devil Fox Soul is
an illusion created by my mother.
My real Martial Soul is this.
You asked me how I was going to replace him.
This is what I meant.
I'm not going back to the palace tonight.
Prepare some food and put it at the door.
From now on,
without my order,
no one can step into this room.
Yes!
Why are we not allowed to register?
You have to clear all the debts
before you can register.
The school owed Tian Dou Empire money.
What does that have to do with Martial Soul Hall?
This is instructed
by the royal family of Tian Dou.
Ask them if you don't believe it.
Who gave the order?
Prince Xue Xing.
Headmistress Liu
has changed the school signboard.
Now Lanba School has become
Shi Lan Ke School.
And we've also
cleaned up the school.
Headmistress Liu is a nice person.
She taught me how to plant
trees and flowers.
One day, when the saplings
outside the school
grow into big trees,
maybe they will bring back
the beautiful forest scenery
that Lanba School used to have!
I heard that Teacher Liu
has given her place
to our headmaster.
Henceforward,
this place will be
the new Shi Lan Ke School.
As she becomes a teacher,
she still can teach us.
Not today.
Before the closing date
for registration,
we must collect 2,000 Gold Soul Coins.
Otherwise, we can't join the contest.
Master and Headmaster
are busy making money.
No wonder Brother Dai and the rest
perform in the street to make money.
The string has broken.
What did you say?
Brother Dai performs in the street?
Yes.
Use Soul Skills to earn money?
No. Tian Dou City is a big city
with so many Soul Masters.
People have seen too many Soul Skills.
So nobody will give them money.
What does he do to earn money?
The drama written by Ou Si Ke.
Brother Dai also has a role.
So both of them act together.
Brother Dai wants to perform
the drama written by Ou Si Ke?
How is that possible?
He refused to do it at first.
But Ou Si Ke said
it could help you guys to join the contest.
So he agreed.
Wait.
Which drama written by Ou Si Ke?
The latest one.
Such a foolish story.
And they want to perform it?
No choice. We need money.
Brother, give some response.
You are the demon.
Brother... That's all for today.
Please do the ending scene properly.
Demon Dai, today I must
bring back the princess.
Brother.
You need to continue.
Show your Soul Rings.
Triple Soul Rings Soul Honour?
Carry on. You're an actor.
Don't stop until I say so.
He has been defeated.
Princess!
Princess. What happened to you?
Poor girl.
Princess.
The princess looks so ugly.
That's right.
What did the demon
do to you with his Soul Skills?
Only a sincere kiss
can save the princess.
Princess.
Give me a second.
Princess, I love you!
You said you wouldn't kiss me.
Just one kiss. We need to make it realistic.
Just one kiss.
I'm done. I'm done.
Where are they?
My dearest princess.
She has got back to normal.
I was entrusted by the Frog Kingdom
and have finally undone
the Soul Skill of princess.
Let her return to normal.
Do you love me, princess?
She says she loves me!
Will you go home with me
and make a baby frog?
She says yes!
Let's stay together forever.
Kiss it.
I love you.
Kiss it. Kiss it. Kiss it.
Good.
That's all for today.
Applause
for the actor who played the demon...
Dai Mu Bai!
Good job!
How dare you!
And the actor who played
the ugly princess, Ma Hong Jun!
Well done.
So cute. So ugly.
Everyone.
Please give us some money
if you have it.
If you don't have it,
just give us some money anyway, okay?
Okay!
But I couldn't understand
why it must be
the frog princess.
Rong Rong and Sister Qing
refused to take part.
So they only have Ma Hong Jun.
Ou Si Ke said Ma Hong Jun was too ugly.
It doesn't make sense to let him play the princess.
So he changed the identity
of the princess.
Does a frog princess make sense?
I don't know.
I wanted to give it a try at first.
But you didn't allow me to do that.
Of course you can't!
In his drama,
he will kiss you!
Brother, you don't want me
to be kissed?
It's because
Ou Si Ke's drama is terrible.
It's fixed. Here you go.
Listen.
This Godly Zhu Ge Crossbow is
very dangerous.
You must use it carefully.
Understand?
I've never used it before.
It broke because Rong Rong
borrowed it to see how it works.
Rong Rong?
But she already has one.
It was broken long ago.
Brother San. Brother San.
Wu.
Rong Rong.
It has been fixed?
Yes.
That's great!
Brother San,
I have something to tell you.
I've sold you out.
As I mentioned before,
the Godly Crossbow you made
is very useful
for Support Branch Soul Masters.
After my clan knew about it,
they were very interested.
I'll bring you to them now.
I guess my clan will
pay you handsomely
for your craft in making the Godly Crossbow.
But the specific amount
still needs to be discussed in detail.
They will surely pay you a good price,
so that you can join the contest.
Everything you did
was for me?
We're from the same school
and the same battle team.
I should help you.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
All of us hope
that we can enter the final round.
We also want to become stronger
and
make Shi Lan Ke School
the top Soul Master School in Douluo Continent.
I'm sure we can make it. One day,
Shi Lan Ke School
will become the top school in Douluo Continent.
The Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke
will become the strongest battle team.
Hopefully, that day will come.
My dad must be very happy.
Oh yes. You asked
about Cang Hui School.
I have asked my dad.
The spy we hired said
that Cang Hui School is
a small obscure school.
Other than that,
there's nothing important.
How about Ye Zhi Qiu?
Ye Zhi Qiu
is a student of Cang Hui School.
But this guy
doesn't have any friends
at school.
And he hardly interacts with anyone
outside the school.
Who does he usually contact?
This... How about
I send someone to keep an eye
on him for a longer time.
No need.
Ye Zhi Qiu is a very cautious person.
Also, he hides in the dark.
It is hard to get any information
by stalking him.
Hare. Hare.
Where is Wu?
Hare for sale.
Let's look for her.
Hare.
Wu!
Hare for sale.
Come and have a look.
What are you looking at?
So many rabbits.
Hare. One for ten Copper Soul Coins.
Roasted hare tastes good.
They are so cute.
Why do you want to eat them?
It's very delicious.
Hare. Hare for sale.
Have a look.
Do you like it? I can buy it for you.
Fleshy rabbits.
Boss,
all my money here is
enough to buy
all of your rabbits.
Send all the rabbits
to Shi Lan Ke School.
No problem.
Rong Rong, you're the best.
But I still think that Tang San
is the best.
I know. I know.
Your Brother Tang San is the best.
But, you're just a little bit
less than Tang San.
Really. Just a little bit.
Just a little bit?
Naughty little hare.
May I ask
where Shi Lan Ke School is?
It used to be Lanba School.
No problem.
How about
we take all the rabbits
and release them?
Sure.
They are your rabbits. It's your call.
Okay. Let's go.
My clan is right ahead.
Where is Tang San?
Did he go
to buy something?
Let's look for him.
Tang San.
This way.
-Tang San.
Gone?
Yeah. We lost him in a blink of an eye.
We thought he was walking around.
But it was getting dark
and we still couldn't find him.
He didn't come back either.
I'm afraid he has been
caught by the enemy.
Who? Ye Zhi Qiu?
Ye Zhi Qiu knows our influence
in Tian Dou City.
I'm sure he won't act abruptly
and kidnap Tang San in public.
He doesn't have the guts.
Also, this doesn't
bring him any benefits.
What should we do?
Anyone else knows
that Tang San has entered the city?
Nobody knows about that.
I just made an appointment with my clan.
Your clan knows about that?
I wanted to help him to sell
his Godly Crossbow,
so that he can get some money.
It's impossible that he was caught
by my clan.
I trust you.
I didn't mean that.
I'm just thinking
who is likely to do that.
He could make Tang San
disappear silently.
This person must be very powerful.
The problem is that we just got here
and we didn't offend anyone.
Don't you remember?
At Tian Dou Imperial School,
we met the...
That mysterious Grand Soul Land Master?
But we don't know
who exactly he is.
But he appeared at Tian Dou Imperial School.
He should belong to the school.
We can go to the school and take him back.
Rong Rong.
Don't jump to the conclusion.
That is Imperial School.
Do you want us to fight with them?
Of course we can't.
How about this.
We will go to see Yu Tian Heng tomorrow.
Don't panic.
There must be a reason
why they caught Tang San.
So for the time being,
he won't be in danger.
Is anybody here?
(Tang San.)
Who is that?
Who is calling me?
It's you?
You have been poisoned.
How can you wake up early?
I have been poisoned?
Do you know her?
We met before.
My granddaughter was poisoned
by rare substances.
This poison has a latency period.
I reckon that she was poisoned
in the Star Forest.
I asked Dragon Duke and The Serpent carefully.
The Serpent said
there had been a green smoke on you
that went into her body.
Tang San. Tang San!
What is that?
In that case,
it should be
the source of the poison.
Did I get it wrong?
You're right.
How to cure the poison?
I don't know.
The poison was given to me by Ye Zhi Qiu
from Cang Hui School.
What do you want me to do?
You followed what he said?
I didn't. It was an accident.
Later, when I met Du Gu Yan,
I was absorbing
the Soul Ring of the Human Faced Demon Spider.
The Soul Bone went into my body
and made me lose my mind.
So I was unable to stop
this thing from happening.
It is indeed
the Human Faced Demon Spider's Soul Bone.
Every word I said is true.
Do you know
what the Grand Soul Land Master means?
The strongest Soul Master.
Only someone
who has analyzed certain power completely,
knows it to the highest extent,
and is able to tell its source
can acquire the title of that power.
My title
is just Venom.
Venom Soul Master.
This is poisonous smoke?
I'm the grand master in the field of poison.
But... I couldn't save Yan Yan.
The poison in her body
is a variant of my poisonous smoke.
That's right.
It was green smoke at that time.
The essence of this poisonous smoke
is a mixture of various kinds of poison.
So is the poison in her body.
This fatal poison
disintegrates and revives all the time.
Each time it revives,
there will be a change.
I couldn't cure it.
Because it is not one kind of poison,
but the mutation of various kinds of poison.
No wonder that when Ou Si Ke
cured her poison,
she woke up
and fainted immediately.
The initial poison was cured
and it generated a new kind of poison.
The reason I tell you all this
is to let you know
that the poison in Yan Yan
is deadly.
Since you got it,
you won't survive.
How dare you lie to me?
Tell me the remedy!
Poison doesn't work on me.
Doesn't work on you?
What do you mean?
My master told me.
The deadly poison in the bottle
didn't have any effect on you.
Probably because it has been suppressed
by the Soul Ring of the Thorn Apple Snake.
Besides, you've absorbed
the Soul Ring of the Human Faced Demon Spider.
Two kinds of poison are reconciled
within your body.
So your body
is immune to poison.
Drink it.
Poison?
Drink it!
Stay right there.
Where is Tang San?
Tang San? We don't know him.
Let me in to look for him.
Tian Dou Imperial School
is not a place where anyone can enter.
Get out of my way.
How dare you try to break in
with only Triple Soul Rings?
What are you doing?
Where is Tang San?
Tang San has gone missing?
Headmaster told Rong Rong
that Tang San is in your school.
Return Tang San to me!
I really don't know
where he is.
Step aside. I want to search the school.
This is Tian Dou Imperial School.
We can't let you do that.
Go away!
You'd better stop it.
I will find him myself.
Teleport doesn't work against me.
I've never seen someone so strong
with Triple Soul Rings.
She is really something.
You go to Lanba School
and ask her teacher to bring her back.
We're not going to punish her
for breaking into the school?
This is a mistake.
Hurry up.
I'm afraid this excuse
would be inappropriate.
Your Highness.
Hang her in front of the gate.
Don't let her down
in three days.
Your Highness, this...
This is too harsh.
Yu Tian Heng.
Are you trying to disobey the rules?
Wu.
She is my student.
Lanba School also wants
to interfere in this matter?
Lanba School has become
Shi Lan Ke now.
If you save her now,
it means that you're against the Imperial School.
Let me say it again.
She is my student!
Your action
will provoke the fight
between the schools.
Shi Lan Ke is very poor.
We have nothing to lose.
Let's go.
All of you have seen that.
Shi Lan Ke School
is trampling on the dignity of Imperial School.
Are you going to allow that?
No!
Senior, I'm done.
I can't drink it anymore.
No poison worked on you.
You're indeed immune to it.
Everything I said is true.
Let me ask you.
Why did Cang Hui School
poison my granddaughter?
I'm not sure about this.
I'll go to Cang Hui School
and check it out.
Senior.
Cang Hui School
has a Grand Soul Land Master.
I'm curious about his identity.
That I persuade you to go to Cang Hui School
is to fulfill
my curiosity.
What does that have to do with me?
I just feel
that I shouldn't hide it from you.
I should make it clear.
Otherwise, it's the same
as to take advantage of you.
You tell me this.
Do you think I will let you go?
I won't run away.
Actually,
I want to go
to Cang Hui School with you.
Okay. We can go together.
I will kill you if you try to run away.
We are almost there.
Kid.
Don't try
to plan anything behind me.
I know.
You've repeated this many times.
What can I do
to harm
a Grand Soul Land Master?
You're not afraid of me?
Everything I said is true.
I didn't harm Du Gu Yan.
Why should I be afraid of you?
I'm Venom Soul Master.
I'm immune to poison.
Your body is considered
unfair to me.
Based on your power,
you don't need poison.
I'm no match for you.
Senior.
Senior, why did you stop?
I can't go any further.
Why?
I had been poisoned.
Can you even be poisoned?
I injected Yan Yan's blood
into my body.
The poison and my smoke
are mixed together. There are more changes.
So I'm affected too.
But why did you inject the blood?
I want to feel the essence of the toxin.
I'm afraid the person who poisoned her
already knew you would do that.
What is the shining thing?
I can usually suppress the poison.
But sometimes it gets out of control.
This jade pendant
is to detect
the changes in the toxin.
It will flash red lights
when the toxin is getting out of control.
How about we
wait for the toxin
to stabilize?
It's not the case.
Senior.
The closer we get to Cang Hui,
the harder it is to control the toxin.
Without the warning of the jade pendant,
once we reach Cang Hui,
I won't be able to fight.
So all of these
are the tricks of Cang Hui?
Let you come to Tian Dou City
to tell me the truth.
And then wait for me to go there.
The arrangements are made for me.
Let me go for you.
You?
We need to know the source
of the poison
to solve this matter.
Why should I trust you?
Because I want to use your power
to investigate Cang Hui.
This is a collaboration.
If you try to fool me,
I'll kill you myself.
Let's work together.
Hi. I want to see Ye Zhi Qiu.
Can you help me inform him?
Go in and look for him yourself.
Why are you here?
I met Du Gu Yan's grandfather.
You poisoned Du Gu Yan
because of Du Gu Bo, right?
The poison in the Star Forest
was to control him.
It has nothing to do with you.
Is this also
the order of Hao Tian Soul Master?
Can I meet him?
Follow me.
Master.
Who?
Tang San, who I mentioned to you before,
is here.
He is Hao Tian Soul Master?
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪