Sub by kisscambodai
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 23
Let go of me.
Let go.
Bro!
I’m the noblest lady in Daye.
How could I be humiliated like this?
I can’t get what I love.
I won’t be happy this life.
If there is a next life,
I wish to be an ordinary girl
and no longer be fooled by the powers.
I,
Jiang Luo, a unfilial son,
got carried
away,
ordered my men to attack Duke Jingting
and framed Shi Feixian.
Duke Jingting was suffered
physically and mentally
and Shi Feixian was exiled.
I’m
snaky and deceitful.
I committed towering crimes
and made a fool of myself.
I’m repentant now.
Please punish me
in any way you want
and do not show mercy.
Jiang Luo.
Luo,
you wrote it?
That’s true.
Your Majesty, look.
Here is Luo’s signature.
Jiang Luo
Such a poor handwriting.
Seems you’re a little unconvinced?
Father, I dare not.
Your Majesty, Luo has been sickly
and spoiled by me.
After all, he’s our son.
Please trust him this time.
Fine.
I get older.
My biggest wish is
you could get along with your brother.
When I pass away,
you’d assist your brother
in governing Daye.
Since you promised,
just apologize to Ban Hua in good faith.
Wang De,
arrange a royal banquet tomorrow
and invite the Bans.
Yes.
Still stand there? Take yourself off.
Father, I have a request.
What is it?
Father,
may Shi Feixian come back?
Stop.
You bastard!
Father, as long as Feixian comes back,
I will never be disobedient to you.
Even if
let me assist my brother.
You, get out!
Get out of here.
Father.
Get out.
The physician said
the girl is not in danger of life.
She’s just in lethargy.
I’ll pay you every month.
Hope you could
look after the girl.
Thank you.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take good care of her.
Thanks.
Your Highness.
The robbers have been captured,
but one of them ran away.
Find him immediately.
Before that,
arrange two guards here
to protect Miss Shi.
Yes.
Luo,
take my advice.
Everything will be fine
as long as you keep a low profile today.
Mother, how could everything be fine
if Ban Hua is in the capital?
I swear
I’ll expel her from the capital.
There is no time
to be slow-witted!
Your father is always unhappy with you.
This is especially true today.
If you contradict him again,
it’s you
not Ban Hua
who will be expelled.
Mother,
am I really
the biological child of father?
How ridiculous!
Your Highness.
Duke Jingting, please.
Princess Ban, please step inside.
Thank you.
It’s so weird.
Nobody greets me?
Hurry up.
Young Master Ban, please step inside.
Thank you.
Luo, be patient.
You must bear with everything today.
It tastes delicious.
I’ll bring Shunzi a drumstick.
Heng, don’t be rude.
Never mind.
It’s a family feast.
No need to be punctilious.
Luo,
why not propose a toast to your uncle?
Uncle, please take the wine!
I’ll do it myself.
Thank you!
You’re a senior.
Just take it.
My fault for what happened days ago.
Please forgive me.
Cousin Luo, what you said is ambiguous.
What happened days ago?
Forgive you for what?
None of your business. Shut up.
His Majesty said,
no need to be punctilious.
I wanted to figure it out.
Is there a problem?
Am I right, Your Majesty?
You two grow up
together since childhood,
but never stop quarreling.
Now you’re both grownups,
but still childish.
Your Highness, you’re right.
If Cousin Luo could grow up soon
and is not so childish,
I’ll definitely get along with him.
Luo,
go to pour wine for Hua.
Have you forgotten our rules?
Cousin Hua, please take a drink.
I had never been
served by Cousin Luo in my life.
Hua, take it slowly.
It’s a good thing
if they could bury the hatchet.
You two should
get along with each other in the future.
Your Highness, you mean it?
Sure, I mean it.
All right.
It’s a just trifle affair
between kids.
Forget about it.
Don’t take it seriously.
Thanks to your donation,
the disaster is alleviated.
I, on behalf of the disaster victims,
express gratitude to you.
I just did
what an ordinary people could do.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
You didn’t see Jiang Luo’s long face.
when he greeted us.
He was wronged
this time.
He wouldn’t let it go.
You’d better be careful.
I’m not afraid!
As long as His Majesty is around,
what can he do to me?
Moreover, I’m not an idiot,
neither you.
Why should I be afraid of him?
What you did is unexpected indeed.
The chef culprit was punished.
And that’s not going too far.
If he makes trouble again,
let’s work together
to sort him out, okay?
Since you recognize my performance,
how will you thank me?
I walk you home
as a thank-you gift.
Not enough!
Full of tricks.
You’re a gentleman.
A gentleman cannot behave like this.
I’m with you every day.
So I acquired some of your characters.
What do you mean?
You teased me indirectly, right?
I’m praising you.
You’re so clever
that Jiang Luo was tricked.
That’s more like it.
Your Grace, with your wisdom,
if you cheat me,
I would probably never know
and be unable to make out.
Even so,
in front of you,
I’m an open book to you.
Really, never lie to me in my life.
Never.
Young...
Young Master, sorry to interrupt.
-What’s up?
To Princess Fule Ban Hua
A letter from Prince Akeqi,
saying Shi Feixian’s been settled down.
Your Grace may rest assured.
On the eve of Feixian’s confession,
His Majesty met with me
and seemed to ask us
to properly handle this
for Prince Luo.
Qizhou event will not be investigated.
Mr. Shi, if so,
you could be relieved about
the letter written in blood.
For safety, we must make attempts
to get the letter.
Sir, you’re right.
I’ll handle this immediately.
I have news about Miss Shi.
Miss Shi encountered robbers in exile.
When are you going to act?
Shi Feixian was exiled.
How dare you kill her!
You knew my affection to her,
but tried to kill her
under my nose.
Xie Chongjin,
do you really think
I dare not to kill you?
I planned this
for your good.
For my good?
Shi Feixian’s exile to Xizhou
was also for my good.
Xie Chongjin, am I a fool?
You fear that Shi Feixian will be
my empress rather than your sister,
so you took the chance
to get rid of her.
Your Highness,
you’ll wrest with Crown Prince
in the future.
To weaken Crown Prince
will be bound to affect the Shi family.
If Shi Feixian does not
break with her family,
you’ll then have scruples
and be kept in the air.
It’s useless to talk more.
Please give me a chance
to prove my loyalty.
Fine.
I’ll give you another chance.
Bring Shi Feixian back
and my commitment remains unchanged.
If Shi Feixian was injured,
I’ll have your life.
Ten.
Your Grace.
Higher.
Your Grace, a letter
from Count Cheng’an.
A letter from Count Cheng’an.
Must be a love letter.
Stop, sit down!
Which is more important,
playing cards with me
or reading the letter?
Yeah, let’s finish this round.
Come.
Father, let’s take some rest
and allow me to read it first.
Forget it.
Gamble knows no kinship. Your turn.
Eight.
-Father.
-Follow up.
Let’s read it.
I wonder how to write love letters.
You?
Who will take a fancy to you?
Hua, it’s your turn.
Right, show your card.
Hurry up.
Read to me.
This is a love letter.
Grab Hua a cup of tea.
No.
I have two cards left
but you still have seven.
If you win,
I’ll return your letter.
Show your card.
A ten.
No higher ones, right?
Go on.
Three, four, five, six, seven,
eight and nine.
I’m out.
Father, my letter.
I quit. What kind of silly game.
-How can’t you afford to lose.
-I’m out.
On the moor is the creeping grass…
What’s this word?
I know.
On the moor is the creeping grass;
Heavily covered with dew!
Heavily covered with dew?
Dear, what does he want to say?
Wild grass is stretching.
Dew gathered on the grass, sparkling.
Three, four, five, six, and seven.
Sparkling?
One more sentence.
There was a beautiful man;
Lovely, with clear eyes!
Lovely...
Lovely, with clear eyes?
That is to say,
Hua’s as beautiful as Xie Wanyu.
No way.
Hua’s more beautiful than her.
-Exactly.
-You’re too much
I got it.
He asked Hua to a tryst...
We met together accidentally;
And he and I were happy together.
Her Grace is asked to run away with him.
No, it’s not.
Yes, it is.
And he and I were hiding together.
That means Count Cheng’an wanted to
run away with you.
Nonsense.
Full of beans.
He didn’t
mean that.
Run away with you.
Lovely, with clear eyes!
It must not refer to Xie Wanyu.
-It means runaway.
-No.
-Indeed, run away with you.
-Impossible.
-That’s not the point.
-No.
-Hua.
-Run away with you.
Hua.
I’m right.
I learned this poem.
Well, explain it to me.
The first two sentences.
On the moor is the creeping grass;
Heavily covered with dew!
There was a beautiful man;
Lovely, with clear eyes!
The beautiful man is you.
So sensational.
How about
the last two sentences?
That doesn’t mean running away.
Am I right?
Not that point.
These two sentences mean
he would like to
spend the rest of his life with you.
Shunzi, well done.
Your Grace.
Count Cheng’an
expressed his love to you.
For a knowledgeable person,
love is a trouble.
That’s true. So complicated.
He must’ve made things difficult.
I’m going to come after him.
You quit the game?
Let’s play more rounds.
Hua.
Your Grace,
what are you doing here?
Hua, I heard from Du Jiu
you’re playing cards with Duke Ban.
I felt bored
so I came here to fly a kite.
Kite?
Your Grace, you made the kite?
I have planned to make it.
But, it’s more difficult
than I imagined.
Well.
Shunzi.
Write what you want to say
to your family on the kite
and fly it to the sky.
Then the family in heaven will know.
Is it true?
Yes.
Shunzi, what do you want to write?
You know?
It’s said that
as long as you fly the kite
with someone,
you two will never be separated
as if tied together by the line.
Is it true?
Yes.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Sir, Zhao Shunzi’s belongings
were searched,
but no letter written in blood
was found.
I felt uneasy
if the letter can’t be found.
Now Zhao Shunzi
becomes my biggest concern.
You mean we should
kill him for safety?
Do it quickly and clearly,
but,
do not let them get anything on us.
Yes.
Greetings, Mr. Xie.
Count Cheng’an.
You shouldn’t be here.
It’s against the rules.
Who exactly killed Mr. Rong?
This way.
Kill Mr. Rong and reward 300 tales.
From Wu, the Shis’ assistant.
Kill Mr. Rong
and reward 300 tales.
From Wu, the Shis’ assistant.
I got it, thank you.
Ban’s Mansion
Your Grace.
Why did the Shi family
kill Mr. Rong?
This probably
relates to the death of my parents.
Since I could remember,
I’ve investigated the past of my family.
Now, I’m close to the truth,
but Uncle Rong was killed.
Hua,
if I continue investigating,
you’ll probably be hurt.
Your Grace, don’t say so.
Everyone knows
I’m the most tough man in Daye.
No one dares to mess up with me.
So,
don’t worry about me.
But when investigating the case,
you need to be careful
and make me rest assured.
Okay?
Thank you, Hua.
Mr. Xie, they say
Count Cheng’an left Fude House,
and went to the Ban’s Mansion.
Till now, he is still there.
Hero becomes a prisoner.
Seems what we’ve done
still fails to urge Count Cheng’an
to make up his mind.
Sir, tell us your scheme.
We’ll follow your order.
The kid is still in the Ban’s Mansion,
right?
Yes, he is.
He’s kept an eye on by the Ban family.
If
Shi Chonghai
knows Zhao Shunzi will be summoned
to the Royal Palace soon.
Could he be patient anymore?
Brilliant scheme.
If Zhao Shunzi died,
Ban Hua will surely
take revenge on the Shi’s family.
Then, we will profit from their fight.
You can’t say that.
I just told the truth
to the one who should’ve known.
There is no profit.
Find a way to
get Zhao Shunzi out of the Ban’s Mansion
and provide a chance for Shi Chonghai.
Recently,
Zhao Shunzi always flies a kite
in the garden in the afternoon.
If the kite flies out,
there’ll be trouble.
Sir.
Sir, bad news.
An informant said,
Princess Ban will take Zhao Shunzi
to meet with His Majesty.
Sir.
Zhao Shunzi can’t meet with His Majesty.
Do something about it.
We must kill him!
-Yes.
Shunzi misses you.
Shunzi
Is it interesting
to fly a kite every day?
Heng, it’s full of fun.
Okay.
Let’s do some shopping after meal.
Great.
I’ll call you later.
Shunzi misses you.
Shunzi, it’s lunch time.
Where’s he heading?
What’s up?
I’ve no idea where Shunzi’s going.
Let’s look for him separately.
Shunzi!
Shunzi! Shunzi!
It’s mine.
Could you return it to me?
Shunzi. Let’s go to eat.
Shunzi!
-Shunzi!
-Hua!
Shunzi!
I’ll make Shi Chonghai
pay with his life.
Sky-holding Gate
The famine is going to be solved.
Everyone, well done.
Your Majesty.
I have a memorial to the throne.
Count Rong, you’re allowed.
Minister Shi failed to
provide disaster relief,
leading to the famine in Qizhou.
Count Cheng’an.
How could you slander me?
You are corrupt
and even hound Official Zhao to death.
Zhao’s death is a natural disaster
and destiny.
It has nothing to do with me.
Shi Chonghai,
I had meant to give you the last chance.
But I’ve never expected…
Read it yourself.
You...
Well,
you dare not to read it?
Your Majesty, I’m framed up.
Of 3000kg relief grain,
large portion was pocketed
by Mr. Shi and his party.
Only 900kg were left for Qizhou.
Official of Qizhou bought the post from
the Shis at a price of 380 taels.
But you lied to His Majesty that
the money was used
to purchase relief grain.
Official Zhao refused to resign
so you killed Mr. and Mrs. Zhao
and let him make way
for the new official.
You...You...
Nonsense.
Your Majesty,
I ask for your deliberation.
You utilized a fire to cover up the fact
but never thought
Zhao Shunzi and his grandmother
fled from Qizhou in advance.
You fear that the letter would be
submitted to His Majesty
so you built Charity House
to seduce to all orphans.
All you have done is to
stealthily lead Zhao Shunzi
into a trap.
Charity House.
You… Nonsense.
Jin, don’t trust him.
He’s talking nonsense.
But you didn’t expect
Shunzi’s close to the Bans.
Your plan failed.
You were driven desperate
so you killed him.
Shi Chonghai,
he’s still a kid.
Count Cheng’an, you sling mud at me.
I’m frank and forthright
and never do such evil things.
Your Majesty,
I ask for your deliberation.
Shi Chonghai,
this is the letter written in blood
you’ve been looking for.
Had it not been for your assassination,
we’d never found
the letter in his clothes.
The evidence is conclusive.
Do you want to defend that?
Shi Chonghai,
you’re
a senior official
witnessing my enthronement
and serving three emperors,
and also my in-laws.
How could you be so stupid?
Your Majesty,
I’m guilty.
I’m overcome by a lust for money.
I deserve a death penalty.
Your Majesty,
I gave my all in my life
and never deceived you.
I do not feel ashamed before you
and before Daye.
Not ashamed before Daye?
You think I’ve no idea about
what you’ve done these years?
Given you’ve served three emperors,
I’ve been lenient with you.
But you’re further intensified,
and you killed the innocent,
including a kid.
Pass my order.
Official of Qizhou is sentenced to death
for buying ranks and killing people.
Assistant Wu is sentenced to death
for corruption.
The Shis...
Your Majesty, I beg you.
Show mercy to my grandchildren.
They’re innocent.
I…
I
am the only guilty person.
I give you the last shred of dignity.
Go back home and look at the last light.
Remove Shi Chonghai from office.
Imprison him some other day.
Even Shi Chonghai is cunning,
he cannot escape from my trap.
The Shis fell from power.
Now, Crown Princess
only has Rong Xia.
Congratulations.
Your big day is close.
Where’s Shi Feixian?
Have you found her?
Miss Shi was rescued by Prince of Aipo
after jumping off the cliff.
She’s settled in a farmer’s home
in Guxian County.
Sir.
Are you going to tell her location
to Prince Luo?
If so, everything we’ve done is in vain.
I will tell him.
But
it should be after Shi Feixian’s death.
Answer my question.
She’s a farmer’s home in Guxian County.
Great.
Saddle a horse.
I’m going to pick Xian up
and surprise her.
Tomb of Zhao Shunzi
You still got the nerve to come.
Your Grace.
Because of your family,
Shunzi lost his parents,
his grandmother starved to death
and Shunzi himself was murdered.
Get away.
Shunzi didn’t need your unction.
Shunzi,
I brought you steamed chicken.
You’re still growing.
Tomb of Zhao Shunzi
Eat a little more.
Shunzi,
rest in peace with your parents
and grandmother.
I’m sorry.
I failed to protect you.
Hua, I promise
such thing will not happen again.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪