Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 24
You’re awake, Miss.
Who are you?
Where am I?
Calm down, Miss.
Call me Mrs. Wang. This is my place.
Have a seat.
Sit with me.
Wang Daqiang, bring me some hot water.
You’ve slept for three days and nights.
That long?
Three days ago, someone brought you here
and paid me to look after you.
Who was that?
He didn’t say,
so I have no idea.
Is he a handsome
and scholarly gentleman?
I don’t know about scholarly
but he’s indeed good-looking.
That must be Count Cheng’an.
He couldn’t see me drift to Xizhou.
Here’s water.
Miss,
wash your hands.
I’ll let you know
when the meal is ready.
Thanks for looking after me.
Don’t mention it.
Take it.
Minister, help, Minister!
Minister, Minister!
I’ve been
in this uniform for 40 years.
But I never thought
I would
take it off today.
His Grace
is not coming for the uniform.
Mr. Shi.
His Majesty
granted you a cup of wine.
It seems His Majesty
would never spare me.
Mr. Shi,
please don’t let His Majesty down.
Count Cheng’an,
I’m now a dying man.
I only have one question.
Why did you corner me?
Shi Chonghai, you don’t deserve
to be the minister.
You’ve killed
too many people for your influence.
Shunzi’s family is not
the only innocent one.
Tell me.
Why did you kill Mr. Rong?
He knew too many things.
You are blaming him after killing him.
How can you be so unashamed?
What did Mr. Rong know?
The guilty deeds you’ve done
for Crown Princess
or the lives
threatened by you?
It seems Prime Minister Yan
has given me away.
I did have the selfish idea!
May I ask you one thing?
You’ve investigated
into the Rong’s case. Any idea?
Why was it uneventful in the court when
two important officials were killed?
Young Master, don’t listen to him!
He’s shifting the blame.
No matter what I guess,
it can’t be better than the cruel you
telling the truth!
Your Grace! You are thinking much of me.
In that case,
I was just consumed by others.
I did a thing right for that moment.
Well!
I
am going to die now.
Since Your Grace
want to know the truth,
I will tell you everything.
It’s because
Old General Ban lost the Tiger Tally.
After His Majesty ascended the throne,
he tried to get Tiger Tally but failed.
His Majesty was upset about it.
So Yan Hui gave an advice,
asking the Old General Ban
for Tiger Tally with your father’s help.
We can’t find it even with Rong’s help.
It seems the Tiger Tally is really lost.
Your Majesty!
I don’t think
Mr. Rong’s words
are believable.
I believe Rong wouldn’t lie to me.
Your Majesty!
Mr. Rong is on good terms with Mr. Ban.
I’m afraid
Mr. Rong will lose his head
for the moment
and cheats you with the Bans.
It’s not possible!
Your Majesty! Tiger Tally matters a lot.
Any carelessness
may endanger your power.
If you keep being softhearted…
Mr. Yan, no more talk.
Mr. Yan.
What are you doing?
This is the only way
to break through the two families
and to get the Tiger Tally.
Mr. Yan.
Mr. Ban and Mr. Rong
are important officials of Daye.
You can’t do that!
Mr. Xie.
You want to be my enemy?
I… Uh!
Mr. Yan.
Why did you ask Mr. Xie
and me to come
in such a hurry?
Mr. Shi.
The wine is from the Western Regions.
At the behest of His Majesty,
please take it to Rong’s Mansion.
Your Majesty!
Mr. Rong died.
What? Why?
Your Majesty! I did that.
Yan Hui! How dare you
kill Rong without my knowledge?
Your Majesty!
I did that to find out the Tiger Tally.
You killed Rong.
Then where is the Tiger Tally?
My men have searched the whole mansion,
but we didn’t find it.
In my opinion,
the Tiger Tally is still in
Princess Royal’s hands
since it’s not in Rong’s Mansion.
What are you going to do?
Aunt is like my mother.
If you dare to act wildly,
I won’t spare you.
Your Majesty. It’s my own idea
but has nothing to do with you.
I’d like to bear
all blame of others for Your Majesty!
Please agree!
Your Highness, hold on!
It’s poisonous! You can’t eat it.
His Majesty wants to kill me!
It’s Yan Hui’s plot.
He did that for the Tiger Tally.
Bastard!
How dare he confuse His Majesty!
I will see His Majesty!
I will teach this evil guy a lesson.
Your Highness, please hold on.
Yan Hui is insidious.
He already killed Mr. Rong.
If you go now hastily,
I’m afraid it’ll be bad for you!
You mean Mr. Rong didn’t die of illness?
Say it!
Yes.
Mr. Rong was poisoned to death
after drinking the wine
from the Western Regions.
My husband was poisoned by accident.
Now Mr. Rong…
Two important officials
were sacrificed for the Tiger Tally.
Yes.
It seems His Majesty won’t let go
if he can’t get the Tiger Tally.
If you have the Tiger Tally,
you’d give it out to save your life.
Do you mean I deceived His Majesty?
No. No. No.
If I know where the Tiger Tally is,
how could I let my husband
and Mr. Rong suffer all that?
I will see His Majesty.
Your Highness!
Please save Mrs. Rong
and Younger Master.
Say it!
Make it clear!
What’s wrong with them?
They are fine now.
But Elder Master…
He died!
Your Highness.
Her Highness and I discussed about it
and arranged you to enter the Palace
as Crown Prince’s study partner,
so that you can become friends
to protect you,
the last one of your family.
I didn’t kill them.
But they died because of me.
Shi Chonghai.
Do you think your crimes
can be covered up by hiding them?
I’ve traced the truth for years.
How couldn’t I know you were in Imperial
Study while Yan Hui was giving
the advice.
The one outside was Count Xie.
You pretended to save Princess Royal
for the whereabouts of the Tiger Tally.
His Majesty and Mr. Rong were friends.
I didn’t expect Yan Hui
to be so bold.
It’s not that you didn’t expect.
You were just greedy!
Yan Hui promised to help your
granddaughter be the Crown Princess.
Yan Hui really betrayed me.
Mr. Rong.
General Ban.
I’m sorry.
Please wait.
I…
I’m coming to meet you now.
Shi Chonghai.
You are not qualified to meet them.
Young Master will never do things like
giving others the poisonous wine.
Count Cheng’an.
You always have good plans.
But you can never win His Majesty!
Have you ever thought
about the reason
why nobody
dare to talk about the old story,
why His Majesty still use
Yan Hui and me?
If the Tiger Tally can’t be found out,
the tragedy will continue.
Shi Chonghai.
How could you let the Shi family
become like this?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Xia, don’t cry.
Your parents will bless you!
I will take care of you from today on.
You are a man.
No more cry!
Will you help Crown Prince slacken?
Do you still feel painful?
It’s impossible.
I feel more painful in my heart.
Young Master.
Please don’t drink more.
You will be drunk.
What if I know the truth?
My brother,
father and mother.
They won’t come back to life.
Ban’s Mansion
Your Grace.
How could you be so drunk?
Hua.
I don’t have families anymore
from now on.
Nonsense!
I’m your family, right?
Yes.
You are right.
I still have you.
If you ignore me too,
I will have nobody to rely on.
Don’t talk the silly words.
I will never ignore you.
That’ll be good.
♪Got drunk in the rainy autumn night♪
♪Haven’t fallen asleep with tears shed♪
♪With light eyebrows, she looks nice♪
♪The makeup cannot be hidden♪
♪The moon shines into the window♪
♪Fall in deep love♪
♪Sing the song gently♪
No matter what is bothering you,
I hope
you can tell me frankly
so that I can help.
♪The beauty crying in an empty building♪
♪Who are you worrying about♪
Hua.
Don’t leave.
♪Calling her and missing her
in lifetime♪
I won’t leave.
Hua.
Young Master Ban.
Why did I sleep here?
How dare you say that?
You’ve been so clinging last night.
I wanted to leave for times,
but you just didn’t let me go.
Ouch!
Why did I do that?
How could I know?
I’m so sorry.
Please forgive me!
It doesn’t matter for me.
But you are so clinging
before marrying my sister.
It would be bad for your fame, right?
Luckily,
I passed by your room last night
and saved your fame.
Thank you.
May I ask
if I offended Hua last night?
Don’t you remember it?
No idea.
What to do?
That kind of thing happened last night.
But you don’t remember it.
Uh.
Did I do something to you
last night?
Don’t worry.
I will be responsible for you.
Oh my God!
Uh.
Count Cheng’an came
for Her Grace last night.
Really?
How about Mr. Du?
He didn’t come.
Why did you care about Mr. Du so much?
I didn’t.
I’m worrying it’s impolite for
His Grace to be with Her Grace alone.
I heard Count Cheng’an was so drunk.
I’m afraid even Du Jiu couldn’t stop it.
What makes you so happy?
Can you tell it to us?
Your Grace, My Lady. Nothing.
The gossip about Count Cheng’an and me?
Yeah.
You silly girl! Why did you admit it?
You don’t need to gossip.
His Grace was drunk
so he came for me to talk.
They are going to marry soon.
Is that so strange?
Yes. Yes.
We are worrying
that others may gossip
about it
and it will make you unhappy.
Yes. Yes.
Enough. Go get some tea.
His Grace can have it after he wakes up.
OK. I will do it right now.
Anyway,
I feel there’s something
that His Grace can’t let it go.
Otherwise, he wouldn’t drink that much.
You should
comfort him when you are free.
Got it.
I’ve taken you in for days.
It’s time for you to pay me back.
What do you want?
Don’t scream!
Wanna run away?
Get up!
Let go of me.
Let me go!
You!
You bitch!
-Mrs. Wang!
-How dare you seduce my husband?
All women from the city are bad.
I take you in
but you seduce my husband.
Wang Daqiang.
It’s just a few days.
How could you do such a thing?
She seduced me first.
Are you crazy?
That’s our tool for money.
Darling, listen to me.
Bullshit!
The woman seduced me first!
Shucks!
Darling! What’s that smell?
Is it on fire?
It’s smoking.
-Open the door!
-Anybody out there?
Please open the door!
-Help!
-Open the door!
-Anybody there?
-Anybody there? Open the door.
Help!
Open the door!
Open the door. Anybody there?
Help!
Feixian.
I’m here to save you.
Why didn’t you wait for me?
Why?
Your Grace. Young Master
pretends not to concern about it,
but he still can’t let it go.
It can’t go like this.
Your Grace, please find a way.
Your Grace.
Hua.
Mr. Du
just told me that you went for
Shi Chonghai that day.
Du Jiu
shouldn’t have told you that.
I can understand.
You don’t want me to get involved.
But it’s a great event.
You shouldn’t have suffered that alone.
We are family now.
Shouldn’t you discuss with me?
Discuss?
So you will also go for His Majesty?
Maybe
His Majesty had no other choice
for the situation at that time.
Why did you speak for him?
It’s not just my family.
Old General Ban also died for that.
Princess Royal knew His Majesty well.
So she hid the Tiger Tally at pains
and gave it to me
till she was critically ill.
Do you think
Princess Royal was wrong?
I didn’t speak for His Majesty.
But we can’t trust Minister Shi.
What if
he misled you on purpose?
I’ve thought about all that.
But what Shi Chonghai said
is the same as your grandma’s words.
It’s just because I know everything.
I can’t do anything right now.
Because
I promised Princess Royal I’ll protect
you and your family.
My mother also wanted me to live well
without thinking about family hatred.
But once I think that
he looks so fatherly
but he might kill my family,
I just can’t bear it.
I don’t know what to do either.
Because you
still have your parents,
and your brother.
But I
am alone.
You are not alone.
You have me.
We’re together no matter what happens.
It’s lucky to meet you.
I hope you can cherish the fate
like me.
You are upset today.
I will come next time.
Shi’s Mansion
Sealed in the fourth month
of the 23rd year of Yunqing reign, Daye
The first family in the capital
Sealed in the fourth month
of the 23rd year of Yunqing reign, Daye
became like this.
I can’t believe
Shi’s Mansion
there is no place for me in the capital.
Practice harder.
You didn’t make a great progress.
Anyway, practice makes perfect.
Two more hours per day.
It’ll be eight hours.
Yes.
Except sleeping,
you have eight hours for other things.
Rocky.
Do we have ginseng and chicken?
The cook did buy some chicken today
for steamed chicken with scallion oil.
For ginseng,
we always have a lot.
Your Grace, do you want chicken soup?
It’s not me.
I want to make some for His Grace.
Hua, please don’t.
You’ve made a lot of strange food.
It’s OK for me.
But His Grace is weak.
He can’t stand that.
I’ve said
practice makes perfect.
Yes.
I’m not good at cooking.
But I can practice more.
His Grace has grown up alone.
I’ll be his wife.
So I should learn more things
so that he can feel the warmth.
The cook can do that.
Why yourself?
To show my sincerity.
What about my steamed chicken?
Have it tomorrow.
Practice hard.
Watch him.
Come on. Practice.
Practice. Practice.
Count Cheng’an. I’ve tried my best.
Amrita Jewel
Your Highness. What do you mean?
Did you set the fire?
Your Highness. I don’t understand.
I’m asking you again.
Did you burn Shi Feixian to death?
Shi Feixian was burned to death?
Really?
Don’t pretend.
For the sake of your sister,
you want Shi Feixian to die very much.
I don’t know
why you think so.
But I won’t do that silly thing
in this kind of situation
even if I am really stupid.
Then what else would it be?
If you insist
I killed Shi Feixian,
you can kill me.
But I have to remind you
nobody else
can help you get the throne.
If I don’t know it, you are dead now.
Prince Luo. Daye’s full of beauties.
Please look at the big picture.
What should I do now?
Count Cheng’an defeated Shi Chonghai.
It’s the weakest time for Crown Prince.
You should defeat Count Cheng’an now.
Then Crown Prince has nobody to use.
Defeating Count Cheng’an?
Who can do that?
His Majesty.
His Majesty?
Rong’s Mansion
Your Grace, what brings you here?
His Grace looks gaunt recently.
So I made ginseng chicken soup for him
to tonify Qi.
Young Master is in the study room.
Please come with me.
No, thanks.
Let him take a break peacefully.
Your Grace, you’ve already been here.
Why don’t you get in?
Yes. Get in please.
If you are not in there,
I’m afraid he will let you down.
Your Grace,
maybe you can get in for him.
Your Grace, come on.
Try the chicken soup I made.
I did that for the first time.
I don’t know how it is.
Here you are.
Hua, last time…
You didn’t feel well.
I didn’t put it in mind.
You made the soup for me?
I will surely have a try.
Mr. Du, will you try some?
It should be only for His Grace.
How is it?
Hua,
you made the soup for the first time.
But it’s so tasty.
Really?
This is all for you.
Drink it all.
It’s about too much.
Let me help you.
No.
You made that for me.
I won’t let you down.
Have some meat too.
I can’t believe
I’m so talented in cooking.
Since it’s delicious,
I will make more for you tomorrow.
Banished Immortal Yard
Some wolfberries.
Hua, there must be a use for my talent.
Like the saying goes…
Dad, please stop.
Don’t beat around the bush!
Hua, don’t make chicken soup again.
It really tastes bad.
Yes.
It’s impossible.
His Grace had it all and praised me.
You can have it yourself.
So bitter?
Count Cheng’an didn’t say anything
and had it all.
He even didn’t let me help.
Don’t you understand that?
He loves you from his heart.
So he didn’t tell you the truth
but taking them all.
Is that so?
So it means our Count
loves me very much.
No.
I will practice my cooking skill.
Please don’t.
It’s really hard for Count Cheng’an.
Xie Wanyu is the one good at cooking.
How do you know that?
That’s not the point.
The point is my brother-in-law.
What was wrong with him?
No big deal.
We’ve talked about it.
He thought of something before
and missed his family.
So he got himself drunk.
Then he missed me and…
Why did he drink alone?
Tell him
I will drink with him in the future.
OK.
I will tell him next time.
You’re excited on talking about liquor.
Who is that?
Feixian…
Your Highness.
Feixian, it’s really you.
Did you get hurt?
I’m alright.
It’s too dark here.
I lost my nerve,
so I disturbed Your Highness.
Please don’t blame me.
It’s OK.
It’s really great
to meet you here.
I thought you’ve been burned to death.
Did you look for me?
Yes.
I saw the ruins and the charred body
when I arrived there.
By the way,
I got your hairpin.
It’s great.
Your Highness,
you care about me so much.
I don’t know how to thank you.
Feixian, I’m sorry
for making you upset by the unkindness.
How about
going back with me to the yard?
Thank you, Your Highness.
But I’m guilty.
I don’t want to bring you trouble.
Feixian.
It’s lucky for me
to meet you here.
I don’t want to lose you anymore.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪