Why did you do it?
Why did you kill him?
Hwa Sun.
Sung Bum.
Don't do this. This isn't like you.
Well done.
(Dark Hole)
(Episode 2)
(Sessak Foundation Scholarship Selection)
Next year, reduce the number to five.
Pardon?
We're giving out too many scholarships.
If anyone can get it,
how is that a scholarship?
You're right.
It must be a special thing if the recipient is to be grateful.
Director Choi.
I'll brief you on the procedure of the scholarship awarding ceremony.
- First... - Leave it.
We do the same thing every year. I know the order by heart.
Director Choi, you truly are remarkable.
If that's all, you can leave, Mr. Choi.
There is one more thing I'd like to run by you.
Mr. Choi.
I said we'll discuss that later.
What is it?
Well, it's about...
I asked you before that we treat our school janitors...
Mr. Choi.
Your job is to teach the kids well!
I'm the one who runs the school.
Do you understand?
I do.
Mr. Choi. You're excused.
What a mess.
He's so soft and weak.
Oh, dear...
My gosh. This is crazy.
Officer Park. This is a sinkhole, isn't it?
It should be on the Guinness Book of Records.
As if!
I'll take a selfie.
(Police)
Hey! What was that for?
What? What?
You pushed me. Be honest!
Why would I push you?
Darn it. I can't see the bottom.
All of this is the director's land, and it might end up worth nothing.
What director?
You don't need to know.
I must've left it in the car to charge.
Will you stop taking photos?
Barricade this place with tape so that no one can come in here.
What?
All by myself?
Just do what you're told.
Okay, sir.
Who is this?
Sir, this is Park Soon Il.
We have a problem.
We found a big hole at the place...
where you plan to build a sanatorium.
A hole? What hole?
Well...
It's a pretty big hole.
What are you talking about?
Why is there a hole suddenly in the middle of the mountain?
Well, I think it's a sinkhole.
A sink... A sinkhole?
Do you know how much money got invested in that land?
No matter how much is needed...
gather people and fill up that hole by today.
If you don't want to get fired, you'd better get it done.
Okay, sir. I'll deal with it.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
How am I going to fill this hole up?
Hey, this is upside down! Do it properly!
Who are you?
What's your deal?
You're fine.
Why do you keep pointing a gun at me? You're a cop.
Don't you remember?
You almost killed me up in that mountain.
Well done.
You're okay, right?
Hey, wait.
What did you see in that hole?
Tell me.
My friend's eyes turned black like yours and he went weird.
You must know something.
- Sung Bum. - Don't do this.
This isn't like you.
Hello?
Hwa Sun, I just found CCTV footage...
of Lee Soo Yeon's car that was taken a month ago.
It was taken in front of Jingan Tunnel in Muji City.
I'll send you the footage right away.
Jingan Tunnel?
Thanks.
I'm sorry. I didn't see anything.
I'll be off now.
Hey, wait.
It'll take you three hours to get to that tunnel on foot.
Get in.
- Hello. - Hello.
Don't run.
Sir, what are you doing?
I'm taking a look because they say this door won't lock.
I think this needs to be replaced.
I see. Do you need to replace the whole thing?
Yes, it seems like it's totally broken.
I don't think this will do.
Hey, Dong Rim.
What happened?
It's nothing.
It's obviously not nothing.
You should go to the nurse's office.
I'll go later.
I'm teaching your next class, so you can just go.
Guys, it's time for class now.
Do you know what number to call?
What number?
The number to a counselling center or a welfare center.
(A call for help for teenagers)
It's useless to stay quiet alone.
No one will know unless you speak out first.
(911 Ambulance)
Sir. Sir.
Sir.
How is his condition?
He suddenly threw up and started having seizures.
Sir, can you hear me?
Let's take him inside.
Gosh. Hello?
Hey, Mr. Lim.
Director Choi gave me orders.
I need the hole filled up by today.
How many times do I need to tell you?
We don't have the equipment right now.
Do you not get what's going on?
If you get on his bad side, you won't be able to do business.
We need to fill it up by today.
If we don't, we'll both lose our jobs.
Okay, fine. I'll bring out the tools tonight.
What? Okay, okay.
And make sure not to tell anyone. Do you understand?
Gosh, this punk. I was going to hang up first.
Do you want me to give you what you want?
Do you want it?
Tell me.
Do you want it or not?
Come.
Come to me.
Those who refuse to accept me will all die.
"Those who refuse to accept me will all die."
Those who refuse to accept me...
will all die.
What?
- Sir. - My gosh.
Gosh, you startled me.
You are loved by the skies, sir.
(Repent for paradise is near you. Get ready to greet the skies.)
Hey, I'm busy right now.
Get lost.
The revelation of the skies will soon begin.
It's not too late to...
What are you saying, you cultist? Stop ruining my day.
Hey, Han Dong Rim!
Hey, hey.
I waited ages for you.
Let's talk.
It's not about business.
I just want to chat, person to person.
I found an interesting video of you.
What are you looking at?
- Raise your head, Dong Rim. - Come on.
Is this a joke to you? Hey.
You don't want your grandma to see this, do you?
What do you want from me?
Don't be so cold.
I just want to show you something cool.
Hop on.
Every time I'm here, it reminds me of when I got kicked out of school.
It feels annoying.
Let's go.
Come on.
- Walk faster. - Stop it.
- What's wrong? - Faster.
- Jin Seok. Hey. - Are you out of your mind?
Where are we going?
Do you know what a sinkhole is?
It's the deep thing on the ground, right?
It's called a hole, stupid.
- It's the same thing anyway. - Gosh, so stupid.
It's not funny.
Anyway, what about it?
There's one up here.
Really? That's so cool.
Hold on. Are you serious?
You brought us all here just for a hole in the ground?
What? You're not interested?
Then go to work and fry chickens instead.
Come on. Don't be like that.
You know how much I hate chickens.
- Let's go see it. - Let's go.
Come. Let's go.
Hey.
Is this fun for you? What are you staring at?
Hey. Don't you think something's down there?
- Hey! - Gosh.
- Were you scared? - No. I wasn't scared at all.
Should we see what's down there?
- Dong Rim. - Dong Rim.
What?
What are you doing?
These guys' phones are new.
Let me borrow it, okay?
(I've never seen the inside of a sinkhole before.)
(It's so dark.)
Gosh, it's super deep.
What is this? There's nothing in there.
It's boring.
How far down is it going?
Wait. What's wrong?
Gosh. Hey, can't you do better?
What? I didn't do anything.
The screen turned black, punk.
I'm just holding the tape.
What's going on? It feels like someone is pulling the tape.
Gosh, let me try. Pull.
Gosh. Darn it.
What is this?
- Gosh. - What just happened?
It really felt like someone was pulling the tape.
What are you talking about?
Do you think there's a monster in there or something?
Why are you such a coward?
Gosh. Seriously.
Gosh, I'm sorry. You don't even have parents to buy you a new phone.
Why would you apologize?
It's her phone's fault.
It's her phone that fell by itself!
Hey. You go in there and get it.
- Come on. - Are you ignoring me?
- Come on. - Go and get it.
- Let go of me. - Go and get your phone.
Let go!
Are you okay?
Are you out of your mind?
Hey, why didn't you hold her properly?
Gosh, how can you be so strong when you're so tiny?
Will you come to your senses if I break your bone?
Hey, do you have a death wish?
Are you out of your mind? Are you?
What are you looking at?
- What's that? - What's going on?
Hey. Are you okay?
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
- I'll kill you all! - Let go!
I'll kill you!
Don't look at me like that!
Die!
Die! I want you to die!
I'll kill you! Die!
Die!
Die! I'll kill you all!
Mom.
Don't go.
No way.
Push!
Push harder!
Harder!
What am I doing in the middle of the night?
Where are you?
We don't have much time. Hurry up.
Come on. I can't even see anything.
Will you take responsibility if I have an accident?
Cut it out.
If I lose my job, you will too. Don't you know that?
That's really not okay.
Whatever. I should just get it over with.
(Tunnel ahead)
The clip is a month old.
The car belongs to a woman in her 20s.
She's still missing.
The car enters the tunnel but doesn't come out.
I think it went out through a door in the middle of the tunnel.
Hwa Sun.
Sister.
Lee Soo Yeon!
Over here.
I'm over here.
Sister.
Black eyes.
Sung Bum.
Don't go.
Wake up, please.
You're in the hole again.
Get out of there.
You can't go in too deep.
There's no wi-Fi here.
I can't look up why your eyes turned black.
Did you eat something weird in the mountain?
My friend's eyes turned black like yours.
My eyes turned black?
Yes.
They're normal now.
It's so frustrating. I can't show you.
I don't know why,
but I see things out of the blue.
You see things?
Young Sik too...
Tae Han, my father is here.
Your father passed away long ago. Pull yourself together.
My father. He's here.
Nurse!
I think he said he saw his dead father.
What did you see?
Lee Soo Yeon.
I saw the serial killer who murdered my husband.
Like the day she killed my husband,
she put a white cover over his head...
and injected him in the neck.
So...
did you catch that Lee Soo Yeon?
No.
I came here to Muji to catch her.
Earlier, in the mountain,
after I passed out on seeing the huge sinkhole,
I think I started seeing things.
Why did you do it?
Why did you kill him?
You should go to a hospital first.
It's on the way to town.
The general hospital.
- Oh, dear. - What happened?
- That scared me. - Goodness.
- Darn it. - My gosh.
- What are we doing? - You moron!
You just put out a whole row of lights!
I said it's dangerous to work at night!
Darn you!
Darn me?
What happened?
Darn it.
You idiots! Is this the best you can do?
Did I or did I not say it's dangerous to work at night?
- Darn you! - What are you staring at, punk?
- You... - Don't do it.
- Come on. Hit me. - Calm down.
- Please, don't. - Let me go!
- You fool. - Come at me. I'll take you on.
What happened?
Mister! Can you do something?
- We're stuck! - Mister.
You're in the way.
There's nothing wrong here too.
Hey, mister.
What are you doing? Is this a joke?
Sorry. We're trying to figure out what the problem is.
- Give me a little more time. - I can't.
What's this now?
Is it a text message?
- Oh, dear. - What does this mean?
(Muji City Dong-Gu: Emergency, Black-out caused by utility pole)
Dong-Gu?
Mom's hospital is in Dong-Gu.
Why is there a blackout?
Did it really blow up?
What do you mean?
Don't you watch the news?
The sun exploded.
- Isn't that Dong Rim? - Who? Dong Rim?
I apologize, Director.
Yes. Of course.
I'll sort it out fast.
Sure.
Hey! Will you work faster?
You don't dare talk back to that old man.
Don't you take it out on us.
What?
Why? Am I wrong?
Do you want to fight me?
- Shall we fight, then? Shall we? - Darn you!
- How dare you? - Don't.
Wait, stop, stop! Let go!
- What are you faking this time? - No, wait.
What's that?
What is that?
- Is that a fire? - Is it a person?
- What's that? - What is this?
What is this?
What's happening?
- Stop her! - Get her off me!
Hey! What is that?
What's going on?
What are you doing?
Help!
Help! Help!
Excuse me!
What's going on?
Gosh, is there something going on outside?
I need to meet someone for dinner.
You're drinking again?
I don't want to end up conducting an autopsy on you.
Hey, how do you know if you'll be doing an autopsy on me?
You might die before me.
My cell phone doesn't work either.
- Try using the intercom. - Got it.
(Authorized personnel only)
Hello, I'm calling from the autopsy room.
Is there something going on outside?
(Mom, when are you coming home?)
Mom?
Please go inside. Be careful.
Hey, sweetheart. It's me, your mother.
Let me inside.
Mom?
- Don't run. Be careful. - Okay.
Can you help him first? Doctor, please.
He's bleeding.
(11 Missing Calls)
(When are you coming, Mom?)
Oh, dear.
(Mom, Incoming video call)
(Mom)
Hey, Do Yoon.
Something came up at the hospital. I'm going to be late today.
I'll be home as soon as I'm done. Just sit tight and wait.
Mom, are you...
not in front of our house?
What? No, I'm still at the hospital.
Do Yoon, what's going on?
Do Yoon, can't you hear me? Jung Do Yoon!
What the...
My baby. Come here, my baby.
Come here!
Do Yoon. Do Yoon!
Do Yoon!
- Come this way! - This way!
Over here!
Just a second!
Come this way!
This place is a mess too.
My gosh.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Sir.
Are... Are you okay?
What are you looking at? I asked you what you're looking at.
I'll gouge your eyes out!
That man...
I'll gouge your eyes out.
That's what I'll do.
I saw him in the mountain.
- What? - His eyes were black just like now.
What... Hey.
Sir! Sir...
Sir, please...
Sir...
What are you doing?
I'll gouge your eyes out.
Sir, what...
Don't move!
(Emergency Room Nurse, Byun Ji Hyun)
I told you not to stare at me.
I'll gouge your eyes out.
I'll gouge your eyes out!
Stop!
His eyes and blood are both black.
He's not human.
How is this even possible?
Detective, please help me.
I think something happened to my daughter.
That woman also had black eyes just like him.
Detective, please help.
Okay. Let's go together.
Thank you.
I'll bring my car right now.
My father is here.
What will you do?
I should go look for my friend.
Wait.
Something might happen again,
so be careful.
Thank you.
You should also be careful as well.
Okay.
Wait, sir.
What's going on?
Well...
Why did you do it?
For now,
keep the smoke out of the hospital at all costs.
Do you understand?
What? Wait.
(Warm and Trustworthy Police)
(Police)
Hyun Ho.
How many guns do we have?
- What? - How many bullets...
Give me a second. This is kind of hard to explain.
- What are you talking about? - I should calm down.
Park Soon Il, calm down.
Officer Park, open the door.
- I'm sorry. - Open up.
The situation is a little...
- Shouldn't we open the door? - Open up.
- Be quiet. - Let me in.
Gosh. Fine.
Hurry up.
You jerk.
- Do you want to die? - Calm down. Sorry.
- How can you do this to me? - I'm sorry.
I can't believe you.
My phone has no service.
Use your radio and contact...
the Blue House or the Police Agency or something.
- Officer Cho, radio the police. - Pardon?
- Right now! - Okay.
What are you doing? It's dangerous.
Hey, why is it so quiet outside?
Do you see that? They've gone crazy.
- Who are they? - Let me see.
Help!
They're gone.
Officer Cho, get something to barricade the door.
Desks, chairs, or whatever.
Officer Park. Do you think Ji Hye will be okay?
Pull yourself together.
Let's go get some chairs and stuff. Hurry up.
Look for things we can use. Desks, chairs, or whatever.
They can storm in any moment. Get moving.
Hurry up. Get anything.
Mr. Bae. Why are you on the floor?
Mr. Bae. What are you doing?
Mr. Bae.
Hey! Mr. Bae.
Pull yourself together, Mr. Bae.
Fire!
Hyun Ho! Get out!
Bring me anything. Quick.
Barricade the door.
- There you go. - Hurry up.
That's enough. Let's go.
Detective. Will my daughter be okay?
She'll be fine as long as she stays home.
We don't have time. Let's leave the car here.
- What? - She might become one of them.
We should find her before that. Hurry.
Okay.
(Restricted Area)
Young Sik.
Jung Do Yoon.
Do Yoon.
There you are. My baby.
Do Yoon!
Jung Do Yoon!
Do Yoon! Jung Do Yoon!
Mom!
I'm here.
I'll come to you. Do Yoon!
Keep calling me.
Where are you?
Young Sik.
- Young Sik. - What is it, Father?
Are you going to beat me again?
I can't stand it anymore.
Stop beating me.
If you don't stop,
I'll kill you.
Young Sik.
Come to your senses.
I'll kill you!
Snap out of it, you punk!
Do Yoon.
- I'm coming to you. - Mom, where are you?
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
My baby.
Let's go now.
Come.
You jerk.
Get off of my Young Min.
I'm not Young Min.
I'm Do Yoon. I'm Jung Do Yoon.
Young Min.
Come to mommy.
Mommy is sorry.
Get in, now!
Get in. Get in, quick.
Mom!
- Mom! - Detective!
Go! Now!
Mom!
Go!
Do Yoon! Do as the detective says.
You must live.
- Okay? - Mom!
Detective! Drive! Now!
Mom!
Go!
It's dangerous. Hold on tight!
Mom!
Mom.
Mom...
Detective?
Detective!
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm okay.
Let's go.
Kid!
Kid?
If you hear this, come to Muji High School.
- We have a shelter. - The school!
- If you hear this, come over. - The school's this way!
- We have a shelter. - Go to the school!
If you hear this, come to Muji High School.
- Kid! - We have a shelter.
We have a shelter.
If you hear this, come to Muji High School.
The smoke is coming!
(Special thanks to Jung Hae Kyun Ahn Eun Jin, Tak Jae Hoon.)
(Dark Hole)
We must save the people outside.
Our students are out there.
This is an emergency situation.
Do you want us all to die?
Our time of redemption is here!
I understand that we may seem strange.
Why did you take the child?
I saw you. That woman inhaled black smoke too.
If he's infected, we'll all be in danger.
I will never give up.
My gosh. This is crazy.
I think it's a sinkhole.
A sinkhole?
What's that?
What did you see in the hole?
- I saw something in the smoke. - Get a grip.
Black eyes. Black smoke.
We must get out of here.
Get in.
(It will make you go, "Oh".)