(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
(Police Line, Do Not Enter)
Do Yoon! Come to me.
Hwa Sun!
Are you okay?
- Are you hurt? - No.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Do Yoon. Do Yoon, are you all right?
Let's go.
(Safety First)
Stay here.
You're coming back, right?
Yes, I'll be back.
Don't come outside, okay?
Okay.
2 times 1 is 2.
2 times 2 is 4.
2 times 3 is 6.
2 times 4 is 8.
2 times 5 is 10.
2 times 6 is 12.
2 times 7 is 14.
Over here!
Hwa Sun.
Where's Do Yoon?
She's hiding. This way.
Are you okay?
How is this possible?
(Dark Hole)
(A few days ago)
(RIP Kang Sung Bum)
(July 20, 1986 to December 25, 2019)
(Episode 1)
Sung Bum, hang in there.
(Husband)
Hwa Sun.
Sung Bum.
Hwa Sun...
(Husband)
Sung Bum!
Sung Bum.
I'm sorry, Sung Bum.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
(Detective So Jung Hwa)
Hey, Jung Hwa.
Hwa Sun.
It's Lee Soo Yeon.
She's back.
Are you sure she's back?
I think you should check for yourself.
NASA announced that they've observed...
massive sunspots on the Sun's photosphere.
According to NASA,
the current size of the sunspots has reached a critical level...
What if the world really comes to an end?
That'd be great. I won't have to pay off my debt.
Sir, Detective Lee Hwa Sun is here.
Are you serious? What if the captain finds out?
Do you want to get suspended...
and be sent back to a patrol division?
But Hwa Sun deserves to know.
Among all the cops in Korea,
she's the most desperate one to catch the culprit.
Do you think I don't know that?
It's just that her personal feelings could mess up the investigation.
But we can't just...
tell her to sit back and do nothing.
Hey, you're here.
Where's the body?
Over here.
Hey Lee Hwa Sun.
What are you doing here?
Do my orders mean nothing to you?
I need to check for myself if Soo Yeon's really back.
You want to check? And do what?
I told you to put your personal feelings aside.
This is already the eighth victim.
Even my husband died.
How do you expect me to ignore this?
Captain, let me catch the culprit.
Are you kidding me?
Sir, she came all the way here, so why don't you let her...
Seriously?
Sorry, sir.
I just visited my husband's grave.
You're right. I'm angry right now.
But it's not because I want personal revenge.
It's because I feel obligated to solve this case as a detective.
Fine.
But this is your last chance. Keep that in mind.
Okay, sir.
Come this way.
Hwa Sun, are you okay?
Hey, let's eat together.
(Muji Metropolitan City)
You promised to buy me black bean noodles.
You made me starve all day...
just to eat this?
Hey, no one obeys the traffic rules when driving a tow truck.
Get to your senses, you punk.
Watch how you talk to your boss.
Boss, my foot.
I don't care if it's illegal.
We really need a police radio.
I at least need to earn enough to pay for my phone bills.
Gosh, that smells nice.
An SUV rolled over right by the underpass.
There are additional vehicles that were involved in the crash.
Please get to the scene quickly.
- Let's go. - What...
Gosh, that's hot! I spilled everything!
How can you be so selfish?
The people at NASA are keeping their eyes on the sunspots.
Recently, the sunspots have been...
causing small explosions, but the recent explosion was big...
Hyun Ho, what are you doing?
An accident just occurred right by the underpass.
Oh, right.
I'll start the car.
A malfunction in the communications equipment...
Take your time. Don't get flustered.
The electromagnetic waves from Earth...
- may travel into space... - The world is about to end.
- from different electric devices... - I'll see you.
- and get exposed to the particles, - Okay, bye.
which will then cause communication disruptions.
Goodness, Officer Park.
Gosh, what's he doing here?
No wonder I craved kimchi stew today.
I'm surprised to run into you here.
Yes, the kimchi stew here is good. They give you a lot of meat.
Enjoy.
Gosh, why are you leaving so quickly?
Why don't we talk for a bit?
We just got an accident report.
Do you think I'm here just to have some kimchi stew?
Officer Park, are you coming?
Give me a second. I'm talking to this man.
Then let's talk just for one minute, okay?
Do you realize you're already two days late?
Oh, that? It's ready. Don't worry.
It's true.
You said that last time too,
but you were one week late.
I had no choice back then.
The deadline is tomorrow.
If you don't make the payment by tomorrow night,
I'll barge into the police station for the money.
If you don't want to be humiliated,
do as I say.
What? Well, okay.
Who is he?
- An old friend. - What?
It's really nice to see him after all these years.
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
Yes, sir.
(Taehan Towing)
Why did you stop? Step on it!
That's why tow truck drivers are criticized.
My gosh.
Then I'll criticize you first.
You stupid punk! We should go and make money!
Why would you stop here? Are you out of your mind?
Let's go before the other drivers take all the money away from us!
Gosh, you idiot!
(Taehan Towing)
Why did he stop here after speeding all the way?
Hey, what are you doing?
- Oh, my. - My goodness.
- Gyung Min! - Yes?
I saw you run all the red lights.
- Did you make a report? - I did.
Help!
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
Sir, please get me out of here.
An ambulance is on the way. Wait...
I can't breathe. Please.
It's okay. Give me just a second.
Calm down.
Calm down. Take a deep breath.
One, two...
You're doing well. Keep breathing.
Don't panic.
- You're beautiful. - What?
You have a dog? What's the name?
- It's Kongchi. - Kongchi?
How old is Kongchi?
She just turned three.
She must be adorable.
My dog is old and barks all the time.
What's your dog's name?
- My dog? - Yes.
It's Youngsik.
- Are you okay? - Yes, I'm fine.
Tae Han, the car's sparking!
- Tae Han, it's on fire. - It's okay.
It's fine.
Gosh! Tae Han, the car is sparking. Get out of there!
Get off me! Drag me out when I tell you to.
It's okay. I'm almost done. Don't worry.
I'm almost done.
Young Sik!
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
(Emergency Service)
Look at you. You make me proud.
You haven't eaten all day. Don't you need a proper meal?
Do you want to go grab a beer?
No, thanks.
Fine. Enjoy your popcorn, then.
Just a second.
Darn it.
What? What's wrong?
Whose call are you waiting for?
It's not like that.
- A woman? - What do you take me for?
- Is it another weird woman? - She's not weird.
- Name? - Yoon Saet Byeol.
- Is she from here? - She's from Seoul.
- How old is she? - She's 22.
What does she do?
Are you interrogating me?
Hold on.
Your eyes are shaking.
- I bet she's weird. - She's not.
She's an angel. A total angel.
Gosh.
What's this?
Darn it.
- You're a monster. - You're a monster.
Gosh, he looks horrible.
How could you let him come to this school?
He creeps the kids out.
What are you going to do?
He should be transferred to another school or something.
The kids are refusing to go to school because they're scared.
How can you tell me to calm down?
- Look at his face. - Transfer him immediately!
Gosh, he looks hideous.
Stop coming to school from tomorrow.
It's our only yearbook. It's so annoying.
Why can't you take a hint? Get lost right now.
- Stop. - You stink. Get lost!
Please stop.
Hey, stay away from him. You might get infected.
- You jerks, I said, stop! - Stop!
I said, stop, you jerks!
Please! Please stop!
Don't you want to get back at them? Let's kill them all.
Honey.
Don't call me that. I don't think of you as my husband.
What did you just say?
Didn't I tell you to stop looking at me like that?
Put that face away. You're scaring away our customers.
How dare you talk to me like that?
I'll gouge your eyes out today!
You're home. Are you hungry?
Why are you standing there staring?
Go change and get ready to eat.
(Hwa Sun.)
(How have you been?)
(Are you asleep already? You're not, are you?)
(I'm sorry I didn't go to your husband's funeral.)
(Don't you want to see me?)
(I so want to see you.)
(Do you want to know why I killed your husband?)
(Because you and he thought you could change me.)
(I really hated that.)
(So I killed him.)
(Isn't that awesome?)
(LOL)
What if they'd grown with the love and care of parents?
Then they wouldn't have gotten involved in crime,
and they wouldn't have to live here.
I think it's not too late for them.
Like we did for each other,
if we trust and love those kids,
don't you think they can change?
Hwa Sun... Hwa Sun...
(Come over if you want to see me.)
(I'll be waiting.)
(Where Sung Bum proposed to you.)
(LOL)
(Hwa Sun)
You can go ahead.
I got a call.
Okay.
Yes, Hwa Sun.
Jung Hwa, I texted you a number.
Locate the caller right now.
What?
Soo Yeon contacted me.
Don't do this. Leave it to us.
We'll catch her.
No. This is something I must do.
Okay, then.
I'll call as soon as I have it.
Thank you.
Hwa Sun.
Yes?
I know how you feel.
So please catch her.
(Detective So Jung Hwa)
There you are.
Did you think I wouldn't find you if you hid here?
How did you know I was here, Mom?
Mom knows everything.
Do you really? How did you know?
- Do you want to know? - Yes.
I'm so curious, it's driving me crazy.
It was your smell.
Really? Do I smell?
I wash my hair every morning.
Not a bad smell. A really nice smell.
- Really? - Yes.
It's the nicest smell in the world.
Did you finish your homework?
- 7 times 8 is? - 56.
- 9 times 7. - 63.
2 times 2.
Four.
- Jung Do Yoon. - Then do I get chicken?
Chicken?
- Tada. - Yay!
Are you pleased?
Yes. You're the best.
I'm the best?
You're the best too.
Gosh. It looks like it'll pour.
I guess.
I'm worried.
You live 10 minutes away. Why worry?
Not me. My Ji Hye.
What about your wife?
Ji Hye's a scaredy-cat.
She jumps awake at night whenever I fart...
Yes. It must be great to be a newlywed.
Just lovely. It's the best time of your life.
- When is your baby due? - Next Monday.
Then you'll be a dad soon?
A dad?
Are you happy?
Your life as you know is over.
Understand?
My gosh. And you're still happy?
- My goodness. - Go home, sir.
I'll see you. Bye.
Be careful on your way home, sir.
- Officer Park. - What? You startled me.
- About the hair salon lady... - The hair salon?
The woman who's married to the guy who picks medicinal herbs.
What about her? Was she abused again?
No, not exactly.
But apparently, her husband hasn't come home yet.
He won't answer his phone either.
Well, tell her to wait for a bit.
He's probably playing cards somewhere.
I bet he'll show up drunk tomorrow morning.
- I'll see you. - Okay. Go home safely.
- I pray to the skies. - Please.
- My goodness gracious. - What happened?
- What just happened? - What happened?
Ma'am.
- Get off me. - What?
I said get off me!
Gosh, I guess the rumours were true.
Her powers are not as strong as they used to be.
Do you think we'll get a refund?
Of course. We paid a fortune for this.
If they don't give us a refund, I'll report them for fraud.
Hey, excuse me.
We'll be getting a refund, right?
Listen, ma'am.
I'm a freelancer. I'm a contract worker.
I might not even get paid myself.
- My goodness. - What a lousy day.
- My goodness gracious. - What an unlucky day.
- Let's go. - Yes, let's go.
My goodness, seriously.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
Just accept it.
If you don't, it'll kill both you and your mother.
Come in.
The shaman is waiting for you.
Promise me.
If I agree to accept you,
promise me that you'll make me the strongest shaman.
So that no one will ever be able to look down on me.
You promised to protect me.
You promised to protect me forever!
I'll gouge your eyes out.
I'll gouge your eyes out. That's what I'll do.
We're seeing unusual explosions caused by the sunspots.
When the sunspots explode,
it could cause communication disruptions...
and GPS signal errors on Earth.
And high energy particles could cause damage...
to the solar panels on satellites and the power system on Earth.
It could cause blackouts and also paralyse...
all communications and bank systems on Earth.
There's been a hit-and-run accident at Muji Intersection.
The suspect is on the run. We need backup at the cathedral.
They'll never get the suspect.
They should try chasing towards the post office.
(Hwa Sun)
(Morgue)
(Detective So Jung Hwa)
- Hey. - Yes, Hwa Sun.
I found the cell phone owner.
Where is she?
But the thing is, it's not her cell phone.
The name of the owner is Kim Bo Eun.
Kim Bo Eun?
Yes, she's a nurse at Muji Hospital.
Answer your phone.
I don't want to. I'm off duty today.
Come on. You'll get in trouble with Officer Park.
Hello?
What?
Yes. I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
What? Well...
Something bad happened.
In this small town?
I can't tell you.
Stress is bad for the baby.
See you later.
Daddy is leaving. See you.
See you.
Have a nice day.
Look at this crowd.
There's nothing to see! Leave.
Hey, you can't take pictures.
- Hey, take a picture. - Please leave.
I said, leave. What are you all doing here?
Hello, Chief. This is Park Soon Il speaking.
Yes, there's one victim. A woman and a man...
Yes, forensics arrived.
Yes. Okay.
- I see. Yes. - Excuse me.
(Police)
Have you found her eyes yet?
No. Not yet.
- Yes. Okay. - My goodness.
I will. Okay. I understand.
Yes, sir.
Hey, it's getting on my pants.
Gosh, it got on my pants.
I'm sorry.
Officer Cho. Pull yourself together.
You're a police officer.
Officer Park. Why do you think he gouged out his wife's eyes?
How should I know?
Maybe he couldn't stand the sight of her.
What?
You don't have to understand. You just got married.
If we fail to make money again today, I'll quit.
We're late because you had to poop.
I had an upset stomach. What could I do?
How can you be so cold?
You're talkative today, Young Sik.
What's that?
Are you catching boars for Joon Seok for chump change again?
Goodness, that's embarrassing. Stop doing this.
I have to do this to be able to pay you.
- You don't want to get paid? - I want to.
Everything you say is right.
Who cares as long as you can make money?
Go ahead and catch all the boars...
before they ruin the crops.
Hold on.
(Taehan Towing)
It should be around here.
Let's go look for it.
A car broke down in the mountains?
We're not in the position to be picky.
- What's wrong? - My stomach hurts again.
Gosh, it's coming out.
I really should fire him.
Hello?
Yes, it's the tow truck driver.
I think we're almost there...
Hello?
What the heck?
Goodness, this day just keeps getting better and better.
What's this?
What could this be? A meteorite?
Young Sik. Are you done?
Hurry up before you get gored by a boar.
Hey.
Your pants aren't even down.
Did you poop your pants?
Hey.
It's fine.
Tae Han.
Help me.
Hey.
What's wrong with your eyes?
Stay away!
I said, stay away!
Who are you talking to?
Go away!
Hey.
- Go away! - Are you out of your mind?
Young Sik.
Are you okay?
(Muji Hospital)
Out of the way!
Coming through! Sorry!
(Administration)
Are you Detective Lee Hwa Sun?
You're the one who called me, right?
Yes.
I'm Detective Lee Hwa Sun.
Well...
You lost your cell phone lately, right?
That's right.
Is this the one?
Wait. Yes, it is.
How did you...
Do you remember when you lost it?
Well...
I think it was about a week ago.
I was getting off work,
and a woman asked me if she could borrow my phone,
so I lent it to her.
I'm really sorry, but could I borrow your phone for one second?
I forgot mine.
Well, okay.
Here you go.
Mrs. Kim.
You startled me.
Where are you going?
My daughter is a little sick, so I'm leaving early.
Then hurry home.
- I'll get going. - See you.
What?
While I was talking to another nurse,
the woman disappeared with my phone.
Was it this woman?
Well...
I'm not sure.
She did have long, straight hair.
My daughter was sick that day.
I was hurrying home and was a bit distracted.
- Coming through! - Out of the way!
- Coming through! - Coming through!
- Sir, can you hear me? - Let go of me.
His temperature is 43°C.
- Let go of me. - Calm down, sir.
What happened?
He must've eaten something bad in the mountains. He suddenly...
Sir, let me put a respirator on you.
Stay away.
- Sir. Nurse! - I said, stay away.
He's hallucinating and having a seizure.
Call the neurosurgeon.
Yes.
Father. It's all my fault.
Please don't hit me.
Father, please don't hit me.
Don't hit me!
Hey. Calm down. What's wrong?
Tae Han, my father is here.
Your father passed away long ago. Pull yourself together.
My father...
Nurse!
Hey!
Are you okay?
Go away!
Can I check the CCTV footage?
Well...
The cameras here were broken and are being fixed right now.
Father.
Stop him!
Don't hit me.
Don't hit me, Father!
Call the police.
- Don't come closer! Stay away! - What's wrong?
Honey. What just happened?
No... What now?
Don't come closer.
Don't. Don't come any closer.
Why did you suddenly jump into the road?
Don't come closer.
Are you hurt?
Hey!
- Tell him to stay away. - What is wrong with you?
- Are you okay? - Don't come closer.
- Young Sik. Hey! - What happened to him?
- What happened? - Young Sik!
My gosh.
He looked badly hurt.
- How come? - He just ran off.
Did you see that?
Tell me.
What did I do so wrong?
I became your follower so you wouldn't kill my mom.
You tormented me so much.
So why do this now?
Why did you abandon me?
Tell me.
Tell me something!
Young Sik!
Nam Young Sik!
Darn you.
Some lunatic jumped right in front of our truck.
He shoved my husband against the truck and ran off!
I think it's the guy the hospital reported.
Which way did the lunatic go?
To the mountains.
- To the mountains? - Yes.
Shoot. Why go... Thank you.
- Get in the car quick. - Okay.
No, I'll drive!
Excuse me.
Don't you want to kill her?
Get revenge.
Kill her. Kill her right now.
Why hesitate? Shoot.
She killed your husband.
Lee Soo Yeon.
Why did you do it?
Why did you kill him?
(Special thanks to Ahn Eun Jin.)
(Dark Hole)
Do not be afraid. You were chosen by him.
You will meet him soon.
What did you see in the hole?
My friend's eyes turned black like yours and he went weird.
I saw the serial killer who murdered my husband.
Lee Soo Yeon!
Black eyes and black blood. They're not human.
Get in, now!
Mom!
Hwa Sun.