[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Adapted from Qiao Yao's novel]
["It's Easy To Dodge a Gun,
But Hard To Prevent a Crush"]
[Episode 21]
Lu Jing.
You're here.
You're early.
I rushed back
knowing that you would be here.
Don't forget about me.
What's going on with you two?
Taro.
Are you done cooking?
Liang Chen has been starving all day.
Go on.
Get cooking.
This is my house. I'm not your chef.
What were you two talking about?
Jia Yun's birthday is in two days.
Taro and I were discussing
what to give him.
When is his birthday?
It's on the 24th of December.
That's Christmas Eve.
What a coincidence.
Christmas Eve? I forgot about that.
It'll be the first festival
we celebrate as a couple.
But I shouldn't skip
Jia Yun's birthday celebration.
I've promised him.
It's okay. Let me choose the present.
Don't you mind?
We should buy him a present.
Here.
Look at this.
How about this?
That's not suitable.
Let's browse some more.
How about a necktie?
I'm sure he has many ties.
How about cufflinks?
Not good.
What should we get him?
How about this?
A little tortoise.
It has good connotations.
It symbolises health and prosperity.
You're doing this on purpose, aren't you?
It's quite nice. Look, it's so cute.
Scrap that.
How about this?
I think it's fine.
What are you doing?
What is going on?
Can't you tell?
Any hints?
Is it obvious enough?
My goodness.
Am I seeing things?
You two are holding hands!
You're not seeing things.
It's exactly what you think it is.
Don't you have any questions for us?
What should I ask?
You could ask how happy we are.
Taro.
Go and be happy outside.
What should we do?
Do you want to watch a movie?
Sure, it's been a while
since I've watched a movie.
I happen to have a cap in my car.
Let's go watch a movie.
[Give it to me!]
-[No way.]
-[Give it to me!]
[No way!]
I'm a little nervous with all these people
around us.
You're so cute.
What?
Nothing.
The movie has started. Pay attention.
[Why don't I dance for you?]
[Do you like it?]
[Yes.]
[Stop crying, okay?]
[Okay, I'll stop crying.]
Is it funny?
Liu Mao Yan is so cute.
I'm cute too.
Who's complimenting you?
Didn't you say that
I look like Liu Mao Yan?
When you compliment him,
you compliment me.
I'm not complimenting you.
Hello.
[Shan Shan.]
[Can you please persuade Liang Chen]
[to choose my song?]
Ms Ma.
What happened to Liang Chen?
Ms Ma, see what I brought?
Ms Ma, stop ordering takeout.
It's bad for your health.
Here, try the home-cooked meal
I made for you.
It looks much more appetising
than takeout.
Not only am I angel in person,
I'm also a devil in the kitchen.
Look, the colour is so nice.
Enjoy the food.
You said you wanted
to talk about Liang Chen.
What happened to her?
Eat up.
I'll tell you while you eat.
It's a long story.
Then make it short.
Liang Chen is in love.
The love birds are so in love.
I can't take it anymore.
I skipped dinner
because I was so mad at them.
Then, I came to your place.
Is it Jia Yun?
Jia Yun is not Liang Chen's type.
You know Liang Chen so well, Ms Ma.
It must be because you were her classmate.
Ms Ma, actually...
I've been single for a long time.
Ms Ma.
Be honest to me.
What do you think of my appearance?
-You're quite...
-Quite good looking, right?
What are you trying to say?
Look, Ms Ma.
I'm quite good looking.
I can cook.
I have a successful career.
More importantly,
I'm single.
I'm a rare gift.
Ms Ma.
Don't you have
any special feelings for me?
Are you done?
If you're done, please leave.
I...
Please.
Eat more.
If you think that the dishes...
Liu Mao Yan is quite handsome.
I met him once at an event.
He held my skirt and helped me
step down the stage.
I didn't know he was such
a good actor, too.
Do you think...
Are you unhappy?
You didn't enjoy the movie?
I'm not happy.
You complimented another man's looks.
You're good looking too.
He held your skirt and helped
you step down the stage.
But
it's your hand I'm holding right now.
Are you happier now?
I'm happier now.
But I'm still a little sore.
Every other couple will be spending time
together on Christmas Eve,
but I'll be celebrating alone.
It'll be so lonely.
On that day,
I'll leave the party early.
Don't force yourself.
It's your friend's birthday party.
How can you leave early?
Fine.
I'll pick you up.
Let me know when you're done.
You don't have to change your schedule
because of me.
No matter how late it will be,
I don't mind waiting for you.
Sleep early. Good night.
Jia Yun.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Here's my present for you.
Do you like it?
I like it.
I'm glad that you came.
You don't have to bring a present.
Where are Taro and the gang?
Take a seat.
Sure.
Are you hungry? Let's eat first.
Taro and the others are not here yet.
We shouldn't start without them.
Let's eat while waiting for them.
Waiter.
Are you going on a date?
Of course I have to be with my girlfriend
on Christmas Eve.
Are you serious?
He Ye and Liu'er went out
early in the morning.
God knows when those two fools
got girlfriends.
Now, even you're heading out.
This is why you don't have a girlfriend.
Lu Jing.
You're heartless.
Do you know that
in order to give you a surprise,
I almost got into a fight
with the Student Council?
Surprise?
What surprise?
It's...
Just wait for it.
Fine, go meet with your girlfriend.
Where did he get a girlfriend?
I don't get it.
Why do all of them have girlfriends?
Am I not handsome?
[Sun Bin Yu]
What's up?
[What else?]
It's Christmas Eve.
Of course I have to
discuss something meaningful with you.
For example, how did
you win Liang Chen's heart?
[Do you have any techniques]
you can share with me?
Lu Jing!
[Have a heart, will you?]
I'm sincerely asking for guidance here.
Aren't you at Ding Jia Yun's
birthday party?
Why are you so free?
I didn't go to the party.
Don't you know that the party
was cancelled at the last minute?
We're almost done eating,
but Taro is not even here yet.
He's not punctual at all.
Let's have some cake.
I don't think they will come.
Please enjoy.
Thank you.
Let me cut the cake for you.
What's wrong? Is it not tasty?
No, it's because
I'm on diet.
That's why I can't eat too much.
It's okay. The cake is custom ordered.
It's low sugar. It's not fattening.
Luckily you came today.
Otherwise,
I'll have to celebrate alone.
The view here is not bad.
It's quite beautiful.
It reminds me of a phrase.
Be it the moon or its reflection,
it's far beyond reach.
[The person in front of me
is the person I desire.]
Liang Chen.
I have something to tell you.
Actually, I've known you for a long time.
It's longer than you think.
I've been observing you in secret.
When I saw you working hard
to pursue a career in music,
I had a strong urge to approach you.
But I was worried that
if I go too close to you,
I may lose you.
I want to tell you something that
I've been keeping inside my heart.
Liang Chen, I love you.
Jia Yun.
I'm grateful for your love.
However,
I'm already in love with someone else.
I respect your choice.
You're here.
I'm here to pick you up.
Let's go.
Look down there.
The company is huge.
Yes. In the future...
Jia Yun.
Let me introduce someone to you.
She's the singer we've just signed.
Her name is Liang Chen.
He's Jia Yun.
Hello, Jia Yun.
Please take care of her.
You're too polite.
-Hello.
Congratulations.
You've finally moved into a new place.
Ding, let me introduce someone to you.
This is my friend, Liang Chen.
Hello.
Orange, let me introduce someone to you.
This is my good pal, Ding Jia Yun.
We know each other.
Hello.
We're friends.
You don't have to be so polite.
What a coincidence.
Take a seat.
-Do you want any drinks?
-Let me help you.
[We didn't break up back then,
but now we've broken up.]
Liang Chen.
Although
we couldn't have dinner together,
I want to be the first person
to give you an apple.
So, despite the cold weather,
you came to pick me up ahead of time
because of this?
Thank you.
Where do you want to go?
I just want to take a stroll
together with you.
Sure.
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♫
♫ Jingle all the way ♫
♫ Oh what fun it is to ride ♫
♫ In a one horse open sleigh ♫
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♫
♫ Jingle all the way ♫
♫ Oh what fun it is to ride ♫
♫ In a one horse open sleigh ♫
I wish
I can sing my favourite song
just like him.
Come with me.
Hello.
How can I help you?
My girlfriend would like to sing a song.
Can we borrow your guitar?
Sure.
Thank you.
♫ The chosen path is a one-way street ♫
♫ Disregard the hearsay ♫
♫ The journey may be more bumpy
than beautiful ♫
♫ Oh ♫
♫ Even if I turn into ashes,
it's alright ♫
♫ I pursue my dream on the stage ♫
♫ The glory on my back
reflecting my hopes ♫
♫ Oh ♫
♫ Passing through the seas of mediocrity ♫
♫ Diving into new beginnings ♫
♫ Holding my breath for the future ♫
♫ Let my youth bloom ♫
♫ In an ocean of dreams and promises ♫
♫ Woo ♫
♫ Every second, I stand firm ♫
♫ Never learning to be obedient ♫
♫ Woo ♫
Her singing was so beautiful!
Don't you think her voice is familiar?
Is it?
Liang Chen! Doesn't she
look like Liang Chen?
Are you serious?
Liang Chen!
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♫
♫ Jingle all the way ♫
♫ Oh what fun it is to ride ♫
♫ In a one horse open sleigh ♫
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♫
♫ Jingle all the way ♫
Look, Thousand Years Box Spirit
is singing.
Is it nice?
How do you make it sing?
I gave it a mechanical heart.
Your singing
is awful,
but I really like the present.
Thank you.
Can you thank me in a different way?
How?
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♫
♫ Jingle all the way ♫
♫ Oh what fun it is to ride ♫
♫ In a one horse open sleigh ♫
♫ Jingle bells, jingle bells ♫
♫ Jingle all the way ♫
♫ Oh what fun it is to ride ♫
-This plush toy...
-♫ In a one horse open sleigh ♫
Ms Liang, whose singing is that?
He's literally tone-deaf.
His singing is awful.
I think it's quite nice.
It's nice.
Ms Liang.
You haven't even chosen the first song
for the competition.
Listening to this kind of voice
will affect your judgment.
Pull yourself together.
Don't worry, I've found the song.
["The Journey of Music Lovers"
participant's info: Unti]
The youngest contestant
in the competition is Unti.
She's one of the trainees
selected by the show.
She has her own fan base,
and she's good at singing and dancing.
Tong Shi Qin and Li Sha
need no introduction.
They're the evergreen singers
of the industry.
Yes, during the rehearsal,
they didn't perform at their best levels.
You're up against some fierce competition.
They're really good at singing.
You have to perform at your best level.
Liang Chen.
I've just listened to your improvised
version of "Unstoppable".
Although it's risky,
rock and roll
is what we lack at the moment.
It's quite fresh.
It's worth a try.
Sure.
You should communicate with the producer
with regards to improvisation.
I'll tell him to work with you.
Thank you, Director Ma.
-Goodbye.
-Thank you for your help.
Ms Liang.
The crew has announced
your choice of song.
The reviews on the internet
are making me so angry.
Let me see.
Chen Chen, see for yourself.
I'm looking at it.
The rock and roll version of Unstoppable.
Liang Chen, please take it seriously.
Liang Chen is such a girl-next-door.
No one thinks highly of me.
Your fans are calling you
a girl-next-door.
You're competing
in a show full of talented singers,
and changing your style
to rock and roll?
Oh no.
My liver hurts.
That's enough. Drop the act.
Think on the bright side.
The reviews can't get any worse.
If I perform as usual,
they'll be pleasantly surprised.
You're so optimistic.
But honestly,
Ms Liang, why did you choose this song?
You've sung this song so many times.
And it never worked out for you.
Now,
I just want to sing
what I want to sing.
Look at this, it's so funny.
Who did it?
Yeah. It's brilliant.
[Congratulations on escaping 23 years
of singlehood, Lu Jing.]
There he is.
What are you looking at?
Why are you so laughing so happily?
Ms Liang.
Nanze University is indeed
full of talented students.
I wonder who did this.
[To celebrate his departure
from singledom,]
[a fourth year student has
put up a huge banner.]
[I almost died laughing.]
[It's my idea.]
[I put up the banner.]
[Hello, my name is He Ye.]
[I typed the words on the banner.]
[It says "Congratulations on escaping
singlehood, Lu Jing".]
[That's so funny.]
[It's true.]
[Lu Jing is popular in the school.]
[Here is his photo.]
Everyone is expressing jealousy
for the girlfriend
in the comment section.
Hold on, this guy...
He's your junior!
Ms Liang.
Please don't tell me
his girlfriend
is you?
Hello, Taro.
Hello, Orange.
I saw the banner.
What's going on?
You've made quite a splash.
Should I celebrate your union
with some fireworks?
I just saw it.
Can't youngsters
be a little more discreet
about their relationships?
I'm busy. That's all for now.
[Are you trying to brush me off?]
[I'm not done talking.]
What else do you want to say? Hurry up.
I'm a little hard up lately.
Can I have a million yuan?
Bye.
[Don't do that. I'm just kidding.]
As the matchmaker who brought
you two together,
is a meal too much to ask for?
Sure, I'll buy you a meal, okay?
-Bye.
-[Wait.]
When are you going to buy me the meal?
You can't just pay lip service.
I'll buy you a meal tonight, okay?
Bye.
Ms Qing.
There's something I need to tell you.
Say it.
I'm in a relationship.
Is it the young man on the banner?
Your junior?
That's so cool.
As expected of you, Ms Liang.
Ms Qing, will I get into trouble
due to the trending post?