[English subtitles are available]
[Adapted from Qiao Yao's "It's Easy To
Dodge a Gun, But Hard To Prevent a Crush"]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 22]
Ms Qing.
I need to tell you something.
Go ahead.
I'm in a relationship.
With that young guy on the banner?
Your junior.
Impressive.
You're indeed amazing, Ms Liang.
Ms Qing.
Would this trending topic
be a problem?
Show me.
Absurd Campus Anecdote.
For now,
you two should be fine.
But I must remind you.
What is it?
When are you going to
officially introduce him to us?
You gave me a real scare.
Thanks.
Jing.
Please forgive us.
We only wanted to
uphold your dignity
in front of Gu Fei Ming.
Look at that fellow.
It was like a carnival
when he's in a relationship.
But you?
That's right.
If we hadn't put you on that banner,
you'd have lost out.
Jing.
This time it's no doubt our fault.
But just think about it.
Gu Fei Ming is always showing off
in front of you.
We really can't stand it.
Hence,
please consider our good intentions.
Forgive us, will you?
Forgive you?
Unless my girlfriend agrees.
What girlfriend?
You...you're lying to us too?
Stop it, you guys.
He's still hurt.
Hello?
Did you see what happened on the Internet?
Your room-mates are really cute.
I'm sorry.
This must have troubled you.
I'm fine.
The trending topic
has nothing to do with me.
Oh, right.
After Sun Bin Yu knew about us,
he insisted that we treat him to dinner.
When?
[Tonight.]
I'll head there now.
Are you done with this nonsense?
Yes, yes. We are so done.
Jing, don't be mad anymore.
It doesn't look good on you.
Your girlfriend won't like it.
Do you think I'm all about my looks?
Obviously.
No, no. You're not.
Fine.
I'm letting you off this time.
Jing, you're really like an angel.
No, not like an angel.
You are an angel.
Jing, you need to head out now.
Don't keep your girlfriend waiting.
Go now. Quick.
Oh, it's you.
Come in.
What's with that tone
and the long face?
Orange.
I'm getting a feeling that you dislike me.
What is it?
You regret inviting me over?
Stop overreacting.
Look at that mess.
It doesn't look like
you're having people over.
Lu Jing is not here yet.
Lu Jing?
Friendship takes the backseat now.
Fine.
I'll forgive you this time.
Since he's not here yet,
let's kill time
with something fun.
What do you suggest?
Let's go down memory lane.
Take out your classmate records
from university
and graduation photos.
We can look through them.
This is what you are here for?
Alright.
I admit I came today
because I wanted to
know a little more about Ms Ma.
Orange, we're close friends, right?
Don't you want to help
your best friend?
Orange.
Please, Orange.
Last Christmas eve,
I waited in front of her house
the whole night.
She didn't come out to see me at all.
I should at least know the reason.
In that case,
we'll just look at the photos.
Strictly no questions, alright?
What's wrong with you?
You invited me over for take-out?
Yes.
Forget it.
I'm not eating with you two.
I'm going home.
What happened to him?
He wanted to ask about Shan Shan
and got mad after looking at the photos.
What photos got him so mad?
That kid is just a wannabe.
Maybe he has aged badly.
187 centimetres?
Impossible.
That's even taller
than what I usually write.
You thick face.
Face? That face...
Fine, fine. He wins.
Wait a minute.
Ms Ma is not superficial.
She definitely likes a talented
and sophisticated man like me.
If that's the case,
I think I won.
Sir, you really don't want
to order some grilled meat?
Don't you see these?
I can't finish them all.
I'm not ordering food.
Ms Liang.
At your age now,
you should take the advice given.
Why insist on doing a rock song?
Are you trying to turn this
into your farewell show?
Well.
You've worked so hard to get on stage.
You should appreciate the opportunity.
Focus on your singing.
[Are you nervous?]
[No. Why should I?]
[But I am.]
[It's just a small matter.]
[You've surely been around
to be as cool as a cucumber.]
[Truly my idol.]
I'm feeling nervous.
This is the first time I see Orange
do a rock song.
Relax.
It's just a small matter.
It's about time to draw lots.
Hope it goes well
so you can perform later.
Don't be the first to go.
What's so bad about going first?
You tend to get more nervous.
Even if you've done your best,
you might not
leave a strong impression.
But if you go later,
you'll have time to observe other singers
and give audience
the strongest possible impression.
That's true.
[Challengers, please come to the studio.]
Don't be nervous.
Break a leg, Ms Liang.
[Hello, everybody.]
Welcome to the fourth season of
The Journey of Music Lovers.
Welcome, everyone.
Thank you for your great energy.
Let me tell you.
The format this season is different.
We have two challengers today
so the competition is very fierce.
This first challenger
to come on stage
is an incredible singer.
She's the queen of reinvention.
Five times best female singer
of Top Chinese Music.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Meng Lan Zhi.
Welcome, Lan Zhi.
Alright.
The second challenger to join us
is also equally phenomenal.
Not long ago, she won
the Best Female Artiste
and Artiste of the Year
in the Golden Cicada Awards.
I'm sure
you already know who she is.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Liang Chen is here.
Welcome, Liang Chen.
-Liang Chen.
Orange takes off to the sky!
We are with you all the way!
Why are you shouting?
You think she can hear you?
Where did your chill go?
Sit down. Sit down.
Quick.
[We now invite the challengers
to pick an envelope]
[to decide who will go first.]
[But, according to our program rules,]
[current contenders
have finished drawing lots.]
[We're now left with number one
and number seven.]
[You can now pick an envelope.]
You're hurting me. Let go.
She's just picking lots.
Why are you so anxious?
It will be a disadvantage
if Liang Chen goes first.
Now we ask both challengers
to announce the number they picked.
Wait.
Ms Liang.
Can we change envelopes?
My heart is about to burst.
I can't even hold
the microphone steadily.
Change the order?
This has never happened in our show.
Let's check if the Director Team agrees.
Alright.
The Director Team agrees.
Now we have to check with
Liang Chen.
Do you agree to change?
Yes, why not.
Whether going first
or last,
it's all the same to me.
Thanks, Ms Liang.
Alright.
We invite the challengers
to announce their number.
I ended up with number one
though I was supposed to go last...
But never mind.
The world is always unpredictable.
In the next segment,
let's look forward
to the amazing performances
from the two challengers.
That was nerve-wracking.
My Orange has luck on her side.
Your Orange?
She's mine.
Fine. Whatever.
Unbelievable.
What a narrow mind for a grown man.
Green monster.
Shameful.
♫ From amidst the crowd ♫
♫ I've risen to the top ♫
♫ The smile is as big as
the pain I've gone through ♫
♫ Look at the camera and wave ♫
♫ The atmosphere is lacking ♫
♫ While the lights still shine ♫
♫ Keep their eyes on me ♫
♫ Don't look down, don't look back ♫
♫ Be it on the stage or behind the scene ♫
♫ From the top ♫
♫ I will endure ♫
♫ Forget the noise around you ♫
♫ Happiness needs no complicated rules ♫
♫ The screen is filled
with the latest trends ♫
♫ Like sand between the fingers,
spilling once touched ♫
♫ From amidst the crowd ♫
♫ I've risen to the top ♫
♫ The smile is as big as
the pain I've gone through ♫
♫ To be at the top ♫
♫ One must be strong-willed ♫
♫ Turn up the lights,
give the mic an echo ♫
♫ Look at the camera and wave ♫
♫ The atmosphere is lacking ♫
♫ While the lights still shine ♫
♫ Keep their eyes on me ♫
♫ Don't look down, don't look back ♫
♫ Be it on the stage or behind the scene ♫
♫ Each time, from the top ♫
♫ I will endure ♫
♫ Forget the noise around you ♫
Oh, no.
I think she's pretty good.
♫ Happiness needs no complicated rules ♫
♫ The screen is filled
with the latest trends ♫
♫ Like sand between the fingers,
spilling once touched ♫
Move it. Quick.
Stage Design Team, look again.
Is your backdrop secure?
Make no mistake.
Check the lighting.
Yes, show me the lights.
Alright, I got it.
Calm your mind.
You have put in 200 percent for this.
Don't let the nerve beat you.
Good luck. I have faith in you.
Good luck, Ms Liang.
Ms Liang.
[Good luck.]
Guo, are we done for today?
Yes, the director has called it a wrap.
[Next up is Liang Chen.]
[I trust many of you share our sentiment.]
[Liang Chen and rock music.]
[Say what? But today, Liang Chen is...]
Orange has really got big guts.
She's really going to do a rock song?
Has she no fear of failure?
Taro.
♫ The chosen path is a one-way street ♫
♫ Disregard the hearsay♫
♫ The journey may be more bumpy
than beautiful ♫
♫ Oh ♫
♫ Even if I turn into ashes,
it's alright ♫
♫ I pursue my dream on the stage ♫
♫ The glory on my back
reflecting my hopes ♫
♫ Oh ♫
♫ Passing through the seas of mediocrity ♫
♫ Diving into new beginnings ♫
♫ Holding my breath for the future ♫
♫ Let the youth bloom ♫
♫ In an ocean of dreams and promises ♫
♫ Woo ♫
♫ Every second, standing firm ♫
♫ Never learning to be obedient ♫
♫ Woo ♫
♫ Never stop. We don't need to♫
♫ Never stop. Bask in loneliness ♫
♫ Never stop. Until the lights go out ♫
♫ I will make my own path ♫
♫ Evening out rocks as I walk
to the end of the earth ♫
♫ Chasing after the steps of my dream ♫
♫ Ah yeah ♫
♫ The chosen path is a one-way street ♫
♫ Disregard the hearsay ♫
♫ The journey may be more bumpy
than beautiful ♫
♫ Oh ♫
♫ Even if I turn into ashes,
it's alright ♫
♫ I pursue my dream on the stage ♫
♫ The glory on my back
reflecting my hopes ♫
♫ Oh ♫
♫ The glory on my back
reflecting my hopes ♫
What's wrong?
Liang Chen, you can do it!
-Liang Chen!
♫ Let my youth bloom ♫
♫ In an ocean of dreams and promises ♫
♫ Woo ♫
♫ Every second, standing firm ♫
♫ Never learning to be obedient ♫
♫ Woo ♫
♫ Let the youth bloom ♫
♫ In an ocean of dreams and promises ♫
♫ Woo ♫
♫ Every second, standing firm ♫
♫ Never learning to be obedient ♫
♫ Woo ♫
♫ Let the youth bloom ♫
♫ In an ocean of dreams and promises ♫
♫ Woo ♫
♫ Every second, standing firm ♫
♫ Never learning to be obedient ♫
♫ Woo ♫
[Orange has my heart. Always with you]
Orange takes off to the sky!
We are with you all the way!
-Liang Chen!
Ms Liang.
That was nerve-racking.
I was way more tensed
than my first time on stage.
Ms Liang, that performance was awesome.
The audience was stunned.
Stop it.
Alright. Let's sit.
But I must say.
That guitar solo was really something.
You're so cool.
Ms Qing, can I have my phone?
Here you go.
You can't part with it for too long.
[Hello?]
Hello? Lu Jing.
How did I do just now?
[Perfect all the way.]
Really?
I was? Alright.
The most nerve-racking moment has come.
Tonight,
between Liang Chen and Meng Lan Zhi,
who will stay and who will go?
Please look at the screen.
-Liang Chen.
-Lan Zhi.
-She won.
-She won!
Liang Chen won.
-She won.
She won!
Congratulations, Liang Chen.
Sadly, tonight,
the singer we have to bid farewell
is Meng Lan Zhi.
You put up a good fight.
You performed well tonight.
I know you're better than me
but I will beat you one day.
Keep up the fight.
Life is full of ups and downs.
But there will be no success
without failure.
I'll continue to work hard.
I hope you'll continue to support me.
Will you?
We will.
Thank you, everyone.
I love you.
Let's thank Meng Lan Zhi again
for the great performance today.
Please give a big hand to Meng Lan Zhi.
-Keep fighting, Lan Zhi.
-Keep fighting.
All the best.
We want to congratulate Liang Chen
for advancing to the next round.
The Journey of Music Lovers welcomes you.
Thank you.
-Liang Chen.
A big hand to Liang Chen.
Amazing.
Epic.
I knew she can do it.
She didn't let us down.
Do you think we should
throw her a celebration party?
Of course. It's on me.
Good.
It's on you.
Ms Liang.
You're on the top trending topic now.
Everything is about you
and The Journey.
The most underestimated rock singer
in history.
Liang Chen's massive music makeover.
She is unstoppable.
Liang Chen rocks.
Liang Chen is so cool.
I want to see it.
Liang Chen.
Director Ma.
Your performance was spectacular.
The response was incredible.
I can't wait
to see your next performance.
Thanks, Director Ma.
I'll continue to work hard.
Good luck.
Director Ma.
I am really curious though.
Why did you agree to let me
do a rock song?
Everyone was against it at that time.
Actually, I saw a video
of you doing a rock song in university.
How did you get that video?
My niece sent it to me.
Ma Shan Shan.
You should know her.
I see.
Get yourself ready for the next show.
See you next week.
Oh, right.
About Shan Shan,
I need a favour from you.
Please go ahead.
All these years,
Shan Shan's temperament has changed.
You were her classmate.
If possible,
please talk to her.
Don't worry. I will.
Good morning.
Time for breakfast.
Can I come in?
Yes, please.
What brings you here out of the blue?
I want to personally
invite you for dinner.
Taro's place. Let's go.
Can I not go?
You can't say no.
It's my celebration party.
How can you miss it?
Finish your breakfast.
We need to go after this.
Alright.
Eat with me.
I've eaten.
Typical female celebrity.
Ms Ma, you are here.
Come in.
Come.
Have some peanuts.
Ms Ma.
Orange juice, coke, lemon tea.
Chips, cookies, pistachios.
What do you want?
It feels like spring outing in here.
I'm just worried Ms Ma will be bored.
Stop talking.
Let's watch television.
Look.
What a constructive suggestion.
Ms Ma, what do you want to watch?
Movie?
Drama, romantic, art film
or...
Rerun of yesterday's competition.
Look.
What a constructive suggestion.
You managed to invite Ms Ma over.
I'll let you off today.
Ms Ma.
Please make yourself comfortable.
I'll make you something nice to eat.
[Ding, where are you?]
[Why aren't you here yet?]
[Are you planning to let me
do all the cooking?]
You're here.
Jia Yun.
Your show was a success yesterday.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Come in.
Long time no see, Jia Yun.
It's so rare to see you these days.
You are...
I'm...
He's my boyfriend, Lu Jing.
Hello, Ms Ma.
I'm Lu Jing.
Hello.
Chef Ding, you're finally here.
The kitchen is waiting for you.
Come, come.
Very professional.
Taro, do you have a colander?
You know how to wash vegetables?
If you're not doing anything,
can you not stand in the way?
What? It's my kitchen.
Why can't I stay here?
Shan Shan.
Thanks for showing Director Ma
my old video.
It happened by chance.
Do you want to come watch
my performance live?
No worries.
I'll reserve the tickets.
Just come when you can.
Taro, I need sesame for the braised fish.
Go buy me some.
Sesame in braised fish?
You can take over.
I'll go instead.
No, no.
Alright, fine.
I'll go.
Wash those vegetables properly.
What's wrong?
Are you going out?
It's all for the perfection
of Chef Ding's culinary masterpiece.
Don't start eating before I'm back.
Just go.
It's you I'm talking to.
Ms Ma is nothing like you.
I'm going now, Ms Ma.
See you later.
If you cook in future,
don't use parsley.
She doesn't like it.
Don't make the food too spicy.
It's not good for her throat.
Thanks.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of her.
Good.
Coming.
Hello, grandma.
Hello, Sun. Come in.
Hello, grandpa.
It's you.
You're reading?
Grandma, do you have white sesame?
I need to borrow some.
Yes, I have.
Wait here. I'll get it for you.
Great.
Sun.
Is Jing at your place again?
Yes, he is.
He always troubles you.
No, it's fine.
I happen to be free today
so I invited some friends over.
-Is that so?
-Here you go, Sun.
-Thanks, grandma.
-You're welcome.
Oh, right.
Your granddaughter-in-law is at my place.
What? What did you say?
Granddaughter-in-law.
The wife of your grandson.
She's at my place for dinner.
Really?
You're not kidding me?
No, I'm not.
Didn't Lu Jing tell you?
He told us he has a girlfriend
but we thought he was joking.
What?
It's for real this time.
That boy...
He finally came to his senses.
I've been worried about him for so long.
Everybody already has a girlfriend.
But that boy
is just a nerd.
All he does is studying and reading.
This is good news.
He has a girlfriend now.
Yes, yes.
I need to get back to my friends now.
Alright, go on.
Alright. Bye, grandpa.
-Bye, grandma.
-Bye.
-Alright, bye.
Old man, our grandson has a girlfriend.
Did you hear that?
What's the use of hearing about it?
Go change.
We'll go have a look.
Right. Let's go.