[English subtitles are available.]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 26]
Who're you?
A snake.
I mean, who are you?
Do I know you?
Who are you?
Do we know each other?
No, we don't.
I don't know you.
So stop asking.
Who is he?
Why I feel so distressed
seeing him cry?
So clever.
Even I was fooled by him.
I'll make friends with him.
Brother Chu,
take it slowly.
This place is unusual.
[Feng Yiyou, the Celestial Artefact Sect]
Let's hide behind the door.
We'll take the long view. Come on.
Feng Yiyou,
you said you would kill me
every time your Celestial Artefact Sect
see me? What're you doing?
Why are you so nice to me?
This is a critical time for the
survival of the Human Race.
Survival is our top priority.
Do you get it?
No.
How about this?
You hide inside.
I'll go
to find out what they are.
Leave them to me. You can go now.
Brother Chu, just leave!
Leave now, Brother Chu.
No no no, Brother Chu.
Let me do it, Chu.
Brother Chu,
your juniors were captured by those things.
Take me there.
This is where Junior Ling was
captured by those
ghost-like men.
Are you alright?
What do you think?
Where are those two assholes?
You bastards.
You want me dead, eh?
I'll blow you up.
Stop there!
Stop!
Just stop it.
I'll blow you up!
I'll blow...
Run!
Wait wait wait.
Just because you have endless Bombs
doesn't mean you don't need to behave yourself.
No one has more
spirit artifacts
than our sect.
Let me show you how powerful my weapon is.
Let me show your mine.
Chu Li, stop it!
Hurry up. Run! Leave!
Stop there.
We'll all die if you don't stop!
The second volume of the Scripture of Nine Hells
has shown itself.
Calling Mother of Earth.
The Land of Chaos.
It's not Du Shaoyang.
It's me.
Ma'am,
what's wrong with you?
Du Shaoyang didn't
kill Qin Lie.
I did.
You said
you once saw someone holding a dagger
The one who killed Qin Lie?
Yes.
That was me.
I was the killer.
I don't know if this is a sign.
What happened just now?
The second volume of the Scripture has been made.
We're calling the Mother of Earth.
Dark Jade City on the Land of Chaos
should be where the second volume refers to.
The Land of Chaos.
Qin Lie,
I need to go to Dark Jade City immediately.
One thousand years ago,
The Venerable launched
the teleportation to get to the Land of Chaos.
The Horned Demon Race had completely changed.
They could no longer co-exist with the Human Race.
One either killed
or got killed on the Land of Chaos.
As a result, The Venerable decided to close the teleportation.
Hence, it became the biggest secret
of our race.
The Nether Race also live on the Land of Chaos.
Do they get along with the Human Race?
Apart from the Horned Demon Race
and the Dark Shadow Race
on the Scarlet Tide Continent,
there's another clan of the Nether Race
the Ghost Eye Race living on the Land of Chaos.
The reason why they can survive there
is because they're pretty useful.
They live a humble and peaceful life there.
The Ghost Eye Race look
totally different from the Horned Demon Race.
But
you're their leader.
You will recognise them as you meet them.
The appearance of the second volume of the Scripture
implies that I have understood the first volume.
The energy of the Mother of Earth
will be released again.
The power of the Earth
belongs to you.
Granny,
the second volume of the Scripture
is on the Land of Chaos.
The teleportation formation happens
to be located right beneath the Nether Realm.
Is that just a coincidence?
Isn't it?
Yeah,
such a coincidence.
Qin Shan happened to save you.
There happened to be a formation
here.
Huang Shuli,
show yourself up!
Come out!
Little bastard. You took it from me
when you lost to me.
Bastard? Me?
Our Master didn't treat me fairly.
I'm the Senior Sister.
I should have got the sword token.
But our Master insisted that
we compete for it.
It's not his fault.
When our Master said we shall compete,
you were so excited.
You thought you were invincible.
But it turned out that I'm better
at martial arts and illusory arts.
You even attacked me unfairly.
You don't deserve the title of Senior Sister.
You were better at illusory arts?
Stop there.
Qianqian.
Who are you?
It's me, Qianqian.
Do we know each other?
No, we don't.
I don't know you.
So, stop asking.
It's you.
It's me, Qianqian.
What gave me away?
The person I met last night
didn't even know me.
Why would you transform into him?
Who is he?
Stop acting like you don't know.
He is your crush.
I sensed that.
Nonsense.
I don't have a crush.
I won't be myself if I don't kill you today.
Again?
You're not Senior Sister?
What're you talkin' about?
Do I look like a woman?
It's you.
Who the hell are you?
Why are you on my mind?
What do you mean "on your mind"?
If you're not,
why would the Senior Sister use you against me?
I...
If you don't explain,
I will kill you. Wanna try me?
Who are you?
I really don't know what you're talking about.
I'm asking who you are.
Why can't I ask that if you ask me?
Let me ask you one last time.
Who are you?
She is mental.
See ya.
Stop there.
Qin Lie, who are you really?
Where are you? Help!
Stop there!
Siqi, stop!
Siqi.
I see you, Siqi.
Siqi, I see you.
Why are you hiding from me?
Siqi,
I let the one who had poisoned you
escape.
Don't worry.
I'll find her
and kill her.
But before that,
let me kill you first.
Who are you?
Why do you want to kill
the one who hurt me and me as well?
Si...
Watch out!
I had known before I came here
that I would either kill others or get killed.
I admit you did better than me.
But please let my woman go.
You think I want to kill her
for the Demon Sealing Tombstone?
Siqi...
She's poisoned by the Voodoo insect.
She will die soon.
Her mind
will be controlled by the Voodoo insect
until it eats it up.
In the end,
she will become a ghost killer
for Black Voodoo Cult.
She would even
kill her own father,
let alone you.
Black Voodoo Cult?
Since she's yours,
do you want to
do it yourself?
Alright.
Let me do it.
Siqi.
Shaoyang.
Are you alright?
You don't want to kill me then?
Do you want me to?
Of course not.
I managed to get rid of my father.
I finally managed to get your love.
I have so many places to visit
and so many things to do.
I don't want to die.
This is the Siqi I love.
Will you love me
even if I am very ugly?
The first time I met you,
you also wore a veil.
I didn't even know what you looked like.
Let alone today when I love you so much.
Shaoyang,
I'm sorry.
Siqi,
do you remember
what did the people look like
who poisoned you?
I've been looking for you
ever since I got out of the Graveyard of Gods.
Later,
I found a couple talking secretly in the woods.
Shaoyang.
Black Voodoo Cult. The Illusory Demon Sect.
They must have the cure.
We must find
Qin Lie at the moment.
Can you still make it?
Let's go.
Siqi.
It should be here.
Why did it suddenly disappear?
Terminator Profound Bombs?
Could it be Qin Lie?
I don't have ears.
I can't hear your voice.
I don't have eyes.
I can't see your face.
You crazy woman. Why are you chasing me?
Yiyuan?
Brother.
Brother, you...
I'm not your brother.
Stop following me around.
Brother, I...
Just leave. Don't cause trouble for us.
Why do you mean?
I'm here to help.
Plus, any friend of my brother's
is a friend of mine.
I don't have eyes.
I can't see your face.
I don't have ears.
I can't hear your voice.
Here it goes again.
My world is chaos.
But I heard you summoning me.
Your voice is the first thing I've ever heard.
Where's the Demon Sealing Tombstone?
Tombstone, you're finally back.
What the hell is that?
Brother,
don't be afraid.
I'll protect you.
If this thing dares to lay a finger on you,
I...I...I'll blow it up.
Don't do it.
Alright.
Gongmu Lie, you're finally back.
Gongmu Lie?
You call him that?
Who are you?
Gongmu Lie, I've been waiting for you for too long.
Thousands of years have passed.
Thousands of flowers have died.
Too long.
Yeah,
I'm back.
But I'm not Gongmu Lie, I'm Qin Lie.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the Night Fairy.
The Night Fairy,
servant of Gongmu Lie.
How do you know about me?
Who are you?
No, you're not her.
How could you forget me?
Did you do this on purpose?
Because you're still angry at me?
Why would he be angry at you?
Grandfather.
You're really Gongmu Lie.
Go and check it out.
Grandpa, what's all this?
They're the Spirit Pillars.
I built them for you to play.
I don't have eyes.
I can't see your face.
I don't have ears.
I can't hear your voice.
My world is chaos.
Who are you? I heard...
I heard you summoning me.
Even though I can't see,
I heard it.
Your voice is the first thing I've ever heard.
Who are you?
I'm your mentor.
I'm a part of the Spirit Pillars.
Spirit Pillar?
The Pillars contain the primary state
of everything in this world.
They're in the primary state,
but if you can grasp it,
you'll be much better than others
on this land.
What's your name?
I don't have one.
You can give me a name if you want.
There's no light here.
No need for light.
True light lives in your heart,
not in the outside world.
So, you live in the dark forever?
That's one way to put it.
I'll give you a name?
I know it.
How about, the Night Fairy?
The Night Fairy?
I like it.
From now on,
I'll be your mentor and your company.
So the Spirit Pillars were made for you.
No wonder they light up when you touch them.
Where's my grandfather?
Gongmu Master? Has he gone missing?
Do you not know?
I don't.
If I was Gongmu Lie,
why am I Qin Lie now?
Why did I forget my past?
What's with the Soul Suppressing Orb
in my brain?
Why did you forget about the past?
What's with the Soul Suppressing Orb
in your brain?
I guess we have two confused humans here.
No.
You're a human.
But you're not.
I'm a human.
You turned me into a human.
You gave me a flesh.
Why do you look frustrated?
Someone went back on a promise.
Don't care about the others.
You just need my companionship.
Only humans can keep each another company.
But you're not human.
You can turn me into one.
Can I?
Everything starts from the primary state,
including human bodies.
You have grasped half of
the 12 Spirit Pillars.
I think you can do it.
Can you see me?
Of course I can.
But,
but I can't see myself.
What do I look like?
Very pretty.
Why you made me like this?
We don't have maids here.
One day, a young maid walked by.
I found it interesting,
and I remember how she looks like.
Then... I'll be your maid from now on.
It's you
that gave me a human body.
that made me felt the warmth
of holding hands,
of relationships.
It's you
that made me taste the fun of being a human.
But, it's me who kept you company till you grow up.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
I just thought you have relationship problems
with this Miss. Night Fairy here.
You don't get it,
no woman is as scary as an abandoned ex.
I need to be prepared.
Don't say a word. Let me test her first.
Oh, so you two grew up together.
Then what happened?
Did you get married?
Made love?
No.
The Night Fairy
has always been the most loyal friend of his.
How do you know?
I read it on The Tale of Gongmu Lie.
The Night Fairy was there for him
for many years,
and they overcome many hardships together.
Bullshit.
That's not true.
He was tempted by a woman,
and betrayed his own people for her.
Wuchun.
You can't go.
Get out of my way.
I'm part of the 12 Spirit Pillars,
you can't get past us.
The Spirit Pillars are mine.
Over my dead body.
She looks so resentful.
I understand your love
and feelings for him.
But he doesn't get it!
The power left in those Pillars
have turned this space into chaotic flows.
I'm weak now.
I couldn't get out.
How long have I been waiting for him?
One thousand years?
Two thousand?
He didn't even come back to get me.
I miss you more,
with each passing day.
I resent you even more,
with each passing year.
So The Graveyard of Gods,
the Demon Sealing Tombstone,
everything was set up by you?
That's right.
So the Tombstone will bring you back here.
No wonder the Tombstone recognizes you.
Now that you're back,
you don't even remember me.
You killed
all the people that came here?
I didn't need to.
This place is filled with the
remaining power of the Spirit Pillars.
If they can't get out,
they will surely die here.
What do you want then?
I want you to stay here.
Stay with me forever.
I'm not sure about my identity.
I don't know what Gongmu Lie was like.
I am good for nothing.
I even lost my friends.
The wind?
The wind
is a manifestation of all things.
The sound travels through air.
I sense that
you have the power from the Spirit Pillar.
Keep calm. Listen to
all the sounds in the air using this power.
Can I?
You're Gongmu Lie.
You can do it.
Help!
It's Yiyuan.
Yiyuan,
where are you?
Yushi.
Wuchun?
Why is she here?
You know her?
Wuchun, Wuchun.
I killed her.
Help!
Stop chasing me! I really don't know you!
How could a lady like you
chasing a man like this?
I won't chase if you stop.
Yiyuan.
Yushi,
please explain to this lady for me.
I just came from the Scarlet Tide Continent.
I really don't know her.
Xuanxuan?
Xuanxuan.
You know her?
Who's Xuanxuan?
Xuanxuan,
I'm your sister.
You got the wrong person.
My name is Pan Qianqian.
Kill them.
Tang Siqi.
You can't kill her.
Stop chasing me!
Why in this city?
What's going on again?
Yiyuan.
You can't escape from me!
Dark Jade City.
Blue Star Association.
There's danger!
Damn. It looks like they've entered through the door!
What's going on?
I heard it.
Someone's inside.
Du Shaoyang?
Qin Lie.
Hi, Qin Lie and Saintess Song.
This is Chu Li from the Terminator Sect.
Where's Tang Siqi?
Let me introduce.
This is the Third Heavenly Swordsman
Yan Baiyi.
The youngest sword holder
in the Heavenly Sword Mountain.
We got separated
as soon as we came in.
I've been looking for you.
I found Siqi first.
It turned out she has been poisoned
by the Voodoo insect.
Black Voodoo Cult?