[The English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 25]
[The Land of Maple Leaves, the Illusory Demon Sect]
Senior Sister,
the last sword token to
be brought into the Graveyard of Gods
must be mine.
[Huang Shuli, the Illusory Demon Sect]
How arrogant!
Just because you think you're talented
doesn't mean you can defeat me.
Try me.
I can't bear leaving you.
Forgive me if I don't look at you.
I will always miss you, father.
Take care.
Pan Qianqian,
The Land of Chaos consists of five continents.
This is your first trial,
Heavenly Calamity Continent.
What are the other four?
Wait till you pass the first one.
The Land of Chaos is controlled by different clans.
You must be familiar with two of them.
The Terminator Sect.
Who uses the Terminator Profound Bomb?
Exactly.
It's a secret weapon
of this clan.
No wonder Master Mohai said
it's not from
the Scarlet Tide Continent.
He is really learned.
The other is the Celestial Artefact Sect.
Forefathers of the Armament Sect?
I'm the Senior Sister of the Armament Sect.
I suppose we can become allies.
Wait till you get to
fight with them.
Of course,
there's another power,
the Heavenly Sword Sect.
Please take our respect.
The first task on the Heavenly Calamity Continent
is the Graveyard of Gods.
That doesn't sound like a safe place.
One could easily die there.
It opens every ten years.
The best students from each sect
will be given sword tokens and enter it.
How...how many could survive this?
Less than one
out of ten.
No one knows how dangerous
the Graveyard can be.
One can only get out safely
if they're acknowledged by
the Demon Sealing Tombstone.
It is said that the Tombstone
is a legacy of Gongmu Lie.
Gongmu Lie?
But no one knows
whether he ever really existed.
Who owns the Tombstone now?
It has never acknowledged any master.
Sir,
why is this place called the Land of Chaos?
It's easy to understand.
Because it is
chaotic.
You'll get to know what that means
as soon as you go down there.
You must remember.
Do not try to be a hero.
You're indeed powerful.
Both of your fathers are from the
Fragmentation Realm.
But the leaders here all belong to
the Imperishable Realm.
Two levels higher.
Li, I heard that there's also a Nether Race
living on the Land of Chaos?
Yes, you're right.
One of its clan, the Ghost Eye Race
live peacefully with the Human Race there.
What do they look like?
Like the Horned Demon Race?
You'll know when you go down there.
What matters most is that
have you got enough spirit stones?
Yes, we have.
You don't look like locals.
Do you need a guide?
Let the Ghost Eye Race show you
around Dark Jade City.
If you take us with you
to Dark Jade City,
we can give the most comprehensive
and detailed information
about the Land of Chaos.
What lovely kids!
We're not kids.
We're the Ghost Eye Race.
We're much older than kids.
People of our race are born
to have the shortest bodies.
We have great wisdom.
My name is La Pu.
I'm La Fei.
I'm La Er.
We're well-informed.
If there's something that we don't know,
no one else
could.
Are you heading to the Graveyard of Gods?
Do you need a guide?
How do you know
we're not locals?
Because we're clever.
We know as soon as we saw you.
And I know
you must have the sword tokens
from Heavenly Sword Mountain.
The floating island where
Li Mu kept the Sixth Heavenly Sword
has just passed by.
You appeared right at this time.
But you don't even know about us.
You landed here
without knowing who we are.
We quickly figured out
you must be the famous five
everyone's talking about recently.
We're famous?
Sure.
You possess five sword tokens.
It's said that Li Mu
did you a favour
on the Scarlet Tide Continent.
Let's go.
I get to like the Ghost Eye Race.
Me, too.
Dark Jade City is ruled by
five Silver rank forces.
Different forces and races
trade with each other here
because of the Graveyard of Gods.
It's a busy place.
I heard that you don't welcome outsiders?
People on the Land are rather tolerable.
Indeed.
But this is a place for the mighty.
Battles and wars
take place on a daily basis.
That's how the Land of Chaos
got its name.
What do you want?
Do you know
what kind of warriors
will the five Silver rank forces send?
Of course.
Keep up. Let me tell you.
If you see anything good
as we walk along,
I can introduce them for you.
You can buy whatever you like.
Do you get commission
if we buy what you recommend?
Of course.
Ladies,
what you like must be different
from what the gentlemen do.
Shall we
show you around the other side of the street?
Cunning kids.
You worry that we might stop them
from shopping?
First, we're not kids.
We're the Ghost Eyes Race.
Second, that's what men are like.
Let's go.
Wanna go with me alone?
I notice that you don't talk much.
No one talks to you either.
What do you think?
Wanna buy a Demon Sealing Tombstone?
This was the secret weapon
used by Gongmu Lie in the war.
Tourists would always
buy some as souvenirs.
Wanna buy some, ladies?
Do you believe
Gongmu Lie really existed?
It's not a matter of what we believe.
The point is
we can earn money from his tale.
You buy this for yourself
or for him?
Who's he?
It's none of your business, kid.
It's the Ghost Eye Race!
It's none of your business, either.
Tingyu,
this is your life.
Why don't you just go for your love?
If you don't take action now,
he will be taken by Ling Yushi soon.
Qin Lie and Du Shaoyang
are both men with visions.
They won't waste time on relationships.
Although Du Shaoyang
may love you,
he won't stay for you.
He's eager to have power.
Qin Lie is also the same.
He won't bother himself with love.
You really don't care about
your true feelings deep inside?
I made my pursuit of love.
I got it. I was in love.
I never regret it.
What about you?
Don't you want to be loved?
Have a look.
Wrap them up for me.
OK.
That's great.
Why are they in a hurry?
Do you know why?
We don't know at the moment.
We will know in a bit.
We have a secret art.
We can get information from plants.
We can also get news
from other people of our race.
Of course, we need to charge for this.
Fine. Go ahead and ask.
It turned out that the gate of the
Graveyard has been opened.
How lucky we are.
Only those from the Manifestation Realm
are allowed to enter.
It's easy to get in
but difficult to get out.
Don't even enter if you're afraid of death.
How about we find a tavern
for you to rest inside?
[The Tavern of the Blue Star Association]
You charge for more than
50 premium spirit stones
just because we asked you a few questions
and you showed us around the city?
That's our price.
Why didn't you tell us earlier?
You didn't ask.
Stop quarrelling.
Shame on you.
I haven't decided to pay as
the Mayor of Purple Mist Sea.
How dare you, as a former Pavilion Master,
to act on behalf of me?
Twenty stones.
Take it or leave it.
Cheapskates.
That's unfair.
They're not stingy.
They're just pretending to be rich.
I didn't expect
things are so expensive here.
Will it cost more
if we stay in a tavern?
Let's ask around first.
The room I showed you is the dining hall.
Let me take you to the Heaven Room.
It was designed by
Master Ru himself.
It's beautiful.
Every item is the only one in the world.
Sects from the five Silver rank forces
have all stayed here. It's top-rated.
Sir.
What's the price for one day?
Five hundred premium spirit stones.
Five hundred?
That's a little expensive.
How about I show you the Earth Room?
It's not as good as this one, though.
Still, it was highly praised
by our distinguished guests.
How much then?
One hundred premium spirit stones a day.
One hundred?
I'll pay for it.
Wait a minute.
We don't know how long we will stay here.
Save some money, Miss.
Do you have cheaper rooms, sir?
We only have the Secular Room then.
Everyone can afford it.
It only costs fifty premium spirit stones.
Can you make it cheaper?
How much can you
afford then?
500 medium-grade spirit stones.
How could you pay me with medium-grade stones?
Piss off.
Don't mess around.
I didn't expect a saintess like you
would become a poor mouth one day.
No wonder Uncle Li
asked us to take more spirit stones with us.
Shall we go to another tavern?
Same price everywhere else. However,
if you've got the sword tokens,
you can use them as a mortgage here.
We can let you stay in the Heaven Room for free.
How do you know we've got the sword tokens?
It looks like everyone's well-informed here.
Let's leave here.
Wanna leave? You wish.
What do you mean?
Leave the sword tokens
and show yourselves out.
Fight or flight?
Fight, of course.
You guys from the Scarlet Tide Continent
are not bad, huh?
Those little bastards of the Ghost Eye Race
took our spirit stones without telling us.
It's them who betrayed us.
I like them.
I'm from Blue Star Association!
It's part of Heavenly Sword Mountain.
If you hurt me,
they won't let you go.
Wanna try us now?
My lady...Master, please don't.
We're appointed by Li Mu of Heavenly Sword Mountain.
Do you want us to
invite him here?
I don't dare to.
There could be many
who are trying to take our tokens.
Take care.
Let's go.
The Graveyard of Gods hasn't opened yet.
Let's just wait.
Who're you thinking of?
Why should you ask?
You tell me then.
Ma'am,
you've won the trust of our people.
That's a huge responsibility.
I need to take it seriously.
Mother of Earth has the power
to change landscapes
and create flowers, bushes
and trees,
even lakes.
You've made it.
That's such a big power
inside you.
I finally understand
why I grew spirit plants
better than others.
I believe
one day,
you're going to take us back to the ground.
I can enjoy
the sunshine then.
I'm not sure about this.
But since you trust me so much,
I don't know what to say.
Ma'am,
don't worry.
The Nether Race will always support you.
The Human Race
are born to be greedy and brutal.
Although they didn't hurt us
when I returned via the teleportation formation
in the Purple Mist Sea,
I believe
it was only because they were afraid of
the Heavenly Sword Sect.
The Profound Heaven Alliance
and the Eight Extreme Temple
were greatly undermined.
But for the help of Li Mu
and the secret escort of the Master of Frost,
they would have exterminated us all.
We need to thank Qin Lie, after all.
He had begged the Master of Frost to help us.
He can't expect us
to stop holding grudges against him just because of this.
Granny,
I don't want to launch another war.
First,
people will suffer.
We need time to recuperate.
Second,
they will only fight back more fiercely
if we ever win over them.
What if they
wage war against us first?
We'll never give in.
I'll never go easy on them
even if I have to turn the Land into ruins.
So I need to cultivate the
Scripture of Nine Hells as soon as possible.
The power of the strongest race
is already in your blood.
You need to take it slowly, even if you're desperate.
You can't rush with your cultivation.
I can't take it slowly.
I said I need to destroy them.
How can I just pose around
without having real power
by that time?
You made me so angry
by asking Li Mu to invite me here,
no matter whether it's because you have pity on me
or you just want to motivate me.
But this time,
I really want to say thank you.
Thank you for taking me to such a beautiful place.
It's only the territory of Silver rank forces.
I wonder what that of
the Gold rank forces will be like.
The gate is about to open. Come down.
Wait. Wait.
The gate of the Graveyard will open twice today,
with a two-hour interval.
I need to tell you something
before you go in.
It's really important.
It's a life-and-death matter.
How much do you want?
One thousand.
Wait.
It's hard to get out alive.
I suppose you will all die in there.
Do you need those spirit stones
as your grave goods?
Why don't you spare us some?
Two hundred. That's what I can give.
Give me.
I was going to offer only 50.
The gate is open.
Tell us.
You need to join hands before you enter
so that you won't get carried away
by strong winds.
You should have known what to do
if you had watched them do it.
You could have saved 200.
Put Tang Siqi down.
Hurry up.
Du Shaoyang, save her.
Chu Li?
Among the students of all sects,
one must be mentioned.
Chu Li.
The genius of the Terminator Sect.
This guy is grumpy.
He always carries a lot of
Terminator Profound Bombs.
He sets them off
whatever his mood.
You can easily recognise him.
The fur of snow wolves
are precious on the Land of Chaos.
If you see someone
wearing a snow wolf fur coat,
that must be him.
I finally find you.
Move aside.
Qin Lie,
did you get the Demon Sealing Tombstone?
Yes.
Let me see it.
You're not Qin Lie.
You're from the Illusory Demon Sect.
The Illusory Demon Sect are good at illusory arts.
It is rumoured that
she can transform herself into a dozen of appearances.
Her bewildering art
is the most terrifying.
She can transform herself into
the person you love and befuddle you.
You love him
but you could still break my charm.
That man I love
would either blame me if I act rashly
or ask me if I get hurt.
He wouldn't just ask me for a
Demon Sealing Tombstone.
Just like La Fei told us,
you're good at illusory arts but not martial arts.
Where can you hide?
Chu Li,
let's deal with her!
Shu Li,
are you alright?
Leave her to me.
Stop right there.
Try me if you want her to die.
What're you doing?
If you drink that,
I can let her survive.
I'm afraid you won't let her go
even if I drank this.
Stop it!
You can choose to leave
or drink that wine.
This is not toxic.
Do you know what poison your woman got?
If you want to detoxify her, drink it.
I would very much like to see
how you two survive this.
Shaoyang, leave!
Du Shaoyang...Du...
All dead.
How powerful.
Save me!
I haven't been to the Graveyard.
I can't just die.
Shaoyang, no!
I can pay you back now.
Siqi,
you need to thank me for it.
But for me, how could you save her?
They were cunning.
They pretended to be dead and ambushed me!
Shaoyang, just leave.
You're ambushed.
Yeah.
Yiyuan, tell us
about how they ambushed you.
I entered the tavern as soon as you did.
I thought you killed that servant.
I was about to praise you.
I didn't expect they caught me off guard
and got me under a massive net.
You plotted this?
Yes.
I was wondering just now
how could you be knocked off easily
by a Blue Start Association member
since you're so powerful.
I didn't think too much
since I remembered Li Mu
had told us everyone is talented here.
You stopped me from getting the Tombstone?
Yes.
I asked Song Tingyu to distract you.
You had been taking advantage of me.
Alright.
If you still want the Tombstone,
go and get it.
You helped Qin Lie to stop me
just because I had lied to you?
You lied to me today.
Are we even now?
No.
I lied to you, not for revenge.
I always know what you're like.
I know what you desire.
Since...
Since you know I want the Tombstone,
why would you help Qin Lie then?
I didn't want you to make any more mistakes.
Shaoyang,
I know what it is like
to be betrayed by someone.
You get to know now.
Qin Lie still chose to stay with you
after so many betrayals.
I don't want you to regret it.
Regret what?
He never takes me as his friend.
I never want to stay with him.
We're destined to be enemies.
From what I observed,
you trusted each other at Nebula Pavilion.
You worked well together in the Armament Sect.
You are good brothers
who get each other's back.
Shaoyang,
why can't you give up those grudges?
When you both achieve great things,
you can have a good competition then.
I'll be there to cheer for you.
Why don't you care about me?
I've been turned into a snake.
When can I recover my body?
Don't you worry that
I might be cooked in a soup?
Lianrou, I miss you.
Better hide somewhere then.
She now has the Tombstone.
I come to save you. How could you talk to me like this?
You are Qin Lie?
Who else would I be then?
You come to save me?
I come to save you
because I'm strapped for cash.
I didn't have enough spirit stones.
I'm wondering maybe
I can take them away if you die.
I've got the Demon Sealing Tombstone. Take it.
Transfer your energy onto it
and see if it reacts to it.
Either this is a fake
or I'm not Gongmu Lie.
That's impossible.
Of course you're not.
I'm Gongmu Lie.
From the Fulfilment Realm?
Don't you want the Tombstone?
Come and get it.
Are you mad?
I just managed to get rid of him.
You're from the Manifestation Realm.
How can you defeat one from the Fulfilment Realm?
They've got endless Terminator Profound Bombs!
Do you fear them? Do I?
We'll fight together
or die together.
Alright.
Let's fight then.
It's so very touching.
Tell you what, I really can't stand
a loving couple.
Don't be ridiculous.
Fight or not?
Man,
you're my hero.
I admire this beauty, too.
A perfect match.
I've got the Demon Sealing Tombstone!
Stop there!
You put on such an act with Tang Siqi
just to distract Du Shaoyang
and buy me time to get the Tombstone?
When did I give myself away?
If Tang Siqi were in danger,
how could you not save her
but hurry to the gate of the Graveyard instead?
So, you knew this was a trap.
But you still came with me.
Did you fear that I might run into danger
in the Graveyard?
Song Tingyu,
let me warn you again.
Don't try to be clever with me.
It's so annoying.
There's danger behind the door.
What is it?
Aren't they supposed to be dead?
It looks like
they don't think they're dead.
I don't have eyes.
I can't see your face.
Who's talking?
I don't have ears.
I can't hear your voices.
It seems to come from behind the door.
How would you know
there was danger behind the door?
I just knew.
I got a strange feeling
as soon as I came here.
It's so weird.
We need to find Yiyuan as soon as possible. Otherwise,
it will be a disaster if they break in.
Lianrou,
I miss you so much
at the moment.
None of them came back for me.
You will
if you are here.