♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 25
Let go of my mother.
Now that you kneel down, what about a kowtow to amuse us?
Do you think your dignity's more important than her life?
Mother!
♫ The past can't be blown away; the moonlight can't be forgotten ♫
Run away.
Hurry.
Mother!
Let's see the doctor, okay, mother?
I'll kill them!
Mother.
Mother, let me take you home, okay?
Mother!
♫ If the moonlight can't be seen in the heart ♫
♫ You're no longer there looking around ♫
Mother!
♫ KNow things change, dream fairy dreams ♫
♫ It's okay life waxes and wanes like the moon ♫
♫ Forget it ♫
Ashile Sher!
Young Khan.
Did you kill her?
No, I didn't.
It was she...
It's too late.
Sun.
Tegin Sun.
- Tegin Sun.
- Sun.
Find Tegin Sun in all directions.
Hurry.
Guard Alir.
Sun.
Find Tegin Sun.
Hurry. Sun.
No!
Mother!
Sher.
Mother, are you okay?
Step aside.
No, Sun.
I'm begging you.
For the sake of my relationship with Alir for years, I'm begging you.
Don't hurt Sher.
Ashile Sun,
Alir died because of me.
Just kill me.
Don't hurt my mother.
No.
I'm his mother.
I can die for him.
Don't hurt him.
No!
Mother.
It's okay.
Sher, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Khatun.
Khatun, are you okay?
Guards, take Ashile Sun.
Sun.
Eagle Division Vanguard is here.
Take Tegin back.
Who dares ask for troubles?
Guards, escort Khatun and Young Khan back.
Don't let them go.
- Take Sher down.
- Yes.
Sun.
Su Yishe.
Piss off.
Sun, calm down.
Sun.
Calm down?
I told you not to act recklessly. Did you listen to me?
If you hadn't been stubborn, how could it be like this?
If you hadn't been stubborn, how could my mother have died?
Mu Jin, take him away.
Assemble the Wolf Division and chase them.
Wait, let them go.
The capital was in chaos, and Khatun was badly hurt.
How can you account for this?
Chase them back.
Go.
Stop.
What's up?
Mu Jin, there's a dry river bed.
You can hide inside.
And Shiba, protect Alir's body.
What about you?
I'll take the troop to the right.
You wanna distract the Wolf Division?
Yes.
After I distract them, take Sun to see a doctor.
No.
After Sun wakes up, he'll blame me.
No, he won't.
I caused his mother's death, and involved Eagle Division.
He must hold a grudge against me.
It's too risky.
Mu Jin, Eagle Division is inseparable from Sun.
You're the only one who can protect Sun.
He'll be clear of the charges Sher accused him of
when Great Khan's back.
Only you can protect Sun well.
Go.
There's no time. Go!
Eagle Division Vanguard, listen to Military Counsellor Li.
Yes.
Go.
Eagle Division Vanguard, go ahead with me.
Wake up, bastard!
Don't sleep.
Go.
Stop.
Military Counsellor, what's up?
Listen to my order, in line with Ashile Tribe's rules,
captives from their own tribe won't be killed.
If Wolf Division arrives, don't resist desperately.
Surrender once being caught.
For the sake of Eagle Division and Tegin Sun, save yourselves.
What about you?
They won't let go of me for I released Luo Yi.
Don't worry about me. I'll run away then.
But...
Remember what I said.
Save yourself.
I'm not under Eagle Division now.
Don't worry about me.
Go.
- Chase them respectively.
- Yes.
Go.
What's wrong?
What happened to Tegin?
Mu Jin, what happened to Tegin?
Go find witch doctor.
I'll go now.
Witch doctor.
Mu Jin.
Mu Jin, wait.
What's wrong with Tegin Sun?
Where's Changge?
Why isn't Changge back with you?
I've no time to explain to you.
Where's she?
Put me down.
Tegin Sun.
Sun.
Where's my mother?
We've taken Alir's body back.
I wanna see her.
Mu Jin, take me to see her.
Mother.
I failed to protect you well.
I know father took you hostage
and connived at Sher's fight with me.
I thought as long as...
as long as I pretend not caring much about you, you'd not be involved.
But I was wrong.
If I had known it,
I'd bring you back even if I disobey Father
or give up everything.
The victory or loss is far less important
than the well-being of families and clansmen.
Mother, you may rest assured.
From now on, I won't be reckless,
or do things causing killing sprees.
Now I just want to protect the ones I want to protect
from sufferings like you.
Please rest assured.
I can only pay my debt of gratitude to you in my next life.
Take the medicine.
Sit down.
What about others?
Su Yishe and other men are captured by Wolf Division,
but not in danger.
What about Li Changge?
Did she return to Central Plains?
She...
She got separated from Su Yishe.
I've sent men to find her.
Luo Shiba went as well.
Got separated?
What do you mean?
Tell me.
She distracted Wolf Division's soldiers.
Now... Now she's missing.
Sun, you haven't recovered.
You've to have a rest.
I must find her.
Don't stop me.
Sun.
Changge finally secured your life.
Are you asking for death?
I've lost my mother.
I can't lose her.
She's unfamiliar with grasslands.
She can't survive.
Li Changge said you must keep alive,
and can't make her efforts in vain.
Neither can I.
I've sent all men to find her.
I'll go as well, and keep you abreast of news.
You must be alive to wait for her return.
Mimi.
Where're you going?
I wanna find Changge.
How can you find her without knowing her position?
Everyone's looking for her.
Why can't I?
Being out of the capital, Changge must be heading for Eagle Division.
I believe as long as she's alive,
she'll even crawl her way to meet me.
I wanna find her.
Let me accompany you.
How's it going with Khatun?
Thank Sirius.
Finally the arrow was taken out.
Khatun's out of danger.
Great.
Young Khan, it's not convenient for you to step close.
Now that Khatun's out of danger, you may as well go back first.
All of you can step in and out to help and look after her except me.
Young Khan, we're all grateful for Khatun's kindness in daily life.
In such a clutch, we'll take good care of her for sure.
Young Khan, don't worry.
If Great Khan knows you're standing here, Khatun will be in trouble.
Just go back.
I'll go.
Young Khan as I am,
I've no right to visit my mother.
I'm not Young Khan at all.
Threatening me with a woman, Sher, you're a coward!
Mother!
Ashile Sun,
how could we be like this?
What've we been doing all these years for?
If I were not Young Khan, and you hadn't gone to Eagle Division,
would we be friends?
Young Khan.
Most of the cavalry of Eagle Division
breaking into the capital have been captured in prison.
Where's Ashile Sun?
We didn't find him in the pursuit.
According to the scout, he returned to Eagle Division.
I know he won't die that easily.
This time, we lost the golden chance to kill him.
It'll be much harder for us to kill him.
It seems you're more desperate to kill him than me.
Isn't it our goal to uproot Eagle Division?
Is your heart softened?
I...
No, it isn't.
Don't you forget Great Khan's expectation of you?
You'll never be satisfied with being outperformed
by Ashile Sun, right?
I don't know if you can meet Khatun after defeating Ashile Sun,
but I can tell for sure.
If you can't win, Great Khan'll never allow you to meet Khatun.
Don't forget without Khatun's protecting you from the arrow,
Ashile Sun's arrow'd have pierced your throat.
Did he show mercy on you?
Young Khan, the kindness to the enemy is the cruelty to yourself.
If Khatun hadn't been that lucky,
you'd have lost your mother forever today.
Enough.
I don't need you to remind me.
Where's Li Changge?
When we surrounded her, a skilled swordsman
suddenly popped up from nowhere.
Is he from Eagle Division?
No.
He's dressed like a man from Central Plains.
I followed them secretly.
Judging from the donkey's hooves, they went straight south
instead of heading for Eagle Division.
Does anyone else know about it?
Except the men searching for her from Wolf Division, no one knows.
Changge,
where're you?
Though she's a woman, she's a hero,
and a true warrior in Eagle Division.
All the men in Eagle Division will remember her.
I don't want her to be a hero.
I just hope she can return safe and sound.
She will.
She likes Eagle Division and you so much.
She'll return anyway.
She's a bastard never knowing how to take care of herself,
but only knowing to press herself.
Mu Jin, I'm really afraid.
Changge shouldn't die.
I believe she'll be okay for sure.
Yes, you're right.
- Maybe our men have found her and taken her back, right?
- Yes.
Maybe she's in Eagle Division now.
Let me take you back.
If you hadn't been stubborn, how could it be like this?
If you hadn't been stubborn, how could my mother have died?
I didn't mean it.
Sun.
Any news?
With so many men having searched so many places,
if she hasn't been found, she may have been captured by Wolf Division.
If so, what's your plan?
How's it going with my mother?
Don't worry.
Khatun's getting better.
She just took the medicine and fell asleep.
Alright.
- You may leave.
- Yes.
Unexpectedly, it's you.
You still remember the previous password.
I didn't mean to kill Alir.
In fact, I...
You killed my mother.
Don't mention her!
It's... It's an accident.
Accident?
My mother died for your accident.
Sher,
is victory or loss that important to you?
Isn't it important?
Because you're the one who always wins.
Ashile Sher, till when can you understand?
Whether Young Khan or Tegin, it's not only a title,
but also the responsibility on our shoulders
for the future of the grassland.
At this point, you're still talking about the false
and ridiculous victory with me.
Naive!
Since our childhood, you've always been so naive.
The moment my mother passed away, no,
even now, I wish I could tear you to pieces.
But I won't.
Because I can't change anything by killing you.
I can't get my mother back by killing you.
Understand?
Revenge and killing
can only bring endless pains and fights.
I've nothing left to talk to you.
Let go of my men in Eagle Division and Li Changge.
Just target at me.
You've got the wrong person.
I can release the men in Eagle Division,
but Li Changge isn't in my hand.
What?
Wolf Division didn't capture her, believe it or not.
Where did she go?
I don't know!
The grassland is full of dangers, with quicksand, swamp,
poisonous snakes and beasts.
She runs away alone.
Do you think it's possible for her to survive?
I experienced life and death with her.
She can't die so easily.
Go find her yourself!
Don't be so worried.
Sun.
Any news?
Sher said Changge wasn't in his hand.
How can you believe in Sher?
It seems not to be a lie.
Did Changge really have an accident?
No.
I believe she won't die so easily.
Yes.
Changge won't die this easily.
Let's find her until we make it.
She is awake.
As I said, she may not live long, but she won't die this soon.
Who're you?
Where am I?
Don't you remember?
No, I don't.
Unbelievable.
Her head didn't get injured.
How come?
It's unreasonable.
Alright.
If you don't remember, let me tell you.
I'm Situ Langlang, a swordsman.
This is Taoist Sun, my creditor.
We just passed by.
I saved you a half-dead from Ashile Tribe,
and he found ways to save you a half-dead.
That's it.
No need to say something like
repaying our favors even after your death.
We get used to healing the wounded and rescuing the dying.
Li Changge, how powerful do you think you're?
Now Luo Yi's dead.
You got yourself, Eagle Division and I involved.
It's the result of your stubbornness.
If you hadn't been stubborn, how could my mother have died?
Leave me alone.
Sorry, Sun.
I caused your mother's death.
- Ask Sher here.
- Yes.
What?
Who told you to report to Great Khan?
For such a big deal, others will report to Great Khan if I won't.
It's my duty not to get Wolf Division involved.
But...
But Alir is my mother's slave.
What if mother gets involved?
It depends on how you explain to Great Khan.
What you said is the fact.
Great Khan'll believe you.
But Alir died because of me.
Why must you... Why must you keep it in mind?
She's just a slave.
Just?
I haven't been able to meet mother for years.
It was Alir who sent letters for us,
so that we can know about each other.
Mother and I owe a debt of gratitude to her.
I acted so recklessly that I threatened Ashile Sun with Alir.
I regret it very much.
What's more, Alir is Ashile Sun's foster mother.
Why can't I return her favor?
You remember her favor,
but forget Khatun's sufferings and tears for years?
How has Great Khan treated Khatun?
Don't you know it?
As long as you have power, you'll soon get reunited with Khatun,
and free her from sufferings.
Ashile Sun is the biggest obstacle to
your grasp of the supreme power in the grassland.
Your mercy on him is your mercilessness on Khatun.
You can't be swayed by his words.
Young Khan, Great Khan asked to see you.
Uncle Khan, I'm sorry for my neglect of duty.
I beg your pardon.
As for Luo Yi, I've killed him.
Please go check with me, Uncle Khan.
Assemble all the crack soldiers in Wolf Division,
prepare bows and crossbows, and go with me.
What for?
Ashile Sun rescued the capture of Tang
and shot Khatun when I was away.
I can't keep such an alienated guy anymore.
Uncle Khan.
I've a thing to report.
Eat first.
You don't sleep, drink or eat.
Before being punished by Great Khan, you'll collapse first.
What's this?
It shows the pastures and waters I found before.
If... If one day the capital forsakes Eagle Division,
move our men out to these places.
Sun, I know what your plan is.
There's no if.
You won't be with our Eagle Division later?
Are you gonna settle everything here and then leave, aren't you?
I'm busy now.
Go out.
I won't.
Are you gonna shoulder all things alone?
What do you think of me?
What do you think of our men in Eagle Division?
- Tegin.
- What's up?
According to our scout, the men from the capital are coming
with banners of Great Khan and Wolf Division.
They will be here soon.
There seems no need for my explanation.
Sun, what about assembling all the cavalry?
No.
A war can only badly undermine Eagle Division.
I'll protect each and every one of you.
Mu Jin,
remember, no matter what you see or hear later, don't act recklessly.
Listen to my orders.
Besides,
prepare to welcome a new Tegin.
In Eagle Division, I only claim Ashile Sun as our leader.
All men in Eagle Division only claim you as our Tegin, Ashile Sun.
Do as I ordered.
Tegin.
I know what you're coming for.
Father, for our years of relationship,
please spare lives of others in Eagle Division.
Stand up.
Let's talk inside the tent.
I know what happened to Alir.
Sun,
you suffered a lot.
I received a letter on the third day of my hunting.
It said Eagle Division helped Luo Yi out, fought with Wolf Division,
and shot Khatun.
On hearing it, I was so furious that I even wanna kill you myself.
But Sher told me what happened in detail.
It was good of you two to compete for Luo Yi,
but held a grudge against each other for credit.
Sun, I know you'd not hurt Khatun on purpose.
Anyway, Alir died because of Sher.
It was his fault.
Sher, apologized to Sun.
I shot Khatun, so I deserve the punishment.
Why're you doing so?
It's not your fault.
I'll justify you.
Thanks, father.
Sun, stand up.
This time I took lots of supplies and weapons from the capital,
and gave them all to Eagle Division.
I know these can't make it up to you,
but now, a dead man can't come back to life.
This time, I took the Wizard with me.
I'll let him pray for Alir.
I'll pray for Alir as well.
Sun, what else do you want?
Just tell me.
Your foster mother passed away, but your father who loves you
will always be by your side.
I've a thing to ask for your permission.
I'll approve of whatever you want.
My mother had always
been eager to visit some further places,
but hadn't found a chance to in these years.
She's no longer here now.
I wanna fulfill her last wish, and visit the world at large.
If you can find someone suitable to take over Eagle Division,
please let him take good care of it.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad