Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The "No Touch" Team 👑 @ Viki
[Mr. Queen: The Secret]
The characters, organizations, and events in this drama are unrelated to any historical facts and all stories are fictional.
I, Court Lady Choi, have lived in the palace for 30 years.
I'm seeing through everything in this palace.
Not only the secrets of all the people in the palace,
even the other side story of all the hectic incidents happening.
I can assure you that there is nothing I don't know in this palace.
I want to go back~!
But I really can't understand why Her Majesty the Queen is acting like that...
Your Majesty...?
Inside the palace, everyone has a secret.
To reveal, it's too trivial. But to cover it up, you get so curious.
Those trivial secrets will now be unfolded.
[The Secret of Male Friends]
... Anti-Fan... Good Morning... Mission... Sexy, Cute and Innocent... Show Window...
... Republic of Korea - Joseon's future, Gold Spoon/Dirt Spoon - Confirming the class, Vote - Once over 18 years old...
There are still many words which meaning I don't know.
There is no other choice but to meet the Queen and ask her myself.
Your Majesty.
Why are you coming out of that room?
I just came to have a chat with Her Majesty.
Do you not have any work to do?
What's your job?
- I'm belonging to the delegation department.
- Then, leave immediately.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Run!
I'll definitely see her today—
What brings you here again, Director of Uigeumbu? (Royal Investigation Bureau)
Then, what brings you here, Your Majesty?
Is any specific reason required when a husband visits his wife?
I also just came to check if Her Majesty is doing well.
Then.
The Queen is doing alright.
Gosh, what a pitiful guy he is.
They say the early bird gets the worm.
Today, I will definitely—
Oh, Y-Y-Your Majesty...
- Even you, Head Chef?
- Ah, yes.
Ah, well, what brings you here this early in the morning?
Don't you need to sleep?
Well, as I get older, I lose my early morning sleep.
Prepare my meal.
Already?
Today, I'd like to have a big feast table.
A big feast table for your breakfast?
Hurry up, this is your penalty!
Officer Hong!
- His Majesty the King is here!
- Alright! One more!
- Let's do one more round.
- Okay, let's do it again.
Starting with i-eung and ji-eut. (a vowel and 'J' sound)
- Yeong-jeong. (meaning 'crush')
- That's right, there was Yeong-jeong.
- U-jeong. (meaning 'friendship')
- Oh, right!
- I've got one!
Yeol-jeong! (meaning 'passion')
Ah, now you've failed! it's you again.
- Oh, there is O-jum. (meaning 'urine')
- Come on!
- This is your penalty! Yeah!
- This is wrong!
Who doesn't take a piss? Argh!
- O-jum!
- Penalty!
- Yay!
- Oh, gosh!
(without honorifics) You're here?
You're here, Your Majesty.
I was going to go to Cheonjeongjeon, but took a wrong turn.
Ae-Jeong! (meaning 'love')
- Hey, give up your back, you need more beatings.
- Oh, come on!
How come your beating is so painful?
Next to the queen, there are always men around her.
- Yes, yes!
- Gosh, one more round!
Not there! Please, not there!
Aren't we just acquainted? Oh, please...
As expected, rather than food for mind, food for hormones are the best.
But, this romance novel is just at the level of middle schoolers.
Your Majesty,
you mustn't keep reading such books like that.
I have to practise reading as I'm learning Eon-mun. (meaning 'Hangeul', Korean letters)
Oh, not yet, yes.
Oh! Wow.
Wait wait wait wait, let me read it just one more time.
God!
Your Majesty, His Majesty the King is here.
What are you reading so intently?
-Oh, do you want to read it too?
-AH
-Oh that surprised me.
RAT! RAT!
There was a rat the size of a calf.
So I'm so sorry for surprising everyone, Your Majesty.
Well if it's the size of a calf, then it must be a calf, why is it a rat?
Wait, where did it go? The thing I was reading?
Your Majesty, it's time to go back to your quarters.
-Right, is everyone there?
-Everyone?
- It seems like you have an appointment.
- Yup.
- With whom?
- Someone.
Obviously.
But I meant if you had just one or more.
What do you want to ask?
Just ask it frankly.
I'm not empathetic enough to read your hidden intentions.
There isn't any hidden intention, though.
- There is!
- I told you, there isn't.
Are you sulking now?
Sulking!? Kings are never sulking!
I'm just, here to get a book I need,
Don't bother me.
Oh, here it is.
The book I was looking for.
"As Eunuch Kim unties my coat string, my mind was also—." What?
Wha-What is this?
Finally, we found something in common.
Our hobbies are the same.
- 'We'?
- Then, enjoy your food for hormones. See you.
Wait,
I want to ask you something.
What?
It's nothing much
But you know, the person that you cherish the most,
who is that?
Hong Yeon.
And our Court Lady Choi, too.
That's not what I meant.
Everyone, leave us alone for a moment. Get out.
- Yes, your majesty.
- Quickly!
Not backwards, but turn around and quickly go out!
What is it about so that you take so much time?
Please answer truthfully.
- It depends on the question.
- If you wouldn't be truthful, then I won't speak.
- Then, don't.
- M-M-Men! Among men, whom do you cherish the most?
Jang Bong-hwan.
Who is that?
Who is he...?
The one and only perfect man in the world.
He's the most charming man I know.
I mean it. He doesn't have a single thing missing.
Looks are looks, personality is personality
And that amazing knife skills of his...
The ultimate existence who is even perfect in books too.  Damn, he's the best.
He's always refreshing, so thrilling!
Then, why aren't you with such a man you're cherishing?
Exactly!
Because I couldn't be with him, it's more ardent, more regrettable and more heartrending.
It's driving me crazy, really.
Are you sighing because of that man, Jang Bong-hwan!?
Because of your longing for him, do you even lose sleep and feel lonely?
Wait, are you being jealous?
How cute.
Cute?
What? Why? What is it?
You're right, it is jealousy.
You're not public goods for everybody. So please no longer use the word, 'we', recklessly.
It's a royal command.
I don't want you to be called 'my cousin' or 'our Queen', either.
Also, am I still cute?
You're cute, very cute, although you can't still beat me.
What's this cliché of heart-throbbing moment, which was used 5 trillion and 5 hundred times already for romance comic books?
My heart would never get fluttered by this—
Or not?
DEFCON Level 1!
Pardon me?
This won't do, I have to confirm it.
Confirm it?
Whether this is my body's mind or my soul's mind.
I should... confirm... it...
Let's do it, confirm.
♫ Like the faded moonlight ♫
Why do I like it? It angers me.
♫ That is covered by the cloud  ♫
Argh, don't do it, Kim So-yong. Don't do it, don't do it!
Don't do it, don't!
Is this angering you that much?
Ah, I'm not supposed to be like this, damn it.
I'm also not supposed to be like this.
♫ And at the moment your beautiful face is also soaked in  ♫
♫ The stars sparkling in your eyes  ♫
♫ Fell into my heart too  ♫
In the library, there are so many interesting books like this.
But there is nothing more interesting than the true nature of elders in the palace.
Inside the palace, everyone has a secret.
To reveal, it's too trivial. But to cover it up, you get so curious.
Those trivial secrets will now be unfolded.
[The Secret of Siblings in Real Life]
[Grand Queen Dowager Sunwon]
[Kim Jwa-geun]
[Kim Mun-geun]
If I get a tiger stick now, that will be perfect.
By the way, I heard about a huge incident that a tiger attacked the town in Gyeongsang Province.
Oh, she must need a tiger stick.
A bigger problem is the rumour that the people are feeling the unusual spirit of dragon floating in the sky.
So, he needs a dragon stick.
No matter which stick I give up, I'm screwed.
What are you doing? You should give up one stick.
Where is the gambler gone?
The thing is... As this game is so nerve-wracking,
my heart feels like mun-geun, mun-geun, you know?
(sounds similar to 'softy and clotty')
In fact, if I put down a wrong stick,
you two seem to chew me up jwa-geun, jwa-geun. (T/N: sounds similar to a Korean mimetic word, 'jal-geun, jal-geun', the way of chewing)
He said, his heart feels like mun-geun, mun-geun,
and you two chew up jwa-geun, jwa-geun.
Court Lady Cheon!
Is that funny?!
I'm sorry.
Hurry up and play your stick! Her Royal Highness is waiting for you!
Damn!
Oh dear... Because of my hand's sweat, I happened to drop two sticks.
This round went wrong, so let's reshuffle them and start it over.
We can't do that!
You're absolutely right, Your Highness.
As the courtesy of a younger brother, why don't you yield?
As the courtesy of an older sister, why don't you yield?
As I was born a woman, I've lived my entire life conceding everything for you.
Every since you became the queen, you've monopolized all the fame and honour of family. Have you forgotten it?
I carried you on my back and raised you, and this is how you pay me?
I don't know about that, but all the memories I have are serving you, Sister.
Well, well, well, please don't fight.
The blood runs much thicker than these mere game sticks.
[Dragon / Tiger]
Ever since we were little, whenever we play games, I've always argued and gotten angry with you, Brother.
Because both of us are so competitive.
That's right.
No matter how much we get older, I'm just a child in front of you, Sister.
I'll concede, take it, Brother.
No, you should take it first, Sister.
You do it, Brother.
You do it, Sister.
Oh my, you two are...
The competitiveness that you don't want to lose,
and even the wildness when you concede.
Anyone can say that you two are siblings.  You two look alike so much.
- There is no way we look alike!
Then... For the sibling's love between you two,
let's say I won this round.
- What do you mean?!
Well...
Gosh...
♫ If it feels like nothing goes as you wish ♫
I really want to go home.
♫ Don't think anything else, but just listen to this ♫
♫ I'm Patrasche who can eat only by running crazy in this life ♫
There is some red energy, coming from the Soutern-East direction and falling down into the palace.
Its intensity is like blaze,
and the river flows reversed,
and the rain of frogs comes down from the sky.
Everyday, some strange incidents are happening.
Due to all these ill-boding omens, everybody is confused and worried.
Among the people, there is a rumour that these are the omen for the world to end soon,
so there are very worrisome.
By any chance,
is the world really about to end?
[The Secret of The End of World]
Tonight, the sky will collapse.
The flames will fall from the sky,
and the entire world will burn in the sea of blaze!
It will become the sea of blaze!
The world might be always ready to be ended.
Whenever it ends, it won't feel strange.
If you have been thinking that way, you should've told me sooner.
If I knew this would happen, I wouldn't have gone through so many hardships,
but just enjoyed my life before my death.
This damnable world...
Still,
I don't think this world will end so easily like this.
Even we, mere lives, are struggling to survive,
so the world can't be so fragile like that.
Therefore, let's stop worrying for no reason and expedite the completion of military strategy book.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Bring the brush and ink.
You're going to squeeze me out until the very last moment?
I won't do it.
Officer Hong.
If today is really the last day of our lives, what are you going to do?
I don't want to die while working until the last moment.
You too, Your Majesty, please consider today is the last day just in case,
and please do whatever you wanted to do.
That's why I'm suggesting to complete this military strategy book,
because this is the work I'd like to finish before I die.
What a fool who knows nothing but works...
Don't you think your words are too harsh?
(without honorifics) Why do you care?
Everything will be over anyway if the world ends.
Did you just drop the honorifics to me?
(without honorifics) That's right, I did!
We all are about to die, so why would I bother with manners?
Calm down, Officer Hong.
(without honorifics) Won-beom, you bastard, youre the worst.  What an evil boss disguised as a friend!
Your Majesty, I've got one thing I should do on the last day of my life.
Even if I die today, I will die after fixing your manners.
(without honorifics) Gosh, yeah, you're older than us, but you're too freaking authoritative.
Moreover, do you really have to be that tall?
You must have eaten all the potatoes by yourself in Ganghwa Island.
Oh, that's cold.
(with honorifics) I've come back to my senses now. My madness is over now.
It's the time of chicken (around 5~7 PM).
Soon, it will be the night.
Will today really be the end?
Where are you going?
I've changed my mind.
If tonight our lives end,
where I should be,
and whom I should be with so that I won't regret.
Gosh, it will be alright, don't worry.
It's okay, nothing will happen.
Still, the rumour is around.
Why do you believe a rumour? It's alright, alright.
Alright, alright.
It's alright, gosh, seriously.
I told you it would be alright.
Why do you believe such a rumour?
His Majesty the King is here.
Are you also worried if the world would end, so that you couldn't sleep?
What end of the world?  As they are too worried, I'm calming them down.
You know, I can't just pass by the worries of women.
You're kind.
Head Chef!
What are you doing this late, instead of going home?
Your Majesty...
Is there something nice going on?
Our Man-bok was that scared to die?
Man-bok was scared—, damn!
You keep saying that to confuse me, although I said my eyes got teary while cutting green onions.
Oh, you did? Yes, yes, alright.
I'm through all the rumours in the palace,
but how come I alone didn't know about the end of world?
By the way, it has been a while since the night fell.
Gosh, it's too cold.
See? Nothing happened.
Geez, I got a bit worried for no reason too. Let's go, go.
The Queen is right,
you all stop worrying for nothing and go back to your quarters.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Let's go.
Your Majesty! T-T-That is...?
It's the meteor shower.
The Meteor shower? Are you saying that's rain?
How beautiful the end of world is...
Please allow me to go back to my original healthy body.
Please don't let my body lose any muscles while lying down in a vegetative state.
My Queen?
Ah, when there is meteor shower like that, if you make a wish, that wish will come true.
Make a wish, make a wish, a wish!
Make a wish.
A w-wish?
And for Cheoljong too, longer and longer than the history said,
please let him live happily ever after
like the prince in fairy tales.
In the next life, please,
please let me born as a rock.
Why a rock?
So that I can live comfortably, doing nothing.
Then, when I'm born again, I'll kick that rock away.
♫ That's why I'm telling you now ♫
♫ So that you wouldn't know  ♫
In my next life, please let me be Her Majesty the Queen's mother,
so that I can definitely succeed
in the rehabilitation of Her Majesty.
In my next life, please let me be Her Majesty's older sister,
so that Her Majesty won't feel lonely.
It was a nice life this time.
I wish my next life is exactly same as this life.
If I'm born again in the next life...
♫ I want to embrace you in my arms ♫
I told you to make a wish, but all of you seem to wish for the next life.
What did you wish to be born again?
No matter how much I thought, I don't want to be born again.
True, if one pours too much in the current life, he would get sick of being born again.
Even if everything is hard, it's alright,
as I know you're putting a lot of efforts.
How much you're trying to not collapse.
But, still, I wish you're born again.
As I've lived the second round of lives, there is something like this.
Those trivial things like, 'How wronged must I have felt if I didn't know this?'
True, how wronged must I have felt,
if I didn't get to meet such a strange person like you, my Queen,
before my life now ended?
Who knows? I might appear in front of you in an unexpected and absurd shape.
So, you should be definitely born again.
You're already unexpected enough.
♫ Even I stretch my arm, I can't reach you ♫
♫ The only confession that I give you ♫
All my family, who left me at the same time, on the same day,
I wish I can meet them in the heaven at least...
♫ I want to embrace you in my arms ♫
♫ But it's okay even if I can't ♫
♫ You're the reason why I want to have a dream ♫
Are you alright?
♫ To you who is asleep, leaning on my shoulder ♫
Did you make a wish alright?
I have one more wish, though.
Although it won't work now,
in the distant future,
with the person I miss,
♫ As always, those two eyes like a child's ♫
I'd like to watch the sunset far away over there,
together with her.
♫ Without knowing any of my mind ♫
♫ They just stare at me ♫
♫ You know, whenever you look at me like that ♫
It would've been nice if she were with us.
♫ I want to hug you tightly ♫
♫ Will you know my crumbling mind? ♫
♫ You're the reason why I want to open my eyes ♫
♫ Lean on my shoulder now ♫
♫ I'm showing my feelings after a long time ♫
♫ I love you ♫
♫ To my one and only you ♫
What's with this mood?
No dating within the company, you know?
(T/N: 'Sa-nae' = 'within the company')
How can men date each other?
(T/N: 'Sanae' = 'man')
Oh, my 'sa-nae' doesn't mean that 'sanae' though...
I, this man, am a sinful man...
I, this woman, am a sinful woman.
No dating within the company.
If I'm born again, I wish I can meet the Queen again.
Even if we misunderstand, hate, and argue,
I wish we can recognize each other in the end.
Not as the king and the queen, but as So-yong and Won-beom, I wish we can meet again.
Dismissed! Dismissed, dismissed.
- Dismissed, dismissed.
- Your Majesty.
The flames are falling like that now.
What if there are some huge fire accidents somewhere?
We're doomed, doomed.
Fire all over the places...
Ah, gosh, I'm telling you, it won't end!
Even if you scream hundreds of times at the world to end, it won't end.
See? Even if everything is in a mess, the world is running well somehow.
Seriously, it's freaking sturdy, this damnable world.
Although it's a damnable world, it will never end, eh?
Geez...
[Mr. Queen: The Secret]
Final Credits
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by The "No Touch" Team 👑 @ Viki