♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 23=
Aren't you their comrade?
Why aren't you following them?
Aren't you their friend?
Why don't you go then?
How are we going to find the Sand Beast
when the sandstorm is so strong?
We should be able to find it
if we head to the place
where the sandstorm is dense.
Let's untie the rope first.
If we can't contact each other later,
just escape by teleporting
right away, all right?
Listen to me, okay?
You can't move any further at all.
It sounds like it's somewhere nearby.
Your child is with me.
It's not working.
It's here.
Wu, stay back.
Don't go there!
It's furious right now.
It's holding itself back because
you're still holding its kid.
What should I do then?
We can't communicate with it at all.
It's very agitated right now.
We still have to give it a try.
We mean no harm.
Your kid is with me.
I'll put him down now.
Wu, teleport now!
No!
I told you to listen to me.
We really didn't harm it at all.
We are not lying.
The sandstorm subsided.
Wu, are you okay?
Brother, I'm fine.
Let's go back.
Tang San!
Brother San!
Wu!
Ou Si Ke.
Sister Wu!
Ma Hong Jun.
Brother San.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Where are Headmaster and others?
Why are you guys here?
I... I don't know.
Never mind, let's talk after we go back.
Let's go.
Come on.
The sandstorm subsided.
Everybody is safe now.
There are so many people here.
Hu Lie Na is here as well.
Good job.
You're quite good.
Take a break
before you proceed with the test.
I don't need a break. I can go
with you guys right away.
What test is he talking about?
You're here to wait for them?
I've seen your ability.
You have the potential.
Does that mean...
he doesn't have to go into the arena?
Let me test you using another way.
What should I do?
Now,
you have to kill the person
who caused the sandstorm.
Hold on.
You promised to keep me alive.
I won't do anything to you.
He will be the one
who is going to kill you.
It... it was a careless mistake.
I don't deserve to die!
You'll pass the test if you kill him.
It's simple, right?
He's right.
The sandstorm was just an accident.
He deserves to be punished,
but not enough to be killed.
I know I'm at fault.
I'll take the responsibility
to rebuild Xi Si City.
Don't you think you deserve to die?
Don't look at me like that.
You said you want to
be on the same front with us,
how can we believe you
if you don't kill him?
Stop hesitating.
Kill him and finish the test.
I quit.
Tang San, don't act recklessly.
You'd better think this through.
This is your only chance
to join us.
Just consider that I failed my test.
Let him go.
Your friend is really disappointing.
Royal family.
What are you doing?
I said I wanted to quit.
I'll kill him if you don't have
the guts to do so.
Remember what you see today.
This is what will happen to
those who are against us.
I can't believe
Officer Ye Zhi Qiu
would appreciate such a weak guy like you.
Let's go.
Wait a minute.
Are you trying to make up for it?
It's too late.
I saw a lot of corpses being exposed
under the sunlight
on my way to Xi Si City.
You were the ones who did that?
You're right.
Those are the people we defeated.
They deserved to die.
I heard people crying
in the city,
because you guys
killed their family.
You think having power
means justice.
However, in the eyes of others,
you guys are just
a bunch of blood-sucking beasts.
You guys are the cause of despair.
What are you trying to say?
I want to challenge you all
at the Soul Arena Competition.
I told you
that you've failed your test.
This has nothing to do with the test.
I want to destroy you guys head-on
and chase people like you
out of Xi Si City.
Tang San, are you crazy?
Cruelty will not bring hope.
I will save this city.
All right.
One day later,
I'll be waiting for you
in the Soul Arena.
I would love to see
how you are going to defeat me
and how you are going to
save this city.
Luckily Headmaster knows how to fly.
That was why he found us.
Fortunately, the sandstorm stopped.
Otherwise, I won't be able
to save so many people.
Master,
is Zhu Zhu Qing really all right?
You asked this question a dozen times.
He's worried about you.
She's fine.
She'll be fine after a few days of rest.
Where are Tang San and Wu?
They might be in the inn.
They don't know
any other places, anyway.
Come on in.
You guys are really here.
What happened to you guys?
What happened?
Why are your clothes so dirty?
What's wrong?
Did you get caught in the sandstorm?
What happened?
We buried
a body here just now.
What's going on?
There's...
There's a Fiend Battle Team in this city.
They killed someone
from the Royal family here earlier.
Ma Xiu Nuo.
Where are Tang San and Wu?
Where did they go?
They...they went out.
What is exactly happening?
If the mastermind behind
Ye Zhi Qiu and his people
is really my father,
what should I do?
I've always thought
that I would take his side
no matter what he did.
However, now...
Now what?
Now, I really hope that
those people from the Fiend Battle Team
are not his men.
Without any conviction,
they killed people
based on their identity.
They also kill people who are against them.
They're all crazy.
What they're doing is wrong.
Is it possible that Ye Zhi Qiu is lying?
It's also possible
that Grand Hao Tian Master
simply has the name as Uncle Tang.
Moreover,
you told me about him previously.
All he did were sleeping, drinking
and forging iron.
Plus, I've seen Uncle Tang before.
He doesn't look like
a bad guy at all.
I have no idea.
Coming to think of it,
it seems that the father I knew
is nothing like him.
How was he like
in real life then?
That's what I'd like to know.
I worked hard to become stronger
so that I can find him
and know him.
I must go to Tian Dou City.
It doesn't matter
even if I fail the test.
I will find the man behind
Cang Hui School.
If it's really him,
I'll try to convince him.
I can't let him go down the wrong road.
What if
he refuses to listen?
I will stop him.
I will.
I'll go with you.
I'm his son.
However, I don't even know
if I've made the right choice.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Good luck.
You must win the battle.
What do you mean?
It doesn't matter whether you win the battle,
but you must stay alive.
Yes, you must come back alive.
Take care of yourself.
You've made the right choice.
I will beat the Fiend Battle Team.
I just came back from the Soul Arena.
Although the Fiend Battle Team
had the place under control,
I still managed to find out
some of their information
and achievements.
The majority of the people from the Fiend
Battle Team have Quadruple Soul Rings.
They're people who stand out the most
even if they're from other Soul Master Schools.
Our skills are way more lacking
compared to them.
I've asked around.
Although they have a high rank,
their training is not systematic enough.
They're just amateurs.
Basically, their skills
are not as good as
the real Quadruple Soul Rings Soul Sect.
Even so, Tang San is still not a match for them.
Do you have any other ways
to make up for it?
I want to see
how Tang San will deal with them.
How can he do it if you can't do it?
Pressure can make people grow.
So what are you planning to do?
Spread despair.
Sister Qing.
They're all ranked
Quadruple Soul Rings. So what?
Your brother is ranked
Quadruple Soul Rings as well.
Can all of you beat him
even if you join hands?
That's...
The bad news is...
there's no hope in winning at all.
You're going to die
if you go into the arena.
The good news is...
Tang San will be the only one
taking up the challenge.
So there's no need for you guys
to get into the arena.
Is... is this what Headmaster wants?
I'm just telling you guys the truth.
I won't interfere
in anything you do.
Are we clear?
Master made himself very clear.
You'll die if you enter the arena.
Tang San started this mess,
it's none of our business.
What do you mean?
Don't you get it?
You want brother San
to enter the arena alone?
Tang San was the one
who acted recklessly,
does it have anything to do with us?
Dai Mu Bai!
What? Do you want to fight?
Let's fight outside.
Brother Dai!
All of you stay here.
No, don't be angry.
Aren't we going back to the hotel?
There's no need for us to rush.
I'm looking for a smithy.
I saw it somewhere yesterday.
There it is.
Hi, Sir.
We would like to borrow your smithy
to make some fine iron.
May I know what the price is?
Didn't he understand what I said?
I'm not sure.
Are you going to forge iron again?
You saw it yourself.
All the people from the Fiend Battle Team
have Quadruple Soul Rings.
We need some new weapons
to defeat them.
New weapons?
Brother, are you going to
cast sleeve arrows again?
You'll find out soon.
Let's go to another smithy.
Is this enough?
Yes.
I'll make the fire bigger.
Sir, how much does this cost?
I heard you're going to
challenge the Fiend Battle Team.
Yes.
I don't want any money.
I just want you to win.
Don't you think that I'll be afraid of you
just because I can't defeat you.
You know what?
I'm going to enter the arena
with Brother San tomorrow.
Keep it down.
Don't touch me. Let me go!
Of course, I'll do the same.
What are you talking about?
Tang San's Blue Silver Plant
has many uses,
but it's not lethal enough.
I can make up for that weakness.
Moreover, you're a Mutant Soul.
If you go berserk in the arena,
it must be beyond
the Fiend Battle Team's expectation.
You should be able to distract them.
I thought you're going to
ignore Brother San.
I'm the leader of Shi Lan Ke Team.
Do you think I'll leave
my brother alone?
So did you say that on purpose?
Our opponent is too strong.
So it won't affect our team's ability
even if Ou Si Ke and the rest
don't join the battle.
There's no need for them
to get involved as well.
So you're not afraid of dying.
I am afraid of dying?
Count me in.
I can initiate a sneak attack in the arena.
I asked you to stay inside.
That's right.
This is the Random Air Hammer Skill.
That is what Tang San does best.
What is this?
Wu, it's dangerous.
Why is this dangerous?
It's so fast and powerful.
It works pretty well.
Sir, do you have extra iron?
Yes.
I want to cast six more of them.
What are you going to do with them?
Wu, if I fail the challenge,
you must bring this weapon back
to Tian Dou City.
This is to make sure Brother Dai
and the rest are well equipped
when they join
the Soul Master School Contest.
After all, the more weapons they have,
the safer they will be.
Promise me.
You said you have
something important to do
in Xi Si City.
So it's to challenge the Fiend Battle Team?
How are you going to
challenge them without us?
That's right.
Brother Dai, listen to me.
I'll deal with the challenge
on my own.
Don't worry about me.
You guys should leave soon.
Don't let this affect
the Soul Master School Contest.
The opponents are too strong.
How can you beat them without me?
The Seven Devils of
Shi Lan Ken is a team.
Master said we have to
trust our teammates.
So,
we won't leave you and Wu behind.
Brother San.
Sister Wu.
You guys have already fought without us
at Star Town.
Don't ever think of
leaving us behind this time.
Moreover,
I want to know the truth
behind the Mutant Soul.
We'll get one step closer
to finding out the real culprit
by defeating the Fiend Battle Team.
I have something to do with this matter.
So I must go into the arena tomorrow.
Tang San,
you're challenging the Fiend Battle Team
to get closer to Ye Zhi Qiu
and find out who is the person
behind the headquarter, aren't you?
How did you guys know that?
I've always kept my mouth shut.
I didn't tell any of them.
About Ye Zhi Qiu...
Ou Si Ke might have overheard me
when I was talking in my sleep.
I'm from the Support Branch.
I... I can't deal with it myself.
So I have to brainstorm
in order to...
Don't disgrace our Support Branch.
Tang San, forget about how I found out it.
Anyway, I can help you if you want to
do a background check on Ye Zhi Qiu.
Don't forget my identity.
I'm the mighty
little princess of
the Qibao Amber Clan, OK?
This is just a small matter.
After we defeat the Fiend Battle Team
and return to Tian Dou City,
I'll ask my father to help us out.
We can find out right away
what exactly Ye Zhi Qiu
from Cang Hui School wants.
You... you guys...
Is the Qibao Amber Clan
at Tian Dou City?
Of course the clan will be at
the tribe's headquarters.
After all, we're the three elders.
Of course we have people
garrisoned in Tian Dou City.
Also, I sensed
a mysterious dark power
hiding and lurking in the dark.
That was what caused
Ma Hong Jun to lose his family
and Wu to be poisoned.
So what?
Performing justice and protecting the weak
is the mission of us from Shi Lan Ke.
Come on.
Never leave anyone behind
and never give up.
That's great.
It can be said that
the team from Shi Lan Ke School
is officially established
from today onwards.
Boss Lan, let's go.
Don't you want to hear
how they are going to
set up their tactics?
It's not necessary.
This dish, this one
and this one
on this menu.
They are cheap.
You're indeed a good brother of mine.
You even know how to save money for me.
What I meant was to
take out those dishes
and take everything else on the menu.
And also, make sure
the portion is big enough.
We have to make sure that
they get enough breakfast
so that they can stay focused on
defeating the Fiend Battle Team.
Are you trying to let me go bankrupt?
What's wrong?
You look a bit pale.
Didn't you sleep well yesterday?
I have a severe headache.
You have to get some proper sleep tonight.
We still have to fight
a tough battle tomorrow.
Let's go and order the food.
My headache is getting worse.
We'll just do as you say.
Our opponents all have
Quadruple Soul Rings.
We won't have any chance to win
if we use conventional tactics.
So we need to plan out
what tactics we'll use tomorrow.
Don't worry.
Tang San has a special measure.
What is this?
This is called
the Godly Crossbow.
It's a mechanical type of weapon.
It's even better than my sleeve arrow.
Hurry up and show them.
Ou Si Ke.
I'll... I'll stay away.
How did you do that?
This is amazing!
It's so powerful.
I bet it can penetrate through metal.
That's right.
It has high invincibility.
The enemies won't notice it
when you wear them on
your wrist without shooting.
It can attack your enemies suddenly
and catch them off guard.
Be careful with it.
Tang San,
where did you get this from?
I made it.
Did you make this?
How do you know how to make this?
My father is a blacksmith.
Do you have a blueprint for this?
No.
You don't have a blueprint?
Where did you get the source then?
I promised my father
to keep it a secret.
All right.
I get it!
I think
it is because Tang San's father is
a blacksmith.
That's why he must have recorded
the steps to make this weapon.
This is what we call
like father, like son.
You're following in
your father's footsteps, right?
That's right.
Is the principle of using this Godly Crossbow
the same as that of the gold thread weapon
you used previously?
The golden thread
that you mentioned,
I call it the Dragon's Beard.
The working principle is
the same as the sleeve arrow.
You'll need Soul Power
to use the Dragon's Beard,
but that's not the case
for this Godly Crossbow.
Look.
It depends on the springs to work.
It has a mechanical principle.
If you use a good spring,
you won't need
any Soul Power to fire it.
Even an ordinary person
can use it easily.
Based on my calculations,
the possibility for Soul Masters
below the Soul Honour
rank to fend off the blow
from this Godly Crossbow is extremely low.
Moreover, this Godly Crossbow
has a great capability in controlling
Soul Masters beyond the Defence Branch.
Will all of us have these?
I wanted to give these
to all of you as a present
when you guys arrive at Tian Dou City
to help you guys out
at the Soul Master School Contest.
I didn't expect
that all of you would stay with me.
That's great.
By the way, I would need
both of you to work with me tomorrow
to use that tactic.
No problem.
You're the tactical commander
in Shi Lan Ke School.
We'll follow your instructions.
Guys, do you think I'll look
handsome and charming
if I use this crossbow?
Stop flattering yourself.
Please be extra careful.
Please don't use it on other people.
Tang San, teach me
how does this work?
Be careful.
Put this on before you use it.
Tang San,
I've never liked these weapons before.
I thought your tactics won't work
in the arena,
but after experiencing some things,
I got to know that
you're a smart and passionate person.
I shouldn't have ostracized you
just because we use
different methods to deal with stuff.
We must let them know how strong
Shi Lan Ke is in tomorrow's battle.
All right!
We'll gain victory!
Just a heads-up,
we teachers won't be involved
in today's battle.
You have to
depend on yourself to win.
OK! Yes!
Let's get ready.
We'll leave in fifteen minutes.
Let's go.
What's wrong?
She pulled Tang San away alone.
Is there anything wrong?
What's wrong with that?
They're alone!
What do you think
she has to say to him in private?
I don't know.
There must be something going on.
Why are you not worried?
They're just talking to each other.
What is there to worry about?
What do you mean by "they're just talking"?
You're such a fool. I quit.
Just give up.
All of them have Quadruple Soul Rings.
How are you going to beat them?
Don't you know
they'll just simply kill people
in the Soul Arena?
I know that,
but I still want to give it a try.
Even if they're very cruel,
what does it have to do with us?
If everybody thinks the same way as you,
this city will be doomed,
but thank you for your suggestion anyway.
Listen to me.
If you didn't save me previously,
I wouldn't even care about you.
How about we do it this way?
We can leave first,
and I'll send someone
to deal with them later on.
Is that okay?
The longer we wait,
the more people they harm.
The Godly Crossbow only works one time.
It's our only chance.
We'll stall for time and
divert the opponents' attention.
We'll have to kill them in one blow.
You're dragging so many people
to die with you?
Wang Sheng,
you deal with your own friends.
However,
how are we going to
explain this to Officer Ye Zhi Qiu?
I'll give you one last chance.
Join us.
Tang San!
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
Strength Boost! Speed Boost!
As you can see,
Officer Ye Zhi Qiu got the wrong guy.
I'll explain it to him.
Here,
there are no rules, only life or death.
Even if you guys surrender,
we'll hunt you down.
This city belongs to us.
Ou Si Ke! Ning Rong Rong!
The Support Branch
is taking action as well?
Hong Jun!
Phoenix Firing Line!
A fight between two tigers.
This is interesting.
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪