♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 22=
After the mutation,
the force behind the Fiend Battle Team found me.
They told me
that whoever works alone will be bullied.
But if we stick together,
it will be different.
If we are united
and help each other,
our fates could be changed.
That's why you joined the Fiend Battle Team?
Yes.
I can't compare myself to Master Ye.
I can only practice hard
in the Fiend Battle Team first.
After hearing from Master Ye
that you would come to have a test,
I was extremely excited.
I have been waiting for you.
But I heard that the Fiend Battle Team
killed many people in the Soul Arena.
We couldn't help it.
It was because they were weak.
Why didn't you just drive them away
instead of killing them?
Our captain said
that we shouldn't spare anyone in a battle.
We should spread the fear,
and no one would dare to question us.
It is too cruel.
But it is very effective.
Under the leadership of the captain,
soon Xi Si City
will be a territory of the Fiend Battle Team.
I know what you are worrying about.
In our team,
there are a few Soul Masters
with Quadruple Soul Rings
that you can't defeat.
But since you're introduced by Master Ye,
the battle
will be just a symbolic test.
As long as you can endure it for a while,
you can pass the test.
Not much risk.
Why did you go
to that alley?
The woman
is the wife of a defeated Soul Master.
The captain asked me to throw her out of the city.
And I happened to meet you.
That's fine. I will deal with her later.
She's just an ordinary person.
You're right. I won't kill her.
Wang Sheng.
I can understand
that you were tortured by Young Master Xiao.
But you have no right
to impose your pains on others
just as Xiao Chen Yu did to you.
Have you forgotten that you were wanted?
You were bullied as well.
Someone told me
that good people might do something wrong.
Bad people might do something good.
Be rational.
The captain told me
people who treat me nicely are good.
Otherwise, they are all bad.
So you want to kill them all?
If you are so merciless,
you are no different
from those people who you hate a lot.
It's enough!
Tang San.
Don't let our captain
hear what you said.
It's for your own good.
Wang Sheng, I think
you're not on the right track.
You aren't going to do the test?
I will attend
the battle.
That's great.
What if I don't attend?
Don't you know
your matter
is personally handled by Master Ye?
The captain takes it seriously too.
If you don't turn up in the battle,
I think that the captain will lead the team
to arrest you.
And kill me?
Since you've stayed,
then we're comrades now.
Don't think too much.
Tomorrow the captain and I
will bring you to the Soul Arena.
I'm sending a group of people
out of the city tomorrow.
Are you escaping?
I won't.
I've been waiting for the battle for a long time.
It's good then. As long as
you don't escape,
your friends, including Wu,
will be all right.
You mean that if I try to escape,
you're going to hurt them?
The captain values you a lot.
Who only knows how to kill people
is the worst Soul Master.
Tang San, mind your words!
Anyway, once the battle is over tomorrow,
we will be on the same team.
Stop saying the words that
you mentioned just now.
How do you feel? Do you get enough rest?
I can still sleep for another day.
I can accompany you.
Don't waste the time.
I don't want your company.
Let's go to Tian Dou City.
Okay.
Headmaster.
What's the matter?
I send you guys off the city.
Brother San, what do you mean by that?
You are not leaving?
I have to stay.
Why?
I have a very important matter
to do in Xi Si City.
What is the matter that makes you leave us?
Brother San.
Yes.
We're the Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke.
We're all here for you.
We will deal with it together.
That's right.
We can help you.
Thank you, everyone.
But I want to solve
the problem by myself.
I don't want to trouble you.
You're right.
We shouldn't involve
Brother Dai and the others in it.
So, let them leave on their own.
And I'll stay with you.
Wu,
you have to go to Tian Dou City with them.
There are the best Soul Masters and resources.
This is not negotiable.
Wu will always stay where Tang San is.
No matter where you choose to go,
I'll always be with you.
You've already decided?
I've already decided.
What do you think?
Shi Lan Ke School
has been poor since its establishment.
But I'm proud of one thing.
Apart from giving you knowledge and power,
we teach you how to develop
your independent personalities.
So, Tang San,
no matter what your decision is,
the school will always support you.
Headmaster, even if I leave,
I will always be a member of Shi Lan Ke.
Me too.
I will always be a member of Shi Lan Ke too.
Master, I'm always your student.
What do you mean by that?
Of course, you're my student.
I won't leave you alone.
Master...
Okay. That's it.
Let's
send everyone off now.
Master,
do you want to leave Brother San here?
Every one of you in Shi Lan Ke
will leave one day.
Do you want Shi Lan Ke
to keep you forever?
But you're an exception.
You have to pay the debt you owed the school first
before you graduate.
I...
Master, I'm your direct disciple.
I can consider reducing the interest.
Brother Dai,
why does Tang San have to stay?
He has his reason
not to tell it.
Everyone has his secrets.
It's unnecessary to figure out the answer.
Just believe him.
You don't need our help?
No. I'm okay to do it alone.
All right.
We're leaving the city soon.
Just leave us here.
All right. Continue your journey now.
Hopefully, we will
meet again in Tian Dou City.
Tang San.
Come to me whenever you encounter any problems.
I'm always your headmaster.
Brother San.
What happened? Stop crying.
Keep in mind what I've told you.
Never give up easily.
Take care, Brother.
All right.
What are you doing?
Why didn't you tell us in advance?
You leave us suddenly.
How can I accept it?
We'll meet again.
Wu, tell us
whenever you need our help.
All right.
Don't be sad.
You meet and you depart.
You depart and you will meet again.
You will leave Shi Lan Ke one day.
There is a bigger stage waiting for you.
Stop crying.
Let's depart now.
Let's go.
Take care of yourself.
Take care, Brother Dai.
I asked you to leave with them.
Look at yourself now.
That's different.
What is the difference?
Surely, I'll be sad when I leave them.
But you're different.
I can't be separated from you.
Why can't you be separated from me?
If I'm separated from you,
my heart seems to be emptied.
But, no one can stay with another forever.
We can try.
All right. We'll try.
Don't cry anymore.
Cheer up, everyone!
Tang San said
we might have the chance
to meet in Tian Dou City.
Cheer up!
Hello. May I know
where Xi Si City Soul Arena is?
As you mentioned,
you have to challenge the Fiend Battle Team
in Xi Si City Soul Arena?
Yes, when we were at Star Town,
Ye Zhi Qiu told me
I could only meet with Hao Tian Soul Master
after I had managed to defeat
the Fiend Battle Team.
Hao Tian Soul Master
is probably my father.
All right. I will challenge
the Fiend Battle Team with you!
What is the sound?
What happened outside of the city?
You...
It's a sandstorm.
Go back immediately.
Don't squeeze.
Find a place to hide.
Hide now! Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Hide!
Ou Si Ke.
Master.
Tang San.
Wu.
Master.
Ma Hong Jun.
Ma Hong Jun, please say something.
Ma Hong Jun!
Please say something! I'm calling you.
Ma Hong Jun, what happened to you?
I...
Ou Si Ke, it's me.
Ou Si Ke.
Let's go to look for Master now.
I don't want to go.
What happened to you? You're scared?
What are you doing here?
Let's go.
Hurry up.
I don't want to go.
Are you going to stay here forever?
Ma Hong Jun, stop moving!
Isn't this the Sand Beast?
Is this sandstorm caused
by the Sand Beast?
Don't let it find out.
I thought I was going to die.
Brother Dai, thank you.
If you hadn't saved me just now,
I might have died already.
I was not saving you, but Zhu Zhu Qing.
I was just saving you both together.
Anyway,
I have to thank you
for saving me.
You said you saved Sister Qing,
but where is she?
How do I know?
Did you lose her?
It's not your fault.
The situation was an emergency.
It's normal if you lose her.
What are you doing?
The storm outside hasn't receded.
You will die if you're swept away by the storm.
Remember to shut the window.
I don't want to die.
Stop moving if you don't want to die.
Help.
Ma Hong Jun.
Help me.
Why are you going wild now?
Please stop it now, Ma Hong Jun.
It will get angry if you keep hitting it.
Zhu Zhu Qing.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Go. Leave me alone.
Stop saying that.
Strength Boost! Speed Boost!
Get up here!
Come on.
Ma Hong Jun.
You can't blame me for this.
No one can save you as you get mad!
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
Eat this big sausage!
Ma Hong Jun!
Wake up!
Did I lose control again?
What happened?
You jumped out and hit it!
Did I hit it?
Let's go now. Stop talking too much!
Are you hurt badly?
I can carry on.
How did you get hurt?
I hid well.
I was hurt because I had to save him.
She hid well
and you caused her injury.
I'm sorry.
Does it still hurt?
Did I get it wrong?
Dai Mu Bai admitted his mistake.
Thank you. Had it not been for you,
it would have been dangerous.
That's nothing.
What happened to him?
Why does he become nicer?
Is your bone okay?
Do you want to bandage the wound first?
It's fine. I don't think I hurt the bone.
Stop moving.
Wait until the sandstorm is over.
We'll find a doctor for this.
I wonder
how Tang San and Wu are doing now?
I think they must be staying together.
Hopefully, they are all right.
Why did the sandstorm come all of sudden?
It doesn't feel like a normal sandstorm.
Is it caused by the Sand Beast?
Who provokes the Sand Beast?
I don't know.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. Luckily, you protected me.
How about you?
I'm fine. We are lucky.
Hold on. It is dirty.
I'll draw a rabbit for you.
Where is Master?
We were separated by the sandstorm.
Headmaster and the others
must have experienced the same.
Let's go and look for them.
Xi Si City is so large.
Where should we start?
The sandstorm blows from
the outside of the city.
I guess they ran back.
We can look for them along the way we came.
The Sand Beast is looking for its mate.
You can understand that?
I can feel its mood.
Is this sandstorm caused by it?
I think so.
Never mind. It's more important to find them now.
It seems to be Hu Lie Na!
She will die
if she knocks on the wall.
Hold on tightly. I will rush into it.
You want to rush into the storm and save her?
What if you are swept away?
But I have to rescue her.
What about I teleport into the storm
and rescue her?
No, it's too risky, Wu.
Keep in mind, if the storm is too strong,
let go of your grasp.
It's now.
Wu, let go of your grasp!
I won't let go!
It was really scary!
Why didn't you let go of your grasp?
I will be wherever you are.
You...
She is awake.
You rescued me again.
Where are the others?
I don't know.
Are you all right?
When the sandstorm came,
I was stunned. I'm fine now.
We're going to look for them
along the way back.
Tang San!
You saved me once
when Dai Mu Bai's brother appeared.
This is the second time.
I've forgotten it.
I remember it.
I'll repay your kindness.
No need. Let's go.
Is anybody here? We are the guests of the inn.
Hurry! Get in.
Are you all right?
Boss, did anyone come?
The sandstorm is here.
No one would come and stay.
I mean my friends
and the two teachers.
We stayed here previously.
No. No one came here.
Headmaster and the others
didn't come here.
I have to go out and look for them.
Don't go out.
The Sand Beast is still out there.
Sand Beast?
Yes.
Can't you hear the cry of the Sand Beast?
This sandstorm is
caused by the Sand Beast.
But why does the Sand Beast cause the sandstorm?
How can I know that?
There must be someone
who provokes the Sand Beast.
I have to go out and figure it out.
You don't want to live?
You stay here. If anyone comes here,
ask them to stay inside
and wait for my return.
Your own life is the most important.
It's unnecessary to risk your life for others.
If I had thought it that way,
you would have died already.
Don't leave now.
You are the Crown Prince's...
Messenger, Ma Xiu Nuo.
Okay.
Hold on.
Anything?
Can you send me off the city?
I can pay you.
I'm going to rescue my companions.
It's very safe here.
You can just stay here.
Please come inside.
It's a very important matter.
What is the important matter?
Come in and you'll know.
Hurry up.
What are you doing?
Come in and see this.
I'm in a hurry to look for my friends.
Who?
They said the sandstorm
was caused by the Sand Beast.
Could it be this one?
The Sand Beast crying out there
is looking for its mate.
Maybe it's looking for this one.
But why is it here?
I saw it at the night market last night.
It was playing alone.
I thought it was an abandoned pet.
Then I caught it and wanted to give it to others.
When I woke up this morning, the sandstorm came.
You dared to do this to the Sand Beast?
I didn't know it's a Sand Beast.
Otherwise, I wouldn't dare to do this.
Take it out now and set it free.
You can help me to get out of the city,
and we secretly set it free outside of the city.
Then we will be all right.
You won't be able to leave here with it beside you.
There's a Sand Beast outside.
What could we do then?
Take it and this guy out to the street.
When the Sand Beast
finds its mate and also the culprit,
the sandstorm will probably stop.
Then I'm doomed.
You should bear the consequences.
Enough.
She just wanted to scare you. Don't worry.
I didn't scare him.
Send this young beast to the street.
Don't let other Sand Beasts discover it.
Right.
Tang San, are you here?
Wang Sheng?
Wang Sheng.
It's great that you're here.
We encountered the sandstorm
on the way.
Otherwise, we'd have arrived earlier.
What's the matter?
The captain is asking for your whereabouts.
Let me introduce to you
the captain of the Fiend Battle Team,
Meng Li.
They are all your friends?
More or less.
Since all of you are Soul Masters,
you can work together.
All of you are Soul Masters, right?
I'm Ma Xiu Nuo from Tian Dou City.
I hire you to send me off the city.
You can tell the price as you wish.
Tian Dou City. Let us tell the price?
Yes. No matter how many
Gold Soul Coins you want.
So generous. You come from the royal family?
You're right. My dad is an officer in the palace.
You can believe me.
Does the royal family even need to hire us?
Why are you laughing?
The sandstorm is still raging.
Should we engage in an internal conflict
at this point?
All of them have Quadruple Soul Rings.
The team is really strong.
He's from the royal family.
So this is not an internal conflict!
I'm not sure if I've offended you.
Kill him.
Stop! I can stop the sandstorm.
You've made the right decision not to leave.
Later,
hold on longer in the battle,
and you will pass the test.
Then we will be on the same team.
You're looking for me.
What does it have to do with him?
The captain gave the order
to kill him.
That's too extreme, Wang Sheng.
Keep your voice down or you will die.
Look at this.
He caught the young beast
and caused its mother to get mad,
which in turn caused this sandstorm.
He is
the culprit who caused this disaster.
I've said
that those from the royal family
don't come with a good intention.
This is the evidence.
I didn't intend to do that.
This is my first time coming to Xi Si City.
I don't know about Sand Beasts.
This is your deliberate arrangement.
You wish to destroy
the whole Xi Si City with the sandstorm.
I don't have the intention.
If I had really wanted to do so,
I wouldn't have stayed here.
I'll give you a chance now.
Say it.
Bring it out of the yard
and find its mate
to let the sandstorm recede.
Even if I can find it,
I will die
once the Sand Beast gets crazy.
Otherwise, you will die now!
Maybe it can go out by itself
without my assistance.
You can't understand human words?
There are two options. Pick one!
You bring it out on your own
or die now.
I'll go for him.
Are you close to him?
Why do you want to die for him?
I heard from Wang Sheng
that you are his friend.
Yes, we're from the same school.
Then why do you help an outsider?
The Sand Beast has gone mad.
If I don't help him, the situation will get worse.
It's his own mistake,
so he has to bear with it.
He is too timid.
You mean you are brave enough?
Someone must do it.
I'm more suitable than him.
Moreover,
if the sandstorm keeps going on,
it'll be dangerous for you too.
All right.
I...
I can go on my own.
Okay, then you have to listen to me.
Aren't you their companion?
Why don't you go with them?
Aren't you an old friend of theirs?
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪