Get your necklace ready.
How close is he?
Take it off now.
Oh In Bum.
Put your necklace back on.
Okay.
Ms. Hong.
(Restricted Area)
(Women's Bath, Men's Bath)
Ms. Hong.
Are you over there?
(Cheonha Sauna)
Ms. Hong!
Wake up.
Pull yourself together!
Hong Ji A!
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
You're fine now.
You'll feel warm soon.
(Episode 6)
What happened to you?
That unrested spirit's memory came into my head,
so I thought everything ended well.
It's my mistake.
I didn't make a visit beforehand, so I missed another spirit.
That unrested spirit bewitched me.
Bewitched?
As in how people say they feel as if they're bewitched by a spirit?
That's it.
When an unrested spirit passes through me,
I fall into a trance against my will.
So this is very dangerous.
This won't happen again. Don't worry.
Did you ever want to do anything else other than this?
(Daebak Realty)
Mom, I got bewitched today.
I thought there was one unrested spirit,
but I saw two once I got there.
I know.
It's because I failed to make a visit beforehand.
I'll make sure I visit the place before I do this from now on.
Happy now?
Don't worry about it.
I came back in one piece.
You've seen him. The con man psychic.
I don't know why,
but my temperature doesn't drop when I'm with him.
So things haven't been too dangerous out on the field.
Help me.
Mom, you know...
Never mind.
Beer tastes the best after work.
One double-serving of jjajangmyeon, one japchae over rice,
and medium tangsuyuk.
What about you?
I'll take seafood jjamppong.
Seafood jjamppong. Okay.
Don't you have an appetite? That's all you're ordering?
I don't feel completely well after I was bewitched last night.
You were bewitched? Why?
That spirit of the college student didn't look very violent.
There was another unrested spirit.
Oh my gosh.
This is exactly why you make a preliminary visit.
You must've gone back to that night. Are you all right?
This time, it was different.
Once I got bewitched,
I went back to the same night from 20 years ago,
but this time, there was a child.
That man, Oh Sung Sik,
came with a child.
What do you mean?
It looks like what I remember isn't accurate.
It looks like the child he brought was...
this nephew of his.
What's weird is...
how the child was missing his eyes, nose, and mouth.
If you remember Oh Sung Sik's face,
isn't it weird how only the boy's face was missing?
You remembered that while you were bewitched,
so it may have been distorted.
Maybe.
But one thing for sure is that...
I can't trust my memory.
Why did I blindly believe that my memory was accurate?
I've been thinking about it,
and there are just too many questions.
Why did my mom try to perform an exorcism without a psychic?
No matter what you hear, do not come downstairs.
Understood?
And why was she possessed by an unrested spirit?
Do you remember what I taught you?
Stab me just as you practiced...
on that teddy bear.
Why did I assume that she had fallen victim...
to the unrested spirit because it was so powerful?
It's rather strange that I didn't question any of this.
I need to get to the bottom of this even though it's already too late.
I'll look into it.
You should focus on identifying the second unrested spirit.
That's of the utmost importance.
Thank you.
(Daebak Realty)
I've gathered all online posts regarding Cheonha Building.
All the reviews on the rooftop bakery...
were filled with complaints.
And the ID was Rooftop Bakery.
Just go to bed if you're going to keep yawning.
This is because the unrested spirit was...
a college student who pulled all-nighters gaming.
Why are you being mean when you already know that?
That's why you should go to bed.
I'm listening to everything.
I can't focus because of you.
Relax.
Go on, please.
Okay.
Check out the complaints.
I was the original owner of Rooftop Bakery.
The once empty alleyway started teeming with people...
after I opened the bakery.
But the landlord kicked me out,
saying that they were going to rebuild the building.
Business was flourishing,
so the landlord kicked out the tenant.
That's not uncommon. It doesn't faze me.
Who are the bakery owners?
They're 2 friends in their 30s.
Their names are Lee Sung Sil and Park In Sook.
The unrested spirit I came across was in her early 30s.
She could've been one of them.
Those women were terrible.
One of them was overly eager.
It must've been tough.
That was unnecessary.
But I'm right.
Was she the one who spread the ghost rumor?
I knew it.
(Missing, Lee Sung Sil)
- Ms. Park In Sook? - Yes?
Hello.
It's about your former partner, Ms. Lee Sung Sil...
Did you find her?
(Tramp Coffee)
- Here. - Thank you.
When Sung Sil first suggested that we open a bakery...
in the middle of nowhere,
I was against it at first.
I didn't think it'd work.
Finally, we've opened our own bakery.
Do you think they'd come all the way here to buy bread?
My friend, don't you worry.
It'll all work out.
(Rooftop Bakery)
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
- It's freshly baked and tasty. - I see.
- Hello. - Hello.
Could you wait a minute?
- Okay. - I'm sorry.
How do you like the coffee?
- Just like Sung Sil had said, - Thank you.
our business flourished.
Other shops that had similar themes started to open up,
and the alley became a commercial district.
Sung Sil?
She tried her best to receive funds to save this district.
She tried so hard.
She made sure there wasn't garbage...
or cigarette butts on the streets.
She really went through a lot.
That's what they said?
They despised her.
They said she was overly eager.
They badmouthed her behind her back.
The other shop owners seem unhappy.
Let's not be so eager about fixing things anymore.
Hey, we need to take care of this area in order to flourish.
It's not about having a lot of customers.
They need to want to keep visiting. Don't you think so?
I know you're right.
But people don't like those who are always righteous.
Still, someone should do the job.
Goodness. You must be busy getting ready to open today.
It's okay.
- How may I help you? - I'm sorry to say this,
but we need to reconstruct the building.
It wasn't like he wanted a higher rent fee.
Since it was reconstruction, we had no choice but to leave.
But the rent in that neighborhood had risen,
so it wasn't easy to find a new place.
Then we were walking past that building one day...
and saw that he had taken over our bakery.
Do you have no conscience?
You were lying about the reconstruction!
I didn't lie!
At times in life, plans fall through!
I'm going to sue you for using our bakery name.
Sue? Be my guest! Do you think that'd scare me?
- Get out. Leave! - Sir.
How dare you push me?
- Dad. - Hye Jung, call the police.
Why are you causing a scene at my store?
We kept getting kicked out, but Sung Sil didn't give up.
- Do you think I want to come here? - Then don't come!
So why did you steal my bakery?
That's enough.
You're going to make all of us broke.
I thought we'd get some peace and quiet,
but here she goes again.
Sung Sil went through so much to revive this area.
We felt completely betrayed.
You're going there again today?
Sung Sil.
Let's just forget about everything.
It's for the best.
I'm disgusted by those people.
No.
We need to right what's wrong.
If we don't, they'll do it again.
Thanks for the coffee.
That was the last time I got to see her.
(Missing, Lee Sung Sil)
I shouldn't have let her go all by herself.
I should've tagged along.
I should've stood my ground alongside her.
Excuse me.
Who's in charge of missing persons?
Him over there.
Thank you.
I have some questions regarding a missing individual.
Sure.
A month ago...
Hello, sir.
Hello.
A month ago, Ms. Lee Sung Sil had gone missing.
I'd like to hear some updates regarding her case.
She's not missing.
What do you mean? Have you located her whereabouts?
No, she's just not missing.
It's not linked to any crimes,
so we've concluded that she has run away.
She went missing after going to Cheonha Building.
She didn't run away.
She did go there that day.
But the CCTV caught her leaving after an hour.
She must've gone somewhere to cool off.
In most of these cases, they eventually come back.
By the way,
why would a realty look for a person?
You're not a detective agency.
Excuse me.
Ma'am.
This is the footage that Park In Sook received...
from the police.
Lee Sung Sil did indeed leave Cheonha Building.
Oh, dear. Where could she have passed away?
(Missing, Lee Sung Sil)
Now that we've confirmed her name and face, let's get on with it.
(Lee Sung Sil)
Doesn't having an unrested spirit in this building mean...
that she had died here?
That's none of your business. Don't play detective.
And In Bum.
You startled me.
Forget whatever memory you absorb tonight.
How can I possibly control that?
Of course, I want to forget it.
Just do it.
What's wrong with her?
Come to think of it, I never heard a thank-you from you.
What nonsense are you spewing this time?
You know that I deserve a thank-you from you.
If I hadn't been there that night, you would have died in here...
after getting possessed by the spirit.
You ought to thank the man who saved your life.
You never answer me when you know I'm right.
I told you that not answering people is a nasty habit...
Thank you.
Pardon?
Are you complaining even after I gave you what you wanted?
No. I just couldn't hear you well.
What did you say? What was that?
What? What did you say?
I know you heard me.
How much longer will you take? Will we be here all night?
I'll finish it.
You are grateful to your psychic.
How will we lure out the unrested spirit today?
- You. - Pardon?
A psychic in the water...
is the best bait for a spirit staying in the water.
- You want me to go in there? - Yes.
Do you know how much this suit cost me?
I don't know. Go in.
You thanked me without a fuss because you need me in the water.
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E11 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"Faceless Boy"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Take off your necklace.
Goodness. I don't know much about it.
Go talk to my husband.
He's not answering my calls right now.
My gosh. Don't you know what time it is? Why are you here?
When I came during the day, you said I was disrupting your business.
That's why I came back here at this hour.
Gosh. Whatever!
You can stand there all night if you want. Gosh.
Seriously. You can just run that small bakery somewhere else.
"That small bakery?"
What does it say about you people who stole that small bakery?
"You people?"
I know you stole it for your daughter.
I'll make sure your daughter never runs that bakery again!
I'll do whatever it takes!
- Are you done? - Watch me.
See if I can do it or not.
I'll give you a fight if that's what you want.
You!
You'd better stay away from her! If you don't, I'll kill you!
That bakery meant everything to me!
You crazy wench!
You'll have to take the bakery over my dead body!
I will not let her run that bakery!
How can you do that? What will you do?
- What will you do? - That's mine!
Die!
Die. Die!
You're okay.
Everything is over.
The person who killed Lee Sung Sil was...
the building owner's wife.
His wife killed her...
right here.
Forget it.
What?
I told you.
Whatever memories you get from here,
you must forget everything.
You knew, didn't you?
Come out once you've calmed down.
(Cheonha Sauna)
(Daebak Realty)
You didn't go home yet?
I wanted to see you come in first.
(Fresh Pork Belly)
Was she murdered as we expected?
I had a feeling that she was murdered...
because of her thirst to kill when she possessed my body.
But she was full of hatred even until the last moment.
I told him to forget it,
but it won't be easy.
Are you worried about In Bum?
Of course.
I don't know what kind of trouble he's going to get into.
Anyway, he only realizes his mistakes after making them.
Just like you.
When did I do that?
- Should I remind you? - No.
Good work today. Go home.
Gosh. Darn it.
Hey, your sideburns look cool.
You scumbags!
- You ate so much. - Hey!
Gosh. Hamburgers.
- Get me out. - Look at that.
Hey!
Get me out!
Get me out.
Get me out of here.
- Are you cold? - No.
I'm all right.
That's right.
You can't complain of being cold after doing a shoddy job.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sir!
Please give me one more chance.
That chance...
- Sir. - Please.
- Please. - That was your second chance.
- Sir. - Please!
- Sir, please spare us. - Please spare us!
- Sir! - Sir!
- Please spare us. - Sir!
- Please spare us. - Please spare us.
Sir!
Don't.
Gosh. What?
I can at least call the police. A woman was murdered.
I'll make an anonymous tip.
What will you say to the police?
Will you tell them you heard it from the dead woman?
- Well... - Do you have evidence?
Or do you at least know where the body is?
Then should I just sit on my hands?
It's not that you won't. You can't.
You helped out with the Green Villas case.
Why did you help out back then?
You were reminded of your mother.
If you find a way just as you did back then...
Do not babble whatever you want when you know nothing about me.
What kind of a person are you?
Do you just sell houses and take commission...
regardless of how a person died an unfair death?
- Is that who you are? - Yes.
If it's that tough, feel free to quit.
You won't have to pay the penalty.
I'm not in the mood to talk.
Don't say a word.
You know that too.
I haven't always been like this.
I wasn't like this at first.
That man is the murderer.
You should use a lie detector or whatever and find out.
Miss, not everyone can use the lie detector...
just by throwing a fit like this.
And you keep saying you saw something.
What in the world did you see?
Are you a witness?
No, that's not the case. I...
If you keep framing an innocent man without evidence,
you'll be charged for libel.
Be careful.
I'm the one who wants to arrest everyone...
who created those unrested spirits and lock them up for good.
Hey, Ms. Hong.
You were eating.
That looks great.
Enjoy.
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency)
Right after Oh Sung Sik's death,
his mother took his nephew and went back to her hometown.
She lives there alone right now.
Her nephew, Oh In Bum, moved out as soon as he graduated high school.
- Oh In Bum? - Yes.
(Certificate of Family Relations)
(Oh In Bum)
Unlike how you were worried,
I don't think anything bad happened to the kid.
I looked through his medical record,
and there's nothing in particular other than a simple cold.
(Daebak Realty)
- You're here. - Yes.
I looked into Oh Sung Sik's nephew just as you asked.
Okay.
His residence is unknown ever since he moved out...
after he graduated high school.
It's not easy to track him down.
- Is that so? - I'll keep looking for him.
Don't mind it.
Okay. Thank you.
Anyway, about Oh In Bum.
I don't think it's too late to call off your contract.
All of a sudden?
I do see why you need him...
since he can keep your temperature up.
But things have been so hectic ever since the day he joined us.
You were busy trying to clean up after the mess he made.
I'm afraid he'll cause irreparable trouble one day.
I feel anxious.
Let him be.
His contract will expire soon.
It's too much work.
It's not like I'll keep seeing him after that.
All right, then.
Die.
Another dream?
Yes.
In Bum.
He seems very different from the last time.
It's very serious.
What if something bad happens to him?
Of course, she's going to be feisty since that spirit was murdered.
He'll be fine in a few days. Live with it.
Even this morning, he swore to kill that murderer,
and his eyes were...
- I think he meant it. - He won't kill anyone.
Is there anything I can do to help?
No.
In Bum has to deal with it.
- But there's something you can... - No, there isn't.
All right.
Please continue with your workout.
Gosh, In Bum. What a weakling.
(Cheonha Sauna)
Hello.
What is it?
- Excuse me. - Yes?
The faucet isn't working.
Can you come and take a look?
Yes, okay. One second, please.
Darn it, why is the faucet not working?
Come in and take a look.
Will you just leave it?
I'll have it fixed later. I'm sorry.
- What's with her? - I apologize.
Hello? Hey, I'm very sorry.
Well... Could you come in just an hour earlier?
I'm not feeling so well.
Yes, okay. Thanks.
Ms. Kim Song Yi?
You know who the deceased Lee Sung Sil is, right?
I don't have anything to say.
I just said someone deceased, even though she's still missing.
Yet you aren't surprised.
Did you already know that?
I don't know what you're talking about.
How would I know if she's dead...
or just missing?
You're too much of a coward to go in there and fix the faucet.
But I guess you're brave enough...
to live under the same roof with a ghost.
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
I'm giving you a chance.
A chance to come clean...
and ask for forgiveness.
Goodness.
I have no idea why you're doing this.
The police have already checked the CCTV.
I have no idea where she is.
I have nothing to do with her.
What a weird woman. I can't believe this.
Goodness.
In Bum, that's enough.
You've been watching this all day.
I swear she died in the pool.
So how did she exit the building?
Ji Chul, isn't she limping?
What?
You're right.
This isn't her. It's the landlord's wife.
She wore Ms. Lee's clothes...
to make her own alibi.
She wore the deceased woman's clothes?
What a scary woman.
But how can we prove it?
The only way to do that is by locating her body.
Ms. Hong.
Gosh, what a killer view.
- I'll take a photo of you. Get up. - Sure.
All right. Look here.
Look at the camera.
No, go over there.
Do you really think the body is inside the building?
It would've been very difficult for her to carry the body outside...
and dispose of it when she doesn't even have a driver's license.
(Cheonha Sauna)
Gosh, saunas are the best when your body feels stiff.
But her husband has a car.
They could've done it together.
It feels good to go to a sauna.
(Restricted Area, Authorized Personnel Only)
Okay.
Was she the one who spread the ghost rumor?
I knew it.
No.
The landlord didn't even know that she was dead.
He could've played dumb.
If An Chang Sub knew,
he wouldn't have asked me to perform an exorcism.
Since they continued to run the sauna and the bakery,
she couldn't have hidden her there.
If a body had been stored indoors for a month,
it would've reeked. She would've gotten caught.
Then where could it be?
- Here. - Why?
Do you see the unrested spirit?
You saw something that night, didn't you?
Only this material is different.
She had recently blocked this area.
You're right. It looks brand new.
What? It was a guess.
Don't be ridiculous. It was a reasonable inference.
Don't get close.
Cheonha Building's basement? Yes, I constructed it.
Why do you ask?
Did you happen to see...
what was underneath the stairs?
Underneath the stairs?
There was nothing.
There were clothes and blankets. Just a bunch of garbage.
Garbage?
So you want me to block this?
Yes.
I understand. Throwing garbage away also requires money.
Let's see.
430mm.
Do people often do that?
Not often, but it does happen.
It's going to be blocked off anyway.
You have to pay to get rid of garbage.
Garbage...
Okay.
We're done.
Do people really get fooled by your lousy tricks?
Lousy?
(Cheonha Sauna)
My gosh! Go away!
Do you still think it's lousy?
Sir.
A... A ghost.
- Are you okay? - No!
Sir!
Look at me.
You're okay.
Let's go inside.
- It's okay. Follow me. - No.
(Cheonha Sauna)
I... I saw it.
It... It was a ghost.
I knew it.
You knew it?
Didn't you already perform an exorcism?
I apologize. We actually came to confirm it.
But I guess you witnessed it yourself.
- You must've been startled. - Confirm what?
Wait. Confirm what?
What is that?
Through our research,
we found out that the student had a lover.
On the day of his death, he had lost his matching ring here.
We believe he's still looking for it.
Ring?
Why would it be here?
That night...
My heart is broken.
Didn't the construction take place after his death?
You're right. It's been a month.
I knew it.
Then what should we do?
We just need to find that ring.
We need to tear down this wall.
Come on. He can't tear down a perfectly fine wall.
Or he can just let...
the unrested spirit haunt him until the day he dies.
Come on.
What should I do?
(Cheonha Sauna)
Here I go.
Goodness. Wait.
- What are you doing? - Honey.
No. Stop this at once! I mean...
Who gave you permission to do this?
He said...
Calm down. I'll explain.
Forget it. Stop this.
Stop it right now!
My gosh.
Honey, listen to me.
A ring that belonged to the deceased student is in there.
That's why his spirit still lingers.
Are you a fool?
Do you actually believe that?
I saw him myself.
And they're paying for everything.
They'll block it up again after.
If not, why would they waste money...
on tearing down a wall that's full of garbage?
Because there's something else back there!
In that case,
is it something you want to hide?
Perhaps,
a body?
What on earth are you talking about?
What? You said the body was here.
You said it was a logical deduction.
Shut it.
Honey, what's wrong?
I'm so sorry.
No. I...
I didn't do it on purpose.
Don't. Don't come near me.
Don't come near me.
What's gotten into you?
I didn't do it on purpose.
How did you know that the victim's body was there?
Gosh. How would I possibly know that?
I went there to find the dead college guy's ring.
Then, did you break the wall to find the ring, Ms. Hong?
By nature, I must follow through when I start something.
I was just trying to help him as a way to work out.
If you're done questioning her, I'll take her with me.
It's not over yet.
Why are you keeping her here for hours?
Why?
She's not a murder suspect.
Must you intimidate her while questioning her?
(Kind, Present, and Swift Police)
I've been to the station more than when I used to scam people.
And who do you think is responsible for that?
Chief Heo!
Why did you help him?
You even staged the wall to look like it was haunted.
You know the side effect of being possessed by a spirit...
who was brutally murdered.
A series of nightmares where you always die...
and the vivid fear and rage.
I was supposed to be going through that.
So in the end, you did it for him.
I knew that given his personality, he'd do something for sure.
I couldn't let him fail.
I didn't want him to experience what I went through.
But you deliberately left me out.
And I am quite saddened by that.
No. About that...
I felt like I was bothering you too much lately.
I am very disappointed.
Ms. Joo.
By the way,
what did the building owner's wife see to get that scared?
Is it possible for the unrested spirit...
to show up even after an exorcism?
I don't know why she acted like that,
but there was no unrested spirit.
In other words, we got lucky this time.
Our teamwork was perfect, and the universe was on our side.
No. There's no guarantee that we'll get lucky every time.
Next time, don't be rash.
Rash? Gosh. Don't put it like that.
It seems you two are getting along better now.
Right? We make a good team.
But Ms. Hong will not admit that.
Don't exaggerate things.
Our late-night food is here.
It smells good.
Why are we having bread? Thanks, anyway.
In Bum made it.
What? I did?
Yes. Don't you remember?
You probably don't.
You made the dough in the morning, fermented it,
and baked it. But you didn't clean up.
So the lady scolded me for the mess.
She said that was way too much food for anyone.
That's all right. I understand it was the side effect.
I'm used to it now.
Ms. Hong, try some. It's really good.
- No. - Gosh.
Did you know?
In the States, when people put their houses on the market,
they bake bread around the time for the open house.
Why?
When people smell bread, they feel at ease and comfortable.
I see. It's a psychological marketing trick.
When people go to the open house,
they think the house feels cozy thanks to the smell of the bread.
That way, people sell more houses.
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E12 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"The Basement Wall"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
It's not bad.
Hello.
What brings you here?
I wanted to thank you.
How did you find this place?
You should keep eating the bread.
Let's talk outside.
- Eat up. - Hey.
"Did you eat dinner, my baby?"
"I'm having bread."
Thank you.
It's all thanks to you.
Gosh. I only did my job.
And...
this isn't much. But it's a reward.
Gosh. You could have wired the money to me.
No. Thanks to you, we were able to have a funeral for her.
I wanted to give you the money in person.
Goodbye.
- Okay. Good luck. - Thank you.
You startled me.
I knew it. You're still a fraud.
You were after the money, weren't you?
Ms. Hong, rewards aren't money.
An expression of one's gratitude. A way to deliver one's gratitude.
If I turn it down, I'll hurt their feelings.
As if you care about their feelings. Come here.
I'll kill you once I catch you. Hey!
No. Wait. Hold on!
I'm sorry.
Is she still begging to thin air?
Don't you think the victim's spirit is following her?
You punk.
A cop is talking about spirits. Good for you.
The murderer is just hallucinating...
because she's guilty.
There are tons of people who commit suicide because of that.
Got it?
By the way, how did the real estate agents know...
exactly where the body would be and tear down the wall?
That puzzles me the most too.
I'm telling you. It's the spirit.
- It's not a regular agency. - Okay.
I heard that they perform exorcisms to get rid of spirits.
Are you kidding me? Get back to work.
(Daebak Realty)
A real estate agency that gets rid of spirits?
Ms. Joo Hwa Jung.
So you became a professional fraud.
(2021 Cheonha Building)
(Daebak Realty)
(Declined)
(Eradication Log)
This year, yellow is the new black.
It's more than just a pretty bag.
It will come in handy when you carry this bag.
The buckle on the front definitely stands out.
But Choi Ji Won is alive!
Ms. Hong!
What kind of a person are you?
Do you just sell houses and take commission...
regardless of how a person died an unfair death?
Is that who you are?
- This is so wide. - Yes.
Since this is nice...
Mom.
When he works, he reminds me of you.
He doesn't give up and recklessly throws himself at the case.
How could he do that?
The more I do this job,
the more I loathe people's greed, hatred, and resentment.
I'm so sick of it.
That's why I've been turning a blind eye to it.
But how did you do what you did?
How were you able to not give up on these people?
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
All right! That's the way to let off the steam.
This is it.
I've been too mean to myself lately.
Taxi!
(Daebak Realty)
Thank you.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
Ms. Hong.
Hey! You can't get water on this expensive suit!
Let me go right now!
Darn it.
You cheap jerks.
He never changes.
I'll kill you all once I get down.
Let me go now!
Please let me go already. Gosh.
Just for a moment.
My gosh.
(Real Estate Sales Agreement)
Ms. Hong, you're really something.
You made me come all the way out here.
That's the sales contract for Daebak Realty. Sign it.
No.
Hey, wait!
Let's talk it out. We can talk this out!
That's enough. You might kill him.
- That hurts. - Can I just kill him?
I think you're the one who'll die.
Those eyes. I still love those eyes.
- Go make a hole in his tummy. - Yes, sir.
Please let me live. Please!
I'll... I'll give you money.
- Stay still! - Please spare my life.
- I can't aim right. - Please let me go.
Who are you?
You promised you'll give us an apartment unit.
What?
I set the place on fire...
and killed people.
Give me the apartment.
The apartment.
(Sell Your Haunted House)
It's cold. Or is it just me?
How dare you take the necklace off?
I thought you were invincible, but you're pretty sloppy.
I don't know when, but I'm apparently possessed.
No matter how horrible it is, I'd want to know the truth.
At times, the truth can torment you.
Oh Sung Sik?
My uncle isn't such a horrendous criminal.
Something is wrong.
I want to see the case file from that night 20 years ago.
What was she like? Your mother, Ms. Hong.
She died helping out people who didn't deserve it.
I'll never forgive them.