(Episode 5)
(Who is the redevelopment for? Wake up, stop the redevelopment!)
(Resident Dissolution Committee for the redevelopment of Zone B)
(Stop the redevelopment from destroying my fortune!)
The world has become way more generous.
Long ago,
we would've demolished them and built the apartment by now.
- No, wait. - Ms. Hong!
- You can't pull that on me. - Ms. Hong!
Move aside.
How dare you block my way to eat?
Hey.
What?
Those two.
We still have something left to discuss.
- Ma'am! - Go ahead.
We don't have anything left to talk about. Sir.
It's the chairman.
Attention, greetings.
- Hello, Chairman. - Hello, Chairman.
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be at the realty office.
It's just... She is CEO Hong of Daebak Realty.
(Taejin Service)
Please help me.
You're younger than I thought.
Who are you?
How bold of you.
You probably had no idea who I, Do Hak Sung, was...
when you messed with Britium.
I see. Dohak Construction.
But you see,
why would someone like you, who's brave and skillful,
do something so lowly as toying with redevelopment?
Don't you know...
that doesn't get you much money anymore?
If you need money, how about you work for me instead?
I sure love your gaze.
I don't work with just anyone.
Anyone?
How cute.
I'll give you a few days...
to decide whether to be my friend or foe.
If you choose the latter,
you can look forward to what'll await you.
I won't wait long.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
Your hands are ice-cold.
There was an unrested spirit here, wasn't there?
Are they still here?
Not anymore.
What? I just held her hand on goodwill.
Hey, how did Kim Tae Jin find us?
Should we move?
Didn't you see him just now?
He was completely intimidated by Ms. Hong.
Let's stick close to her.
Did they leave?
- Yes. - Yes.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
Ma'am, are you okay?
I was terrified...
that they'd barge in here again and cause a scene.
Have they been doing that?
They come at least once or twice every month.
They want me to sell this land.
Ma'am.
Instead of enduring all this then eventually getting kicked out,
maybe you should just receive the compensation.
Chief Heo.
What?
Do you know why she named the restaurant Changhwa?
It's the name of her son who left home 12 years ago.
She can't leave this place...
in case he comes back.
You want me to investigate your mother's final client?
Yes.
I want to know why he died.
He's dead?
I ran into his unrested spirit.
Are you sure it was him?
You only saw him once 20 years ago. You could be mistaken.
No.
I still remember every little detail about that day.
Okay. I'll look into it and let you know.
Hello.
What?
It's still early evening. Why do you look so down?
Seeing how you're all hyped up,
you must've found something.
I told you.
I noticed a world star couple just through a shadow...
Let's begin the briefing.
After 15 hours of investigation,
using the cutting-edge method of social media,
I've looked into every single person...
who was even slightly connected to the Green Villas fraud.
There were three people who lost their lives.
You see...
It's the third photo. The mom.
- How are you so sure? - Because I saw her.
I see.
Her name is Joo Kyung Hee. She's 60 years old.
She died of myocardial infarction.
I've never seen her so elated before.
That's why I couldn't stop her even though I was concerned.
She looked extremely happy.
I should've dissuaded her back then.
We don't even know when this house will sell.
Why did you sign the contract already?
You don't have to hurry.
I can cover the down payment with the money I've saved up.
The sales agency will also help us...
receive a loan.
- Loan? - Don't worry about anything.
This is the very 1st house I've purchased in 60 years.
I made sure to be thorough.
Look at you. You never wanted a house.
What has gotten into you?
I should have a house to my name before I die.
You cannot go there alive
- Are you that happy? - What? Yes.
Gosh. I love it.
Hey, had I known it'd feel this great,
I would've purchased a house much sooner.
Goodness.
You guys should just move in here...
even before your house gets sold.
- We'll think about it. - Gosh.
Honey. Mother. Look here.
Sure. Come here.
All right. 1, 2, 3.
I love you.
Every day, she cleaned and wiped the house...
even though there wasn't much to clean.
Who is it? Goodness.
But she couldn't even last a week in her cherished house.
What do you mean?
This house isn't mine?
I'm illegally residing here?
What's wrong with you?
This is my house!
You can't come in here with your shoes on!
Don't do this!
Don't do this! Stop!
This is my house!
You should've checked! What is this?
So what do you expect me to do?
I had no idea either!
I'm so frustrated.
- Mom. - Mother.
She died...
of anguish, not myocardial infarction.
She was heartbroken and furious.
It got the best of her.
Those people...
are murderers, not frauds.
Green Villas, Block B has stairs in the middle,
and eight houses in total.
Our client in Unit 302 doesn't live there anymore.
But we need approvals from the rest of the families.
The unrested spirit is obsessed with Unit 302...
and won't leave that place.
We can carry out the exorcism tonight without their approval.
We'll perform it at 3am when everyone's fast asleep.
Okay.
Gosh. No way.
How are we going to lure out the spirit this time?
Will you threaten the spirit?
I thought the other houses wouldn't be affected.
I'm just preparing myself for a possible variable.
A certain fraud and psychic jammed me up a bit lately.
Don't tell me you're talking about me.
What?
Not answering questions is a bad habit.
- Don't take off your shoes. - Pardon?
Keep your shoes on.
This is my house!
You can't come in here with your shoes on!
What?
Gosh. What's going on?
Oh In Bum!
Now. Take it off!
Get out!
- Get out of my house. - Get out of my house.
- This is my house! - This is my house!
- This is my house. - This is my house.
- I bought it for my daughter. - I bought it for my daughter.
- My house. - My house.
Gosh.
Here's a warm drink for you.
Okay. Thank you.
My daughter's family and I want to move in together...
- to a deposit-based house. - Gosh.
No one wants to rent out deposit-based houses.
They all want monthly rent.
Well, that will be quite difficult for our finances.
Then, why don't you buy the house instead?
If you have enough for a deposit,
it's better to just buy the house with a mortgage plan.
Oh, right. We have some cheap units for a small apartment...
because they weren't sold when they were on the market initially.
Please wait.
How big is the house?
There are 2 options. One is 79.2m², and the other, 105.6m²
- Those are nice units. - Take a look at them.
No. Just call me...
when you have a nice listing for a deposit-based house.
Gosh. Sure. I'll do that.
Oh, right. Just in case.
Why don't you take this home and read it through at home?
(Selling Incredibly Cheap Units, No Commission Fees)
- Thank you. - Sure.
Young Mi...
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E09 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"Mother & Daughter"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
I'm glad you changed your mind. Your daughter will be so happy.
You won't regret it.
The developers and construction company are...
very solid.
There's nothing for you to worry about.
You can just live happily in that house.
You have nothing but a happy future ahead of you.
You cannot go there alive
What do you mean?
This house isn't mine?
I'm illegally residing here?
- Hey, take everything out. - What are you doing?
Even if you sue them for fraud,
it will be hard to get all of your money back.
You didn't wire the money to the designated trust account.
So legally speaking, this house doesn't belong to you.
I'll bring my mom here.
How can we live with her in that small studio?
I can't let her stay at her friend's house forever!
I know that. But let's try to find another way to help her. Okay?
Even if it's a small studio, she'll be better off with me.
I'm sorry.
I'm old and foolish.
- How can I... - And I got scammed.
I just wanted...
to buy a house for my daughter...
whom I hadn't done much to help.
My daughter.
I am...
sorry.
I'm sorry.
(Daebak Realty)
She bought that house...
after working at restaurants and as housekeepers.
She worked so hard for that money. Gosh, those scumbags.
How did you have this job for 10 years?
I would have killed a few people already.
What's the point?
I would just have more unrested spirits for me to get rid of.
I didn't know you made jokes.
I wasn't joking.
The duty of an exorcist ends after sending the spirits off.
That's where the job ends.
I see.
You want me to try to pretend that I watched a sad movie again?
You know what? My parents passed away when I was very young.
So I have no memories of them.
And I had never missed them either.
I must know them to miss them.
But earlier, this crossed my mind.
When my parents had to leave me in this world alone,
did their hearts break just as much as this?
And I hoped that it wasn't the case.
My princess.
I am...
sorry.
Mom?
Is that how you felt too that day?
Is that why you are still here? Because you can't leave me?
Help me.
No matter what you hear,
do not come downstairs. Understood?
Promise me.
- I promise. - You must keep that promise. Okay?
Okay. I got it.
Mom!
Ji A...
Mom?
Ji A.
Pick up that needle.
Do you remember what I taught you?
Stab me just as you practiced on that teddy bear.
No.
Pull yourself together, Ji A!
Get your mind straight, and do it.
I can't do that, Mom.
You can. You have to.
I don't want to do it, Mom.
Mom.
Hey, Ms. Joo.
Right now?
Yes, it's fine.
(Oh Sung Sik)
Oh Sung Sik.
He killed himself?
Yes, 20 years ago,
two days after he came to Daebak Realty.
Does this have something to do with my mother's last exorcism?
That's not the case.
There were lots of conflicts between the residents...
and real estate developers in the squatter area.
The residents were to get kicked out for petty cash and no compensation.
He set the town on fire out of anger,
but a total of seven people died in the fire.
He couldn't deal with the guilt, then committed suicide.
Then why is he haunting the chairman of Dohak Construction?
Golden Properties was the contractor for the redevelopment,
the former entity of Dohak Construction.
Do Hak Sung pushed ahead with redeveloping the squatter area.
He probably became an unrested spirit to haunt him.
That could be a possibility.
How's the lawsuit for Green Villas coming?
They haven't located President Hwang of the design company. No progress.
Why do you suddenly ask?
I was reminded of my mother.
Can you find all the properties which President Hwang owns?
Yes, ma'am.
The evicted resident union is...
making an issue out of the joint owners' agreement?
The committee gave their approval. There's nothing to make an issue of.
The thing is...
they bring in other civic groups and put up a fight together.
They also bring reporters...
from independent media or something.
So did you get scared...
as the head of the borough and want to revoke the agreement...
for the redevelopment of the joint-owned area?
Things aren't like the way it was in this day and age.
Come in.
I got farmed ginseng for 49 dollars to abide by the Anti-bribery Act.
But you should still feel a little burdened.
Goodness.
All redevelopment projects suffer from conflicts against evictees.
Don't worry about it, Chairman Do.
Anyway, that's that.
What's happening with Assemblyman ﻿Han Eui Sub?
I already mentioned it to him...
to set up a date for us.
Good. All right.
- Have a drink, sir. - All right.
This is my home!
No.
This is my home.
You need to get up.
Five more minutes.
How can you sleep right now?
I couldn't sleep at all because I was too heartbroken.
Forget it. I need to sleep.
I said wake up!
Mom, come on.
Hey.
You sounded just like my mom right now.
Man, I hate it too.
Is this the aftereffect of that unrested lady spirit?
So please find President Hwang for me.
I need to find him and take my precious money back...
for me to live in peace.
That's not exactly your money.
What?
Darn it.
I have no idea what's going on.
Living as a psychic seems really stressful.
So we just need to find President Hwang?
Yes.
Goodness.
Hey, look.
No way. President Hwang is a guy.
I know that.
This is his younger sister, Hwang Ji Yeon.
On her call history, I saw a number she has been calling often...
ever since her brother went missing, and it's a burner phone.
Of course, it has to be President Hwang.
Hey, I knew you'd do it, Chief Heo.
Anyway, did you locate the phone?
I'm almost done with that too.
(Your violation of the traffic regulations...)
Don't be so cheap about food.
Go eat cup noodles.
We shouldn't treat him too nicely.
- Eat up. - Okay.
What is this?
What the heck is this smell?
- Your foot? - Speeding?
When did I get caught?
Pharming completed.
We just have to wait until he calls someone.
Nice job!
That lady must be here again. You're cleaning.
But it's great. Everything looks neat.
(Daebak Realty)
The rumors went on for about two years...
that President Hwang is the main guy for Do Hak Sung to secure funds.
The police tried to investigate,
but there was no evidence, so it came to nothing.
Then there's a high possibility Do Hak Sung took the money...
for selling the apartment units, instead of President Hwang.
If that isn't the case, Do Hak Sung wouldn't have let him live.
Is this all President Hwang owns?
Hwang Ji Yeon is listed as a joint owner for most of these.
Yes, that's his sister.
What's the current market price for these properties?
It has been ages since it dropped by half or less.
It looks like he was fooled by another real estate agent.
The con man has been conned.
Let's go with this.
My goodness, what's going on?
Did I just clean this place?
I don't know.
Things don't look much different from the ordinary.
What do you mean?
This place was full of dust.
It wasn't that bad.
My gosh, a man's hands are what defines him.
I didn't even put on rubber gloves.
Ms. Hong.
I talked to them. Let's get going.
Okay, I'll be there.
Where are you going?
To eat.
At this odd hour?
I eat whenever I want.
If the sales have been made...
Go.
What were you doing?
You put me up for work, then went to her office?
I'll explain it to you later.
And remember. Don't let Ms. Hong catches you.
I don't want to die either.
Ms. Joo, Oh In Bum or Chief Heo can't know about my involvement...
- with President Hwang. - I'll keep it a secret.
They might not know when to butt in if I give them a chance...
to get involved.
I hate cleaning up after them too.
Goodbye.
I'll give you 70 percent of the price...
you paid for the property three years ago.
I know that...
the current value is well below 50 percent of the original price.
That's why I'm looking to buy it.
It's my job to make an investment for its future value.
If you're keeping it for a reason, then it's fine.
I thought you wanted to sell it.
My brother and I are joint owners of this property,
so I have to ask him.
One second, please.
Hello? Jae woo.
(My Love)
Oh, hey.
Hey, we found President Hwang's location.
Then when do you want to seal the deal?
As soon as possible.
I'm willing to sign the paperwork along with Mr. Hwang Jae Woo today.
Well, actually...
He's at work right now.
I can get his power of attorney and sign for him.
I can't do that.
I don't make deals unless I meet the title-holder in person.
Gosh, why do you do that?
If you can't do that, let's call this off.
Wait.
Once you see who President Hwang is,
you'll report him to the police, then get out. Okay?
Who is it?
- Parcel delivery. - Leave it in front of the door.
I need a signature.
Could you come out for a second?
I'm not expecting any delivery, so just take it back, then.
Aren't you Mr. Hwang Jae Woo?
This is from Ms. Hwang Ji Yeon.
Where do I sign?
I need the receiver to sign it himself.
I am the receiver. Where do I sign?
It's not you.
What the heck is wrong with you?
Hey. Are you crazy?
It's you. You jerk! Hey!
Who are you? Why are you here?
I'm working part-time. You wanted me to pay you back.
I need to make some to do that.
What are you trying to pull?
Darn it.
So Mr. Hwang Jae Woo is here.
Oh In Bum. Hey, In Bum.
In Bum! You idiot.
- Gosh. - You do it.
Take this. You idiot.
You idiot.
- Hey. You idiot. - Hey!
Stop making a scene out there, and do it inside.
Okay.
You're ordering me around again.
Don't you get tired?
It's tiring. Let's go inside.
Come here, you idiot.
- Come! - Why are you trying so hard?
Why can't you drag him back?
Jae Woo.
Ji Yeon.
Ms. Hong?
Ms. Hong!
In this quarter, we are looking to promote...
premeditated and systematic control...
over our real estate businesses...
President Hwang was arrested by the police.
That dimwit.
Which station?
Call the chief there.
Yes, sir.
Continue.
We didn't confine or assault anybody, officer.
Officer, look at our faces before you say anything like that.
Those two beat us up! Especially the woman!
She's a total thug.
Please stop shouting.
Why did you get into a fight?
- Are you two acquainted? - It wasn't a fight.
I'm the only one who got beaten up.
And this guy. He's on the wanted list,
so will you please look him up?
Mr. Hwang, you are on the wanted list.
See that?
Let me call my attorney.
Are we all done? May I go?
Not yet.
Why not? It was self-defense.
They hit me first!
That's why I told you to stay quiet.
My blood boils...
whenever I think of that con man. How can I not do a thing?
Do you finally understand how all of your victims felt...
when you conned them?
That's different from this one.
All of my victims deserved it.
Speak for yourself.
What about you?
You told me not to do a thing. So why were you there?
You should speak for yourself.
Will you all be quiet?
(Our officers will work hard for the safety of the people.)
- Oh my. - What is this?
- Come here. - Hey, bring that over.
- Darn it. - What is this?
Tofu. We have to eat this.
Man, what tofu?
Hey, make sure you eat some tofu.
Let's go.
It hurts.
(Warmhearted and Trustworthy Police for the Residents)
Good luck.
This isn't right!
Darn it!
Did I get beaten up for no reason?
Kim Tae Jin was at President Hwang's place.
That means Dohak Construction and President Hwang...
were both in on the fraud.
There's only circumstantial evidence.
Without any proof,
they'll either get probation or a fine.
And they would rather pay a fine...
than compensate the victims.
How did you track President Hwang?
I used pharming on his phone.
Can you also hack his phone and retrieve a file?
It is possible but...
It's a burner phone, so you won't find anything.
Just give it a try first.
Scumbags like him...
often make sure they have a way out.
What is this? Why are you singing a different tune?
Didn't you tell me not to do anything before?
We should always finish what we've started.
I'm finally liking you.
I'm not doing this for you.
Okay, ma'am.
(Daebak Realty)
No way. In Bum.
Yes?
There really was something.
Play it.
Did you ask the chairman to allow me to fly abroad?
He's currently talking about it with the old man, so be patient.
Will the money be sent late?
Those Filipinos only work well when I'm there.
I understand, so please wait.
President Hwang Jae Woo of Mirae Design...
and Secretary Choi of Dohak Construction's call...
went viral and caused a commotion.
It's proof...
that the two companies had joined hands in this fraud.
Despite this concrete proof, the police aren't investigating.
This just shows that the police and the judicial system...
are all on the same side.
- Despite the victims' pleading, - They must apologize!
Dohak Construction has not released...
any official statement regarding...
I'm sorry, sir.
I had no idea that Mr. Hwang would be recording the call.
Don't worry.
It was time to toss him anyway.
The public will forget about this in a week.
Make it look like he embezzled the money on his own.
Make sure to put an end to the lawsuit. Don't let it drag on.
And prepare for a press conference.
Yes, sir.
(Dohak Construction)
As the chairman of Dohak Construction,
I am deeply heartbroken that our company had a part...
in causing...
unforgivable scars on the victims...
due to criminal activity, committed by the head of the agency.
As our way of taking moral responsibility,
regardless of the lawsuit's ruling,
we decided to provide all of the victims...
with condolence money.
I sincerely hope that this will bring...
at least a bit of peace to the victims.
Once again, I would like to offer...
my sincerest apologies.
- Sir! - Sir!
- Wait! - Answer our question, please.
Did you find who posted the call online?
I believe the people who were at his apartment...
that day were behind this.
Ms. Hong Ji A, the CEO of Daebak Realty and Oh In Bum.
You've met them once.
Why would they do that?
The prosecution demanded the court to sentence...
Mirae Design's President, Hwang Jae Woo,
to seven years in prison...
and collect 3.6 million dollars.
The call recording...
The real mastermind behind this is Dohak Construction.
But they'll only take away his money?
How can a paper company give back that much money?
That just means that they won't compensate the victims.
Was it just a pipe dream of ours?
I hope they give a big sum for the condolence money.
They ought to compensate the victims, not console them.
How shameless! What? He'll give them condolence money?
Among the victims, they entrusted the agency...
to oversees the sales...
Ms. Hong.
Did you see...
The client will be here at 8pm.
Oh, my. She ripped it apart.
When did she start punching it?
As soon as that shameless Do Hak Sung...
started to babble about the condolence money.
So she just lost it and started punching it.
It's been over an hour.
I'm glad she didn't beat up anyone.
That sandbag is saving a lot of lives.
The exorcism was complete.
Then, you just have to find a buyer, right?
Actually, that's why I wanted to meet with you.
Is there a problem?
You should find a tenant, not a buyer.
A tenant? Why would I do that all of a sudden?
There will be a light rail station in your neighborhood soon.
If you sell it now, it will be a big loss on your part.
Are you sure they'll build a light rail station there?
I did hear something about that.
Yes. Trust me and don't sell the house for five years.
Okay.
Goodness.
Ms. Na Young Mi.
Peekaboo.
You are so beautiful.
Let me get that for you.
I'm Hong Ji A of Daebak Realty.
The house is on the market?
But I can't buy that house.
Even with that condolence money,
after I pay the medical bills and the interests on the mortgage...
The landlord decided to rent it out as a deposit-based house.
The deposit isn't that high. I am sure it'll be within your budget.
But why are you offering me this listing?
My job is to find the perfect tenant.
I've been thinking and you are the perfect tenant for the house.
Think about it and call us.
If you want the house,
we can proceed with the contract electronically.
So you don't have to bring your baby all the way to our office.
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E10 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"Life in Vain"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
You rarely see a south-facing house like this one nowadays.
Doesn't the house get a lot of sunlight?
People say small apartments are built poorly, but that's outdated.
Fire-resistant materials were used for this house.
And it was designed to endure earthquakes as well.
You have nothing to worry about.
Oh, right. The master bedroom is the wow factor of this house.
I like that the mountain is so close.
You like listening to the birds in the morning.
The thing I love the most about this house is the elevator.
With the elevator, when your baby is born,
you can easily go down with your stroller.
Mom. Thank you.
(2021, Green Villas)
Why are you smirking like that? It's creepy.
How did you come up with the idea of sweet-talking him to find a tenant?
That was the perfect move.
"Sweet-talk"? I'm not you.
I was merely reminding my client to consider...
the property value as his real estate agent.
Anyway,
you did what the deceased wanted to do for her daughter.
Suit yourself.
(Daebak Realty)
Right here.
What are you doing in here?
I asked, what are you doing?
My goodness. What just happened?
Why am I here?
No way. Was I cleaning here again?
Goodness. Darn this side effect after being possessed. Gosh.
Do you have a death wish?
How dare you act as if you don't know what you are doing here?
- Let's talk after you let go. - Get out.
It was foolish of me...
to think for a second that you actually might be a good guy.
I was just trying to study.
You scare me that I could die from this job...
whenever you get a chance.
And I can't handle the emotions from the spirits...
after the exorcism.
You know,
it was my first time hating someone so much...
that I wanted to commit murder.
And I realized for the first time...
what it meant to have your heart broken out of sorrow.
But after doing the exorcism,
it made me feel like I was helping people.
So it made me feel good.
That's why I was trying to find a proper solution.
I'm not talking about punching the sandbag or drinking to forget.
I wanted to find a proper solution that I could accept.
After the contract,
you can just live an ordinary life like before. That's the solution.
Besides, there are no solutions.
So don't waste your time and leave.
(Cheonha Building)
("Ghost Chaser")
Hello. As you requested,
I'm on my way to film the spirit at the PC cafe.
(Cheonha Building)
Every lot on the ground level is vacant.
Is it because of that spirit?
(For Rent)
(Cheonha Sauna)
This is where the spirit of the PC cafe is sighted.
The PC cafe is closed down now.
Sir. Hello.
Are you here?
If you are, please answer me.
("Ghost Chaser")
I thought you guys specialize in managing haunted buildings.
- You guys never seen this before? - They are part-timers.
Please go on.
I mean, I'm already angry...
that a perfectly fine building is haunted.
Now that this kind of footage is online,
no one would want to rent out the lots in my building.
My building is the only one that has vacant lots.
If I could, I just want to sell it.
- But my wife is against it. - Of course.
It's an up-and-coming neighborhood.
- It'd be foolish to sell it now. - Right.
We will find great tenants for you soon.
My goodness.
Did anyone die in that building or did you kill anyone recently?
Pardon?
So you saw the unrested spirit in this video.
She's just asking you if you have any ideas who that might be.
Given the nature of our job, we must ask this question.
You don't recognize this guy? You don't?
Name, Han Dong Hee. He was 23 when he died.
His story made the headlines three months ago.
He played games in the PC cafe...
which is in the basement for two days without any sleep.
And he came outside late at night for a brief moment.
Then, he dropped dead due to a heart attack.
- A life in vain. - One could be that exhilarated.
But is it possible for spirits to be filmed on cameras like this?
It's not common, but this happens from time to time.
Well, for us, we get to identify him without making the trip,
so it makes things easier for us.
Can we find out the time of death?
Around 4am.
(Current Time, 3:53am)
Tell me about the building.
Cheonha Building.
The building owner runs a dry sauna in the basement.
And his daughter runs a bakery on the rooftop.
And the lots on the rest of the floor are vacant.
Should we start it now?
I know his face and name.
There's no point delaying it.
(One way)
(Cheonha Sauna)
Take it out from the bamboo tube and scatter it.
Make sure to cover the entrance.
What's this?
Salt.
I see. This is salt.
By the way, why are we scattering it?
It's a way to block the unrested spirit...
from running away after possessing your body.
I see.
Wait. Then, what if this shield breaks?
What happens?
You saw it yourself.
When we first met.
Will you do that all night long?
Gosh. My life depends on it.
I can't do a half-hearted job.
Do you have plans this late at night?
Why do you keep checking the time?
The unrested spirit will show up soon.
How do you know that?
This unrested spirit is endlessly repeating...
what happened right before he died.
He will show up at the exact location...
where he died at the exact same time.
Get your necklace ready.
How close is he?
Take it off now.
Oh In Bum.
Put your necklace back on.
(Basement Level 1, Sauna, Red Clay Sauna)
There's one more unrested spirit?
I'm possessed.
This is not real.
Hong Ji A. Open your eyes.
Come to your senses, Hong Ji A!
Mom.
Mom. Help me wake up.
I'm sorry.
Hong Ji A.
It's dangerous to stab everywhere like that.
You have to stab it in the heart, in one go.
Let's try again.
Help me.
Wake up.
Ms. Hong.
Ms. Hong!
Hong Ji A!
Are you okay?
Are you all right?
Help me.
A child.
There was a child.
(Sell Your Haunted House)
There are too many oddities.
Why did my mom...
try to do an exorcism ritual without a psychic?
You remembered that while you were bewitched, so it may be distorted.
I need to know what exactly happened on that day.
I found everything on the internet regarding Cheonha Building.
We're a great team.
You want me to go in here?
No matter what kind of memories come into you,
forget them right away.
Was that unrested spirit murdered as we expected?
Even this morning, he swore to kill that murderer, and his eyes were...
As soon as Oh Sung Sik died, he took the nephew and...
Oh In Bum?
It's about Oh In Bum.
I don't think it's too late to call off your contract.