[English subtitles are available]
Hold on!
Dear customer, we're sorry,
but no touching is allowed here.
You…You got me wrong, Hitch!
Titans' memories are often triggered
by physical contact, so...
I thought I might be able to get
important information from this.
It's not like that I had any improper
thought or anything!
You're a guy, after all.
I understand why you would want
Annie's precious information.
I'm sorry, okay?
Just please don't throw me out…
I'm not gonna do that.
I'm sure Annie is bored just
having me as her chatting partner.
Eh?
I can't believe you.
All you do is sleeping, so why
are you so popular?
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Angels planning disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
(#71 Guides)
I don't mind you being interested in her.
But do you know what's
going on in the world?
Yeah.
Read this.
"The military continues to cling to
power and unjustly detains Eren Yeager."
The concern towards the military
is at its boiling point.
The military hasn't said anything
that pleased the crowds, after all.
Even so, they can't reveal the existence
of Zeke or the Rumbling.
Only Eren can save Eldia!
Only Yeager can avenge our citizen who were eaten!
The New Eldian Empire can
not exist without Eren Yeager!
What is this?
It's said the people have surrounded
the entire military base.
Hey, Hitch! Help us out!
Ugh, more work...
Armin!
Mikasa!
Thank goodness.
I'm glad you made it here safely.
We can't waste this chance we got.
Let's hurry.
The new recruits of Survey Corps?
What are they doing in the HQ?
I did go to meet Eren that day.
Oh?
I'm sorry that I didn't tell you earlier.
No wonder you'd detain the volunteers.
You sure act meek all of a sudden.
That was my thought before.
You people don't know what
the world is like.
It would be too late if you kept
postponing the discussion.
Eren had the same concern as I did.
So that's why you advised Eren to infiltrate
Marley to force the military into action?
I didn't say anything of the sort.
But I did say the military
government needed some push.
Is that all?
You put yourself in danger
just to meet him in secret.
Surely you had a specific agreement in mind.
Of course.
We weren't in a position to formally
request a meeting with him, after all.
Yet you still decided to
meet him in secret,
thus successfully manipulated Eren
and accomplished Zeke's goal, right?
There was no point of doing that!
I just wanted Eren Yeager to
get to know me and…
Anyway,
to us, Eren's Founder was the key
to crush Marley once and for all.
He delivered a massive blow to Marley
just as we had hoped.
No.
It was beyond what we imagined.
He punished Marley that made us
suffer for years all by himself.
He's a such a powerful person
who even possesses the Founding.
Commander Pixis.
Do you know what's unfolding
before us right now?
We're witnessing the moment
when the history changes.
This world will be reborn
thanks to the brothers.
I just want to witness it
right next to them.
In other words, what drove you to
meet Eren in secret was your curiosity?
You can say that again.
The other Volunteers don't know
that I met him in secret.
This is all because of my reckless action.
It's true that I deceived you,
but everything I did was for Eldia.
I hope so, too.
Tell us what you talked about. All of it.
Do you know the best way of telling lies?
The best way is to mix truths in it.
I can't believe this.
I'm honestly disappointed that
you guys still doubt us after all this time.
We're comrades, aren't we?
We broke a sweat together
in these past three years.
We built rails, trades system,
and everything to flourish this island!
We were completely devoted to Eldia.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect this would happen only ten months
after the opening ceremony of the railroad.
Yes, indeed.
We swore to fight for
Eldia's future, and yet...
What…What is it?
Eh?
Yelena admitted that she met
Eren in secret?
Is that true?
So you really don't know?
Of course I don't.
Really.
It does look like it.
At least to me.
Yelena...
"There is no way Yelena would do that."
It's what people usually say here.
Should I assume you've expected her
to do something like that since you didn't say it?
Well, that's...
It came in the wrong order,
but now we've got enough convincing
reasons to detain the volunteers.
Tell us everything you know about Yelena.
For the sake of our future cooperation.
As you already know, it was
Yelena who organized the volunteers.
It was hard for us to work together at
first as we were suspicious of each other.
But each time, she would
get her own hands dirty
to show her loyalty towards
Zeke and the organization.
She'd even kill the friends who
lived with us for a long time.
All the Marleyan who doubted us
were gotten rid of as accidental deaths.
We overcame that by believing it was
all for the sake of our stolen homeland.
That's odd.
Eh?
In here, she argued with the military
government for Marleyan's human rights,
even though she used to
be merciless on them.
Yet on this island…
Now,
come with me, Onyankopon.
Eh?
Hange is still on the move, isn't she?
Yes.
She said there's something
she needs to confirm.
Yeah.
I did allow her to take
one of the volunteers along, but...
I can't let you two meet Eren.
Why is that?
Because we're now certain that
the volunteers are in contact with him.
Eren concealed his secret meetings
with the volunteers,
leading up to the assault on Marley.
We're currently looking for the mastermind
behind these meetings along with his followers.
Eren has maintained his silence ever
since these facts were brought to light.
We still know nothing about what
he did during his time alone in Marley.
We believe that Eren is being
controlled by Zeke.
I only share these because
you're his close friends.
So please keep it a secret.
Eren is being controlled?
No way...
What will happen to Eren?
What's that?
Hmm?
It's nothing.
I had nowhere else to put this,
so I had the recruits bring it here.
But Sir!
If he's staying silent, then maybe
we can do something about it!
I can't guarantee you that we can
get Eren to speak the truth,
but it should be worth a try.
This situation requires great caution.
That is all.
Why?
As you said,
it should be worth a try.
So why did he refuse?
If I had to think of a reason...
The military government might've
already given up on Eren.
Excuse us.
If that's the case, they would already
start looking for the Founder's hire.
I'm going to eavesdrop.
Wait, Mikasa!
It's okay. I won't let them see me.
We can't afford violating
any rules now.
Given the situation, we need to know
the military's next move as soon as possible.
Whatever happens, I won't let Eren…
Armin! Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Put out the fire!
- What happened?! Anyone injured?
- Hurry!
Over here! Get help!
Hurry!
Are you two okay?
Hitch, what happened?
The Supreme Commander's room
just suddenly...
Where's the Supreme Commander?
Dedicate your heart!
Our anger has reached them!
Now is the time to fight!
I will fight, too!
- Me, too!
- So will I!
That's right!
Let us bring victory to
the New Eldian Empire!
Dedicate your heart!
Supreme Commander Zackly's
personal custom chair.
It is believed that a bomb
has been planted in it.
Four soldiers, including Commander
himself, were lost in the explosion.
The culprits and their motivation are unknown.
He was with me all day.
And the volunteers are
under house arrest.
Then are there any other
factions you can think of?
That chair...
Commander said that he had
the recruits bring it for him.
From which branch?
He only said recruits.
But before Mikasa and I visited his room,
we saw recruits running away from the HQ.
They're from the Survey Corps.
Speaking of the Survey Corps...
I heard some of its members were punished
for leaking information about Eren.
Could it be...
Emergency!
Eren Yeager has escaped from
the underground cell!
Assemble all soldiers
and search for him!
Roger!
Hurry! We will go, too!
Armin...
Just... what is happening?
What a big group.
How many are here?
We have more comrades
beyond the ones present here.
Including those who blew
Darius Zackly away with bomb.
You're the only one who can
save the Eldian Empire.
Eren Yeager.
It will be okay, Mikasa.
Eren will understand.
I'm sure he will,
once we talk with him.
Locate Zeke's position.
Over a hundred soldiers,
including Flock Foster,
have disappeared from their
cells along with their guards.
It is believed that all of them have abandoned
the military after Eren's escape.
It should be safe to say that they're also
the ones who killed the Supreme Commander.
We need a name for them.
We will now call them the anti-military
organization, the Yeagerists.
As for their objective...
Do you know, Hange?
Their one and only goal should be
to put Zeke and Eren in contact.
Then, to reform the military
under the leadership of Eren.
They're showing their resolve through
assassinating the Supreme Commander.
The final trigger was the Military's plan
of transferring the Founding Titan
without notifying us
in the Survey Corps.
We knew exactly what would've
happen if we had told you.
Not to mention, most of the Yeagerist
are from the Survey Corps.
How are you going to take responsibility
for that, Commander Hange?
I will accept any punishment necessary.
But resigning from my position right now
would be the most irresponsible thing to do.
And we still don't know how many
hidden Yeagerist are out here
or which branch they belong to.
That's right.
They might even be standing
right in front of me right now.
Any of you could explore here
and I wouldn't be surprised.
Roeg, don't be ridiculous.
How are you going to prove it?
Unless you can, we can't let
the Survey Corps roam free!
Enough!
We still have a guest here.
Don't we have other things to do
besides bickering amongst ourselves?
Hange.
How many soldiers know
where Zeke is being confined?
Levi and the 30 other soldiers
who were watching over Zeke.
Plus another three who were responsible
for resupply and communication.
And me.
Bring those three here.
Nile, is the Queen's residence secure?
Only a select few know where it is,
but I'll go back and check.
Eren's first objective would be
to make contact with Zeke.
Next, Queen Historia.
We need to make sure these two
are under absolute protection.
Yes, sir!
Commander Pixis!
Now that we've lost the Supreme Commander,
the only one who can
lead all of us is you.
Do you have any plans going forward?
We've lost.
Let's surrender to Eren.
There's nothing we can do
with enemies inside the military.
Even if we did manage to smoke out
every last one of them,
a lot of blood would be
spilled in the process.
We have no time to waste on such folly.
Our actions have made many soldiers
desert the military.
That is why we lost.
No way!
Are you going to give in to those
who killed the Supreme Commander?
I knew Zackly for a long time.
I'm sure he'd be satisfied to
live and die for the revolution.
Most of all,
the four who died wouldn't want their
funerals to come at the cost of Eldia's fall.
So you're planning to submit
to the Yeager brothers?
It's not submission.
We will negotiate with the Yeagerist
using Zeke's location as a bargaining chip.
We'll do the Rumbling experiment as planned
and stake Eldia's survival on it.
However, we will not talk about
the assassination of our top dog.
If that's what's needed to prevent the deaths
of hundreds, if not thousands of our comrades,
then it's worth it.
Now all of you, get on it!
Yes, sir!
Commander.
I apologize for that unseemly display.
No, it's a path any country would go through.
We can no longer ensure your safety.
Please stay close to the port until
the situation is under control.
Yes.
We sincerely hope for Eldia's victory.
Miss Mikasa.
If anything happens, please
escape to our ship at once.
Thank you for your consideration, Lady Kiyomi.
But I am an Eldian.
I want to watch over the future of
this island where I was born and raised.
Please, no need to mind me.
What are you saying?
We came here for your sake…
Even without the underground resource?
You don't care who leads this nation...
...as long as the Rumbling succeeds, right?
...Yes.
If the Rumbling's power is not
what it promised to be,
Hizuru will surely cut off
their ties with us.
What we've invested will be
for nothing and Azumabito will meet its end.
In that case,
I have more reason to not rely on you.
We Azumabito have always adapted
to tumultuous times.
But now we've been derided as
wretched, penny-pinching vixens.
Still...
We can't afford to lose our pride as a clan
that your mother handed down to you.
Whatever happens to this nation,
I will do anything to protect you.
Can't believe we're supposed to work with
Eren who killed the Supreme Commander.
We still don't know for sure
if Eren is the one who did it.
Keep your voice down, Mikasa.
You know people already suspect
us being Yeagerist, right?
Seriously speaking, whose
side are you on, Mikasa?
I told you Armin and I nearly
got caught up in that explosion.
Is that not enough clue for you?
Huh?
Stop fighting.
Like Commander Pixis said,
infighting will only lead to our downfall.
Then are you saying it's okay to
entrust everything to Eren and Zeke?
No.
That's not good.
Judging from the situation,
Zeke and Yelena's insurance plan
is taking effects.
We should expect they have more
under their sleeves.
We need to figure out Zeke's intentions
before they make even bigger fools out of us.
Of course, it would be nice if this
is all just my wild speculation.
Do you have any leads?
The Marleyan POWs workplaces
that she oversaw seems suspicious.
Like the restaurant, for example.
What a nice place!
It's the first time
I've been in a place like this.
Me, too.
Isn't this great, kids?
Make sure to eat a lot today.
Yes!
Those darn soldiers sure are noisy today.
♫ In an instant ♫
♫ In an abandoned world ♫
♫ If you can't fly, please tell him ♫
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes
I will be immortal ♫
Gabi and Falco seek help from
the captured Marleyan soldier.
Will they find a bright future
from what they believe in?
Or perhaps...
Next Episode: Children of the Forest