♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles and
reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 1=
(Wake up.)
(With your authentic self and ceaseless hope,)
(look for the deepest secret
in your heart.)
(Wake up.)
(Then, you will see your authentic self.)
(Then, you can reveal
the glossed-over truth.)
(Go through the sincere lies)
(to your innermost thoughts)
(and somewhere far away.)
(Maybe you will be reborn.)
(Maybe you will fall
into the deepest darkness.)
Dad.
The nails to be sent
to the village head today...
Dad.
Why are you drunk again?
You will catch a cold here.
Come on. Let me help you in.
Dad, easy.
Sit down.
Come on.
(Purple Demon Eye!)
(Hundred Projectiles!)
Where is he?
It is spilled all over the ground.
What's going on?
(I can't get rid of it.)
(What should I do?)
(I can't run back home,)
(or the monster will follow.)
(Ghostly Trace!)
(Since I can't get away,)
(I can only take the plunge.)
(Purple Demon Eye!)
(It wasn't killed.)
It has been blinded.
Did you destroy its eye?
(Lone Wolf Shield Body!)
Are you a man or a ghost?
I am Su Yun Tao from Martial Soul Hall.
My name is Tang San.
What's so scary?
Haven't you seen
Martial Soul Shield Body?
Thank you for saving me.
I have to go.
Where are you going?
I'm going to catch the spider.
Kid, do you know
the Human Faced Demon Spider
is cruel and bloodthirsty?
It is a frightening creature
among Soul Beasts.
You were just lucky
that you weren't devoured by it today.
Kid, don't run around
in the forest.
I'm almost a grown-up.
You are almost a grown-up?
Your Martial Soul is
not even in the waking state,
but you managed
to destroy the eye
of the Human Faced Demon Spider.
I just threw out a nail.
It moved too fast and hit it by itself.
Why do you carry nails with you?
My dad is a blacksmith.
Normally,
only Soul Masters can fight Soul Beasts.
It's a miracle for a boy like you
whose Martial Soul hasn't awakened
to blind a Human Faced Demon Spider.
I was just lucky.
Martial Soul is the manifestation
of one's inner strength.
Dad.
I saw a huge spider
in the forest today.
Fortunately, Mr. Su
came to my rescue.
He also gave me a book.
At first,
I thought he was strange.
Later, I realized
that we are the strangest ones.
Dad.
Do you think this book is reliable?
The book says
that everyone in the Douluo Continent
has Martial Soul.
Dad.
Have you been
to any places
beyond the Saint of Soul Village?
The wine is finished.
I'll take care of it.
Dad.
Mr. Su
was really amazing.
And he had Martial Soul.
His Martial Soul could transform.
It looked like a wolf,
very scary.
But he beat off
the huge spider.
He said he was a Soul Master.
Dad, do you know what a Soul Master is?
He also said he was
from Martial Soul Hall.
The huge spider was a Soul Beast
called Human Faced Demon Spider.
I haven't heard of it anyway.
But Dad,
I destroyed an eye
of that huge spider today.
I think
it is pretty good
to become a Soul Master like Mr. Su.
He was charismatic!
Will I have the chance
to be such a Soul Master
in the future?
Did you use your ability?
I used Purple Demon Eye, Ghostly Trace,
and some projectile skills.
Did that guy see it?
Dad, rest assured.
I assure you that he didn't see it.
Dad.
What is a Soul Beast?
I didn't find
any relevant content in the book.
They are fantastic animals
with Soul Ring power.
They can be any kind of animal.
Are they ferocious? Are they man-eaters?
There are good and evil people.
So are the Soul Beasts.
It turns out
that there are good and evil beasts.
Soul Beasts are not wild beasts!
They are
far more intelligent
than ordinary beasts.
The Soul Beasts that have lived
for more than 100,000 years
can change into the human form.
By then, there is no difference
between humans and them.
Are there many Soul Beasts
that change into the human form?
Soul Masters and Soul Beasts
are natural enemies.
Soul Masters hunt
and kill Soul Beasts endlessly.
It's never easy for a Soul Beast
to live more than 100,000 years.
Are you the officer
from Martial Soul Hall?
Your place
hasn't held
any Martial Soul Awakening Rite
for a long time, right?
The Saint of Soul Village
is relatively remote.
The road condition is bad.
It's really been a long time
without any Soul Master coming here.
Officer.
Can we have the pleasure
to have someone from Martial Soul Hall
to carry out
the Martial Soul Awakening Rite here?
I will be staying here for two days
to prevent the return
of the Human Faced Demon Spider.
I can carry out
the Martial Soul Awakening Rite.
Thank you, Officer.
I will inform the children
and let them come here tomorrow.
Okay.
The village is surrounded by mountains.
Beyond the mountains is the river.
Where is the river flowing?
To the outside world?
What does
the World of Martial Soul look like?
Maybe it is
not as good as Mr. Su described.
The Saint of Soul Village is safer.
There are neither Soul Beasts
nor Soul Masters.
Tang San!
Village Head?
Village Head, please come in.
I am leaving soon.
Long story short.
Come to my house
after you wake up tomorrow morning.
To repair the roof again?
No.
Officer Su Yun Tao
is going to carry out
the Martial Soul Awakening Rite
for us tomorrow!
Martial Soul
is like a seed
planted by a farmer.
It is planted in everyone's heart.
When the Martial Soul awakens,
the seed no longer sleeps.
It will be awakened!
And then,
when you have
the right Soul Ring one day,
you can become a Soul Master!
A Soul Master?
What about after becoming a Soul Master?
You will be respected by everyone.
Do you want
to stay here and be a nobody
doing chores for your whole life?
Should I help you to tell everyone
to attend the rite?
It can't be done
after a certain age.
In short,
you must come to my house tomorrow.
He is not going!
Dad.
If I
had held out longer today,
I might have been able
to escape by myself.
You don't study Xuan Tian Records
to make your escape,
but to defeat
all Soul Beasts and Soul Masters,
and become
the strongest man in Douluo Continent.
Dad.
Doesn't it sound a bit overstated?
Since you've already known
about the Martial Soul,
Soul Masters, and Soul Beasts,
why didn't you tell me?
I didn't tell you,
but you learned it anyway.
Have you memorized this book?
I have.
Every single word.
Dad, what are you doing?
Since someone from Martial Soul Hall
has come to the Saint of Soul Village,
I can't keep this book anymore.
Why?
Remember.
You must keep everything
about Xuan Tian Records to yourself.
Never tell anyone about it.
I remember that.
Dad.
What exactly is Xuan Tian Records about?
Why have you been telling me to practice it
since I was young,
while I can't tell others about it?
Dad.
Is Xuan Tian Records
related to my mom?
Dad.
No!
Don't eat me!
I'm too skinny, not yummy!
(Tang San.)
(I'm waiting for you.)
Why am I weeping?
(Tang San.)
Who are you?
Dad.
Go wash up since you are up.
Remember to buy me wine.
I had the same dream again.
It was still the same field of Blue Silver Plant.
I heard a voice
calling my name.
What else did the voice say?
She said she was waiting for me.
The voice sounded
especially warm and gentle.
Could it be my mom?
Ever since I practiced Xuan Tian Records,
I have been having the same dream.
Was it
my mom's voice?
How is Xuan Tian Records related to her?
You are not qualified
to learn about your mom yet.
I will tell you about it
when you are strong enough.
Why do you say that every time?
How strong do I have to become?
Keep practicing.
Will I become stronger
after the awakening of my Martial Soul?
Yes.
Then, I should
join the rite
in the village head’s house.
You are not allowed to go.
You asked me
to become stronger, didn't you?
Dad.
Where is
my Essential Soul Master Handbook?
There wasn't enough firewood,
so I burned it.
I'll gather some firewood later.
Focus on the hands.
It's a Tool Soul, the sickle.
Not too bad.
It is something of a weapon.
Withdraw it using your mind.
Touch it with your right hand.
Kid.
You have no Soul Power,
so you can't be a Soul Master.
Thank you, Officer.
(One can't become a Soul Master)
(even when he has Martial Soul?)
Tang San.
Why didn't you come in?
Mr. Su.
I thought about it all night long.
My dad, the village head,
and you
told me
about the World of Martial Soul
beyond the Saint of Soul Village.
But each one of you
told a different story.
Since you are eager to know,
you should figure it out yourself.
Don't you want to know
what your own Martial Soul
or your family's Martial Soul is?
I can also know
my family's Martial Soul?
Martial Soul can be inherited in the family.
The Martial Soul of either parent
will go to their offspring.
You didn't cower when you
confronted the Human Faced Demon Spider.
I can see that you are
strong-hearted.
I believe that your Martial Soul
may also be powerful and special.
So you are very likely to have
the potential of becoming a Soul Master.
Apart from becoming a Soul Master,
is there any other way to get stronger?
In Douluo Continent,
there are no other possibilities.
I want to get stronger.
I want to be a Soul Master.
Stretch out your right hand.
Blue Silver Plant?
How could it be Blue Silver Plant?
Come out.
Is this my Martial Soul?
This...
Blue Silver Plant
is the commonest useless Martial Soul.
It can neither attack, defend,
nor support.
A person with such a useless Martial Soul
can never be a Soul Master.
I can't get stronger anymore?
Since you are here,
take the test
and see how strong your Soul Power is.
Officer,
with a Martial Soul like Blue Silver Plant,
strong Soul Power is meaningless.
I know.
Come on.
You were born with full Soul Power?
That is one in a million.
Thanks for letting me know
what my Martial Soul is.
I'm quite happy about it.
My dad is waiting
for my return with firewood.
I should get going.
Village Head, I'm leaving.
Tang San.
Do you want to join
Nuoding School?
Don't I have a useless Martial Soul?
Why didn't you
go with Su Yun Tao?
Since you didn't agree with it, I wouldn't leave.
I forbid you to go
to the awakening rite,
but you went there anyway.
Dad, I know I was wrong.
But Mr. Su said
I inherited my Martial Soul
from you and my mom.
I joined the Martial Soul Awakening Rite
in order to know more
about my mom.
What is your Martial Soul?
They told me
it is a useless Martial Soul,
but I still stand a chance.
I can become a Soul Master
and attend Soul Master School.
You chose this path in the end.
I allow you to go,
on two conditions.
You can be a Soul Master,
but you must not join Martial Soul Hall.
Why?
Make a vow.
I vow
that even if I become a Soul Master,
I will never join Martial Soul Hall.
But Dad,
as they said, I've got a useless Martial Soul.
Make the fire stronger.
Aren't you curious
about Xuan Yu Hand's function?
I will tell you now.
Make the fire stronger.
Dad, does the Martial Soul
only manifest on the right hand?
I somehow felt that there was
something hidden in my left hand
when I was
at the Martial Soul Awakening Rite.
Spread your palm.
Focus.
Release the power in your heart.
Twin Martial Souls?
Is having Twin Martial Souls rare?
Make it visible.
Dad.
This is so difficult.
I feel that something in my heart
is suppressing me.
Release your inner strength.
It really is Hao Tian Hammer.
Hao Tian Hammer?
Dad.
This hammer looks ugly.
It's too heavy.
Dad, I can't hold on anymore.
Take it back.
Don't let anyone see
the Martial Soul in your left hand.
I got the hammer and Blue Silver Plant
from you and my mom?
If one day,
this hammer can no longer be restrained,
you must remember
that this hammer is not a tool for killing.
It is meant to be a guardian.
A guardian?
What does it guard?
It guards your right hand
and protects the Blue Silver Plant
in your right hand.
Remember.
In the future,
always protect the plant
in your right hand
with the hammer in your left hand.
Always.
I remember it, Dad.
Look.
This is the second condition.
You have to work this piece of iron
into a fine needle.
Then, you can leave.
Dad.
Are you exaggerating it?
Look at me.
It is too fast to be seen.
Use Purple Demon Eye.
I see it clearly.
The hammer
hits it at the same point every time.
It makes no mistake.
This is the gist of Tempering a Thousandfold.
Gather all your strength at one point.
Turn a piece of ordinary metal
into a magic weapon.
This is Xuan Yu Hand.
When you use the hammer,
fill your hands with Qi.
It turns out that Xuan Yu Hand
is for forging.
Dad.
Village Head, I did it!
You are leaving,
but he doesn't even see you off.
Actually, my dad is nice to me.
Nice to you?
He just doesn't know how to express it.
Okay, we'd better hurry.
We have to travel across the mountains.
Come on.
(Never let anyone see)
(the hammer in your left hand.)
(Never mention Xuan Tian Records)
(to anyone.)
(You have to walk on your own.)
What's wrong?
I forgot to bring the nails.
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination
is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways and
we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as
another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break
ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways and
we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as
another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break
ordinary rules in life♪