(This is based on the Tale of On Dal in Chronicles of the Three States.)
(Characters, incidents, and dates do not match historical facts.)
I would like to speak.
It is about the Princess' marriage.
You will never get your own way.
I am offering a chance.
A chance for you and your offspring to save your lives.
They are looking for the King's son-in-law.
The Princess will marry.
I will always be on your side no matter what.
I cannot accept your feelings.
I must have her...
even if that means I have to use force.
(Episode 9)
What is that sound?
They are officially announcing the royal wedding.
They are calling the candidates into the palace.
Princess.
Come here quick.
Look at this. Are they not pretty?
What is all this?
What do you think they are?
We need to make a dress for your wedding.
Not just a wedding dress.
From head to toe, you will need so many ornaments.
They have not yet selected her husband-to-be.
- Why would you already... - How dare you to interrupt?
I will not marry.
Stop being so childish.
The King gave the command,
and the Five Tribe council decided on it.
Do you not know this is a joy for the palace as well as the people?
The wedding where the bride is bartered...
is not a joyous occasion.
Princess.
How dare she?
She has such an odd temperament.
What now?
Where could she go other than to see her father?
Princess.
Many young men of noble birth...
have applied to be your husband.
The King is greatly blessed.
That means your influence is even greater.
The influence that made this preposterous marriage...
a possibility.
You have everything in the world.
What more do you want?
Tying me down with marriage...
will not benefit you at all.
This is not for me.
The marriage is for you, Princess.
If you keep lashing out with stupidity and bravado,
you might...
follow in your mother's footsteps, and we cannot have that.
If your mother had acted appropriately for her status,
she would not have died the way she did.
Shut your mouth.
How dare you mention my mother?
We do not need any more...
misfortune in the royal family.
The King saw my intentions...
and allowed your marriage.
A man crazed by jealousy...
killed his own wife and people.
Does he deserve to sit up here?
Father.
Did Go Won Pyo threaten you...
into agreeing to my marriage?
Do you fear his weapons that much?
Why?
You are King.
I had a dream every night.
A dream in which you and your mother die.
A nightmare in which my people are slaughtered.
I committed those dreadful deeds myself.
How can I avoid punishment?
When you returned to the palace,
I was afraid.
It felt as if my past wrongdoings had come back to life.
And I was also pleased.
Your mother...
had given me a chance to atone.
If they had known how you felt,
the Sunno Tribe migrants would also rejoice.
However...
Before being the King,
I am but a powerless father.
I wanted to...
do whatever I could to protect you and the Crown Prince.
So...
is that what happened?
Did Go Won Pyo...
threaten you with our lives?
I am sorry.
I did all that I could,
and yet I could not prevent your marriage.
Princess.
Will you forgive me?
Father.
The herb gatherer is gone,
and a young noble is here.
Your clothes...
did more than just change your looks.
Mok Tae Seon, a silk merchant from Jami Province.
I just have to say I am his son?
Creating a fake identity is not all.
You will be questioned to see if you studied all the classics.
When given a theme,
you must also write a poem.
I do not need to do that.
Do you truly think that is possible?
Even if you apply as a candidate,
General Go will end up marrying the Princess.
That will not happen.
I cannot let Ga Jin be forced into a marriage.
We feel the same.
You are in love?
Fate.
She and I are destined to be together.
So I cannot let her marry.
I will do whatever it takes.
They turned us into traitors so they could get rid of us.
I was a fool.
I underestimated Go Won Pyo.
For Father.
And for Ga Jin.
Go Won Pyo.
I will kill you and die myself.
Read the theme for the poem in the envelope.
I heard that General Go did not apply.
Does that mean we have a chance?
You are such a fool. Do you think your father or mine...
sent us with hopes to become the King's in-law?
It is what the Five Tribe council commanded.
What do you mean by that?
They will fail all of us and when they think there is no one worthy,
they will recommend General Go as if there is no substitute.
If his eldest son were to enter the selection process,
how would Gochuga manage to judge fairly?
Darn it. I am here to stand in the background, then.
Let us go and get drunk with some girls after this.
Next.
Here she is.
I am here at your command.
Welcome.
I called her because...
she deals in herbs and also rare accessories.
Hey. It was my idea to call her.
Do you feel better?
Both the Princess and Crown Prince act as they wish.
No one knows how stressful that is for me.
I just hope my son has an uneventful future.
I heard a talented fortune-teller has set up shop in the city.
Shall I ask for you?
Fortune-telling? I have so many questions too.
Where is he?
I brought some accessories that will suit you.
- Pick a few later. - No, thank you.
I will say this because I agreed to not keep secrets.
I was unable to do as you asked.
That young man. On Dal.
The more I get to know him, the more intriguing he becomes.
What about Dal?
He will be in the palace about now.
Next.
Oh!
You look handsome and manly.
- Take a seat. - Thank you.
Let me see.
Your family does not live within the Capital.
You are from Jami Province.
- That is so. - Your father is Mok Tae Seon.
Mok Tae Seon? I have heard that name.
Is he not a merchant who sells silk...
and cotton goods?
What?
We are here to select the King's son-in-law...
and a merchant's son applied?
Do not say more than you need.
A theme for a poem is in the envelope. Write something.
I will do that.
Lord Hae, it is such a pity.
Do you not think so?
A merchant's son applied. That looks bad on us.
Stop.
- What is it? - He hid his identity...
to sneak into the palace.
He hid his identity?
Then is he not Mok Tae Seon's son?
That is true.
Oh, dear...
Then who are you?
Dal.
- "Dal"? - "Dal"?
[VIU Ver] KBS E17 'River Where the Moon Rises'
"The Princess' Husband"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
I heard something disgraceful happened...
during the selection process.
What was that?
Tell me immediately.
I wished to protect my husband.
- What? - "Husband"?
What did you say? "Husband"?
This man here is my husband.
What? Her husband?
- They are married? - This is unbelievable.
How could this be?
The Princess is married?
It is too early to be dreaming.
I am not making this up.
A eunuch rushing from the hall told me.
The Princess appeared with a young man at her side...
and announced they are already married.
That is nonsense.
Then go to the hall yourself.
It was turned upside-down.
What...
This is not your fortune.
Whose fate is it you wish to learn of?
You really are as good as rumours say.
You have such great skill,
so what did you do before you came to the Capital?
She is leaving.
I would like to hear my fortune before I am thrown out.
Did you see that person's future?
Corpses are stacked as high as mountains,
and blood flows like a river.
Starved wild dogs gather from all around,
and there is nowhere to flee.
This karma can only be atoned for with death.
What a pity.
A fate that is unavoidable.
A fate that is cursed.
When I had lost my memory and was wandering,
he showed me the way...
and allowed me to rely on him.
His unchanging heart...
is what moved me.
You asked me to release a young man from prison.
You said he had saved your life many times.
Was that this man?
Yes.
At the time, you clearly said he was a friend.
And yet now you say he is your husband.
Are you insulting me?
Father. It is not like that.
Shut your mouth.
Please calm down.
I believe the Princess is scheming to avoid her marriage.
Yes.
You are already married?
That is very hard to believe, Your Highness.
How else do we say what has been done?
- What? - How dare you?
I am...
the Princess' husband.
You are out of your mind!
How dare you raise your voice here?
You sneaked into the palace under an assumed identity!
That is very true.
We cannot accept a man of unclear identity...
and status as the Princess' spouse.
Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty. - Your Majesty.
What is your name?
My father was Daemodal...
and a Widudehyeong.
(Widudehyeong: A 5th Grade rank)
I am the son of General On Hyeop, the 17th chief of the Sunno Tribe,
My name is On Dal.
On Hyeop's son?
What?
Long time no see, Hyeop.
If you admit that you are a traitor,
I will spare the lives of everyone else.
My goodness.
You are actually the son of On Hyeop?
That is true.
Yes.
I remember that gaze.
You take after your father.
On Hyeop...
was beheaded for committing treason.
The reason his family...
and the remaining people of the tribe...
were allowed to live was by the King's grace.
He forgot about all that...
and entered the palace, causing this fuss.
He must be severely punished!
That is correct.
Please punish him severely.
Punish him?
They may have married in secret,
but he is the Princess' husband.
Must he be dealt a severe penalty?
Your Majesty. You must not do anything to harm your authority.
Having a royal marry someone from that bloodline...
already harms the royal household's authority!
Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty. - Your Majesty.
Silence!
Your Majesty.
- My goodness. - What is happening?
You did nothing but cause trouble since you returned,
and you ended up bringing disgrace on your father.
- Father. - Shut your mouth!
You are no longer my daughter.
Leave the palace immediately.
I will accept any punishment. The Princess...
Did you not hear me?
I no longer have a daughter.
The next time I see you,
I will behead you both on the spot.
Are you all right?
My lady.
The Princess was ordered to leave the palace.
She must leave?
I am sorry, Nanny.
I am leaving after causing you much distress.
You are not married.
Tell the King that you lied. Please?
Do you not believe it either?
I cared for you even before you could murmur.
Do you think I do not see through you?
I would rather leave the palace with you.
I will look after you and...
No. You must protect my brother Won.
You are the only person I can entrust...
his safety.
Oh, dear...
Are you the man my sister married?
Oh, the Crown Prince?
Crown Prince.
Are you really leaving?
Leaving me on my own?
Father is so furious.
I have no choice.
You must beg.
Ask him to forgive you.
Beg to let him allow you to stay.
If you leave again,
what do I do alone?
You might never be able to return this time.
I will return.
For you and  Father, I will come back.
You and Father both. I hate you.
I hate you all.
Do not say that.
Father is trying to save my life.
This is the only way I can avoid the royal wedding.
Father gave the order but he is crying inside.
The Princess came to say goodbye.
Are you out of your mind?
There is no princess in this family.
You must leave without seeing your father.
Father.
Do you hear me?
I am leaving the palace.
I wish more than anything to remain here with you,
but accepting your command is also my filial duty.
So I shall leave.
Until now,
I did nothing but cause you concern.
Please forgive me.
Do not worry!
I will protect the Princess.
You have made a very difficult decision.
Since the Princess has left,
the palace will finally find peace.
Are you happy about that?
Of course not.
I only wish for peace and safety in the palace.
If you have any regrets,
you can always tell the Princess to come back.
How could he kick you out like this when you are a princess?
He is so mean. He did not even see you out.
Dal.
I need to stop by somewhere.
Where?
I will be right back, so you should go ahead first and wait there.
Let us meet at the entrance of Mungyeongsaejae.
You are going alone? Let me tag along.
Do not worry.
From now on, we will always be together.
Make sure to come back fast!
I was surprised when I heard that you are already married.
And you had to be kicked out of the palace all of a sudden.
I do not know how to console you.
You need not say anything.
I am here to ask for your help.
It is a waste to take you as my enemy,
but I cannot fully trust you to have you on my side.
But you came to see me nonetheless.
That must mean that you want to put trust in me.
I also wanted to know why you helped me.
I know you are good at figures, and you have nothing to gain from this.
Do you remember what I have told you?
I...
abhor Go Won Pyo.
I may not resent him as much as you do,
but I want to protect...
the tribe my father has been keeping, the Sono Tribe,
even though I am his step-daughter.
Then you should help me.
Let us stop the Gyeru Tribe from abusing their power,
and together we will bring Go Won Pyo down.
I thought you would be grief stricken,
but I guess I do not know you enough.
Will you be on my side?
There is something I want to ask.
If you wish to proceed with your plan,
what will you do with General Go?
What if the two families of the Go's...
shed blood?
I trust Master Go.
He is different from his father.
I thought I would catch up with you at the hill if I hurried.
But what are you doing here? Where is the Princess?
- She left first. - Is that so?
Then you must have been waiting for me.
There is nothing I want to talk about with you.
That is a shame.
But my sword has a lot to ask you.
I will keep you updated regarding the King and the Crown Prince.
I will secretly help with your plan,
so entrust it with me.
I appreciate it.
I feel like I have finally found a friend in the Capital.
I am flattered, Your Highness.
If you go back to the King and tell him the truth,
I will spare your life.
But if you keep pretending to be the Princess' husband,
I will end your life here.
I pity you.
You do not want to admit that you lost Ga Jin.
That must be why you want to behead me.
Shut your mouth.
Go ahead and kill me.
Even if I die,
I will never give Ga Jin to you.
All right then.
I cannot waste my sword to kill someone as lowly as you.
I will end your life with my trick instead.
I think I have started to like you.
Get up.
How dare you...
come at a general of Goguryeo...
with the skills you gained from collecting herbs and hunting?
Do not act up and come at me.
All right then. I will end your life here.
- Get this! - Stop it!
Stop it, Dal.
There is something I need to talk about with Master Go.
Do not dare to run away!
It is over, Master Go.
The royal wedding and the arranged marriage...
are all over.
- Let us go. - What do you mean it is over?
What do you mean it is over?
Did you ever give me a chance to start?
It has been eight years.
No, it has been longer than that.
I have been longing and...
waiting for you.
I have missed you a lot.
But why did you...
tell me to give up before I even had a chance?
Why? Why did you?
It is not something we started.
Our fates have been twisted for so long...
that neither of us can untangle them.
I will untangle them.
I will remove anything that comes between us!
- So please... - Master Go!
It is all over now.
I need to leave now.
I am sorry, Master Go.
The Princess of Goguryeo, Princess Pyeonggang,
was kicked out because she incited the wrath of the King.
Since the arranged marriage came to a fail,
I will write to you again once I find out what Go Won Pyo...
cooks up for a scheme.
General Go!
General Go! What happened?
Bring me some medicines.
I cannot go back to the palace in this state.
General Go!
What will you tell the people of Ghost Valley?
Do not worry.
I will tell them that this all happened...
because of the royal wedding, and that our marriage is not true.
What if they find out?
What?
People from the Castle...
might come and spy on us to see if we are a married couple.
What will you do if they find out we are not a real couple?
Hey, then we can pretend to be living...
Should we live together?
This is about us, not anyone else.
I know.
I am your husband, and you are my wife.
What is he saying?
- Ga Jin. - What?
Let us do that.
We can tell the villagers that we got married.
That way, people from the Castle will not be able to find out.
But this does not count as a real marriage.
Why not? Am I not good enough as your husband?
Darn you!
It does not matter if it is real or not.
As long as I can be with you...
and protect you.
My father was Daemodal...
and a Widudehyeong.
I am the son of General On Hyeop, the 17th chief of the Sunno Tribe,
My name is On Dal.
On Hyeop,
you are tormenting me even after your death?
I knew this would happen!
So the rumour about the Princess being kicked out of the palace...
must be true!
- I guess so. - You just found that out?
Did she really get married to the son of a merchant?
Are you kidding me? I hear he is a fool.
I hear he is a total idiot.
I have never heard of that. My gosh.
That must be why the King was infuriated.
It is certain that the royal wedding has been cancelled.
I think she was kicked out of the palace last night,
but I have not found out her whereabouts.
She must have gone to the village of the herb gatherer.
Then the guy she got married to...
Ga Jin is helping me.
Sorry?
We would have definitely run into Ga Jin...
if we went into the palace.
She left at the right time.
Should I still tail her?
Leave her be.
When we see full moons several times...
and when the stars shine in different places,
she will come back herself.
[VIU Ver] KBS E18 'River Where the Moon Rises'
"The Married Couple"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
General Go, are you up?
How did you bring me here?
You came to me yourself.
I did?
Take the medicine.
It will soothe your nausea.
Do not be worried. There is no poison inside.
Do you not think you need to pour me a glass...
since I have kicked out my own daughter?
Here. Let us get drunk.
The Princess must have gone to...
the village of the Sunno Tribe.
Well, I do not wish to know...
where she is staying.
Why not?
Were you not planning to...
bring back the Sunno Tribe into the Five Tribe council...
up until recently?
You did not eliminate the source of trouble.
That is why you are facing trouble now.
Who knew the spouse of the Princess...
was the son of On Hyeop?
You need to put out the ember even if it is too late.
I remember it.
You and General On studied under the same teacher as young men.
Although you were older than him,
I heard General On was more skilled in martial arts.
On top of that, he was beloved and trusted by the people.
He must have upset you in many ways.
However,
he was beheaded for committing treason.
You were the one who ordered it.
My sins in this world run deep and are heavy.
That is why I called you here today to ask for a favour.
I have disowned my only daughter.
And I only have two sons.
And if you try to use my sons...
to threaten me again,
you must kill me with this arrow first.
I will pay for my sins in death. However,
you and your family will also be in a pool of blood.
All right. Okay. Let us drink.
Here.
You can stay a bit longer to gather yourself.
Vicious rumours will spread if I, the eldest of the Gyeru Tribe,
was found in the room of the daughter of the Sono Tribe.
I was not aware that rumours had sway over you.
I will send someone to pay for the medicine.
General Go.
You must take care of your mind and body.
How could you bring back the fate that had already been lost?
Know your place.
The Princess lied about her marriage.
There may be a piece of truth...
in that lie.
I can carve it out...
whether it is the truth or not.
Mother, you will hurt yourself.
You ungrateful son.
You little brat. Do you wish to see me die?
My goodness. You brat! Because of you,
I could neither sleep nor eat.
I could have died, worrying about you!
Did you know that?
My gosh. This hurts!
You may kill me at this point.
Come here.
Are you all right?
Gosh, do not worry. I am all right.
Goodness. You troublemaker.
Who is there? Who did you bring?
Have you been well?
I came back with Ga Jin.
Ridiculous. How can that be?
You said she was a princess.
She should be in the palace. Why is she here?
It just happened.
So tell me how on earth that happened.
Well...
Let me tell her.
I hope this will not come as a big shock to you.
Actually, Dal and I...
are married.
What? You are what?
We are married.
I cannot understand what you just told me.
So who is married to whom?
So Ga Jin and I are married.
I am her husband. She, my wife.
What... What on earth...
You punk! How dare you tease your blind mother!
Mother, it is true.
I do not want to hear it.
Gosh.
He is back!
- He came back! - Hey!
Dal is back now.
My gosh, he is back?
But why are you out of breath?
But he did not come back alone. He brought Ga Jin.
No. He came back with the Princess!
- What? The Princess? - What?
Hey. My Ga Jin is back? Are you sure?
She is back. But the thing is...
Come on, tell us. You are making me dizzy.
They are married. Ga Jin and Dal got married!
- Married? - They are married.
- Married? - Really?
What is going on? Dal got married?
Ga Jin.
My gosh. I thought I would never be able to see her again.
Mother, open up.
I get that you are furious.
But at least hear our side of the story.
Mother! You are not going to see your son ever again?
Dal.
We should give her some time.
She must be shocked.
Gosh.
They must be scared because you are the Princess.
Thank you for taking good care of my father.
But I am not here as the Princess.
Then, what are you?
Are you really Dal's wife?
Yes.
I am Ga Jin's husband.
That is true! They got married!
Gosh. What a way to shock all of us.
Did you spend your first night together?
- Gosh. - Goodness!
What did I tell you?
I told you these two were fated to be together!
Congratulations.
Father.
It is your son.
I came with Ga Jin.
You remember her, right?
General On, I am indebted to Dal and the Sunno Tribe...
once again.
Please be generous and watch over us.
She is your daughter-in-law.
That is true.
Come on.
The Chief is here. Do not make him stand here.
No matter how it happened, this is a happy occasion.
Please accept them with your generous heart.
Please think about the kids who must have been through a lot.
You do not know anything.
They are facing a long road of trouble and pain now.
Why did they... Gosh.
Are you telling me that you lied to avoid the royal wedding?
What choice did we have?
Ga Jin was about to get married without this lie.
The three of us knew something was up.
When we saw you at Pyeongyang Castle,
you did not seem to be engaged.
We cannot lie to you.
But you must keep this a secret.
If this gets out, it will put Ghost Valley and us in danger.
I heard you spend your first night at the bride's house.
Yeom Deuk was preparing the blankets for you.
What?
Gosh. Hey!
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
- Look at them! - What are they doing?
My gosh. What are you doing? That is so vulgar!
Get out of here! Go!
- Look at them! - Leave already!
Hey. Let me crash at your place tonight.
- Of course. - Let me sleep over there.
- Dal, do a good job! - Gosh.
Bride. Groom. Sweet dreams!
- They have no time to sleep! - Gosh. Get out of here.
- Leave, you punk. Go! - Look at them!
Gosh. I did not think about this.
Right.
Do you want to go to sleep?
I should.
- Go ahead, then. - What about you?
- This is comfortable for me. - I am good too.
Go to sleep already. You must be sleepy.
- No, I am not. - You even yawned.
You are the sleepy one.
I am not sleepy!
Why are you getting mad?
I am not sleepy, but you keep telling me to go to sleep.
You are getting mad at me for nothing.
Hey. Where are you going?
I need to use the bathroom!
Why did you touch me?
My goodness.
Gosh. Seriously.
Gosh.
Moon.
Tell me what to do!
Do you have an answer?
I should not have gotten married!
It is making my heart do somersaults!
Gosh. It feels weird. Seriously.
Gosh.
What is taking him so long?
- What is it? - Gosh.
If you went out to use the bathroom again, you might pass out.
Why do you care?
What about you? Why are you playing the pipe in the middle of the night?
You cannot even play it.
Why do you care if I play it or not?
I never had the chance to learn it.
Cheonjubang?
I am good at playing the pipe.
Hey. That...
I mean...
Hey, you are dirtier than I thought.
"Dirty"? How could you say that about me?
What about this, then? Why put this on your lips?
If I wanted to kiss you, I would have done it a long time ago.
Why would I put my lips on this sogeum?
Liar.
You are the liar. You are sleepy, but you are not going to sleep.
You are the coward.
Kissing does not scare me.
Same here.
Then, try it.
You try it.
You...
(River Where the Moon Rises)
It feels weird to lie down here with you.
I came back here to live as Dal's wife.
I am not here as the Princess or to play.
Are you sure you will not regret it?
What is my daughter-in-law doing?
I am coming.
I ask to be the head of the royal bodyguards.
You despicable spy.
I will end you here, so you never go back to Silla.
I will get everyone at the palace on my side.
Get the Prince's trust first.
You planned it when you were at the palace, right?
And me becoming a general must be part of your plan.
Do you know why I am not teaching Dal the swordsmanship?
Once he wields the sword, he is bound to see blood.
That is the fate of a swordsman.