EPISODE 13
Angel? What a joke.
WELCOME TO SEBOM HIGH SCHOOL'S
ADMISSION INFORMATION SESSION.
- It's Ju Kyung.
- Hey, it's Lim Ju Kyung.
Seriously?
Ju Kyung. Is this really you?
The real face of Saebom High's Lim Ju Kyung.
She was the dumpling girl
before she transferred.
You guys will faint when you see this.
She's mad ugly. It's all makeup.
This is too much.
- No way.
- What a joke.
Look at this. My gosh.
Unbelievable.
Ju Kyung.
Lim Ju Kyung.
An angel? As if.
Drag her along.
No, let go of me.
Let go!
I thought it was Han Seo Jun you were dating.
But Lee Soo Ho?
- Seriously?
- What a flirt.
How did you seduce him
with this face of yours?
No way.
Does he know your real face?
If not, he'll dump you.
But if he does know? How
are we to interpret that?
An angel, my foot.
Grab her.
What are you doing?
- Stand still!
- Come on.
We just want to look at your real face.
- No, don't!
- But it'll be fun.
Don't!
- Unbelievable.
- Darn.
Is that her?
- No, don't!
- Why not?
Her skin already looks different.
- What a joke.
- Don't!
- Seriously.
- Are you kidding me?
Just look at this.
- No way.
- Can you believe it?
Get your hands off her.
Ju Kyung? Ju Kyung!
Ju Kyung. Out of my way!
Where are you off to?
Are you crying?
Hey, Ju Kyung!
- Have you seen Ju Kyung?
- Did you two argue again?
Did you see her or not?
She ran that way...
Whatever. Who cares if they argue?
Seo Jun! You won't believe
this about Lim Ju Kyung.
Don't ever mention her to me
again. I'd rather not care.
Just take a look at this. Here.
SHE'S MAD UGLY. IT'S ALL MAKEUP.
BOYFRIEND
The fact that Lee Soo Ho's dating you...
makes him seem like a loser too.
BOYFRIEND
4 MISSED CALLS, BOYFRIEND 3
- Did you see that video?
- Of course.
I can't believe we almost fell for it.
Angel Lim Ju Kyung? As if.
Tell me about it. Look how ugly she is.
Seriously.
Darn it.
- What did you just say?
- What?
- I dare you to repeat that.
Darn it!
Are you kidding me?
- Hey...
- What's your problem?
- Shouldn't we call the teacher?
- Guys, stop it.
What?
- Say that again.
- What?
I dare you to say it again!
- Say that again!
- Say what again?
Lim Ju Young, stop. Just stop!
Don't.
Have a seat.
Calm down and let your anger subside.
There you go. Good job.
I'm upset about what happened to Ju Kyung,
but violence should never be the answer.
They say, "Not even a flower
should be used as a weapon."
Anything can be solved through words.
Hand.
When did you become a puppy?
Here. I saw scars on your hand.
She's unrecognizable, don't you think?
My eyes nearly popped out.
- What happens now?
- Beats me.
- Is it something entertaining?
- Hello, sir.
- It's this way.
- I know.
It's time for the morning assembly.
I don't see Ju Kyung or Soo Ho.
Maybe they went on a date.
Mr. Han, I think Ju Kyung
is going to be absent today.
I wonder if she's sick.
By any chance, is she absent because of me?
Hee Kyung.
- Hello.
- Mr. Han?
We're dating.
Why do you have to date my homeroom teacher?
This is going to make my
school life so uncomfortable.
Mr. Han, Seo Jun is absent too.
- He's absent too?
- Yes.
It's Han Seo Jun.
What's he doing here?
He's so good-looking.
- Who is he?
- I don't know. He's so handsome.
Is he from Saebom High School?
Hey, Seo Jun.
I heard you asked for me. Why?
I told you I won't stand still if
you did this kind of thing again.
And what exactly are you going to do to me?
Delete it while I'm being nice.
- Delete what?
- The video you showed me yesterday!
You uploaded that on our school community.
What? Your school community?
What are you talking about?
Someone uploaded that on
your online school community?
My gosh, that's unbelievable.
You came here because of that?
Well, I'm sorry to tell
you this, but it wasn't me.
- It wasn't you?
- No, it wasn't.
Dumpling doesn't even go to our school.
Why would I upload it on
your online school community?
No one else would do that garbage but you.
That's not true.
How do you think I found out
that Lim Ju Kyung was Dumpling?
Will I...
be able to get married?
The guardian card?
Mr. Prince, is Ju Kyung here?
No.
My goodness. Hey, Soo Ho.
Hello, by any chance...
My gosh, why do you look so haggard?
- Is your leg okay?
- Yes, is Ju Kyung...
How's Joo... I mean, how's your father doing?
I guess he's doing okay.
I shouldn't have asked.
- By any chance, did Ju Kyung...
- What? Ju Kyung?
Never mind. I'll be off now.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
Don't skip meals!
And be careful of cars. You don't
want to get into another accident.
Shouldn't he be at school right now?
I wonder why he came here.
Ju Kyung, that brat.
My gosh, she must've bought
more makeup products.
What's this?
STUDENT REGISTRATION CARD
"COSMETOLOGIST LICENSE WRITTEN TEST BOOK"
That little...
Soo Ah, you really didn't know?
You and Ju Kyung were best friends.
Best friends, my foot.
- Come on.
- She acted like she was pretty...
and even became our school model?
- I know, right?
- How did she end up dating Soo Ho?
- I'd never be able to do that.
- I'm sure he didn't know...
how she looked like with no makeup on.
- Do you want to make a bet?
- Watch what you say.
What was that?
Follow me outside.
- Why?
- Do you want me to say it here?
The class is about to start.
Just follow me outside.
- What's going on?
- Hey, stop him.
- Shouldn't we stop him?
- What's going on?
Let go of me.
Were you always a piece of trash?
- Delete the video.
- No.
"No"?
Why do you care?
What do you think Soo Ho would
think of you if he finds out?
Delete the video before I
go and tell him it was you!
Go ahead and tell him. I'm not scared.
- What?
- Plus, I can't delete it.
It's not like deleting it
is going to change anything.
Everyone in the school
has watched it already.
Why are you doing this?
Is it because of Soo Ho?
Do you think he'll even think of
you as a friend if he finds out?
"A friend"?
I don't want to stay as his friend
only to like him one-sidedly...
like you're doing with Ju Kyung.
I bet you think...
you destroyed Ju Kyung by doing this.
But you just destroyed yourself.
- Cho Rong.
- Yes?
- Come outside.
- Let me just get this...
precious poop out.
Just get out there already.
Gosh.
- My gosh.
- Hey, what are you doing?
I heard only the school community
webmaster can delete the posts.
Who's the webmaster?
How would I know?
Why don't you know?
I don't even know when this
poop is going to come out!
Then hurry up and find out.
How do you expect me to find
out who the webmaster...
Wait a minute, Seo Jun.
What do you have anything to do with this?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, you're being...
No way. Do you like Ju Kyung?
Cut the nonsense. Just find out who it is.
How am I supposed to find out, you dumb punk?
What's the matter with your class?
I heard two of your students...
didn't come to school without notice.
That's probably because their
homeroom teacher is too busy dating.
"Dating"?
Hee Kyung, do you think we were too selfish?
Hey, kid.
You know this is the last stop, right?
Where are you? Ju Kyung.
Just tell me where you are.
GIRLFRIEND
Hey, kid.
You're still here?
You missed the last bus.
It's too late. You should go home.
It's cold outside.
You should hurry up and go home.
Go home, okay? My goodness.
BOYFRIEND: JUST TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE.
YOU HAVE 4 MISSED CALLS.
You will be directed to voicemail.
Ju Kyung, where are you?
Where are you?
Just tell me where you are, okay?
- Hello?
- Is your sister home yet?
No, she isn't.
Where is she at this hour?
Got it.
Ju Kyung!
Ju Kyung.
"COSMETOLOGIST LICENSE WRITTEN TEST BOOK"
STUDENT REGISTRATION CARD
Ju Kyung, is that you?
Where did you go with your phone off?
The study room.
- Don't you lie to me!
- Honey.
You went to this makeup academy, didn't you?
I wondered where you were
until late every night.
Let's talk later.
Where did you get the money to pay for this?
I've had a really tough day.
- Let's talk tomorrow.
- Answer me!
Where did you get the money to
do this garbage behind my back?
You're home.
- I got a job.
- What?
A job?
You got a job instead of working?
Who said you could do this?
I said let's talk tomorrow. Leave me alone!
Yes, honey. Let's talk tomorrow.
- Yes, Mom.
- Shut it.
Say you won't do this
stupid makeup stuff. Now!
Why...
Why must it be makeup?
Do you want to end up like me?
Demand a refund tomorrow.
No. I'll do it myself.
If you do this again,
I'll kick you out of this house. Got that?
Why must you do this too?
I want to do it. What's so wrong with that?
Why does everyone tell me no?
I want to do what I want
and see the person I like!
Can't I be happy?
Don't I have that right?
You brat! Get back here!
- Honey. Honey.
- Ju Kyung!
- Honey.
- Let go of me!
Let's talk about it tomorrow.
Ju Kyung.
She's dating Soo Ho with this
face? They are not a good match.
Soo Ho, get it together, man.
Shouldn't we get a new model for the school?
What if people call us the ugly school?
What an easy life thanks to makeup.
Compared to her, I have the face of an angel.
I'd kill myself if there
were a video like this of me.
Who posted this? Isn't this school violence?
I'll kill everyone who posts
nasty comments after me.
Look at his face.
"I'll kill everyone who posts
nasty comments after me."
How cringy.
"I'll kill everyone who posts
nasty comments after me."
Shut it.
"Shut it."
Why you... Cho Rong. Cho Rong!
Did you find the webmaster?
Wait.
Tell me who the webmaster is, and
you get a date with Han Seo Jun.
- Not a joke.
- Seo Jun.
What will you do once we find the webmaster?
Are you her knight in shining
armor who will save her?
- Seo Jun likes...
- Hey.
- Eat this.
- Ju Kyung!
Where?
Hi, I'm Ju Kyung. Hi, Seo Jun.
I'm not that easy.
Please wait for the next signal.
Why are you calling? To hear my voice first?
Stop.
Don't cross the street.
Let's talk like this.
I'll lose my resolve if I see your face.
What do you mean?
Let's...
- break up for a while.
- What?
Out of the blue? Why?
I don't think this is right.
I didn't know it would
hurt Ju Kyung this much.
Had I known you were her sister,
I wouldn't have even started it.
That's overkill.
Who breaks over something like this?
I... I'm being transferred next year.
In a year's time.
Exactly at this hour on this day next year,
if we still love each
other in a year from now,
let's get back together then.
What? A year?
Stop. Stop.
Please stop.
Goodbye.
Joon Woo!
Han Joon Woo!
What kind of a breakup is this?
Soo Ho.
- Why have you come?
- I've known you for years.
I felt I should apologize
for causing you pain...
with Se Yeon's matter.
You should apologize to
him and his family, not me.
You're right. I went to them...
and begged for forgiveness.
I'll live in repentance
for the rest of my life.
Soo Ho. Your father really...
didn't know.
He took the fall for it though.
Even in the past. He never crossed the line.
Why are you the one explaining that to me?
He may not be good at expressing it,
but he cares deeply for you.
That I know.
So resent me all you want,
but not your father.
I wanted to tell you that...
after hearing how much pain this brought you.
I'll get going.
Are you free today?
I'm leaving the country soon and
would like to see you before I do.
- Soo Ho!
- Where's Ju Kyung?
She'll probably be skipping school today too.
Then tell her to pick up her phone.
I doubt she's in a position to do so.
Aren't you going to school?
All this because I forbid you
from taking makeup classes?
Why is she suddenly being a moody teenager?
Just head to the salon.
I'll have a quiet talk with her later.
RESTRICTED ACCESS
Then tell her I'll be
waiting at Prince Comics.
Gosh. You really must love her.
Skipping school yet again?
No, just get to school.
I'll tell my dad to have
her answer her phone...
once she calms down a bit.
Off we go.
Hold on. Which brand are those sneakers from?
That was immature of me, right?
Forget I said anything.
The online bulletin board has been firing up.
- My goodness.
- Look at all these hate comments.
We should probably shut
down the school website.
I guess we should.
Gosh.
Is this why she was absent
from school yesterday?
How are we supposed to handle this?
The kids in the video aren't
students at our school,
so we can't call a committee hearing.
And how are we supposed to
find out who posted this?
What about Ju Kyung? Is
she not at school today?
No.
And we have a student
refusing to come to school.
The incident seems to be of grave nature,
so you should discuss this
with Ju Kyung's parents.
Yes, sir.
Han Joon Woo, did you have
to overreact like that?
In a year's time.
If we still love each
other in a year from now,
let's get back together then.
Hee Kyung, do you have the
materials for the meeting?
A year, my foot!
Darn it.
Okay, take all the time you want.
REAL FACE, MONSTER
Look at what they did to her face.
- Soo Ho, it's you.
- Hey.
Watch what you say, okay?
UGLY FACE! ROTTEN SMILE!
Who on earth did this?
Why not just rip it off?
SUPER UGLY!
How's Ju Kyung?
The one who uploaded that video of her...
I know.
You do?
I love you so much, oh dear
You're too pretty, what do I do?
My eyes already need cleansing.
I'm not in the mood to laugh, so stop.
How about a smile? I'd love to see it
Just smile for me, giggle!
Leave it to you to make me smile.
You laughed!
I love it that you smiled
Oh, dear
What do I do?
I'm thrilled
You're too pretty, what do I do?
Soo Ah, I love it that you smiled
Oh, dear
I'm on the moon, my gosh
Guys, take your seats
for the morning assembly.
Once again, Ju Kyung is absent today.
Mr. Han, will we be choosing
a new face for the school?
- Kids have been wondering.
- Exactly.
How can Ju Kyung be the face of our school?
- I know.
- Right?
Gosh.
Is that why you ripped all her posters off?
You know why she isn't at school today...
and must be aware of...
how she's feeling right now.
But I see that no one's worried about her.
I'm disappointed in you all.
Your actions terrify me.
How can you laugh at a video...
of your friend being humiliated like that?
Is the pain that Ju Kyung had to suffer...
just a joke to you?
Ju Kyung, have you eaten anything?
Don't tell me you're still crying.
- It's Lee Soo Ho.
- Do you think it's true?
I doubt they're dating.
Yes, Ju Kyung and I are dating.
- What?
- No way.
Soo Ho, don't you have anything to say to me?
Like what?
Why didn't you tell me
that you two were dating?
After all I did to bring you two together?
It killed me inside...
to know that she had rejected you!
Being worried...
kept me up at night. I
thought I was your friend.
Right. Sorry about that.
Ju Kyung wanted to keep it a secret.
Do you know what's more upsetting?
Han Seo Jun seemed to be
aware of you two dating.
So?
You make up and now I'm kicked to the curb?
Who would you save if Seo Jun and I...
- were both drowning?
- You.
Me? Really?
Seo Jun's good at swimming.
You'll still save me first, right?
- So...
- Yes, my friend. Ask me anything.
What's the best way to lift
up a girlfriend's mood?
I wasn't going to tell you this, but...
RESTRICTED ACCESS
Ju Kyung, don't you want anything to eat?
I taped back the student registration card...
for your makeup classes.
I'll persuade your mother on this,
so please come out and
eat something. Ju Kyung?
Ju Kyung...
Check out that smell.
Can this look any better? I
bet it's driving you crazy.
Welcome to "Dad's Delicious Food Trip".
The pork belly grilled by
me couldn't be juicier.
This looks amazing.
Come on out. How can you persuade
your mom on an empty stomach?
Don't you want her approval?
Okay, let me take a bite first.
You won't believe how good this is.
I've never tasted pork belly quite like this.
Is this pork belly or ice cream?
Come on out and have the
pork belly I grill...
that melts in your mouth.
Seo Jun! Seo Jun...
- I...
- What?
What are you saying?
Is it huge?
Is it your stomach?
Is it about a university?
It's about the school community!
- Found...
- You found...
You figured out who the webmaster is?
Who is it?
FRESHMAN, JIN HUI JEONG
Seo Jun, wait.
Wait for me!
- Stop it.
- Get back here!
Let go of me, you crazy cow!
I know it was you.
I don't care if you received a
tip. How dare you post that online!
Take it up with the one
who actually posted it!
Who am I to censor everything?
- Why that little...
- Let go of me!
Didn't you tell me that
violence wasn't the answer?
Not even a flower should
be used to hit people.
And who on earth are you? Let go of me!
Get your hands off her!
- What...
- No way.
It's Han Seo Jun.
Seo Jun...
Yes, it's Han Seo Jun!
- It's Han Seo Jun!
- Who are you to butt in, brother?
Brother?
Did you know?
What did you just say to my sister?
Sister?
He's her brother?
Han Go Woon's his sister?
A crazy what?
- No way.
- My gosh.
Are you the webmaster of
the online school community?
Yes.
You'll take the video down, right?
Unbelievable. I told you not
to make it known at school.
Was I supposed to stand by and do nothing?
I held back, you know.
You should've held back more.
By the way, why don't you want
people to know I'm your brother?
- Are you ashamed of me?
- You're clueless.
You...
It'll be like middle school all over again.
Girls will ask me to set them up with you...
and pick on me for not looking like you.
Tell me who they are and I'll...
Forget it. Don't ever set your
foot on the freshman floor again.
Go Woon!
Fly, don't you dare follow me.
Why not? I thought you were
deeply worried about me.
You.
What... What?
Are you still bothering her?
Must I teach you a lesson?
Why though?
Am I not even allowed to like her?
Haven't you ever liked anyone before?
Do you think I can just
stop loving her just...
because you tell me not to?
I have no control over my feelings, okay?
Bye then.
I'm sorry.
Did something happen between you guys?
What? No, why?
Never mind.
That video of Ju Kyung got
deleted from the school community.
Really? That's great.
Let's go.
Soo Ho.
Gosh, you came again?
I told you I'll let you know
once Ju Kyung feels better.
Why don't you just set up a
tent in front of our house?
Can you give her this?
This is a nice gesture,
but she won't even come out of her room.
Then she wouldn't have eaten.
Are you going to let her starve?
It's nice that you're looking out for her,
but my job isn't to run your errands.
Do you want me to pay you?
Do you want my shoes?
Soo Ho, I'd love to have...
No, wait. I shouldn't use my
sister to get what I want.
Give me that. I just need
to give it to her, right?
Ju Kyung.
Gosh, you're so quiet in there.
Is she thinking of doing
something bad to herself?
Ju Kyung! No!
Ju Kyung! Ju Kyung, no!
Ju Kyung... What?
What are you doing?
Ju Kyung, you startled me!
Hey, wait.
Soo Ho bought you this.
You should have a bite.
Soo Ho's been waiting for
you ever since yesterday.
At least pick up his calls.
I've been meaning to
come to see you, Mr. Han.
I found out...
that Ju Kyung wants to learn makeup.
You have no idea how
frustrated I am right now.
She even got a part-time job...
and enrolled herself into
an academy behind my back.
My goodness.
Did you know about this?
Ma'am, the thing is,
that's not why I wanted to meet you today.
That's not why?
This might shock you.
But I feel like you should know
what Ju Kyung's going through...
since you're her mother.
Is...
Is this Ju Kyung?
Are you sure this isn't fake?
Is this really my daughter?
Ju Kyung...
Ju Kyung?
Hey.
Did you wait out in the
cold? You should've called.
I came to ask you something.
You came to ask me something?
I know it can't be you.
But I couldn't stop imagining stuff.
Soo Jin.
It wasn't you, right?
You're the only one...
who knows my secret including the fact...
that I'm dating Soo Ho.
I couldn't think of anyone
else who knows that.
But still, it wasn't you, right?
You weren't the one who uploaded
that post online, right?
If you don't think it
wasn't me, why are you here?
Because I wanted to hear it from you.
I'm sorry. I can't tell
you what you want to hear.
Why?
Why did you do that?
Why would you do something like that to me?
Because I hated seeing you with him.
What?
You came to our school
because you got bullied...
at Yongpa High School, right?
Why don't you go ahead and run away again?
You're good at doing that.
Run as far as you can and hide...
so no one finds you.
That's all I have to say to you.
LIM JU KYUNG'S SPOT. SIT WITHOUT
PERMISSION, AND GET A HAIRY BUTT!
I organized all the books. Is there
anything else you want me to do?
You don't need to do anything.
Just read the comic books.
I need to do something to kill time.
Why are you killing time here?
Be honest with me. Ju Bal
dumped you, didn't she?
- No.
- Gosh, come on.
If a guy waits night and day in
front of his girlfriend's house,
that's always why.
That's not it.
You're frustrated, right?
Pick a card.
I'll tell you how Ju Bal feels.
I'm good.
You have to kill time anyway.
Pick one.
Wait. That's the Lovers card.
What does it mean if you
pick it up upside down?
Hold on.
THE LOVERS
UPSIDE DOWN: PARTING
- Ju Kyung.
- Where did you go?
Out front.
Did you eat?
I'm not hungry.
Why not? You brat...
My baby.
Mom.
Mom went to your school today.
Why didn't you tell me?
You should've told me.
Why did you keep it pent up all by yourself?
Because I knew you'd do this.
How could I tell you?
Even still! You should've told me!
I had no idea that was happening to my baby.
Who was it?
I'm going to get them
back. Tell me. Who was it?
- Mom.
- Mom. Stop crying.
You'll upset Ju Kyung.
It must've been so painful for my baby.
Did...
the kids hit you?
Where did they hit you?
Tell me now.
No. They didn't hit me.
It's in the past. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
My baby.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know because she was always smiling.
It's because I killed her self-esteem.
She was too scared to tell her own mom.
It's all my fault.
Why is it your fault?
We got pregnant with Ju Young...
right after we had Ju Kyung,
so we left her with my parents to raise her.
That's why people said she was adopted.
She received no love at home,
so she got no love elsewhere.
It's my fault for not raising her nicely...
or treating her like she was precious.
Whom else could I blame?
It's my fault.
You had to work your fingers to the bone...
and had no time to look after
the kids. It's my fault.
I yelled at her for wearing makeup.
That was why she got so upset
when I threw out her makeup.
I'm sorry I didn't know.
It's nothing.
Ignore what those kids say.
You decide your own worth.
If you're confident, no one
can touch you. Understand?
Stop crying, and go to sleep.
Get out.
- Why?
- Get out.
- Where are we going?
- Just come.
Seriously.
Will you remove your glasses?
I think it'll cost quite a bit.
Just make her beautiful. Like an angel.
- An angel.
- Mom.
First, she already has double eyelids,
so we can alter the shape of
the eyes to make them stand out.
We'll slit the inside and the outside.
We'll make them bigger. Like the beauty apps.
As for her nose, we'll add silicone...
to raise the bridge.
As for the tip, we'll cut off
a piece from the left ear,
implant cartilage to make it stand up...
She has such a cute nose though.
It's like a clove of garlic.
People complimented her nose all the time.
From a medical perspective,
it is not a pretty nose.
Also, we'll slice her hairline...
and give her a facelift.
We'll make it as tight as
possible and sew it on.
Then we'll take fat from the butt...
and inject it into the
forehead, chin, and cheeks.
With a full face fat transplant,
her flat face will have a
more three-dimensional look.
Why does she need that?
She isn't a westerner.
We'll grind down the entire
surface of her jaw...
and carve out her cheekbones...
Why would you grind her face?
It's not a coffee bean or a spice.
That will give her a
narrower jawline. The v-line.
You need a wider jawline for good fortune.
What do you want from me?
If you want to make this face pretty,
you need to change everything.
This isn't a renovation.
What do you mean, change everything?
She'll become pretty if
you cut, carve, and grind?
Who sets the standard for
what's pretty and ugly?
My daughter is pretty in my eyes.
Mom. Stop that. Let's go.
My gosh. Do you want to see it?
For this face to become pretty like this,
you have to change everything about it.
Oh my gosh. This is the face we
get after spending all that money?
She looks like this with just makeup on.
What is this?
Plastic surgery is not as good
as my daughter's makeup skills.
Let's go. Why would we put a
knife to this perfectly good face?
But...
What? An angel?
I heard that video spread
all over the school.
Don't worry.
I'll transfer you to a school
where nobody knows you.
What?
Why don't you go ahead and run away again?
You're good at doing that.
Run as far as you can and hide...
so no one finds you.
That's all I have to say to you.
Ju Kyung's here.
Were you crying?
No.
So why won't you let me see you?
Because I'm sorry.
- About what?
- Because of me,
kids have been making fun of you too.
It's why I can't look at you.
I'd still like to see you.
I waited for you here all day, my squirrel.
How can that not make you laugh? Meow.
Those jokes are old, you know.
- You still don't get it.
- What?
I'm so glad.
I missed you so much.
- Let's go outside.
- What?
You can't hide here forever.
Let's go.
Are you exhausted already?
Yes. Why don't we go back down?
- Put some muscle into it.
- I can't.
I've been starving all day,
so I'm lacking the energy.
- That leaves only one option.
- Yes, let's walk back down.
I said we should walk back down!
- I'm heavy, you know.
- Let's go.
I said I'm heavy.
What do you think? Isn't it nice up here?
Yes, it is.
Why did you run off that day?
You have me by your side now,
so why did you run off?
You're right.
I ran off again.
I guess I wanted to hide.
Why would you hide when
you did nothing wrong?
Because it's humiliating.
The kids...
now know what I really look like.
What do I do?
Are you saying you look fake with makeup on?
No matter how you look, makeup or no makeup,
you're always you.
So this is what I once read.
Do you know which country
produces the tastiest tomatoes?
Spain.
- Really?
- Yes.
The soil there is the hardest
for tomatoes to survive on,
which made them that way.
How so? It's not the best condition to grow.
That's exactly why.
Trying to survive the toughest terms...
makes them tastier and richer.
I see.
You know how fruits...
that aren't conventionally
pretty taste sweeter.
I'm sure that's the case with people too.
Are you trying to tell me that I'm ugly?
Yes.
I'm only joking. I guess
I don't know everything,
but you're stronger than you think you are.
You're even stronger than me.
I'm going to try and be stronger now too.
Why on earth am I here?
They fit perfectly. You can
walk toward me in these.
I'll be good to you.
So be with me, Joon Woo.
My two feet...
keep walking toward you, Hee Kyung.
Oh, no.
- Hee Kyung.
- Hey.
What brings you by my office?
Your agency's being sued for various charges.
Are you heading home?
You get hungry around this time of the day.
Why don't we grab some dinner?
I don't see why I'd go to dinner with you.
Why can't you? It's not like
I'm asking you out again.
It's only an innocent meal.
Wait, are you seeing someone?
A boyfriend?
Of course not.
For a year, I won't be able to say that I do.
Sure, let's grab dinner. Where should we go?
You like spicy food, so how about that?
Sounds good.
Thank you.
Are you all right?
LIM JU KYUNG
Is Lim Ju Kyung all right?
LEE SOO HO
The video was taken down.
Are you going to skip school tomorrow?
My mom offered to let me transfer schools.
What?
I'm sure she didn't mean it.
I doubt we have any money to move again.
I don't want to go back in there.
Seeing how heartbroken my mom is upsets me,
and I feel sorry for doing this to her.
So you'll stay out all night?
I wouldn't mind that.
I'll head inside.
Wait.
Here.
It's up to you...
to make sure that Ju Kyung
sleeps without worrying tonight.
- I'll see you tomorrow then.
- Sure.
I'll head inside now.
BOYFRIEND
JUST TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE.
I love you so much, oh dear
You're too pretty, what do I do?
How about a smile?
I'd love to see it
Just smile for me
You're too pretty, what do I do?
I love it that you smiled
Oh, dear
I love you so much, oh dear
You're too pretty, what do I do?
Just smile for me
I'd love to see it
I love you so much, oh dear
You're too pretty, what do I do?
How about a smile?
I'd love to see it
Just smile for me
Giggle
I guess he's gone.
Soo Ho.
What are you doing outside?
What's this?
I'll be off now.
You should go back inside.
You'll catch a cold.
Okay.
Good night.
It may not be easy right now,
but I think it'll be nice to talk it out.
I'm leaving the country soon and
would like to see you before I do.
I don't want you to regret anything.
Thank you.
Hey, Soo Ho.
I'm in front of your place. Are you home?
My place?
- You're in front of my place?
- Yes.
My goodness, I'm at the airport.
I'll be in the States for a while.
- The reporters in Korea...
- When are you coming back?
I need to take care of
some stuff at the office,
so I'll be back next month.
Soo Ho.
How would you like to live
with me in the States?
You can study music there.
No, I'm not interested.
Let's meet when you come back.
You can...
buy me something delicious.
- I'll hang up now.
- Soo Ho.
Okay, I'll see you when I come back to Korea.
- Mr. Kang.
- Yes?
Have a restaurant booked...
- the day I come back to Korea.
- Okay, sir.
Actually, never mind. I'll book it.
Just tell me what kids like these days.
Okay, sir.
- Is that Lee Joo Hun?
- Isn't that Lee Joo Hun?
Come and eat breakfast.
Gosh, it smells amazing.
Did the smell seep into your room?
Yes, is it someone's birthday today?
No, it's for Ju Kyung.
She hasn't eaten for days.
I see you cooked bulgogi,
Ju Kyung's favorite.
There's even japchae.
Gosh, Mom cooked Ju Kyung's favorite dishes!
Ju Bal.
DO NOT ENTER
Ju Kyung, come down and eat.
Ju Kyung?
Ju Bal, why aren't you answering?
What? When did she leave?
- My gosh.
- Seriously?
She came looking like that?
She has no makeup on.
She's wearing no makeup?
Hey, look.
Seriously?
She's so brave.
She has no makeup on.
Look at her.
Hey, Ju Kyung.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
Ju Kyung, you're amazing.
I admire you so much.
Soo Ah.
Soo Ah! Soo Ah!
Where are you going?
Soo Ah!
Soo Ah! Soo Ah!
Hey, I heard Ju Kyung came
to school with no makeup on.
Where does she get that confidence from?
But do you really think she's dating Soo Ho?
I saw her with no makeup on earlier,
and she looked worse than in the photo.
I bet they broke up after
he saw her bare face.
Who would date a girl like her?
Isn't Soo Ho a little out
of it these days as well?
Remember what happened to his dad?
He must be dating anyone because
he's not in his right mind.
I can't believe you said that.
- Let's go.
Seriously?
Hey, look.
Hey, you!
Take back what you just said.
- Who are you?
- Who is she?
Ju Kyung?
You must be nuts to go
around with no makeup on.
Aren't you going to take it
back? Fine. I'm dating Soo Ho.
Soo Ho is my boyfriend!
Who is she?
Is that good enough for you?
Does that satisfy your curiosity?
- She must be nuts.
- Yes, it looks like it.
He doesn't judge people
based on their appearances.
He likes me for who I am.
He's incomparable to girls like you
who have horrible personalities.
So don't badmouth him just
because he's dating me.
From now on, come and talk to me in person.
I'll deal with you myself. Do you understand?
- She's amazing.
- She's so brave.
And if you have time to
judge other people's looks,
why don't you use that
time to study a bit more?
Do you know which king
comes after King Sejong?
- I bet you don't!
- Isn't it Sin Saimdang?
You're so dumb. Get out of my way.
SPECIAL THANKS TO LEE HAN
WI FOR HIS APPEARANCE.
EPILOGUE
I'm hungry.
Hey. Should we get tteokbokki?
- Okay.
Hey.
Can I join you?
What? But you're not our friend.
- What's her problem?
- I know, right?
Let's go.
COMICS
Are you crying?
Is it because the story is scary?
It's okay. Don't cry.
It isn't scary at all. Look, I'm a squirrel.
A squirrel. A squirrel.
Isn't that funny? Meow. I'm a cat.
Meow. I'm a cat. Meow. I'm a cat.
You're smiling. I'm a squirrel.
I'm a squirrel.
Did you know? If you cry then
laugh, you'll get a hairy butt!
I'm a squirrel. A squirrel.
TRUE BEAUTY
I'll only listen to people who like me.
I won't run away or hide anymore.
Ju Kyung, did you see the
post on the Community?
How will Soo Jin show her
face around school now?
Can I tell Ju Kyung how I feel?
What?
Ju Kyung!
Why didn't you answer your phone last night?
Soo Ho!
Where are you going? Why
are you running away?
Let's break up.