# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 20
Are you crazy?
Such an early morning.
Keep knocking and knocking.
Can you let me sleep?
Your brother has gone to the periodical office.
He asked me to tell you.
He put your breakfast in the fridge.
Don't forget to eat it.
What do you care?
Leave, I need more sleep, bye.
What's the time now, still sleeping?
I will get up whenever I want to.
Too much sleep will make people stupid.
Did I sleep on your bed?
What do you care?
Why did I hear a baby crying?
Did I let you in my house?
What're they doing?
What's wrong with you? Get off!
How can you old lady fight with a child?
Go away!
Seems it's an old lady bullying a kid.
How could that happen?
Look!
That kid is so upset by that old lady.
But....why does she look so familiar?
Whose grandma is she?
My grandma...
Grandma!
Here, here, don't cry. Don't.
Grandma, what're you doing here?
What took you so long?
Lighting. Wait me here.
Zorro needs me.
Grandma.
What's wrong with her?
-Look what she did to my child!
-Sorry, sorry.
[Mingzhu Nursing Home]
Where did she go?
What shall I do?
That old lady...
Director
How would my grandma run away from the nursing home?
Grandma.
How did you get out from the nursing home?
Them?
They think they can stop me?
Right, right, right
Okay, I know.
I'll see what I can do.
Grandma, have a little rest here.
Ye Muxi, come.
Although I don't have high expectation on you.
But now I need you a favor.
This weekend, me and someone need to do something
which has to be done.
That people said, they will be right there.
So I hope you can take care of my grandma for me.
Me?
I have something to do this weekend.
What do you need to do?
Many things, to set my mind free.
Watch TV.
Please.
Thank you.
[Cons]
[Pros]
Monitor, stop waiting. He won't be here.
Let Yali on.
No.
He will be here.
As long as he promises
No matter what that is, he will deliver.
But... But there's only three minutes left.
If he can't be here.
We'll have to abstain.
Sorry, I'm late.
Liao. Shouldn't you explain this a little?
Enough.
Liao Danyi.
Let's start.
Let me tell you a story.
Story?
A nice story about Zorro.
Grandma, grandma.
Another one?
What kind of story do you want to hear?
About grandpa.
About him?
Really?
Why do you want to hear that?
That day I saw those letters from grandpa.
So I'm interested.
That was a very long time ago.
I know.
Okay, that was in...
Song Dynasty when Huizong emperor was in rein.
People in the Central Plain were like  living in hell.
Come forward.
I...
You what? Hands off me!
What're you wearing?
You think you're the emperor?
I'm the emperor.
Wait, wait. Stop.
You're so annoying.
Get down.
Don't talk to me from stages.
Speak on the same floor.
What're you reading?
How the steel was tempered.
How the steel was tempered?
You were not reading it at all!
You saw me since I was still far.
Still pretending?
You're pretending that you're well educated, right?
No. I...I didn't.
Enough, enough, stop!
I told my mom.
You can't trust a blind date.
And she dressed me like this.
So embarrassing. Bye.
Miss. You made a good impression on me.
I don't have a good impression on you. Bye
Miss.
My feet hurt like hell!
Open the door!
That's how we met the first time.
How is that? Exciting?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Amazing, like a story.
Look what you said. Bummer.
Then what?
Then?
Then, in two ticks.
We were in the Republic of China era.
There were so many people in the capital.
Why are you following me?
I told you, I have a bad impression about you.
I...
I want to confess to you something.
I did see you since you were still far.
But...
I wanted to leave a good impression.
So I was quite embarrassing.
So, I stood there.
Quite nervous.
You were nervous?
Yes.
I was quite nervous as well.
After grandma started to talk.
She couldn't stop.
She started to tell me the story about her and grandpa.
Even I can tell.
Some of that is true, some not.
Because that had jumped from
Song dynasty to Republic of China era.
And the location ranged
from the Imperial Palace to Mt. Hua.
But I still enjoy it.
Because it's a story.
Story is memory with imagination, right?
Why do they look like me and Liao Danyi?
What're you thinking about?!
Make it easier for you to understand. Just that.
Okay.
A bottle of wine for your girl?
Thanks, thanks.
You keep this.
Then we came to the age to get married.
That's quite exciting.
Once more....
You open the door....
Honorable judges, dear classmates. Good morning.
Welcome to the first school-level debate competition.
Today is the final debate competition.
First, Let me introduce the Pros: Boya Middle School.
And the Cons: Maple Leaf Middle School.
Today, our topic for debating is
Whether it's unfilial to say no to the elders.
Menci said, a filial son should respect the elders.
They not only gave us our life.
And they raised us.
They worried about us, day and night.
Even the animals know to love their parents.
Don't we humans need to?
The opposite side, I think you have mixed two conceptions.
We have never denied anything about respecting our parents.
or being filial to parents.
Respecting and being filial to parents
doesn't mean to do whatever they say.
Menci didn't say a filial son
should obey all of orders from parents.
But when they get old.
We're all they have.
If we do things against their wishes,
wouldn't that make them feel sad?
Don't you feel it hurtful?
The opposite side,
I think you should understand
which one is more important,
one moment or a lifetime?
If you do wrong things
against principles to make parents happy.
Is that the real filial thing to do?
People all make mistakes.
So at that time,
people around them should
help them to make the right choice.
Not play up to them.
The opposite team doesn't want
to disobey their parent to upset them.
Then are you willing
to watch them make bigger mistakes?
Until there's nothing can be done?
Bitter pills, and sweet poison.
I think you don't need me to explain it.
I totally disagree the square one debate on my side.
Student, which side are you on?
Can't get me!
Stop running.
- Catch ya!
- You can't!
You can't!
So beautiful.
Such a beautiful view.
Let me recite a poem for you.
Like you play music with the woods.
Please consider me as your musical instrument.
Even my leaf would wither like the woods do.
Your extraordinarily harmonious and strong spirit,
will make a deep autumn song from me and the woods.
Your strong soul is also my soul.
I will become the strong you.
Please let me...
Why are you sleeping?
It's so boring.
-Always recite poems.
-Get up.
Poems are very beautiful.
I like this poem very much.
I hope you will like it too.
I told you to read more books.
But you wouldn't listen.
When we met the first time.
I was reading how is steel was tempered.
You said I was posing.
Right. Because that book is not interesting.
Then what do you like?
I can climb the tree.
Let's race. See who will get to the top first.
Come down. It's too dangerous.
I can do it.
Be careful.
Come down.
I'll catch you.
Come.
Come down.
I can catch you.
I can catch you, jump.
You...
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Then why didn't you hold my hands?
They said that will make you pregnant.
Is that too soon?
Slow down. Slow down.
So we joined hands
to China Photo Studio in Wangfujing streets
and took a marriage photo.
It's colorphoto.
I was wearing a red apparel.
Your grandpa was wearing a Chinese tunic suit.
He used some hair oil
So handsome!
The opposite side two square.
How do you comprehend the word "NO"?
"NO" means to deny and reject.
So you have denied your parents?
Of course not.
So what kind of people do you think your parents are?
My parents are excellent and great.
and caring.
So you admire your parents
Respect your parents?
You can say that.
So can I say you're filial kid?
Of course I am.
So according to you,
A kid who respects her/his parents
without going against them
should be considered as a filial kid?
Well, well.
So, cherish that, students.
Time lapses.
The elders don't have too much time with us.
To do things they want
for us, it's not much.
But for them, it can bring them huge happiness.
What other reasons do we have to not cherish that?
So we should seize the moment.
Don't let them down.
Xiao Yuwei. You really shot a bullet!
Of course I will.
Don't you remember what you have done?
Xiao Yuwei, do you really have to?
What do you mean?
That's necessary!
You did a wrong thing.
Of course you should get this.
All these dramas.
It's just about an electronic blanket!
What electronic blanket?
You're doing this again.
You're always like this.
Never take my word seriously.
I said I was wrong.
I said it. okay?
When did you say that?
Not okay. You are doing this again.
Every time when you admit you're wrong.
You'll say. I was wrong, okay?
What okay? Is that a threat?
You don't mean it at all!
Your apology is not serious.
If you really think you were wrong.
You wouldn't say that.
Did I mean to piss you off?
I... I was trying to reason with you.
-You always shoot me.
-No more that!
Of course I'm right. Come on.
I didn't fire, okay?
You didn't fire,
but you hurt me by words!
My heart is broken, bleeding.
I... Take this!
Come here, come here.
I said come here, come here!
I'm gonna fire.
Come on.
- I'm gonna fire!
- Yeah, really?
I'm gonna fire!
You really did?!
You shoot me?
If you keep doing it, I'll throw it.
Come on, throw it. you dare?
Bully me, bully me.
You open fire on me!
I want divorce! Divorce!
Why did I marry you?
I want divorce. Come here!
One. Two. Three!
Today, this problem must be settled.
You will not let me explain it no matter what?
Of course not.
I have my reason.
But you can't beat my son!
I was teaching him.
He is also my son.
You know that? You heart doesn't hurt?
But he stole from people.
You should talk to him nicely.
Talk to him nicely? Did he listen?
But you can't beat him!
I'm his father.
I should teach him.
He said he didn't mean to do it.
-He didn't mean to steal it?
-He picked it from the floor.
You're his mother.
A kid steals pins will be a thief who steals gold.
You spoil him too much.
What if he grows up and becomes a bad guy?
Enough.
Don't be angry.
I'll talk to him nicely next time.
If you beat him, I'll beat you.
Okay.
Don't be angry.
Grandma, you're here.
Yezi, I didn't realize I said that much today.
Why do I always talk so much whenever I see you?
I heard you live nearby.
Right.
Take grandma to check your place.
Wh....why?
Don't ask why.
Take grandma to your place now.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Nice speech from Pros Square three.
Let's hear the statement from Cons Square One.
Today's topic is actually a problem in my life.
Before I came here,
I had to make a choice.
My grandma, she loves me so much.
She loves everyone in my family.
But now she is more than eighty years old.
Sometimes, she could be
a painful choice in our family.
So, what is the best for the elders.
I ask myself a thousand times everyday in my heart.
I don't want to talk about now and forever.
To be honest.
I treat everyday like it's the last day we have together.
Danyi, tell your dad.
If he doesn't want me.
Then just ignore me.
Why did he send me here?
With these people around every day,
I'm not happy, you know?
I can go out rent a house myself.
I can make money.
I can raise myself.
I won't be his problem.
You know that? Okay?
Grandma. Don't talk nonsense, okay?
I'm not talking nonsense!
My dear grandson.
I know exactly what I'm talking about.
Grandma. I...
Since you all think I'm crazy.
Fine, I'm crazy.
You're all spies of Vilter.
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Grandma. What do you want to say?
I just want to tell you
A bad wife will destroy your whole life!
Grandma.
That's beautiful! Okay!
So Beautiful. Yes.
But why did I say no?
In fact, it's not because I'm selfish.
It's because I think that's love.
It's a virtue in life.
To pass love along.
I think
when all things come to an end.
I can tell my grandma with no guilt or regret.
Grandma.
I love to listen to you all my life.
I totally disagree the statement of Square One.
His logic is a mess,
That's moral pollution.
And I totally can't accept his appearance!
This student, please be serious.
Sorry, sorry.
Boss, boss.
Don't worry.
I'm writing the last two thousand words.
I'm not lying, how is that possible.
Impossible.
My mistake, last one thousand words.
Give me some time. Will finish it soon.
Okay, okay.
Brother.
Yezi, you're back.
Who is this old lady?
Brother, be careful of her.
Be careful?
Did she bully you?
No, no, no.
Too dirty.
What too dirty?
Madam, you must have lost.
Clean it up.
Clean it up now!
Stop talking.
You must have lost.
Come, I'll send you home.
Clean it or not?
- Clean it or not?!
- Yes, yes. Yes.
Clean it or not? Clean it or not?
Louder! Clean it.
Yes, yes!
Hurry up. Clean it all up!
Okay, okay, okay.
Look, look, look.
Here, here!
Hurry, hurry.
So slowly.
Hurry, clean it up!
paper, paper, so many papers.
Fold it well. Hurry.
Look, that way.
Hurry, behind that.
Look, look.
Look at your desk. Look.
What the hell is this?
You eat and have things left!
Lazy pig, lazy bones, stupid donkey.
Hurry, clean it!
Hurry, hurry!
I'm so pissed!
I'm so tired.
Look, look. I knew it.
So sloppy.
Look, dust!
Yezi.
Why do you have a photo of you
and Danyi when you were both young?
So funny. So funny.
Look, look.
How cute you were!
Right?
I forgot I have this photo.
But I was a little ugly  back then.
Not at all.
He was.
You were ugly.
Not him.
I mean he was ugly in a cute way.
I didn't expect he would become so annoying.
I have so many photos like this one.
I hide them away.
Do you wanna see it?
Then come with me.
Come, come, come.
Come.
Dear brothers.
After eighty-one disasters.
I can finally show you this beautiful episode!
You know, nice things will never be too late.
Hope you can see my sincerity in my work.
Okay, that's it.
Brother, I'm leaving with grandma.
Okay, bye. Bye.
We're leaving.
Bye, bye, bye.
Finally!
Listen to me.
Remember to clean your house every day.
Yes, yes, yes.
Who sent her?
What did I do?
Did I press delete?
I didn't press delete, did I?
I didn't press delete.
I didn't press delete. Gosh!
What kind of life is this?!
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Now I'll announce the result for the debating competition.
The winner is
Maple Leaf Middle School.
Miss Xinyi, we win! We win!
We win!
We're the winner, you're the loser.
Let's leave.
Follow me!
We're the winner, you're the loser.
Wait for me, wait for me.
What took you so long?
Sorry.
What if anything happened to...
His penis.
- Look, how cute he is.
- Grandma.
What're you doing?
Watching your childhood photo album.
Okay, you're sending me to prison again.
You're happy now?
Grandma, don't say that.
Yezi, I trust you.
Come to see me every weekend in the nursing home.
Okay.
Pinky promise.
It's a deal.
Ye Muxi. I didn't expect you could actually help.
What do you mean?
Usually, you would mess things up.
I...
I did well.
Why do I hear the sound of water?
Water?
That door.
Anyway, because of my mistake.
There is a flood in Liao Danyi's room.
I need privacy, you know?
We have different viewpoints.
How could we live together?!
I heard that.
Well, I need to talk to you. Yezi.
You know the floor of Danyi's house is in flood, right?
Consider it a joy to help others.
It's what a wonder girl does.
You know that.
You're a wonder girl.
I won't say any other things.
Deal with it.
You know that.
But that depends.
Besides...
Please believe me, I won't do anything to you.
So, to sum it up.
This guy is living in my house temporarily.
My god.