# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 19
[ Danyi, can you see me under the banyan tree after school? ]
[ Looking forward to your reply, from Guan ]
[ You Are The April of This world, by Phyllis Lin ]
What can I help you?
This is my favorite novel.
Now I lend it to you.
Why?
Don't ask.
I'm looking forward to your feedback.
I'm here.
I want to tell you...
Don't say anything.
Listen to me first.
When mountains have no ridges,
when rives stop running,
I only hope,
I can have the love that never
parts each other even if the world ends.
Maybe I can only make it come true in my dream.
One is like a cloud in the sky.
Drifting alone.
Sunlight goes through it to illuminate the Earth.
But the cloud itself doesn't know where it's heading to.
You know what?
I love oceans.
Mountains.
Rivers.
Creeks.
And you.
Like a boat in the ocean,
I hope I can dash into your heart
under the helps of waves.
[ You Are The April of This world, by Phyllis Lin ]
[ Class Ten, Grade One ]
[ Danyi, can you see me under the banyan tree after school? ]
[ Looking forward to your reply, from Guan ]
What can I help you?
This is my favorite novel.
Now I lend it to you.
Why?
Don't ask.
I'm looking forward to your feedback.
Liao Danyi.
Keep it yourself.
What's the matter?
I don't come to you once there's a matter, okay?
I'm here for Xiaodong.
Xiaodong.
Xiaotian!
Why did you run into my room?
Why did you take my pillow to your nest?
You made a mistake. Now you want dinner?
I've told you when you drank from the toilet.
Don't make mistakes again.
Behave yourself. Okay?
Xiaotian, look at me.
Look at me sincerely.
Don't make mistakes again.
Behave yourself. Okay?
Do you hear me, Xiaotian?
Which student can answer this question?
Teacher. Teacher, that...
That... He... He says that he can.
Liao Danyi, come up here.
Sorry, teacher.
I was a little absent-minded.
Didn't hear it clearly.
Okay. Sit down.
Teacher, I got stomachache.
It hurts.
Gotta take a break.
Mr Wu.
Danyi.
I think you're not yourself lately.
Messy hair. Pale face.
Wrong buttons.
And only one sock.
Even your handwriting goes crooked.
If you were some other student,
I will think he has stayed up playing video games.
I've been there.
I understand.
But you, Liao Danyi.
You're not that kind of student.
Tell me.
What happened to you lately?
Danyi.
Have you browsed some illegal website?
Not like that, Mr Wu.
It's because my father went to a business trip.
I stay at home alone...
Got it.
Your father is not home.
So you start to browse some illegal website.
Right?
Danyi, such websites
will do harm to you teenagers' healthy development.
Do you understand?
Mr Wu, here is the thing.
I've got a trouble back home.
Ms Luo.
Isn't it inappropriate for you
to send me the flower before my student?
Isn't it more inappropriate for you
to be so shameless before your student?
Someone sent me the flower as a gift.
Danyi, let's continue.
The illegal website thing...
Mr Wu, there's really no that kind of website.
That's better.
Then I believe you can adjust yourself well to it.
Pull yourself together.
Excuse me, then.
Bye, teacher.
Okay.
Ms Luo, is it because you've been single for so long
that you bought a flower for yourself
to gratify your sense of presence?
Get lost.
Normal people don't have that kind of mentality.
Thinking of it that way means you're mentally ill.
I've told you, this flower is from someone else.
I'm beautiful. Isn't it normal
for people to send me flowers?
Leave me alone. I gotta go to class now.
I forgot to tell you.
I got to know this flower guy online.
We also agreed to see each other
in People's Park this weekend.
To talk about life and dreams.
Ms Luo, may you have a happy date.
What?
Please make way.
Where are you going?
Home.
Why do you rush home after school every day?
Are you hiding something from me?
Tell me. I will keep it a secret.
Nothing.
Tell me.
You're really boring.
I won't tell anyone else. Just let me know.
Trust me.
Shoot.
Indeed, I've hidden something from you for a long time.
I feel that I should let you know.
But I think you can't take it now.
Are you ready?
No, I think you're not.
Relax.
Close your eyes.
Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Breathe in. Breathe out.
Let's go.
Come here, Xiaotian.
Now I want to talk with you about a few problems.
Look into my eyes.
Don't.
Don't make such a grimace.
Look at me.
Firstly, don't jump on my bed in the morning.
Secondly, Don't bite my slippers.
Thirdly.
Don't drink from the toilet again.
Fourthly.
Also the most crucial problem.
Don't defecate indiscriminately.
If you can observe the rules above,
we'll get along well with each other.
Don't try to avoid eye contact.
Look at me.
I believe you can make it. Okay?
I believe you.
I believe you're a good dog with due virtues.
Let's shake hands like real men do.
Good.
Let's go.
Could you tell me how can I get to Rd. Huachang?
Rd. Huachang?
Walk this way.
Turn left, then turn right.
Turn right again and you'll be there after two blocks.
Okay. Thank you.
No problem.
Young man, why don't you
walk your dog at night but hold a dog leash?
I'm walking my dog.
Where's my dog?
Haven't seen it.
Xiaotian.
Xiaotian!
We just made an agreement.
Then you did such a dangerous thing.
You'll get hurt in this way, you know?
As your master,
I gotta make you remember this lesson.
So I'm gonna beat you.
I'm really gonna beat you.
Here it is.
It's really good that you're safe.
For example, to choose one
from boys in our class as boyfriend.
Which one will you choose?
Which one will you choose, Li Yao?
None of my business.
-Hypothetically
-Yes.
If all boys in the world were killed by a bomb,
except boys in our class,
which one will you choose as your boyfriend?
I choose... To live on my own.
No. You must choose one.
How about this...
Let's go through an elimination process.
The first one.
Xiong Tiancheng.
No.
He writes good essays!
-Yes, such a scholar.
-So talented! Yes.
-Why don't you like him?
-No.
Well, Huang Nan and Huang Yi.
So cute. Makes you happy every day.
They're too noisy and annoying.
-But makes you happy.
-So much fun to be with either of them!
Won't feel upset everyday.
No.
Well, Liao Danyi.
Commissary in charge of studies. Excel at studies!
No.
Are you gonna choose my Xiaodong?
Definitely no!
That's good.
Only one boy left.
Cheng Ling.
Cheng Ling...
Something is going on here...
Enough! Enough!
I'm done. Now it's your turn.
What shall we eat tonight?
There's a newly opened milk tea store at the school gate.
Shall we go try it?
And then...
And then we'll go have some hot-pot.
I'm gonna kick someone's ass!
Where is that milk tea store, again?
Let me Google it.
Okay. Let's go now.
-Let's go.
-Google it over walking.
Unbelievable! Wait for me!
That Luo Li...
Have a date in a place
where retirees come to have square dances?
What a low taste!
Xiaotian?
Xiaotian, what brought you here?
Xiaotian.
Mr Wu?
Student Liao.
I haven't seen Xiaotian back in school for days.
Because you adopted him.
Yes, but he gives me headaches lately.
High five. High five.
Come here. Come here.
Xiaotian.
No wonder you're in a bad state these days
Because you've been looking after Xiaotian?
Yes.
And your parents are not home.
You look after him alone.
It's really not easy.
In fact, I didn't tell my dad that I adopted Xiaotian.
My dad will be back in a few days.
He won't let me have a pet dog.
-Walks away.
-I think...
Walks away!
Mr Wu!
Ms Luo?
Voice down.
You're stalking her?
What did you mean by that?
Sounds like I'm so vulgar.
You're still too young. Won't understand this.
Here is the thing.
Ms Luo.
You're not young any more.
Still believe in cyber Love?
Ms Luo?
Ms Luo, don't leave.
Stop talking nonsense. What cyber friend?
Haven't seen him yet.
But he's already so romantic.
Attests to his culture attainment.
Compared with some unreliable man, he's much better!
Who is that unreliable man?
One of your cyber friends?
I really don't want to talk with you.
We agreed to meet each other
in People's Park at 3 p.m. this Saturday.
I'm very looking forward to that.
May I ask, in the playback,
why did Ms Luo Li emphasize time and location of the date?
And stopped you from coming?
That doesn't matter.
What matters is, she's on a date with some cyber friend.
This is one hundred percent unreliable!
Me and Ms Luo are good colleague and old classmates.
She's my junior.
Of course I should take care of her, right?
But,
her cyber friend hasn't come till now.
Is he really reliable?
She's stood up?
He's coming...
She waves to him.
And in our direction?
What were you guys doing here?
-Walking dog.
-Watching flowers.
I think you guys are stalking me.
Who's stalking you?
I heard that student Liao adopted Xiaotian.
I haven't seen Xiaotian for days, right?
I missed him.
So I told student Liao
to play with Xiaotian in the park today.
Coincidentally, we bumped into you.
Right?
Ms Luo.
Aren't you gonna meet a cyber friend today?
Where's he?
You're stood up?
Look, what did I told you?
Cyber friends are unreliable.
Artists are unreliable.
Cyber artist friends are most unreliable!
But you wouldn't listen.
Yes. Yes.
Now I feel so bad.
What should I do?
Don't be sad.
I'm here to help you out, see?
Really?
Yes.
That... That's so great!
Well, where are we heading to next?
I... I feel so embarrassed after being stood up.
How about walking the dog with me?
Okay.
Student Liao.
Let's go.
Teachers, my dog...
Go back home now.
Study hard.
My teachers' acting skills are so not natural.
Student Liao, you have a nice bedroom.
Looks so orderly.
Yes.
Everything's here?
Xiaotian.
Xiaotian, why do you lose weight?
Mr Wu.
Have you abused him?
What are you talking about, student Liao?
I'm an ambassador of love.
I treated him so well.
Am I right, Xiaotian?
Did I treat you well?
Student Liao.
I know you missed Xiaotian very much.
And as requested by Ms Luo,
today I took Xiaotian here to get together with you.
But in the future,
Xiaotian will be in the charge of me and Ms Luo.
And you will focus on study and adjust yourself.
Mr Wu.
Last night, you and Ms Luo, you two...
Me and Ms Luo...
We talked a lot about education.
Had a nice talk.
Student Liao.
Have you mistaken the relationship between me and Ms Luo Li?
No, I haven't.
Me and Ms Luo Li... were schoolfellows.
Now, colleagues.
Although Ms Luo is very casual normally,
deep down,
she's still a little bunny immature.
Look, she's a girl.
Having a date with some unreliable cyber friend.
How dangerous is that!
As her senior,
shouldn't I go to protect her?
With you guys looking after Xiaotian,
I really feel assured.
Also, thank you guys for that.
Just rest easy.
These stuffs are all what I've got.
Including his toy.
Xiaotian.
All right, I gotta take Xiaotian away now.
I'll come again with him to see you some other day.
Okay.
Let's go, Xiaotian.
Xiaotian, let's go.
Xiaotian, what's up? Don't want to leave him?
Let's go home.
Then cook delicious food for you.
Let's go.
Go.
Why don't you go?
I will visit you later.
Xiaotian, let's go. Go.
Xiaotian. Xiaotian.
Why don't you go?
Just go.
Xiaotian, just go.
Why don't you go?
Why?
Xiaotian.
Xiaotian. Xiaotian.
Let's go, Xiaotian.
Xiaotian.
Be good, Xiaotian.
Be good.
-Xiaotian, just go.
-Let's go, Xiaotian.
Xiaotian.
Xiao...