#Head held high, stride forward #
#Dream big break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world ( No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play  to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Intro. Credits to: Babel Fansub
Kris Nicole, Kharla May
The Big Boss
Episode 21
Ye Muxi
You can not remember
When you were seven years old
I once had told you
the story of green teeth
I have a good news to tell you
a sequel
I don't want to know, I'm not listening
Yexi
You are dingling in the daytime
Toss this and toss that
What's wrong with you ?
No fever
Nothing wrong with your eyes
Let me check your pulse
Come come come
Women is less safe and impatient
Hmm
There is a bit of irritability
Your face is a little bit
suspicious
But for me
I still have to persuade you
The rivers and lakes is so dangerous, stay at home is more secure
Do not say I and Danyi bad
We just want you to be safe, isn't it right?
You are muffled without a word
Is there any thoughts to talk about ?
How do you not talk to me
But also let the most annoying person
Live with us
I am 16 years old this year
Soon will be 17 years old
Plus a few months in mom's stomach
I am 18 years old
I am a woman
An adult woman
I can make my own choice
Make your own decisions
But you did not ask me
You did not think about my idea
You did not ask my decision
You're guilty because you don't care about me
And then count you are my brother
Have you ever thought about me
Wait wait wait
I am your brother
Am I not your brother ?
Of course it is a matter
How can I let you go out
One more thing
Danyi is also a kind, good hearted boy
He has some trouble
He come to live here
What's wrong?
Do you know Danyi
Do you really know him?
Do you know him ?
Do you think you know him better ?
Have you ever been with him for ten years
Elementary, middle and high school
Do you have it?
No
I have!
Do you feel that
You know he has a lot of good habits
Let's not talk about his good habits, since right now
he's living in our house let's talk about his bad habits
What if he comes to my room at night
What if I am bathing and he peeks then what do i do?
He is going to use my toothbrush, my blanket, my chair,
What if he uses my markers?
He can't use my markers! I cannot let this happen
What if he eats my snacks?? This cannot happen too
In addition, your room is there and his room is there
Although it's so close, in one second
in that one second
in the one millisecond
what if in that second, he comes and kill me
he muffles my scream, you won't hear it
will you hear it? You won't!
Ok, what you have depicted is indeed very dangerous
and it embeds a lot of horror
From observing your actions
I can come up with a conclusion that
you are extra talkative today.
I want to leave home now. You don't care about me, I'm leaving now.
Robber and pervert
Maybe robbing is possible,
but pervert is definitely out of the picture.
You are thinking too much.
What do you mean?
Why did you enter my room? Get out.
I've been standing by your door for a long time,
just wanted to come in to say hi
I have my own privacy, don't you know that?
So if we can't tolerate one another,
we can't live together.
Mind you, this is not even a marriage, what are you talking about.
Dan Yi's house floor has some problems
you know this too, don't you?
Helping others is happiness,
you should know this!
Ok, I would say more, you settle the rest yourself
In addition,
Please believe me, I won't do anything bad to you.
You should give a criminal
What are you looking at?
What's wrong?
Why are you looking around my room? What's wrong with my room?
Listen to me,
no random person is ever going to enter your room
even they could, they wouldn't be able to leave
even the mosquitos can't enter, just rest assure.
My room is exceptionally perfect.
Come, come, Dan Yi, eat more, eat more
Dan Yi, eat more, eat more. Thank you, Yi Han
Thankfully you came into our house
otherwise you won't know how hard it is for me to wake Mu Xi up
need about 7 to 8 times of waking up.
The breakfast today is really good,
it has brought back the old times. So wonderful !
I'm so happy.
Of course, Dan Yi is now staying at our house
Your brother has to whip out some good dishes for him.
You culinary skills has really improved a lot.
Hurry eat, eat more. Don't scald your mouth.
I can hear it,
you are trying to shut me up
do you have any hidden motive?
Is it after eating steamboat,
you don't want to wash the dishes?
What? Do I look like that kind of person?
I... I won't do that !
It's okay, you don't have to.
I have to pay the rent if I am living here,
but
I have already used finished last term scholarship money
What about this,
I will clean up the house to cover the rent.
This morning, I have cleaned the bathroom
I did simple packing
No wonder I felt that something was wrong.
I tell you, you shouldn't leave your toothbrush
lying on the top of the sink, you will get sick easily.
I have always placed my toothbrush like this, but I have not fell sick
But that's because your immune system is strong,
but after a while you will definitely fall sick.
So what? I will put it wherever I like, don't touch my stuff
I am just putting your toothbrush into the cup.
How would you know if the soy sauce bottle likes lying down or standing,
and you are not it so you don't know what it likes.
Why is your debating skills so much better than your language skills.
but you still have to put your toothbrush into the cup
but
that's my toothbrush, I understand what it wants
it tells me that it likes lying down
it likes it, so what do I do, you understand?
Ok, ok ok.
Stop quarelling.
Er, Dan Yi in this case
you just have to make sure that the house is clean.
The packing and arrangement aspect
I also can't do anything about it
But you don't have to worry,
I will credit you for your efforts.
To reward you, I have decided
that today I will buy you a
beanbag sofa so that you can sleep more comfortably.
Thank you Yi Han, bro.
But
if there are no used socks stuffed under the sofa
I think my quality of sleep will be much better.
You're right.
Come, come eat more.
But Yi Han bro, I think steamboats lack some nutrients
Tomorrow morning I will cook some red glutinous rice porridge
plus some salted eggs and red bean buns.
Tomorrow after school, I will go to the market
to buy the red dates.
These red dates are really good
super fragrant and sweet.
Dan Yi
you should have came to our house earlier
We welcome you, stay longer
Kill ! Kill !
Yes ! Yes ! Yes !
Stop it, stop it. Seat down.
Why are they up there?
Did you watch too many teen shows?
Walking on this street,
I feel so regenerated, filled with energy
and hence went up.
This is time when I unleash my usefulness
You both are not even close to reaching it.
How about this,
we climb onto one another.
Ok then you bend down,
I should be at the top.
You are a girl, if you are on top it is not very appropriate
That's right, so what should we do?
Ok ok I'll go down.
Good luck !
How about you come in front.
This is not very appropriate right
Forget it, forget it.
Let me think first.
There's nothing that we can use to hit them down.
How about this, we use our bags to hit them down
Right?
Ok let me try first.
No use, no use.
Half an hour ago, it was still very clean here.
It's my house, I do what I like.
I say, Ye Mu Xi can you respect others effort
When did I not respect?
I have spent my efforts cleaning this place
Touch you neck and ask yourself do you have any conscience?
Of course I have.
If I have no conscience, look
I would have done this.
Pick it up,
Pick it up. No i won't.
Why are you childish, you better hurry pick it up
That is food, don't waste
I'm not wasting it
So actually cleaning up is such a simple thing to do.
Move away, move away.
Move
Make way.
Such a mess.
Where are my markers?
Why are the caps on?
Why are they on the markers?
LIAO DANYI
LIAO DAN YI !!!
Tell me what happened,
there's perfume smell on you
You definitely created trouble again
its the fault of your nose.
Speak properly, tell me exactly what happened.
I was just playing a joke on him.
A joke?
There must be a line to a joke right
It's for his good.
For his good? Stop talking nonsense.
I tell you
I tell you, Dan Yi this young man
is a guest in our house
how can you treat him like that ?
Ya right, Liao Dan Yi we really need you
Still talking back,
Dan Yi, you shouldn't leave
you are a guest that I invited to our house
Look, the past two days that you came
and I need to praise you
you have done a good job in cleaning the house
not only did you improve the environment of the house
and every time when I come home,
I always feel that this house is filled with youth energy
Ya that's right.
You shut up.
Dan Yi young man,
Mu Xi is just a little immature,
don't be petty.
She's just an immature young child,
that's right I'm just a young immature child
and there's also a big immature child, we both need you
Dan Yi young man, how about this,
just think of her as a fart,
just let her go, let her go that's it.
Brother, you.... you
You what you, Ye Mu Xi,  I'm telling you
hurry apologise to Dan Yi. Why should I?
Ok, fine you don't want to apologise is it?
I'm just an immature young child, I don't know anything.
Ok fine, you don't want to apologise?
I can't cure you, Ye Mu Xi I'm telling you
if you don't apologise, from tomorrow onwards,
steamboat will be cancelled, no more of it.
Steamboat??? You...
You what you. I tell you
tomorrow morning I will throw the hotpot away.
We won't be eating steamboat anymore.
The hotpot???
Our very own hotpot?
Did you even think about it, 6 years of relationship and you are letting it go because of him
How do we eat steamboat then?
We must eat steamboat ! Did you think about my feelings
Ok ok I don't want to hear what you say
Steamboat!!
Come Dan Yi come here.
Really did you think about my feelings
You shut up. Ye Mu Xi, I'm telling you,
if you want to eat steamboat, I'll tell you one way
From today onwards, you be a good person
be gracious and kind
and
from today onwards, remember
you cannot disturb Liao Dan Yi normal way of life. You promise me.
Why should I promise you that? He is the one that is disrupting my life.
Let me tell you about my markers, the ones that I have to remove the caps before drawing
Every pen cap was placed on the markers
Do you know that everytime I have to open the pen caps,
all my inspirations just vanish like that. Do you know that being an artist,
must use a marker that gives me inspiration.
What do you want? I ask you do you know why those markers need to have caps?
Say it. That's because those caps are to prevent ink from evaporating
and extend their lifespan.
Even if I don't know,  do I need you to say it?
You don't even know how to cherish your materials,
confirm won't be able to draw beautiful drawings.
You have the guts to say that?
and then, and then what
Ok ok stop quarrelling.
You also take a chill pill,
Yi Han bro, I didn't want to quarrel with her.
but she's really too much
It's just drawing but when I opened her sketchbook
those drawings are practically a child's painting
Eh what you mean by a child's painting, do you even understand arts?
Do you know how to draw? You don't know how so of course you don't understand.
You didn't get my permission and
doodled on my textbooks. You still have to guts to say.
You even destroyed the umbrella that my best friend in elementary school gave me
Mu Xi, I have to reprimand you for this.
Why did you destroy his umbrella?
In addition, you didn't get my permission to change my pencil case
to a pink color one.
I really really really hate pink color
I don't understand why there are people like you.
Are you sure you hate pink? Your whole face is pink now
Dan Yi
Dan Yi, you're having a fever.