# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 22
Don't worry. I'll take the responsibility.
I made you ill.
So I'll take good care of you.
Don't worry, I'll fix you.
Hand.
What?
My hand...
You're pressing my hand.
Sorry.
Liao Danyi.
Liao Danyi. You can't sleep!
Liao Danyi. You can't sleep! You can't die!
You'll die in sleep.
Liao Danyi. Liao Danyi.
I thought you were going to die.
I'm not in a snowy mountain!
Ye Muxi.
I hate you.
You want more water?
Okay, don't worry. I'll go get water.
Okay. Wait, roger that.
Where is he?
Really? He has been burnt into ashes?
Feel better?
Much better.
God, do you still feel weak?
You scared me to death last night. Your high fever.
I sweat a lot last night.
My quilt is wet.
Sorry.
Thank you for taking care of me.
You're welcome.
Try some soup I made.
The millet is from Lvliang, Shanxi Province.
The soup you made is quite delicious.
It might not have been cooked thoroughly.
I will go boil it a little while.
Soup is good.
The elders like soup too.
But from my experience.
Soup is not enough for the patient.
You also need some other food.
Come.
Eat this in three hours.
This one in six hours.
Before meal. After meal.
So attentive. That's unexpected.
I'm quite attentive, okay?
And you know what.
For things I like, I'll do my best.
That's true.
I made you ill.
So I'll apologize.
Sorry.
That high fever makes me a little dizzy.
I forgot it.
That's great.
Who is that?
Huang Nan.
Huang Nan?
What day is it today?
I'm a patient.
How can I tell you?
Today is 16th, Sunday.
I might have promised them something.
What did I promise them?
How would I know?
They will come in.
I'll go check.
No, no, no!
You go hide yourself.
Why would I do that?
Or shall I hide?
Okay.
I'm the Commissary in charge of studies, right?
That high fever turned you to a fool?
This is my home.
The world knows it.
There're just me and my brother.
Do you want the whole world think that
you're living with me?
Then where shall I hide?
The bathroom.
No, no, no, no.
What if any one of them wants to use the bathroom.
I'll get busted.
Then where?
In here.
I mean, I'll stay in here.
My... My room?
Okay, off you go.
Hurry, open the door.
But my room....
Go, go, go....
Hi, guys.
What took you so long?
I.... Well, I...
I was sleeping, didn't hear you.
That doesn't like your style.
No, I was...
and I used the toilet.
Didn't hear the closestool's sound.
I was washing my hands.
Doesn't need to explain that...
No, no.
I'm scrupulously clean, I gotta
wash my hands before I open the door.
Do you feel she is so abnormal today?
Indeed! So abnormal. Abnormal.
Enough!
You two are always in a replay mode.
I feel so dizzy!
Like echo of the cuckoos in the valley.
Listen to me, I'm the hunter now.
I'll shoot cuckoos first.
And cook you two.
Shut up.
Such a heartless hunter.
Evil, heartless!
Enough, enough.
Why brought you here today?
You forgot?
You said you want to help us with our study.
Right.
After Liao Danyi helped us with our study.
We made a lot of progress.
You said that narcissist is too cocky.
Did I say that?
Didn't you?
You also said you will drag his nose off.
Put it in his mouth.
And use your Yezi Kongfu
to beat his teeth into his nose.
You also drew a picture of that.
You can't deny it.
Wait!
What's that?
My toy fell off on its own.
Why are you blushing?
I'm not.
Liao Danyi is such a nice guy.
Why would I say something bad behind his back?!
Didn't you say he is a scumbag?
Scumbag?
Liao Danyi, it's impossible.
I wouldn't say that about him.
You said even a scumbag is better than him.
Right.
And you also said,
You want that guy who is worse
than a scumbag kneel in front of you.
Right, right. Kneel in front of you to worship you.
Wait!
I mean it, wait! Sit down!
That really fell down on itself.
Is that?
Brother Yihan, are you up there?
No, no, no.
My brother is not in.
I forget to close the window.
So it fell down on itself.
I'll go close it.
- I'll come with you.
- No need!
My room.... Trust me. you don't want go in there.
Besides, a boy shouldn't go into a girl' room, right?
I'll go with you, then.
No! Sit!
Strange.
Strange. Strange.
Why did you throw things down?!
You talk behind me.
- Talk behind me.
- Wait!
We got company. Lay down!
Big boss, you're so strange today.
Right, it's so noisy in there.
What happened?
Nothing. I'm here alone.
You're really strange today.
We need to check inside.
That...
Fine.
In fact, there's a man in my room.
My new boyfriend.
I was gonna tell you guys.
But didn't find a right time.
Besides, today we were dating.
I forgot to tell you.
But I think it's a good chance.
You can go meet him.
He is in there. Come in.
Monitor, you have a boyfriend?
You have a boyfriend!
Hurry, hurry.
That's hilarious!
We'll wait you downstairs.
Hilarious!
Keep still!
Monitor, we're leaving. You're so funny.
Monitor is so humorous.
Bye.
Okay, class begins.
Today we'll gonna learn the way we look.
Unit one.
[Sword II]
[Sword III]
[Sword VII]
[Sword VI]
[Sword VIII]
[Sword VIII ]
[ Sword IX ]
[ Death ]
We are gonna use
Hanxin's trick in the lesson you are learning.
It's called Sneak In.
Seems quite impressive.
To make him confused.
After you draw his attention,
then you perform another action plan in the dark.
So you mean.
In class, if Liao Danyi tells me to focus on class.
I should do the opposite.
To draw his attention, right?
Smart!
So I'm gonna pretend I'm sleeping.
When he lets down his guard.
I can fight him back hard.
Fight back, back, back.
Wait a second.
Wonder girl.
We can talk! We can talk!
Don't!
Don't beat us! Don't beat us!
Don't fight, don't fight.
That hurts. Hurts.
Stop!
Could you use another character than this?
There's a square.
There's a character "Bow".
If you use character "Bow" or square.
You can beat us as long as you want.
I like this character, shut up!
Didn't you tell me to draw his attention and
Beat back, back, back?
Where's that?
Why only I got beaten?
That's because....
I've run out of words.
Wait, wait, wait!
Stop beating us!
Stop!
I have a question.
What is that?
Why he is always the one who gave you the bad idea.
But I also got beaten?!
Seems so!
Because I like it!
Don't beat me, don't, don't!
I'm dead!
What kind of strategy are you gonna use?
I know a kind of secret weapon.
Called Arrow Blow.
That kind of secret weapon
is from Amazons.
and rain forest in south America.
The local people in America use that tool to hunt.
Although that is not a powerful weapon,
but it's very accurate.
Even without the help of poison,
it can still catch and kill some
birds and little animals.
That Arrow Blow usually came with poison.
Bravo!
Ye Muxi.
Read the letters on the blackboard please.
Okay, sit.
Miss, may I ask where's Mt. Zhou?
Are you asking about the one in Zhejiang Province?
Exactly, that famouse Mt. Zhou.
You got the right person.
That Mt. Zhou is famous for porridge and shirt.
That one?
You know it.
I want to visit my spiritual homeland.
My homeland of my life.
In my life,
If I can have porridge and shirt, some homely food.
I think I can't ask for more.
Miss, do you want to taste some?
Sir, please come with me.
Screw you!
Who wants your porridge?! I'll go back and eat hotpot.