# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 25
Hello?
Okay. Okay.
Bye-bye. Bye.
Why do they have to call me before coming here?
I have nothing hidden in my home.
Any munition? No.
Any man? No.
Why are you still here?
-I'll fight back if you keep doing so.
-Leave. Hurry. Hurry.
-They're coming.
-What are you doing?
-Why are you fighting in such an early morning?
-He's bullying me!
That... That...
It's okay. It's okay.
Aren't you stupid?
I can tell them that I came here earlier. Okay?
Yes. I'll go open the door.
With your pajamas on?
I'll go change. I'll go change.
What's going on?
Okay. Okay. I got this.
Coming. Coming.
-Morning, brother Yihan.
-It's you guys.
-Hi, brother Yihan.
-Morning, guys.
Danyi, you're so early.
I live more closely to here.
So I arrived first.
Yes. Yes.
He does live more closely.
Where's Yezi? Still not up?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Aren't you Liao Danyi who lives very closely to my home?
You really arrived earlier than them.
Come, let's study.
Yes. Yes. Hurry, come on in.
Brother, your phone is ringing.
Someone called editor Chen...
No!
Someone out there. I got this.
Brother.
Yezi. Yezi, don't let them in!
Mr Ye, we're here to pick you up.
They're gonna take me away!
We're here! No one can hurt my brother!
We're gonna send you to the beach house.
They're gonna lock me up in the beach house.
To abuse me!
They said...
Beach?
Someone said that we're gonna go to the beach?
I also heard 'beach house'?
Thank you, brother.
-You're welcome.
-Thank you, brother!
No problem. No problem.
Brother, you're the best!
But why did you invite him?
Well, because you and lad Danyi are both...
Shanqi!
You...
So naughty.
I'm totally locked up in the cage this time.
But it's also good.
With wonder girl Ye and lad Danyi,
and so many younger friends staying with me...
Brother, I'm gonna go to the beach! Bye-bye.
Bye, brother!
Bye, brother.
Bye...
Ocean! Ocean! Ocean!
Beach! Beach! Beach!
And Shanqi! Shanqi! Shanqi!
-Shanqi!
-What are you doing?
Watching beauties.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Where are they?
You don't understand. When beauties show up,
we'll look back naturally.
To spark the flames of love.
Xiaodong.
Look, the sunlight is so hot today.
Need me to apply some sunscreen cream to you?
No, thank you. I've already had it applied.
Zhu Shanqi. We still haven't.
Never mind, brother.
It's okay, we can help each other.
Bros, you're well-trained. Well-trained.
Very rigorous.
Very burly.
You must often do body-building.
Bros.
Well... Don't be too nervous.
Actually, we... Writing, you know.
Sometimes, we want... Well...
Smoking. Smoking.
This...
This is not from the brand that I usually smoke.
But it's good enough. It is.
But sometimes, when it comes to...
When writing becomes very depressing...
I need... Right, I need to drink.
You also got wine...
You really have everything prepared.
Well... In fact...
You know, we writers need many inspirations.
I also need some... For example, coffee...
No. Bros.
Bros. Be gentle. Be gentle. Bros.
It hurts...
Bros, we can talk. Don't be mad.
Can I go outside to have some fresh air?
Thank you. Thank you, bro.
A phone is also okay!
Bros!
Bro!
Lately, we students are prompted to go beyond our school.
To approach Nature.
To feel Nature.
To conquer Nature.
So we have to use our valuable learning time
to spend a vacation on this beach.
Now, you guys can enjoy your time.
Sit down.
Look at the sea.
Take a picture.
Done.
We together have spent a pleasant and wonderful time.
Now, any one wants to continue sightseeing?
Then you can go back home learning.
Thank you, monitor.
Thank you, big boss.
Big boss!
What are you doing?
Pressing the shutter.
Recording this beautiful moment.
Is that necessary?
What do you know?
Where else can you see so many girls?
They're everywhere, aren't they?
I got this! I got this! I got this!
Look!
Can you play this or not?
You got this.
You like catching the ball.
What did you mean?
Nothing.
I just feel that you have no team spirit.
Why shouldn't I catch it when I can?
If you don't let your teammates join you,
no matter how awesome you're,
a hundred wins won't help.
It's enough if I can beat you.
-Give it a try.
-Are we done?
How about we go eat something first?
-No!
Let's go.
Do you have the nerve to play again?
I'm in.
Just try me.
Sea wind blows the fine sands,
along with my thoughts.
Who can listen to me talking about
a love that can't be answered back?
So let this drift bottle...
Go into the waves.
With my youth.
Drifting and drifting.
Can it drift into my love's heart?
But, I know.
This is just a fallacious dream.
The ocean is so vast.
But his heart...
More ruthless than this ocean.
This little drift bottle...
Will soon be swallowed by the deepness.
Diving and diving.
Sea wind blows the fine sands.
Brings a little drift bottle to me.
Is it the kismet? Or fate?
Although I don't know its owner,
yet everything in this letter,
betrays the writer's sensitivity.
I hope all the lovers can marry each other.
I hope the world will be in peace forever.
Little drift bottle.
Can you return to your owner under the help of waves?
Tell her.
At the other end of this boundless ocean,
there's someone,
sharing the same thoughts with her.
Who's that? Who wrote me back?
Is it the kismet? Or fate?
Does God really grant my wish?
Is there really a miracle in this world?
Is it... Is it...
Miss Xinyi, you're also taking a sunbath?
Once upon a time...
There was a very heinous ghost.
It only ate KFC...
Once upon a time.
There was a ghost with a pathetic life story.
Every time it went to scare people.
Ended up being spooked.
Three rounds. Two wins decides the winner.
Twenty-one throws in total.
Today we'll see which one of us is the winner.
Be my guest.
I won't lose to you.
Me, neither.
Well, why do we have to be enemies?
I don't know, either.
Are we still good brothers?
For a lifetime.
Well, where are Shanqi and Xiaodong?
Shanqi had a sunstroke.
Xiaodong went back with her.
Shanqi, are you alright?
Still feel dizzy.
Let I get you an ice bag?
Okay.
Your forehead feels hot.
Why is your face so red?
Because of the sunstroke.
I failed to catch that.
You failed to catch that, what the heck?
What makes you so weak?!
Even I am better than you!
Try again!
Sorry, I failed to catch that.
It's okay. Believe yourself, you can do it.
Ye Muxi.
Seemingly we're neck and neck.
But in this competition, you're bound to lose.
By winning this competition,
I'm gonna make you realize the importance of teamwork.
For your teammate's failure,
you always criticize him, deny him.
But when my teammate fails,
I'll encourage him.
As time passes by,
my team's cooperation and team spirit
will become stronger.
While your team's morale,
will become weaker.
If it goes on like this,
the gap between us will...
Remain unchanged!
With morale or not, we're both being undermined!
I've ignored their inability!
You've proved that you're useless!
Gosh, playing with the sand here?
The final try, I'll do it myself!
I'm really sorry.
Yes!
Yes! We win!
Gives me sense of accomplishment!
Have you learned the lesson?
What lesson? You played by yourself.
You lost anyway.
I didn't.
What did you mean?
You hit the line.
It's inside the line.
Outside.
Inside.
Are you trying to deny it?
Always do this since childhood.
Aren't you childish?
You're childish.
-What do you want?
Parroting me?
Parroting you?
Why parroting me?
I dare you do that again.
Okay.
Will you admit your loss?
No.
Okay. Let's have another competition.
The best of three.
Okay.
The one who loses will eat sands.
No problem.
-Drink seawater.
-No problem.
Okay. Another competition.
Okay.
The best of three.
Twenty throws in each round.
Okay.
Let's leave first.
Let's go.
At last, the ghost...
Finally found a ghost who was the same as it.
They lived happily together ever after.
No longer felt lonely.
Open the door. Mr Ye wants to go out.
Thirty-eight to thirty-nine.
Where are they?
It seems that they've left.
Some people feel nothing before winning or lose.
Yes. People who are not serious are the most annoying.
Take this!
Thirty-nine to thirty-nine.
Come on! I'm not afraid of you!