# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 26
What're you thinking about?
I'm thinking, it's time to return the favor.
Return the favor?
These years,
brother has been cooking nice things for me.
Especially my favorite Hotpot.
I think I should do something for him.
What are you gonna do?
An eye for an eye.
He cooks for me.
So I'll cook for him.
Please think twice before you do anything.
Are you his enemy?
I remember the first time,
you almost set the house on fire!
The fire fight truck came.
The second time,
You poured a bottle of sauce in.
Your brother felt sick for a whole week.
Then... What should I do?
Order some take-out.
Sincerity is what matters.
So it has to be cooked by you
to make him feel your sincerity.
Although your cooking skill is a little...
But we can learn.
As long as we start from the basics,
In some days,
You will be a good cook one day.
My advice is, cooking lessons.
But if I go there alone.
That will be so embarrassing?
It's summer vacation.
Your classmates are all free at home.
I think if you call them.
They will all come.
It's deal then.
Liao Danyi.
You fool.
Fool. Fool.
So handsome!
Liao Danyi.
Why can't I get tired of your photos?
If you want to win a man's heart.
Win his stomach first.
I should go attend a cooking lesson in summer vacation.
I don't want anyone to see me wearing this.
Hello, dear students.
Today, we're gonna learn dessert.
But I need to remind you first.
It's really not an easy thing
if you really want to make some delicious dessert.
Seems students in class Ten have all realized it.
I heard cooking is a very promising career.
Maybe what you need is not a training class.
You should transfer to study in here.
You think that will upset me?
Not at all.
Now I have told you everything.
And you have all the materials.
Now I'll leave the place for you.
It's not clean.
Teacher. Ye Muxi is playing with her food.
Teacher, is this okay?
Teacher. Ye Muxi is really playing with her food.
Look...
Like this?
Teacher, look!
Teacher, it's like my heart. Here it is.
I didn't know you're so good at this.
As Miss Xinyi's follower.
It's a basic ability.
I wonder class Ten...
What're they doing?
Don't know. So gross.
So scary.
So gross.
Add some blood!
Cheng Ling. Try this.
Is that delicious?
So yummy!
You're lying.
- Are you okay?
- So yummy.
It's really yummy.
So bitter.
Did you put spicy strip?
I did.
Or it would be worse.
What a waste.
I wonder how is Xiaodong doing.
This looks so tasty!
Want a bite?
Xiaodong cooked this...
Shanqi. Calm down.
Oh, one last step.
Be delicious.
Shanqi, don't.
It's so amazing.
I see light.
Grandpa, grandpa.
Wait for me, I'm coming, grandpa.
Shanqi, don't go into the light.
Grandpa?
You two want a bite?
Big boss.
How is Shanqi?
Xiaodong sent her back home.
Hope she is fine.
Li Yao.
Why do you want to learn to cook?
Because...
Try it.
How is it? is that bad?
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
It's my first time to cook.
I will cook better.
Sorry.
You fool, it's very delicious.
But no matter how tasty it is.
It's not as good as one thousandth of you.
Li...Li Yao.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing. You should not learn to cook.
Why?
You have seen it.
It's not easy to make dessert.
Our intention is the thing that really matters.
Think about it.
The dessert you're making
is for the one you love the most.
Make it with your heart.
That will help you a lot.
In fact, I'm doing this for the person
who matters the most in my life.
I will make it better than you.
Because...
This is for the one I love.
Every time, when I sleep on the couch.
He would take off his jacket.
And put it on me.
Miss Xinyi. Are you okay? Miss Xinyi.
I'm fine. Go on.
And every time when I couldn't sleep.
He would hug me and touch my head
to comfort me.
To make me feel so safe.
Miss Xinyi. Are you really okay?
I'm okay. Go on.
He also cooks for me.
Breakfast, lunch, dinner.
Every meal.
He is so good to me.
I want to make something good for him.
Love.
Love. I love you.
I Love you.
Love.
-I love you.
-Love
You...
You, you,
You're away too far!
Miss Xinnyi.
Miss Xinyi. Wait for me.
What's wrong with Class one?
Who knows?
Teacher. I'm done.
Okay.
Good, not bad.
Thank you, teacher.
Next.
Teacher, please try it.
Is it good?
Good, very good.
Thank you, teacher.
Next.
Good. Very good.
Really? I can make dessert!
Good, really good.
We made progress! We made progress!
Goodbye teacher.
Bye, students.
Bye.
Goodbye teacher. See you next time.
Okay. Goodbye, goodbye.
It's so awful.
I'm glad they're gone.
It's really hard to make dessert.
Today's topic of Chinese Essay is...
Those adults.
Which adult will we see every day?
Like Mr. Wu Heng.
How can I describe him?
But not reliable anyway.
And little narcissistic.
He is not young anymore.
But sometimes, he is more like a child than us.
But, when he is serious.
Unexpectedly, he really seems like a teacher.
A teacher who barely passed the standards.
In this way, he looks,
he is destined to be the head teacher of Class Ten.
First.
What the hell?
Is this a horror movie?
Students, in this examination.
Your classmate, Liao Danyi
has got the best score in our grade.
It's the forth examination.
Four examinations. Liao Danyi is always the best.
What does that tell you?
That I'm the best teacher.
I'm very proud.
So all of you should learn from Liao Danyi.
Hear me?
Answer me.
Yes.
This, this, this.
This, look at this.
Move. Move. Move.
Tell me.
Where did you get this book?
Read this kind of things in your age.
Is that right?
You can't even understand your textbook.
This?!
Go back to read your textbook. Hear me?
Move!
Oh my god!
Sorry, sorry.
Wu sir.
Wei.
Compass and fortune telling.
I don't encourage that.
It's superstition.
But today, I want to ask you a favor.
I have been in a bad luck recently.
Can you check it for me?
Since Wu Sir asked.
Of course I will do it.
But, it's 10MB a time.
What?
I'm your teacher!
You asked me for money?
Hurry, hurry.
Recently, Mercury is retrograding.
It's easy to get stuck with bad luck.
But it can be changed.
This. As long as you keep it with you every day.
Trust me, your bad luck will go away.
Thanks.
Well, I'll make an exception. I'll charge you eighty.
Eighty?
It's cheap. I charge the others for a hundred.
Do you have changes?
Never mind.
Gimme.
Keep it between us.
Bye, teacher.
Secret.
You've worked hard today.
I'm arranged your schedule of tomorrow.
I'll send it to your phone.
Give me a break, Annie.
I have class tomorrow.
-Morning.
-Hi, Xiaodong.
What a coincidence.
You're so early.
You're also very early.
I just got here.
How is it?
How is your summer vacation?
Good.
I'm on a touring concert.
You don't say.
I watched. I watched.
- Really?
- So handsome!
-Hi.
You're so early.
Right.
First day in school. Should come early.
Tell me what did you do in vacation?
-I haven't finished my homework.
-Hi, guys.
You haven't?
-Morning, classmates.
-Listen,
I was playing rock music my whole summer.
That.
Morning. Long time no see!
Long time no see! Miss you so much.
How are you doing lately?
Pretty good.
Just finished my homework yesterday.
Homework? Do we have that?
-Copy ours.
-What homework?
I haven't finished it.
Our new semester has begun.
You still haven't finished your homework.
My god!
Cheng Ling, help me.
You're good at this.
Don't bully Cheng Ling.
Yezi will be here soon right?
Forget it then.
Where have you been lately?
The amusement park is amazing!
Aren't you my favorite students?
Hi, teacher!
I'm so glad to see you all!
Wu sir.
This feels so strange.
The school is so empty!
Seems we're the only students here.
What's going on?
Right.
It's a long story.
Let me write it down.
Write it down?
In fact,
School has informed all the head teachers
at the end of last semester.
A teaching building in our school needs a restoration.
All the head teachers had informed their students,
But due to my little negligence.
I forgot to tell you.
So, here, I need to say this to everybody.
[ New semester begins tomorrow ]
Sorry!
Stop there! Stop!
Don't run. Don't!
Okay, Xiaodong, I heard you.
Someone confessed her love to Xiaodong again.
The fifteenth case this month.
Get ready, plan A.
Yali, you know what?
The biggest virtue of you,
is that you never overestimate yourself.
After all, Xue Xiaodong doesn't know you well.
Later, there's a possibility that he might refuse me.
But it's okay.
Think about Seiya and Monkey D Luffy.
Never give up.
Isn't that the most valuable character of the heroine?
Xue Xiaodong likes music.
Before he can say anything.
I'll surprise him with my singing.
To strike a sympathetic chord.
Finally it's my show time.
I've loved him for two months.
Being brilliant isn't my fault.
Yali.
Xue Xiaodong.
This song is for you.
Someone confessed her love to Xiaodong
Look, so romantic.
Hi, classmates, can I have a look?
Thanks.
Yali, this song is for you.
Thank you for your love.
I like music.
Nothing else.
I'm glad that you like me.
But for your love
I can only give you more songs.
Can you be the guardian star of my music career?
Please.
Of course I do.
Xue Xiaodong. You're so amazing.
I see. I'll continue to support you.
Thanks.
I have a concert next month.
Hope I can see you there.
I will. I will.
My idol just sang a song for me.
That's amazing.
Let's go.
I'll take you to join his fans club.
I will go buy the ticket now.
Wait for me. I will be there.
Wait for me.
Target is gone.
Everyone, clean the site and get your meal.