So,
it's our last class in this semester.
Keep studying hard during the vacation.
Guys, this is your homework.
Remember to do it back home.
Do we have to be so sentimental?
It's not our graduation after all.
Just an ending of a semester.
See you in the next semester.
Vacation!
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 23
I love you.
I love watching you smiling.
I love watching you being noisy.
I love you rushing into my world directly.
Ye Muxi, I love you.
Not that kind of love between friends.
Would you like to be my girlfriend?
[ A few hours ago ]
Performance lesson?
Yes.
My company got an idol drama for me.
Have you watched the idol drama I performed?
They said I'm such a poor actor.
So my broker arranged me some Performance Lesson.
And told me to go.
Good. Work hard on it.
But my teacher told me,
I need a familiar and ethereal girl as my partner.
Ethereal? Me?
Forget it.
You're really not going?
I just feel that performance is not my thing.
It's too hard. I'm not in.
Fine.
If you're not going, I'm not going, too.
What should we do in such a good afternoon?
How about we go bodybuilding?
Tell me about the performance lesson.
Where? And When?
Sit in the back row.
- I came first.
-Go.
Liao Danyi, you're also here
for the Mathematical Olympiad lesson?
Well, we can see each other more during the vacation.
Shall I compare thee to a summer's day?
Thou art more lovely and more temperate.
Rough winds do shake the darling buds of May.
Sometime too hot the eye of heaven shines.
And often is his gold complexion dimm'd.
Bravo! Completely perfect!
You're indeed a mentor who teaches many famous actors!
Bravo.
Shakespeare's sonnets.
My forever favorite.
You're recommended by director Famous?
Famous has briefed me on your situation before.
So, from now on,
I'm your performance teacher.
My family name is Biao.
You can call me Miss Biao.
The famous Director's name is Famous.
So the Performance teacher's name must be Performance.
Little girl, what are you talking about?
I'm not that shameless like director Famous.
Called himself Famous.
My full name is Beauty Biao.
Famous sent me this script,
from which I've chosen two paragraphs.
Now, you two perform for me.
So I can know your performance levels.
Here's a misunderstanding.
This little girl is here just for fun.
Today, I brought my superstar Xiaodong here
to attend your class.
So I can be his performance partner.
I also majored in performance.
Xiaodong. My dear Xiaodong.
I love you so much.
Why you always have tears in your eyes?
You're lightning. You're light.
You're the only miracle.
Annie, you... You gotta calm down.
No. No. I can't. I can't calm down.
Xiaodong! Xiao... Xiao...
Miss Biao, what are you doing?
Your performance is too exaggerating and dry.
You need moistening.
Flunk. Flunk. Flunk.
Out. Out. Out.
Xue Xiaodong, you're like a blank sheet.
You don't need her. She doesn't deserve it.
I need a sincere performer.
That little girl.
Come and give it a try.
In fact, I'm pretty interested in performing.
Performing is very hard.
Not as easy as you thought.
It's something that we should revere.
First of all, clear your mind.
Done.
Recite the lines.
Be ready for the role as soon as possible.
I've heard that there was a kind of bird
with no legs.
It could fly and fly only.
When it got tired,
it slept in the wind.
This kind of bird could land only once,
that was the time it died.
We broke up right on the April Fools' Day.
I was convinced that she was joking with me.
I bought thirty cans of pineapple.
Because it's her favorite food.
I told myself...
Those cans of pineapple were to expire on May 1st.
May 1st is my birthday.
I told myself, if she won't show up on that day,
our love will expire, too.
Am I right?
Is that what you want?
Miss Biao, how is that?
Let's try a new paragraph.
In fact, I have so much to tell you.
I had a relationship before.
I... Loved him so much.
He also loved me so much.
Maybe we were not meant for each other.
Or I didn't cherish him well.
So many problems happened.
I always felt that I couldn't find someone
who could love me again.
But didn't expect that I would bump into you.
So I feel that it is meant to happen.
Do you have something to tell me?
How is that?
Try again.
Miss Biao, can I have a look at the lines?
So we...
From now on, we'll be friends for one minute.
You belong with me.
I belong with you.
For one minute.
Done.
A long time ago,
when one had a secret,
he would go deep into a mountain,
to find a big tree and dig a hole.
Then told his secret to that hole.
Then sealed it up with some soil.
In that way,
no one would know his secret.
Is that what you want?
Today, we brothers are gonna have an unprecedented
courageous challenge!
That girl. That girl.
Look, everyone.
That girl is taking a selfie.
And we're gonna go kiss her.
Let's go.
Hello, sis.
Can I take a selfie with you?
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
I'll help you get him!
Stop!
Are you crazy?
Run! Hurry!
Our courageous challenge today
completed successfully!
Brother, she's coming!
Run! Run!
Run!
Stop!
Guan Xinyi.
You can solve this problem in this way.
Thank you.
How about you try to cry this time?
Because I'm leaving.
I gotta cry?
Yes...
Cry?
For example, I'm leaving you.
So you... You...
Let me feel your sadness.
If I leave you some day,
will you get me back?
I will.
What are you laughing at?
What are you laughing at? What's so funny?
Are you done with the song?
I gotta release the album in three days.
What my Xiaodong should do?
He gotta go to school.
If no red carpet at the newcomer award,
no solemn introduction,
no cooperation with Zhang Yimou,
I won't go there!
Can you see...
The biggest star?
If you're very capable,
can you pick it up for me?
Yes.
Well, when you make big money some day,
can you buy a big home for me?
Yes.
How about cars?
It doesn't feel that way.
Let's try again.
No! No! No!
My Xiaodong performs really well.
I've never seen such a potential actor.
What the hell that little girl performs?
I can't bear it any more.
Even I perform better than she does.
I love you.
I'm willing to pick up the stars for you.
I'm willing to pick up the moon for you.
And then?
You're my only one.
I'm so bad at this, right?
It's okay. It's okay.
-Let's try again.
-Try again.
Okay.
I love you.
I'm willing to pick up the stars for you.
I'm willing to pick up the moon for you.
You're my only one.
Better?
A little.
I've told you!
No. No. We won't join it
if less than eight hundred thousand! Okay?
Okay. I got it.
Lion!
Gorilla!
Electric fan.
Electric fan?
Liao Danyi.
You solved that problem very nicely.
I had a dad who loved me very much.
We often flew kites together.
With the whole family.
When I was four,
we flew kites in a very, very big park.
I believed that he led the way ahead of me.
I was running and running. But suddenly, I lost him.
Since then, he just disappeared.
As of that day, my mom got depression.
Went mad.
And then, when I was fourteen,
my mom passed away.
Since then, my brother started looking after me.
He worked hard every day.
He did various jobs.
And he studied very hard.
To get scholarships.
Then he could be admitted by a good school.
And took me there as well.
No more words. I gotta write.
Fight for my sister.
Ye Muxi. Ye Muxi.
For my sister. For my sister.
I'm really happy to have such a brother.
But...
Sometimes I really want to know
how it feels to have dad and mom around.
My brother went working every day.
No matter how tiring it was,
whether he sweat or bled, when he came back home,
he will still smiled at me and said,
never mind, it's okay as long as you're happy.
Because we ran out of money,
we could only live in a twenty-square-meters house.
And...
We only had one bed.
So he slept on the floor.
I slept on the bed.
It's okay if he couldn't have enough meals.
As long as I was full, he would feel happy.
What?
Look at your bag, it's wide open.
Look nice when in school.
Sis, I must stop here.
Come, look what I have made for you.
Here, sit.
So many delicious food.
This is your favorite fried eggs with tomatoes.
A cold dish for you.
And a chicken.
Hurry, start eating.
Did... Did that old lady bully you again?
Tell me.
Here, I made a ginseng tea for you.
Drink it. Good for your brain.
When I make big money,
I'll take you to eat hot-pots all around the world!
I've been touched enough
since you can think that way and say that.
Later,
I met dad.
I found that he married another woman.
With other kids.
Although I hate him very much,
I still wish that he could be happy.
I feel that I'm living a happy life.
Very happy.
My only concern is that I have too many fans.
I'm afraid that they'll recognize me every time I go out.
Boring!
Try again.
That day we worked very late,
my broker sis Annie sent me some chicken soup.
Dull!
Try again.
That signing session...
Boring!
Look at your performance.
Look at Ye Muxi's.
Look at your eyes, so empty.
Confession of life can best mobilize an actor's emotions.
But look at you.
Where are your emotions?
Give me some.
Try again!
I can't. I can't.
I also need a break.
Listen, you're besieged!
Put down your arms and surrender!
I can spare you life.
Listen, I won't surrender!
Listen.
This is the final duel between you and me!
Only one of us will live!
You're dead!
Don't try me!
My bike is broken.
Lend yours to me.
Come and get me.
So naughty. Let me give you a ride.
My bike is broken.
Lend yours to me.
Come and get me.
What are you doing?
This is the final duel between you and me.
Cut the crap. Come on.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five!
What's wrong?
I find it so hard.
Why I can't make it till now?
Maybe I'm not a performance material.
I better be a little fatty.
Nonsense.
In fact it's very simple.
How did you make it?
I don't know, either.
Anyway, I think I should be natural.
And think about someone I care about.
Just the one I talked about, my brother.
I think you can do it when thinking about
the one you care about.
The one I care about?
What?
In fact, only Ye Muxi knows about this matter.
So, please help me keep it a secret.
When I was a kid, I was fat.
Very, very fat.
I had no friends.
Because they all mocked me, excluded me.
I was really angry back then.
I always vent my anger on my mother.
Because I thought it was all her fault.
She indulged me.
She made delicious food for me.
She made me become a big fatty.
A laughingstock.
One day, I had a fight with my classmates.
They said I was a pig.
I was furious.
When I went back home,
I found my mother had made
a table of delicious food for me again.
I was so angry that I turned the table over.
I shouted to her, crying.
It's all your fault.
You make me become a fat guy.
You make me disgusting. I hate you!
But mother didn't say anything.
She squat down quietly.
To clean up the dishes.
I... I was shocked.
Because I saw her tears.
That was my first time to see mother crying.
I always thought...
She's a very strong woman.
She always smiles to life.
I didn't expect that she would cry.
Since that day,
I find that mother smiles or cries all because of me.
It's been so many years.
But I still owe her an apology.
I love you.