No, can't do this.
Maybe I can...
My lady, you can't.....
You shut up.
Our lady is always so busy.
She doesn't have time for these stupid homework.
My lady. We can't take the shortcuts.
You should do it by yourself.
Copying answers will do you no good!
My lady, listen to me.
The one who succeeds does not care for trifles.
It's a kind of courage to pursue things at all costs.
Don't learn from some Lius, always hesitating.
And some Lius' ministers,
Never can do you any good.
This Sima,
he was a treacherous minister when he was alive.
His offspring are all unfilial and disloyal.
Usurp throne and betray, you name it.
You big green bug, who are you talking about?
You!
I've been enduring you for a long time.
I want to kick your ass for a long time!
This is happening again.
So my brain stopped working.
I didn't expect you have advanced a lot since the last time.
You, too.
Seems there's only one way to bang it out.
Come on, I'm not afraid of you.
If I win,
Yezi will never copy answers anymore.
What if I win?
Then I'll say no more about this.
Deal!
Sima, I must win.
I really need to copy the answers.
My lady,
Although you're not on my side.
But I'll still do my best.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Wait, best of three sets.
Okay.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Best of five sets.
Fine, I'll give you that.
Rock, paper, scissors.
This game is so easy!
Wait!
You will always go with rock?
Yeah.
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 32
You're here.
Amazing.
One hour. That's fast.
I know it's a right choice to reach you.
I only admire three person in the world.
First one, Bill Gates.
The second one, Buffet.
The third used to be Steve Jobs.
Now I think that one should be you, only you.
It's not right.
The answer should have one more page.
I'm just about to ask you that.
What do you mean?
The test paper you gave me.
Lack of the two last topics.
How did you know that?
It's 150 points in total.
It has marked,
There's only less than 130 points.
That's impossible.
Where did you get these papers this time?
Maybe you got it wrong?
That's impossible.
It's stole from Director Yan's office...
What nonsense are you talking about?
How about this.
I'll leave first.
If you got the last two topics.
Take a pic and send it to me.
Why not picking up?
Who are you calling?
We're calling the same person.
How would that get through?!
Hello.
The papers have two more topics.
That's impossible.
Why would we lie to you?!
Check it yourself.
I stole it from director Yan in person.
Is that Yan's trap?
That damn dog!
I'm tailing them. Talk later.
What's wrong?
Nothing, let's go.
We're followed.
One, two, three!
Here.
Thanks.
Take care.
Here.
Okay, thanks.
You're welcome.
Hello, where're you?
I'm at the cinema.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
Come.
Bro, the paper you gave us isn't completed.
Not completed?
That's impossible.
Impossible?
We're in the light.
Teachers and the supervisor team will be after us.
So you only care about yourselves.
If I didn't guess wrong.
The one in the middle is Answer.
Answer?
Three of us
are on the same train.
It's called on the same boat.
Read some books, okay?
Fine.
Three of us,
are sitting on the same boat.
So, this thing will benefit no one.
You'd better find out what is happening.
Otherwise, we'll lose our customers.
I'll deal with it soon.
Let's go.
This way.
What's going on？
Right, so many errors.
It has spread out.
Right, what happened?
That's big news.
Yesterday's test,
the answer was all wrong.
Those students who cheated all got punished
Cheaters can't go to class?!
Is there any law in this world?
Law?
They'll be expelled, right?
Stop saying anything.
Who said that?
You're in my school.
There's school rules and regulations. Law?!
What is the time now? Law?
Do you think those students shouldn't get suspended?
Listen to me.
This is Maple Leaf Middle School.
A high-level school!
A school for the nobles.
We're not tolerating these bad tendencies in here.
Nor cheating.
This is protecting the other students' interests.
This time is suspended, recorded of demerit.
Next time, that's dismiss!
Troublemakers.
What're you doing?
Voice down.
Low profile.
Now we've got too many enemies.
So the answer was from you?
That's away too far!
No, it's not our fault.
We didn't know why it suddenly got out.
That Dog Yan changed the answers.
And the worse is,
those wouldn't even read the paper first before they copy it.
No, I mean. You didn't give me a copy.
Here, here, here.
The answer of today's monthly examination.
I don't want it.
Why?
It's free.
No, I'm afraid the director will catch me.
And expel me out from school.
Are you a monkey?
Today he is killing some chickens to alert the monkeys.
If you don't take this answer. Then you're a monkey.
Take a bet, you can turn your bike to a motorbike.
Take a bet, you can turn your motorbike to a land rover.
Fine, fine.
Read it first.
Must be right.
Why give me so many?
This time the answer lacks the last two topics.
But these can at least get you pass.
Go spread it.
Consider it as a bonus for our old customers.
Difficulty Easily Solved Corp
I knew it.
I knew this is not free.
They are over there!
-Over there! Go get them!
-Bye! Move, move, move.
-Hurry, don't let them get away.
-Hurry, over there.
Over there, hurry.
Hurry, hurry.
Look, we don't have the answer for the last two.
It should be okay, right?
Should be okay.
Good.
Those people who bought our answers,
that should get them pass.
We can give them twenty percent off.
Okay.
Did you give Ye Muxi a copy?
I have.
Ye Muxi is our loyal costumer.
Never expected that.
Big boss, I was wrong.
Big boss, forgive me, okay?
Big boss, I'll never do it again.
Big boss, I'm the last.
You're the best.
Teach me, teach me.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Teach me, okay? I was wrong.
I...
It's nothing.
I only got more than twenty points than you.
Nothing.
Big boss,
I'm the last. I'm the last!
I was wrong, teach me.
No, don't tear it up.
-Big Boss, I was wrong.
-It's okay.
I was wrong. I was wrong.
What're you day dreaming about?
You just wait for your miserable death.
You?
Lian Danyi, listen to me.
I'll get a better score than you this time.
Wait to see me laughing at you.
No need, I'll kill myself.
Wait and see.
If you beat me in exam with no cheating.
I'll let you laugh.
None of your business.
Miss Xinyi, I heard you wanna see me?
Did I? I don't think so.
Miss Xinyi, just tell me.
I'll make it for you no matter what it takes.
There was something. But now it's okay.
Miss Xinyi.
You called me here but now sending me away.
You treat me like I'm disposable.
I wanna cry.
Bad girl, bad girl, bad girl, bad girl.
Stop, stop, stop!
Look.
These are the last two topics of tomorrow's paper.
Take a look. I've to go first.
Interesting.
I'm ranking the fifteenth in our grade.
Why do I need this?
Miss Xinyi. Where're you going? Wait!
Big boss.
Boss, what're you doing here?
Sunflower seeds.
How are you preparing for the test?
Great. You know.
Liao Danyi bet with me
that I won't beat him.
He didn't know I have the answer.
Yes!
But... Where did you get the answer?
Leave that to us.
We have our own ways.
We've to go first.
See you later.
Bye. Bye.
[Maple Leaf Middle School]
Today, I've to tell you three points.
First, Confucius told us
If someone lied to us once, we shouldn't trust him again.
That tells us the importance of integrity.
But lately, in your school,
there has been something unpleasant going on.
The phenomenon of plagiarism.
What kind of behavior the plagiarism is?
Plagiarism is being irresponsible for oneself.
Why do we say plagiarism is being irresponsible for us?
That's because,
Plagiarism is being irresponsible for oneself.
What the heck?
Same sentence again and again.
It's like, I'm man.
Why am I not a man who is not a woman?
That's because I'm a man.
That logic.
I have to say I admire you, director.
Of course.
Our school has punishment to this kind of behavior.
Those students who were caught with cheating sheet,
will be suspended for a week as from today.
Then according to his/her attitude and practical action,
we'll decide the follow-ups.
I hope the rest of you will take warning.
Although you fell in front of the enemies' gun.
But you shot a bloody way out for our revolution.
Salute to you.
[Exam Room No. 7]
[10:30- 11:45]
Ye Muxi, what're you doing?
Drinking water.
Students, no more talking.
This examination is city-wide uniform examination
We use the simulating senior high school entrance test method.
With school-wide disorder seats.
You'll sit in a strange classroom
and strange environment to write your papers.
But I hope you can make adjustments
and do your best.
Nice, fate has brought us together.
Miss Xinyi, I'll protect you.
That student, stop talking.
Teacher, I need to go to the restroom.
Okay, Guan. Make it quick.
The exam is about to start.
My bottle.
That student, what're you doing?
I need to go to the restroom.
Not you.
I need it too. Urgently.
You want to leave right after Guan left.
Can I suspect you for cheating?
I'm in a hurry.
You can go after Guan come back.
But....
There's no but.
Say no more, or you'll be disqualified.
Why did you take my bottle?
To throw it away.
It's empty.
Yes, but it's still my bottle.
That's strange, why do you need an empty bottle?
Is there anything on it you don't want anyone to know?
No.
Then the conversation is over.
Or if there is, you go with me to see Director Yan.
Do you dare?
Forget it.
Answer.
Are you speaking to me?
Yes, still denying?
You mean this?
This paper belongs to you, right?
This has my name on it.
Of course it's mine.
Ninety points?
Check the last topic.
It is difficult.
So I did it wrong.
Then why these students wrote it in the same way?
These are the last two topics of tomorrow's test.
You don't need me to tell you how important it is.
You're the only one who has this.
These are the last two topics of tomorrow's test.
You finally admit it. Answer.
Even I'm Amswer.
I'm Answer, I'm Answer.
I'm Answer, so what?
You can't catch me.
That's not what I want.
I just wanna know why.
For money?
Money?
You think money is what I want?
Then for what?
To take revenge on society?
For Guan Xinyi.
My only Goddess.
What do you mean?
Once you step on the top,
It's hard to go back to the ground.
Guan Xinyi is also like that.
I grew up with her,
she was always the first in the class.
Until that time in middle school.
She was the second.
She was so sad.
And I felt sadder than her.
So I made an oath.
As long as I'm here.
Guan Xinyi will always be the first.
So I started to sell answer.
So those who got the first rank by luck
would copy cheating sheets, get addicted.
So their grade will descend.
And they will never be the opponent for Guan Xinyi.
Wait, there's a flaw.
What flaw?
Haven't you considered of me?
You?
Your middle school entrance test was forty points under mine.
You what?
I missed one exam.
I got the full mark for all the rest.
So, as long as I'm here.
None of you can get a higher score than mine.
So this spy plan...
I mean this boring plan was shattered
due to the stupid chief plotter didn't think clearly.
Answer disappeared from school ever since.
Without the source,
Huang Nan, Huang Yi's group shattered as well.
Ye Muxi, do your homework on your own.
Really can't do it.