# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 27
Cut! Camera A, camera B, playback.
Any problem with this shot?
No.
How about the voice? Any bloopers?
Lighting?
Director, lighting is okay.
Okay. Pass. Keep it.
How is that, sis Annie?
You've done a great job, Xiaodong.
But I don't understand.
Why do you value this thing so much?
Remember what happened to Chi Wanjun?
After she refused a boy's love improperly at school,
paparazzi used that boy
and spread rumors to damage her reputation.
Caused many negative effects on her.
As a students' idol, your image is very important.
Besides, I've done some study on that girl Yali.
Her family background is very good.
Might help your career more or less.
Believe me, Xiaodong.
Follow the path that our company paves for you.
You'll have the entire world under your feet.
Or, you still don't believe me?
Of course I believe you, sis Annie.
All right. Are there too many activities for you lately?
You have dark circles around your eyes.
Go have some rest.
Remember, Xiaodong.
Everything that we do is for you.
I know.
I promise, our company and I will spend all our time
and energy on you, and only you.
Xue Xiaodong. Xue Xiaodong.
Don't worry. I'm here not to do something improper.
I want to tell you that I've bought all the VIP seats
in the first two rows for your next concert.
So can I be the president of the third fans club of yours?
Thank you so much, Yali.
But, the fans club...
Yali.
In fact you didn't need to spend so much.
Let's talk about some details about the fans club.
Excuse me.
Teacher.
You seem not one of our Class Ten, right?
I'm a student of Class One.
Then why didn't you go back to Class One
but come to our Class Ten?
Okay. I'll go back now.
Teacher, let me introduce myself.
I know who you are.
You don't, right?
And you don't know my profession.
I know your profession.
Nothing but to build cheap idols in this faithless times.
To make huge profits.
Am I right?
You may leave now.
Fine. I'm leaving.
Bye, teacher.
Xiaodong, good luck.
Sorry, teacher.
I shouldn't bring my broker to school.
Xiaodong, as your teacher,
I feel obliged to remind you.
You're here to study, not to sing.
I hope you can be serious about your study.
So even if those speculative people
abandon you after using up your value,
at least you can rely on what you've learned
to establish yourself in society.
Okay. Got it. Thank you, teacher.
Go back to your seat.
Right, my new album will be released soon.
Good luck to me!
Good luck!
Bestseller!
Thanks.
What's up?
My bottleneck period.
So I think, should I change to another style?
To surprise people with one try.
Yet still accord with populace aesthetic.
That's what I'm good at.
Are you sure? What you're good at is not
to scare people with one try?
So funny.
Well, after all we're friends, right?
I said I can, then I can.
All right...
I can help, too.
My gratitude is in this wine.
No, in this coke.
Drinking and drinking? I... I want food.
May our watermelon alliance grow bigger!
Watermelon?
I don't want to any fruit like watermelon.
It's a nickname for Xiaodong's fans.
Aren't you silly?
But I'm not his fan.
I am.
All right.
Anyway, thanks, you guys.
Let's start eating!
Eat. Eat.
Don't eat my meat!
Yours. Yours. Here. Here.
Speaking of that He Lvxi in Class One.
He really has many funny stories.
My brother and I were in the same class
with He Lvxi back in middle school.
One day, we two went to take a shower.
Guess what we had seen?
What had you seen?
We saw He Lvxi serving instant noddles with the bath water.
Can you believe that?
My god!
Listen to me.
When we raised the national flag,
he walked in the front.
His trousers had a seam split.
Guess what color was his under-pant?
Floral, with strawberries!
Why should a man wear a strawberry under-pant?
My god!
I remembered.
We lived in the same dorm with him back in middle school.
So we took bath together.
One day, I saw him walk in the bathroom.
I asked, why did you bathe with shoes on?
He replied, so I can wash my shoes over the bath!
Speaking of shoes, I remembered one thing.
Once his classmate exchanged his shoes with some girl's.
He wore them for a whole month.
And that pair of shoes were pink!
How could he fail to find that?
Why didn't he wear those pink shoes today?
Sanitary inspection.
Right. Right, I remembered another thing!
Once when we were in school...
When we went back to the dorm,
at the door we saw a...
At first I thought it's a shoe.
But later I found it's a sock!
Very sticky, very stiff, standing right there.
Can you believe that?
So smelly!
What socks is he wearing today?
Lvxi, do you still have that sock?
-Lvxi, time to wash your socks.
-So smelly!
What a beautiful tune!
A tune that feels like this.
It feels like being caressed by a breeze.
So relaxing.
It must be related to clouds.
Or ocean.
Done!
The lyric!
So fast?!
Yes. Come on. Sing it out loud.
Okay.
Beyond the mountain, beyond the sea.
There are living a mysterious master.
If you ask him what does he want to sing?
He'll secretly shoot you with trench mortal.
Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
Indeed very powerful.
A shot will send you back home.
Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
Indeed very powerful.
A shot will send you back home.
Doesn't it fit well?
Fit what?
What the hell did you write?
Listening to his tune, I could only think of this.
Whether you listened to his tune or not,
what you could think would still be this, okay?
But I think trench mortal is pretty cool.
Sorry.
Suddenly I entered into the world of trench mortal.
What kind of world is that?
You really beat me.
Let's think about other themes.
Xiaodong?
Trench mortal?
-Xiaodong?
-Trench mortal?
Xiaodong?
Think about that.
Trench mortal is really an interesting theme.
Right! I think so!
Ye Muxi. I have another tune here.
Help me.
Okay. I got this!
Okay. I have so many ideas.
This one seems good as well.
So awesome!
Yes.
Then we can write this...
Have you... Have you heard of Doraemon?
Right. Then we can add it to this.
Then this...
Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
Trench... Trench... Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
One, two, three. Three. Three. Three...
Trench mortal.
Tr... Trench... Trench... Trench mortal.
Ye Muxi.
I gotta tell you something.
Please don't disturb my inspirations.
Something really important.
Let's talk outside.
Go ahead.
Right here?
Ye Muxi.
You and Xiaodong are best friends, right?
You also hope his career can grow better and better, right?
Of course.
I want to tell you that...
The lyric that you wrote seems a little inappropriate.
No. I think it's pretty appropriate.
Those blades and mortals you wrote...
Don't you feel it's too low-age?
What did you mean?
Means too childish.
Totally different from his style.
Childish...
Look, this is called interesting, you know?
Interesting songs should have interesting lyrics.
It's a match.
Interesting?
I don't find it interesting at all.
Don't impose your aesthetic on other people.
Or feel everyone's aesthetic is the same as yours.
He'll lose fans like hell, you know?
Well, your lyric is good.
Mine is rubbish, right?
No need to explain.
Your job now. I don't want to write any now.
Where are you going, Ye Muxi?
I got an emergency.
Lvxi.
What's up, Miss Xinyi?
Do you think I'm charming?
In you boys' eye...
Am I kinda a popular girl?
Do you think I'm a cute girl?
Miss Xinyi, don't be like this!
In my heart, you're an idol!
If you flirt with me like this every day, I'm gonna go crazy!
What should I do?
My heart beats so fast! Miss Xinyi.
Sadness of this city.
Turns into hope in this moment.
The second line and the fourth line.
Which one is better?
Look.
Shanqi?
Shanqi.
Look, the second line and the fourth line.
Which one is better?
I think, the latter is better.
The former doesn't rhyme very well.
Makes sense.
Needs modifying.
Well, your lyric is good.
Mine is rubbish, right?
Xiaodong.
Although I want to help you write the lyric,
I gotta go to do something right now.
What's that?
Something very important.
Excuse me.
In the past, I didn't like making friends.
Nor communicating with other people.
Every day, I just sat before the computer.
Felt very happy facing the computer.
But someone changed me.
Who?
Ye Muxi.
Big boss?
She showed up.
Made me feel the communication between people
seems a little different from facing the cold screen.
There's temperature.
So after I came to Class Ten.
Being with everyone else,
and the one I admire the most,
I've been every happy every day.
What are you making?
A tomb.
Whose tomb?
Our friendship's tomb.
Don't take it so seriously.
I'm joking. Just making a mound.
But I still have to apologize for what I said to you.
Never mind. No big deal.
Not angry now?
I didn't get angry. It's no big deal.
All right. We still are best friends.
In fact, the lyric you wrote sounds pretty good.
Don't lie to your conscience.
Otherwise I'll be struck by lightning.
Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
Bombs tanks into ashes.
Makes you die fast.
What are you laughing at?
Sounds awful.
You sing, then.
Listen, you gotta feel this song.
Feel.
Feel it?
Okay. Come, let me teach you.
Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
Bombs tanks into ashes.
Right. Right. Right.
Feel it. Right. Try again.
Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
Bombs tanks into ashes.
Makes you die fast.
Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
Right. Right. Feel it!
Eighty points!
Brother, I got...
Eighty points.
Brother, you're so awesome!
I only got seventy points.
What's your secret of this success?
Awesome, brother.
Eighty points.
Awesome. Awesome.
Eighty points. Eighty points. Eighty points.
It hurts!
Congrats! Huang Yi got eighty points.
Now, warm applause to Huang Yi!
Sir.
Do you need a paper worth eighty points?
Look at this. Look at this. Eighty points.
Tiancheng, can't believe that I got eighty points!
Look. Look at this. Look, eighty points!
Tiancheng, just take a look at this.
It's really eighty points.
Shen Wei.
Do you know what's the secret of my eighty points?
No need. I got ninety-seven points.
The secret of my eighty points is...
Persevere! Work hard! And never give up!
Most importantly, that...
That heart.
Shanqi.
Have you heard of some voice?
What voice?
Listen.
Listen carefully.
Eighty points.
Huang Yi got eighty points.
Yes. This is a call from the soul.
Shanqi.
Have you heard of the song of eighty points?
Nope.
Let me sing it for you.
Eighty points comes again.
Huang Yi's eighty points.
Points...
Right. It'll be better if I do some rap.
Huang Yi eighty points.
You're so noisy and so annoying! Get out!
So noisy.
Eighty points. Eighty points.
Now class begins.
Let me tell you something before we start.
I got wrong papers last time.
It's for Grade One in middle school.
But you all have done a good job.
The average score is ninety-five points.
Very good.
Okay. Let's get started now.