Have you watched the idol drama I performed?
They said I'm such a poor actor.
So my broker arranged me some Performance Lesson.
And told me to go.
Performance Lesson?
My family name is Biao.
You can call me Miss Biao.
The famous Director's name is Famous.
So the Performance teacher's name must be Performance.
Little girl, what are you talking about?
I'm not that shameless like director Famous.
Called himself Famous.
My name is Beauty Biao.
Lion!
Gorilla!
Electronic Fan!
Electronic Fan?
Look at your performance.
Look at Ye Muxi's.
Your eyes are so empty.
Life story is...
The best way to enhance your enthusiasm.
Look at you.
Where are your emotions?
-You're dead!
-I'll kill ya!
One. Two. Three.
Four.
Five!
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 24
Guan Xinyi.
I'm one of the class committee of Class Ten.
I'm responsible for what Huang Nan and Huang Yi did to you.
Don't take it to the heart.
I'll punish them.
Please wait here for a while
Why are you looking at me?
Danyi is back?
Brother.
Nothing. Nothing.
Something is going on here?
Brother.
She is just my classmate.
Classmate. Really?
It's true.
Classmate.
Guan Xinyi, he is my big brother.
-Hello, I'm Ye...
-His name is...
Liao Yihan.
I'm Liao Yihan.
Hello, brother.
Hello.
I won't interrupt your two.
I'll go write my stuff.
Go for it, brother.
Go for it.
Sit.
Why did you call me here?
I like you.
Ye Muxi. I like you.
Not the friend kind of like.
Would you.... Be my girlfriend?
Say it.
I like you.
I like to watch you smile.
I like to see you bump into my world.
I like you messing around with me.
I like the true myself in front of you.
I... I really like you,
Not that kind of like to a friend.
Would you be my girlfriend?
I do.
Cut!
God! Look! You're much better!
Look, look! That's impressive!
I almost bought it!
That's real something!
You made a great advance! Amazing!
I bought that you love me part! Gosh!
Gosh! Gosh! Again, again.
Go on, go on, go on.
Did you see? Did you see?
Did you see?!
Today is your first lesson.
Xue Xiaodong. Your score is...
Flunk.
But, you have potential.
I knew....
Little girl.
I like you very much.
I hope you can really think about to be an actress.
I'm just a normal girl.
Not an actress.
That industry is too complicated.
No, no.
Fine.
Thank you for your sincere performance today.
Thanks.
Thank you, teacher.
Performance is quite interesting.
Right.
One day you'll realize it.
It's not for you.
So this is Liao Danyi's home.
Do I need to refine the make-up?
Bathroom?
Oh, there.
Damn, I've ran out of stories.
No inspirations.
Inspiration, Inspiration
What shall I do?
Brother.
Yezi.
When did you come back?
Already changed into your pajamas?
I'm back for a long time.
And you know what?
I went to have a performance lesson.
How did that go?
It's quite interesting.
I know you must be good.
I'll go have some rest.
Off you go.
And Liao Danyi.
What?
I mean,
He snores every night.
So noisy!
Yezi, now we're all living under the same roof.
So be magnanimous, okay?
No grudges will last overnight.
It's okay.
Go, sleep.
Brush your teeth.
Good night.
Don't know what to write. I give up.
Right.
Must cook some breakfast for Yezi and Danyi.
Better prepare a little.
Guan Xinyi.
Your clothes is dry now.
Monster!
What just happened?
Why do I feel so tired?
I also feel it is more exhausted to play than to study.
I'm so tired.
Stop!
Don't move! Don't move!
My waist. My waist!
No, I don't want to move. My leg cramped.
Wait. Wait.
Are you feeling better?
Let's go. Let's go.
-I gotta go back and sleep for two days.
-No more play.
I need two days sleep too.
Exhausted.
Meijing!
Shanqi!
Shanqi.
What's wrong?
I started to burp this morning.
I can't stop it.
I can help.
Waiter, a glass of water.
Shanqi, Meijing.
What's wrong?
I burped a whole morning, until now.
Shanqi tried many ways.
But it didn't stop.
That's right.
The eight trigrams tells me.
You're in very bad luck today.
How can we turn her bad luck into good luck?
Follow the compass.
Stop!
That's the place. Northeast.
If you stand here for one forth incense's time.
You bad luck will disappear.
[ Restroom ]
Shanqi.
Hi, hi.
Hi Meijing.
What happened?
I burped a whole morning until now.
Shanqi and Weiwei tried many ways but all failed.
That's reason.
Come with me.
Where're we going now?
I know a way.
If you get spooked,
You'll stop burping.
Then where're we going?
To see Li Yao.
Li Yao. Come down!
What's it?
Meijing.
I heard you need my help?
We have tried every way.
Why none of them worked?
Maybe it's destined.
We can't change it.
Don't get upset.
We will.... Find a way!
Are you okay?
I don't know what's happening to me.
Is that a kind of contiguous sickness?
That's impossible.
I think it's...
Destined!
Seriously?!
Coming. Coming.
- Danyi, it's you.
- Brother Yihan.
Brother Yihan.
Have you seen my grandma?
I didn't.
Grandma?
-I've to go.
-Wait. Wait. Wait.
What is that?
Tell us.
What happened?
My grandma ran out from the nursing home again.
Where did that old lady go?
She is making my life miserable!
That old lady.
Call the police.
The police won't take the case
unless it's over forty-eight hours.
What shall we do?
Let's do this.
Yezi. You and Danyi.
Go search around the nursing home.
I'll go to the pedestrian zone.
We'll go find her separately.
When we find her, inform each other, okay?
Keep in touch.
If any of us find her.
-Okay.
-Go, go.
Hurry, Yezi. Let's go.
So sad!
- So sad!
- Huang Nan, Huang Yi.
What's wrong?
Don't mention it.
I'm so in a bad luck today.
What's wrong?
Who bullied you?
He insisted to try the high-level skate board move.
So he ended up like this.
Let's go.
Live with it.
No, not that.
I'm not crying for my knees.
It's my skate board.
Skate board?
Before he could get up.
An old lady stepped on our skate board and slipped away.
An old lady?
It's a limited version.
Took by an old lady like that.
What kind of old lady?
About sixty or seventy years old.
Move, move, move.
Gimme.
Stop! Stop!
Stop running.
Stop!
Grandma?!
Where did she go?
That way.
She is so fast!
We can't stop her!
Let's go.
Remember to tell her when you see her
We admire her so much!
And could she return my skate board?
Return our skate board!
One, two, three. Woodman!
Okay, now we know the direction.
Won't be far.
She should be okay.
I know too little about my grandma.
I didn't know she can play skate board.
That's a piece of cake for her.
I heard when she was young,
she surfed in the ocean a lot.
Her sense of balance is great!
I'm so ashamed.
Even you know her more than I do.
I also feel it strange.
She has so many amazing stories.
She didn't tell you?
My grandpa died before I was born.
Then no matter what my parents said,
grandma insisted to live at home.
She said she must protect her home.
Later, the old house was torn apart.
We planned to let her live with us.
But we didn't expect she seemed
had collapsed with the house together.
Then she became like this.
My father insisted to send her to the nursing home.
No wonder I didn't see her when I was young.
She always took care of me.
She has been very strict to me.
I can only go see her in the weekend.
And we don't talk much.
- Fedi. My Fedi.
- Calm down.
I'm gonna go save Fedi, let go of me!
I must save Fedi.
- Calm down.
- I must save Fedi, let go!
Fedi! My Feidi!
Protect it. I'll go find Zorro.
Thank you.
This old lady is such a heroine!
Skate board?
Fedi.
One, two, three. Wood.... Man...
One, Two.
Gosh! So scary!
One, two, three, woodman.
Hi, Miss.
Have you seen this old lady?
No.
Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Hi, have you seen this woman?
No, haven't.
No, no.
Thanks.
It's okay.
We can't go on like this
Must narrow it down.
Otherwise, it's like looking for a needle in the ocean.
How shall we find her?
How?
We must know where did she go?
How to know that?
How?
First, we must know what she is thinking.
Grandma always talks about grandpa.
Grandpa?
But he has passed away.
Could she go to visit his tomb?
That's impossible.
Grandpa doesn't have a grave.
She won't go there.
She won't.
It's impossible.
That will be hard.
It's all my fault.
Since she was ill.
I never took her illness seriously.
And I never bothered to know her past.
If I tried to know it.
This wouldn't happen.
It's okay, don't worry.
I'm here.
Don't be afraid. We will find her!
I know it!
One, two, three, woodman!
Woodman!
-Grandma!
You two came.
How did you know I'm here?
Grandma, don't ran out by yourself.
We're so worried about you.
This place,
is the place where your grandpa left.
Danyi,
Grandma is getting older and older.
There're a lot time I'm in confusion.
When I'm myself.
I realize that,
So many people, so many things, so many places
I can't remember it at all.
But only this place.
I don't want to forget.
Grandma, grandma, grandma.
Grandma, grandma!
Grand...grandma!
Look, you two are so silly.
You thought I'm dead?
I won't die that young.
I'm very strong!
Look, look!
I'll live to see the end of the world.
Yes.
Okay, now. You go sit over there by yourself.
I need to say something to Yezi alone.
Go, go.
I'll go find you soon.
Yezi.
Why did you know I'm here?
I peeped at your letter in the box.
You peeped in my box?
So you and Danyi were looking for me?
We're not family.
I'm also worried about you.
Your hand.
This is for you.
Isn't this the bracelet in your box?
Yes, it is.
It's my gift for you.
Take it.
No, I can't.
Take it. Grandma told you to take it.
It's not expensive. It's cheap.
But you can't throw it away.
Can't lose it.
Let's go.
Walk me to that shitty nursing home.
Although I don't want to.
But I have to go.
Right.
Otherwise.
They'll search everywhere for me.
Why the bracelet is with you?
Grandma gave it to me.
Be careful with it.
What? Want it?
I can give it to you if you want.
No need.
Since grandma gave it to you.
Keep it safe.
Yali, what're you doing?
Monitor.
As a student from Maple Leaf Middle School.
I hope you can pay attention to your behavior outside.
Sorry, monitor.
You must remember you're one of us.
Be proud of Maple Leaf today.
And Maple Leaf will be proud of you in future.
Go pick it up.
Yes.
Yali, as a man.
Of course I can pick it up for you.
But I want you to remember this lesson.
Let's go watch The Fast and the Furious 8 next week.
-Okay.
-They say it's amazing.
I heard so.
I've seen the one to seven episodes.
Me too. I was gonna...
Classmates, what're you doing?
You must know that your priority is study.
Don't let puppy love virus
infect your pure mind.
Remember you're one of the Maple Leaf.
Be proud of the Maple Leaf today.
The Maple Leaf will be proud of you in future.
Understand?
Understood.
I hope you two can keep an appropriate distance.
That's so cool!
It's so boring.
So much homework.
Let's go out...
Students, are you from Class Ten?
Yes.
What're you wearing inside?
What kind of trousers is that?
I hope you can wear your uniforms properly.
Remember you're one of the Maple Leaf.
Be proud of the Maple Leaf today.
The Maple Leaf will be proud of you in future.
Wear your uniform well.
What a jerk?!
So handsome!
The vice-chairman of the student union.
An ace in every lessons,
handsome
and well-educated man.
Of course.
When Guan Xinyi is not by his side.
Miss Xinyi. I'm here!
Miss Xinyi. You're so beautiful!
Full score.
Miss Xinyi. You're so pretty today.
Miss Xinyi, have you dined?
We have a meeting today.
When shall we go?
Miss Xinyi, Miss Xinyi. I mean...