Yezi, time to get up.
Listen, you're not getting up late today.
Even I have to get through eighty-one difficulties,
I will wake you up.
Ye...
You're up?
This...
Dressing so nice in the early morning?
Where're you going?
I've got things to do today, talk later.
Won't have breakfast with you. Bye. Bye.
Yezi. Yezi!
What about dinner?
Not eating breakfast.
Where's she going?
No way.
Something is going on.
Let's go.
Did you tell your brother about the place we go?
I didn't, why?
Because he has been following us.
Where're they?
Brother, why're you following us?
Here's the thing.
I got up this morning.
Seems the weather is nice today.
So I got out to get some fresh air.
Well....
You two...
Come.
To be honest, I have thought about this day before.
But I didn't expect,
that would come so soon.
But it's good.
It's you.
You're better than anyone else.
My Yezi,
her future,
is on your shoulder now.
The truth is,
the reason why I got out with him is...
grandma is ill.
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 34
Madam, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Long time no see.
Dad.
-Grandma.
-Danyi.
Grandma.
What took you so long?
I miss you so much.
I went to get you some fruit.
Don't need fruit.
As long as you're here, it's great.
Come to see me right after school.
Okay.
Where's your dad?
My dad?
He's busy, so he left.
Left again.
Let him leave, as long as you're here.
I just wanna see you.
Where's Yezi?
Grandma.
Yezi, Yezi.
I'm just asking him about you.
I'm so happy to see you.
You're amazing.
Danyi, give Yezi an apple.
Grandma, you eat.
I had enough for today.
You eat.
I'm happy to see you eat an apple.
Okay, I'll eat.
Grandma.
I bought those apples for you.
Let her eat.
I wanna see her eat it.
Stingy.
Who is stingy?
You.
You...
I...
I...you...
We...
We're a team.
You two.
Every time I see you two,
Laughing and arguing,
Reminds me of me and your grandpa.
When I miss him,
I sit at the beach,
It's like he comes towards me from the sea.
When I'm old,
Your grandpa told me.
Hey, old woman.
If one day I died,
cast my ashes into the sea.
When you miss me, just sit on the beach.
So Danyi,
If my time comes,
Cast my ashes into the sea.
I'll wait for your grandpa to pick me up.
Grandma.
Grandma, don't say those ominous things.
How is that ominous?
It's life.
Humans all will die one day.
But I am not a normal human.
I'm an old fairy.
Can't die even if I want to.
So watching you growing up makes me so happy.
I like Yezi.
I like grandma.
Good girl.
We two are from the same school.
You got better scores in school.
Higher points.
More popular.
Then you went overseas to study.
You should have better opportunity than this.
But you came to Maple Leaf Middle School.
You have the ability and the qualification
to choose the best class in school, Class One.
Aka my class.
But you chose the most difficult class,
Class Ten.
I want to know
were you doing that for me?
Miss Luo. I was not.
What's the fun to choose a bunch of good students?
To make the worst the best,
that's more challenging for me.
You.
You know what?
In overseas, scores isn't the thing they values.
It's a student's comprehensive ability.
Miss Luo, how do you distinguish
the good students and the bad students?
I don't know what you mean.
I just want to unlock their potential.
See if those bad students in your eyes
can make some success.
I don't buy it.
Wu Heng.
I know it.
If you were not doing this for me.
Then you are doing this against me.
You were like this when we were in school.
Now you're still the same.
I know you purpose now.
You just want to turn a backward class
to a good class like mine.
To let all the people know that you're better than me.
Right?
So we both need to work harder.
As your companion,
to supervise and urge each other.
I think it's a good thing.
Wu Heng.
Every time I try to talk with you,
You'll give me a lesson.
You're a boring man.
Fine, no more business then.
Just enjoying these beautiful sunshine in the weekend.
Grandma, time for your pills.
Grandma.
No!
If you don't eat this, you'll get worse.
You think I'm a kid?
Easy to lie to?
Pills are poison.
I know my body.
Grandma, stop playing.
What're you talking about?
Why do you sound so like your father?
Pills are all poison. You know?
These pills make me hard to sleep at night, hard to eat.
I have so many nightmares.
I could only lie down here and wait for my time.
Danyi, are you expecting that day would come sooner?
Grandma, what're you talking about.
She doesn't want it, so don't.
Right.
She is not your grandma, of course you're not worried.
I...
Grandma.
Danyi.
I want this cake.
Eat your pills.
Cake first, pills later, okay?
No.
If you want the cake, eat the pills first.
I'm dying.
Grandma, grandma.
Yezi,
After I died,
I have to ask you to take care of my grandson.
No, grandma, he is so annoying.
I don't want that.
He is not annoying.
Just one flaw.
He is stingy.
He wouldn't let his grandma have a piece of cake.
You.
You won't let grandma have a piece of cake?
Pills first, cake later.
Let her eat.
No.
Grandma, I want cake, too.
I know.
Grandma, I'm gonna go get your lunch.
No need.
I don't want lunch.
You wouldn't let me have a cake.
So I won't have lunch.
No lunch, then.
Ye Muxi, outside.
Come.
What?
Grandma won't eat her pills. What shall we do?
How would I know?
Why would you give her the cake?
She likes cake.
She won't eat her pills with cake around.
Then what shall we do?
I have an idea.
It's a cake.
What?
Her pill.
You want to poison her?!
This is the medicine powder.
I just spill it on the cake.
So grandma will eat it.
This is smart.
I'll give her,
Grandma.
Yezi, you're back.
You wanna eat cake?
Of course I do.
Don't eat this.
This one is chocolate flavor,
This one is strawberry flavor. You will like this.
You bought it for me?
Yezi, Yezi, you're my sweet baby.
Since you bought this cake for me.
Get some milk tea as well?
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Thanks.
Some days later,
grandma ran out from the nursing home again.
But this time, I know where to find her.
Where is that old lady again?!
She is making this hard for me!
That old lady...
Dad.
I heard grandma goes to the seaside a lot.
Let's check the beach.
That's impossible.
The beach is more than ten kilometers away.
How could an old woman get that far?!
Just check around this area.
If we can't find her before the dusk.
I'll call the police.
Eyes wide open, and check carefully.
Yezi, why did you come?
Because you told me
This is where grandpa left.
Good memory.
That's right.
Grandma, they said you're very sick.
Are you afraid?
Yezi.
In this world,
There's nothing that humans can't figure out.
Except one. That no one has figured out before.
Which is, where will people go
and what they will they do after death?
Now, it's my chance to find that out.
I'm so happy.
Why would I feel afraid?
Not nervous.
Not afraid.
Yezi.
I really like you.
Look, you're growing up.
People will come and tell you,
you need to do this, do that.
To make you become sophisticated.
They say that will help you in this world.
Just tell them,
Get the hell out.
If growing up means to be sophisticated.
I'd rather you'll be a kid forever.
Like now.
A pure and innocent little girl.
Yezi.
My Zorro is coming to get me.
I'm so looking forward to it.
Grandma, grandma.
Grandma!
Yezi, you silly girl.
I made jokes like this with you many times.
Why you would never learn?
Okay, tell me a story.
I want to hear a story.
Okay.
Once upon a time.
There's a princess.
Called Snow White.
She was the fairest
and the most beautiful girl in the world.
But because of that,
many people were jealous of her. Especially that witch.
So she sent some men to kill her.
But they couldn't.
Because she had a good fate.
She was very powerful.
Many people loves her.
Every people who saw her.
But...
Me and grandma were sitting there for a long time.
Until Liao Danyi and his dad came to the beach.
After you found my mom,
why you didn't tell us?
Grandma said, she doesn't want you to know.
Who gave you the right to make decision of my family?!
This is your friend?
Little girl, listen.
This isn't over.
But first, you need to stay away from my family as from now!
Danyi!
Several weeks after that thing,
Grandma passed away in her sleep.
Although he is a governor.
Looks so careless.
But in fact, he is a hero.
That's so beautiful! Okay!
This way, this way.
Kill him, kill him.
Go!
Game.
Although I don't play it, but I know.
Many games can be replayed again after you finish that round.
To get more bonus.
So you could get to the end sooner.
Or maybe even get a better result.
It's called Game In Hard Mode.
If you fight like this, your account will be a waste.
You have to play it again.
She has passed away.
It's the nature rule.
One day, I'll pass away as well.
So will you.
So, don't be sad.
In Maple Leaf School
how did you end up in Class Ten?
I missed a course.
Why you didn't retake that test?
I know you're still the best student.
But environment matters.
Luckily, me and your school master are close.
I arrange a make-up test and re-classgrouping for you.
Dad.
What if I tell you I don't want to go to any other classes?
Why is that?
For your friends?
Especially that girl.
I dislike her very much.
If she told us about your grandma's whereabouts at once.
Maybe...
I can blame her death on her.
But if you stay away from her,
I can leave her alone.
Do you understand?
Danyi, I hope you can go to Class One.
Go to A college after graduation.
Followed by two years study overseas.
After you come back,
I can arrange you in a famous corporation as a supervisor.
Not like me.
Struggling in the business circle.
That's the life I've planned for you.
All about you.
University dad wanted to go.
Country dad wanted to go.
Corporation dad wanted to go.
Dad has treated me as his Game In Hard Mode.
Dad has found me a new place to live.
I'm moving out tonight.
I'm transferring to Class One.