# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 36
You came.
What's wrong, Xiaodong?
Has Liao Danyi been transferred to Class One for a long time?
You bet.
His seat is empty for so long.
It makes me feel so sad every time when I see the vacancy.
Vacancy is not only on his seat.
What else?
So is Ye Muxi's seat.
Recently, she is either in the library or on the way to it.
Do you feel that Ye Muxi has changed?
Right, right. She has turned to a lady.
She is very gentle to everyone.
Yeah, even her voice is so gentle.
Right, right.
But her hair looks so pretty.
Listen, now she is so attentive in class.
No more scrawling.
Right, right. Her score leaps and bounds.
But which one do you like better?
The new one or the old one?
Anyway, makes me feel quite strange.
Right , right.
It's just.
I can't tell.
Right, right.
I wanted to say this a long time ago.
You all feel that, right?
She is totally different from before.
She has no energy.
I don't think she feels happy now.
To be honest, we all saw it.
Although Ye Muxi has changed in a good way.
But also in a wrong way.
When Liao Danyi left,
His all plans have worked.
He wants to give Ye Muxi a chance to grow up.
Seems she really does.
But don't you feel she is covering something?
She is not really happy.
But look,
Liao Danyi and Ye Muxi,
they two have this weird and tense relationship.
That can't last forever.
I miss the old days when we were all together and happy.
Me too.
So we're gonna help them.
How?
That's why I called you here.
To discuss how.
The way Lian Danyi treated monitor is not what he said.
More bark than bite.
Liao Danyi is so stubborn.
Won't say anything.
So we must create a chance.
To ask them out.
Talk face to face.
But in their condition,
how to make them two talk nicely?
To let them sit down and talk!
Sit down is not necessary,
as long as they can be in the same space.
We have to make them stay in the same space.
Lock them behind iron gate.
It can't be a scary place, need to be romantic.
Need some item from the romance story.
It's better at night.
With some dim light, will be better.
Since we have the same thoughts,
the best place for that should be...
School!
Amusement park is fine.
Since that.
Let's make a plan.
First, on Saturday, I'll hand the ticket to Ye Muxi.
Ask her to the amusement park.
We'll hand one ticket to Liao Danyi.
Ask him to the amusement park.
So they can be together alone.
Saturday, the amusement park is crowded.
Alone is not possible.
Then let's choose a day off.
So I will ask Ye Muxi to the amusement park on the day off.
There's no electric on the day off.
The equipment won't work.
Then we'll turn the power on by ourselves.
How to make them stay together?
To make them play the merry-go-round.
If it's merry-go-round,
they won't be able to talk.
Send them on the sky wheel.
Light some romantic firework!
Lure Ye Muxi onto the sky wheel by food.
Snacks!
Then we'll tell Liao Danyi through broadcast that
Ye Muxi is waiting for him.
Then we steal the key.
Let them go in and close the door!
As long as they can stay alone together,
they'll make it up.
Succeed!
Sorry.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
I also did wrong.
Then, don't transfer to Class One.
We're still friends.
Okay, I won't go.
Let's go, let's go.
Time to eat.
Barbecue! Barbecue!
I can't see a flaw.
Then let's do this!
Where're Huang Nan and Huang Yi?
Where's Shanqi?
Xiaodong,
do you need some mosquito-repellent?
It's okay, I'm fine.
Shanqi, why're you laughing.
When it occurs to me that Ye Muxi and Liao Danyi
will be back together because of us,
I feel so happy.
Hope nothing will go wrong.
It won't.
Everything is under our control.
The lovers finally are back together.
We played a critical role.
Later, we'll light this firework into the sky.
So romantic!
Li.
Do you remember Hua from bumper cars factory?
Yes.
Every morning at a quarter past eight,
she will pass by my door on time.
In a pink bath towel.
Don't wander too far.
Back to our topic,
See, in so many philosophies.
Why Hitler chose Nietzsche?
Such an aggressive kind?
If he didn't choose him,
Would the history change to a totally different direction?
In that world,
Will Hua still be covered by a bath towel?
The starry sky is so beautiful.
Yes.
Under that starry sky,
Our sky wheel looks even prettier.
Right.
So pretty.
Li, isn't today should be the day off?
The sky wheel should be dark.
Oh, screwed!
Let's go. Let's go.
But why are they still not here?
No worries.
- So many mosquitos here.
- No worries, no worries.
It's okay.
It's so late.
What're you doing here?
None of your business.
Security.
Stop!
Stop running!
What's wrong?
What is that sound?
What's going on?
Li. Li.
Seems our firework has exploded.
No.
Huang Nan, Huang Yi.
Someone is after them!
Run!
Hurry, run!
Stop running! Stop!
Stop!
Stop running!
Snacks.
Who is that?
Who opened the equipment?
Where's that?
Who stole our key?
You.
You, don't run!
Don't run!
Stop her, stop her!
Over there!
-Ye Muxi!
-We finally catch you.
Ye Muxi, are you okay?
What're you doing here?
Who is he?
I'm security.
Who are you?
Li.
Are you okay?
It's not right.
Shouldn't he faint after I hit him?
You two, come with me to the security room!
Tell me
How did you get the key?
Sorry, sir.
I know this doesn't seem true.
But I really don't know it's the day off.
In fact, I think I have figured out the whole thing.
I think should be some students from
our Class ten planned this for some reason.
Our Class Ten?
You're no longer from Class Ten.
What the heck are you talking about?
It's so obvious, okay?
You're just a couple who sneaked in to date, right?
A pretty girl and a handsome boy.
Must be a couple.
This couple feeling.
Makes us so jealous.
Thought provoking!
Look at you young generation.
Knows nothing about rules!
Have seen too many movies?
Too many idol dramas?
It's late in the night?
Romantic?
You're disturbing someone, you know?
You've affected people's life, you know?
I was gonna watch my Baskets tonight.
I was gonna watch Horace And Pete.
And you...you opened the equipment?!
Do you know how much electric you've wasted?
If boss finds out,
he'll deduct our wages, you know?!
Our wages are so poor already, you know?!
It'll be harder for us to find a girlfriend, you know?!
Watching you two showing off your love
makes us more angrier, you know?!
What's that called?
Single dog abuse.
Right!
Not right!
You're a dog.
No, Li.
That's harsh.
It's what exactly you were thinking !
What...what I mean to say is...
Flashbomb. Right, flashbomb!
What flashbomb?
The word you're thinking was single dog abuse.
No. I swear I was gonna say flashbomb!
You swear? What's that gonna do?
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
Say it, out.
Never mind.
Say it.
I hate people when they save a half.
I know what you wanna say.
Must be about the poker game that night!
You must have cheated!
I didn't. I didn't. I didn't!
I've told you a hundred times!
My card was folded.
What a coincidence.
You folded two, three and five
To against my leopard?
And you won me twelve in one round!
I'm say it on my parents' name.
You still won't believe me?!
I gave you twelve.
You insisted!
Listen ,if I knew you don't believe me.
I wouldn't take that money.
Enough, enough. Stop it.
Aren't you ashamed?
I mean it.
If you don't believe me, I'll return it now.
I said I believe you.
This is over, over.
Now.
Listen to me.
Money doesn't matters.
But reputation does!
Heine said it, life can't blossom in lies.
Tagore also said it,
The hypocritical sincerity is more hideous than devils.
Fine.
There's no point in this.
Just twelve Rmb.
I'll return it now!
One.
Two.
Students, do you have ten yuan?
Us?
Yes, yes. Lend it to me.
I have.
Lend it to me.
I'll return it via Wechat.
Well..
I'll scan yours.
Scan, scan.
Okay.
Receive.
Click Receive.
Thanks.
Where did Ye Muxi and Lian Danyi go?
Who knows, our priority should be hiding from those two guards.
They two are quite scary.
When can we leave this place?
So worried.
So, we can leave...
Sit back.
Do you have any idea what kind of trouble you're in today?
Although I don't know which law you're against.
But there must be one!!
Although you both are good-looking,
maybe we'll let you go without calling the police.
Don't think before your political lesson by us,
we would let you leave.
No, I mean.
It's their first time.
Just let them go.
Why're you looking at me like this?
You're doing this again.
What do you mean by that?
You're always like this.
You have to go against me every time.
Do you know how much he likes to be a teacher?
Last time, we went to eat the Northeast cuisine.
I only said one word.
It's tasty.
Next time when we go to Northeast.
We must try some authentic Northeast cuisine.
Then this man,
he had given a long speech of There's no such thing in Northeast
during that meal!
This course is invented by the outsiders to mock the Northeast people.
It's just a meal!
It's a knowledge point okay?
So you can learn something over a meal.
I don't want that.
I just want to have my dinner peacefully!
Look, you're over thirty.
Why you just don't want to learn anything like a kid?
Who is like a kid?
Look, you don't know him.
He and I are roommates.
He can't even take care of himself.
Threw his underwear everywhere.
Never put the trash in the trashcan.
You can't imagine
how painful it is to live with this man.
I can.
How could you say that?
You think what you do is clean and tidy?
It's called crazy!
Always scrubbing your security badge.
His clothes are either in washing or drying in the sun.
That never ends.
The worst is,
the most disgusting thing is,
he even cut his vibrissa on time.
His vibrissa!
A weirdo, right?
That's weird.
But if you don't cut it,
would you let it show out in the air?
Exactly.
We've been working together for two years.
We almost spend every day together.
This man,
one day, I asked him for a hundred yuan.
I lend it from him.
He told me,
I must return it in one week.
Otherwise, I must pay him two hundred.
I didn't think twice and said okay.
I lent in on Wednesday,
And I paid him back the next Wednesday.
He still asked me to pay him two hundred.
Did you miss something?
Did you pay it back on Wednesday?
It was a quarter past zero o'clock on Thursday.
A quarter.
Fifteen minutes!
What's the big deal!
That's away too far.
If you knew that,
Why you didn't it earlier?
That has no human feelings.
It's not about human feelings.
It's a principle.
What's not a friend should do!
What do you mean by that?
Fine. What about Li?
What about her?
Listen to me,
Li is a girl who is quite close to us.
She operates the merry-go-around in our park.
We are quite close.
One day, we went to sing in a KTV bar.
He was busy, so he didn't come.
So me and Li were playing truth or Dare.
There's one topic ,I got dare.
So I kinda kissed Li.
I promised Li that I will never tell anyone.
But I can't bear it. so I told him.
So I told him, do not tell Li about it.
Don't let her know that he knew I kissed her.
And he promised he wouldn't tell Li.
Then what?
Li came to play with us the next day.
The first thing he said is
I heard you two kissed yesterday.
How could you do this?
That just came out.
I didn't mean to.
Just came out?
Do you know that hurts Zhang and Li?
Do you know that you let Zhang down?
He said it just came out.
Why do you have to criticize him?
That's enough.
The power of word could raise a dead from the grave.
Could bury a person alive.
Could turn a dwarf into a dinosaur.
Could break a dinosaur.
Look, look.
More lessons.
You're always like this.
Why all the trifles are big troubles in your mouth?!
Because nothing of you is just a trifle to me!
What?
Zhang.
Listen, I can't stand you anymore.
Tell me, are you gonna never let go that thing about Li forever?
Yes, so what?
We're over.
We're over. What's the big deal?!
Okay.
Two years' relationship.
You just gonna throw it away?
It's not that easy.
You said it's over.
What do you want?
A big fight at least!
How dare you?
-You think I don't dare to touch you?
-Come on.
Come and touch me.
Here, take this.
No, no, don't.
Too soft!
You should do it like this.
Like this!
No, no, don't.
Don't.
Don't, don't. Enough. Stop.
Enough, enough.
Don't fight.
Bro, bro.
Bro, don't.
Does it hurt?
I'm okay.
Why are you so silly?
Hit yourself.
You girls know nothing.
I know it.
You didn't want to hurt Zhang.
But you didn't want your friendship to end like this.
So you put up some drama to imply him.
Right?
In fact, Zhang cares about you.
He doesn't.
If he doesn't care about you, he wouldn't say so much.
The truth is, every thing he said about you is true.
But you're proud.
You don't want to admit.
You wanna change.
But you don't him to know you care about those things he said.
So...
In a sword,
You're too proud.
You should go apologize.
Why should I?
You know it.
You're too strict with him.
Although I saw you didn't really to hurt him.
But how could you do that to your good friend?
What you did was wrong.
I don't understand it.
What I did...
He always talks without thinking first,
he has upset so many people.
There're not a lot people in the park would talk to him.
What I did
is for his good.
I know.
But have you put yourself in his shoes?
You two came here at the same time.
You're better than him in every aspect.
Won't that hurt his pride?
You keep saying that he wouldn't change.
What about you?
Have you thought about how to change him in a better way?
Besides,
What do you expect of him?
To change him into you?
Who told you your life is better than his?
Is he the only person who doesn't want to change?
But he is so annoying.
Then why are you willing to spent so much time with him?
In fact, you also admire him.
You also want to be like him.
Excellent and perfect.
In fact, you also thought about
to live a real life like him everyday.
Just being honest.
Would that be happier.
He is the only one in the world who understands you the most.
So if he disappeared like this,
wouldn't that be a pity?
In fact you know it.
What you felt about him is more like curious and admire.
Because he is always doing something against your experience.
But still so happy.
You didn't know when did he become
your only connection with this world.
You know it.
He is not that bad like you said.
You complain so much, just want to draw him closer.
So you can reach him easily.
In fact you should see it earlier.
You wanted to change him so much.
But in the end, you're the one who is changed.
You can't erase him.
Because he has become the most important part in your life.
So go and apologize.
To your best friend.
So go make it up.
With your enemy.
Well...
Li is such an easy l girl.
She has been seeing our manager a long time ago.
And she is flirting with our colleagues.
I don't want to see you get hurt.
So I did it on purpose.
Why you didn't tell me earlier?
I think things like this don't need explanation.
No, I mean, are you a fool?
I'm a fool.
I'm the biggest fool.
Zhang!
Li!
Well...
Can we leave now?
Where... Where are you going?
Let's have kebabs together!
No. No. Don't you see?
We've detained this young couple for a long time.
They still have to...
No. That...
We're really not a couple.
Understand. We understand.
Why do you wink at me?
Right, Li.
It occurs to me that your book called Love in the Time of Cholera,
is still in my place.
I gotta go get it to you.
It seems that tomorrow, our company's stage-play team
is gonna rehearse Uncle Vanya!
-Yes. We haven't recite our lines yet!
-Yes.
Let's go. Hurry. Hurry.
Let's go.
We...
Don't say anything.
Don't need to say anything.
No matter why you came here.
And leave here.
We'll forever give you our best wishes.
Remember to come visit us often.
Bye-bye.
Ye Muxi.
Do you remember we played hide-and-seek when we were kids?
That time, I went to the Olympian math class.
I left you alone out there.
I ignored you.
That made me very guilty.
So since then, I thought I should be responsible for your growth.
That's why I missed one exam and came to Class Ten.
Because I was concerned about you.
In fact, I didn't send Xiaotian to the Animal Control.
I adopted him by myself.
Later, I was afraid that I can't take good care of him.
So I entrusted Mr Wu to take care of him.
Now he's living a good life.
I check upon him every week.
In fact, I also didn't blame you for what happened to grandma.
Because you accompanied her to spend her last days wonderfully.
In fact, I didn't want to transfer to Class One.
But my father threatened me.
If I didn't, he would come to our school and make trouble for you.
So I did.
All right, I'm done.
Don't feel guilty.
Aren't you silly?
You're always like this.
Everything you do, you think it's for my good.
And then be proud of yourself.
Am I Superman?
Do I know what you're thinking about?
If you don't tell me, how could I know?
Can I read mind?
Superman can't read mind. He can only fly.
Nonsense.
His... His eyes can emit laser!
The point is not about that laser.
Forget it. I don't want to argue with you.
Do I want to argue with you?
What kind of good student are you?
You're totally an idiot!
You think you can shoulder everything by yourself?
Are you... Are you looking down upon me?
I...
Liao Danyi.
Listen to me.
From now on, don't hide anything from me.
No matter it's good or bad, you're gonna tell me!
And we'll shoulder it together!
Because...
Because I'm your boss.
Hear me?
Got it.
My boss.
Wait a minute!
Don't be like this. Don't.
Lucky that we came in time.
Otherwise you're gonna fight again!
Yes. Yes.
Sorry.
This is my idea.
It was gonna help you patch things up.
Didn't expect...
It's okay. We patched things up.
Really?
That's great!
Liao Danyi doesn't need to go to Class One, then.
Still need to.
All the formalities are handled.
Can't be kidding before such things.
How could this happen?
Didn't you patch things up?
Yes.
The storyline should be, after you patch things up,
you volunteer to go back to Class Ten.
And we give high fives!
And we've already chosen our BGM.
It goes like this.
All right.
What on earth are you talking about?
Life is not a written idol opera.
How could we just do whatever we like?
But it's fun just because of that.
Right, Shanqi?
Let's play sky wheel?
Better not.
Those two guards...
They're on our side now.
We could play whatever we like.
It seems that you really want Li and Zhang lose their job?
Target, sky wheel.
Go!
I'll stay with Xiaodong! Let's go!
Shen Wei.
In fact, I've fallen for you long ago.
Sorry.
You're not my type.
Look, she refuses you!
Only takes half a second this time.
What about me? Me?
This is okay.
Miss Xinyi.
You're upset?
No.
But you always cross your fingers when you're upset.
And lean against the back of the chair.
Won't sit very tight.
I'm upset or not, doesn't it have anything to do with you?
Aren't you annoying?
Yes, I might be upset.
But do you have any way to solve my trouble?
You don't.
Can you leave me alone for a while?
When you feel upset, eat snacks.
This is your favorite snack since you were a kid.
Eat some and you'll feel better.
If you don't want to eat the snack, it's okay.
Last time, you said that you like little animals.
Paper cranes.
So I learned how to make paper cranes.
Now I can fold one very quickly.
Six seconds for each.
If giving ten minutes, one hundred paper cranes.
If you need, I can fold one at any time.
If you don't want to see me,
I can put it in the drawer.
If you want one, just pick it up.
And...
Last time, I broke your mug by mistake.
I've fixed it.
Look.
Although it looks uneven, it becomes very burly.
And I've disinfected it.
It can be used. Don't worry.
I know, it means a lot to you.
If you can't use it,
I'll order another one online.
Delivered in two days. Very fast.
No need.
This one will do.
Tell me.
What's so good about me?
Why do you have to follow me all the time?
Why?
You're the blooming flowers over the trees.
You're a swallow twittering between the beams.
You're love.
You're warmth.
You're hope.
You are the spring of this world.
As long as you're happy, I'll be happy.
Don't you know you're really childish?
Pasted the mug with stick band.
How could I drink water from it, then?
And these snacks.
We're not allowed to eat snacks in school!
Don't you know?
Be happy, Miss Xinyi.
As long as you're happy, I'll be happy.
Wipe your tears.
What tears?
Did you see me crying?
Or shedding tears?
You're lightning. You're light.
You're the only legend.
I only love you.
You're my superstar.
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Are you happy?
Yes.
What about you?
In fact, I don't like the colorful running.
Pigments go into eyes.
And clothes become hard to wash.
Like many things.
It looks more wonderful than you experience it.
Well, are you happy?
Yes.
Liao.
Didn't you go to Class One?
Why come back?
I missed one course during the class transferring exam.