Brother, you know what?
To be honest, I always have this idea
about the final episode of One Piece.
I think...
Gol·D·Roger's son isn't Ace.
But Luffy is.
Ace is more like Monkey·D·Dragon's son.
But the navy wants to kill Roger's son.
So Luffy is the one they're after, not Ace.
I think Ace must have died for Luffy.
Eiichiro Oda must have the same idea with me.
Among all the animes.
Small Carp Adventures is my favorite.
Think about it.
Small carp, it's so inspirational.
Look, after so many difficulties,
He finally learned magic.
He saved the whole Carp Village.
That's great! So inspirational.
In fact, I also want a little white dog like Crayon Shin-chan's.
No passion.
Our mom would never let us raise pet.
And I also want a Doraemon.
So we can sleep half an hour later than we usually do.
We open the door, it'll be our school!
And we won't need to do our homework.
But no,
there's no such a thing in the world.
# In the lonely sky, and lonely rain comes down #
I know how to sing it.
-I wanna know the name.
I don't know, either.
You know I can never remember the name.
Have you done your homework?
I'm just about to ask you.
I only wrote down my name.
I haven't written a word.
What shall we do?
When will the class begin?
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 30
Last night, the werewolves killed Zhu Shanqi.
She has no words left.
I'll remind you again.
Hope all of you can follow the rules.
Please confirm your identity cards.
Don't let other players see your cards.
Now it's getting dark, please close your eyes.
Werewolves, open your eyes.
Werewolves, meet your companions.
Werewolves, kill a player.
Now, go back.
Day breaks.
Last night, the one got killed by the werewolves is...
Ye Muxi.
Yezi.
Yezi, are you okay?
I just got an identity.
What is my identity?
You're a hunter.
What is that?
Now you can shoot one person.
It's you!
-Trust me, it's not me.
-Not me!
It's you!
It's not me, boss.
It's you?
No, No, not me, boss!
You!
Boss, I'm innocent!
You?
Shoot me, so I can die with you.
I'm the judge!
You? You?
Boss, boss.
It's not me! Not me!
Boss, it's not me!
You!
Yezi.
Yezi, Yezi. Why you're so silly?
Boss.
Yezi, Yezi, Yezi!
I still can't pull the trigger at any of you.
Yezi!
Do you wanna continue or not?
Okay, okay. It's time for a speech.
Time for a speech.
Speech.
Shen Wei, you begin.
Hurry.
I don't know. I wanna observe a while.
I don't know!
Day breaks.
Game over.
Werewolves win!
What?
Zhu Shanqi
Why vote on me? He is the wolf!
why vote on me?!
He told you, he is a werewolf!
Zhu Shanqi,
Can you listen to me?
With no personal emotions in, okay?
I'm a prophet.
I checked last night that Xue Xiaodong is a werewolf!
Why didn't you listen?
I don't wanna listen, no, no!
He is a prophet?
What does that mean?! What does that mean?!
You, you, don't do a thing.
You, you, you too!
You're my friend. But you didn't save me?!
Listen, you owe me an explanation.
How could I save you?
I can't speak!
It's okay, it's just a game.
-Just a game.
-You guys are a bunch of...
Calm down, calm down.
It's dark. Close your eyes.
So how should we play this game?
I'm so nervous even with my eyes closed.
I'm so afraid of getting killed.
Don't kill me, don't kill me.
Finally, I'm the werewolf.
Don't waste this chance,
who shall I kill?
That feeling to dominate other people's life
Feels great.
Not the werewolf, I don't know how to do that.
Great, I'm a civilian.
Hope Xue Xiaodong is also on my side.
Witch, that's really my thing.
At least I can save myself.
In the cruel world,
you have to be selfish if you wanna survive.
Sorry, guys.
I won't use the saving card that easily.
Last night, Xue Xiaodong is out.
Now it's Huang Yi's turn.
It's so difficult.
Now I'm so confused.
I don't know how to play this.
I don't know who are the werewolves.
I'll listen to the others.
Anyway, I'm one of the good guys.
What're you looking at?! I'm not the werewolf.
But if any of you vote me out
or kill me.
Then I'll ....
Don't be mad.
I don't know who are the werewolves.
Anyway, I'll listen to you guys.
So cute!
Huang Nan, you wanna say something?
Last night, I've talked with Huang Yi.
It's very clear now.
As for the werewolf.
We have known it.
Then who that is?
The werewolf is... What's it to you?
Why should I tell you?
You think I'm stupid?
If I tell you.
then what is left to play with?
Wanna trick me?
Pass!
Okay, okay, guys.
After these speeches.
and non-nutritive deductions.
I think each of you has realized the identity of the others.
I'll not keep it implicit anymore.
This time, I'm not afraid of being killed by the werewolves.
Because I'm the hunter.
So far,
no one has suspected my identity.
So it's confirmed I'm the hunter.
I hope you won't vote me out.
So I can lead you to catch the werewolves.
If I die in this round.
Then I'll take a werewolf down with me.
Let's begin with the first night.
The first night, Zhu Shanqi got killed.
The first I suspect was Ye Mui
Why? Zhu Shanqi and Ye Muxi are besties.
And newbies.
Only the newbies would kill each other.
So Zhu Shanqi is possibly killed by Ye Muxi.
That's right, what my brother told me yesterday.
But after last round,
Ye Muxi was voted out by all of you.
But game was not over.
Then I realized
I made a huge mistake.
Ye Muxi's speech has exposed she is a prophet,
A girl like Ye Muxi whose brain doesn't work so well.
She is dead as a prophet.
That won't affect anything.
So the question remains.
No one died in the second night.
So the werewolves must have killed.
And the werewolf must have used the cure.
Am I right? Shen Wei.
Why are you asking me?
I don't know anything.
Stop faking.
We all know it.
She? How could she be the werewolf?
Right, why did you say that?
Do you have any proof?
Don't interrupt me.
I didn't say she is a werewolf.
She is the witch.
Didn't you see?
Shen Wei always uses fortune-telling to use the witch card.
Maybe she likes the witch.
Thinks it suits her.
She saves herself every time.
Didn't save any of you for once.
Did you see it?
It's so obvious.
You also found that?
So cute!
After Yezi got executed.
Xue Xiaodong got killed by the werewolves.
Now it's very clear.
Yezi, Zhu Shanqi, Xue Xiaodong.
They're all the good guys.
Shen Wei is the witch. I'm the hunter.
Who are the guys left?
Huang Nan, Huang Yi and Li Yao.
Li Yao has been proved.
She must be the good guy,
Now let's cut the crap.
Back to the point.
Huang Yi, you're always playing dumb.
You think I don't know?
Huang Nan, your words don't make sense.
You have been misleading us,
to make a mess.
So I suggest we should vote Huang Yi out first.
Then Huang Nan.
Game over.
Anyone wants to vote Li Yao?
Shen Wei?
Huang Yi?
Huang Nan?
Anyone wants to vote Xiong Tiancheng out?
You....
This game is so difficult!
You talk too much.
Who are you? To steal my thunder?
You're ended miserably.
You deserve it.
We'll kill you first.
Why me?
The talker seems more suspicious.
Right, right.
This game is too difficult.
What? what?
I don't know.
A wolf's head.
I... I'm a werewolf?
Why you didn't tell me?
Why you don't believe me?!
You, don't do a thing.
You, you, you too.
You're my best friend. You didn't save me?
Listen, you owe me an explanation!
How could I save you?!
My death is so unfair.
I'm just a civilian.
Now I'll summarize.
You girls. Can't you take a good look?!
I'm so cute.
I can't be the werewolf!
Werewolves, please open your eyes.
Werewolves, meet your companions.
Werewolves, kill a player.
Couples, open your eyes. Discuss.
Couples , do you know what you are supposed to do?
Are you excited because you can open your eyes
while the others can't?
Okay, you can close your eyes now.
Close your eyes.
Why me? Why me?
Shanqi, Xiaodong. You trust me, right?
Trust me.
Yezi, I'm so sorry.
We don't know who are the werewolves.
Sorry about this.
Not me. Not me.
We'll just light one person up.
Light it up, maybe there'll be some surprise.
No, I'm not the werewolf!
come on, let's do this.
No, No!
No!
What's so hurry?
I saw you thinking.
I didn't want to disturb you, so I was going out.
Scared?
Who is scared?
I think you're not only scared.
And you're sweating now.
Sweat? Where?
You can't talk fluently.
You are.
Stop it.
I know you're a werewolf.
We're brothers.
You think I didn't know you?
When you're scared.
You can't talk fluently.
How about this?
We'll vote you out tomorrow.
So you can be free.
I'm a werewolf?
That's a venomous slander!
You were the one sneering towards my statue.
You wanna kill me?
What brothers?
You despicable man!
Sneer? What're you talking about?
Stop faking!
You were the one sneering towards my statue.
I saw my noodles almost ready.
So I was so happy.
So I smiled.
Well, do you still got some left?
I want that too.
Brother, I'm sorry.
We're brothers.
But I suspected you.
We're brothers, don't need to apologize.
As long as you know it now.
Right, we're brothers.
Brothers united will beat anything.
We must unite.
We're a team.
Right, you're right.
Those fools need us to lead them to victory.
Good pal.
Nice buddy.
Brother, you're smarter than me.
Enlighten me.
Good, you know I'm smarter.
Now, I'll analyze it for you.
First, from Zhu Shanqi's death.
We know it's not Xue Xiaodong.
Why is that?
Think about that.
Zhu Shanqi and Xue Xiaodong.
An idol and his fan,.
Think,
which idol would kill his idol?
Make sense.
Next, we can eliminate Yuan Ke'er.
To be honest,
She seems very cold outside.
But according to my observation.
She is very warm-hearted.
And she is so cute.
That makes sense, too.
Shen Wei doesn't look like the werewolf, either.
Think about it.
She is too cute to be the werewolf.
She is so cute!
I really want to pinch her face.
And Li Yao.
She can't be the werewolf.
Why is that?
I don't want to get beaten by her.
Who is left?
Our big boss.
Yezi.
Impossible.
Think, she is a fool.
If she is the wolf.
She will kill herself.
Right.
So, she can be eliminated.
As for Xiong Tiancheng.
According to my observation
He is more like a prophet than a werewolf.
He has got this strict logic.
I almost bought it.
Brother, so
Most of them are eliminated.
Who is still left?
Come on, let's start from the beginning.
The beginning.
Not Yuan Ke'er.
Not Shen Wei.
Not Li Yao.
Not Xiong Tiancheng.
Not Xue Xiaodong.
Not Xue Xiaodong
Who is left?!
Brother, I trust you.
-Brother, I trust you too.
-Hug, hug, hug.
Let's do it again.
Well, well.
Not Yuan Ke'er.
Not Xiong Tiancheng.
Not Ye Muxi.
Not Xue Xiaodong.
Not Xue Xiaodong
Not Shen Wei.
Not Li Yao.
- Who is left?!
- Who is ...
Brother.
It's okay, it's okay.
Let's do it again.
Slowly, slowly.
I really don't know.
Who are they?
Anyway. Brother, I trust you.
I trust you.
Let's vote together.
I think it's a great idea!
I won't vote you out.
Me either.
After tonight.
We can kill anyone we want.
We can free anyone we want!
Vote them out!
Vote them!
tomorrow, we'll win!
We'll never lose!
We win!
Victory is ours!
We're the strongest!
Strongest!
Two men died last night.
Which are Huang Nan, Huang Yi.
One is killed by a werewolf.
One is killed by the hunter.
They didn't leave any notes.
Now you take turns to speak.
Werewolves, please execute.
Werewolves, go back.
Prophet, open your eyes.
Prophet, please identify.
This means good guys.
This means werewolves.
Now the witch, open your eyes.
The person who died last night is "him".
Prophet, close your eyes.
Witch, open your eyes.
Last night, the one who died is "Him".
Do you want to use the cure?
Do you want to use the poison?
Who are you gonna intoxicate?
Save or not?
Poison or not?
Witch, please go back.
Day breaks.
Yesterday nobody died.
Players, discuss begins.
Well, I don't know.
You, Shanqi.
First, I think Xiaodong can't be the werewolf.
Why is that?
Xiaodong has such long legs.
Werewolf can't have such long legs like that.
So he can't be the werewolf.
Yezi and Shen Wei.
I don't think it's them.
Because we're all so kind.
Superstar·Xiaodong, who do you think is the most likely werewolf?
I don't know if you have noticed that...
the looks on Nan and Yi's face at the first day breaks.
I didn't.
They had eye contact.
Like this, see?
Then I'll keep an eye on them in next round.
But in my heart.
You're the most unlikely werewolf.
Your eyes are so kind and sincere.
Every word from you made me so touched.
Lazio·July trusts me with all her heart.
I'm away too far.
Xiaodong, what's wrong?
Miss Lazio·July,
I have something to tell you.
I also have something to tell you.
I can't stand it.
In fact...
I...
Good luck, good luck.
Who shall we kill the next?
I think... Yezi.
So the most likely werewolves,
must be that two.
You two.
Don't go, don't hide.
Right, you.
You.
Yes, you.
But, this game is so terrible.
Why you're all werewolves?
You are one.
Pass.
According to my analysis.
You three are the most likely werewolves.
Who killed me?
I'm a good person.
Because it's my first time to play this.
I don't know how you play it.
I think Ye Muxi is right.
I think we should listen to her.
Today, we're gonna burn
Zhu Shanqi.
Come on, tie her up!
- No!
No, no, not me. Help!
Wait!
I'm done with this.
I'm done burning one of my dear friends every night.
Don't you have any feelings?
Not even a little sympathy?
Every day, guess who is the werewolf.
Who are the others.
Have you thought for the werewolves?
This game is so cruel.
Have you? Have you?
Don't you think the werewolves have their reasons?
They don't want to be werewolves, either.
He didn't want to kill anyone.
He has feelings, too.
As from today, I decide,
I will find out the werewolves.
I'll help them.
You know that?
I'm the witch this time.
Listen, I'll find the cure.
I will save the werewolves.
No more killing my friends.
No more killing werewolves.
Who?
Who is with me?
Me!
I'm with you.
I'm done with it.
I admit it.
I'm the werewolf.
I'm the killer.
I don't want to kill anyone anymore.
Every full moon night, I can't control the desire of killing people.
Aren't we friends?
I hope you can save me.
I don't want to hurt anyone anymore.
I'm also a werewolf.
I support Yezi.
Werewolves should have the right to choose.
I... I don't want to kill anyone anymore.
Do you know how painful it is to kill a person?!
I don't wanna kill anyone.
Yezi, I don't wanna kill anyone anymore.
Okay, we'll save you.
Who are we?
We're friends.
We're family.
Right, Yezi, I'm on your side.
We can try to make a cure for the werewolves.
We... We can help.
Maybe there is a way.
Right, family.
Family.
Seems, this game isn't for Class Ten.