Xinyi, be careful.
Senior, this Flirting Swordplay is so exhausting.
Can we quit?
Every move needs to flirt with the eyes.
That's truly tiring.
How about we practice Everlasting Love Swordplay?
Everlasting Love Swordplay?
I'm afraid you won't be able to hold it.
Don't you remember that night in the mountain
when we were practicing Hot love Fist.
If I didn't try my best to resist.
I'm afraid we would made some huge mistakes.
Come on,
I was the one resisting you.
Don't talk nonsense.
Tell me, do you really love me with your all heart?
Of course.
Since I came here when I was seven.
I have never seen another girl.
Why wouldn't I love you?
What if you see other women.
Will you stop loving me?
I'm not a dandy.
Of course I'll love you.
Excuse me, may I ask where is the Maple Leaf Middle School?
Hey, why are you ogling him?
Listen, we've been engaged, he is my man!
I didn't ogle him.
He is ogling me.
Who wants to look at him?
I don't care if it's you ogling him or he ogling you.
You're not allowed to look at him.
Look at me if you want.
I've been watching you for decades.
This doesn't matter.
Miss, May I ask why do you want to go to Maple Leaf Middle School?
Don't answer.
Don't ask.
I want to answer.
I need to see director Yan.
Do you know where he is?
Don't answer!
Thanks.
Please.
What?
She said please, so I said back.
Why did she say that? Does she love you?
I don't know why she did that.
Then do you love her?
I don't love her, sis.
I don't believe you!
Where're you going?
To disfigure her.
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
SUBTITLES BY Babel Fansub
Alina, Katherine
The Big Boss
Episode 28
Liao Danyi.
Sorry, I'm reviewing.
I'm here not because of some personal things.
It's for official business.
I heard some students say that
students of Class Ten didn't dress properly according to the rules.
I hope as a member of class committee
you can correct them.
Sorry, I didn't know about this.
Xiaodong, one of my friends is your big fan.
She wants to see your concert.
Can you get her a ticket?
No problem, I'll settle that.
Thanks.
Ke'er is dressing the uniform style.
Xiaodong is wearing the shirt of the uniform.
I don't think it's inappropriate.
Let's go. Let's go.
You're away too far.
I see.
It's just I'm the commissary in charge of studies.
You should talk to our monitor.
Your dress is so beautiful!
-You really think so?
-I like this line.
And the heart shape is so cute.
Right, so cute.
Yeah, I agree.
You look like the super model.
I see the severity here.
I will deal with it.
As the commissary in charge of studies,
I shouldn't host this committee meeting.
So, don't.
But there's some problems have to be mentioned.
Don't, then.
And it's very obvious.
I don't see it.
It's our uniform.
Any problem?
Our school uniform is for us to wear it in school.
But some students are wandering in school in some strange clothes.
What will other students think about it?
This is the school uniform.
We only changed it a little.
See? School badge.
You call this "changed it a little"?
It's totally different apparel, okay?
Only Xiaodong kept his school uniform shirt.
Ke'er is still wearing the school uniform.
As for the others, Huang Nan, Huang Yi, Zhu Shanqi,
what you're wearing has nothing to do with our uniform.
What're you talking about? Okay.
No more words.
We have our reasons.
What is that?
The school uniform is too ugly.
No, I think it's good.
I... I think it's pretty.
It's the most beautiful clothes I've ever had.
See?
Why they can wear it, but you can't?
Let me tell you why.
Because you're so low, we're high fashion.
We have youth, we have fashion.
What do you have?
Rustic. You rustic.
We're so fashion.
Youth, shining.
Fashion.
We're so high fashion, right?
Put it on!
Easy, easy, easy.
You're always like this.
You hooligan! Hooligan!
Big boss.
Now it's our Class committee meeting.
I won't argue with you.
Since we have different opinions.
Let's solve this in a fair and democratic way.
Let's vote.
Vote?
So boring. Gosh.
Listen, if we have dissenting opinions.
Solve it by fist.
I don't know how to answer you.
Since people who want to wear the uniform and who don't are the same.
There's no point in voting.
How about this.
Let's play a game.
The losers will obey.
That's right.
What game?
I have an idea.
Xue Xiaodong suggested we solve it by competition.
And he also suggested a nice competition mode.
Live CS.
That's right.
Everything was leaded by that suggestion.
That incident
was called Class Ten Civil War Incident later.
As a person who experienced it.
I'll do my best to reproduce that horrifying day.
Today, this Uniform War's purpose
is to determine how we'll wear our school uniform in future.
It's also a thing which indicates the justice and democracy of our class.
So I hope you can deal with it rationally.
At last,
Be safe.
Yes!
Annihilate them at all costs!
Have you had it enough?
Yes!
We have our right to choose what kind of clothes and shoes we wear.
To choose our hair style and makeup.
Fire it up!
Liao Danyi you bastard!
You'll be killed today, fire it up!
Go! Go! Go!
Wipe them out! Skin them alive!
Wipe out their heart and drink their blood!
Come on!
Ke'er, that's too bloody. Under eighteen restricted.
At that time,
neither of them had realized
it's a seesaw battle way beyond their estimate.
Don't know it's a coincidence or god's plan.
Two teams were neck and neck.
Once the first bullet was fired.
They were both on a close-quarter bloody battle which was too late to mend.
Now, as the writer of this biography.
Allow me to introduce the strong fighters of both team.
First of all, myself.
Who vowed to protect the school uniform.
Xiong Tiancheng.
Back then, I would never join this kind of thing.
Because I was a loner.
I couldn't even take care of myself.
The only thing I'm proud of is my article.
Which was wrongly used when I initially joined our class.
Until I met a teacher who appreciates my talent,
and our monitor who seems quite careless.
Then I started to change.
With the help of the monitor and our classmates
I changed my imagine.
And started to try to blend in.
Just because now I see myself as a member of class Ten,
I decided to devote myself in this vital moment.
Just shoot me.
I have sunstroke and sprained my ankle anyway.
I wanna go home.
Should we help Zhu Shanqi?
Is that a trap?
She seems so sincere, shouldn't be lying.
Let's go.
Come, come, celebrate!
Come on, give me five!
Xiaodong.
I want to invite you to eat ice cream after school.
Mew Mew. Xiaodong.
Would you like to eat ice cream after school?
A kiss for you.
Mew Mew. Xiaodong.
Would you like to eat ice cream after school?
A kiss for you.
No, no, no.
Xue Xiaodong.
Wanna eat ice cream after school?
Yo, Yo.
Xue Xiaodong, wanna eat ice cream tonight?
What're you doing?
I want to invite Xiaodong to eat ice cream tonight.
So hemming.
Xiaodong.
Zhu Shanqi wants to invite you to eat ice cream today.
Are you free? Will be waiting.
Is that a little mean?
-Maybe a little.
-Let me hear it.
Xiaodong.
Zhu Shanqi wants to invite you to eat ice cream today.
Are you free? Will be waiting.
I'll send him another.
Xiaodong, this is Ye Muxi.
Zhu Shanqi wants to invite you to eat ice cream today.
Are you free?
Xiaodong, this is Ye Muxi.
Zhu Shanqi wants to invite you to eat ice cream today.
Are you free?
[Ye Muxi] [Zhu Shanqi]
Luckily, we've many talented fighters.
Apart from me and our team leader,
There's also a heroine who is as good as any male great fighters.
Li Yao, kept the situation under control.
Li Yao, I'm gonna play basketball.
I'd like to.
You? You also like basketball?
Right, I like restive sport
That's so you.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
- Let me help.
[Li Yao]
Can't drop physical training in vacation as well.
Aerobic exercise is necessary.
As the both sides were fighting vigorously
Forces from beyond Class Ten have been drawn.
Monitor of Class One and their vice monitor He Lvxi
sneaked in the battlefield to help Liao Danyi shoot the enemy.
As for their motive... .
Miss Xinyi.
We're not from Class Ten.
Why came here?
To make sure they all will wear school uniform properly.
So we must fight this game.
Right, this thing has nothing to do with Liao Danyi.
Don't get me wrong.
Although she denies it
But I know that the monitor of Class One
carries a touch for Liao Danyi.
As a writer.
Must have the insight which others don't have.
You didn't see Liao Danyi today either, right?
Me too!
But you must be impatient.
You should think it this way.
You gave him a chance to date you.
He didn't come.
So that kind of man,
doesn't deserve your love.
So must quit him. Quit him.
Anything I can help with?
This is my favorite novel.
I want to lend it to you.
Why?
Don't ask why.
I'm looking forward to hear your feedback.
You really don't wanna know what I'm gonna say to you?
You already knew?
Are you pretending or you really don't know?
Sorry, I've to go.
As from now,
Don't think of Liao Danyi.
No Liao Danyi in your head.
Come, follow me.
Don't think of Liao Danyi.
Liao Danyi. Liao Danyi.
Now all I can think is Liao Danyi!
What shall I do?
No, stop!
Enemy, on the slope.
Three enemies, two hundred meters away.
Got him.
Two enemies up there.
Two.
Guan Xinyi's joining
made the balance slide to one side for a short while.
But soon after that,
a forth side joined
and pulled the game back on balance.
Xue Xiaodong's broker, Annie.
Speaking of that...
An adult came to play with a bunch of kids.
She should be ashamed.
Seems broker has many free time.
After the war,
I interviewed her.
As the broker of Xiaodong.
I should be prepared to fight for Xiaodong at any time.
She said that.
[Annie]
[Xue Xiaodong]
Isn't that our classmate Liu Ran?
What a coincidence.
What kind of tricks are you playing?!
Nothing.
Just thinking
The world is so small.
I saw you shared an ice cream
with a male senior student in an amusement park.
Today, here you are.
Stop talking nonsense!
Sorry to tell you that
That image is so touching.
So I took a picture of that.
I didn't expect.
After you ate the ice cream
you two dare to do this?
I feel so...
What did you do?
Liu Ran, what picture?
Liu Ran, don't!
That voice...
Aren't they our classmates Fu Xiao and Zuo Zuo?
And fatty.
What a shame.
I have three other pictures.
Let's go.
[Huang Nan][ Huang Yi]
I heard you're our new commissary in charge of sports?
I heard your speed is quite shocking.
Let's race.
Okay, let' go out and race.
No, let's flip our hands.
Okay.
Watch it. I'm gonna win.
My brother will win.
Ready?Go!
Cheng Ling.
You started a little too earlier.
You must have cheated. So cunning.
Right? Shen Wei.
I didn't see that.
Maybe, we can rewind?
Ready?
Go!
Seems I underestimated you.
Come on, one more round.
That's the reason.
Now the warm up is over.
Ready? Go!
Interesting.
Huang Nan, you...
Is this the flip hands game?
Interesting.
Seems you need to hold this for me for a while.
Brother.
You wore such a heavy thing to compete?
No wonder you lost.
Now you're gonna win!
Ready? Go!
Be serious.
Use all you've got.
So can I.
I'm gonna use my secret weapon.
Finally, brother.
Ready? Go!
That's the whole point of the flip hands game?
What's the whole point?
Brother, I just realize that
did we forget to turn off our faucet?
Let's go home to turn it off.
No wonder you lost.
Because you were bothering by that.
Hurry, we need to turn the faucet off.
See you next time!
The war has begun.
No one can stay aloof from the affair.
What kind of future for Class Ten
would this battle about school uniform lead to?
Let's wait and see.