# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 35
Miss Xinyi.
I always followed you.
Follow me today.
Look at this place.
Why did you bring me into Class Ten?
Look at these desks.
These test papers.
And that blackboard.
Do they have a single certificate of merit?
But from such a class,
some student is gonna transfer to our Class One.
I know that.
But...
Class Ten is a bad class.
He transfers to our class. It's a shame to our Class One!
Liao Danyi is the No. 1 in the entire grade.
He's qualified to transfer to our class.
But... But don't you forget?
Liao Danyi and Ye Muxi.
And all the students in Class Ten.
What did they do to our Class One?
Do you forget the blackboard newspaper issue?
The sports meeting?
Isn't it a telltale?
We lost because we were not as good as them.
But Class Ten is a bad class.
-Isn't it inappropriate...
-Enough!
If you're thinking about such unimportant things,
you better focus your energy on yourself.
You're losing your title as the No. 100 in our grade.
I'm disappointed at you.
Think about it yourself.
I hate Liao Danyi!
I don't understand.
Why do you value him so much?
Whether I value him or not is my own business.
What's it to you?
I hate all the people whom you value.
Brother Liao, you're gonna leave like this?
So disloyal.
Yes.
We can never play in the same class again.
How about throw a farewell party?
Yes.
No need.
We'll still be in the same school.
We'll meet a lot.
Wang Anshi once said,
The loyal never pretends himself to get honor.
The faithful never breaks his promise to get profits.
An educated gentleman must be resolute and broad-minded,
for he has taken heavy responsibilities and a long course.
But....
If you leave like this,
won't Ye Muxi feel sad?
I think it's not a bad thing for her.
I've kept her under strict control.
As time passes by, she'll kinda rely on me.
My departure, maybe...
is a chance for her to really grow up.
A farewell party?
We gotta throw a farewell party.
We'll celebrate by ourselves. Don't invite him.
Let's celebrate the departure of the evil boss.
Wang Anshi once said,
The loyal never pretends himself to get honor.
The faithful never breaks his promise to get profits.
What did you say?
But if Liao Danyi leaves in a such a quiet way,
you really won't feel sad?
Why? Do I look unhappy?
I'm very happy!
I'm extremely happy.
I... Finally he's gonna leave.
Why would I be unhappy?
We should celebrate.
Get high.
Wu Sir.
Danyi, you're here.
I'll sit an exam for class transferring in days.
If I pass the exam,
I'll transfer to Class One.
Can you tell me why?
Wu Sir.
Over the past days.
I've had a happy time in Class Ten.
But after thinking over it,
I think only Class One's study vibe
can better help me fulfill my dream.
To get in a famous college.
Danyi.
You may explain to your classmates in this way.
But you can't fool me.
You want to transfer to Class One, is because of Ye Muxi?
Wu Sir.
I... I...
You all call me Wu Sir.
We're not only teacher and students, but also friends.
You and Ye Muxi are friends. You and me are also friends.
Have you ever thought of Ye Muxi's feelings
if you transfer to Class One?
Ask yourself carefully.
Transfer to Class One...
Is it really what you wanted?
As a friend, I want to tell you,
stay in Class Ten.
Whatever difficulty it is, we can face up to it together.
How many days left?
There's an exam for class transferring in days.
If I pass the exam,
I'll transfer to Class One.
Aren't you the No. 1 in the grade?
You'll pass it.
You know what?
I don't buy it.
Whatever you think.
I don't believe that you go to Class One for study.
Remember the day of my registration?
Back then, in order to help me
sign up in time,
you changed clothes with me.
To block my fans.
Since then, I knew,
you're the same like her.
That's the reason why I like Class Ten.
And you guys.
Since you've made your decision,
best wishes to you.
Liao Danyi.
Ye Muxi.
This is for you.
A three-year high school study plan.
If you learn according to it,
you'll see your score improved obviously.
Why did you give it to me?
I just want to complete something.
Thanks.
Ye Muxi.
I appreciate your kindness.
But I don't need this study plan.
And I don't need you.
As you know.
I'll transfer to Class One in days.
After I leave,
Xiaong Tiancheng will be your commissary in charge of studies.
Please cooperate with him in his future work.
Over the past days, we...
Thank you, everyone.
[ Head teacher is busy. Self-study! ]
All right. Students.
It ends.
Let's continue our lessons.
Monitor.
Shouldn't you say 'stand up'?
Morning, teacher.
Morning, students. Sit down, please.
Now, please turn to page seventy-eight.
Take a quick look at the text.
Don't find it odd, everyone.
Liao Danyi is still your fellow student.
It's just, he's transferred to Class One.
Let's continue our study.
Huang Nan. Huang Yi.
Make a schedule as you did before.
Shen Wei.
You may check our classmates' situation.
And report it to me.
If you have any ideas, feel free to tell me.
Xue Xiaodong.
Take charge of music classes.
Teach them to play piano and stuff.
Zhu Shanqi.
Remember to help those students who need extra tutoring.
Mr Wu Heng.
Yezi, what's up?
I don't want to be the monitor.
Ye Muxi, do you want to go KTV?
No, thanks. I'm going home.
Have fun.
Trench mortal. Trench mortal.
A shot will send you back home.
Indeed very powerful.
Trench mortal. Trench...
Stop. Stop. Xue Xiaodong.
What are you singing?
Trench mortal.
To my wonder girl.
What's wrong with you?
You're gonna sing this song tomorrow night?
Don't be impulsive.
You're the future superstar.
Don't worry.
I know what I should do.
Some things, if you let slip,
you'll never make it.
[ Liao Danyi ]
Hi, everyone.
I'm Liao Danyi.
Hereby I request,
to work as monitor of our Class Ten.
Wait!
I, Ye Muxi, want to join the monitor election!
Liao Danyi.
You're the one I hate the most in this world.
How could you do this?!
Ye Muxi, you gotta know.
This is the reality world.
Not those scribbles on your books.
So she will come after you again.
What a nice scene!
What the hell do you want?
This, body language.
People in the world all know it means OK.
-I love you.
-Love you.
You...
You've gone too far!
Big boss, I was wrong.
I'll never do it again.
It's okay. It's okay.
Come with me if you dare!
We can't leave you.
Anyway, you lost.
Idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Idiot!
Liao Danyi sent me a message today.
He says, a date?
Stay with me.
Okay?
No.
Ye Muxi, what were you doing here?
Liao Danyi, you find me.
Let's go home.
You should hide away so I can go find you.
Some other day.
Let's go home to eat hot-pot, okay?
Brother, what brought you here?
I... I'm here to give you some yoghourt.
Take it.
Yezi.
What's wrong with you today?
Why do you look unhappy?
Liao Danyi transferred to Class One.
Sis.
Let me ask you a question.
Tell me.
The one drinks up yoghourt first and the one drinks it up later.
Which one is happier?
I think the one who drinks it up later must be happier.
Why?
Think about it.
The one who drinks it up first
finishes it quickly before fully feels its flavor.
Then has no more yoghourt.
Can only watches the one who drinks it up later...
Tasting it slowly.
Feeling various flavors in the yoghourt.
What the hell are you talking about?
Well...
Lines in the drama are indeed deceptive.
According to the drama,
when someone is upset,
get him some yoghourt.
And then,
tell him a meaningful story over the yoghourt.
After the story, he'll feel much better.
Liar. Liar.
I don't know what nonsense I was talking about.
But I do feel better.
Think, at such a moment,
someone still cares about me and comforts me.
Feel better.
Brother, thank you.
For playing with me over the past ten years.
Don't... Don't say that.
After all, I'm your brother.
It's my duty.
Make room! Make room! Excuse me!
Hurry. Hurry.
No. 100!
You're the No. 100 in this test.
[ Liao Danyi, Class Ten ]
[ Guan Xinyi, Class One ]
[ Ye Muxi, Class Ten]
[ No. 100 ]
Boss, any response?
Boss is always calm before such trifles.
Can't care less, okay?
Yes.
But, to be honest.
Liao Danyi also scores high for us!
Traitor!
No. 100...
Ye Muxi, you're the best!
Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi!
Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi! Ye Muxi!
Go away. Go away.
Don't you know no noise during lunch break?
Miss Xinyi.
Top 50 are all from our Class One.
But Liao Danyi is the No. 1 again.
That doesn't matter.
As long as he's in our class.
Am I right?
Ye Muxi.
I haven't said congrats to you.
You got a nice score this time.
No. 100 in the entire grade.
Spinster.
None of your business!
Why are you always meddling around?
I find that you really like
poking your nose into other people' affair, huh?
You like whatever an old spinster likes to do!
Let's go. Let's go.
Why should you leave?
You relied on yourself and got the score.
They're obviously bullying us!
I really don't know
what your damn Class One is gonna do this month.
You think you're very amazing since you all scored high?
So you can bully others here blatantly?
Why do you get so excited?
I'm congratulating her sincerely.
Or, the answer has something to do with you two?
What did you mean by that?
Nothing special.
Ye Muxi's score is earned through hard work on her own.
She reviews lessons and studies by herself in the library every day.
Besides, we've lost the source of answers now.
I didn't say you have something to do with the answer.
Don't admit it so fast.
You may eat whatever you like. But don't spread rumors.
We got those answers thanks to someone in your Class One.
Enough.
Well, I hope,
I can see your names on the standings next time.
Goodbye.
Take care.
Ugly woman.
Isn't this Miss Guan Xinyi?
If you wanna congratulate her, say something more.
It's a fruit of your hard work. What's to fear?
I saw you arrive in school at five o'clock every morning.
Read books until the library got closed.
If they don't believe you, let them test you.
To see if you can't explain any question that you answered right.
Raise your head.
I rank at the bottom. But I dare raise my head.
Why you not?
What's wrong with you, Superstar Xue?
Are you preparing for a new soup opera?
Or you want paparazzi to play up it?
Do I need that?
Will you go watch my show?
Yes!
Superstar Xue, you're very popular.
But, so what?
Yes.
Why so cocky?
We're in a school, not society.
Score is the most important thing.
You rank the fifth from the bottom in your class.
Do you have any right to talk here?
Class One has fifty students in total.
But you rank the fiftieth.
You rank the fist from the bottom in your class.
A chicken among cranes, what's the big deal?
Xue Xiaodong...
Miss Guan Xinyi, what else can I do for you?
If no, I shall leave first. Bye.
You...
What makes you invite me to drink coffee here?
To celebrate you being top 100 in our grade.
I think it's nothing to celebrate about.
No.
Through your own effort, you managed to be top 100.
I'm really happy and proud of you.
In fact...
I always want to tell you this.
Thank you.
Thank you for forgiving my tantrums when you first met me.
Thank you for stopping me when I wanted to leave this school.
And staying with me.
Thank you for accompanying me to learn
the most important performance lesson in my life.
And many other things.
So I want to tell you...
You're welcome.
Aren't we friends?
Don't need to say thanks to me.
I'm your friend.
It's my duty to do that.
Right.
I just want to make you happy, Ye Muxi.
Actually I'm pretty fine.
It's just...
I don't laugh and joke so much as I did.
In fact, I know, that's not right.
Being like that...
Might make some people distaste me.
And think I'm silly and very childish.
I think...
It's time for me to change.
No.
I won't feel you're childish.
And I won't feel you're silly.
And I won't distaste you.
I think you're not really happy now.
I prefer the old you, always laughing and smiling.
You know what?
I started to know this society since I was very young.
Being a star.
This world is full of plots and schemes.
Interests about money.
To put it pessimistically.
Many people are gonna spend their life in that way.
So was I. Until I met you.
You made me know what's called 'live in the moment'.
And the happiness and importance of 'live in the moment'.
So I want to thank you.
And I also hope you can live in the moment as you did.
I believe.
I will find some way to make you happy.
So, what are you gonna do to help me?
First, please drink up this milk tea.