# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 33
Why did you come here?
Don't say anything.
You must come here asking for help, right?
Well, tell me your birthday respectively.
June... June sixth.
Yours?
September fifteenth.
September fifteenth...
You're a Virgo.
Very thoughtful and agile.
A strong existence among women.
But during Mercury retrograde, you seem a little slack.
You must be kind to friends around you.
Then it'll help your study and career.
As a Gemini, you're lively and active.
But during Mercury retrograde, you seem a little downcast.
You gotta keep positive in life.
Meanwhile, actively participate in collective activities around you.
Then it'll help your finance rebound a lot.
Miss Xinyi...
Well...
Let me give you some material help.
Miss Xinyi, we have money now!
Thank you! Thank...
This... This is invalid.
You're welcome. You're welcome.
Don't say anything.
You're hungry, right?
Come with me.
In this world,
the most delicious thing is spiritual food.
Come, read it with me.
The mountain's height never matters.
It'll be famous if housing immortals.
The water's depth never matters.
It'll be ethereal if holding dragons.
A humble room as it is, it showcases my virtues.
A humble room as it is, it...
Miss Xinyi. Miss Xinyi.
Please save her!
-Miss Xinyi!
-It hurts!
Knowledge is power.
Read more and you'll be alright.
Miss Xinyi, wake up!
-A humble room as it is, it showcases my virtues.
-Miss Xinyi!
Miss Xinyi.
This can be divided into six portions.
We have food for two days.
I'm a princess.
How should I suffer this?
Miss Xinyi.
Please have your breakfast first.
Please maintain this pen for me.
Okay.
What pen is this?
This is...
The Will-lost Pen! A fabled epic pen
left by ancient gods which can command everything!
The Will-lost Pen?
It's said that whoever has this pen can control the entire world.
For this pen, many people had killed or been killed!
Since then, this pen disappeared. No one knows its whereabouts!
Didn't expect.... Didn't expect...
Didn't expect that it's in your hands!
Be careful. Keep it safe.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Where should we place such a valuable stuff?
Safe box! Safe box!
Right. Right. Safe box. Safe box.
No. No. No.
We... We should take a pic and post it on Facebook.
Right. Right.
Let's go.
Camera. Camera.
Camera! Camera!
No!
Star Tianlang falls.
No good intentions.
Disaster!
You thief!
Give me back that pen!
Shut up.
What brought you here?
That is my pen!
Do you know what paper fears and what cloth fears?
Fire and scissors, just in case.
That's not funny. Listen to mine.
Once upon a time, someone (was) called Xiaoming.
Xiaoming didn't hear that.
I... I have a funnier one.
This slap...
Comes so suddenly.
I have a little donkey. But I've never ridden on it.
One day, I went to the market with it on impulse.
My hands...
Nobody. Nobody but you.
I was drunk alone.
But other people in couples.
Watching them with my eyes.
I wished nothing but get a girlfriend.
Who is tender and plays the zither.
Like two swallows happy in purple bamboos.
For this spoony girl, I'm willing
to travel a thousand miles to find her!
Why she can't be controlled?
My will is not as weak as theirs!
I'm gonna destroy this pen!
No. Wonder girl.
If this pen is destroyed,
there's no pens in our village.
You'll never finish your homework!
To save you guys, this is no big deal!
The sin of being unable to finish homework,
let me bear it by myself!
Monitor.
Big boss.
Miss Xinyi! Miss Xinyi!
Miss Xinyi!
Just because of that.
My pen got broken.
So I didn't do my homework last night.
Can I copy yours?
Boring.
You don't believe me?
Where's the trust between people?
[ Maple Leaf Middle School Spring Sports Meeting ]
What does the zoo have?
Giraffe!
Lion!
Rabbit!
Elephant!
Ostrich!
Monkey!
Turtle!
Danyi, play with us!
Finally, we're outdoors.
But you play such a game?
Didn't you sign up for sports events?
Don't need to get ready?
Never mind.
We never won for once since childhood!
We're used to it.
Yes. Yes. We're used to it.
But I can seckill them!
Yes, big boss.
But this time, we're okay.
You know why?
Why?
We have Cheng Ling!
Come on!
Hands! Legs! Hands! Legs!
What does the zoo have?
Blue sky. White clouds.
Cellphone. Spicy strips.
Such a sports meeting.
Perfect!
Li Yao.
Why no one around us?
Got it.
But.
Today, whether our class,
will win or not doesn't matter.
Anyway, we can't possibly win.
It's enough if Cheng Ling wins.
Makes sense.
It's okay. It's okay.
Competitions are just competitions.
Right?
We'll lose anyway.
It's enough if Cheng Ling wins.
It's enough.
Friendship comes first, competitions second.
-Yes. Whatever.
-Such a good day today.
It's enough if Cheng Ling wins!
The sun is in a right position.
Cheng Ling! Go for it! Cheng Ling! Go for it!
Pray for you!
Go for it! Cheng Ling!
Cheng Ling! Go for it!
Relax. He'll win. Don't worry.
Go for it.
Go for it! Go for it!
Miss Xinyi.
We'll get the first place today.
Go for it! Go for it!
Hurry! Go for it!
Cheng Ling! Cheng Ling!
Make way! Cheng Ling!
Tell me.
Did you knock that student down deliberately?
Our Class One must defeat Class Ten.
But in a fair and square manner.
In future, I don't want to see you play any tricks.
Got it?
Leave.
Come. Here. Here.
Cheng Ling, are you alright?
Are you alright?
Cheng Ling, how do you feel?
Sorry. I didn't get the first place.
They've gone too far.
I saw that clearly.
A student of Class One tumbled him down.
Ye Muxi, where are you going?
Let's go. Let's go.
Wait for me here. I'll be back soon.
Guan Xinyi!
Make way!
Miss Xinyi, I got this.
Don't you Class One feel ashamed?
What did you mean?
Someone knocked him down. You know?
What happened just now is just an accident.
Accident?
Let me show you what's called accident!
Guan Xinyi.
Competitions should be open and fair.
Isn't that way too far?
Liao Danyi.
That's really not what you thought.
That's just a misunderstanding.
Besides, Class One defeated Class Ten.
It's a matter of course.
Guan Xinyi.
Today, we just wanted to experience the competitions.
But, the total points.
We Class Ten will get more points than you Class One!
Let's go!
It's really not like what you thought.
You should feel luck that you left fast!
I'm so mad.
Listen to me.
By all means, we must defeat Class One!
Ye Muxi!
Listen to me.
I really understand your feelings now.
I know Class One defeated Cheng Ling by despicable means.
But if we defeat Class One in the same way,
aren't we the same despicable as them?
So Cheng Ling still won't feel happy.
Am I right?
Yes, monitor.
So, I need you to promise me.
In the following competitions,
don't use any indign means.
If we want to win, we win fair and square.
Can you promise me?
Look into my eyes and say it.
Yes.
Okay. Let's go compete.
You all hear that?
Monitor promised Liao Danyi.
Said that she won't use any despicable means
to deal with Class One.
But...
We didn't promise him.
Look at Xiong Tiancheng, can he possibly win?
Without this!
He can't win.
What's this?
This is laxative.
Let's go.
Bro, thank you. Drink some water.
Okay. Okay. Good luck.
Come, drink some water.
Winner!
Come. Thank you. Drink some water.
Nice, bro!
Good luck! Good luck!
You'll definitely get the first place!
Come on. Let me drink some.
-Don't.
-Drink what?
Come. Drink some water.
Come on. Drink more.
Here, let me help you.
Okay. The first place.
Amazing.
I made it.
I made it! I jumped over it!
I jumped over it!
Ke'er, actually, you didn't.
Good luck! Good luck!
I wanted to compete with you long ago.
Today the chance comes finally.
I'm gonna let you know what's called the elite of elites.
Good luck! Good luck! Good luck!
Good luck! Hurry up!
Go for it! Go for it!
Go for it!
Liao Danyi, good luck!
Liao Danyi!
Don't mind me! Run!
Why don't you leave?
What are you doing?
I won't leave any friend behind.
Come. Let's go to the terminus together.
Okay!
Boss! Good luck! Boss! Good luck!
Class Ten! Class Ten! Class Ten!
I can't make it without you guys!
Our success is created by us!
You!
And you!
Class Ten, bravo!
Bravo! Champion! Champion! Champion!
Class Ten!
Anyone can get me up?
[ Shorter bangs ]
Shanqi.
Can you help me cut my bangs?
I tried but couldn't do it right.
But I'm afraid that I will ruin it.
No. No, you won't.
You're so clever. You'll do a good job!
Shen Wei, you're so cute.
You'll look very nice whatever it'll be.
But I'll be very careful.
Okay.
Just a little bit shorter.
You'll look very beautiful after this.
How is that? How is that?
Didn't I say 'just a little bit shorter'?
Yes. Just a little bit, shorter.
I did make it just a little bit, shorter.
Didn't I say 'just a little bit shorter'?
Are you deaf?
I did make it just a little bit, shorter.
I mean, a little bit shorter than it was!
You idiot!
I thought, you want it shorter than it usually is.
Sorry.
Never mind.
If being cute works,
will my bangs come out by itself?
But, but the two sentences sound alike.
Different understandings, different meanings.
So it's partly my fault?!
I wanted it to be just a little bit shorter than it was!
I think this is very funny.
Let me post it on Facebook.
Come on, take a pic.
My bangs...
How could you post it so soon on Facebook?
There is nothing to be mad about.
Just your bangs. Not that serious.
You know what?
In this world, there are three irretrievable things.
Knowledge acquired.
Meals eaten.
And my bangs!
Well, I'll cut mine for you.
Can they be linked to mine? You idiot!
Whether I'm an idiot or not
has nothing to do with your bangs, okay?
-It has everything to do with my bangs!-Why is that?
Just because you're an idiot.
You didn't hear me clearly.
No wonder you're called Zhu (pig) Shanqi. Zhu Shanqi!
Aren't you a pig?
Listen.
Don't make fun of my name as you like.
Everyone could mishear.
Besides.
Don't keep nagging like an old lady.
Do you know how much important my bangs mean to me?
It's huge! A matter of life and death!
Don't you know teenager girls!
It's just some damn bangs!
What's the big deal?
That's because you don't know
how much it matters to people with or without bangs!
With bangs.
Without bangs.
See?
See their difference?
You idiot!
Okay. I'm an idiot.
And you?
Your fortune-telling every day, murmuring incantations.
Anyone understands that? So quirky.
You deaf, stupid idiot, apologize to me!
Apologize? Okay.
Sorry!
Done.
Not to that. Apologize to me!
You idiot! Idiot! Idiot!
Shen Wei, I won't repeat this again.
Don't think you can yell at me
just because you look cute!
Don't think you can cut my bangs as you like
just because you look beautiful!
Don't think you can play tough to me
just because your fortune-telling always works!
Don't think you can cut my bangs as you like
just because you bounce about every day
and are popular among boys!
I'm very popular?
My fortune-telling always works?
Yes.
Yes, you're very popular.
Shen Wei, you're really very cute.
Don't yell at me.
Shanqi, you're so cute.
Be careful when you cut my bangs next time.
I didn't mean to do that. Sorry.
But you're really super cute.
You, too.
-You're cutest.
-You, too.
Come on. Help me check if I have
good luck in love today.
Okay. Okay.