# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 29
All the things started from that quarrel.
People who don't want to be confined by uniformed style.
And people who stick to the bottom line of school rules.
They took up arms, went to the battlefield.
The war on school uniform is still on.
Amid this bloody event...
An epic love was born.
That's not true.
Shanqi, why did you grab my pen?
Does people's entrance sequence
have anything to do with my writing level?
You've been murmuring and writing for a long time.
But the most important story
between Xiaodong and me is not mentioned yet.
Your writing sucks!
Go away. Let me write this.
Xue Xiaodong and Zhu Shanqi's
romantic encounter amid the flames of war.
Start.
It's for official business.
Students of Class Ten didn't dress properly according to the rules.
I hope as a member of class committee
you can correct them.
I will deal with it.
Put it on!
You're always like this.
You hooligan! Hooligan!
How about this.
Let's play a game.
The losers will obey.
Today, this Uniform War's purpose
is to determine how we'll wear our school uniform in future.
It's also a thing which indicates the justice and democracy of our class.
Annihilate them at all costs!
Have you had enough of it?
Yes!
So I hope you can deal with it rationally.
Xiaodong, danger! This way!
Xiaodong, danger! That way!
Xiaodong, I'm in danger!
Shanqi.
I haven't seen any danger yet.
You haven't? Enemies are everywhere.
Miss Xinyi.
There must be sniper up there.
How about we observe for a little longer?
Okay.
No. We can't be like this all the time.
Miss Xinyi.
In fact, I've fallen for you for a long time.
You're so excellent on every aspect.
And you're always standing on the topmost place.
Shinning from head to heel.
I have a wish.
I hope I can stay by your side forever.
And support you.
What did you say?
We can't be like this forever.
But I've come up with an idea.
What's that?
Fold it.
And fold it again.
How to fold it?
Miss Xinyi, what are you doing?
Are you doing paper folding?
None of your business.
I was really good at this when I was a kid.
I can make many little animals.
Really?
Make one.
Okay.
I was really good at this before.
But now, I'm still good at this.
Didn't expect that you could help more or less.
All right, Miss Xinyi, I'm done.
Close your eyes.
Close my eyes?
Three. Two. One.
Isn't it very cute?
What's this?
A little frog.
I want a paper crane! Why this frog?
But... But...
I can't make paper cranes any more.
But this one is very cute.
Look, because it can jump.
Jump. Jump. Jump.
Look, this little frog...
Little frog!
Little frog, are you okay? Little frog.
[ Guan Xinyi ] [ He Lvxi ]
You're dead.
Please return to where you started.
Muzzles are roaring.
The ground mourning.
In the battlefield, no one can stay aloof from the affair.
[ Yuan Ke'er ]
Wherever there's a war, there are casualties.
We might see our comrade-in-arms die at any time.
Before the war, life looks so fragile.
Ye Muxi, watch out!
Shanqi! Shanqi!
Shanqi, why are you so silly?
Yezi.
I... I wanna go home.
Okay. I'll bring you back home.
No. I really want to go home.
I have movie reviews to write tonight.
Okay.
People were downsized on both sides.
Finally, the strongest ones of them met each other.
If possible,
I really don't want to be your enemy.
I don't understand.
Aren't you friends?
Just because we're friends.
I have to be responsible for her.
If you're friends, you should respect her choice.
If so, we don't have to argue any more.
I agree.
You're dead.
Please return to where you started.
I hope you really know what she wants.
The duel between Liao Danyi and Xue Xiaodong had a result.
At the other side of the battlefield,
Captain Ye Muxi was besieged by her enemies.
Yezi, it's the time!
It's the time to give play to our bulk!
No! No!
We're your strongest, widest blindage!
Don't say anything. Don't ask any questions.
Everything lies in tacit.
[ Wolong And Sima's Little Theater ]
Stargaze.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Shuffle.
Pass.
My god.
Kill.
Duck.
Pass.
Stargaze.
One.
Two.
Can you make it faster?
You once died of stargazing!
Remember?
Sima Yi, my round, my choice.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Are you done?
Walk away with it.
Take it. Take it.
Kill.
Screw you.
[ Sima Yi ] [ Wolong ]
Go!
We knocked down the monitor!
Please return to where you started.
Right. We don't have substantial bodies.
It seems that we forgot this important point.
It's okay. It's okay. Next time we'll work better.
Right. Right. The important thing is that we've participated.
Let's go. Let's go.
The weak left one after another.
The war was about to end.
And the powerful embraced their final faceoff.
You're dead.
Please return to where you started.
Cheng Ling!
You're dead.
Please return to where you started.
Liao Danyi, it's time for us to have a duel.
You're killed.
Unexpectedly, only us are still alive.
-Let's start. Three. Two. One.
-I told you, you're killed!
I'm not!
This is a new helmet!
I have another life!
Where did you get the helmet?
I stole it from Yuan Ke'er.
Big boss has gone too far.
She's gone too far.
Big boss, you've gone too far!
You're cheating.
-I'm not. When did I cheat?
-Just now.
I didn't.
You're always like this.
You're killed.
Why did you grab other people's helmet?
Aren't you impolite?
You're killed.
I can't hear what you're talking about.
-I can't hear you.
-Why are you so rude?
- Aren't you childish?
-Can't hear you.
You can't grow up, right?
Stop!
All right. I'll give you another chance.
Liao Danyi.
We take you as our brother.
But you?
If Ye Muxi didn't tell us,
we would be kept in the dark till now.
Haven't you gone too far?
Still pretending, aren't you?
Happy birthday!
Happy birthday to you.
Liao Danyi!
Stop.
It's your birthday. You still do cleaning?
Let me help you.
Are you alright?
I'm fine. Do cleaning. I can help.
The monthly exam is coming.
How are you doing with the preparation?
None of your business.
Look, you're not stupid.
Why don't you spend your energy on study?
I can't focus.
Listen.
People like me have difficulty in learning.
In America,
they'll reserve a seat for me in universities.
Stop daydreaming.
You're not in America now.
Besides, you don't have the learning disorder.
You're just lazy.
You're not me. How could you know me?
Ye Muxi.
Anyway, I gotta tell you,
don't cheat in exams.
Got it?
You're dead.
Please return to where you started.
I win!
I win finally!
After so many years, I finally beat you!
Hallelujah!
You're dead.
Please return to where you started.
We win. We win.
We win, right?
What are you doing?
Big boss, I'm Shen Wei.
Why are you still alive?
Shen Wei managed to live till now.
You didn't count deaths.
Today, Saturn is prograde. Wind and fire cooperate.
I knew that something good would happen!
Didn't expect that we would win at last!
Great! So happy!
[ Shen Wei ]
The war on school uniform
culminated in Liao Danyi team's winning.
End of a story.
But the fight between Ye Muxi and Liao Danyi lasts still.
Isn't this pretty good?
I think you all look nice in this clothes.
Indeed,
school uniform is the most beautiful clothes I've ever seen.
Done? Let's go.
Wait.
Put up your sign. Take pictures.
[ I promise, I'll never come to school in strange clothes. ]
Turn left.
Turn right.
Okay.
Done?
Liao Danyi, listen to me.
Although you make us wear school uniform,
you can't stop our free style!
One!
Two!
Go.
Look, kite.
Kite? Flying kite in such a day?
Brother.
It's said that there are many robbers here.
You know?
Really?
Really. I saw the news yesterday. Let me find it.
Look. Look. Look.
It's true. So unbelievable.
-Very rampant. Open robbery.
-Yes. Yes.
Look, isn't it?
Your phone!
Bike! Bike!
Excuse me!
Lend it to us!
My bike! My bike!
My bike!
Brother, you can't ride bike?!
You don't know that?
I don't!
Are you my brother?
No... I am!
Hurry! Get me up!
It's okay. Just ride.
I'll hold you behind.
Okay.
Hurry. Hurry.
Slow down. Slow down.
Slow... Slow...
Slow down! Slow down!
Damn it. Riding bike turns out to be so hard!
Are you gonna give up so easily?
No. I'm not.
Okay. Let's continue.
When Huang Nan and Huang Yi
remember the reason why they learned riding bike,
the sun sets already.
At last, they choose to call the police.