Hello. I'll be back right now.
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (No limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Running, with schoolbag on our back #
# Sunlight, goes into our coat #
# Fermenting, happiness in a right heat #
# Hi, monitor, I'm all ready #
# Waiting, the signal for running #
# Class begins, my mind is dancing #
# After class, we laugh and sing #
# Striving, our unchangeable pride #
# On the way to the future #
# Thunder and storm won't matter #
# Forever young heartbeats #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Blue sky, green campus (handsome lads) #
# Review the new self again and again #
# Memory speeds up, give full play to youth #
# Head held high, stride forward #
# Dream big, break the limits #
# Work hard for the future world (no limits) #
# Draw one thousand and one fairy tale plots #
# Growth speeds up, give full play to youth #
Katherine, Alina
The Big Boss
Episode 31
My life is described as,
what millions died that Caesar might be great.
But I don't agree with it.
We go out in the world.
We decide whether we'll live or die.
You guys are newcomers in this trade.
Your identity is most innocent.
How you'll continue on this road,
depends on your choice.
All right.
May you succeed in your class.
Members of the class committee.
-How does it go?
All settled.
-Make a bundle.
Morning, director Yan.
Morning.
I have something to tell you.
This is new test papers for today.
Hand out them later.
The test papers were changed all at once.
No one could know the answer.
Today, you must find out the black sheep, okay?
Okay.
Come on. I believe you.
Thank you, director Yan.
Okay.
He Lvxi.
Look these students on the playground.
How many of them are good students?
And how many of them are bad?
Why do you ask such a question?
Miss Xinyi.
What's up?
Many test papers showed up with identical answers.
So did the homework.
I heard that...
It has something to do with a student named Answer.
What do you think of it?
I heard something, too.
It seems that he's a genius.
He can get the test paper that's barely disclosed.
And give standard answer.
At last, he sells it to all the students at a very low price.
You've seen Answer?
Actually, no.
Miss Xinyi, where are you going?
The student union.
Let me follow you, then.
Go. Go.
-No. No.
-Big boss.
You seem a little powerless.
I, Huang Yi...
I, Huang Nan...
Now grant you the power of dark.
Too fast. Go away.
Big boss.
You have no idea of what's called power.
Why did you let go of me?
Come back!
Let's go.
[ The Student Union ]
The Integrity Campaign on campus is a duty for all of us.
Today.
We must wipe out the black sheep Answer and his team.
Now, all set out to the teaching building.
Make sure that all students coping the answer be captured.
Especially, Huang Nan and Huang Yi.
All this time, we have no evidence to prove
that they're doing black market transactions in our school.
But today.
Our chance comes.
Newly-arrived mineral water!
Expires this afternoon!
Hurry, open it and drink!
One hundred percent discount!
Don't need a single penny. It's for free!
Do you want it? Do you want it?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Here, brother.
Take this. Take this.
Bro, take this.
[ Morning Exercises' Answer ]
Hurry. Hurry. Hurry.
Two hundred.
So much? We made a bundle!
Rubbish.
Can't care less.
Look at you.
None of your business.
Can you copy faster?
Buy another copy if you're that capable.
You... Have no spirit of sharing.
Copy faster!
I'm... Not done yet. Don't turn the page!
Director Yan will come soon to collect the homework.
Anything to do with me? I'm not done yet.
Don't touch it!
Brother, cops! Abandon goods!
Stop!
Huang.
Nice meal.
Yes.
I made investigations.
This morning.
You were distributing adlets for our school canteen.
So you'll set us free?
Yes. Any time.
Sorry for holding you up for a long time.
You're very busy, huh?
Now that we're so familiar, cut the crap.
Besides...
We haven't dined in here for a long time.
Tomorrow... How about tomorrow?
Forget it. We have nothing in our hands.
How could we not feel sorry to come here again?
No. No. No. We should be sorry.
Have wasted too much of your time.
We must have made you earn far less money.
You think you can knock me down by sending a spy to me?
Likewise. Likewise.
Miss Xinyi!
Miss Xinyi, you're so cool! Miss Xinyi!
You may leave now if there's nothing else.
Goodbye.
Have you seen any poor student
shake hands with a top student?
Let's go.
Fighting is not easy after all.
What's wrong, Yezi?
Why so upset?
Not feeling good.
Who bullied you?
No one bullied me.
Yezi.
If you bumped into any trouble, tell us.
Tomorrow, teacher will ask some questions in class.
If I can't answer, I'll be punished.
Aren't you being punished all the time?
Why do you start to worry today?
But I'm the monitor now.
Although what Guan Xinyi said is very irritating,
I think she's right.
As a general,
I must lead my soldiers to win this fight.
Now, people all look down upon students in Class Ten.
I think I should be responsible for that.
Right.
That makes sense.
I want to be a good monitor.
So I need your help.
Yezi, you know what?
In fact you've had the best learning environment
that all the other students can't possibly have.
Where?
We both come from the textbook.
In fact, we're very awesome.
Whatever you want to know,
we'll find it out from the textbook.
Then we'll teach you directly.
It's definitely more effective than
rote learning that students normally do.
For example, me.
I come from the Northern Expedition Memorial.
That's my setting.
Yes. Yes.
Listen.
We know all the literature about the Three Kingdoms Period.
Back in the period, we were praised as the Twin Stars.
The cleverest two persons in the Three Kingdoms.
Here, more. Come. Come.
Hi, I'm Li Lei.
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you. And you?
These two are more awesome.
Even though they're retired now,
but they together have dominated the English textbooks for years.
And this.
Our country is taken even mountains and rivers remain unshaken.
When spring comes here, nothing but weeds grow wildly everywhere.
The loom goes on creaking; at the door Mulan is weaving.
Yezi, don't worry.
We will help you a lot!
So great to have you guys around!
I shall no longer worry about my scores!
Ye Muxi's Wolong and Sima, what they've got,
in fact, totally overlaps with what she has learned.
They can't help anything
when it comes to improving her scores.
It takes time for her to realize this point.
Hi, director Yan.
Director Yan.
I still haven't found the source of the answer.
Never mind. Never mind.
This is kinda a victory for this phase.
Keep this name list.
Students who scored zero in today's test are all here.
Post it up in our school's bulletin board tomorrow morning.
Punish them and detain them for further observation.
Okay.
This is called 'kill one as a warning to the others'.
Those troublemakers never try their best to study.
Their days are numbered.
Okay. Director Yan.
Guan, here is another thing.
Tomorrow afternoon.
There's a municipal Education Level Assessment Test.
A pretty important test.
What can I do for you, then?
This test.
Relates to our teachers' levels of education.
So, I hope you can try your best to get the first place.
To win glory for our school and me.
Okay?
Okay.
Good luck.
Thank you, director Yan.
You also ride bike today?
What a coincidence. I ride bike, too.
How about we go home together?
No need. I've got something else. Excuse me.
Liao Danyi, why are you so arrogant?
Miss Xinyi!
Miss Xinyi.
Didn't expect that you can ride bike, too.
Bravo, Miss Xinyi!
What's the big deal?
For me, it's not hard at all.
Do you have something else?
If no, I shall leave first.
Miss Xinyi, let me walk you home.
Whatever.
Miss Xinyi, wait for me!
Danyi, sorry for keeping you waiting.
This is a test for tomorrow.
Make sure that it's done.
Where are they?
Didn't they say that they're gonna sell the answer here?
Where have they gone?
Well...
We're here for the answer.
Where is our answer?
Take it out.
-Let go.
-Gimme.
Gimme. Gimme.
Stop running!
Can't be like this forever.
We gotta find a helper.
A top student?
Let's go.
Go.
Liao, do us a favor.
Brother Liao. Brother Liao.
Don't leave.
Please hear us out.
In fact it's more than a favor.
We're including you in a good deed!
Will you join us?
Brother Liao. Brother Liao.
Look, don't know whom we've offended lately.
We... Failed to sell out anything!
So impoverished.
Brother Liao, what you'll do is to save life!
We even can't afford our breakfast now.
Come to see me again after I'm done with running.
Ruthless.
Heartless.
Cool!
I'm starved.
Stop faking.
So ruthless.
So heartless.
Let's go.
Okay. I'm home.
Miss Xinyi.
This is your home?
Bravo, Miss Xinyi.
Thank you for walking me home.
No problem.
Miss Xinyi!
I will always support you!
After the emergency today,
we've lost our allowance for half a month!
What emergency?
Answer to this morning's test is so irrelevant.
Shouldn't I return all the money to them?
But it's not our fault.
Because they're so foolish that they
didn't realize the test paper had been changed.
Understandable.
They believed us too much.
But they filled in the blanks with A B C D.
Just because they believed us too much?
We were entrapped. Who the hell is the spy?
Hard to say.
After all, you've sold it to so many people.
Could it be you?
I think it's you.
Bro!
Coming.
Arena of Valor coaching?
Full set of LOL champion skins?
QQ coin twenty percent off?
World of Warcraft on sale?
The answer?
Answer sells really well.
Isn't that Liao Danyi?
A top student.
Let's go.
Go.
In fact, it's very simple.
Finish the test.
Then give us the answer.
Money-coming. With huge profits.
Okay. But on one condition.
What's that?
Don't tell anyone that I did this.
Deal.
Nice cooperation.
Ruthless.
Heartless.
Cool!
Everyone, be alert around the clock.
This time, we must catch Answer.
President, how shall we work respectively?
That problem...
He Lvxi will explain it to you later.
Where's He Lvxi?
He Lvxi.
Xinyi. Xinyi. Invincible Xinyi!
President. President. Formidable president!
May our dear Miss Xinyi live long and depart from the world!
Depart... From the world?
What the heck?
It should be... Keep pace with the times and stay different.
Shine forever like the sun and the moon!
Vie with Heaven in altitude!
Miss Xinyi, happy birthday!
Happy birthday what?
But... But isn't it your birthday today?
How could I not know my birthday?
But it reads 'birthday' on your calendar.
I got it.
You don't want to occupy our work time?
So dedicated.
Shouldn't we applause to that?
He Lvxi.
What's up, Miss Xinyi?
Look at my mouth.
Miss Xinyi.
I didn't hear you. Please say it again.
Out!
You may go there first.
That idiot.
The 'birthday' marked is not mine.
But his.
You're here.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
I gotta do homework.
Please leave if there's nothing else.
There's... There's something.
Someone's selling answers in our school.
But I haven't got a chance to prove that.
Huang Nan and Huang Yi are in your class, right?
So I want to...
None of my business.
I want to ask you to do me a favor.
Okay.
I can help you.
Anything else?
Guan Xinyi.
You really don't have anything else?
What brought you here?
Can't ask you out if there's nothing else?
Excuse me, then.
Some official business.
This is the answer for tomorrow's test.
How did you get this?
Director Yan gave it to me.
But the answer is fake.
What did you mean?
Whoever follows the answer tomorrow,
will get zero point.
So you may give it to Huang Nan and Huang Yi.
How long will it take before this ends?
You said, only three days.
But another three days after that...
If it keeps going on like this,
Ye Muxi will be doomed to get worse scores.
Soon. It'll end soon. Don't worry.
Excuse me, then.
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
You're here.
You're really something.
After only an hour. So fast.
I knew we're right to ask you for help.
In this world, I only admire three people.
The first one, Bill Gates.
The second one, Buffett.
The third one, should be Jobs.
But now I think should be you, must be you.
It's not right.
Why is threre one page less?
I also want to ask you about that.
What did you mean?
The test paper you gave me...
The last two questions are missing.
How did you know that?
There should be one hundred and fifty points in total.
It's written on the front page.
But it turns out less than one and thirty points.
That's impossible.
Where did you get the test paper this time?
Did you get the wrong one?
Impossible.
We stole this test paper from director Yan's office.
What nonsense are you talking about?
How about this. I'll leave first.
If you find the last two questions,
send me a picture.