That's enough.
Jang Han-seok.
Damn it.
You got me.
How did you find out?
You can hide the fire,
but you can't hide the smoke.
I guess there was still some smoke left
even when I had the fan on high.
Say your last prayer.
Kill me already.
You Mafia bastard.
As you wish.
That was a blank,
but next time, it'll be a real bullet.
Put the gun down.
This man is the real boss behind Babel,
Chairman Jang Han-seok.
I'm not Jang Han-seok!
-Why are you doing this to me?
-Shut up!
If he really is Chairman Jang Han-seok,
I'll take care of everything.
I'm not Jang Han-seok! I'm not!
Mr. Cassano.
We're going to fire.
Shoot me if you can, you Mafia prick.
Put the gun down.
Come on. Do it.
Mr. Cassano.
The day after I saw the broadcast,
I went to the Yangdong Underpass.
It was cleaned up, but there were
bullet marks and bloodstains.
I've been keeping an eye on you
since that day.
Take him.
Please come with us.
Okay.
EPISODE 12
You're leaving already, Mr. Chairman?
-Cha-young.
-Of course.
Mr. Jang is a victim of attempted murder.
There's no reason at all
for him to be kept here.
Cha-young, there must be
a misunderstanding.
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
Cha-young, please hear me out.
Ms. Choi, just a second.
I have no idea what's going on.
Fine, let's say it's no big deal
for a person to fool another person.
You had fun, I feel like shit,
and we'll never see each other again.
But this is on another level.
You brutally murdered innocent people
and shamelessly put on an act
without feeling any guilt
about killing them.
That means you are less than human
and don't deserve to live.
Understood?
Cha-young, I'm innocent, I swear.
Please don't say that.
You're incredibly consistent.
I'll give you that, you jerk.
Why don't you go and try to save Vincenzo?
Illegal firearm possession,
attempted murder…
This is the end for him.
It's my business whether this is
the end or the beginning.
Take good care of your master.
Cha-young!
PROSECUTOR JUNG IN-KUK
Mr. Cassano,
your gun turned out to be fake.
As well as your bullets.
It's Mr. Vincenzo Cassano's hobby
to collect fake guns.
He is also in the Italian Mafia.
The Cassano Family's consigliere.
That's just an aspect
of my client's personal life.
And you used a fake gun like this?
That's unexpected.
So he just violated
Article 11 of the Gun Control Act
by carrying an imitation firearm.
It's aggravated intimidation,
not attempted murder.
You had no intention
of killing Jang Han-seok, right?
I'll answer that question as his attorney.
No. I want Mr. Cassano to answer it.
If I do, will you exempt me
from being arrested?
You'll have more to gain by releasing me.
That's not enough to convince me.
You're going to kill Jang Han-seok, right?
No. My plans have changed.
I recalled the Italian rules of revenge.
"One.
Give your enemy what they fear the most.
Two.
Take away what they value the most."
What Jang Han-seok fears the most
right now is his identity getting exposed.
He also fears
the collapse of Babel,
the most precious thing to him.
Let's aim to give him both.
But that means…
you'll have to stay in Korea longer.
It was partly for you, actually.
Even if I kill Jang Han-seok and leave,
Babel will remain strong,
and you'll continue to fight against them.
I didn't want to leave you
fighting the long war alone.
First, we'll pressure Jang Han-seok
into revealing his identity himself.
We'll start…
by using Prosecutor Jung.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COOPERATION
WITH THE REDEVELOPMENT
-Yes?
-The man following you since yesterday
is one of Prosecutor Jung's men.
I usually don't enjoy talking at length,
but I had to stall until you arrived.
As you wish.
We've done our part pressuring him,
so it's your turn now.
Why should I pressure him?
Isn't it your goal to summon
the real chairman of Babel?
I heard that you're ready to bring
all six charges against the Babel Group.
They will be brought one by one
and are on an unimaginable scale.
The reporters must have been talking.
This time, we'll gladly help you.
We're the only ones…
who are on your side.
"To find a true friend
is like finding a treasure."
Damn it.
The floor got all dirty!
Why did they have to come in here
with their shoes on?
Why wasn't Vincenzo wasn't arrested?
-Well…
-Prosecutor Jung concluded
that his gun was fake and he should
only be charged with intimidation.
Give me just a second.
His gun was fake?
I think Prosecutor Jung fabricated it.
He calls himself
a prosecutor of integrity,
but he's colluding with a Mafia member.
Why don't you lay low for a few weeks?
I'm fine.
Let him kill me if he can.
It's not Vincenzo, it's Prosecutor Jung.
-He's trying to summon you.
-Summon me?
The thing is, Mr. Jung is ready
to bring six charges against Babel.
Is he seriously planning to summon me
to the prosecutors' office?
Sir, I'll attend the investigation,
so why don't you stay
at Father's vacation home for a while?
Buongiorno, Gilbert.
I mean, Inzaghi.
Who was Gilbert again?
Gilbert.
I like your name.
It's actually gilbeot, not Gilbert.
Korean for "a friend on the road."
Anyway…
so you heard about the gold
at a bar?
Did you tell anyone
other than the Plaza people?
Just them.
They gave me beer and pizza,
so I spilled the beans.
I have a favor to ask.
Can you leave this neighborhood for good?
Why should I?
As you leave,
forget everything about the gold.
I don't want to.
I'll spend the rest of my life
as a beggar in Geumga-dong.
You'll easily find a neighborhood
much better than here.
Are you kidding me?
Geumga-dong is my favorite area.
Is that enough to make you leave
and forget about the gold?
What's gold? Gold?
What are you talking about? What gold?
I'm getting a little tipsy.
Who are you?
What's this?
Why is your phone in my pocket?
-Thank you for everything.
-Not at all.
-Eat up before it gets cold.
-Okay.
I've got to the bottom of the rumor
that there is gold hidden in Geumga Plaza.
Is it true, Mr. Cassano? I'm sure it is.
Not at all.
It was all made up.
That can't be.
Gilbert even showed us a picture
of some workers
in front of that very gold.
Oh, that picture?
I'm sure he downloaded it
from the Internet.
What kind of beggar uses the Internet?
He couldn't even pay his phone bills.
You can use Wi-Fi for free on any street.
Korea is the leader in IT!
Those who survive in the wild
have a strong survival instinct.
It'll be cold up there, so wrap up warm.
Bring hand warmers, too.
Thank you.
-No problem.
-Thank you very much.
-What?
-Bye.
-My goodness.
-Mr. Park!
Mr. Park, listen!
There's gold hidden in this building.
I'm not even going to react.
It's true.
Everyone here knows about it.
Why do you look so serious?
It's not like you.
Unbelievable.
JIPURAGI LAW FIRM
Gosh, you startled me.
Do you have something to tell me?
I heard this
from one of my students' grandfather.
What's hidden in this building is
not gold but a ghost.
It's in the basement.
Ten years ago, there was an office there.
The CEO killed his employee,
buried them, and poured cement over them.
Every full moon, the ghost whispers,
"Cement, cement…"
Thanks to the power
of Buddha from Nanyak Temple,
the ghost is trapped in the basement.
So you should never dig there.
If you do, you'll be possessed
immediately.
Okay.
Why are you telling me this?
I wonder why.
Cement, cement…
Cement…
What's with her?
Take good care of things while I'm away.
-Call me if anything happens.
-I will. Don't worry.
Before, I was worried you were too dumb.
Now, I'm worried
you're becoming too reliable.
I'm working really hard.
I'm studying a lot, too.
Then go ahead with auctioning off
the Babel Tower while I'm away.
I thought we were waiting
until after the groundbreaking ceremony.
We should hurry up.
I wasn't expecting to be attacked.
Okay. I'll do my best with the auction.
Have fun messing around
with the higher-ups.
I'll get going.
Take care.
Mr. Cassano doesn't seem to be
able to help us.
I think we pushed him too much.
There's no way he'd know anything.
The gold isn't his.
You're right.
The gold does belong to someone.
If the gold is found,
it will go to the building owner.
Does that mean
the gold belongs to the Babel Group?
Then there's no way
we can let them have it.
We have to stop them from getting the gold
for the sake of justice.
Starting today,
let's not bother Mr. Cassano
and quietly look for the gold ourselves.
I'll take my leave then.
I need to help Mr. Cassano.
I'll let you go.
Seriously. Seeing your face up close,
it's like watching a horror movie.
Then what are you, a war movie?
Your face is in ruins.
Gosh, how can someone look like that?
-What are you looking at?
-What?
That martial artist prick…
What brings you here, Mr. War Movie?
Well, I heard there was gold here.
I overheard everything.
Don't say that. You're cramping our style.
And what if we did?
Seriously.
You could have just told me.
We have no idea what you're saying.
What gold? There's no gold here.
Cut the crap. You're a horrible actor.
Well, just let me know if you need help.
I'm an expert in this field.
Assuming that Jang Han-seok does appear,
we'll have to support these charges.
Every single charge is massive.
To do that,
we'll have to look into Babel's
accounting, stocks, and connections.
Which one will be the first?
Babel Chemicals'
illegal anti-union activities.
That's most likely.
Wusang and Babel would think the same.
Yes. I've planted a spy
to see what they're up to.
Then we'll have no problem
getting information.
Why don't we go and talk to him later?
Sure, let's do that.
Let me be your spy, too.
If you can't accept me officially,
can I at least be an intern?
-What are you talking about?
-Sorry?
He asked me
if he could help us in any way.
Right. I'm sure I can be of help.
Just tell me what to do.
This work is not for everyone.
If you're not as smart
and quick to react as I am--
Great. Let's work together.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'm going to prove myself to you.
Fine.
Yes?
I see.
Okay.
Jang Han-seok
has left his nest.
Let's go.
How's it going?
Who are you?
I'm agent Lee Cheol-uk from Jipuragi.
Mr. Cassano said he told you about me.
Nice to meet you both.
Actually, we've met before.
At the underpass. Three men.
Anyway, let's monitor what they're up to.
Can you give me the binoculars?
Thanks.
Among these six charges,
which one will Prosecutor Jung
pursue first?
-Can you guess?
-Yes.
Babel Chemicals'
illegal anti-union activities.
The Babel Chemicals labor union
seems invincible.
They're like a weed that never dies.
They're Babel's strongest labor union,
and the union leader has a lot of power.
They're causing all this trouble
because we didn't trample them properly!
What's your plan, then?
We'll have to go with a classic method.
"Classic"?
-Mr. Park.
-Yes?
Request an urgent meeting
with Babel Chemicals labor union leader.
Are you thinking of doing the thing
you did to Daseong Textile's union?
Something like that.
Just make sure we have enough money
to pay for their lives.
Wait.
The world has changed.
What will you do if something goes wrong?
Why don't we let Mr. Jang Han-seo
take care of the negotiations?
He's done business for a while now.
He seems to have gotten quite good at it.
Seung-hyuk.
Yes, Myung-hee?
Let me give you
a sincere piece of advice as a friend.
All right.
Be careful which ladder
you choose to climb.
If you choose the wrong one,
you'll end up falling to your death.
Keep that in mind.
You're scaring me.
Myung-hee!
From the look of things,
I could tell that there's a conflict
between Mr. Han and Ms. Choi.
It seems like they're
supporting different people.
And Mr. Han seems to be loyal
to Jang Han-seo.
I knew it wouldn't last long.
Did you start working
on the Babel Chemicals labor union?
-Hang on.
-Yes?
When are you going to send me
to the new law firm?
Oh, that…
Well…
Some things still need
to be taken care of in Boston.
Then I can't give you any info.
Not until I join that law firm.
Seriously?
How about the legal team
for Lomborgheni in Korea?
What? Lomborgheni?
I'm friends with the branch manager,
so I can get you in.
They're the best sports car company,
so the pay is good,
and the work isn't that difficult.
I can get you a job at the head office
in Italy, too.
My goodness!
Do they give you a Lomborgheni
as a company car too?
I can arrange that for you.
Well, about the Babel Chemicals
labor union…
Ms. Choi said she'd take care of it
using classic method.
But that's all I know.
That would mean they're going to
use brute force.
I have a favor to ask.
Sure. Anything you want.
Can I see you do an impression?
I watched Parasite recently.
It was pretty good.
Are Lomborghenis that good?
Are they that fast?
Yes, they're the fastest cars
in South Korea.
Once you step on the gas…
If Mr. Han teams up with Jang Han-seo
and Ms. Choi with Jang Han-seok,
it'll be so fun to watch them
fight each other.
Which side do you think will win?
My money's on the underdog, Jang Han-seo.
Simple-minded rookies win sometimes.
Underdogs may be appealing,
but they don't win that often.
Thank you.
Do you know the difference between
bungeoppang and ingeoppang?
Of course.
Really? No one seemed to know
exactly how they differ.
Tell me.
The shapes of their mouths are different.
No, that's not it.
The dough is different.
The dough is the same.
The shapes of the mouths are different.
Should we make another bet, then?
All right. Why don't we do
a finger flick like last time?
I'm going to flick your forehead
real hard.
-Are you sure you can handle it?
-Of course.
-I won't go easy on you.
-Me neither.
-I'll flick your forehead…
-Fine.
Take a look.
This is actually an ingeoppang.
-Yes, look at the shape.
-The bread is crispy.
-I'm right.
-About 85 percent
of the bungeoppang we eat
is actually ingeoppang.
You and your nonsense.
I'm telling you, it's true.
-What's that?
-Hey, Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
It turns out we were in the same field.
You were the Italian Mafia,
and I was the Geumga-dong Mafia.
How nice.
You're not a Mafia.
You're just a common thug.
Come on. I'm not trying to pick a fight.
Anyway, I'll let you two use
our service for free.
Tell us if you need to run away somewhere.
Come on, let's get along well together.
My goodness.
You're getting prettier every day.
At least you have an eye for beauty.
What is this?
Hot-air balloons?
Is this Around the World in Eighty Days
or what?
The idea is pretty good, though.
It does look fun.
No, you'll die riding it.
-Let's ride one together.
-No way.
Come on!
The fuel expenses…
It's too exhausting handing out flyers.
There aren't many people
who want to flee abroad.
We should work diligently.
The most diligent street dogs
will get to eat the warmest garbage.
-Why would we eat garbage?
-Let's work harder.
-Hey, did you--
-Hello, Mr. Park.
-Try this, too.
-It's tasty if you dip it in this.
-It's delicious.
-Isn't it good?
This is really tasty.
But what's gotten into you guys?
Well, we'd like to let go
of our past grudges
and get along with you.
Please visit my restaurant next time.
I'll treat you to an extravagant meal.
Come on, you're making me feel awkward.
You want to find the gold, right?
Do you know how to find it?
You said you're an expert.
My goodness.
The food is great.
Who is he?
Why does he look like a total fraud?
Don't be ridiculous!
He's the best gold prospector in Korea,
currently working around Mount Taebaek.
Mr. Keum Gwang-jin.
Keum Gwang-jin? His name sounds fake too.
No, he was just born to do this.
He's the best
when it comes to finding gold in Korea.
-Let me see.
-He seems…
My goodness.
Should I invite him over?
I heard he's on Mount Odae right now.
I miss him.
All I need to do is get to the floor.
I'm the only one who knows
that you're the real Kim Jin-min.
If you're gone,
I can become the real Kim Jin-min.
You'll never have your way.
THE AGE OF STRAY DOGS AND WILD DOGS
Looks like I did already.
Darn it.
You know, fish eyeballs
are considered a delicacy.
You should try some.
I'll never accept the terms you suggested.
Come on.
You'll be the vice president
of the US branch.
You'll be getting 20,000 shares
of Babel Chemicals as compensation,
and we'll be paying
for your children's education in the US.
I heard your eldest child is
really bright.
Send them to Harvard.
And we'll double your severance pay.
Tell me if you want anything else.
Don't offer such a dirty deal to me.
It's despicable and it offends me.
How could you turn down
such a wonderful offer?
I'll tell the prosecution
about this as well.
You're making a mockery of our union.
I didn't mock you.
I'm not a mockingbird.
I'm leaving.
I'm not a mockingbird
You should've accepted my offer
while it was still on the table.
Where are the eyeballs?
Here's one.
It's too fishy.
-Yes?
-What did you do?
Oh. Mr. Jang Han-seok.
You mean the bottled water?
Well, I went through something awful
because of bottled water
when I arrived in Korea.
I had no one else to take it out on.
REVOLUTIONARY PRODUCTS
But it was too easy,
so I don't feel that satisfied.
You still failed to kill me.
That means you're just not good enough.
Don't kid yourself.
I kept you alive on purpose.
How many fingers?
Three!
I tested it
to make sure the effect would only last
a short time.
Had it lasted ten minutes, you'd be
checking in at hell's entrance by now.
Why didn't you just kill me?
I really am going to kill you soon.
If I kill you now,
you'll be dying
as a rookie lawyer of Wusang.
I prefer that since it's quieter.
Because I don't want to see an obituary
as Chairman Jang Han-seok
of the Babel Group.
Run to another hideout if you're afraid.
I'll follow you there too.
I'm not running away.
Try killing me again. Come and try!
Sorry. The music's going to
hit the climax soon.
Change all the guards standing outside.
No, get a new security company!
I'm sorry, sir. But it's Wusang's most
trusted company… I'll change it, sir.
How can someone almost get killed twice
over three days?
Why don't we have our men
get rid of Vincenzo
when they attack Geumga Plaza?
I ought to…
You must have been startled.
But I have good news for you.
What is it?
The labor union leader of Babel Chemicals
is gone now.
He's up there now.
That was quick.
Then what will happen to the union now?
The stronger the leader,
the bigger the absence.
They'll fall apart soon.
Ms. Choi. You've made me feel much better.
You're the best!
The victim was identified as Mr. Lee,
the Babel Chemicals' labor union leader.
He died at the scene of the accident.
The truck driver had a BAC of 0.171,
enough for him to lose
his driver's license.
Babel and Wusang are at it again.
I'm so sick of them.
Is that what she meant by "classic"?
In order for them
to kill people like that,
they need to keep hiring thugs and hitmen.
I have no idea where they find
all those bad people.
This is just unbelievable!
It's so annoying!
The most villainous lawyers
use the law like money.
They offer to lighten their sentences
or stop them from going to jail.
They have plenty of people to make use of.
Do you do that, too?
Mr. Cassano!
-What brings you here so early?
-Good morning.
We won't bother you anymore
about finding that gold.
We decided to ask a professional to do it.
-Mr. Keum Gwang-jin.
-Gold?
Keum Gwang-jin?
I don't know what you're talking about,
but do whatever you want.
What are they talking about?
What? Didn't Mr. Cassano tell you guys?
Apparently, there's a huge pile of gold
in this building.
Is that really true?
It's just a rumor.
It hasn't been confirmed.
How did you two not know?
Everyone in the Plaza knows about it.
Right. How could you not know about it?
My goodness. This is so funny.
-Let's go.
-My goodness.
Hang on.
Don't you dare fight over this, okay?
It's fine, let's go. We'll see you later.
What should I do then not to fight?
All right.
I remember.
You brought up the gold at that bar.
Where did you say it was hidden?
Beneath Nanyak Temple,
in a secret room.
Help us, merciful Buddha!
Then you should've told me it was true!
I did tell you that it was true.
Anyhow, I'm the only one who didn't know.
I was the only one left out.
I've gone through the good and the bad
with you…
for several months now.
Well, the others don't know
where exactly the gold is yet.
Did you say it was worth 150 billion won?
What?
Mr. Nam.
The gold bars are worth
a trillion and 50 billion won.
Why did you say it was 150 billion?
We weren't that close back then.
-Hey!
-Sorry.
I'm so hurt.
I thought of you as my family.
My brother.
-No.
-Come on.
-No…
-There, there.
-It must've been tough.
-My brother.
-You're my brothers.
-I…
HAIR DESIGNER MI-NU
HAIR DESIGNER SEO-NU
Why don't you stay somewhere else?
No, I'll stay here.
Just place twice as many guards here.
All right, sir.
Don't make me look too young.
I want to look neat and strong.
-Yes, sir.
How about going hunting near by with me
to get your mind off things tomorrow?
I heard the permit expires next month.
Wait.
Should we?
-We haven't hunted since Father died.
-Right.
Then we have to get guns
from the police station.
I'll tell Mr. Kim to bring them tomorrow.
Continue.
A trillion and 50 billion…
It's like a national budget.
Is it all yours?
Just 70 percent of it.
The remaining 30 percent is for Mr. Cho.
Seventy percent…
It's 730 billion!
You were actually Korea's Mansour!
Since we're a family now,
we have to protect it together.
Does that mean that we get a share?
Of course.
I'll think about how much.
Give me a gun.
I'll stand guard
in front of Nanyak Temple every day.
This is crazy! This is unbelievable!
I can't believe this is happening!
Please lower your voice.
But what will you do
if the tenants keep searching for it?
First, we should play dumb.
We should.
To maintain peace in this plaza.
Wait. It's… Hold on. That area's sore.
Gosh.
I heard you visited the prosecution.
What's this fuss about?
There was a leak from the International
Security Intelligence Service.
And the prosecution got a hold of it.
And?
Do you remember?
The Intelligence Service's
Guillotine file?
Of course, I do.
They decided not to disclose it.
Turns out that wasn't the case.
After the file was created,
it was hacked and lost.
But they've pretended as if
they had it all along.
The Prosecution Service is in an uproar.
Hurry up and sit down.
How could one of our papers be leaked?
Who in the world leaked it?
This means the prosecution has learned
about the Guillotine file.
Gosh, we've totally humiliated ourselves.
Come back here and help fix this issue.
I can't, sir. Things are hectic
over there as well.
Hey. You're an executive in the bureau.
You need to act like one!
I need more time, sir.
I'll wrap things up and return
as soon as possible. They're in trouble.
Hey. Mr. An.
-I'm sorry, sir.
-Hey.
Hey!
No. Let's just halve it,
chip in, and invest--
Mr. Consigliere!
What is it?
I urgently need your advice.
About what?
It's related to our intelligence service.
I need your take on…
"Intelligence service"?
Oh, I guess you didn't know.
He's a double agent of the International
Security Intelligence Service.
-Isn't that incredible?
-"A double agent"?
I was left in the dark again.
Why doesn't anyone tell me anything?
Why is it me every single time?
What am I to you? A kettle?
It must hurt. Just like how I'm in pain.
Several years ago, a former president
gave our intelligence service an order.
Assemblymen, prosecutors,
people in finance, culture and sports…
Look into every single one of them.
From the moment they wake up until…
We collected all corrupt deeds
made by those individuals
and put them into a file.
It was called the Guillotine.
What a terrifying file name.
The "Guillotine" file?
Why did he order it?
To sugarcoat it,
he wanted to protect himself
from his enemies after his resignation.
To put it bluntly, he didn't want
to end up behind bars.
Correct.
However, a big problem surfaced.
DRAGON
A year later, hackers
from the North Dragon Gang in China
hacked our intelligence service
and stole the file.
Afterwards, they deleted the file
on our end.
GUILLOTINE FINAL REPORT
TOP SECRET
The service hid this fact,
marked it as classified,
and swept it under the rug.
As if the file was never lost.
They really put their all into it.
Any information on the hackers?
After a long search,
we finally managed to identify
the boss who gave them the orders
from Shanghai.
And we were trying to trace him.
However…
I'm curious.
I'm sure it's going to be shocking.
The boss had hidden the file
as well as his secret fund
somewhere in Korea
and died of a heart attack one year ago.
That Chinese boss…
What's his name?
Wang Shaolin.
In any case, the file did return to Korea.
If you were Wang Shaolin,
where would you have hidden it?
I'm not sure.
Could you think before--
I really don't know. I'm drawing a blank.
So where is that file?
Who knows?
The entire country will be in an uproar
if this is exposed.
It'd be like dropping a nuclear bomb
in Yeouido and Seocho-dong.
And Babel is no exception.
How serious are the details?
I don't know what it's about exactly,
but Babel has been paying
the intelligence service
two big ones every month because of it.
So it's obviously quite serious.
We need to find it quickly.
Exactly, but how?
This is driving me crazy.
Should we tell Chairman Jang?
No.
Let's feel it out first.
We should inform him
when the time is right.
The Guillotine file.
Wang Shaolin.
He hid it in Korea
alongside his secret fund.
That means…
This is nice.
Gosh, I haven't held a firearm in ages.
Tell me about it. I think it's been years.
Hey, are you sure
we don't need any hounds?
Yes. It's a hassle to handle them.
Let's just go alone.
Sure.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
This is great.
Do you remember?
I saw you for the first time
at this vacation home.
Yes, I remember.
Our father took us hunting
so that we'd become close.
We were terrified of the sound of gunfire,
so we just hid behind him.
I was truly petrified.
Me too.
Over there.
Damn it.
Where did it go?
This is your chance, sir.
You should bid farewell to your brother.
Look here, Mr. Han.
Are you telling me to kill him?
Yes. For your sake.
I can help you become a happy Abel.
You don't need to be afraid of Cain.
But still--
The smaller the gap
between ambition and action,
the better the result.
You must do it now
to make things easier for you.
What are you doing?
-Come up.
-Coming!
Han-seok! I see something over there.
Where?
To your right!
To my right?
Yes, that's right!
I think I see it.
Sir…
You…
should've aimed properly.
What's going on?
Help us!
Sir!
Wake up, sir.
-What happened?
-Please help us.
Look at all this blood. Sir…
Sir.
Hello, is this 911?
Yes.
This is…
Sir…
I was right.
Come here.
What is it?
An expert in bungeoppang
and ingeoppang wrote this.
This is how they differ.
"Their taste and texture differ
due to the dough that's used."
It has nothing to do
with the shapes of their mouths.
That's absurd.
But I'm right.
You need to be flicked.
Your forehead, please.
Fine. I should be a good sport.
Stay still.
Don't move unless you want to get hurt.
I am standing still.
Enough with the warm-up. Get on with it.
Ms. Hong.
I think I got brain damage.
I only used half of my strength.
Had I not,
I would've fractured your skull.
Yes?
When?
Okay. Keep an eye on them for now.
What is it?
Jang Han-seok
went hunting with Jang Han-seo
and was shot by accident.
He's not dead, is he?
He's been taken to the hospital.
That's all we know for now.
I seriously doubt it was an accident.
If this is true…
I guess a war broke out
between the two of them.
Doctor, how is he?
He was bleeding excessively
due to the bullet in his liver.
But we've successfully stopped
the bleeding and removed the bullet.
You don't need to worry anymore, sir.
Thank you, Lord.
Don't be scared. Don't regret it.
Han-seo. Han-seo!
Don't be scared, okay?
Don't regret it either.
Ever.
Sir.
I had a terrifying nightmare.
I was buried in a nameless cemetery.
Someone was…
pouring dirt over my face.
There was no one else.
I've managed to survive,
but it's likely that the dream…
could end up coming true, right?
Please answer me…
my consigliere.
It's time for you to make a decision.
This could very well happen again.
If you don't want to die namelessly,
you should reveal yourself
and become the chairman.
But I've been hiding it so well until now.
If you continue,
it'll become your biggest weakness.
Just like this incident.
Gosh, my poor brother.
You should've aimed properly.
Let's not jump to conclusions.
It could have been an accident.
An accident?
Sure, let's say that it is for now.
Hello, Mr. Cassano.
I'd like to speak with you urgently.
Thanks.
Why did you want to see me so suddenly?
To tell the truth, my daughter
had to quit her violin lessons last month.
My wife dropped out of her
Pilates class as well.
That's how tough my situation is
right now.
So I'd appreciate it if I could get
my share of the gold soon.
-You want to take the gold out?
-Yes.
Let's just take out what we can
and check the condition
of the room as well.
How much do you need? I'll give it to you.
For now, I need 30 billion won.
-What?
-I need 30 billion won.
What did you do to have that much debt?
For the past several months,
I've been spending money on
cryptocurrency, stocks,
and also on horse racing and other sports.
You shit!
You…
-I'm sorry. You son of a…
-It's all right.
I'm sorry, sir. I am.
-I'm sorry.
-No, I'm sorry.
You were never the type!
-No, I wasn't.
-Why…
Knowing that I'd get the gold
got the best of me.
All right.
Let's take out the amount you need.
We need to talk after that.
Okay. Thank you, sir.
But it'll take a few hours
to take the gold out.
What should we do about the temple?
How can we make the monks
vacate the temple?
Should I take them out for a picnic?
No. We need to close down the plaza,
and there should be no one left inside.
Right.
The residents often visit each other.
They may make a surprise visit.
I have a great idea.
What do you mean?
A night at the hot springs?
You've all been through so much lately,
so I'd like to send you on vacation.
Go have a good rest
and come back feeling rejuvenated.
Here. Please take a look at this.
Jipuragi will cover all expenses.
I specifically looked for a place
that is 53°C, has a pH level of 8.3,
and is slightly alkalic.
But I have lessons every day.
My students really don't like it
when I cancel on them.
Same here. I'd need new clothes to travel.
I don't want to spend money.
I'll go. I could use some relaxing.
-Me too.
Me too. I haven't scrubbed my body
in a while.
Who'd like to scrub my back?
I'll get rid of all your dead skin.
Just imagining it makes me feel refreshed.
This is a luxury for us.
We can barely make ends meet.
And we can't leave the temple unattended.
You must take extra good care of your skin
-since it's humid in there.
-Right.
I have baby skin. I'm fine.
-Let's go.
I forgot to tell you
about the prize money.
Whoever takes the best photo
during the trip
will receive 20 million won in cash!
-Twenty million?
-Seriously?
It's all yours.
What are you talking about?
All right.
We didn't build Babel Tower
to make a profit.
We built it to display our gratitude
to the assemblymen,
director generals,
and Chief Prosecutor Hwang.
From now on, whomever helps Babel,
we're going to give them
this much of the tower.
We'll start with the penthouse.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Your decisions will affect your future--
Damn it. What is it? What is it?
Sir.
That's not how you do it.
Do you think this is telemarketing?
Hey, you. Who are you?
Chief Prosecutor Hwang.
Have you been well?
Who are you?
Oh, right. You couldn't see my face
because I was wearing
a helmet and a mask.
I'm Choi Myung-hee, a lawyer at Wusang
and Babel's legal representative.
And he is the eldest son of Babel
and Chairman Jang Han-seo's older brother.
-What?
-"The eldest son"?
This is embarrassing.
My name is Jang Han-seok.
From this moment on,
I will lead the Babel Group.
My brother, you've worked so hard
until now.
Come here.
It hurt so much, I thought
I was going to die, you bastard.
-All right, get in.
-Welcome.
Byebye Balloon is lending you this bus
-for free.
-Get in.
I'll pay for the gas as well.
Look at him boasting.
This is wonderful.
We'll get going now.
I feel bad for leaving you behind.
-Let's go. Hurry.
-Let's go.
-Get on.
-Didn't you say you were not going?
-Okay.
-Watch your step.
Goodness.
This is so wonderful.
Goodbye.
Let's go.
NANYAK TEMPLE
"Nanyak Temple."
Let's go inside.
The door
is unlocked.
They leave it open
in case anyone comes to pray.
Please excuse us.
-Use that.
-Okay.
-Here.
One, two, three.
-One, two, three.
Grab it.
-Grab it!
Do it again.
One, two, three.
Grab it!
Help me.
-Help me with this.
-Okay.
-One…
-Hold on.
Lift it.
Help me.
Be careful.
Today…
We finally made it.
I still can't believe
that this is all gold.
There are cultural assets as well.
SPECIAL THANKS TO AHN CHANG-HWAN,
HWANG CHANSUNG, NICHKHUN
Subtitle translation by: Min-jin Kim