Darn it! When did this happen?
Hello, I have a blind date at 4 p.m.
That cheeky nurse!
I'm sorry I'm late.
My name is Lee Soo Ryeon.
(Episode 2, The Shoes That Fit Me)
Write everything down, okay?
This method has a 99.9 percent
success rate of being rejected.
This data is based
on all the blind dates I've had.
Just follow my instructions,
and getting rejected
is just a matter of time.
I'll have coffee. Just black please.
I'll have...
First.
Leave a strong first impression
when you choose the menu.
I'll have a beer.
So it'll be one black coffee
and one beer?
Okay.
I guess you like to drink.
Yes. I can't live without it.
Whenever I feel sober,
my hands tremble like crazy.
I see.
May I have a sip?
- What?
- You make it look so delicious.
Now this is some nice beer.
But keep in mind that it's useless
to guys who are heavy drinkers.
So you need to switch
to the modern woman mode.
It's an obvious fact
that most men...
believe in a patriarchal society.
Did you come here to find
your future wife?
That's usually the case
when it comes to blind dates.
Did you have something else in mind?
No. I came to find my husband too.
But I'm quite a picky woman.
First of all,
I've never done any work at home...
and I'm not the type that stays home
to support my husband.
My career is more important.
I like that.
My ideal type is an ambitious woman.
I'll never have a baby either.
That's up to the woman, of course.
I won't force you to do anything.
I'll never look after
my parents-in-law either.
No need to worry about that.
My parents don't care about me
at all.
You're not as picky as I thought.
I guess we're pretty compatible.
If he's a guy
with a smooth tongue...
that has an answer for everything,
it's time to turn on
the philosopher mode.
First of all, put on a hazy look...
and sigh as if everything in life
is futile and say...
What do you think marriage is?
I'm not sure.
What a profound question.
But...
do you know
you didn't even ask me my name yet?
And your name is?
It's Hwang Hee Tae.
Hwang Hee Tae.
Hwang Hee Tae?
The one who went to...
Seoul National University
College of Medicine with top marks?
I guess you saw the banner.
Gosh, practically everyone
in Gwangju saw that banner.
"Congratulations on your acceptance
to SNU, Hwang Hee Tae."
Boom.
I'm glad my father put up
that banner...
since you're showing
such deep interest.
I didn't show any interest.
Why don't you stop drinking,
so we can go eat?
Eat?
Yes, eat.
If he says he wants to eat,
that means something is going
awfully wrong.
At this point,
you need to switch to filthy mode...
and stimulate his basic instincts.
Use the sense of sight,
smell, hearing,
and every other sense
you can think of...
to make him feel uncomfortable.
Oh, my goodness!
Almost all the men
who come on blind dates are similar.
They all grew up being sheltered.
Thank you.
Let's eat.
What? You should have a bite too.
Did you bring me here
thinking I'd be repulsed?
What?
Is this the best you can do?
I know worse places than this.
I guess you grew up
being sheltered...
since you're the daughter
of Changhwa Industrial.
I'm not...
the neat, spoiled son
you have in mind.
I'm someone who grew up
eating other's leftovers.
What?
Go on and eat.
If he doesn't bat an eye
and keeps eating,
then...
that means he's a hard one to crack.
Why?
It means he's a guy
that likes easy-going women.
And if you stuffed your face
with gukbap in front of him...
But Myeong Hee, don't worry.
There's still a way.
There's one thing that guys
who dig easy-going women...
hate most in the world.
Let's go shopping.
Shopping? Now?
It's my rule to go shopping...
at least once a day.
Sure. Where do you want to go?
There's a shop I frequent.
Follow me.
Guys who like easy-going women...
tend to hate it
when someone is extravagant.
Oh, dear. What do I do?
I left my wallet at home.
How about you buy me something
as a gift?
To celebrate our first date.
Sure.
Look around freely.
And if he's still pretending
to be unfazed,
then it's time
for the second strike!
Show me your most expensive items.
Please come this way.
These are
your most expensive items, right?
Gosh, I don't know
if it's because of the price tag.
I really love all of them.
Excuse me, Soo Ryeon?
Yes?
Choose anything you want.
Don't worry about the money.
(330 dollars)
This bag is worth
three months of my pay.
Why don't you carry it around?
It's the same brand
as the dress you're wearing,
so it'll be a perfect match.
Oh, that's why it felt familiar.
I already have this one at home.
I'll look around some more.
(Madonna Fashion)
You bought a passport case
when you don't even have a passport.
What odd taste you have.
Well, it's my hobby to buy
useless stuff.
Thank you for today...
- Gosh.
- Why are you getting in?
What are you doing?
I'll take you home.
Goodness. That's unnecessary.
I can go by myself.
My father told me to take you home
no matter what.
Please drop this lady off first.
Sure. Where to, ma'am?
Hyangrim-dong...
That came out wrong.
Please drop me off
in Dongmyeong-dong.
It's in the middle of the semester.
You must be busy.
What courses are you taking
in the school of law?
What kind of student takes classes
at a time like this?
We're boycotting all courses taught
by government-funded professors.
We consider all classes
to be canceled.
I see.
You consider classes to be canceled.
Then you must have more time
on your hands.
What about you?
Most interns don't even have
time to sleep.
How did you find the time
to go on a date in Gwangju?
I have a lot of time.
I'm not an intern.
I've deferred my graduation.
You deferred your graduation?
Goodness. You must've failed
the medical licensing exam.
I heard that a few people fail
every now and then,
but you're the first person
I've met in real life.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but I passed the exam.
Then why haven't you graduated?
I'll tell you when we become closer.
This is me. Are you happy now?
Hurry up and go home now.
Today was the most fun
I've had in a long time.
By the way, take this.
What is this?
You'll need it on our next date.
Our next date?
Didn't you say we have to meet
at least three times?
When should we meet next?
Well...
I'm not sure when I'll have time.
Hold on. Are you turning me down?
The thing is...
I hope you're not.
I'd love to see you again.
Me too. You should leave now.
- Can we meet again then?
- Yes. Call me.
How can I reach you?
Sir, please get going.
Wait.
Myeong Hee?
Soo Chan.
Are you just coming home now?
Wait. Why are you two
coming in together?
We met at the gate. That's why.
Hold on. Look at you.
Is that what you wore
to your blind date?
Myeong Hee looks like
she went on that blind date instead.
- What?
What? I was just joking.
Myeong Hee looks different
than usual.
I look funny in these clothes,
don't I?
They're all Soo Ryeon's.
You look great.
The clothes suit you perfectly.
Did you go somewhere nice?
What? Well... She was on a date.
We're going upstairs.
A date?
How did it go?
Even when you did everything
I told you to?
He's no ordinary guy, I tell you.
No matter what I did,
he did something worse.
What a weirdo.
What's all this booty
that you brought back?
Don't tell me you even got
to the boutique phase.
I'm not shameless.
I picked the cheapest one.
I don't know what this could be.
He gave it to me.
A pair of shoes?
Try them on.
They fit perfectly.
How did he figure out your size?
No idea.
Is this guy a pervert?
You know, like guys who have
an obsession with women's feet.
He did seem a little weird,
but he didn't really come off
as a pervert.
For now,
- we're putting these back in.
- Why?
"Why?"
Do you want your feet
to give him the okay sign?
Next time, we should plan ahead...
Forget it.
It's not going to work anyway.
It'll only torture me.
And I don't care
if I have to meet him a dozen times,
as long as I can get the airfare.
Hey, that's no problem.
I promise I'll get the money
before the third date.
So don't worry about anything
and get ready for your studies.
Anyway, what should you wear
on your next date?
We should probably pick out
some outfits beforehand.
Are you just getting home?
Have you been waiting for me?
Did you do anything that her family
might disapprove of?
No, not that I can think of.
Our family's future
depends on this marriage.
A communist brat like her...
might not be easy to control
at first,
but no girl is impossible to tame.
Make sure this works out.
Goodnight, Father.
Gosh.
I'm sorry I'm late.
My name is Lee Soo Ryeon.
I'm not the neat, spoiled son...
you have in mind.
You'll need it on our next date.
Honey.
Can you stop by Mudeung Stadium
on your way to work?
The stadium? Why?
Jung Tae has a meet today,
representing Gwangju...
in the provincial preliminaries.
Are you running again?
It's about time you quit.
If you're that focused on it,
you'll have no energy to study.
By the way, Hee Tae.
Have you asked her out
on a second date?
I'm working on it.
I'll see her again soon,
so don't worry.
You remember
the appointment today, right?
They're important people,
so don't be late.
Okay, Father.
(Kim Myeong Hee)
Myeong Hee, you have a call.
Me?
I'm not expecting a call.
A man asked to speak to you
in an urgent voice.
What?
Hello?
Myeong Hee!
Myeong Hee, I'm in Gwangju now.
You haven't forgotten
about the meet today, right?
You have to come!
Kim Myeong Soo!
I told you not to call...
I told you not to call me at work.
You're coming, right? You'd better.
I'll keep calling you
until you come.
Okay. What time does it start?
Let's start with this.
Then I will...
My goodness.
Your father will faint
when he comes home.
Why don't you set up
a command center here?
You jerk! Don't crack such a joke.
Keep talking.
I'll be right back, guys.
What's your problem?
Do you not want this?
(540-3 Boncheon-dong,
Seo-gu, Gwangju)
How did you find out?
You said it'd be hard.
I stumbled
upon an unexpected helper.
I went to middle school with her.
Jang Seok Chul isn't a common name
for girls, you know.
We met briefly the other day.
What's your name?
I'm Park Sun Min.
Thank you, Sun Min.
She must be that girl.
Your secret girlfriend in Gwangju.
The three of us
should grab a bite together soon.
Bye, sis.
- That crazy jerk!
- What's he saying?
Soo Ryeon!
Goodness.
Soo Ryeon.
(Madonna Fashion)
You should always watch
where you're walking, Soo Ryeon.
I'm sorry. I called you,
but you didn't hear me.
Hwang Hee Tae?
Did you follow me?
What?
I'm going to the bus stop too,
so don't be so guarded.
You're rich.
Why won't you take a taxi?
Isn't your family wealthier
than mine?
I wasn't sure
whether it was you or not.
Your style is very different
from the last time I saw you.
I was at a rally earlier.
Oh, is that right?
That makes you even more likable
than last time.
Don't be sarcastic.
I really meant it.
By the way,
what are you looking for?
I can't find the bus token.
You can be on your way.
I have to get some tokens.
Oh, I have some that I can spare.
Will this be enough?
Do you sell tokens?
How do I go about doing that?
Should I charge interest?
Well, then I'll just take one...
It's not like I can dig the ground
and find these.
Take them all
and pay me back with interest.
Sure, okay.
We should meet again.
The flowers are in full bloom.
Sorry, I have somewhere to be.
Bye.
What? Wait.
Soo Ryeon!
Soo Ryeon! Then how about tomorrow?
What's this?
Get out if you're not getting on.
Just a second please.
You, the lady over there
with her head facing the window...
and with her left hand
over her face!
Are you free tomorrow?
Miss!
He's asking you
if he can see you tomorrow.
Yes, sure!
Where? What time?
My goodness!
Just meet at Woo Cafe around 4 p.m.
Okay, 4 p.m. at Woo Cafe it is.
Thank you all for waiting.
All right!
- Go for it!
- You got this!
Good luck!
Kim Myeong Soo!
Myeong Hee!
(Naju)
Good luck, Myeong Soo!
Thanks!
(Go, Suseong Middle School!)
(Go, Eungbo Middle School!)
- Good luck.
- You got this!
Best of luck!
- You got this.
- Good luck!
- Go for it!
- Do a good job!
Myeong Soo, my gosh...
(Gwangju)
My gosh!
Go, Myeong Soo!
(Gwangju)
Myeong Soo! I'm so proud of you.
You made Naju proud!
What are you talking about?
I came in second.
This means I'm out.
What? You didn't know?
Second-place winners can participate
in the Junior Sports Festival.
You now represent
South Jeolla Province!
What? Seriously?
My gosh!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
My lungs are about to burst.
This is an announcement.
Catch your breath.
I have to go to the main desk.
Teachers, please come
to the main desk.
My gosh.
Even though your shoes came off,
you almost beat Hwang Jung Tae.
You totally could've come
in first place.
What is your name?
I'm Kim Myeong Soo.
Myeong Soo?
It sounds like a digestive drink.
I'll see you
at the Spartan training.
"Spartan training?"
Myeong Hee!
I did it. I made the team!
The second place winner can join
the South Jeolla team too!
What?
Gosh, I'm so proud of you.
My little bear.
What do you want to eat?
Just tell me.
I'll buy you everything.
I want...
What? Is it because of your friends?
Bring them along. I'll buy...
Father!
We don't need any entrees.
We'll just have three bowls
of jjajangmyeon.
We'll have tangsuyuk too.
Make it a large.
One large tangsuyuk and three bowls
of jjajangmyeon coming up.
Oh, my.
This jjajangmyeon looks delicious.
Let's eat.
You're supposed to be a runner.
Look at the state of your shoes.
With good shoes,
you would've easily won the race.
Mind your own business
and get some new shoes yourself.
What kind of grown woman wears
shoes like those?
The more I think of it,
the stranger it seems.
Is the bank clerk intercepting
all the money...
or does your wallet have a hole
in it?
Where did
all my hard-earned money go?
Oh, I almost forgot.
Can I stay with you
at the boarding house...
for a few days?
The provincial representatives
will be training in Gwangju.
Does that mean...
you'll be coming to Gwangju
every weekend?
Actually, it's not just
the weekends.
We'll be training there
throughout May.
What did you say? Throughout May?
What about school?
The teacher said...
the school wouldn't care
as long as it's for training.
No.
Enough with your nonsense.
Just stay in school.
Father.
Do you break your children's wings
as a hobby?
What did you say?
I'll look after Myeong Soo
during his training.
Stay out of it.
Just worry about yourself.
- Get up.
- Father.
Sit back down.
We haven't had the tangsuyuk yet.
Are you coming or not?
Well... Excuse me.
Is this Ms. Jang Seok Chul's home?
Is someone here?
She started sending us
less and less money.
In the end, she stopped completely.
Is it about a guy?
No, that's not it.
She probably stopped sending money
because of the factory strike.
It's been going on for months.
A strike?
Did she get arrested
for going on strike or something?
No, she didn't get arrested.
The thing is,
she got seriously injured.
She's in a hospital in Seoul
right now,
but she'll be transferred
to a hospital in Gwangju soon...
Wait. If she's sent here to Gwangju,
she can't work
at the factory anymore.
Right now,
she's not in the condition to work.
This isn't much,
but use this for living expenses...
and her medication.
Who cares about her medication?
My eldest son...
can't go back to school
because he can't pay his tuition.
Why did that wench have to...
go on that useless strike?
The boy's family told me that...
the date went well. I'm surprised.
What else could I do?
Going on three dates
was the condition.
Goodness.
Your effort has paid off.
You should go and see.
What do you mean?
I got a call that
your gang has been released.
Is that right?
Father. Father!
My goodness. That's enough.
Father. I'm going out for a bit.
See you later.
My gosh.
(Shut down professors' offices!)
Guys, I brought tofu for you.
(Report the facts!)
Hold on.
Why do you all look so serious?
Did something happen?
Have some tofu first...
How did you get us out?
What are you talking about?
No. Maybe the first question
should be how you got out.
Tell us.
You're the one who got caught
holding a bunch of flyers.
So how come you were the first
to get released?
What could I do?
With all our seniors
being wanted and on the run,
I couldn't let you guys
go to prison.
In that case,
why don't you ask your father
to let them off the hook too?
Guys, don't be like that.
We're all here to fight
for democracy.
Yes, we're all here
to fight for democracy...
except one person is
here to play tag.
You apparently had no problem...
with using my father's factory
for printing out flyers.
And all of a sudden,
we belong to different classes?
You could've been straightforward
and said you don't like me.
Wait, Soo Ryeon.
Come on.
While trying to save five seconds,
you may lose 50 years of life.
No jaywalking.
Sir, you're not a car.
Please use the sidewalk.
- Sir!
- Gosh.
Wait.
How dare you try to jaywalk
right in front of an officer?
Aren't you the criminal
that I caught red-handed?
Hey, there.
Do you break the law as a hobby?
Your father won't be able to
get you out this time.
Shouldn't you try
to keep up appearances?
A well-off person should set
a good example...
I was just...
I didn't mean to make you cry.
Hey, Hyun Chul.
It's not a market day today.
What brings you here?
Well...
Show us a pair of running shoes.
They are...
for the National Sports Festival.
So show us the best pair you have.
The National Sports Festival?
Myeong Soo!
Are you participating in it?
We have these ones and...
There's this one too.
Take your pick.
This one?
Unlike your father,
you have a good eye.
Do you want to try them on?
All right, come here.
Here, the right foot first.
Let's see.
There. Perfect.
Father.
It's really okay.
I guess he doesn't want new shoes.
Forget it then.
No!
Now, try on the left shoe too.
Put them on and try running in them.
Come on. Hurry,
before your dad changes his mind.
Try running in them. Yes, try now.
How is it?
It should be somewhere around here.
What's that, Father?
The recipient is Kim Myeong Hee?
(To Kim Myeong Hee)
What?
Oh, I brought this because it has
your sister's address on it.
Father, did you write her a letter?
Give me that.
I'll hand-deliver it.
This way, you don't have to buy
the postage stamp.
You rascal.
Hey, that tickles.
- Stop.
- Oh, it's Myeong Hee.
Myeong Hee!
I should get going.
Here, take your shoes.
I'll stop by the training camp later
and drop off your clothes.
What? Aren't you going to say hi
to Myeong Hee?
Go on. She's waiting.
Myeong Hee!
Dear Lord.
Please bless us with the ability
to help those in need...
and spread kindness.
Please give us the strength
to fully carry out our mission...
using the abilities
that you bestowed upon us.
Lord, we pray to you...
with all our hearts.
- Amen.
Amen.
I'm sorry I'm late.
You're late indeed.
You should introduce yourself.
Sure.
Hello.
My father must've already told you
lots of good things about me.
It's nice to meet you in person.
I'm Hwang Hee Tae, his eldest son.
My gosh.
My goodness. Mr. Hwang,
what a happy family you have.
Your wife is the most gorgeous lady
in Gwangju,
and your son attends
the number one university in Korea.
And...
your younger son is adorable.
I'm sure just looking at them
makes you happy.
Kiddo, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
A doctor, like your big brother?
I want to...
Actually, Jung Tae qualified...
to compete
in the Junior Sports Festival as...
He wants to become a soldier.
He's already training...
to attend the Military Academy
later on.
Clearly, he takes after his father.
What a blessed family!
Wait.
Don't eat so fast.
You'll burn your tongue again.
You can eat now.
If someone asks me what I'd want
to eat in my final moments,
I'd pick ramyeon cooked by you.
Eat up.
Eat it with kimchi at least.
I said I could fix you
a proper meal.
My gosh, thank you.
- Eat up.
- I'm home.
Hey, you're back.
Oh, I smell ramyeon!
Careful, it's hot.
Who's this kid?
Myeong Hee, is he your secret child?
Gosh!
You wench, watch what you say.
He's my baby brother.
He's here
for his track and field training.
Hello, I'm Kim Myeong Soo.
Unlike you, he's very friendly.
Cut it out.
- Take your shoes off, will you?
- Gosh.
- And go wash your hands.
- That hurts!
- That's the point!
- Stop hitting me! It hurts.
Like I said, that is the point!
- Why you...
- Stop! I'll take them off.
Here. Are we good now?
Myeong Hee.
If you're going abroad,
when will you return?
I'll come back when your grandson
is getting married.
You're leaving
because you hate our family, right?
What is this nonsense about?
Can you not leave?
If you leave,
you won't get to see me win a medal.
Father doesn't even know
that you're leaving.
You're just a kid.
Stay out of grown folks' business.
I just...
want to see you and Father
get back on good terms.
Like the old days.
Back then, you smiled a lot
even when you were at home with us,
like you're doing here.
You little rascal.
Just go to sleep.
Get home safely, ma'am.
A few more dinners with them
will make you quit smoking.
I told you not to be late.
Where were you?
I went to see Soo Ryeon.
You said
I should see her again soon.
I'm meeting her tomorrow.
Myeong Hee,
can I borrow your powder?
You'll start middle school soon.
How do you still not know
how to tie your own shoelaces?
It's because I've never owned shoes
with laces before.
Stop! That's way too tight.
This way, it won't come undone
even if you run.
There.
Are you sure
I don't have to go with you?
I'm not a baby.
I can look at the map.
I'm very good with directions,
you know?
See you later, Myeong Hee!
Watch out for cars.
And come home
as soon as you're done!
My goodness.
It's warm today.
What's with the coat?
Well...
My hands and feet
get cold so easily, you know.
See you later!
- I told you.
- Who can I take?
You can go with Ms. Choi.
Would she be free?
My gosh, Myeong Hee!
Are you going somewhere today?
Why did you get all dolled up
to come to work?
Who are you trying to impress?
My goodness.
Not you, obviously.
Just finish that cigarette.
Why that little...
- Rock-paper-scissors. Paper.
- Paper, paper.
Are you here for the training?
You can come stand here.
Oh, that's...
Always be careful
and eat well, okay?
Don't push yourself too hard.
- Call me if anything happens.
- Okay.
Even his mom is so pretty.
She's prettier than Jung Yoon Hee.
She used her looks to become
a mistress.
My mom told me...
that Hwang Jung Tae's mom
is a mistress.
"Mistress?"
It's nice to meet you.
I'm your coach who's in charge of
your overall training,
Park Chul Bum.
The month of May will become
a month you'll remember...
as the most passionate moment
of your lives.
I'll make that happen through
a Spartan-style training program.
Now, everyone get into groups
according to your main event!
- Center.
Move faster.
You two have the same shoes.
They're not the same.
His shoes look cheap.
- What?
- It's fake.
Did you buy that at the market?
Why do you care what I bought...
or where I bought it from?
Hey, doesn't he smell like a beggar?
What?
You little...
Hey, Myeong Soo and Jung Tae,
come here.
Get over here now!
The hardest thing in the world
is to become a steady sponsor.
I'll make sure
this money is put to good use.
Oh, yes.
Okay.
(Executive Director, Lee Soo Chan)
Thank you for your time.
Gosh, I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
(Emergency Room)
Excuse me, when can you check this?
Oh, I'll be right there.
I'll be right back.
Oh, dear.
(Emergency Room)
Ma'am.
You look very busy.
Hey, Soo Chan.
What are you doing here?
Are you hurt?
I come here often
even when I feel fine.
Is it about time to go home now?
I'll be waiting outside.
How about dinner?
I'm sorry. I have plans tonight.
Plans?
Oh, is it that date
you mentioned last time?
No, it's not a date. It's...
Soo Chan, I'm still on the clock.
Oh, right.
I'm sorry to bother you
when you're so busy.
I'll see you next time then.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
Excuse me?
Which fork do we have to use?
There are so many.
This is the salad fork,
and this is for the main dish.
Thank you.
I thought you were used to stuff
like this.
Aren't you rich?
I'm totally clueless,
but I just came here because I heard
this place is expensive and famous.
I just wanted to impress you.
Oh, right.
My tokens.
My gosh.
Are these brass coins or what?
I can't deny it.
Every time I meet you,
it feels like I laugh more
than the past few years combined.
Gosh.
You say that to every girl you meet,
don't you?
No. You're the first.
After struggling with my life
all day long,
I feel free whenever I meet you.
You're really special. I mean it.
It is special to be the daughter
of Changhwa Industrial.
Did the shoes I bought you last time
fit well?
Well, the thing is...
Man, this place is nice.
It took me a month
to get a reservation at this place.
I never expected you
to bring me here.
Why? Shall I order something else?
I suddenly feel thirsty.
What kind of drinks do they have?
- I can't believe it's just us two.
- Is your hand trembling?
- Shall I order some beer?
- Where are the girls?
- No, I'll just have water.
- Come on, I barely got us a table.
- Go on and eat.
- You can come with her next time.
"Her?" Who?
You know,
that nurse in the ER
that you're hitting on.
- That cold-hearted girl.
- Oh, her?
Cold-hearted, my foot.
It turns out she's a total vixen.
She's just wagging her tail
to marry into a rich family.
What a true surprise.
You know, that guy who supplies
our hospital with imported medicine.
Don't force yourself to eat.
You'll get sick.
I'm not feeling well.
- Can we...
- But you know,
no matter how hard she tries,
no rich man will want her.
She should know her place.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Soo Ryeon, I'll go get some water.
Why is she trying so hard?
Let's choose our menu.
I'll have the New York steak course.
What shall I have?
What the...
Are you crazy?
My goodness. I'm sorry.
My hand must've slipped.
How could your hand slip on my head?
- Darn it.
- I'm so sorry.
- I'll pay to get it cleaned.
- What?
I can't believe this.
Hey, Myeong... Wait...
Use this to get it dry-cleaned.
And watch your mouth from now on.
(New York Steak)
Soo Ryeon!
Are you okay? Can you get up?
I'm fine. It's just a sprain.
- Let me carry you.
- No.
I said it's okay. I can walk.
How can you walk wearing this...
I said I can walk!
My gosh!
What are you doing?
You need treatment.
Let's go to the hospital.
No.
Not the hospital.
Lift your foot.
Wow, look at those flower petals.
I took an introductory course
on Botany,
and I bet all these flowers
will wither by next weekend.
So that means...
we must meet again
before next weekend.
Does your father keep forcing you
to meet me?
I'm the daughter of
Changhwa Industrial,
so you must marry me, is that it?
To be honest,
it wasn't my first time seeing you
at the hotel.
I witnessed the car accident
in front of the hotel.
The whole time I was waiting...
for Ms. Lee Soo Ryeon
in the coffee shop,
I was thinking,
"Gosh. Who cares about this date?"
"I should've talked to that girl
from earlier."
But then...
you walked in...
as my date.
You didn't have to be Lee Soo Ryeon,
the daughter of Changhwa Industrial.
Even if you were Ms. Song Mal Ja...
or Ms. Kim Bok Soon,
it would've made no difference
to me.
It's done.
My goodness.
I can see
that you received good training.
If only you had passed the exam,
you would've made a great doctor.
Gosh. I said I passed.
Why can't you believe me?
It's not that I failed to graduate.
I chose not to.
Why would you choose not to?
Do you want to know why?
But if I tell you,
it'll mean we're close.
I'm entering
the University Song Festival.
What?
I'm not qualified once I graduate.
I can only enter it
because I'm still a student.
I can sing for you sometime.
Can we meet again
before the flowers wither?
Did you write the song yourself?
I did.
Then I'd love to.
The more I think about it,
the angrier I get.
To think how proudly they pointed
their fingers at me...
like they were independence fighters
or something.
They'd find fault
with whatever you do.
Don't let it bother you.
What's that anyway?
Oh, I came to return your clothes.
I'll return the blouse
after washing it.
Did you meet him again?
When? How?
I've been ignoring all his calls.
I ran into him.
I couldn't reach you,
so I just went to see him.
I couldn't answer the phone
because I was too upset.
Did anything special happen?
I'm meeting him once more soon.
But I feel so bad for lying to him.
Why did those punks have to kick
at the tofu I brought?
They could've just returned it
to me.
Sorry.
What were you saying?
I'm meeting the guy once more soon.
You don't have to anymore.
What?
You've done enough.
I only asked you to meet him
to get those punks out.
I'll still give you the money
for your airfare as promised,
so don't worry about that.
Thanks for all the trouble
you went to for me.
Soo Ryeon,
come downstairs for a moment.
You really didn't have to.
Soo Ryeon, get over here.
Mr. Hwang sent us
this precious gift.
A gift? What gift?
And his son brought it
all the way here in person.
You must be surprised
that I showed up unannounced,
Soo Ryeon.
(Youth of May)
This is Mr. Hwang's son.
- You know him well, don't you?
- What?
What kind of scheme brings you here?
I'm here to figure out your scheme.
I'd like to apologize.
Do you and Myeong Hee
know each other?
Would you mind writing down
your phone number here?
I'll write it
with a permanent marker.
Are you here to order rice cakes
for your wedding?
- Marriage?
- It seems like...
our parents are talking about it.
My in-laws are looking
for a business to invest in.
Hee Tae. How did you find my house?
- Just a moment.
- Do you drink?
I'll have just one glass, sir.
Are you drunk?
Can you sit with me for a moment?