ការកំណត់ពេលវេលានិងចំណងជើងរងនាំអ្នកដោយ kisskh.me
the លែងភ័យស្លន់ស្លោនៅពេលយប់ដាច់ភ្លើង black
♫អ្នកនៅក្បែរខ្ញុំហើយបំភ្លឺខ្ញុំ♫
be ចង្វាក់បេះដូងកើនឡើង, អុកស៊ីសែនថយចុះនៅពេលដែលភ្នែករបស់យើងជួប♫
breathing ការដកដង្ហើមរបស់អ្នកធ្វើអោយខ្ញុំថ្ពាល់ខ្ញុំ♫
♫ជាមួយអ្នកកំដៅឆាកឡើងសុភមង្គលមិនដែលឈានដល់ភាពជិតស្និតឡើយ
jok កំប្លែងគួរឱ្យធុញបន្ថែមភាពផ្អែមល្ហែមខ្លះទៅអាហារពេលល្ងាច♫
life ជីវិតរស់នៅប្រចាំថ្ងៃរឹតតែដូចជារឿងកំប្លែងជាងរឿងកំប្លែងខ្លួនឯងទៅទៀត
♫សុភមង្គលនិងទុក្ខព្រួយ♫
♫បង្កើតពេលវេលានៃជីវិត♫
days ថ្ងៃវស្សាកាន់តែពិសេសព្រោះអ្នក of
♫រើសមនុស្សណាម្នាក់អោយអាណិតនៅតាមផ្លូវ♫
♫មិនថាពេលណានិងកន្លែងណាទេអ្នកតែងតែបង្ហាញខ្លួន♫
♫កាន់ខ្ញុំយ៉ាងណែនហើយវិលជារង្វង់♫
days ថ្ងៃវស្សាធ្វើអោយខ្ញុំស្រងាកចិត្តព្រោះតែអ្នក♫
coming ក្លាយជាផ្នែកខ្លះនៃការចងចាំ♫
♫ដើរតាមផ្លូវដោយមានអំពូលភ្លើងបំភ្លឺគ្នាទៅវិញទៅមក♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr.Ling]
[Episode 3]
Hand.
I don't need your help anymore.
I can put on my clothes myself.
Not only was your service not up to par, you also saw every part of me.
Shouldn't you pay me for mental trauma?
W-W-Who extorts people like that?
Anyways...you pulled me, which is why I fell in.
It's not like I did it on purpose.
But you saw every part of me.
What's so great to look at on you? A dry stick like one of those telephone poles.
You make it seem like I want to look at you. Tsk!
Dry? How am I dry?
Whatever. I won't argue with you this time.
There's no need for payment either. Watch out next time.
122 total visits?
Why is it so little?
Poster, has your village just received Internet?
Who looks at this sort of story now?
-I'll take some space!
-Li Tao: Let me give you some advice, poster.
Stop drawing those wholesome boring things. How about some dominating boss cartoons?
Shut up! Shut up all of you!
Can you all stop being keyboard warriors?
I think she draws well. I really like these warmhearted stories.
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breathing grazes my cheek ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up someone pitiful off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
-What's wrong?
-Let me borrow your computer.
Alright. Thanks.
Don't mention it.
It seems you have a deep impression on my...dried up body.
Are you a pig, Gu Anxin? Are you a pig?
-Good morning!
-Morning.
[Zhao Shang Bank: A total of 6000 Yuan has been deposited in your bank account 0979 as of May 20th]
[Quick Arrival Delivery Service]
Where's my wheelchair? Where's my wheelchair? Where's my wheelchair?
Everyone! Welfare distribution here!
Here, here, here, here. Come take your gift. Everyone has one, everyone has one.
-Thank you!
-Good work these days, everyone.
Tonight, I'll treat everyone to dinner. How about it?
Ok!
-Manager Du.
-Anxin, long time no see.
This...I left for you.
Thank you.
Dinner tonight...you must come. Alright?
Go ahead and work.
-A toast!
-Thanks everyone!
Sister Anxin, I am the new person, Xiao Xu.
-Let me give a toast to you. Please take care of me.
-Please take care of me.
-Anxin...she can't drink alcohol.
-I can drink.
I'll drink this cup for her, alright?
Here, here, here.
Wooow, so manly!
-The car's here. Bye!
-Bye!
Bye! See you at the company tomorrow!
Ok, ok, ok!
Anxin, where do you live? I'll give you a ride.
I...live pretty close. The subway entrance
-takes me straight home.
-This place is really far from the subway entrance.
I'm worried if you go alone.
Give it to me. I'll take you. Let' go.
Let's go. Come.
Manager Du, my home is right ahead.
I'll just go home first. Thank you.
No need to always call me manager.
In the future, call me Du Ming.
I'll still call you Manager. I think that's more...polite.
Then I'll go up now.
Anxin, I-I think
these few days you've always been sending packages and speed deliveries.
You must be very tired.
- How about you help me with my work and account books?
-No need, no need, no need!
I like my life right now.
I also like this job as well.
I'll just go back first...
Anxin...wait a second!
I have something for you. Wait a moment.
Why do I have a bad feeling?
How cliche...
Anxin, I like you.
Ever since you came to our office, I've liked you!
I only dare to say this because of the alcohol.
When I was out of town these days, I've missed you everyday.
I know it's a little sudden,
but...please give me a chance.
I have a boyfriend...
-When was this?
-Just...a few days ago?
Few-
Where is he?
-He's not upstairs is he? You're living with him?
-No, no!
W-We're long distancing. He's not in this country.
That means I still have an opportunity.
Here, take it.
-J-Just take it. I'll leave now.
-N-No need...
W-Wait Manager Du!
Go.
Did you see the two vases I have at home?
No.
You seem to be in a good mood today.
So so.
What's up with you? Such a long face.
Something's up with the room.
No. In fact, there are bursts of rose fragrance. It smells pretty good.
It's already 11:20 PM.
You held up on 20 minutes of my sleeping time.
- If you come back so late—
- If you come back so late again next time,
you will have to compensate for my sleeping time.
You can also choose to...
Choose what?
Choose to sleep.
Acting so weird.
You're awake.
Why did you cover it? It will go bad.
It attracts flies.
It attracts flies? Where are there flies?
There are.
What's in that box?
Wait a moment.
As you requested, a wheelchair imported from Germany.
Try it.
- Imported from Germany?
- Yeah.
- This doesn't look too sturdy.
- How can that be? You have to look here.
This slender design and this flowing line.
It's perfect. And it's easy to fold,
and it's very lightweight.
Even if my leg wasn't broken I'd want to sit on it.
How about you give it a try?
How is it?
This is manual?
Manual...
Don't you have a broken leg that prevents you from getting exercise?
You can just treat it as exercise, it's good for your health.
Look. Now I only owe you 108,800 yuan.
(~$17,000)
Agree?
You didn't spend your money on this wheelchair imported from Germany, right?
Smart.
Ever since you arrived, the water bills, electricity bills, and living expenses,
multiple fees are increasing nonstop.
I have difficulties. Try to understand them.
Try it.
I forgot.
I'll push you around.
How is it? Don't you think it's pretty nice?
Look outside the window.
You have to get used to using this.
Try it for yourself. I'll take out the trash.
Throw the flowers away too.
Quite wasteful.
[Novotel]
The project from last time...we really aren't including Nan Xi?
I heard the rate of return is very high.
Many people want to get a share.
Then do they know...that project
hasn't even received approval?
Wow, you!
No wonder you aren't eating meat right by your lips.*(Not taking advantage of something right in front of you)
So you already knew there was a problem. As expected of Gu Xin'er.
A toast!
Sha Sha?
Sorry, I mistook you for my first love.
As an apology, can I treat you to a drink?
This guy's pickup lines are so old-school.
Why are you being a stranger?
What are you doing?
Why did you hit me? Security!
He hit me! Hurry and catch him!
Hey, you've caught the wrong person!
Xiao Shen?
You were that little wild kid who always said they'd marry Xin'er?
- Long time no see.
A tiger has five mountain holes in front of him.
Then every hole has a lamb.
However he only went into the second hole.
Do you know why?
Because the lamb in the second hole is fatter.
No.
Because he can go into whatever hole he wants to.
That's a joke?
No.
I attended a prize event while walking in the market today.
They gave me two movie tickets.
You're lucky enough to receive movie tickets?
Then go by yourself.
I...don't need two tickets.
That's right...
Then give me one.
I'll put it up for you for sale.
No need. It can't be sold for much.
Even though a mosquito's small, it still eats meat.*(A small thing is still valuable)
How about I gift it to you?
The movie's on Friday at 8 pm.
You...should be off work then...
I don't have time...
Anyways, the movie's on Friday at 8 pm. Come if you want.
Anxin, we might have to get off late again today.
-Why?
-There was a notification just now saying there was a batch of products organized incorrectly.
But you see...Fei Fei and Xiao Yan have already left.
-But today I-
-Sister, please don't let me work overtime by myself.
-I can only stay with you for awhile.
-Ok, ok, ok. That's fine. We can finish it quickly.
-Ok.
-Thank you.
Hi Sir, here is the popcorn you wanted.
Hello, how can I help you?
Here. Anxin. Anxin!
There's these too.
Hello, welcome to Movie City.
The 8'ock screening of Zootopia
Is now allowing the watchers to come in and get their tickets checked.
Viewers who bought tickets for the current screening
please come to the gate to have your ticket checked.
Thank you for your cooperation and enjoy the movie.
We are finally done.
-Oh no!
-What happened?
I had an appointment with a friend to watch a movie at 8'ock.
8 pm! If you go now, it might already be over!
Xiao Ba?
No way.
You didn't watch it?
There's no point in watching it alone.
-A coworker...
-Don't worry about it.
Let's go.
Wait!
Wait a second.
How can we miss the movie you wanted to watch?
I'll treat you to this movie, so it's on me.
Then let's go.
I'll hold it for you.
Let me hold you.
Walk slowly.
Oh my god!
Anxin.
Nothing, go to sleep.
Good night.
Anxin.
Nothing, go to sleep. Good night.
Good night.
Did he really leave?
The words he didn't say last night,
Was that a farewell?
The movie tickets were a farewell gift?
This is a bit big.
Can you hold it later?
Anxin?
Anxin! Why are you dozing off? The package.
Oh, Phoenix Neighborhood?
What's wrong? You're not in the right mind today.
Nothing, I probably didn't sleep well.
Kind person, have some pity on me.
Give me some food.
Have some pity on me.
Kind person, please give me some food.
Please have pity on me.
Please give me some food.
Kind person.
Please have some pity on me.
Xiao Yan, something came up at home!
Can I switch shifts with you?
What happened?
My house... my house's cat is missing.
-You raised a cat?
-Just a cat that grew up with me.
There's a problem with its legs, and we suddenly lost it.
Can we switch shifts?
Okay.
Boss!
Did you see the guy that smashed all your beer?
No.
Thank you.
Okay, go play with them.
Doctor Xiao!
That's really you?
Is your leg
okay?
It's fine.
You are pretty smart to guess it was me right away.
Of course.
Besides you, who else knows I would be here every weekend?
Besides you, who else would be so psychotic to send me a message using binary.
Did you get what I sent you?
It's here. Your report.
Thank you.
Give me your wallet.
Give it to me.
My-
I-
Ask Ai Li to reimburse you.
That's fine with me.
Do you really not want me to take a look at your leg?
Lawyer Chen,
what you mean is that my father wants to give 50% of the shares to this women?
That's right. Jin Guan is no longer in this world.
Based on the policy,
the shares will be transferred to that girl.
Daughter?
Could it be his secret daughter?
I don't know if it's his secret daughter,
but he has always been looking for her.
Then that means, as long as we have her 50% of the share
the inheritor position wouldn't depend on the old man's choice. Right?
My brother always knows about this?
Right, Lawyer Chen?
Then who am I?
You don't know who you are?
First pay the fee, then take the bill to get medicine.
Hello, can I borrow your phone?
Thank you.
-Hello, who is this?
-It's me.
President Ling?
As long as you are fine, I can rest assured.
Is there any movement on Ling Fang's side?
Ling Fang's people have followed me the whole day.
If nothing unexpected comes up, this matter definitely has to do with them.
-Is there evidence?
-As of right now, no.
Then I won't make an appearance yet and observe for changes.
I'll wait for them to fall for the bait.
President Ling, where are you right now? Let me prepare somewhere for you to stay.
No need.
I found the girl, the CEO want's to find.
300,000 yuan? Are you blackmailing me?
Then let's call the police, a collision is not a minor charge.
So, how about...
You can stay at my house.  00:32:33,950
Xiao Ba! Where is my toothbrush?
When I used the restroom, I by accident knocked it over and it fell into the toilet.
-What is this?
-A toothbrush.
You seem to relate to this a lot.
Because I was also adopted.
[DNA result for Gu Anxin. Paternal index for 0.09. Less than 0.0001]
Good thing she wasn't the CEO's secret daughter.
It's me, how has it been?
For the matter concerning when the company's firewall was attacked by a secret group,
we have already found their location with the IP address you provided.
It's President Ling Fang and them.
Don't worry. I have already fixed the firewall.
Do everything according to plan.
That's right. There's a new e-commerce business called Fei Te.
Recently, they've continually hooked away our people.
They claim that those who leave Niu Wei
can receive double the salary.
The fish are about to bite the hook.
Also recently President Ling Fang has been hiring people to find out more about Miss Anxin.
What did he find out?
He didn't find out anything so far.
Watch him closely, don't let him find out about Anxin.
Okay, don't worry.
Tell me honestly.
Don't tell me you're some kind of wanted criminal, gangster,
or someone who committed misconduct, so you're hiding in my house because you're scared that you'll be found.
If I were a wanted criminal,
I would have made a move on you first.
After all, you're all by yourself,
and you're gorgeous.
♫ Those times we want to wipe away tears ♫
♫ Those times we withdraw our hand ♫
Wait here. I'll go turn off the water.
♫ No need for right and wrong in a relationship, how dull ♫
♫ Look at me, don't avoid me ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
Let me push you around.
Take a look outside the window.
♫ The fragility of a hug ♫
How can you miss the movie you want to watch?
Consider this as me treating you. It's on me.
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Without walking through it ♫
♫ how could you understand ♫
Sorry. Excuse me.
Have you seen a boy with fair and clean complexion,
- riding a wheelchair?
- No, we haven't.
Thank you.
Xiao Ba!
Where are you?
I won't kick you out again. Do you hear me?
I heard you.
Where did you go?
♫ Meeting unexpectedly, those lost memories ♫
♫ Without logic, too much like comedy ♫
♫ That day of bad weather ♫
♫ was good fortune that brought you into my life ♫
♫ The ambiguous atmosphere spreads around us ♫
♫ Unbelievably stimulates telepathy ♫
♫ The you who appears cold ♫
♫ starts to reveal your childish self ♫
So you heard everything I said earlier?
I wasn't the only person who heard what you said.
The whole street heard you. You can't go back on your promise.
♫ The hint of fate was already present ♫
I just went out for a walk.
♫ Resting against each other in sleep that dark night ♫
What do you mean, you went for a walk? You were out for so long.
You left so suddenly and didn't give any notice.
Not having a phone is really inconvenient.
I am truly a little...
short of  money.
- Where did you get the money to buy so much RIO alcopop?
- I picked it up.
No way, you can even pick up money while going for a walk? Where's the money?
I spent it all.
You spent it all?
Then what if they come to square accounts with you?
Don't I still have you?
Am I your ATM machine?
Let's go home.
If you weren't sleeping, why didn't you make a sound?
I just wanted to see what you'd do to me in the middle of the night instead of sleeping.
What I would do to you?
There's no need for you to worry about that.
Drink together?
This is mine.
Impressive.
In the future, let me help you with any physical tasks like opening bottles.
Okay.
Then in the future, for physical tasks like household chores,
I'll also leave them to you, how's that?
You're really getting more and more arrogant.
Do you need me to remind you who the creditor is?
I'm only making a joke.
Just casual talk.
Although after enough time, this angry bird look of yours
is actually quite cute.
Who's angry?
Just always stay by my side like this.
[Harmony]
President Ling Fang, I saw someone today I suspect to be Ling Yue.
But I lost his trail.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Clearly, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫រឿងរបស់យើងទើបតែចាប់ផ្តើមទេ begun
♫ប៉ុន្តែការចង់បានយូរមិនអាចបញ្ឈប់បានឡើយ
ស្វែងរកផ្លូវដើម្បីត្រឡប់មករកអ្នកវិញ♫
♫រឿងរបស់យើងទើបតែចាប់ផ្តើមទេ begun
♫ការប្រើគុណនាមដ៏ស្រស់ស្អាតបំផុតរបស់ខ្ញុំទាំងអស់♫
still នៅតែមិនទាន់គ្រប់គ្រាន់ដើម្បីពិពណ៌នាឈ្មោះរបស់អ្នក♫
♫រឿងរ៉ាវរបស់យើងគឺរឿងរបស់យើងទាំងស្រុង♫
pal បាតដៃរបស់យើងកាន់គន្លឹះទៅអនាគត to
♫ប្រើស្នេហាដើម្បីបើកយឺត ៗ ♫