[Please]
[Express Your]
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫  Your breathing is nestled close to my face  ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage, happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up someone pitiful off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 2]
Oh right, I should warn you.
In the dead of night, as you lie on the couch,
there are 84 cockroaches in this house.
Just in case at night, they crawl and crawl and crawl,
and crawl onto the couch,
take care.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by Rabbit and Wolf Team @ Viki.com
[Cockroach pesticide]
One cockroach can produce 84 larvae.
Just in case at night, they crawl and crawl and crawl...
You didn't stay awake all night, did you?
I was just scaring you. How could the cockroach go onto the couch?
You've watched Infestation too many times.
Where are you going?
I'm going to buy you some pesticide to keep you from driving yourself crazy.
- Then I'll go too.
- I'm fine going by myself.
I'm not worried about you. I'm worried about myself.
"I'm not worried about you. I'm worried about myself." Who wants your worry?
[Bargain price: ¥9.90]
Green tea flavor...
You scared me!
Get this one.
[Hot-selling: ¥49.90]
Let me tell you,
this one has nice, showy packaging, but it's actually not very good.
This one is simple and definitely effective. We'll get this one. Let's go.
Then let's buy both and see which is better.
Fine, fine, we'll buy yours. We'll buy yours.
I—
Are you satisfied?
Coward.
Let me borrow your phone.
- What for?
- I want to look something up.
Are you done?
Did you do this?
You just used my phone and it became like this.
You did it, didn't you?
It looks like you're a coward too.
Get rid of it, get rid of it.
This code is only effective for thirty minutes.
After thirty minutes, it will automatically stop.
I'm telling you, I have a full day of work today. I'm very busy.
You just stay at home and do nothing, you hear me?
[New Way]
Nana!
Did you hear? The President has already died.
Where did you hear that from?
All of the gossip groups on the work forum have been spreading it.
The upper levels of Ling Group are afraid it will affect the company's stock price, so they haven't made it public.
But the general shareholder's meeting has already secretly begun making arrangements.
If the President really died, then won't we all have to leave?
I'm telling you this in confidence, you can't tell anyone else.
I've heard Fei Te is hiring. We better make preparations as soon as possible.
The President of Ling Group, Ling Yue, has been missing since falling into the ocean half a month ago.
Ling Group's subsidiary Niu Wei has also been in constant turmoil. Its technology was almost leaked by hackers.
Breaking news! The President already has no chance of return.
Ling Group is already secretly preparing a funeral.
Our reporter found Niu Wei's current representative to seek confirmation.
With regards to the false rumors spreading on the internet, we have already found an attorney.
We will use the law to protect our rights and interests.
We ask our friends in the media to stop making wild guesses.
You can't run all over the place.
If you get hurt, no one will look after you.
[Lost Dog]
How come I didn't think of it?
Am I that attractive?
Narcissist.
Then why are you taking pictures of me?
I'm helping you find your home. I'm taking pictures of you
so when your family sees your picture, they'll contact me.
That way, you can go home.
Don't delete them!
Stop messing around! Give it back!
What do you want to do, leaning so close to me?
I don't want to do anything. Don't think that way.
There's something off.
I think there's something off about  you.
Tell me the truth.
Surely you're not some kind of
wanted criminal from the underworld
who broke the law and then hid in my house, afraid to be found?
If I was a wanted criminal, I would take care of you first.
You are alone after all, and are appetizing.
Don't take care of me.
If you hurt me, your 250k will be gone.
You haven't finished giving back the money,
so how could I finish you off?
I will return it to you!
No matter how far and where you are, I will return your money to you.
But right now, it's just very inconvenient for a guy and a girl to live together.
Just let me take a photo of you.
Look this way. Turn around.
So...you really want me to leave?
Xiao Ba, come here. Open the flashlight! It's so dark!
Don't you have a phone?
Right...
That's not right. I remember I just paid the electric fee.
Have you received a blackout notification?
The night before yesterday, I saw it in the stairwell.
It said it would stop tonight from 9 to 11 pm.
Because of electrical maintenance, there will be a temporary blackout.
No wonder.
Why is your bracelet so ugly?
How is my bracelet ugly?
Are you 800 degrees nearsighted or astigmatic?
Why do you keep wearing something so ugly?
My brother gave me this. It can block out nightmares.
That's to trick little kids.
Don't talk if you don't understand.
You seem to really care about him.
That's right.
He's my closest family.
What's this?
I made a bracelet that filters nightmares.
Not only is it pretty, it'll also eat all your nightmares.
Really?
There won't be electricity for awhile anyways. I'll tell you a story.
In the past, there was an old king.
He wanted to find an inheritor. Therefore,
he called his three sons to him
and said...said I'm old.
I am going to pass down the throne to you.
You three must battle and decide the inheritor.
After it began, the third prince threw away his sword first.
He said...between his two brothers,
I am the weakest.
And I don't have any ability to inherit this country.
I choose to give up.
Now...only the first and second prince are left.
Throughout their fight, the second prince's sword
already brushed against the first prince's neck. However, he hesitated.
At that moment...the first prince took advantage of the second prince.
And then?
And then the first prince won.
This king just watched his sons kill each other?
The king believed in a cruel and savage education.
He didn't even care for the life of his second son.
I think maybe he just didn't like this second son.
Maybe...
his birth was a mistake.
What do you mean?
He's an adopted son.
Adopted son?
What's wrong?
You seem to relate?
Because I'm also adopted.
I'm kidding! Are you a pig? Believing in me like that.
Alright. Sleep early. I'm going to go sleep.
What's wrong?
You forgot to take this.
I'll be outside. Call me if you need anything.
What could happen?
Anyways, even if I needed help what use would you be with that crippled leg?
How come you old fellows
have time to come see me today?
Chairman, how could you say that?
The doctor says you need to rest.
How could we dare to disturb you with normal little problems?
That's right, Old Ling.
Right now, it's crazy outside.
They all say Xiao Yue has met misfortune.
The company's workers are all uneasy as well.
That secretary that he has
isn't of the Ling family. He can't replace Xiao Yue.
That's right. We should quickly choose a new President
to replace Xiao Yue's position.
My son's life and death is still uncertain,
yet you all have started to form alliances already?
Old Ling, we don't mean it that way.
-Then what do you mean?
-Everyone's worked so hard all these years,
so we can only be well if the Ling family is doing well. We don't have any selfish ideas.
Let me think about this matter.
I am tired. Please leave.
Then...we will head over now.
Hey! Did you see my Transformer?
No.
What are you hiding?
-Nothing!
-Let me see!
Isn't it just a stupid spinning top? Why are you hiding it?
Acting all weird.
I'm warning you. Don't you dare tell mom and dad.
Or else just you wait!
Here, eat some more.
Xiao Yue! Xiao Yue!
What's wrong?
Morning.
Xiao Ba!
Where's my toothbrush?
I accidentally knocked it into the toilet when I was using the restroom.
C-Can I beg you
to not touch my things?
Then...I'll help you take it out?
How could I put something you picked back up into my mouth?
Makes sense.
[You You]
Xiao Ba, don't talk.
Hello, You You?
Anxin! I have good news! I saw Mike!
He's so much more handsome than in TV!
Then did you take a photo with him?
Of course! I'll be back in a few days.
Can you let me live at your place for a few days?
I don't want to go home, or else my parent's will remind me about marriage again.
No. These few days don't work out.
Why not? Could you have
hidden a man in your home?
Its-No, no, the company held a training session and chose me.
They want me to go train outside of the city for a few days.
So you can't live here.
I'm scaring you! Alright.
Then I'll play a few more days before coming back! Bye!
Bye...
I noticed you're pretty good at coming up with stories.
I can also not make them up.
You move out and make some space.
It's alright.
I think the way you speak nonsense is pretty cute.
Oh, right. Remember to help me buy a wheelchair.
Imported from Germany.
Imported from Germany?
Then isn't that several thousand...
Aren't you about to receive money?
H-How do you know?
You talk about it everyday. "I'm getting paid on Wednesday."
You scared me...
Huh? Why does my right eyelid keep twitching?
Grandpa Liu.
-Grandpa Liu, your grandson sent you some good food!
-Hey Anxin.
Here.
There's a new one today?
The joy of getting a package is no longer what's in it,
But it's to see what your new manga is about.
-I'm glad you like it. I'm going to leave first.
-Okay. Walk safely!
I'm leaving.
What is the new perfume you're using? It smells really good.
Layered Fragrance. This perfume is not bad.
You can try it too.
Isn't it Gu Anxin?
Anxin? Is it really you?
What a coincidence.
-Gu Anxin, it's been so long since we have last seen each other.
You are still the same.
Nancy, you know her?
Of course. We went to the same school.
Did you guys know, this delivery girl
was the adopted daughter that was abandoned by the Gu family.
Adopted daughter? The one who was kicked out of school?
-Ya!
-Nancy.
Stop talking.
Give me President Wei's namecard.
Anxin, this is the business my friend opened.
You can go look for him,
he will give you a good job.
No need. The job I have now is pretty good.
-Just take it.
I really don't need it. Thank you.
You are already in dire straits and you are still so arrogant.
She's helping you because she finds you pitiful.
You are really uneducated.
There's really no upbringing at all.
What are you doing?
People like me without any upbringing won't know what actions I would take.
Please watch what you say.
I'm leaving.
Take this.
Oh yeah, Nancy. About your boyfriend's project
our company won't be investing in it.
This decision is from top management. Please relay this message to him.
Wait, Xin'er.
Gu Xin'er!
How can they do that?
You bastard, get out of this family.
Why did you tattletale to Dad?
I- I didn't.
It was you. After you came everything has changed.
It's because of you!
It's because of you, you bastard.
It signifies wealth when the left eyelid twitches.
What are you trying to do?
I'm asking you. What are you trying to do?
I'm talking to you.
I am the victim, why are you acting like that?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you shaking?
Are you scared of water?
Wait here.
♫ Look at me, don't avoid me.  ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Let me try to touch your hard shell  ♫
Wait here. I'll go close the water.
♫ Hug me lightly  ♫
♫ give me the last of yourself  ♫
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Without walking it before  ♫
♫ how would you understand ♫
♫ Look at me, don't avoid me.  ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Let me try to touch your hard shell  ♫
♫ The fragility of hugging  ♫
♫ Hug me lightly ♫
♫ give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Without walking it before  ♫
♫ how would you understand ♫
Why are you looking at me?
Nothing.
Your holding the magazine backwards.
Let me calculate this with you.
Based on today, you are responsible for everything.
Maintenance: $490.
Spanner, ¥$30.
Thread seal tape, ¥$10.
Tee pipe, ¥$20.
Faucet: $35
Water pipe: $53.23
Pliers: $15
In total it is...
$653.23
I understand.
Oh ya, we can clean these things tomorrow.
But you need to help too.
Even if your hurt, you need to help.
What's wrong.
Aren't you cold?
The weather forecast says today is 30 degrees.
There's a big difference between indoor and outdoor room temperature.
So weird...
You have something here.
Just-let me help.
Do you know how many germs are on a bottlecap?
How many?
1.59 million.
Wow.
And it's easy to hurt your teeth resulting in gum infection and enamel buildup.
It does sound pretty scary.
Hurry and eat. We still need to go to the hospital afterwards.
Doctor, are you really sure everything's normal?
Of course it's normal. It's not like he's hurt anywhere else.
Was I too rough?
No. Is the doctor married?
Doctor Liu? He doesn't even have a girlfriend, so who could he be married to.
Everyone's too busy working in the hospital. No one has time to date.
Sometimes, I'll walk around at home.
What about you?
No.
Then do you have a girlfriend?
Right there.
Aren't you brother and sister?
Isn't it the trend right now to call each other brother and sister?
I still have something to ask you.
His leg is healing well,
but right now I think his head has some problems.
Just...he often
says and does some very odd things.
I don't know what's wrong with him.
The CT scan of his head is perfectly fine.
What you're saying must be after the patient is injured, his mental health is impacted as well.
The patient's family must slowly make sure he recovers.
Can you keep walking?
I'm alright.
Watch out!
So accurate?
Oh my...
You aren't hurt?
How could I be hurt? I've trained before.
Trained?
I catch quick delivery.
Wait.
The skin's broken.
What's wrong with that? It's a small problem.
What are you doing?
It doesn't hurt?
It doesn't hurt...it's just a small injury.
I-It's a small injury. I'll do it myself.
Alright.
Thank you.
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up someone pitiful off the street ♫
Hurry! Hurry! The rain's getting heavier! Hurry!
The rain's so heavy. Let's call a car.
[Confirm service]
Let's keep waiting. Bus 23 will be arriving soon.
It's here! It's here! Let's go, let's go!
I'm sorry. It's 25, but I thought it was 23. So it was 25...
Call a car! I'll pay.
W-Why are you taking off your clothes?
What? You don't need to shower after getting rained on?
Y-You shower but you don't need to take your clothes off in front of me. Go inside and take them off.
Oh, right. I forgot to tell you.
The showerhead is broken, so you can only use the bath tub.
Go and shower first. I'll shower after you shower.
I need you to help me.
Help you do what?
Help me shower.
What are you thinking about?
What am I thinking of?
Or are you expecting something?
W-What's there to expect?
Y-Your foot's hurt, not your hand.
You can shower normally before, but you can't today?
But I need to bathe today.
What's the difference?
The difference is that I, an injured person, cannot sit into that bathtub.
Figure it out yourself.
100 a time.
200.
Your good?
Then I'll leave.
Wait.
I can't reach the shampoo.
Gu Anxin!
Hand.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Clearly, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up ♫