Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 29
Your Highness,
if you have any problems,
you can go to Mr. Shi Jin.
Mr. Shi is loyal to you.
You can trust him.
Your Grace is right.
But about this,
it’s embarrassing
to get Mr. Shi involved.
What a big issue is it
that Mr. Shi can’t get involved?
Since only families are here,
I’m just getting straight to the point.
Luo brought Shi Feixian
back to his mansion directly.
Is it true?
Do Her Highness and His Majesty know?
Father feels not so well now.
It’s better not to worry him.
Zhang, you’re always like this.
You become so hesitant
as long as you’re facing
with Prince Luo’s issues.
It’s clear that he’s the person who sent
assassins to kill His Grace earlier.
But you covered for him and
blamed it to Prime Minister Yan’s men.
Princess Ban,
it can’t be judged merely
by your verbal statement.
If you have any proof,
please ask the Court of Judicial Review
to investigate it.
Otherwise, please watch your mouth,
not to destroy the harmony.
Crown Princess,
are you indulging Prince Luo?
Jiang Luo even tried to kill His Grace.
He may get worse later.
Hua, you’re worrying too much.
Though Luo is impulsive,
he’s not a bad man.
I just want to remind you here.
You’re indulging Prince Luo,
but he won’t thank you for that.
It’s you!
What did I do?
Don’t put on an act here!
I’m in this situation now.
Are you happy?
You gave me so many contraceptive herbs.
Are you satisfied
with my thank-you gift, Mr. Xie?
Shi Feixian,
aren’t you afraid I’ll kill you
since you keep me alive?
The injured people
are better to be peaceful.
Well.
I’m coming to tell you
Crown Prince sent a troop last night.
Your Fude House
has been a history.
His Highness has a weak character.
How could he do this?
His Highness couldn’t do it.
But Count Cheng’an could.
Now you have only two options.
You can choose to assist
Prince Luo to ascend the thrown with me,
or choose to perish together with me.
Whatever your choice is,
I shall take on you to the end.
Why are you here?
Wanyu.
His Highness is worrying
about his injury,
so he especially asked me to come.
I will take care of my brother.
You don’t need to come.
Take good care of Mr. Xie then.
His Highness is so worrying
about his injury.
If he is really worried,
why doesn’t he come in person?
Why call her to put on the act?
Here. Chongjin.
You’re prince’s wife.
How can you stay so long
in your parents’ home?
I’ll ask someone to escort you back.
He doesn’t like me at all.
What do I go back for?
Go back now.
Apologize to Prince Luo.
Beg him to keep you in his mansion!
Shi Feixian is living
in his mansion now.
Do you still want me to beg him?
Wanyu!
I’m useless now.
If you are also abandoned,
who else can the Xies rely on?
Wanyu.
Father is getting old now.
He’s going to retire soon.
Qilin is blind.
He can’t be an official for this life.
And I…
I am a disabled man
who can’t even have a child.
Do you really want to see
Xie family declining
and being a joke?
I…
Now Xie family
can only rely on you.
Qingyu House
Hua, Count Cheng’an.
His Majesty is really generous
this time.
Thanks to His Grace.
Go.
Qingyu House
Look at that. Look. Look.
It’s so beautiful!
So His Majesty cares about Hua so much.
He plants Hua’s favorite peonies.
Your Grace,
when Huahua moves in,
you can draw more pictures for it.
What name do you think
we can call this house?
Bai
Baishou House
Baishou House.
What does it mean?
It’s called Baishou House.
Hope I can live together with you
till an old age.
Here. Put a bet!
Half chance!
Win as much as you bet!
Pay you as much as you bet!
Come on! Put a bet!
Put down!
Put!
It’s such a surprise that
Princess Ban and Count Cheng’an
are really getting married!
I wonder it’s Princess Ban’s luck
or Count Cheng’an’s luck.
Red color represents the Bans and Rongs
will tie the knot.
The black one means they won’t.
Come on. Put a bet!
Young Master Ban,
have you bet on it?
Certainly.
I bet on the black one.
You really have the heart to bet that.
-Yeah.
-What do you know?
I never win a bet.
So the black one means
my sister will get married smoothly.
I bet on the red one.
Change it.
I’ve got some business. I’m going.
You can keep playing. Bye.
-Bye.
-Don’t leave.
When I saw you last time,
you were fancy like a peacock.
Why are you like
a roasted chicken today?
What? Prince Luo abused you?
I’m not in good mood today.
I don’t want to argue with you.
I see.
Does your sister betray you
and take your Prince Wude?
Ban Heng, have you done?
Or do you feel annoyed
because you haven’t cooked for long?
Do you know
where I can get
some nice almond shortcakes in the city?
Almond shortcakes?
When I’m in bad mood,
I’d like to eat almond shortcakes.
But today I’ve hunted
the cake shops all over the city.
They are either too sweet or too dry.
Almond shortcakes…
Actually,
if you can make cakes,
I can lend you the kitchen in my home.
Really?
But in one condition,
that is,
you must allow me to have a taste.
It’s done.
Come on. Have a taste.
Taste it.
It’s hot.
What do you think?
Good.
Xie Wanyu.
I can’t believe that your cook skills
are so good.
I will also find a wife
who can cook well.
There are few girls
who can cook in the city.
Indeed.
It’s a pity that you’re prince’s wife.
I can’t…
I mean,
you’re prince’s wife. You can’t cook.
What’re you thinking?
Whoever you want to marry
is none of my business.
It has nothing to do with you
that who I want to marry.
I can marry anyone.
Why are you worrying so much?
It’s more than my sister does.
Let me tell you.
Since childhood, my sister
has been so good at boasting herself.
Who are you bad-mouthing?
Hua. Hua.
Oh, good.
He praises your cooking every day.
I happen to need your favor.
Chef Selection of Ban’s Mansion
Chef selection of Ban’s mansion
is beginning now.
You two can leave first.
You haven’t tasted yet.
How come you just ask them to leave?
A good dish should be a perfect
combination of color, aroma and taste.
Those two are too ugly.
No need to taste them.
You can leave, too.
You three’s specialties
are in different styles.
It’s hard
to judge them now.
You. You’re eliminated.
Why?
You’re easy to sweat. It’s unhygienic.
Go. Go. Go.
Congratulations, you two.
You can throw your dishes away now.
They’ve left.
Why are you still here?
It’s such a good dish.
What a pity to throw it away!
The person who cherishes ingredients
and knows what a good dish is
is a good chef.
Princess Ban, it’s her.
Celebratory Bedding and Clothing
Are there some high-quality quilts
in this shop?
My princess is finally getting married.
We should choose the best ones.
You can rest assured.
I’ve found someone
to ask around before we come.
It’s the best shop
in the city, even in the country.
Really?
Let’s go.
Celebratory Bedding and Clothing
Are you choosing quilts for wedding?
-Exactly!
Not for us.
It’s for my young master and her lady.
Do you need me to introduce for you?
No. We can pick.
Okay. Take your time then.
I’m available at any time.
This one is good.
My young master likes quiet colors.
But my princess likes those beautiful
and big ones.
Why do you need it to be so big?
Princess kicks her quilt off a lot.
I think she kicks people a lot.
What do you mean?
What do you…?
It is improper for men and women
to touch each other.
Do you think you are qualified?
I…
Ban’s Mansion
Anle.
Anle, why are you here?
I heard that you’re getting married.
You didn’t tell me.
So I have to come here myself.
Don’t play joke on me.
But when will you remarry?
So many people are adoring me.
I can’t decide whom I’ll marry with
in a short time.
There’s no time.
I’m here to bring you to my mansion.
I haven’t met Hua for long.
Now I’m bringing her to my mansion
to have a chat.
Would you mind it, Count Cheng’an?
I dare not reject
Your Highness’s invitation.
But it’s getting dark early in spring.
I hope Your Highness can consider that.
Rest assured.
I’ll definitely send Hua
back to you safely.
Anle,
why do you take me to
your princess’s mansion?
Silly girl. You’re getting married.
There’ll be no chance to go crazy. Go.
What’re you going to do?
Young Master,
Princess Ban has really gone
to Princess Anle’s mansion.
Hua and Her Highness
haven’t met for long.
They must have a lot to talk about.
But I heard that
Princess Anle
called all her followers to the mansion.
Be careful not to get cold,
Young Master.
This…
This is the happy single banquet
I prepare for you specially.
They are all thoroughly accomplished
in lyre-playing, and painting.
You can choose whatever you want
to listen and watch today.
It’s… It’s hard to choose.
You’re right.
How about I introduce
two young men to you?
This one is Mr. Zhang.
You’ll not be bored
by his face, even for a hundred years.
To be honest,
it can be compared
with that of Count Cheng’an, can’t it?
This girl…
This is Mr. Wang.
A man?
You two must can get along well.
He’s a famous singer in the city.
If you want to listen to any operas,
you can ask him to sing it for you.
Rong’an Mansion
Your Grace.
If you don’t know which one to choose,
how about you show yourselves to her?
Please rest assured, Your Highness.
We will take good care of Her Grace!
Rest assured.
Don’t. Anle.
I’ve been engaged.
Your Grace.
Sir, do you have anything to talk?
Why are you getting so close to me?
If I remember it right,
I didn’t invite you to come today.
Your Highness, sorry for the rudeness.
I happened to pass by.
I notice the trees are in blossom,
so I decided to come in
to enjoy the scenery.
Enjoy the scenery?
Then why are you holding two
buckets of water?
You’ve misunderstood me, Your Highness.
I saw that they were getting close.
I thought they were up to no good.
So I drove them away with water.
Hua, I take you back to change.
It’s not convenient today.
I’ll come another day.
Come again?
Go.
How can you go back
with your wet clothes?
Do you think I’m lack
of clothes in my mansion?
If Hua wears your clothes,
I’m afraid it’s an arrogation crime.
It’s my mansion.
I have the final say.
He’s right.
As Ban’s Mansion is not far away,
I don’t want to bother you.
Silly girl, don’t talk.
I’m helping you.
Helping me?
Don’t you want to see
Count Cheng’an being jealous?
Hua, let’s go.
Actually it’s okay
to change clothes here.
Yes.
I have not only many
beautiful clothes here,
but someone to serve Hua to get changed.
I will serve her.
No. I will.
-I will serve her.
-I will. I will.
No need.
Her Grace is only used
to the customized green tea soaps.
She is uncomfortable outside.
It’s better to go back.
It’s also good
to change the flavors occasionally.
Hua.
No one here knows
the water temperature Hua uses.
What if she gets cold?
What if she’s burned?
You keep saying no to my offers.
Are you going to bathe her yourself
when Hua goes home?
Anle, what’re you talking about?
Your Highness, the joke goes too far.
We are famous for our gentleness.
Your Grace can just enjoy.
Yeah. We’re so gentle.
If Count Cheng’an doesn’t
want to bathe Hua,
I have many people here
who’re willing to do it.
I’ll bathe her!
A word uttered cannot be taken back.
Don’t go back on your words,
Count Cheng’an.
Go back.
Your Grace,
what’s wrong?
It’s only been two days.
You have planted so many flowers.
So amazing.
I won’t have you bathe me.
Don’t be shy, Your Grace.
After drying yourself,
just go back to your room.
Are you still jealous?
Open the door first.
We can talk about it.
You poured me water.
I haven’t blamed you for that.
Now are you mad at me first?
Come out or not?
I will tell my father and
ask him to kick your ass.
I’m wrong.
I will admit my mistakes
to Duke Jingting someday.
You…!
You can just stay inside for your life!
Once I think of
the powerful chest
of Mr. Qin,
I feel safe.
How about I borrow him from Anle
and ask him to be my bodyguard?
Don’t you dare!
I never know
you’re a jealous man.
I’m a gentleman
who takes country development
as my responsibility.
How will I be jealous
of those followers?
Alright. It’s my mistake.
I didn’t intend to go there.
After all, all men in the world
can’t be compared with you.
Is it right?
Look at me.
I promise.
Even if
there are a thousand handsome men
in front of me,
I won’t see them. Really.
If they force me to see,
I’ll blind myself
to keep your purity.
If all people in the world
are so good at talking like you,
the Court of Judicial Review may
find it hard to settle a lawsuit.
The peonies are so beautiful.
What to do if they wither?
They may get ugly.
When we move in after getting married,
we’ll live here together forever.
There’ll surely be the blossom time.
By then,
I hope
I can be carefree like now.
Your Grace, you can chop
firewood over there.
And I can primp myself in the room.
If you are drawing pictures,
I can play the Qin
by your side.
What do you mean?
I…
Are you saying
that I can’t play it well?
No. Not at all.
I think that as you still miss
beautiful tunes.
I’m so pleased.
Well.
Between that I play swords
and I play the Qin,
what will you choose?
Play swords then.
It must be so pleasant
to see you play swords here.
Look at you.
You’re saying I can’t play the Qin well.
Hua, listen to me.
I didn’t mean that.
I mean, you…
You don’t deserve the Qin.
Hua, I didn’t mean that.
I… Hua. Hua.
Shen Nong’s Herbal Classic
Miss, I’ve served the soup
to Miss Wanyu.
Change clothes for me then.
If it’s late,
the soup will be cold.
Yes.
Are you afraid?
Don’t drink that!
What do you mean?
The soup is mine. You can’t drink it.
How precious is your soup?
You can drink it,
why can’t Miss Wanyu?
Shi Feixian, what’s your problem?
Let’s talk it through today.
You’ve misunderstood me.
But the soup…
The Huanhua herb!
Isn’t it a kind of contraceptive herb?
Miss, she’s hurting you purposely!
Nonsense!
It’s for my lady herself!
Stop talking!
Why are you doing it?
I’ve felt sorry for you
that I’ve been His Highness’s concubine.
If I give birth to His Highness’s child,
it’ll be a bigger harm to you.
What’s done is done.
What do you want
by telling me these?
I want nothing.
I only want you to know
I’m missing you all the time
and missing those years when
we were having fun in the forest and
when I taught you to draw a fish tail.
Today
I bring you the shortcakes I made.
Almond shortcakes.
I know you have a fancy
to almond flavor.
Do you remember that there’s a time
when you had three shortcakes at a time,
and I gave you mine
to bring back.
No, I don’t.
It makes sense.
Now you’re
a noble wife of the prince,
but I’m just a criminal
who can’t either go home
or visit others.
If you like it,
just taste my shortcakes I made for you.
I’m leaving first.
Don’t…
Miss,
are you going to forgive her like that?
I also feel sad
when seeing her in this situation.
But, as long as I’m prince’s wife,
I can’t get along well with her.
But aren’t you going to divorce?
But Chongjin…!
If I divorce now,
the Xie family will have no hope.
Bad things keep happening
to my brothers.
I can’t be so selfish.
I should think for the Xie family.
Miss, what’s wrong?
The almond cakes are so good.
I feel more anxious now.
Mother asks to see us today.
If you dare to talk
about divorce in front of Mother,
or mention Shi Feixian,
I will not spare you.
Rest assured. I’m not that stupid.
Smile.
-Greetings to you, Mother!
Mother, I’ve been busy lately,
and haven’t come to greet you a lot.
Please forgive me.
Mother,
I’ve prepared this specialty from south
for you.
Wish you can be healthy
and happy forever.
Don’t be angry, Mother.
I don’t know what I did wrong.
Please tell me.
I will correct it.
You are a prince’s wife.
But you let the harem be in such a mess.
Where’s the decency?
Mother.
I have only Wanyu in my harem.
How can it be a mess?
You brought a girl back from outside.
You think
I don’t know it at all?
You’ve been married for long
but have no child.
You’re a second son.
If you still have no child,
your father may
send you to a fief now.
I know.
You are a legal prince’s wife.
Though your husband has concubines,
you will never
lose your control over anyone.
So
you can just relax
and give birth to a noble child.
As to the others,
I will deal with them for you.
Thanks, Mother.
Luo,
your brother and Crown Princess
are such an affectionate couple.
How can’t you
learn from your brother?
Mother,
I have something else to do.
I’ll leave you to rest then.
You…
I’m leaving now.
Chongjin!
Chongjin! Chongjin!
Your wound hasn’t healed. Don’t move.
Son, why are you up?
Qilin, help your brother
go back to his bed.
Leave me alone.
Chongjin!
Chongjin, health is the most important.
Don’t pretend to be strong.
Mother is right.
If you are hurt again,
it’s no use however high rank you’re in.
I must see Prince Luo.
Chongjin!
Prince Luo. Prince Luo.
You could lose your life.
How can you see Prince Luo?
If we knew it would be so dangerous
to work for him,
you shouldn’t have done it.
Now we can satisfy ourselves
with enough food and money,
there’s no need for you
to work hard, son.
Darling.
Father,
your words
are beyond my expectation.
But I can’t leave the bad situation
to Wanyu alone.
Father.
Let me go.
Chongjin!
-Chongjin!
They said only methods
of governing the country before.
Now they even ask me to learn
private issues from him.
Your Highness.
Feixian.
You got scolded by Mother a lot before.
But I’ve never seen you
being so anxious.
There must be other things
that annoy you.
Feixian.
I can never hide from you.
Mother said, when Jiang Zhang
ascends to the throne
and I have no kid,
Father will send me to a fief.
You are suffering the grievance for me.
I feel so sorry.
I’d better leave tomorrow.
I don’t allow that.
If I can’t even protect the girl I love,
how can I still be a prince?
I’m not worth it.
Don’t feel inferior.
Xie Wanyu is unqualified
to have my child.
I have only you in my heart.
Your Highness.
But
if you don’t want to sleep with Wanyu,
there’s only one way to go.
Stop Crown Prince ascending the throne.
That’s exactly what I’m thinking.
You’re so smart and considerate.
How can I not love you?
But it’s a pity that
Xie Chongjin is injured now.
I have no one to discuss with.
I’m coming.
Xie Chongjin, how’s your injury?
Though Mr. Xie is injured,
he won’t delay discussing
the big issue with Your Highness.
With such a loyal counselor,
Your Highness should cherish that.
I’m willing to work for Your Highness
till my death.
Great.
Good.
You have lived up to my expectation.
Your Highness,
I have an idea
to help you ascend the throne.
I don’t know if you dare to do that.
This is the colored-glaze hairpins
from the west.
Hua, this is for you.
Rong Xia, that’s Shan Ke’s
legendary painting tools.
You can take them back.
Your Highness, just cut the crap
and speak it out.
Days ago, it’s indeed Jiang Luo
who assaulted you.
I’m sorry for that.
Please forgive me.
I accept your apology.
But I want to say something, too.
You covered up for him this time.
But if he doesn’t correct himself
and serves the devil again.
It may be a big trouble.
Hua.
It doesn’t matter.
Now the Farming Festival is coming.
Father doesn’t feel well this year,
and entrusts me this major task.
Luo has always
showed no interest
in sacrificial activities.
Yet this year
he offers to help
with preparing it a lot.
Last night, Suyue reminded me that
maybe Luo
is plotting something again.
The sacrificial activity
is a big affair.
If he does something bad
in the sacrifice,
Your Highness’s fame must be damaged.
Prince Luo wants that to happen exactly.
It’s understandable
that you’re worrying.
Princess Royal’s birthday banquet
almost triggered a court fight.
If the Farming Festival can’t go well,
I… I’d feel ashamed to see Father.
Are you asking for help, Your Majesty?
I hope Hua and Count Cheng’an can
attend the sacrifice in the Festival.
Attend the sacrifice?
Aren’t only married people
allowed to attend?
Don’t worry.
Father has written an edict.
From now on,
you’ve been
the legal husband and wife
approved by His Majesty.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪