Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 30
Shennong Temple
Princess Fule, Count Rong.
Why are you here?
Mr. Shi, don’t be surprised.
His Majesty has allowed us
to get married.
We are specially invited here.
Congratulations.
Sorry for being rude.
Please come in.
Thank you, Mr. Shi.
Luo, there you are.
Nice to meet you.
Pay my respects to you.
You are exempt.
Father will be very pleased
to see you two so affectionate.
You are way more affectionate than us.
Don’t say that.
Husband and wife should
live a happy life
and respect each other.
You two should be more in love
and strive to have a baby soon.
You have no children yet,
how dare I have a baby ahead of you?
It’s getting late.
Zhang, you’d better get in now.
Offer blood!
Offer five cereals!
Offer wine!
Why are you absent-minded?
Still worried about
your brother’s injury?
My brother is fine.
Thank you for your concern.
You look nervous.
Is there any hidden secret?
You are making a joke.
There is no secret.
Did Jiang Luo treat you badly?
No.
In your life, you can’t
make do with someone you don’t love.
Are you willing to waste
the rest of your life in Wude Palace?
You mean...
I mean
if you keep putting up with it,
you are wasting your life on that idiot.
Burn incense and pray!
God bless us.
Protect us from disaster
and bring us luck.
God of Land and Grain
Grant Daye good weather
and grant people health.
and grant people health!
God of Land and Grain
Bow!
Kowtow!
Kowtow again!
Kowtow the third time!
Rise up!
The end! The Crown Prince returns!
Play the music!
Rong Xia.
I didn’t get anything.
Do you have any news?
Prince Luo has been
focusing on the ceremony.
There is no sign at all.
I don’t know if he is plotting something
or there is no plan at all.
Sure enough.
His Highness thinks too highly of him.
I think
he dares not to make any trouble today
even we ask him to do it.
The ceremony is not over yet.
Hua, you mustn’t take it carelessly.
The ceremony is finished.
Thank you for your efforts.
Please enjoy the coarse food.
The first one, please.
What are these strange things?
Scallion pancakes?
The second one, please.
Rice?
The third one, please.
The third one.
Let me see.
Dumplings.
How is it?
What’s this? Why is there no meat?
Hua, you used to a fancy life.
You definitely don’t know about misery.
After Father ascended to the throne,
he replaced meat for the sacrifice
with coarse grains
to show sympathy for people’s suffering.
Count Cheng’an, it’s Hua’s first time.
Why didn’t you tell her in advance?
Your Highness.
It’s also my first time.
Sorry for my bad memory.
Your Highness, didn’t you
prepare fresh juice?
Right, come on.
Yes.
Serve the juice.
Please enjoy it.
Finally, there is something tasty.
Why so little juice?
Hua, why did you drink it up?
Cousin Zhang, it’s my
first time to have
such fresh juice.
I couldn’t help myself.
If you like it,
you can also drink mine.
Really?
It’s very kind of you. I’ll drink it.
Look at her!
Thank you.
I have a stomachache
and need to go to the washroom.
Sorry, Your Grace.
It’s okay.
It’s good that you are not hurt.
Hua.
Drink mine.
Really?
I will be happy
as long as you are happy.
It’s very kind of you.
Hua.
Hua, what’s wrong?
Hua!
-Hua!
Come on, summon the physician!
Hua, what’s wrong with you?
-Summon the physician!
-Hua!
Hua!
Who is so bold
to use poison in the ceremony?
Hua.
Sir, how is Hua doing?
This poison is strange
and difficult to cure.
We have to use another poison
to force out the poisonous blood
as soon as possible.
Well...
Hua.
Hua!
Her Grace is unconscious.
She can’t take the medicine.
What should we do then?
Hua.
What to do, sir?
Yeah.
Is there any other way?
There is nothing I can do.
Let me do it.
This medicine is poisonous!
You can’t drink it!
Count Cheng’an!
-Hua!
This medicine is highly toxic!
You mustn’t drink anymore!
-Hua!
Hua! Hua!
You can’t have more!
Hua. Hua.
Hua...
Hua!
-Hua!
-Count Cheng’an!
-Physician!
-Hua!
Do something about it!
These two kids...!
Hua!
Rong Xia. Rong Xia.
Wake up. Rise and shine.
Rong Xia.
Hua, you’re awake.
You are fine now.
You saved me again.
As long as you are safe.
I’m willing to do anything for you.
Hua!
Mother.
Master! Master!
-Hua!
-Who woke up?
-Hua woke up!
Her Grace woke up!
Hua!
Hua, you must be hungry now.
-What do you want to eat?
-That’s great.
I’ll ask someone
to get whatever you want to eat.
Yeah, yeah.
Father.
Didn’t you say
they would serve meat and fish
in the ceremony?
Did you lie to me?
Yes, so what?
You only care about food.
I was going to find a wife for you.
But I didn’t expect you
to be so useless!
What’s wrong?
Let Physician Yu take a look first.
Come on, Physician Yu!
-Physician Yu, come on.
-Come on.
-Take a look at her.
How is she doing?
What’s the situation?
Physician Yu, how is she doing?
Master, madam.
Her Grace is doing fine now.
I need to observe for a few more days.
Okay. Okay.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
I’ll give you one more chance.
What did you see on the day
of the ceremony?
I won’t change my answer
no matter how many times you ask me.
You knew that cup of juice was poisonous
on the ceremony.
Get off me!
As my wife, how dare you not trust me?
They might not know it.
But I was sitting by your side.
I saw it clearly!
You are the one who put poison
in the Crown Prince’s juice!
Xie Wanyu.
I am being generous
to give you a chance again and again.
But you don’t cherish it.
You ask for your own destruction.
From today,
you are not allowed
to leave this room anymore!
Your Highness.
Princess Fule has woken up this morning.
You can rest assured.
Good.
Remember,
never let His Majesty know about it.
Yes.
What is so mysterious
that I can’t know?
What happened to Hua?
Say it.
Your Majesty.
Princess Fule was poisoned
during the farming sacrifice ceremony.
But she is awake now.
Please rest assured, Your Majesty.
Poisoned?
How dare you hide
such a big thing from me!
I was wrong.
I’m just worried about your health...
Are you worried about my health
or that I will scold the Crown Prince?
Your Majesty, please calm down.
This is odd.
It’s definitely not Zhang’s fault.
Who else’s fault could it be?
He screwed up
every task I gave him!
It’s fine if Hua is all right.
If anything happens to her,
how should I explain to my aunt?
Send the best tonic in the Palace
to Ban’s mansion.
Yes.
Hurry up!
Saussurea involucrata.
Young Master Ban.
Cordyceps.
Blood ginseng.
Father, they are valuable.
May I know about
His Majesty’s intention?
After hearing that Her Grace feels ill,
His Majesty asked us to
send tonic in the Palace
to Her Grace for her health.
I appreciate His Majesty’s kindness.
It’s just when can we
finish all these tonic?
I will keep some of them.
Please bring the rest
back to the Palace.
Mr. Ban.
How can His Majesty withdraw his words?
If there are too many for you to eat,
then use them to cook chicken.
Use the rest of them to make tea.
If there are still any left,
put some saussurea involucrata
in the water when you take a bath.
Duke Jingting,
it’s up to you.
A saussurea involucrata bath?
Father, it’s such a waste.
In that case,
obedience is better than politeness.
Thank you very much.
Come on, come on.
Come on.
Come on, let’s eat.
-Here.
-Have more.
The hot pot is still the best choice.
Give it to me.
I’ve been worried
and lost my appetite these days.
Hua, you know me the best.
Be careful. This isn’t a race.
I’ll ask someone to get more
for you if it’s not enough.
Ban Heng.
You are not young anymore.
You need to grow up a little bit.
You are going to take care of
our parents in the future.
Understand?
Hua, did the fever damage your brain?
You are too gentle.
I’m a little scared.
As a grown-up,
you actually burn yourself!
Such an idiot.
Do I have to say it out?
That’s who you are, Hua.
Our daughter made an
escape from death this time.
It’s worth celebrating.
Come on, cheers. Come on.
Come on.
Let’s drink all we want today.
Good, come on.
Good wine!
Come on, have a drink.
-Drink slowly.
-Come on.
Okay. Madam, this is for you.
Come on, Count Rong.
Let’s drink together.
Come on.
I can’t detoxify the poison
left in your body.
It all depends on the fate
whether you can survive it or not.
Come on, let’s eat.
Rong Xia, I’m feeling
a little uncomfortable.
Can you take a walk with me?
I will always be with you
wherever you want to go.
Hua, why don’t you show it to me?
I’m not good at writing.
I won’t embarrass myself.
Whatever you write
is always the best for me.
Show me yours first,
then I’ll tell you.
May we be together forever
May we be together forever.
What about you?
Nice try.
May Rong Xia live a happy life
and be with someone he loves
♪The seed of love grows in the dream♪
♪Endless tenderness for you♪
♪Startle the time♪
♪Words and flowers can express my love♪
♪Standing under the crabapple tree♪
♪Try to tell our future♪
♪May I tour the world with you♪
May Rong Xia live a happy life
and be with someone he loves
We wrote our wishes on the ribbon
and tied it here.
Will it work?
As long as we are sincere,
our wish will come true.
♪Send the poems to the God♪
♪Count the clouds in the sky♪
Rong Xia.
If
I die one day...
Hua.
Don’t talk nonsense.
I’m just curious.
Actually, I also thought about it.
If something really
happens to you one day,
I will go with you.
We will meet in the afterworld.
We can skate and shoot arrows together.
I’ll teach you about zither, chess,
calligraphy and painting.
Don’t talk nonsense!
If I really die,
no one will care about you.
You must remember
to eat well and sleep on time.
You can resign if you don’t want to
be an official anymore.
Okay.
Go after whoever you like.
Marry her and teach her
to play the zither.
By the time,
I will watch in the sky
when you get married.
Hua.
Could you stop that?
Let’s talk about something else.
Look at this yard. How great it is.
I really want to give birth to a girl
and a boy for you.
By that time,
we can watch our children
play and roll on the ground.
You can
play the zither here.
I can put my head
against your shoulder quietly
and listen to the music you play.
Then you will praise me
for being the most beautiful woman
in your heart.
How wonderful
it will be to spend
the whole life with you.
You and I will grow old together
and have many children.
Hua! Hua!
Hua!
May Rong Xia live a happy life
and be with someone he loves
and be with someone he loves.
A thorough investigation.
Again?
What else can you say
except these two words?
Father, please don’t be mad.
I will...
fully investigate this case.
What did you find?
My incompetence disappoints you.
That’s all you can say?
Look at yourself.
How should I explain to the Ban family?
Father.
I’m inadequate and indecisive.
I know I’m insufficient
to supervise the country.
Please allow me
to resign from the Supervisor of Daye.
I will fully investigate this case.
Zhang, what are you talking about?
Your Majesty, please calm down.
I should have realized
that you don’t have the talent
to rule the country.
It’s such
a waste of time and energy
to cultivate you.
Fine.
I will remove you
from the Supervisor of Daye.
Ban’s Mansion
Sir.
Didn’t you say that the poisoned
blood has been released?
Why does her condition worsen?
How deep is the hatred
between the poisoner and Her Grace?
He is ruthless indeed.
Hua.
I remember you once had a fever
when you were a kid.
I stayed by your side
for three days and nights
just like this.
Then you woke up by yourself.
You didn’t let me down.
I hope you won’t let me down today.
Just wake up, all right? Hua!
Master.
Wake up, Hua!
Master. Master.
Sir, is there any other way?
Find the poisoner
and ask for the antidote.
Maybe it can save Her Grace’s life.
I’ll go and get the antidote.
-Rong Xia!
-Count Rong!
Where are you going to get the antidote?
We both know
who dares to hurt Hua in Daye.
Count Rong.
You must be very careful.
Uncle, don’t worry.
I will get the antidote back for Hua.
Thank you, Count Rong.
What should we do?
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
Something happened to
Duke Jingting’s mansion!
What happened?
It’s Princess Fule.
The poison has attacked her.
No medicine can save her now.
She might not be able to make it!
Hua.
I
failed my aunt.
I failed Old General Ban.
-Your Majesty!
Feixian?
Is that really you?
We haven’t met just for a few months,
but you are very haggard now.
I guess my sister didn’t tell you
that I’m back.
It’s great that you are back safely.
I’ve been worried
that something might
happen to you out there.
I’m not here today to renew our kinship,
but to give you a chance to
be exempt from punishment
and reinstated.
His Majesty won’t let me go easily.
His Majesty won’t survive tonight.
The person who will sit on the throne
will only be the Prince Luo.
What did you say? Prince Luo?
So, you and Prince Luo...
A word of mine can make
our family the most powerful one
in Daye.
And you can become a minister again.
That’s great.
It was all my fault.
I was wrong.
Since you know you were wrong,
then admit your mistake.
You will kneel down sooner or later.
You’d better get used to it earlier.
What did you say?
I’m your grandfather!
I...
When you abandoned me,
my relationship with
the Shi family was over.
Wude Mansion
Zhang resigned from
the position by himself.
He saved me from the efforts.
Congratulate Your Highness on having
the power to supervise the country.
Feixian.
You can take
half the credit.
I should love you more
from now on.
Your Highness.
Count Cheng’an presents himself.
Count Cheng’an is here as I expected.
Close the door! Hurry up!
-Okay.
-Come on.
Hua!
Light the candles!
There is light, there is life.
Hua, hang in there.
Rong Xia will be back soon
with the antidote.
There is light, there is life.
Don’t let the candles go out.
I ask to see Prince Wude!
Count Rong,
nice to meet you.
Where is Prince Luo?
His Highness is busy now.
I’ll entertain you for him.
Count Rong, please come in
and have some tea.
No need!
I’m here today
to ask for the antidote for Hua.
It’s not impossible to save Hua.
But I have two conditions.
Firstly,
break off your engagement
and stop seeing anyone
of the Ban family.
What about the second one?
Help Prince Wude
ascend to the throne.
What if
I don’t agree?
It will take nine days before
the poison attacks the heart.
This is the sixth day
since the ceremony.
For the rest of the days,
Count Rong,
you have to hurry up.
Rong Xia!
Hua is saved! Hua is saved.
Rong... Rong Xia.
Did you get the antidote?
I didn’t get the antidote.
Father!
-Master!
Sorry.
Uncle, Aunt.
I’m incompetent.
Please forgive me.
We won’t blame you.
Maybe this is the fate of Hua.
We remember
what you have done for our Ban family.
Get up.
Uncle, Aunt.
I want to...
Heng, be good.
Help your father back to his room.
-Help Master back to his room.
-Take care, Master.
Father.
Hua is deeply in love with you.
Spend more time talking to her.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Hua, you know what,
during these days,
you have become my medicine.
You get underneath my skin
and I can barely live without you.
But today
someone forced me to trade you
with the antidote to save your life.
♪Sleeping under the moon
Hearing the sound of wind and snow♪
♪Wither like a flower
Love stays forever♪
If you were awake now,
you would tell me
that we will face it together.
There is no difficulty in this world
that we can’t solve.
You are right.
But I can’t afford
to lose this time.
♪When can I see your face again♪
♪I wait and wait all my life♪
♪In my dream I want the eternal♪
Marriage Contract
This marriage contract
is invalid now.
Marriage Contract
From today,
don’t miss me anymore.
I hope you won’t suffer anymore
because of me.
♪We will meet however hard it is♪
♪Regardless of the floating life♪
♪We stay in a small town♪
♪I have you to love in my life♪
♪I wait and wait all my life♪
♪I want to spend my life with someone♪
♪I want nobody but you♪
♪I would fulfill my dream♪
Hua.
This is the last time to see you.
♪I want to spend my life with someone♪
♪We will meet however hard it is♪
♪Regardless of the floating life♪
♪We stay in a small town♪
♪I have you to love in my life♪
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪