Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 25
Even without Minister Shi,
you’re still sulking
as I heard, Count Cheng’an.
Why is that?
Prince Luo, if I understand correctly,
our appointment
is about something shady, right?
As secretive as it seems,
it’s just what you’re longing for.
Why don’t you cut to the chase,
Prince Luo?
You can sleep on it.
I’m sincerely trying to help you
and I’ve prepared everything
to bring justice to you
and your deceased family.
Hold on.
Where are you going?
I’m ordered
to make a delivery by His Highness.
Really?
What is it?
For whom?
I...
I have no idea.
Show me what’s in the basket.
What are these for?
Please don’t make it difficult for me.
I really don’t know.
You don’t know?
Guards!
Take him to the local authority.
Your Highness,
I’m asked to deliver it
to the courtyard.
That’s all I know.
What are you doing?
I should ask you that.
Who’s the slut
that you’re giving the jewels to?
I can give them to whoever I like.
It’s none of your business.
You...
Please calm down, Your Highness!
She didn’t mean to annoy you.
Steward.
Yes, Your Highness.
Put everything back.
Yes.
He’s crossed the line!
I can’t take this.
Don’t stir up more trouble,
Your Highness.
We don’t know who we’re against.
What if something goes wrong?
What’s there to be afraid of?
I’m bestowed to him
by His Majesty.
She should be afraid of me, if anything.
Find out
who he’s seeing behind my back.
Yes.
Feixian.
Greetings, Your Highness.
Feixian,
I’m so glad that you’re safe.
I thought
I could never see you again.
I’m fine, Your Highness.
Don’t worry.
Don’t call me Highness.
That’s for strangers.
Feixian,
you aren’t mad at me anymore?
Wanyu,
it was all my fault.
I didn’t mean those hurtful things
I spewed out in a rage that day.
When I was in exile to Xizhou,
all I could think of
was the days we spent together.
I realized
how much I missed you
after losing my family,
but I didn’t get to tell you that.
I’m so sorry.
Feixian,
thank you for forgiving me.
All these years,
I’ve always regarded you as my sister.
After you left,
you don’t know
how much
I missed you day and night.
I didn’t think you’d
run into such a villain.
Luckily, you managed to escape
unharmed.
I returned to the capital,
but I found Grandfather was dismissed
and Shi’s Mansion was sealed.
I didn’t know where to go.
Coincidently,
I met Prince Luo and he helped me.
Rest assured, Wanyu.
I won’t stay here for long.
Feixian. You could’ve written to me.
If I had known you returned,
I’d have found you a place
to settle down.
I used to treat you badly.
How could I ask you for help?
It’s all in the past.
It must be that Heaven was touched
by our sisterhood and have you here.
Feixian. Just be frank and tell me.
It doesn’t matter.
It’s very safe to stay here,
but...
You fear that
it could bother His Highness and me?
Feixian.
I’m reluctant to say this,
but I don’t think
His Highness is good enough for you.
You don’t have to bear this.
Wanyu. You know it
that I love Count Cheng’an.
But now,
where else can I go?
Don’t worry. Leave this to me.
I’ll help you out.
Your Grace.
Young Master was urgently summoned
to the palace.
What was so urgent?
The eunuch came and said
His Majesty felt unwell
and asked Young Master
to go to his bedroom
for important issues.
Would he do anything stupid?
Your Highness.
In Father’s bedroom,
all the people are mine except Wang De.
Count Cheng’an.
It’s the best time for your revenge.
You want to slay the emperor by my hand?
As for what you are investigating,
you can get revenge for your family
or you will get yourself doomed.
Don’t worry.
I’ll leave a way
for the Ban family and you.
I’m sure
you know what to do.
Your Majesty. Slowly.
Your Majesty.
Rong.
You come at the right time.
I have something to talk with you.
You may leave.
Come and sit.
Your Majesty.
Shi Chonghai and Yan Hui
gang up for their own gains.
They’re powerful and overwhelming.
Your Majesty, do you really not know it?
They both helped me ascend the throne.
That’s why I was misled by them.
They all helped you ascend the throne.
Why did Old General Ban and my father
get killed by poison?
Rong Xia!
Given your contributions to the state,
I’ll pretend that
you didn’t say anything.
Leave.
Unless
you tell me what happened back then,
I wouldn’t leave even if I’d die.
How bold!
If you insist,
don’t blame me
for ignoring our affections.
If you don’t tell me the truth,
how can I know your affections
are out of pity
or guilt?
Rong Xia!
I
only want the truth.
You want the truth?
Alright.
Let me tell you the truth.
Back then,
I was enthroned in danger
and many things were to be done.
Only with the joint support
by the four families,
Ban, Rong, Yan, Shi,
could I restore the court.
Unexpectedly, after three months,
Old General Ban was poisoned
at the banquet.
Your father also got killed by poison.
Even your brother got drown
for no reason.
I was resentful but unable
to do anything,
for I couldn’t find the culprit.
Not until Princess Royal took you
into the palace,
did I realize
it’s plotted
by Prime Ministers Yan and Shi.
You were not supposed to take me in.
You should have punished Yan Hui
and Shi Chonghai for justice!
You think I didn’t want to?
But people needed peace and stability.
I had to swallow it.
Do you know why
I keep you by my side?
Not only to avoid
Shi Chonghai and Yan Hui
from hurting you,
but also to pay
what I owed to your father
all to you.
Your Majesty.
Why do you make it so emotional?
You keep me only to use me.
Use the blood debt of my family
to counterbalance Yan Hui
and Shi Chonghai.
It’s been over ten years.
My kindness to you cannot be fake,
can it?
True or fake, does it matter?
You had many choices to make,
yet you turned a blind eye to them,
and overindulged them
to control the state affairs,
hurt the people and endanger the state.
It’s outrageous.
Sorry,
but I cannot tolerate it.
What... What do you mean by that?
You want to kill me?
My kindness to you is always true.
I’ve given you everything
you wanted.
Everything?
I want my parents alive.
I want all my family alive.
Sorry but I cannot be like you,
being blinded
by power.
Don’t!
You are...
From now on,
our bond is severed like this robe,
whether kindness or grudge.
We have no affections anymore.
Hua.
Thank you.
But
I didn’t do anything for you.
Actually,
your chicken soup awakened me.
That soup was very bitter.
It’s bitter indeed.
But after the bitterness,
there was some sweetness lingering on.
Hua, you are right.
I’m no longer alone.
I have you.
I’m glad
that you think so.
Rest assured. I promise.
In the future,
I’ll never let you worry about me.
Count.
You questioned His Majesty like that.
If he killed you
out of anger,
my sister would really
be a predestined widow.
His Majesty did that
because he felt guilty about the past.
Otherwise, how could he be so kind
to Count Cheng’an and our family
all the time?
Father.
Now that both the two families
have fallen,
you’re likely to
be Prime Minister again.
And more likely for Count Cheng’an.
We have made the decision.
We’ll resign and stay away
from the court,
leading a happy and carefree life.
To live better than them
is also a way of revenge.
I’m afraid
His Majesty
wouldn’t allow Count to leave.
Your Excellency. Madam.
Young Master. News from the palace.
His Majesty fainted.
Why did he faint?
Don’t know.
Father, I’m going to inquire.
Count, be very careful
before I get back.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Your Majesty.
Come over.
Where is Rong Xia?
Your Majesty.
Give him some time.
Daye
cannot lose him.
Father.
I think Rong Xia must be too impulsive.
Hua, Father is right.
Now the state has no Prime Minister.
Rong Xia shouldn’t leave at this time.
Rong Xia.
Hua says you have something
to talk to me.
Your Highness.
This is Old General Ban’s Tiger Tally.
Rong Xia, what do you mean by this?
Your Highness,
please give it to His Majesty.
Tell him it’s found by you,
so that the court can be stabilized
and your position can be reinforced.
With you here,
why should I worry about the court?
Cousin Zhang.
We hand over the Tiger Tally,
because we mean to leave the court.
That won’t do.
Rong Xia, Father is sick.
The state needs you.
It’s our wish.
Please approve it, Your Highness.
Yes.
Your Majesty, the physician said
you just woke up
and needed more rest.
What are you looking for
in such a hurry?
I am
looking for the script
when I gave name for Rong.
Why are you looking for it?
I want him to know that
I’m sincere to him.
I don’t want him to leave me
or blame me.
Your Majesty, go back to rest.
I can help you look for it.
No, I’ll do it myself.
Why bother?
I found it.
I found it. I wrote this.
I... I gave him the name.
Your Highness.
How is His Majesty?
The physician diagnosed that
His Majesty has a serious fever
due to the cold,
but it gets serious
due to anxiety.
Can it be cured thoroughly?
It is mental disease.
It depends on if His Majesty
can open up his mind.
This is...?
The thing that troubles His Majesty.
Rong Xia
It’s personally written by His Majesty
and offered to your family.
Your Highness.
Could you please
tell me the origin
of it?
I clearly remember
it was at 11:00 PM
on the Start of Autumn.
His Majesty and I were about to sleep,
while Wang De brought us a message.
Your Majesty. Being blessed by you,
Mr. Rong got a son.
Mrs. Rong and the baby are both safe.
Great!
Really?
I must give Rong and his wife
a big gift.
Xia
Your Majesty,
forgive me for my ignorance.
What’s the meaning of the name?
“Xia” means the defect on a jade.
People tend to see it as a defect.
“Rong” is his surname.
“Rong Xia” shows my...
His Majesty’s blessings to you.
Wish the child...
Wish the child might have shortcomings
and make mistakes,
but people would tolerate
and forgive him,
and give him a chance
to right the wrong.
Rong Xia, I know you’ve been
bearing a grudge.
I don’t expect your forgiveness.
But the court cannot lose you.
The people cannot lose you.
Father.
Rong Xia gave me this.
For you,
I’ve lost too much.
Go.
Summer Count Cheng’an to me.
Father.
For the sake of
his loyalty and devotion,
I beg you.
Please spare him.
My son.
Count Cheng’an found Tiger Tally for me
and settled what had been haunting me.
I would greatly reward him.
I’m going right now.
We’ve arrived, Count.
Count, if you still feel upset,
you may take a rest inside.
I’m not upset.
After so many years,
it comes to an end anyway.
Your Grace, Count.
I finally catch up with you.
His Majesty has an edict for you.
Please take it in person.
I’ve issued an edict that
Count Cheng’an and Ban Hua
will marry in Moon Palace
by the ritual for princes.
Father, what did you say?
Your Majesty, since the state was found,
no outsider has ever married
in the palace.
Is it improper to do this?
From today on, a precedent is set.
I’m the emperor. I have the final say.
What is improper?
Father, you have a point.
But according to books,
the emperor shall stick to rules,
which are passed from ages.
If it goes against rules, I think...
You bastard!
You barely read books,
yet you dare to talk
about rules with me?
Calm down, Father.
Listen up.
It’s my decision.
No one shall object it.
Your Majesty. Please calm down.
Count Cheng’an is
the pillar of the state.
And we watched Ban Hua growing up.
You may count on me
to make the schedule
and take care of their wedding.
I will not let them down. How is it?
Zhang!
Luo.
Zhang.
Do you have anything
to talk with me?
Zhang. About what Father said,
do you just accept it?
Count Cheng’an is a subject.
How can he get married in Moon Palace?
I don’t feel it proper either.
But on second thought,
Hua is our cousin,
half a royal to some extent.
Rong Xia is loyal as well,
and has made many achievements.
So, Father’s decision is...
Zhang.
The other day,
Rong Xia threatened Father
with a dagger.
Have you forgotten it?
Luo. Don’t... Don’t talk nonsense.
We are in the palace.
You’ll put him in danger.
In danger?
He is a subject to us.
How can he break the rule?
What... What do you mean?
I really doubt if we are brothers
sharing the same blood
in our veins.
Zhang.
Father ordered him to resettle refugees.
Do you know it?
Now refugees are swarming
in the capital.
If His Majesty knows it,
he will surely be furious.
Do you understand what I mean?
I... I don’t quite understand.
You are hopeless.
Never mind. I can get another way
to deal with him.
Luo... Luo!
Don’t do anything stupid!
The 28th next month is said
to be a good day.
But what is it
to do with me?
Turns out
my own wedding is arranged by others.
And he is the emperor.
You cannot disobey him.
Don’t feel bad for it.
If you don’t like this wedding,
I’ll hold another one for you.
Really?
Don’t you think I’m melodramatic?
Of course not.
It only happens once in your life.
Of course you need to consider
how to have a grand wedding.
How could it be melodramatic?
Now that I decide to marry you,
I shall give you the best.
I will never let you feel upset.
Who said I could only marry once?
Many girls remarried in the capital.
♪Wait for the silent wind♪
♪With you all the four seasons♪
♪I care for him forever♪
♪I love him♪
♪Or Her♪
♪All my life♪
♪I want to enjoy my whole life♪
♪With you♪
♪I care for him forever♪
♪I love him♪
♪Or Her♪
♪All my life♪
♪I want to enjoy my whole life♪
♪With you♪
I don’t allow you.
You can only marry once in your life.
You can only marry me.
Sir.
Two coins in cash.
Sure.
Just a wedding.
Where it will be held doesn’t matter.
A wedding ceremony in Moon Palace
is the one and only in the capital.
It’s good.
Thank you, Suyue.
The Shi family has fallen.
Those flatterers
were all gone.
You get implicated,
and can’t even have some hot tea.
Is Crown Prince cold to you?
He’s good as ever.
But Feixian is missing.
I’ve mentioned it to him several times,
but he refused by the excuse
of His Majesty’s sickness.
Since Crown Prince is good to you,
don’t worry about other issues,
lest your relationship is affected.
As for Feixian,
my friends at the border would help.
There will be a result anyway.
I never thought
the three of us
would end up like this.
We don’t know Feixian is alive or dead.
Your marriage is also delayed.
If Feixian can be found,
my marriage
is no hurry.
Jin.
Ban Hua is going to get married.
Do you still hold on it?
I’ve been on it for years.
I can’t let it go that easily.
Hurry.
Your...
Yongsheng Casino
Good Fortune Yongsheng Casino
Ban. Ban. Ban.
Who is it? Zhou Changxiao.
Why are you hugging me in public?
Ban, you finally come.
You have no idea
how skilled the new gamblers are.
They play dice like magic.
I’ve even lost my pants.
Ban.
You must help me win them back.
Stop.
I’ve promised my sister
not to play dice again.
Ban, it’s not about money.
It’s about dignity.
If you
don’t teach them a lesson today,
they will show no respect
to you and me.
It’s your dignity.
None of my business.
We’ve been friends for years.
How can you stand by?
Ban, just two rounds. Just two.
Not for money. Just to help me.
Alright.
Well... Let’s have a deal.
Only two rounds.
Yes. Just two.
Let’s go.
Come on. Go.
Small
Big or small. Buy and move hands off.
Big
Big! Big! Big!
One, two, three! Small!
Big
Wager on big again.
Small
Big or small. Buy and move hands off.
Big Small
I’ll wager on small again.
Big
Big.
You wager on big? I wager on small.
Small
One, two, three! Small!
Big
Small
Come on. Silver.
Go on.
Fine. Big again.
Big
Small Big
Come on. Hurry.
Small! I still wager on small!
Small! Small!
I listen to you. Big.
Come on. Sliver.
Small.
Go on. Come on.
The silver is all mine.
This is yours.
Gentleman.
You win every game.
You are in great luck, aren’t you?
Let me tell you, man.
I win every game
because of this.
What is it?
This is
the most popular amulet in the capital,
Count Cheng’an Amulet.
Can Count Cheng’an bring good luck?
Listen to me.
There’s news from the palace
that Count Cheng’an
is the emperor’s love child.
Love child?
Think about it.
He’s taken by the emperor
as a son at 20.
Shouldn’t we pray to him for good luck?
Yes. Pray.
Let’s pray.
Come on. Go on.
Go on. Go on.
Have... Have you heard about it?
Count... Count Cheng’an is going to
be Prime Minister.
All the court affairs
will be
in his charge.
That’s no big deal.
He’s His Majesty’s love child.
To be Prime Minister is nothing.
Even if His Majesty passes
the throne to him,
I won’t have a blink of eyes.
I heard that
the edict to pass him the throne
has been written
and hung behind the plaque in the hall.
What a coincidence.
I have a doll of Count Cheng’an
in Crown Prince’s wear.
It looks good.
Keep talking! Why do you stop?
Don’t you like gossiping?
Should I
sew up your mouth?
Forget it, Hua.
Just some gossips.
Don’t lower yourself to their level.
Go. Go. Go.
I’m thick-skinned and get used to it.
But you are different.
Since we got together,
you’ve been bothered by gossips.
That’s annoying.
You are underestimating me.
I can be with you.
The gossips are nothing.
But I do think
this doll of me is pretty cute.
How about making another one for you
to be a pair?
Your Grace! Your Grace!
Bad news!
Young Master got detained in the casino.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪