Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 27
Young Master.
This is a letter from Crown Prince.
It’s supposed to be the findings.
According to our informer,
people in Wude Palace
did go in and out of the courtyard.
Xie Chongjin didn’t cheat us.
The evidence is solid.
Then we can tell Crown Prince
According to the investigation,
about Prince Luo’s hiding
those who tried to kill Count Cheng’an
of Shi Feixian.
are remnants of Prime Minister Yan.
Please don’t doubt Luo.
Not now.
According to the investigation,
those who tried to kill Count Cheng’an
are remnants of Prime Minister Yan.
They are just fall guys.
Crown Prince is tender by nature.
He’ll consider their brotherhood.
It’s hard for him to get the truth
about things related to Prince Luo.
Crown Prince is supervising now.
It can’t work without his permission.
One person is more worried
about Shi Feixian’s location.
Commander Shi Jin.
You don’t tell His Majesty
but the Shi people about
Shi Feixian’s return.
This is our best chance
to fight against Prince Luo.
It’s a pity
to do so.
If Commander Shi knows she is back,
he won’t stand by.
Shi Feixian is the one causing barrier
between Prince Luo and Xie Chongjin.
If she is alive,
Xie Chongjin will always
keep things reserved.
Prince Luo won’t completely trust
Xie Chongjin at the same time.
So Shi Feixian is the best choice
to balance them in their battle.
If she is killed,
Prince Luo will do things
out of control.
It won’t be good to anyone.
The medicine is ready.
Please take it.
Feixian.
Jin.
Since you’ve been back,
why didn’t you tell me?
Why didn’t you go home?
Wait. It’s very dangerous here.
We can’t let anybody know
you are back.
Don’t worry anyway.
I will find you
a safe place.
Feixian.
From the day I was banished,
your words now
has been too late.
Feixian, listen to me.
I promise
I will keep you safe from now on.
I won’t let anybody hurt you.
I don’t need it.
Grandfather chose to give me up.
I can also have my choice.
I’ll never enter the Shi’s anymore.
Never?
So will you depend on Jiang Luo?
It’s hard to live alone.
Without Jiang Luo,
I won’t have a place to stay, will I?
Prince Luo is scheming and cruel.
If anything happens to him one day,
he won’t care about you.
He won’t?
You think the Shi family will?
The Shi family chose the wrong side.
Crown Prince is so timid.
Jin.
Do you really think he can succeed?
Feixian, watch your mouth.
If you need,
I can help you
say something good to Prince Luo.
That will surely get you promoted.
Only if you are well,
I don’t care about honor and rank.
Please leave.
I won’t go with you.
If you
really feel sorry to me,
I’d like to see Suyue.
What?
All my words are true.
Luckily, Miss Shi didn’t accept that,
and still lives in the courtyard.
Who told Shi Jin that?
I have no idea.
Get out. I’m unhappy now.
I have a word with you.
Didn’t you hear me? Get out!
I will go if you agree about my request.
I want to divorce you.
Divorce?
Only I can divorce you.
It’s not up to you to divorce me.
If you don’t agree,
I will ask the Empress for help.
How dare you!
Let go of me!
Someone!
Lock her up!
Never let her leave
without my order!
Yes!
You are still useful.
How can I let you go?
Take her away.
Let go of me!
No incense ashes.
No acupuncture.
We’ve tried every way,
but she just isn’t awake.
So
this is also the wrong way.
She doesn’t care about it at all.
Besides Count Cheng’an,
what else does she care about?
Here you are.
Oh yes, the clothes.
What? What clothes?
Here you are.
Uncle.
Your Grace.
Thank you for your hard work.
You may go back for a rest first.
I will take care of Hua.
Thank you.
Watching
Get up! Hua.
Grandma.
Hua, you know what?
During the days you’re sleeping,
the peach flowers have bloomed.
The pomegranate tree in the yard
comes into bud.
I want you to have a look.
When will you wake up?
Though there’s beautiful scenery,
I have no one accompanying me.
Whether you can wake up or not,
I will be with you in my lifetime.
Why stop?
I’m trying to continue.
Hua, you are awake.
Keep saying. I want to listen more.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
No hurry to get up. Slowly.
I’ve been awake for a while.
I seldom hear you
saying these sweet words.
So I want to listen more.
When did you begin to listen?
Do you hope I heard more
or less?
If you want to listen,
I’d say so every day and night.
If it’s not enough,
I will say so all my life.
You can say such romantic words now.
You got something in the mind
while being assassinated that day?
Hua.
Promise me
you will never leave me, OK?
Don’t worry.
I will be with you all my life.
You can’t get rid of me.
Holy Prince Qixian
Thank God for your blessings.
May Hua be safe.
Hua, look.
I take your clothes…
Hua.
What’s that in your hands?
Nothing.
I’ll tell Mother and Father
you are awake.
Excuse me.
Please continue.
Continue.
Hua, you know what?
When you were sleeping,
your parents couldn’t sleep well
all days and nights.
They went to everywhere in the capital
and tried to find a way to cure you.
They never had a break.
Heng worried about you too.
I’m so lucky
to have the family and you.
This is the reason why
I should try harder to protect you all.
How about we move outside the city?
Let’s not live such a worrying life.
I…
I’m afraid I’d stay in the Palace
for some more days.
Why?
Don’t you blame His Majesty now?
But you’re the one they wanted to kill.
Didn’t you find it out?
For the past,
we can surely just let it be.
But if we just leave like this,
Prince Luo will take the throne.
What will the ordinary people do?
I understand your thoughts.
But if you get yourself hurt,
I will never let it be.
Hua, you are together with me now.
I promise
I will be safe.
Come on. Be quick.
Hua has become starveling these days.
This porridge with red dates
and lotus seeds can benefit qi.
Pheasant with tortoise to refresh you.
Which one do you prefer?
This one.
Make it cooler.
Blow it. Don’t burn her.
Don’t worry about it.
Here. Slowly.
Take more.
Father. I’m fine now.
Sorry to make you worry.
Here. Slowly.
Oh, Rocky.
Go get my embroidered clothes.
I will go into the street.
No.
You just recovered.
Yes, you can’t go now.
I’m really fine. Go get it quickly.
Miss, how about changing to another one?
-Why?
-Change it.
I haven’t gone out for days.
Surely I’d wear the most beautiful one.
But that one…
Was…
Ban Heng.
Ban Heng!
Come on, Miss, don’t be angry.
-Come on. Blow it for her.
-Don’t be angry.
-Blow it.
Feixian, it’s really you.
Sorry for your suffering.
Did you hurt?
Where are you living now?
Thank you for caring.
I’m great.
But Crown Prince didn’t do a good job.
You must have suffered a lot.
Feixian, how could you say so?
Anyway, don’t worry.
When Prince Wude ascends the throne,
you don’t need to suffer that anymore.
You are living in Prince Luo’s?
I wanted to kill Count Cheng’an
but hurt Ban Hua.
It’s not my aim, but it makes
Count Cheng’an heartbroken.
It’s a good thing in other way.
You…
You can take this as a gift for you
to celebrate my coming back.
It’s you.
Prince Luo did that.
Prince Luo and Crown Prince
are brothers.
They should have worked together.
Am I right, Suyue?
Feixian, you changed.
After going through the affairs,
everyone would change.
Anyway,
if you need any help,
you can try to beg me and Prince Luo.
Feixian. Feixian.
She must be angry,
so she lost her way.
Please hide this thing.
How could Feixian become like this?
I will help her see the truth
and leave Prince Luo.
Miss. Be careful.
How many years we haven’t been here?
You just recovered.
So we take you to this quiet place
for your recuperation.
Isn’t it quite nice?
Come on. Let’s go.
Let’s go, Miss.
Come on.
It’s clean.
I’ve known you for years.
But I didn’t know you are considerate.
Of course.
People have cleaned here before we come.
Where is Count Cheng’an?
Miss, how about I give you a massage?
Yes, when you were in the coma,
Rocky has learnt the skill of massage
for recuperation from an expert.
It’s good for your body.
Now it’s time for you to enjoy.
Yes.
But…
Don’t worry, Hua.
If Count Cheng’an comes,
we won’t disturb you two.
Yes.
-Come on.
-Be quick.
Miss, this way, please.
Enjoy it.
Let’s go.
Oh my God!
Time for the major business.
Do you mean
Luo brought Feixian back?
Feixian was weak in mind.
Prince Luo took advantage of it.
Your Highness, would you please
take Feixian back?
I know your feelings.
But Feixian’s identity is special.
And it’s a business of Luo’s.
I can’t have a hand in it.
Prince Luo has an ulterior motive.
He always plays hard for his goal.
If he’s in danger one day,
he will surely give Feixian up.
Your Highness, please help my sister
for the sake of me.
Suyue.
Luo has deep love into Feixian.
He won’t abandon her.
Maybe Feixian
can marry Luo as a concubine.
It will keep Feixian safe.
No.
Why not?
You have fewer supporters than before.
Just Shi’s former men
are assisting hard.
Now Prince Luo got Xie’s force.
If he marries Feixian now,
those who supported you before
will work for Prince Luo.
It won’t be that serious.
You are the future emperor of Daye.
You should be on guard
against Prince Luo.
Wude Mansion
Wanyu was talking nonsense.
Please don’t be angry. Your Highness.
You love Miss Shi very much.
I know it, but Wanyu doesn’t.
Please forgive her.
And please let me see her.
The Yan and Shi are declining now.
Wanyu is a bond
between you and the Xie family.
Thank you.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Softy.
The flowerpot is slanting.
Slanting? How about this?
Again. OK. Stop.
Chen.
The shelf.
Everybody, be quick.
Yes.
It’ll be bad if Hua finds this.
Find what?
You left me in the courtyard alone.
What are you doing here stealthily?
-What should we do?
-It’s not me.
Wedding jewelries.
Who is the girl you love?
Yes.
I’m not young anymore.
I hid it from you because I was too shy.
I can’t believe
you have such a good choice.
The bracelet is unique.
It’s great you love it.
What are you talking about?
So
Count Cheng’an arranged this?
I just want to help you two,
so I did it secretly.
He really took great efforts.
It seems someone has worn this dress.
Was he cheated by others?
How is it possible?
Nobody dares to cheat Count Cheng’an.
You are thinking too much.
That’s the design.
What about the hair?
How will you explain it?
Tell me the truth.
Otherwise, you have to practice sword
for 10 hours per day from now on.
10 hours?
Say it.
Xie Wanyu borrowed it that day.
Xie Wanyu?
Anything wrong with you?
How dare you divorce Prince Luo?
I don’t like him.
He doesn’t like me, either.
We shouldn’t have married.
If you worry about Shi Feixian,
it’s unnecessary.
Only if Shi Feixian doesn’t give birth,
she won’t take your title away.
Under the current circumstances,
you still don’t understand?
I don’t want to be the prince’s wife.
Don’t mention it again!
Two prime ministers are down.
Crown Prince is weak.
Working with Prince Luo
is the best choice.
I won’t let your willfulness
ruin our Xie’s future!
Have you ever thought about this?
You don’t want to be controlled by
the Yan’s, the Shi’s,
Princess Ban and Count Cheng’an.
What about me?
I’ve been under your
and Father’s control.
You misunderstood me. I definitely not…
Chongjin.
You’d better leave now.
Your Grace.
It’s been a long way.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
It doesn’t matter.
Rocky is so good at massaging.
I fell asleep
and I’m just awake.
That’ll be great.
Hua, you know what?
There is a mysterious place behind.
Mysterious?
What is it?
Of course,
it’s a place you’d go there on your own.
Hua, just come with me. You will know.
That’s great.
Let’s go then.
Come on.
Is this cave the mysterious place
you mentioned?
What have you hidden in it?
The cave is so mysterious.
I will take you in.
Hua, follow me closely.
Don’t open your eyes
if I don’t ask you to.
Hua, open your eyes.
Hua, will you marry me?
From now on,
you are my wife.
I will love you forever.
Be careful, Hua.
Why do you stop?
Follow me.
Your Grace, where are you taking me?
Why did you blow it out?
Don’t open your eyes
if I don’t ask you to.
Wait for me.
Hua.
Open your eyes.
Hua, look over there.
I’m skiing.
You are there too.
I went skiing with my brother
when I was a child.
My parents were looking aside.
After the Rong’s was destructed,
I haven’t gone skiing any longer.
On that day,
I felt the long-lost ease.
It’s like I was back to the old days.
Playing the Qin?
I only remember my hair was caught.
It’s embarrassing.
In order to be in love with me,
you tried something you didn’t like.
It’s romantic, not embarrassing.
Fall hunting!
It’s the first time
you taught me archery.
I was drunk at that time.
In a daze,
your dedicated face
looked beautiful.
I’ve born it in mind for a long time.
This is…
Neither you nor I expected
the kiss in the dangerous situation
led our love in this life.
So you planned it a long time ago?
It’s not a plan.
It’s fate.
Everybody, attention please.
Play the music as soon
as they come out later.
OK. OK.
It’s my sister’s big issue.
No error is allowed.
Got it.
-Got it.
What’s going on?
Why haven’t they come out?
After we get back to the capital,
I will apply to His Majesty
for allowing us to leave
and live a country life.
Are you serious?
I was originally filled with gloom.
Luckily, I met you.
I’ve thought it over.
You’re the most important in my life.
Hua.
Will you marry me?
From now on,
you are my wife.
I will love you forever.
No.
What are they doing inside?
Young Master. Here they are.
Step back.
Ready.
Three, two, one.
Hua, why are you out alone?
Where is my brother-in-law?
Yes.
Hua.
Am I too anxious?
How could you just refuse him?
It’s none of your business.
How could it be none of my business?
These days,
he prepared three sets of wedding dress.
Come on. Take a look.
He carefully selected them
for your wedding.
He caught the glowworms
all over the mountain.
He hung on the cave top
at night to paint honey to the wall.
He did so many things,
but you refused him.
Don’t you like him anymore?
Since you still like him,
why did you refuse him?
Are you worrying about the dream?
Enough. Say no more.
It’s my own marriage.
It’s none of your business.
Hua.
-Hua.
It’s all because of you.
Well, enough.
He even got mad.
Coming.
Sorry for disturbing you at night.
What’s the matter?
Please give the letter to Her Grace.
To Princess Ban From Rong Xia
See you.
He just failed the proposal.
Is he going to escape?
Miss Softy, I didn’t go too far away.
Maybe you could keep the voice down.
He just gives up
when meeting such a setback.
How can he get the girl
if he has the jitters?
May I ask you a question?
How can I get the girl I love?
Which girl is she?
I can’t tell you that.
If you don’t make it clear,
how can I answer it?
Hua.
When I married your father,
I was two years younger
than you are now.
Of course, I know it.
You’ve said it for several times.
Others said your father was foppish,
ignorant and incompetent.
He only knew game foul.
He’s impossible to be
a good husband and father.
They even said life was hard for me.
It’s destined to have a painful life
if I married into the Ban’s.
They were talking nonsense.
You have such a good life now.
Then why do you think you can’t
have a good life if you marry him?
You love each other.
Both take the other side
as the most important one.
That’s the most precious of all.
For one’s life,
the most difficult thing
is to find one engaging with your minds.
Everything else
means nothing other than it.
Hua.
Life is what you make it to be
but not destined.
Don’t miss your lifetime beloved one
for a moment of timidity.
Young Master.
Go home.
Young Master, are we really going back?
Won’t you talk to Her Grace again?
Maybe I was too abrupt.
I did that without asking her.
So the thing went like this.
Now I feel too ashamed to meet Hua.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪