Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 26
The little brat! Gamble again!
I’ll have his hide.
Where’s he?
Upstairs.
Your Grace, wait for me here.
Place your bet.
Come on. Place your bet.
Whether Count Cheng’an is
the love child of His Majesty?
Let’s start from one tael.
No waiting after the set time.
Place your bet. Come on.
Whether Count Cheng’an is
the love child of His Majesty?
Place your bet.
Come on.
Stop.
How dare you
distort the royal family in public
and set up a gamble about it?
Who are you?
Don’t you know it’s my turf?
Though gambling isn’t prohibited,
you shouldn’t speak such nonsense.
Are you preaching at me?
Just go home.
Don’t disturb us.
Exactly. Go home.
-Right.
-What?
-Go back.
-Go home.
How dare you abuse my man?
I’m really blind.
I didn’t know
Princess Fule and Count Cheng’an
are here.
I was just joking.
Please don’t get angry with me.
I heard everything.
You said Count Cheng’an is a toy boy.
Look at me.
I just envy Count Cheng’an
for his youth.
That’s why I used improper words.
-Improper words.
-Cut the crap.
Let’s resolve this matter
as per gambling rules.
If I win,
remove the gambling table.
If there is still chat
about Count Cheng’an from you,
don’t blame me for not being nice.
Well…
What if you lose?
If I lose,
I’ll never inquire into your gambling.
All his money is yours.
What do you think?
Hua.
It’s my private affair. You need not...
Your business is mine.
Relax.
I won’t lose.
Small
Come on. Place your bet.
Hurry up. Come on.
Big
Come on.
Small
Big
I was too ignorant to identify you.
Your Grace.
Please stop rolling dices.
Mercy on me.
Well, this table...
I’m gonna remove it.
I dare not take Count Cheng’an as a bet.
That’s more like it.
I’ve never thought you have such knack.
Not practicing for a long time,
I’m a little rusty on it.
You underestimated my sister.
She once was famous
for her gambling skills,
the legendary master
in the circle of gambling.
-Ban Heng.
-It hurts.
Are you looking for trouble again?
Haven’t I told you not
to gamble anymore?
Don’t blame me.
It’s Zhou Changxiao.
Where’s he?
It hurts.
Remember what I’ve told you?
Yes.
Losing money in gamble
is easier.
Listen up.
Life is like a gamble.
You shouldn’t take it too seriously.
Losing money drives you to gamble again
and seek justice.
But forget advancing and retreating.
Then you’ll lose totally.
I got it.
That’ll be fine.
Go home by yourself.
I send His Grace home.
You’ll go to his home again?
Is it Okay?
You wanna get beaten?
All right. Hua, let’s go.
Hua.
Thank you.
What you said to Heng just now
is also said to me, right?
Is it so obvious?
But you’re right.
Taking life for gambling,
I’ll lose more.
I should’ve moved forward.
Now, you know it.
It’s worth it.
It’s my pleasure to have you around me.
Actually,
His Majesty asking us to
get married at the Moon Palace
is to make it up to you.
The rumor’s going around.
There will be many conflicts
in the court.
Rest assured.
I’ll take care of it.
Well, let’s go home.
Why do I send you home again?
Because
without you
I can’t do anything right.
I heard Rong Xia was here.
Father,
you look better today.
Brother, what you said is improper.
It will be not bad
if he does not make father feel worse.
Why could he cure father’s disease?
Father, haven’t you heard
everyone in the capital said
Count Cheng’an is your love child?
Count Cheng’an neither clarifies it
nor minds it at all.
How despicable!
Nonsense!
Right. I also thought it’s nonsense.
Get out.
Get out of my face.
Your Majesty, you...
Father, did I say anything wrong again?
Get out.
Your Majesty, Luo is straightforward,
but it’s for your good.
The rumor’s going around in the capital.
It’s not a good thing.
You’re Empress.
How could you believe such rumor?
Of course, I don’t believe it.
Rumor is more fearful than a tiger.
It’d be better if he were my son.
I would be better than now.
No so many worries, either.
Why are you kneeling here?
What you said also makes sense.
If I had a brother like Rong Xia,
he should inherit the throne.
Zhang.
Ding You
Mr. Xie. Count Cheng’an met His Majesty
with a dagger.
Now, the rumor of bastard gets out.
I’m afraid...
Clearly, it’s time to settle it.
Tell me your scheme.
Tell the followers that
Prince Luo ordered
to kill Rong Xia.
It’s all your fault.
Look.
It’s going to rain.
How should I go home?
If you can’t,
why not stay here?
I don’t think your father will mind.
I feel
there must be a catch.
Catch? Why do you say so?
Look.
You’re knowledgeable.
How couldn’t you know
it would rain today?
You’ve planned it, right?
Hua, you get me wrong.
The weather is not cooperating.
I have no other way.
All right. I now trust you.
Now?
I swear I didn’t lie to you.
A little salt. A little sugar as well.
Du Jiu.
What on earth does it mean?
It means...
Sir, it’s hard to say.
You tried to keep princess here
just to make her breakfast.
You’re...
You’re really the model of Daye.
That’s really touching.
Sir, look out.
Du Jiu.
Go to protect Hua.
Nothing can happen to her.
Sir.
Obviously, they come at you.
If I’m not with you, what would you do?
Go.
Be cautious.
I won’t get killed so easily.
I wonder
what rewards Xie Chongjin promised
to get a dozen of you here.
We get paid to kill you.
It’s none of your business.
Get ready to die.
Go.
Your Grace.
Your... Highness.
Feixian, I miss you.
Feixian.
Am I on your mind?
You’re drunk.
I wish
I could show you my heart.
I know.
But if you still have affections
for Rong Xia…
Your Highness.
In my heart, there are no others
but you.
You mean it?
Even if I kill him, is it okay with you?
Kill him.
Hua.
If you get to hurt him,
you have to get my permission.
Go.
Hua.
Leave him alive.
Get out of my face,
if you don’t want to die.
You’re just a woman.
How dare you brag?
Go.
Back off.
Hua.
I’m busy today
and have no time to play with you.
Kill him.
Don’t try to hurt him.
Sir.
Hua. You got hurt.
What do I usually tell you?
Don’t just read.
Practice martial arts more.
If you had listened to me,
it wouldn’t end like this, would it?
You’re right.
It’s my fault.
If it were not for my powerful martial art,
if I hadn’t come in time,
your...
Hua.
Your life...
Miss.
Where are you going in heavy rain?
Well,
Feixian is afraid of thunder
from childhood.
She has no one around her now.
I’m going to accompany her.
I’ll go with you.
No, stay here.
She does not want to be disturbed.
I’ll go by myself.
I’m off.
Miss, be careful on the way.
Feixian?
Wanyu...
Jiang Luo. You’re shameless.
Xie Wanyu, are you insane?
It’s between me and Feixian.
Stay out of our business!
As long as it involves Feixian,
I’ll step in.
I’ll call somebody if you don’t leave.
Feixian, go now.
Don’t worry about me.
Wanyu, it’s true love between us.
Please don’t stop us
from being together, alright?
You told me
you didn’t love His Highness
and you loved Count Cheng’an.
Was it a lie?
Did you cheat me?
Right. I cheated you.
Because I know,
His Highness is your husband
and I shouldn’t love him.
But, love is not based on
the order of arrival.
Wanyu, forgive me.
You’re a cheap crook.
I will
never forgive you.
If I can’t get your forgiveness,
I only have to die.
Feixian...
Xie Wanyu.
For the sake of your brother,
get out.
If something happens to Feixian,
I’ll make you pay for that.
Wanyu.
Feixian.
It’s a long night.
Let’s continue.
But,
Wanyu is your legal wife.
It’s just a title.
I only have you on my mind.
Shi Feixian, I treat you sincerely.
But you cheated me.
Seems
there’s nothing in the capital
worth my cherishing.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Her Grace is in a coma
because of excessive loss of blood.
In the normal sense,
she could wake up soon.
But why hasn’t she?
I have no idea.
I got it.
Thank you.
Thanks for your help.
You’re welcome.
It’s my bounden duty to cure her.
Goodbye.
Hua. It’s my fault.
I never thought a rumor
led to the danger.
I’m sorry.
Hua.
-Hua.
-Hua, I’m coming to see you.
Hua.
What happened to you?
You never got hurt since childhood.
Why did you get hurt like this?
My baby girl.
Mr. Ban, I’m sorry.
I didn’t take good care of her.
Your Grace.
-Don’t blame yourself.
-Hua.
The priority is to
find out the manipulator.
Hua.
I’ll absolutely
find out the person.
Once the person is identified,
I’ll kill him.
Where’s Ban Heng?
Ban Hua is severely hurt.
Why hasn’t he come?
Your Majesty. He went out yesterday
to prepare wedding gifts for Her Grace.
I’ll get him back immediately.
Hurry up.
What have we done wrong?
Why is Hua’s marriage so difficult?
My baby girl.
It hurts.
It’s me. Ouch.
How come it’s you?
What are you doing here?
Ban Heng,
are these made by yourself?
You bet.
I only have one sibling.
I definitely want her
to have the best proposal.
But, Count Cheng’an is a bookworm
and can’t get the point.
So, everything depends on me.
You’re very kind to your sister.
Certainly.
She is my sister.
Don’t your siblings treat you well?
My eldest brother is kind to me,
just because of my identity.
In the end,
I’m still alone.
Nobody cares about me.
Xie Wanyu, you mustn’t cry here.
A master said
this is a good place.
If you cry,
it will bring bad luck.
Stop crying.
Why… Why did you
get wet?
It’s raining heavily.
What’s the fuss about?
Why didn’t anyone
hold an umbrella for you?
Stop it.
Fine.
You’re lucky.
I prepare this for my sister.
But it’s the time for you.
Go get changed. Don’t get cold.
Or I’ll be in trouble.
Don’t get me wrong.
I’m just afraid you’ll die of illness.
Then I’ll commit a serious crime.
Otherwise, I wouldn’t care about you.
Thank you.
It is quite baffling.
Have you changed yet?
Why does it take so long?
Does it look good?
Err...
Not too bad.
Not bad.
Thank you.
The wedding gown
looks terrific.
Don’t be pretentious.
Though the gown is
not bad,
compared with your wedding gown,
this one is a little inferior.
We even dare not embroider a phoenix.
With phoenix, so what?
If I could choose,
I’d rather marry a true love.
It would be better than now.
A lonely life in the deep palace.
Stop quoting poems.
I don’t understand.
All in all, Jiang Luo is bad for you.
Then find a new one.
Why do you look so sad?
How is it possible? He’s a prince.
So what?
He has nothing different
from ordinary people.
You’re just fear of making
you father and brother unhappy.
It’s you who get married.
Why do you be so obedient to them?
Is it possible that
others can give Prince Luo
a baby for you?
Ban Heng!
Sorry. Out to lunch.
Come on. Don’t think too much about it.
Just get by. No big deal.
Just eat well, sleep well.
Take good care of yourself.
After Jiang Luo dies,
you can remarry.
It’ll stop raining soon.
Why not get some sleep?
I’ll tell you when it stops raining.
Poems about Mountains and the Moon
Well, here you are.
You’ll like it.
Poems about Mountains and the Moon
And these flowers help you sleep.
I put them here.
Poems about Mountains and the Moon
Have a good sleep.
What’s up?
What’s the matter?
Nothing.
It’s just a nightmare.
Nightmare...
Look at you.
I haven’t eaten my chicken in the dream.
How will you pay for my loss?
Well,
take this.
Bracelet?
Why did you give it to me?
I can’t trade it for chicken.
You can.
What did you say?
Nothing.
Seems it stops raining.
Let’s go.
You may leave first.
If we go back together,
your fame probably will be ruined.
Your bracelet.
It’s yours now.
I don’t like to owe favors.
I’ve kept it since I was a kid.
Keep it for me.
When I divorce with Jiang Luo,
I’ll get it back.
Divorce?
You finally figure it out.
Then, I go get changed.
Bang Heng, after a night of thinking,
I figure it out I should live for myself
rather than for others.
Like Ban Hua,
I want to take control
of my own destiny.
Miss, don’t worry.
You’re in poor health.
You can be pregnant
after some careful treatment.
My lady is not somebody
but the wife of Prince Luo.
Bi’er, stop it.
Wanyu is the wife of Prince Luo.
I’m not blathering.
Prince Luo has stayed here
for several days.
A new baby
can be expected soon.
Go get the medicine with the physician.
Pay attention to it.
Don’t worry.
Your Highness.
Rong Xia.
You just came in time.
I followed Wu Daozi and imitated
the Portrait of Flower-wearing Maid.
-Your Highness.
-Have a look.
Have you heard dozens of martial artists
sneaked into my home and
tried to kill me?
Is it true?
Where is the chief minister
of the Court of Judicial Review?
He should track down the manipulator.
Manipulator?
I have a suspect.
I came to ask
if you get ready for taking over Daye.
Rong Xia.
Father will long live.
Let’s change the subject.
His Majesty once asked me
to assist you in reforming
the governmental abuses.
Now, His Majesty is in poor health.
And assassins came to kill me.
Who do you think the manipulator is?
I...
You know it very well.
Prince Luo is at the same age as yours.
How could he be willing
to be your servant?
After Duke Jingting was assassinated,
I found out that
Prince Luo has close relations with
men of the world.
Those who tried to kill me
were men of the world as well.
Rong Xia.
There must be some misunderstanding.
Luo...
Luo is not like that.
Though I exercise royal functions,
Father is still living.
You’d better discuss with him
about this matter.
You’re kind-hearted,
but others may not be.
Rong Xia.
I only like planting flowers.
Why do you bother to force me?
Since it is so,
you can pretend I never came here.
Count Cheng’an.
I’ve been waiting for you
for a long time.
It’s only half a day.
Is Mr. Xie eager to check
whether I’m still alive?
You’re smart.
So, you should know
it’s not my purpose to kill you.
Either Luo or you,
what’s the difference?
My heart aches for
what happened to you.
So, I’m here to work with you
to break the ice.
We don’t share the same belief.
Shi Feixian has come back.
Now, she lives in the courtyard
of Prince Luo.
It turns out you’re afraid of losing
your position.
So, you ask me to join hands with you?
Rong Xia, given the current situation,
this is the best choice.
Master, I’m getting confused.
Isn’t Xie Chongjin following Prince Luo?
Why does he want to join hands with you?
Didn’t he send the assassins to kill you?
Either Luo or him,
that’s no difference.
Shi Feixian is an obstacle for them
and also the soft spot of Prince Luo.
He wanted to use me to kill Shi Feixian.
What’s your plan?
Let’s take a drastic measure.
What a good-for-nothing!
When Hua needs you the most,
where have you been?
Hua.
I haven’t been out for a long time.
What happened to you?
Open your eyes and look at me.
If you keep sleeping,
you’ll miss your wedding day.
Your marriage is hard-won.
Go for it.
Shut up.
Nobody treats you as a mute.
Stop making noise.
Physician Yu said
she’s physically recovered.
She just doesn’t want to wake up.
So, she’s been in a coma.
Rest assured. Mr. and Mrs. Ban.
If she doesn’t wake up in one day,
I’ll keep her for one day.
If she doesn’t wake up
in one or two decades,
I’ll keep her for one or two decades.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪