Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 28
Young Master.
Go home.
Young Master, will we really go back?
Won’t you talk to Her Grace again?
Maybe I was too abrupt.
I did that without asking her first.
So the thing went like this.
Now I can’t face Hua.
Princess. Princess is coming for you.
Will you leave without saying anything?
The man I love
can’t crawfish like this.
Hua.
I thought too much during the day,
so I refused your proposal.
It makes you sad.
But now I feel regret.
So are you still willing to marry me?
I…
I can refuse you.
But you can’t refuse me.
Go. Don’t look.
Mom is so cool.
Otherwise, the fireworks I bought
would be wasted.
Anyway,
what did you say?
I just told your sister
things happened between your dad and I.
What did you say to the girl?
Yeah, what is it?
Just things happened between us.
What kind of mother you are!
I, Rong Xia, promise,
I won’t separate with Hua in this life.
I, Ban Hua,
also promise,
I will do the same.
With such fine view,
there should be some phrases.
Nature draws without ink.
Rain plays songs with bamboos.
Fireworks are still there
but people have changed.
It’s just a few months.
I can’t enjoy the fireworks
like before any longer.
Ban’s Mansion
You go first.
Yes.
Ban’s Mansion
Ban Hua, Rong Xia.
I…
You just ignore your brother.
Do you forget
I helped you to get him back?
Mr. Du, can you tell me
who the girl you love is now?
Young Master Ban.
-What? It’s weird.
-Say it!
-You…
-Who is she?
Don’t follow me.
Please tell me.
You are all in couples.
I am the only one alone.
So sad.
Uh.
What’s going on?
Why did she come to my mind?
Hey. Son.
Do you want to get married too?
I don’t.
It’s happy to have fun alone.
I don’t need a wife to control me.
Have fun?
You have fun only when you have a wife.
-Yeah.
-No.
So stubborn.
The poems or something like that
fit you.
The flowers are good for sleep.
Have a good sleep. I’d put it here.
Miss, time to sleep.
Miss.
Do you want to cook again?
The dishes are great.
But nobody understands it.
It’s still meaningless.
Miss.
Hua, you are still weak.
So you should take more rest.
But you are not here.
It’s boring for me alone.
OK. You’d promise me
you will be careful.
I will feel at ease in that case.
I promise.
Young Master, time for changing dresses.
Or it will be late for going to court.
Hua.
Don’t go anywhere.
I will see you once I finish the work.
I won’t go anywhere.
I’m leaving.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Young Master,
here are clues and evidence.
His Grace’s assassination
is not as simple as what he said.
Things are different.
Du Jiu.
Make sure the Ban’s won’t get involved.
Find out the assassinators.
I won’t forgive them.
One more thing…
In general…
Princess…
Don’t let Count Cheng’an know my plan.
can’t get involved in it.
According to your order,
we have people pretending
to pay for killing officials.
Nobody took it
no matter how much we paid.
Fude House sent the secret letter
for the date in Qili Pavilion.
Rong Xia Life Price Silver 3,000 taels
His Grace’s Life is 3,000 taels.
Ban Hua Life Price Silver 5,000 taels
Mine is 5,000 taels.
The prices are proper.
Softy.
Did you find
the list lacks of something?
Even I am on the list.
I don’t think so.
It’s the Xie’s.
Xie…
Do you mean Xie Chongjin did that?
Especially you,
don’t ever make His Grace know this.
Ban Heng Life Price Silver 100 taels
Why am I just 100 taels?
See? You didn’t practice more.
Now you know you are cheap?
No, something is wrong with it.
Look, Shi Jin is 2,000 taels.
Shi Jin Life Price Silver 2,000 taels
Rong Xia is 3,000 taels.
Shi Jin is more skilled than Rong Xia.
Why is his price lower?
Seems
I have to say something hurting you.
It’s business.
There must be a buyer.
Heng.
I don’t think anyone wants your life.
Wanna increase your price?
Of course.
Take the action with me tonight.
Weird.
I feel a bit familiar.
Lower your voice.
It’s just an old man.
Don’t be so nervous.
His footstep is steady and powerful.
But it’s silent.
He must be a master.
Master?
Is he the one trying to kill His Grace?
Young Master.
You are just a woman.
How can you talk big like that?
Guys. Action!
That’s him.
He’s the head of the killers.
What are we waiting for? Go get him.
Mr. Shi. Why’re you in Xie’s Mansion?
I
saw you and I was worrying about you,
so I followed.
Mr. Shi, you are worrying too much.
We are fine.
What’s wrong with you, Mr. Shi?
If the matter of Shunzi
is still confusing you,
it’s unnecessary.
Because I know
it has nothing to do with you.
Thank you for your understanding.
But this is your boudoir.
It’s inconvenient for me to be here.
Martial artists neglect
the minor points.
Yes. And I’m with you.
You are not here alone.
That does make sense.
But there will be gossips.
I’m afraid it’ll distain Her Grace.
Mr. Shi, you must be joking, right?
Does she have any reputation?
How dare you!
Ouch! Ouch!
Mr. Shi is there.
The most important thing
is to find out the Fude House’s Den
and wipe it out.
But how?
Mr. Shi, do you have a way?
How about we pay someone to do it?
Then Mr. Shi can capture them
and ask for that.
The…
Hua.
My son-in-law is here for you.
Come on. This way.
Hurry.
Look.
I bring you my son-in-law.
Look. My son-in-law is visiting you.
I didn’t expect you to come so late.
Hua.
Young Master Ban is here too.
Heng, you are a man.
How can you sit on the girl’s bed?
Come on. Come here.
She’s not anybody else but my sister.
Hey, kid.
Come on. Sit here.
Leave it.
No. It’s comfortable here.
You don’t listen to me, right?
You little jerk!
There must be something
I can do with you.
Come down!
-Don’t drag, ouch!
-Come down!
Mr. Shi?
Why are you on my daughter’s bed?
Offer your hands. Shi Jin.
And you.
Say it!
Why are you three
in Hua’s room?
Dad, I’ve said it just now.
We are discussing swordsmanship.
Mr. Shi, say it.
What are you doing on Hua’s bed?
Please forget me, Your Excellency.
We are frank and forthright.
Frank and forthright?
Dad, Mr. Shi is not the one to blame.
I asked him to come.
My girl.
You have an engagement
to Count Cheng’an.
Now you let him be on your bed.
You…
Your Grace…
What’s going on?
I don’t know.
I really don’t know. Dad.
I know nothing about it.
Your Grace, I…
You little jerk! How dare you run away!
Come back. Come back!
Hua.
It’s my fault.
Please don’t blame Her Grace.
It’s my bad.
Your Grace, please don’t get mad.
I won’t get mad.
But you have to tell me
if you are investigating
the case of Fude House.
No.
Definitely not.
Hua.
Yes.
To be honest,
I’m investigating it too.
Under the circumstances,
let’s be frank
and exchange what we know
so that we can get rid of it early.
So,
you aren’t angry with me now?
If you dare do that again,
I will wait in your room every night
to see who dares to come.
I’d like
to do anything for you.
Young Master.
Say it!
Accountant Zhao Xiancai of Fude House
is take actions.
Where is he?
It’s said all killers of Fude House
will gather Yuzhen House gradually
before tomorrow noon.
A group of killers
gather in the first teahouse openly.
They really get a nerve.
It’s under the blacklight.
Maybe we can only figure it out
after we see it in person.
Feixian.
Your Highness.
Sit down.
Thank you.
What are you sewing?
Can I take a look?
Thank you for your kindness.
I don’t have anything else
but making these things to repay you.
May you realize your ambition
and all your wishes come true.
You are so nice.
I will be with you tonight.
Your Highness, I have something to say.
But I don’t know if I should.
Just say it frankly.
Only if I can do it,
I will promise you.
Your Highness.
Princess Wanyu is my friend for years
and we are like sisters.
I’m begging you
not to give her the cold shoulder
for me.
What do you mean by that?
Don’t you hope I
love you more?
I’ve felt sorry
for being loved by you.
How can I fight against her for love?
You
are too kind.
Don’t worry about Xie Wanyu.
I can say nothing more to her.
When the time is ripe,
I will surely divorce her.
At that time,
you can stay with me
in just ways.
Your Highness, please don’t.
I’ve felt lucky
and satisfied
since I can be with you
like now.
Yuzhen House
I’m a frequent visitor of Yuzhen House.
You investigate the case without me.
You are looking down upon me.
Today, I will show you my competence.
Thank you.
Young Master Ban
Young Master Ban is here. Go welcome.
-Please go ahead!
-Young Master Ban, sorry.
The last room was booked.
It’s OK. I can sit anywhere.
OK.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Stop looking.
So impolite.
My lord, one more.
-God!
-Who is he?
Young man, have a tea together?
Fude
Fude House?
I…
Did you get in the wrong room?
You came in suddenly without a word.
I’m afraid it’s impolite.
What’s going on?
You are asked
to practice at home.
Why did you come out for tea stealthily?
Yes, why did I come out for tea?
Everyone, I’m sorry
for disturbing.
I will treat you today’s tea.
Yes.
I have a lot of money.
All these for today are on my treat.
Let’s go.
Wait.
There are a lot of people.
Be careful.
Are you silly?
If Mr. Du weren’t there,
you could be dead, you know?
You are right.
I won’t do that again.
No, that’s not the key.
The key is I saw people of Fude House.
Fude
And their boss
seems to be the one we saw at the Xie’s.
It’s critical.
Did you see it clearly?
Of course.
Hua, since you asked so,
I feel it’s just
almost.
Zhao Xiancai was in Yuzhen House too.
So the one you saw
probably be the head of the killers.
So Yuzhen House must have something
to do with Fude House.
Mr. Shi, how about we assign more people
to take them down?
Don’t act rashly.
Maybe there is an ambush.
Yeah. We will capture them all.
Heng.
Why are you looking at me?
Fishing
always needs some bait.
Sir, anything wrong?
You look great.
But the pulse condition
is worse.
Will it affect giving birth?
According to the pulse condition,
it’s hard to be pregnant,
let alone giving birth.
What?
The tea is ready.
May I have a look?
OK.
Why is there Huanhua Plant in the tea?
Huanhua Plant?
That explains.
If a female take the herb often,
it will cause a lifelong infertility.
How bold you are!
You dare to poison me.
I dare not.
It’s Mr. Xie.
He said it’s for your health.
I have no idea.
Xie Chongjin
tried to do harm to me
for several times.
I can’t feel at ease
if I don’t take the revenge.
Who are you?
Even you three want to kill me?
Ban, open the door please!
Ban!
Ban. It’s terrible!
It’s a big trouble!
Blabbermouth, what do you want?
Ban, my son Chongjin was assassinated.
It’s very dangerous.
Maybe it’s a life danger.
Your son is in trouble.
What does it to do with us?
Listen.
Don’t try to bother us again.
Ban, please don’t say that, OK?
I’m begging you for help.
I heard you have
a Physician Yu who is more skilled
than imperial physicians.
Please forgive me
and help my son.
Rocky, go get Mr. Yu.
Yes. Madam.
Thank you. Mrs. Ban.
Ban, look back,
I’m really sorry.
You are so generous.
Thank you very much.
We have a lot of troubles before.
Then let’s forget it.
Thank you.
Mr. Yu, please go quickly.
Mr. Yu, please go help him.
Mr. Yu, thank you. Please.
Thank you.
For the Xie family,
the second son got one eye blind.
Now the eldest son was assassinated.
Hope Mr. Yu can really help them.
So
man should always be kind.
Blabbermouth has been too mean
so he got his family luck away.
Master is right.
It’s a big trouble.
Why don’t Heng and Hua come out?
Yes.
Young Master went out with Miss.
Go out?
Where are they?
They went for tea.
Tea?
Yuzhen House
Please follow me.
This way please.
Serve me the top tea here.
OK.
Yuzhen House
Sir, come in please.
What is this tea?
How dare you offer me such bad tea?
Young Master Ban.
This is the finest tea here.
Is Yuzhen House
a gangster inn
offering chaff for grain?
You even call this kind of tea
the finest tea?
Go get your boss.
If you don’t make me satisfied today,
I will smash the plate
of your Yuzhen House.
Young Master Ban, please calm down.
I will go get our boss for you.
Hua,
did you recognize the head of killers?
Sir,
Ban Heng is looking for trouble
with a Young Master.
He wants to see you.
I’m afraid they have other purpose.
It doesn’t matter.
I will see him.
You go through the back door.
Yes.
Stop.
You have a dark forehead.
I’m afraid your life is in danger.
How about I tell you the fortune?
Young Master, sorry for our bad service.
This is the finest tea here.
Please try some more.
Don’t block my way. Get out of the way.
Who are you?
It’s just a few days.
But you’ve forgotten me.
You came here yourself…
You think so?
How about we work with her?
Guys.
Find a chance to withdraw.
Action.
Wait.
I have silver.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
It’s wronged for you
to work in Fude House.
How about confessing here?
If so I’ll allow you
to work in Ban’s Mansion.
Hua, are you OK?
Seems we can’t survive today.
If you can tell us Xie Chongjin’s plot,
I will let you go today.
I won’t eat my words.
Everything runs as per its own rules.
From now on,
no Fude House anymore.
Young Master, it’s poison.
They killed themselves
to protect their boss.
Your Highness, my father is guilty.
If I just get in like this,
it may ruin your fame.
Feixian, don’t worry about it.
I’m with you.
Nobody dares to make you in a pickle.
Your Highness.
Get a wing-room for Miss Shi.
She will live in the Mansion
from now on.
Serve her well.
If you are remiss,
I won’t forgive you.
Yes.
Your Highness,
Fude House has an accident.
Fude House has many masters.
What the accident would be?
None of the masters
in Fude House survives.
Who did that?
Count Cheng’an and Mr. Shi.
Why did they work together?
There are many problems
for the social force.
Where is Xie Chongjin?
He was assassinated.
Now he’s seriously injured
and nursed back to health.
Seriously injured?
He managed Fude House.
Everyone feels terror-stricken about it.
Now it’s destroyed.
And Xie Chongjin was assassinated.
Your Highness.
Count Cheng’an worked with Shi Jin.
They must have someone behind.
Do you mean
Crown Prince?
Fude House is a force for Xie Chongjin
and you can dispatch it.
But if His Highness wants to
crack you down,
he will surely take actions first
and wipe out Fude House.
Yes.
Feixian, you are right.
Crown Prince is the only one
who can dispatch both of them.
Yun, what’s wrong?
Miss, bad news.
Young Master Chongjin was assassinated
and got seriously injured last night.
What? Assassinated?
Where is Chongjin now?
He’s recovering at home.
Let’s go home and take a look.
Make way. I’ll go home.
Your Grace, we can’t let you go
without His Highness’s permission.
I’d say it again. Make way!
How dare you be so unbridled?
Back off.
Go down.
Wanyu.
Shi Feixian, I don’t need your help.
You misunderstood me.
I intended to see you
and we see this situation.
Save it.
I’m tired with such kind of words.
Wanyu.
Miss.
Wanyu, I know you are mad at me.
I don’t want to explain.
I’ve begged His Highness
for allowing you to go home.
He agreed.
Wanyu, trust or not,
I’ve always been caring about you.
Wanyu, just go home soon.
I heard your brother
was seriously injured.
Hope he could be fine.
Back off.
Xie’s Mansion
Please save my son.
Dad, Chongjin…
I don’t take it.
Chongjin.
-Why are you doing this to yourself?
-You…
You still need to take the medicine.
If the wound is infected,
it will be injurious to life.
I’d rather die.
Sir, how is my brother?
We stopped bleeding timely.
There is no danger of life.
But he can’t have children of his own.
You’d better enlighten him more.
Can’t have children?
You mean Xie Chongjin can’t
have children anymore?
Here is the thing, Hua.
I asked Zhou Changxiao to get a killer
to kill Xie Chongjin.
He just refused.
But when we took actions,
Xie Chongjin was assassinated.
Is it Zhou Changxiao paying for it
because he is unreconciled?
Zhou Changxiao isn’t that bold.
Look.
They didn’t kill Xie Chongjin
but make him unable to
have a baby anymore.
In my opinion,
it’s for love.
It makes sense.
I can’t believe Xie Chongjin is spoony.
Miss! Miss!
An eunuch from the Palace said
His Majesty wants to see you
and Count Rong.
Please go to the Palace immediately.
Your wedding is drawing near.
I got you
a superior house in the capital.
Take it as my gift for you.
Your Majesty, I can’t accept that.
It’s too big as a gift.
I give it to you,
so you only need to accept it.
That will make me happy.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Just tell me if you need anything.
Your wedding ceremony
must be big enough.
I’m old.
I like happy things.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪