(Episode 4)
You're here.
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
What are you doing
with all the lights off?
Is Ms. Jin not here?
Don't turn the lights on.
I can't wait any longer.
Seok Hoon, let me know
that you love me tonight.
What do you think you're doing?
Joo Seok Hoon!
How can you leave like that?
What do you think you're doing?
Our contract states
that we study together...
and share our tutor. That's all.
If you're going to be like this,
let's not study together anymore.
Don't ever call me here again.
Just promise me one thing.
That you won't fall for Ro Na.
Ro Na and I...
are not together anymore.
It's old news.
- Did I keep you waiting for long?
- No, I came early.
I got the wine recommended.
Do you want the same one?
Sounds good.
How's the hotel? I rented it
for a long time.
You can come
whenever you need a break.
Even better if you want
to come with me.
Thank you. What a surprise.
The view is amazing
and this is so cozy.
There's one more surprise.
Come.
What is it?
You seemed to like
Designer Baek's dresses,
so I got a few custom-made ones.
You can wear them
to your performances this year.
I'll get you new dresses next year.
Why aren't you looking?
What do you think? Do you like them?
Yes, they're beautiful.
Why don't you wear this one
for the luncheon?
I put special care into
customizing this one.
I'm so touched.
When did you prepare all of this?
I'm happy that you're happy.
Shall we throw a toast?
We can relax and drink
until tomorrow.
What should I do?
I think I should get going.
What do you mean?
My mom...
says that she isn't feeling well.
I can't shake her off my mind.
Is she not feeling very well?
That's why you seem so anxious.
You're shaking right now.
I don't think it's anything serious.
I need to go.
Okay. Let's go.
You look pale. I'll give you a lift.
No. I can drive myself.
I'll get going then.
Let me know how Mother's doing.
Did you come back? To see me?
What are you up to?
What do you want?
How did you know I was here?
Did you follow me?
Calm down.
I wondered why you came back.
It was obvious...
that conniving witch Yoon Hee
was using you to get back at me.
Do you not see that
or are you pretending not to?
Let me talk first.
You still have feelings for me,
don't you?
That's why you brought Yoon Hee...
and her daughter to provoke me.
Do you think that will work?
Do you really think...
I'll leave everything I have
and go back to you?
That is so you, Yoon Chul.
Did you just laugh?
Sure. That would be fun,
if I'm putting on an act
just to get you back.
But sorry.
I feel bad for disappointing you
and for your wild imagination,
but I love Yoon Hee.
I guess it really bothered you
that I came back.
I thought you were happy
with Joo Dan Tae,
but I guess not.
Just tell me why you're here
at this hotel.
Why did you do that to me
in New York?
What do you mean?
I don't remember anything.
- Even now?
- What's wrong with you?
I had a meeting at the hotel,
and I saw you in the lobby.
I wanted to confirm...
whether New York was a mistake.
And I did confirm
that it was a mistake.
That's all.
Your feelings for Yoon Hee are real.
You expect me to believe that?
I don't care if you don't.
What's for sure is,
you are no longer in my heart.
So please be careful from now on.
That jerk.
Don't show your face again
if you don't want to die.
That's what I want as well.
(Get lost murderer)
You're just a murderer's daughter.
I'll make you pay, Ro Na.
Hey! What are you doing here?
Did you do this?
Just look the other way...
unless you're with the murderer.
That... That rude brat.
Look at how she talks to an adult.
(Get lost murderer)
Why are you home so late?
Did you hide treasure
in Min Hyuk's home or something?
Something like that.
Why are you still up?
I waited up to talk to you.
Can it wait until tomorrow?
I had a drink, so I'm sleepy.
What is it?
Never mind.
I'll tell you another time.
Okay. Sorry.
I'm going to bed then, okay?
- I love you, princess.
- Me too.
- What is it?
- Ro Na came back to the school.
Ms. Cheon re-enrolled her.
She permitted her re-enrollment.
Ro Na is a murderer's daughter.
It drives me mad already
living in the same building,
but I have to go to
the same school too?
If you have time
to get upset like this,
why don't you prepare
for Cheong A Art Festival?
Other kids can get in
by their talent, but you...
Forget Seoul University of Music.
You can't get into...
any decent college in Seoul without
the principal's recommendation.
You're a moron who can't
even take the midterms...
unless I get you
the answer sheet ahead of time.
You don't expect me to buy
the CSAT answer sheet, do you?
What will you give me...
if I win the grand prize trophy?
Anything you want.
- I want to move out.
- Move out?
Living with Eun Byeol makes me sick.
I want to move out
once I get into college.
I have an apartment
in my name anyway.
You'll move out.
Fine.
I'll think about it
if you bring home the trophy.
I promise.
I'll do whatever it takes...
to bring home
the Cheong A Art Festival trophy.
Is this how you were being treated?
You came back for this?
I won't change my mind.
Go back to the US.
Don't even think
about moving in here.
I'm...
going to live here.
Says who?
I told her to come.
What are you thinking?
Come in, Ro Na.
You must be tired.
I got your room ready. Come in.
Watch your step.
Let's do our best.
Remember there's always someone
on your side whenever you look back.
I'll always cheer you on. Mr. Ha.
(Bae Ro Na's re-enrollment
has been approved.)
Did you ever meet Seol A?
No.
Not even once.
Mr. Lee.
My mom...
did that to Seol A because of me.
I kept throwing a tantrum
and bugged my mom every day...
that I wanted to go
to Cheong A Arts High School.
So...
please hate me.
Please don't hate my mom too much.
Whenever I saw you at Cheong A,
I was reminded of Seol A.
She sang very well like you.
Singing was her dream.
The first day she met Cheon Seo Jin,
she called me.
Anna Lee, correct?
Yes. Please just call me "Anna".
I met Ms. Cheon Seo Jin
for the first time,
and I was so nervous
that my mind went blank.
So I didn't get to say
the stuff I had prepared.
That I'm her huge fan.
She was much more beautiful
in person,
so I must've been in shock.
I saw a photo of her singing,
and my heart pounded so hard.
I suddenly
desperately wanted to sing.
I imagined learning under her
at Cheong A,
and singing a beautiful song
on stage.
And win Cheong A Art Festival's
Grand Prize trophy.
Just by imagining those things,
I became so happy.
If I had a mother,
would I have been able to sing?
(Bae Ro Na)
Seol A.
I'll make your dream come true
on your behalf.
I'll win Cheong A Art Festival's
Grand Prize trophy...
no matter what.
After that,
I'll never sing again.
What are you talking about?
She should, of course,
come back home.
She's too young
to be in the US alone.
So you signed
a parent consent form...
without talking to me first?
Ro Na contacted me directly
and asked me. I couldn't say no.
Yoon Hee, why are you against it?
I really don't understand you.
Ro Na can't be here.
Don't you know what kind of place
Cheong A Arts High School is?
Cheon Seo Jin won't leave her alone.
Don't worry about that.
Ro Na.
I just got a text saying
that I've been re-enrolled.
I'm going to school.
Ro Na, wait for me.
I'm going to work.
Don't skip breakfast.
- Wait...
- Ro Na!
Ro Na.
Let's go.
Ro Na, here.
You didn't have breakfast, right?
Thank you.
Thank you for the necklace too.
I like it.
- Mr. Ha.
- Yes?
Be nice to my mom.
I want at least you...
to be nice to her.
Ro Na, wait for me.
This is so annoying.
Come to my office. It's urgent.
What's going on?
You said it was something urgent.
Do you remember Reporter
Son Hyung Jin of Simin Daily?
He's famous for his critical
articles about me.
Did he publish
another problematic story?
He just got in touch with me.
(Is Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin's
Wedding Called Off?)
(Rumors about Cheon Seo Jin's
Secret Lover)
Reporter Son is planning to publish
these articles today.
What happened?
Didn't you tell me you were going
to your mother last night?
Well, the thing is...
I went back to my room
to get my wallet...
and ran into someone on my way out.
It was someone I'd never met before.
He was drunk and tried to hit on me,
but I pushed him away and left.
These articles are
complete nonsense.
Do you expect me to believe that?
Since when do you
keep secrets from me?
You lied to me
and went to see another man.
Deny it if you can.
Who is he?
Who did you meet last night?
I already told you
that I don't know him!
Do I have to explain about
a drunk man who bumped into me?
You don't know him?
Secretary Cho, come in.
Who is the guy?
We're still trying to find out
because the pictures are blurry.
- Did you contact the hotel?
- I asked for the CCTV footage,
but they refused
for privacy reasons.
Instead of giving me
such a lame answer,
go find him right now!
The word must have
already leaked out.
Our stock plummeted today.
I'll give you an hour.
Bring him in front of me.
Stop!
Secretary Cho, you may leave.
I already denied it.
Shouldn't you believe
whatever I say?
I can't sort this out
unless you tell me the truth.
That leech would do whatever
to publish those articles.
But we should at least
try to make a deal.
That's not necessary.
I can take care of it.
The situation is
not to be underestimated.
I said I can take care of it.
You're lashing out without giving me
a chance to explain.
I don't like it.
I have to get back to school.
Pick up, Yoon Chul.
Pick up, you jerk.
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
Eun Byeol.
Did you know?
Don't your mom have
more power than this?
Is she really so weak
that she had to re-enroll Ro Na?
Watch your mouth.
I'm just as annoyed as you are.
We all have one more
competitor now, you idiot.
Can you do as I say?
We have to kick that girl
out of this school.
You and I are a team now.
How about we fight together...
against our shared enemy?
Why didn't you pick up...
You're here.
Why are you out of breath?
Is it something urgent?
What are you doing here?
Back to our conversation.
I'm waiting for your answer.
Who did I meet last night?
Why do you want to know that?
Just answer my question.
The man in these pictures
is you, right?
That's a rather strange question.
To me, it sounds like
you already know the answer.
Yes, I did meet Seo Jin.
Do you expect your fiancee to report
everything she does to you?
It was late.
And you were at a hotel.
We just ran into each other
by chance.
Don't you think these pictures
look a little contrived?
Don't tell me
you're doubting Seo Jin.
Is everything all right
between you two?
That's it.
You got your answer, so leave.
You've humiliated me enough.
Maybe I should have just walked
past my ex-wife without saying hi.
My bad.
It must be tough for you.
Having to deal with
such an oversensitive fiance.
In today's world,
even silly rumors can
cause stocks to crash.
Are you sure
that rumors are to blame?
Is your company all right?
Ha Yoon Chul.
I'm sorry if I was out of line.
I said that out of concern.
I lied to him because I didn't want
him to get the wrong idea.
Anyway, thank you.
Reporter Son Hyung Jin
of Simin Daily, right?
I'll explain to him.
I didn't do this for you.
It was for Eun Byeol.
We can't hurt her again
with things between you and me.
Mr. Ha, everyone is waiting. Do you
want me to cancel the meeting?
No. Let them in.
From now on, I don't want us
to meet privately.
Yoon Hee wouldn't like it.
Well then.
You couldn't trust me?
You made me apologize to Yoon Chul
for your behavior!
I thought our relationship
was more than this.
You should have told me
that you met Ha Yoon Chul.
Why did you have to complicate
things by lying?
It's because you overreact
to everything.
I didn't want to fight.
It was to protect you.
I had to stop
such ridiculous rumors.
Legally, we have nothing
to do with each other.
Disappoint me again, and I'll...
seriously reconsider
our relationship.
Both our merger...
and marriage.
Cheon Seo Jin.
This is the last time
you can get cute with me.
Did your daughter get back safely?
You knew that Ro Na was
back in Korea.
Why didn't you tell me?
It was Logan's order
to not tell anyone.
You said you'd protect Ro Na.
You promised you wouldn't
let her near Korea.
Didn't you also break your promise?
What do you mean?
Logan must've told you...
to find Seok Kyung's birth mother.
How can I find someone...
who even you guys couldn't find?
You should've approached
Joo Dan Tae.
He'd know where she is.
Why are you looking
for Seok Kyung's birth mother?
You'll find out...
when we find her.
(J King Holdings)
I guess the scandal was quite a hit.
Chairman Joo seems
like he's quite shaken.
Don't you think so,
Reporter Song?
It was quite good for a one-man act.
Well...
I put in quite a lot.
Okay.
Cheon Seo Jin and Joo Dan Tae,
I'll make sure that
I separate you two.
I'll make you two loathe each other.
(Cheong A Arts High School)
Attention!
As announced,
today's the preliminary audition
for the Cheong A Art Festival.
Since it's a school event that will
help with college admissions,
I'm going to make sure...
that every part of the process is...
done completely fairly.
The preliminary round will have
two students pair up...
by a random draw
and have them compete.
I'll now begin the draw.
(Cheong A Arts High School
Classical Singing Preliminaries)
Group One is...
An Eun Woo.
- Why am I in Group 1?
- Next, in Group 2,
Joo Seok Kyung.
And going against
Joo Seok Kyung will be...
(Yoo Jenny, Bae Ro Na)
(Yoo Jenny)
Yoo Jenny.
We're in the same group.
(Joo Seok Kyung, Yoo Jenny)
Group Three.
(Ha Eun Byeol)
Ha Eun Byeol.
Ha Eun Byeol will go against...
Bae Ro Na.
- What?
- Really?
The two are going against each other
in the preliminary round?
I guess so.
It's like a preview of the finals.
These are the groups.
Next, the song
for the preliminary round is...
("Serenade" by Schubert)
"Serenade" by Schubert.
The preliminary round will begin
in two hours,
so get your practice until then.
That's all.
Hello, Chairman Joo.
It's me, Ma Doo Ki.
I've done as you've requested.
You took care of it well, right?
As requested, Eun Byeol and Ro Na
are in the same group together,
meaning that one of them
will get eliminated.
That's one less rival
for Seok Kyung.
There's a chance that Eun Byeol
might get eliminated?
That's right, sir!
Also, I've already talked...
to the judges.
Great work.
Please keep up the good work
until the finals.
If Seok Kyung wins,
you'll get a reward...
that's different from any
that you've received so far.
It's not like I'm doing this
for anything in return,
but thank you.
I'll do my best to make sure...
that you get your way.
Yoo Jenny. Bring that right now.
Headshot!
What are you doing?
Red looks good on you, Ro Na.
Must be because
your mother is a murderer.
The case is already closed!
My mom was proven innocent,
and the real murderer was caught.
Why do you keep saying
that my mom is a murderer?
Shut it!
Your mom is the one
who killed my mom.
You'll forever be
a murderer's daughter.
Is this...
because you feel sorry for your mom?
What?
Are you bullying me
because you feel guilty...
for not having been good
to your mom?
Does this make you feel better?
What are you doing?
Bae Ro Na! What happened?
The preliminary round is
starting soon.
How can you be messing around?
That's not it.
Go to the bathroom and wash up.
Your uniform will stain.
You don't have much time,
so just wash up quickly.
Everyone, get to the auditorium.
Goodness.
I'll help you. Come on up.
(Cheong A Arts High School)
Quick!
What are you two doing here?
My goodness.
You haven't gone yet?
We're heading to the preliminaries.
It's tomorrow
for the piano majors, right?
Did you get a lot of practice?
Yes. I'm heading
to my lesson right now.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Take the blouse off.
I'll wash it for you.
It's fine. I'll do it.
We don't have time.
The preliminaries are starting soon.
You can clean your skirt.
Thank you.
We should just go.
You're going to be late too.
Jenny? What are you doing?
Excuse me! Please open the door!
The door is locked!
It's no use.
Nobody is coming.
You and I are being bullied.
Did you know from the start?
That's the rule
at Cheong A Arts High School.
The rule that Seok Kyung
and Eun Byeol made.
If you help the one being bullied,
you'll get bullied as well.
Didn't you know?
(Cheong A Arts High School
Preliminaries Group One)
(The 28th Cheong A Arts High School
Classical Singing Preliminaries)
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
Next, Group Two. Joo Seok Kyung.
(The 28th Cheong A Arts High School
Classical Singing Preliminaries)
Yoo Jenny.
Where's Yoo Jenny?
Jenny and Ro Na aren't here.
What? They're still not here?
What should we do, Director?
Should we wait for them?
Let's see the other groups first.
We should at least
give them a chance.
(The 28th Cheong A Arts High School
Classical Singing Preliminaries)
What are you doing?
Get out of my way.
I won't let them take me down.
I won't lose to them!
It's no use!
Let go!
Yoo Jenny!
(Cheong A Arts High School)
Get out already.
We don't have much time.
What are you doing?
That's all the groups.
It wouldn't be fair to wait
for them any longer.
By default, why don't we pass...
Seok Kyung and Eun Byeol instead?
- What?
- Nice!
I guess we have no choice.
We'll eliminate Yoo Jenny
and Bae Ro Na.
Joo Seok Kyung and Ha Eun Byeol are
going to the next round.
I'm here.
I'm not late, am I?
That's too bad. Time's up.
You've just been eliminated.
Please let me sing.
It's not over yet.
Being on time is the key in tests.
This is a consequence
of not being on time.
Accept it.
Someone locked me in the bathroom...
on purpose.
Who would do that?
Joo Seok Kyung, Ha Eun Byeol.
Why did you do that? Tell me.
Were you that insecure
about your singing?
Were you that scared about me
going to the finals?
Bae Ro Na! What are you doing?
I won't give you a chance
just because you do this.
I'm serious. Please believe me.
How can you prove it?
Jenny was with me.
Jenny is a witness.
She's lying!
What's happening?
Ro Na said that we should pretend
to be locked in the bathroom...
because we can't beat the girls
with our skills,
and that we have to
frame them as bullies...
to go to the finals.
She locked me in the bathroom
and didn't let me out.
Did you plot
all of this on your own?
Ro Na, are you insane?
Jenny, why are you doing this?
Are you done?
Yes.
Jenny, we are
in the same group, right?
How can you be so unlucky?
I guess your ticket
to the finals is already gone.
You're not going to try hard...
to beat me, are you?
Don't be scared.
We're here to help you.
There's one way that you can
make it to the finals.
What is it?
Just prove to us...
that you're our friend, not Ro Na's.
Then, you'll make it to the finals,
and you won't be bullied.
We can let you
into the SNU Club too.
What do you think?
Ro Na! Are you
seriously that dirty?
How can you plot all of this
even if this is important?
What a terrible person you are.
Yoo Jenny.
Are you speaking the truth?
Can we count on your words?
Yes, you can.
No, she's lying.
I didn't do such a thing.
I was the one who was locked.
I'm the victim here!
Mr. Ma, with the authority
as the Director,
I'll send Bae Ro Na
to the disciplinary committee.
Any insulting behavior
against Cheong A Arts Festival...
cannot be forgiven.
Please punish her...
according to the school's rules.
Go and tell them
that I didn't do it.
That they made you do this.
Were you in on their plot too?
Were you one of them all along?
Why? Why can't I be?
Do you know what I've been through
because of you?
I've been bullied and cursed at
instead of you!
Just because I bought you
some bread.
Just because I said that I feel
sorry for you once!
So, shouldn't you
take one for me too?
I have to make it
to Seoul National University...
as I've been through so much for it.
College is the only way
out of this nightmare.
So,
you're saying that it's okay for me
to be expelled again?
I was never a kind person.
Get up.
When did you come?
I watched everything
that happened to you and Jenny.
I know you hate me,
but you need my help right now.
I'll make sure that you can
still attend this school.
A bully?
Min Hyuk is the one with
the broken arm here.
How dare they blame him?
Nonsense!
Ro Na's mom is a lunatic.
That's not the important thing.
Because of Ro Na,
my Jenny got eliminated from
the preliminaries. How can it be?
We need to have a parents' meeting
and make sure they suffer.
A bully?
You!
You should've just quietly
backed off if you were insecure.
Why did you bring
my innocent Jenny into this?
You got my Jenny eliminated too.
What are you going to do?
How dare you come back here...
and ruin everything?
I didn't do anything!
Calm down.
We're going to get blamed
if you keep acting out.
How can I calm down?
"Participated in the finals
of the Cheong A Arts Festival."
You know how important that is
for student records.
This girl stripped
that chance away from Jenny!
Jenny is resilient.
She can do well on the CSAT
and still go to college.
Ms. Cheon, please give
Jenny a chance.
She was unfairly stripped
of her chance.
Shouldn't you give her a chance?
Do you even care about Jenny?
What is she saying?
Are you still insane?
Tell them the truth!
Get your hands off of my daughter!
Ro Na!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
How can an adult do that to a child?
Don't you realize that
this is abuse?
How can all of you just sit
and watch child abuse happen?
If you lay a finger on
our Ro Na one more time,
I'm going to sue you all.
You sure love law enforcement.
But...
you can't deny the law of genetics.
A criminal mom bred a bully.
This is just great.
This is why I say
the family matters.
You nobodies with no roots.
Shut your mouth!
Hit me.
If you want to end up in jail.
That will suit you right.
That's enough!
Please act accordingly
with the prestige of Hera Palace.
Everyone take your seat.
Seriously.
Ro Na. Who are the school's bullies?
Joo Seok Kyung.
Lee Min Hyuk.
And Ha Eun Byeol.
What?
Do you have proof
that you were assaulted?
She has no proof.
She's making it all up
so she doesn't get expelled.
That's what you call
making a false accusation.
Do you know how serious it is
to make a false accusation?
My daughter is here as a victim,
not as an assailant.
Shouldn't you listen
to the victim first?
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
Ro Na. Go on, tell them.
Today, Joo Seok Kyung filled
a bucket with water and paint...
and poured it on me.
While I was washing up,
she intentionally locked me
and Jenny in the bathroom.
Ro Na. Your dream must be
to become a novelist.
Ha Eun Byeol and
Lee Min Hyuk watched on,
but they did nothing to stop her.
No one saw it
and no one said they did it.
Why should we believe you?
It's your word against theirs.
The kids are lying.
If the assailants deny it,
is there no victim?
Ma'am. You can't believe
just what your child says...
and post such a serious lie...
on the Office of Education website.
Post a correction
and apologize officially.
If you don't, be prepared
to face a criminal charge.
The school isn't interested at all
in uncovering the truth anyway.
Also,
the disciplinary committee
has already decided...
to forcibly transfer Bae Ro Na for
tainting the image of the school...
and trying to turn students
against each other.
As all the teachers have consented,
we will process it expeditiously.
I understand.
If you insist on denying it,
you give me no choice.
I will submit a formal complaint
with the Office of Education.
Are you mad?
You're not calling anyone!
Are you trying to keep our kids
from going to college?
- Let go.
- You should apologize.
How shameless!
- How dare you touch her?
- Is this why you came?
Honey! Call the cops on her!
Fine! Tell the Office of Education!
I'll tell the reporters...
- and take this up officially.
- Get off.
You jerk.
How dare you threaten us?
Stop it, Mom!
Jenny! I'm glad you're here.
Tell them everything she did to you.
Make this brat stop lying.
She's not lying.
What Ro Na said...
was all true.
What?
What? Are you saying
Min Hyuk is a bully?
You'd better think carefully
before you speak.
Did... Did Ro Na threaten you?
You little witch.
What did you do
to my innocent daughter?
I said to stop!
I'm the one who was bullied!
For a year, I was beaten up
and cursed at.
I'm the one who was bullied.
I'm an outcast just like Ro Na.
You don't know anything!
So stop it!
Outcast?
What do you mean? Why?
Why were you bullied?
- Oh my gosh.
- Goodness.
What... What's wrong with your hair?
How long has it been this way?
How long has it been?
Who was it?
Who did this to you?
Who did this to my daughter?
Tell me!
This is Jenny's medical record
I got from the hospital today.
She has suffered from...
stress-induced hair loss
and reflux esophagitis for a while.
Jenny won't betray us, will she?
Definitely not.
She has to do as we say...
if she wants to compete
at Cheong A Art Festival.
What's the point in making it
to the festival?
She won't win anyway.
Isn't it better to frame her
as Ro Na's accomplice?
How dare she try to go to
Seoul University of Music?
Darn it. This is a secret.
You know Jenny's mom lied
about going to Ehwa University.
For real?
My mom's the alumni chair
of Ewha's School of Communication.
She looked into it,
and Jenny's mom wasn't on the list
of Home Economics grads.
Did she lie about her education?
No wonder.
She was so obviously ignorant.
Even the way she speaks is so cheap.
She's a total outcast
in Hera Palace, isn't she?
That's why she was close to Ro Na.
Birds of a feather.
Birds of a feather flock together.
It's scientifically proven.
Maybe her designer bags
are knockoffs.
It must be so hard to act rich
when they're poor.
Will you just keep being bullied?
Let go of me.
I've reported it
to the Office of Education...
that you were assaulted
by school bullies.
So you should let it out too.
Why did you do it?
Who gave you the right?
I said I didn't want to. I said no!
At least your mom needs to know.
If she finds out later,
she'll feel worse
and even more heartbroken.
I personally recorded this today.
What was that?
Ro Na did nothing wrong.
I lied.
My gosh.
We'll post this...
on the Office of
Education's website...
as evidence of school violence.
Seok Kyung. What were you thinking?
How could you do this?
A bully at Cheong A?
Do you know how serious this is?
Sorry.
I got too upset.
No. Seok Kyung was wrong.
I think Ro Na's family
is determined.
They already reported it
to the Office of Education.
The investigators
will come tomorrow.
If what happened to Jenny
gets out too,
things will blow up
to be much worse.
Sorry. You'll have to
fix this for us.
Apologize to her this instant!
I only did as Eun Byeol told me.
I may be the only one in the video,
but Eun Byeol was next to me.
It was her idea to throw
the paint on her...
and to lock her in the bathroom.
It's the truth.
Putting the blame on
Eun Byeol is going too far.
I'm disappointed.
I heard you did it although
Eun Byeol tried to stop you.
Did she say that?
That she tried to stop me?
That's what all the kids said.
That you led the bullying
of Jenny too.
Eun Byeol brought all the foods...
that we fed Jenny.
Why are you only protecting her?
I see.
She gets preferential treatment.
You said we were family.
Was it all a lie?
That's enough!
You should repent!
How dare you accuse her?
Why don't you believe me?
She weaseled out by herself?
Ha Eun Byeol.
Be careful until you get into
the Seoul National University.
This is the most crucial time.
With school violence
in your student record,
you'll have to forget
about early admission.
Get your act together.
An assemblyman's son shouldn't
get involved in school violence.
Lie low from now on...
and pin everything on Seok Kyung.
Answer me.
Gosh, I know how to handle it.
Who is it at this hour?
Who is it?
Oh, my.
What's wrong?
- Ms. Kang, what are you doing?
- Give that to me.
What's going on? Why are you
taking away my son's phone?
- Start.
- Let's go.
- What are you waiting for?
- Drink it.
You look the prettiest
when you're drinking soda.
Drink faster.
Ms. Kang, you're scaring me.
Get off me!
Ms. Kang, calm down.
Think of our friendship.
You need to calm down.
Kids fight all the time.
It's not a big deal.
Shut it, you jerk.
What...
Is she out of her mind?
Gosh, I was so close
to capturing the castle.
This is not okay.
That woman is out of line.
Seok Kyung! Open the door!
- Open it!
- What's wrong, ma'am?
- Calm down.
- Get out of my way!
- Where is Seok Kyung?
- Please calm down.
- Ma'am.
- Move.
- Seok Kyung! Where is she?
- Calm down, ma'am.
- Get off me.
- Ma'am.
I said, get off me!
What's going on? It's still early.
How can you be sleeping?
Go apologize to Jenny right now.
Why? I didn't do anything wrong.
She is the one who betrayed me
and sided with Ro Na.
- That turncoat.
- Shut it, Seok Kyung!
Have you lost your mind?
Who gives you the right to hit me?
Who do you think you are?
Does that hurt?
Get your act together.
I can't put up with you anymore.
At least pretend to be sorry,
or I'll blow up
the whole penthouse, okay?
What is going on here?
You need to raise
your daughter better, Mr. Joo.
Are you lecturing me now?
Are you in the position to?
I won't let this slide.
I'll make sure she can't enter
Cheong A Art Festival...
and is punished,
whether she is expelled
or transferred.
You want the daughter of the head
of operations transferred?
I don't think that's possible.
Our contract ended today.
We're even.
I don't owe you anything anymore.
Do you want me to reveal
what you did to my husband,
which you tried to cover up...
by giving me an apartment?
I don't think it's a good idea
to bring that up, Ms. Kang.
It was for Jenny's sake
that my husband took the fall...
and went to prison instead of you.
To give our daughter a good life.
And your daughter
ripped her heart to pieces.
Nothing can stop me now.
I don't know how far I'll go.
Be prepared. I might even...
kill your daughter, Seok Kyung.
You're out of your mind.
What? Do you think
it serves me right?
I know you think it's only fair.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
Yes.
I wonder if you finally
understand me.
What?
When your child is bullied,
you become
so frustrated and upset...
that your body shakes...
and your blood boils.
You can neither sleep...
nor eat.
You want to destroy everyone.
You can't understand it
until you've experienced it.
I've been there.
I'm being punished now, right?
Because of me, Ro Na was called
by the school violence committee.
I hit, insulted,
and bullied the innocent girl.
I'm being punished for that now.
I've been a terrible parent.
It's all my fault, Ms. Oh.
Save your energy.
For now,
be strong and focus
on protecting Jenny.
Feel free to tell me
if I can help you with anything.
If you fall apart, it's over.
Jenny has no one else to rely on.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Ms. Oh.
I'm so sorry.
(Cheong A Arts High School)
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
Jenny's mother is asking the school
violence committee to step in.
Once the Office of Education
starts investigating,
things will get quite complicated...
with Ro Na and
Jenny's incidents and everything.
To protect the school,
someone will have to take the fall.
Put up a notice.
(Disciplinary Committee's Decision)
(Joo Seok Kyung: Probation and
disqualification from Art Festival)
(Yoo Jenny and Bae Ro Na:
Participation in Art Festival)
Probation? This is insane.
Is this your mom's doing?
Ha Eun Byeol. So you ran away?
(Joo Seok Hoon)
You're the one who got me
out of the bathroom, right?
Why didn't you reply to me?
I sent you an e-mail.
I was busy.
I know you're going through a lot,
but you don't have to feel
uncomfortable around me.
I wanted to know how you were doing.
Both in the US and when I got back.
What about you?
Did you ever think about me?
What are you doing over there?
Nothing.
Hey. Eun Byeol!
Gosh, what was the pattern?
Was it "J"?
Yes.
I'm the only one being disciplined?
Not a chance.
Eun Byeol. I'll tell the world
who your boyfriend is.
- Let go!
- Please!
Let go!
Let go! Oh no.
What is this?
Seok Kyung! It was you, wasn't it?
You took my phone.
Why did you steal my phone?
I didn't steal it.
You dropped it,
so I planned to return it to you.
Did you look through my phone?
I don't know your lock pattern.
Why? Are you hiding something big?
She didn't see it, did she?
Why are you here?
You said I was your daughter too.
Can't a daughter
visit her mom to hang out?
I'm busy.
Say what it is and leave.
I have many documents to review.
Cheong A Art Festival is
in a few days.
I've waited really long for it.
What dress should I wear?
I'm so excited.
The notice should be up by now.
The teachers decided today...
to disqualify you from entering.
What you did was too heinous.
It was out of my hands.
Don't make jokes.
My dad asked you, remember?
Just let me compete.
You're the director.
You have the power.
Oh dear. Did I surprise you?
I was imitating Eun Byeol.
I don't need to
respond anymore, right?
Since you're being nice anyway,
how about you give me
the grand prize?
- What?
- If you truly love my dad,
you can do that much for me.
Are you kidding me?
You have no skills. How could you
ask for the grand prize?
You know...
I can't beat Eun Byeol
with my skills.
That's why I'm being shameless
and asking you for this favor.
Must I call your dad
for you to shut your mouth?
Get out.
Now.
You'll regret it
if you act like that.
I know a pretty big secret,
lady.
What?
When Director Cheon Myung Soo
passed away,
you were on the staircase with him.
Why did you just run away?
Instead of saving your dad?
What did you just say?
You must've been shocked.
Okay, then. Shall we restart
our discussion?
(The Penthouse 2)
I hear you're stepping down
as director. Is it true?
Even if you hate me,
how could you attack me
with Yoon Hee?
You must have many enemies
on top of me, Seo Jin.
You must beat Ro Na.
Even if you must kill her.
No matter what anyone says,
you're my only daughter, Eun Byeol.
Then prove
that I'm your only daughter.
The recipient of the Grand Prize,
given to the singer...
who has the most-divine voice, is...
Did you want the grand prize
that badly?
Is everything set
for me to win the grand prize?
Seok Kyung.
I won't let anyone
take Cheong A from me.