THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
FINAL EPISODE
Stop.
- Search it.
- Yes, sir!
There is nothing suspicious.
We have arrived.
Check all the wagons with the
gifts for the King thoroughly.
Yes, sir.
- Your Highness!
- Head Inspector.
How...
Your Majesty!
I finally caught that little rat.
When does the ceremony start?
- In the afternoon.
- Then we have some time, right?
We should not let our
guard down. Let us hurry.
Hold on.
- What was that for?
- I don't know.
I am sure we have enough time for this.
- We should really get going.
- Okay.
EPISODE 20, MY LIFE WITHOUT ME
Your Majesty.
Wait. I am not done cleaning up.
Oh, my goodness!
Your Majesty.
How wronged must you feel...
for your soul to be
wandering around the palace?
Your Majesty.
Head Eunuch.
Come with me.
With you?
Go away!
Your Majesty. Please enter Nirvana.
You should come with me.
Your Highness.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty! You are alive!
Your Majesty. What happened to you?
It goes well with your royal robe.
I have such good taste.
Over there!
You little jerk.
Oh, yes!
Why are you so good?
Shall I say it's a vibe
that comes from experience?
What comes from experience?
I'm amazing with knives.
Do not attempt to do anything meaningless.
How many soldiers are protecting the Palace?
You are too late.
That is the sound that signifies
the start of the enthronement.
How dare you speak down to me!
The enthronement ceremony
is starting already?
Bow in reverence...
four times...
and sit upright.
I cannot believe they
started the ceremony early.
Hey. I have to tell you something.
I set up a backup plan just in case.
What are you doing? Hurry up and continue.
The thing is...
the Royal seal has disappeared!
The Royal seal is missing!
I must have lost my mind.
I got overexcited upon hearing
that it was a special mission.
Raise your head.
I am offering my greetings to
you for the first time, Your...
Highness?
Lee Saeng Mang.
You are Lee Saeng Mang.
Have you lost your mind?
Or have I lost my mind?
You had the Royal seal stolen?
I'm a bit crazy, you know.
That means we still have a chance.
- Let us go.
- Okay.
I was able to do it last time.
- Do it properly.
- Be quiet.
Why you...
Special Director Hong.
Is it you again?
I told you not to come!
The thing is...
I do not have anyone I could ask.
The Queen had asked me to
steal something for her.
This bright and precious-looking item...
seems quite ominous.
What is that?
The Royal seal.
Do you know...
where you came after stealing the Royal seal?
This is the Department of Justice...
Did I come to prison on my own volition?
Why are you giving this to me?
What are you doing here?
I came by to see my friend.
You must not be here. Please leave right now.
Hold on!
Who dares lay a hand on my best friend?
Have you lost your mind?
How could you blatantly
reveal the Royal seal?
"The Royal seal"?
Do you want to take a look at it?
- It is a bomb!
- Everybody run!
They passed the gates of Hanyang
and all the gates to the capital?
Yes, sir. If you give us the
orders to use the cannons...
Finishing the enthronement without
a problem is most important,
so hold off on using the cannons.
And send all of the soldiers
to each of the capital gates.
Hurry!
Once the enthronement ceremony ends,
I will get rid of all of them.
How can we hold the enthronement
without the Royal seal?
Goodness. How could such a thing happen?
What on earth are you doing?
How can you be so useless?
What is it?
So?
As of right now, it is
hard for us to attack...
due to an unidentifiable acrid smoke.
Since the enthronement must
end without any problems,
I have sent soldiers to each
gate to stop them completely.
It is a confusion tactic.
What is it?
A CONFUSION TACTIC TO FEINT TO
THE EAST AND ATTACK IN THE WEST.
It is nothing.
I will bring the Royal seal myself.
Call the soldiers back
into the Palace right now.
- Pardon?
- Did you not hear me?
Yes, sir.
It's so empty in here.
I see things are going
according to our plans.
We have come all the way here.
Are you scared?
I am, and I am...
overwhelmed.
Right. This is how you feel...
right before you face the boss in a game.
That is correct. The boss.
If you die before you can beat
the boss, you end up cursing...
because you have to start
from the beginning again.
We only get one chance.
Gosh. I'm getting scared.
Shall we get going?
He caught him.
My Queen!
I'm okay. It's because
the noise surprised me.
It doesn't hurt.
My Queen!
My Queen! Do not move.
We have to stop the ceremony.
You come first.
I must take a look at the injury.
My King.
Am I going back?
No.
Why now of all times?
Please...
After I see that he's alive.
Let me just make sure he's okay.
DANGER, RISK OF FALLING
Is it my body? Am I back?
What about Cheoljong?
No. I must save him.
But how can I?
That happened 200 years ago.
VIP WARD
What? Jang Bong Hwan?
Mr. Jang Bong Hwan!
Jang Bong Hwan? The patient?
Stop!
You can't run like that! You just woke up!
Mr. Jang Bong Hwan!
- Mr. Jang Bong Hwan!
- Go after him!
Mr. Jang Bong Hwan!
Stop right there!
Stop him!
- Stop him.
- Gosh. Why are you doing this?
Goodness.
Come on.
- What?
- Hey!
Darn his youth.
Was he really in a vegetative
state for a few months?
DAEHAN BOOKSTORE
"Veritable Records of the Joseon Dynasty".
"VERITABLE RECORDS OF THE JOSEON DYNASTY"
Please don't die. You can't die like that.
THE 22ND KING OF THE JOSEON DYNASTY
THE ERA OF KING CHEOL...
THE ERA OF KING CHEOLJO'S DIRECT RULE
He is not here.
He is gone.
Your Majesty.
You cannot leave like this.
Please wake up, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
- Your Majesty.
- My Queen.
Are you okay?
I am okay.
But you are bleeding a lot.
Seeing how it is utterly painful,
I guess I will not die from it.
These bulletproof vests saved both of us.
Thank goodness.
What on earth are you doing?
How can the King sides
with the Donghak believers?
I guess...
I am still the King.
You should not have done anything.
If you accepted your place and stood still,
everyone would have been happy.
I am...
the family of those you killed.
I am the King of the people you trampled on!
Standing still is impossible.
You are out of breath.
I doubt that you can dodge my sword!
Your...
No. Please, my baby. Please.
Kill me.
Live.
Living in humiliation...
is your punishment.
If you kill yourself,
I will do whatever it takes to save you.
I do not care about the damage
or the pain I put you through.
But I will make sure that you are breathing.
Living like an empty shell.
That experience...
will be engraved deep in your bones.
What will you do? Hiding in
the crowd is your specialty,
but there isn't a single soul
walking by because of the curfew.
You no longer have anywhere to hide.
My Queen.
Go finish your fight first.
No, I will not do that.
Nothing matters more to me than you do.
Do not worry.
I will overcome this no matter what.
Your Majesty!
I will escort Her Highness.
You must go.
We do not know what will happen if we stall.
Please, you should go.
I will be back very soon.
Okay.
Your Highness.
Are you all right?
Find a way!
You are all utterly useless!
Show your dignity as the King.
I am terrified, Grand Queen Dowager.
You ought to protect your position!
Out of the throne.
Grand Queen Dowager.
I shall greet you.
Greet His Majesty the King!
My Queen!
Her Highness is unconscious at the moment.
What happened?
Her Highness is showing signs of miscarriage.
There is some vaginal bleeding.
If it continues, both Her
Highness and the baby...
will not be safe.
Then why are you removing the needles?
At the moment, even this acupuncture
treatment is too much for her.
All we can do is wait and pray
that they will get through this.
She might not make it tonight.
- Your Highness! No!
- Your Highness...
Your Majesty. We are truly sorry,
but please leave the room for
a moment so we can treat her.
Your Majesty, we should give them a moment.
Your Highness!
There is nothing I can do!
My Queen.
Both Her Highness and the baby are okay now.
Your Majesty.
I am truly relieved. Both you and our baby...
You are both okay.
Your Majesty.
It is all over.
Who knew that the King was truly outstanding?
Your Highness!
How dare you scream like
that? Where are your manners?
Well,
the King has given an order to
move you to the West Palace.
What?
How dare he try to confine
me at the West Palace?
Who does he think I am?
What are you doing? Open the door now.
I cannot open the door, Your Highness.
Open this door immediately!
The Queen is here.
Open it.
I heard you were in critical
condition last night,
but you seem fine.
It is all thanks to you.
Where are you going?
Must I report my whereabouts to you?
It has been decided that you
will stay in the West Palace.
Until then, stay at Tongmyeongjeon Hall...
and you are not allowed to go out.
Are you telling me you
are locking me up here?
Do not be ridiculous.
Move!
You cannot leave.
I told you to move!
Your Highness.
If your last day comes,
it will be at the palace.
Court Lady Chun, what are you doing?
Yes, Your Highness.
How dare you?
This is no longer your era.
The ruler of the Internal Court...
is me.
I am the ruler.
I am still here!
It belongs to me!
From this day on, everything will change,
especially the rules and the etiquettes...
you made and maintained.
They have been around for thousands of years!
Do you think you can
tear them down overnight?
They are already collapsing.
The change you have feared the most...
has already begun.
Darn it. That totally hit the spot!
Gosh.
Court Lady Choi, what did I just say?
"Darn it. That totally hit the spot!"
That is what you said.
Perhaps, my hidden
instincts have been awoken.
That really hit the spot.
I cannot stop saying it. Darn it.
Shoot.
That felt nice.
Darn it! Scumbags!
Darn it.
What is this about?
"The following offender, Jo,"
"spread a rumor to slander the Queen..."
"and brought doubts to the royal blood."
"In the end, she had
disgraced the royal family."
"You will be punished for
bringing confusion to the empire."
"You will be exiled in the West Palace."
This is another conspiracy.
I have never done such things.
Are you telling the truth?
I swear it on the honor of the late king.
I have never done such things.
Come in.
"The following offenders'
assets will be confiscated."
"And they will be smacked 100 times..."
"and become the slaves of
the empire in Jeju Island."
"But their wives and children will
not be punished for their crimes."
"Former Chief State Councilor Kim Byung Hak."
"Former Right State Councilor Jo Man Hong."
"Former Left State Councilor Kim Seok Geun."
"Former Minister of War Kim Chang Hyup."
"Former Chief Secretariat Kim So Heun."
"Former Minister of Personnel Jo Deok Moon."
"And other offenders
listed on this decree..."
"will not be executed."
"Their assets will be confiscated."
"They will be imprisoned for three years."
- It is not true, Your Majesty.
We had no choice as we were threatened...
by Kim Byeong In who plotted
the whole thing alone.
We never wanted...
to plot treason.
I ask for your mercy, Your Majesty.
He is right, Your Majesty.
Our only crime is that...
we foolishly believed the false
news that you were killed...
by the Donghak believers. Our
foolishness is the only crime.
Is that so?
Then, I will name another
crime you have committed.
Right now, in Joseon,
the ones with a lot of
assets are the guilty ones.
Is anyone here considered poor?
You filled your stomachs with
the hard work of the people.
You have forgotten your duty of
leading and taking care of...
the people by maintaining order.
You stood over the people
and trampled on them.
You made the people to farm...
on a rocky mountain by plowing the field.
And in exchange, you
extorted even more taxes.
When you lived in luxury
with an abundance of food,
the people lived in poverty
and worried about food...
all night long.
"How can I get more money?"
"How can I get more power?"
"How can I become more influential?"
When that was all you could think about,
their lives became nothing but pain.
Thinking about their future was
the last thing on their mind.
They had to live in pure torment.
Your first crime is...
valuing your life more than the people's.
Your second crime is...
torturing them and robbing
them of any future.
Making the fathers hopeless for
failing to protect their families...
and the King, his empire,
is your third crime.
If you are not guilty of these crimes,
step forward.
Never forget your crimes.
And repent.
You are...
just a group of shameless thieves.
But...
- What a jerk!
- He deserves death.
- My gosh.
- He should be ripped to pieces.
- You ought to die!
- Scumbag!
- Jerk!
- You must be punished!
- You deserve death!
- What a scumbag.
- Goodness.
- Pay for what you did!
- He ought to die.
- What an awful man!
- Goodness.
- You deserve death!
Leave them here.
But you always wear makeup.
I know that you will never be
able to leave the West Palace...
or meet anyone.
But...
I kept you around...
because you carelessly reveal your thoughts.
You are not the type to
have ulterior motives.
That is right.
Everyone lives their lives differently.
Your Highness.
Why are you not getting mad
at me like you always do?
You are so tactless until the very end.
Even I am holding in my
tears, so why are you crying?
Your Highness.
I will survive this.
Surviving this...
is the only way I can win.
Join hands with me, just until
you can get out of this unscathed.
What are you up to?
If such memories are intact,
So Yong is still alive inside you.
You found me again, Byeong In.
Even when I was hiding.
- I apologize, Your Highness.
It is nice to hear the sounds of laughter.
You have changed a lot, Your Highness.
I was not like myself for a while
after the Royal wedding, right?
It is because...
becoming the Queen was
such a big change for me.
You have changed a lot from how
you were before the Royal wedding.
I thought that the only decision...
I could make for myself was death.
I CAME HERE FOR NOTHING. JANG BONG HWAN
Have you returned well?
Your Highness!
- Father!
- No!
Your body must feel heavy,
so do not come to me.
I will go to you.
- How is your health?
You may speak first, Father.
No, it is okay. You may go first.
- I am fine.
Have you been well?
Of course.
I am alive thanks to you.
When the rebel army...
penetrated the gates of
Hanyang during the ceremony.
all of the noblemen were in fear.
The village people came forward
to protect our home then.
They said we were a virtuous family
who opened up our storehouse...
and helped them.
All I did was do as you said,
so I felt sorry and embarrassed.
You can show your virtue from now on.
Of course.
I must become a respectable grandfather...
for your child.
Oh, my. He is kicking.
Is he already kicking?
My grandson must be a genius!
Is the scent of scallions too strong?
What are you so focused on making?
I am trying to recreate
the samhyang ramyeon...
that the Queen made.
Then may I have some ramyeon?
It will be done soon.
I thought I could take it easy
once the reign of peace started,
but I am busier than ever.
Nobody is here.
Special Director Hong.
I am busy. We can play tujeon later.
I have stopped playing tujeon.
You did?
Because I made such a big contribution,
the King has decided to
give me a government post.
But...
I am still Special Director Hong.
Did you ask for a position as a premier?
What is that object that makes you look ugly?
You are so unaware of new trends.
I have applied as a delegate
for the foreign ministry.
Joseon is too small for such
a talented person like me.
Congratulations on quitting tujeon.
What about becoming a delegate?
Having to walk until you
get blisters on your feet...
is nothing to be congratulated for.
I still cannot believe that
Lee Saeng Mang is the Queen.
you had not figured that out.
Du Il, Are you done with...
I see you were here too.
It has been a while Jong Cheol...
If Lee Saeng Mang is the
Queen, then Jong Cheol, you...
You must be a woman.
Gosh, Kim Hwan.
You are incredibly astute.
I heard you received a government post.
I received it from the King.
Oh, my goodness.
- Sam Wol, you should go in first.
- Yes, ma'am.
What brings you here?
It is so cold. Did you wait long?
No. I just got...
What is wrong?
Just a cramp.
How is everything?
Good.
All is well with His Majesty.
No.
I was asking about you.
I am...
Things are pretty stable
with Samjung Ijungchung now.
Thanks to it, I am swamped with work.
So? What is next?
I wish...
to share my power with every
single one of the people...
so they can be stronger than
me when they come together.
That way, the corrupt shall never
be able to exploit them again.
I believe that is how
this difficult battle...
and this wonder-filled journey...
should end.
So you are saying I'll be even busier now.
Let us call it a day.
My goodness.
Let us just go home.
You can go through that tomorrow morning.
We just don't click.
But you should tidy up before...
- Have a restful night.
- Will do.
Du Il, you need to organize...
Du Il!
Gosh, that punk.
THE QUEEN'S DICTIONARY
Did I lose something?
From time to time, I feel...
He did it.
He managed to pull it off.
THE ERA OF KING CHEOLJO'S DIRECT RULE
THE ANNALS OF KING CHEOLJO
My Queen.
Is this not funny?
Jang Bong Hwan!
Don't come closer.
I must find Secretary Han first.
No, would it be the fastest to
just go directly to the media?
Why are you running away?
You did a good deed!
"Good deed"?
Then why are you keeping tabs on me?
No, we're trying to protect you because...
you sent us a tip for the
sake of public interest.
"Public interest"?
Well, remember the CCTV
camera in the food storage?
You fixed it in secret.
I did?
Hold on.
Do you manage the CCTV camera?
It's odd that it keeps breaking.
I must catch this thief.
Why did you do something so useless?
This is very unlike you.
There you are. Why didn't you
come sooner to tell me this?
I already got myself in trouble.
- What?
- I sent the CCTV footage...
to the media for free,
which is very unlike me.
He's lying.
Yes, I'm sure.
The Jang Bong Hwan I know
doesn't care about justice.
He'd come to me and try...
to strike a deal before going
to the media. Am I wrong?
You're right.
That's the kind of jerk that I am.
But you know what?
- I've changed.
- Really?
- Why?
- No idea.
I just wanted to do it.
You scumbag!
Chef Bu!
- Darn it.
- You jerk!
Cheoljong managed to change his fate,
and I've changed too.
Then how come Secretary
Han is still the same?
BOOK BROWSER
CHEOLJO
Don't tell me the world didn't change at all.
Are Cheoljong and I the
only ones that changed?
"THE VERITABLE RECORDS
OF THE JOSEON DYNASTY"
CHEOLJO'S ACHIEVEMENTS
"CHEOLJO'S GENTLE CHARISMA
SHOOK JOSEON TO ITS VERY CORE"
"CHEOLJO LED THE REFORM WITH THE PEOPLE"
"KING CHEOLJO AND QUEEN
CHEORIN'S ACHIEVEMENTS"
"SERVED AS MODEL FOR PRO-REFORM KINGS"
"CHEOLJO LAID THE FOUNDATION FOR DEMOCRACY"
- A comment, please.
- Say a few words!
- Do you admit all the charges?
- Over here!
- Just a comment, please!
- Is it all true?
- Do you admit all the charges?
- Are the allegations true?
- Is it all true?
SECRETARY HAN PYO JIN COMMITTED
EMBEZZLEMENT FOR YEARS
History goes on, and things change.
But those conniving rats who engage
in corruption always survive.
Maybe a good world isn't
completely devoid of rotten parts,
but it allows us to cut out
such corrupt, rotten segments.
If you keep trying to change
your life for the better,
you'll bring about positive
change to the world,
just like Cheoljong and I did.
- Your Majesty.
- Yes.
It's upside down.
Oh, right.
Your Majesty, are you
having trouble focusing?
I wish to see my Queen so much...
that I cannot focus.
This is not good.
I should go see my Queen first,
then focus on this later.
Next.
All women in the Internal Court
who are over the age of 18...
are permitted to wed.
Yes, Your Highness.
Also, no one under the age of 10...
should be accepted into the
Internal Court as a court maid.
And...
What is next, Your Highness?
Your Highness?
I'm sorry, Court Lady Choi.
I see that you are having trouble focusing.
It has only been a little while
since you last saw His Majesty.
It is not me. My baby misses him.
For the baby's wellbeing,
would you like to go see
His Majesty for a moment?
I wholeheartedly agree.
- Your Majesty.
- Yes.
Her Highness is headed to
the Seonjeongjeon Hall.
Oh, no. We just missed each other.
His Majesty is at the Daejojeon Hall?
Yes, Your Highness.
Wait for us, Your Highness!
Look how excited she is. My gosh.
Oh, no. Did we miss each other again?
My goodness, are we playing
hide-and-seek or what?
This is not working.
In that case...
Finally, we meet.
After...
missing each other so many times.
Those fleeting moments felt like an eternity.
By the way, why do you keep talking
to me so formally these days?
Are you plotting something
to surprise me again?
MR. QUEEN
THE EPILOGUE WILL BE REVEALED
EXCLUSIVELY ON TVING.
SPECIAL THANKS TO CHOI JIN HYUK