THE CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
INCIDENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND BACKGROUND OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL.
THE 28TH CHEONG A ART FESTIVAL
The highlight of the 28th
Cheong A Art Festival,
the recipient of the Grand
Prize, given to the singer...
who has the most-divine voice, is...
THE 28TH CHEONG A ART FESTIVAL
GRAND PRIZE IN SINGING CATEGORY
Grade 12 of Cheong A Arts High School...
Over there!
- Oh, my!
- No!
Who's that?
FOUR MONTHS AGO IN NEW YORK
EPISODE 1
Bravo!
Thank you for the invite.
Thank you for coming.
The Korean-Americans here chose you...
as the person they'd like to
meet the most, Director Cheon.
- Indeed.
- Of course.
You know that my wife is a
huge fan of yours too, right?
I'm honored.
You're stunning, ma'am.
You have no idea how hard our
organization worked to have you.
We pulled every string we could.
Why didn't Chairman Joo come with you?
He had something important.
He was very sad he couldn't come with me.
We reserved the best suite in this hotel...
because we thought you were coming with him.
I heard that you two are
getting engaged soon.
Congratulations!
It's him.
I guess he's dying to know what's going on.
Please excuse me for a moment.
I should've been there to watch
your beautiful performance.
It's too bad.
I know. You should've
taken the day off for me.
I was amazing today.
It's for Cheong A Art Center,
which is just as important.
I can't just overlook it.
But you know that I'm always
thinking of you, right?
How's the construction going?
You better be excited.
I'm going to build a perfect
opera house, just for you.
What are you doing next?
I'm so tired that I might just pass out.
I'm flying back on the
first flight back to Korea.
All right. See you at home.
You must've been nervous
about your performance.
Having a little drink isn't a
bad idea for a night like this.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Who are you?
It's been a while.
You...
What brings you here?
I had business to take care of in New York.
Did you perform? I guess you're staying here.
Yes.
You look good.
It's so strange to see you here.
- How long has it been?
- About two years.
Go to your suite. You're drunk.
Are you still alone?
Do you want me to walk you to your suite?
Goodness.
Did you forget something?
Who are you?
Why are you doing this?
Looks like you put your
hands on the wrong woman.
Who sent you?
Was it Joo Dan Tae? Jerk.
Break his hands.
No more surgery for you, doc.
Throw him in the water.
No. No.
No!
Good work.
Make sure there are no problems later.
Ha Yoon Chul.
Why did you do that?
Eun Byeol.
Are you going to school already?
It isn't even 7am yet.
Did you forget? The
practical exam is tomorrow.
I have to stop by the studio before school.
I rushed home to have breakfast with you.
My performance in New York...
Was amazing, I'm sure.
Tell me about it later.
Are you back yet?
Come for breakfast.
I'll be waiting.
TO: CHEON SEO JIN
DIE! JUST DIE!
This came again.
She has taken it too far.
It's too sick to even talk about.
I'm sure it's Oh Yoon Hee.
She's the only one...
who would do this.
Calm down. It may not be her.
A lot of people envy you.
Do you know how many times
this happened already?
They couldn't take this risk
unless it was for revenge.
I feel like I'm being watched too.
You know too.
As long as Yoon Hee is alive,
we can't be completely free.
She went missing over a year ago.
She still hasn't been caught.
She either died...
while running or hiding.
- It's one or the other.
- I won't believe it...
until they find her body.
Are you keeping a close eye on her daughter?
She's a murderer and fugitive's daughter.
The police are watching her 24 hours a day,
and I put someone on her too.
Don't worry.
If she can't come to see
her one and only daughter,
she must be dead.
- But...
- Stress is bad for you.
You've been way too on edge lately.
What is this?
Did you cook yourself?
I missed you a lot.
You look especially beautiful today.
Thanks.
How was the party?
Did you get drunk?
Did anything happen?
No, nothing.
I drank enough to get a happy buzz.
The real estate policy...
that throws non-homeowners into despair...
must be eliminated!
- It must be eliminated!
Ministers who own multiple
houses must repent...
step down as ministers immediately!
- Step down!
On the fifth day of my hunger strike,
one citizen...
wrapped this scarf that she
knitted around me and said...
her lifelong dream was to own her own house.
ASSEMBLYMAN LEE KYU JIN
I, Assemblyman Lee Kyu Jin...
REAL ESTATE POLICY
I'll make your dream come true!
ASSEMBLYMAN LEE KYU JIN
Like the morning dew
All together!
That endured the long night
On the leaves
More beautiful than pearls
I...
- Assemblyman Lee!
- Honey!
Like the morning dew
- Assemblyman Lee!
- You can't die like this!
- Assemblyman Lee! Please breathe!
- Wake up!
Assemblyman Lee! You can't pass away!
I'm starving.
I start shaking if I skip even one meal.
I've set it all up already.
Mother sent seafood chicken
soup, japchae, grilled shrimp...
All of your favorites. Eat.
How long must I keep up
this stupid hunger strike?
It's freezing out.
I'm going to get sick.
This is pathetic.
Your acting was incredible today.
Since you fainted, we can end it naturally.
If we loosen restrictions
and let apartments go up...
and make banks give loans easily,
it'll solve everything.
- Hey.
- Yes, sir.
You made me do this garbage
on purpose, didn't you?
To make me suffer.
That's not it. It was to
make up for your mistake...
during the inspection...
I guess you never make mistakes.
I guess not.
Then you should be the assemblyman.
- Hey, you.
- Stop it.
He's trying hard. Look at him.
He has no respect for me
because it's my first term.
I have the fifth-largest
assets among assemblymen.
Do you know...
how hard it is to save that much
while living with integrity?
Honey. That's enough. Look at this.
There's an article.
Chairman Joo and Cheon Seo
Jin are getting engaged.
They're getting remarried after
cheating on each other's spouses.
Why are they announcing
their engagement now...
like it's the love of the century?
Cheong A Foundation and J
King Holdings are merging.
So their stock prices shot up today.
Hey. Did I or did I not
say let's buy that stock?
How could an assemblyman not know that?
You. Get over here.
I told you to tell me.
Did you buy it?
I went all in.
You little freak. Hey.
You were a nobody, and I gave you a career.
Get out. Get lost.
Go home. Go!
- Get lost!
- I'm sorry.
Why you...
CHEONG A ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
Hi, Eun Byeol.
Give me your bag. It must be heavy.
My dad brought me this chocolate.
Eat it while you study.
Eun Byeol. This is the latest.
My mom got it for you
from the department store.
You look extra pretty today.
Your face is brighter than my future.
Eun Byeol. Let's hang out at
my dad's hotel after school.
No. I have a lesson today.
Then want to go to a
restaurant with me tomorrow?
No, I'm busy.
CHEONG A ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
STAFF RESTROOM
Unbelievable.
"Chairman Joo Dan Tae of J King Holdings..."
"and Director Cheon Seo Jin of
Cheong A Foundation are engaged?"
I didn't see this coming.
Here they come.
Unbelievable. Your father
announced his engagement today.
It's become a top story.
Seok Kyung, how does it feel to
become sisters with Eun Byeol?
Who will be the big sister?
Who says we're sisters? That's disgusting.
What's disgusting about it?
Do you hate my family that much?
I couldn't be happier to be sisters with you.
I really look forward to it.
Is she out of her mind?
Calm down.
- What?
- You stepped over the line.
I stepped over the line.
LOSER'S SEAT
BAE RO NA
Look, that's her.
It's her, right? The murderer's daughter.
- How disgusting.
- I'm creeped out.
That's you, right?
This is crazy. How can you be so shameless?
You're a murderer's daughter.
So creepy.
Her mom stabbed a person to death.
She must have the psychopath gene too.
She's a potential criminal.
We'd better stay away.
Are you serious?
Get lost. Go away.
Go away!
- Oh, my.
- Look at that.
Is everyone here?
It seems like it.
You guys will be seniors next year.
The Seoul National University
prep course starts today.
Come back here after school. Also...
Here are competitions that
you can write about...
in your student record
and cover letter later.
I've prepared a plan so
that the prizes can be...
fairly distributed among you.
CHEONG A ARTS HIGH SCHOOL'S
COMPETITION SCHEDULE
They're organized by the school
under the director's protection.
You guys just have to do as I say.
Now, go to your seats and
start filling out applications.
CHEONG A ARTS HIGH SCHOOL
COMPETITION APPLICATION
Moving on.
Chairman Joo Dan Tae of J King Holdings...
has announced his engagement...
to Director Cheon Seo Jin
of Cheong A Foundation.
It's been said that they
were seeing each other...
casually for a while...
but recently decided to get married.
According to a J King Holdings employee,
after Chairman Joo's ex-wife, Ms. Shim,
was murdered at Hera Palace last year,
- Director Cheon comforted him...
- Good afternoon.
"Good afternoon"?
- The company hopes the public...
- Hey.
- will support their new start.
- Who are those people?
Are you really a murderer's daughter?
I mean, are you this woman's daughter?
Hey, get out of here. Right now.
Get out of here.
Go away.
Leave! Get lost.
Ro Na, can we talk for a minute?
Have you heard anything from your
mom? When did you last see her?
- Please say something!
- Ro Na!
- She didn't pick up her phone.
- Say something!
- Ro Na!
- Wait!
You've all heard about our engagement, right?
Congratulations, Mr. Joo.
Congratulations, Mom.
Thanks.
Thanks, Eun Byeol.
Most of all, I hope you guys will get along.
Why wouldn't we?
Will we be living in the penthouse too?
I love this place.
Don't you two have anything to say?
No, I don't.
Excuse me.
Sit back down. We're not finished yet.
Don't you know?
I get an upset stomach if
I eat with someone I hate.
Joo Seok Kyung!
Eat up. The steak turned out amazing.
Get up.
Don't be so childish.
This is not only a marriage
but also a business deal.
You getting on my nerves
will do no good to your dad.
You're so creepy.
Does my dad know you're like this?
Don't interrupt me. It's rude.
Now that you've become my family,
I won't put up with your
disrespectful behavior anymore.
Too bad.
If you were a little smarter, you
wouldn't have behaved this way.
I wish your mom had taught you better.
Don't talk that way about my mom.
You're the one who should watch your mouth.
It might have been different before,
but I will never let you ruin my reputation.
Behave yourself, Seok Kyung.
How do you like the lemon charlotte?
I heard that it's your
favorite, so I tried making it.
Did you make it yourself?
It tastes lovely.
Is there anything you're bad at?
You come from a prestigious
family, make a ton of money,
and are good-looking. And
you're a good cook too?
I'm glad that you like it.
By the way...
When my mom isn't around, you
don't have to try so hard.
What?
I'll tell her that you're nice to me.
So loosen up a bit.
Seeing you try so hard to win my heart,
I feel so sorry for you.
Something doesn't feel right.
Maybe I'm just being oversensitive.
YOU DON'T DESERVE TO BE HAPPY.
YOU WILL BECOME MISERABLE.
YOU CAN NEVER BE HAPPY. DIE.
YOU HAVE THE VOICE OF A DEMON!
DIE, CHEON SEO JIN!
DIE!
Secretary Do is checking
the security camera footage.
He hasn't found any suspicious visitors yet,
but I have a bad feeling.
How could this happen right after
our engagement was announced?
This person is right under my nose.
What if it's Oh Yoon Hee? What if she's back?
She's on the run. She couldn't
approach us so easily.
Then who did this?
We'll find out.
I'll tighten up security.
Don't worry too much.
Why did you have to take
away Oh Yoon Hee's house?
Couldn't you stop at having
her bank accounts seized?
When she finds out her daughter is
moving from one place to another,
wouldn't she become
determined to get back at you?
If I hadn't accused her of embezzlement,
I would have gotten in huge trouble.
You know that I had no choice.
Still,
you should have left Bae Ro Na alone.
A mom who has lost everything
would fear nothing.
You...
made a mistake.
Do you think...
I asked you to take care of
her to be treated this way?
You keep disappointing me.
How am I going to trust you again?
I'm sorry, sir. I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry, sir. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
NO LITTERING
Why are you here?
You went to see your mom, didn't you?
Where did you meet her?
Who gave you this?
Is it your mom?
You went to see your mom, didn't you?
No!
Where is she?
You better tell me now!
I really have no idea.
If you find out where she is,
let me know too.
Stop coming to me!
When are you going to stop?
Until your mom, that murderer appears,
you'll never be able to escape
the hands of the Chairman.
If you're caught contacting your mom...
or meeting her,
I'm going to kill you.
Do you understand?
What am I supposed to do?
I have nowhere else to go.
Even if I get beaten to death,
I'd like to see my mom before I go too!
That idiot!
Why did she let her take her sandwiches?
So stupid!
Yoo Jenny.
What are you doing here?
Are you guys following me?
I told you that something was odd.
I knew something was up when
she came in late every day.
You completely fooled us.
Tell us.
Have you been hanging out
with Bae Ro Na all this time?
Well...
That's not it.
Did you buy her sandwiches and food too?
Tell us!
Yes, I'm friends with Ro Na!
Don't you guys feel bad for her?
Both of her parents are gone!
She's the daughter of the
murderer who killed my mom.
I lost my mom because of her.
But that's not Ro Na's fault.
So you're saying, you're on Ro Na's side.
I'll be telling Mr. Ma...
that you won't be in the
SNU prep course anymore.
Eun Byeol!
DIE!
That witch!
Get away from Chairman.
Joo Dan Tae is my man.
I won't let anyone take him.
Die! Die, Cheon Seo Jin!
Die!
Die, Cheon Seo Jin!
Ms. Yang, you're here!
Director Cheon,
what brings you here?
My goodness.
I thought the white sneakers looked familiar.
It was you, indeed.
Do you think you can curse me with some toys?
Do you think Chairman can
become yours with that?
Please forgive me, Director!
Please don't tell Chairman that I did this.
I can't live without Chairman.
We don't have time to be
bothered by someone like you.
Just get out of this house right now.
If I see you again,
you won't make it out of the house alive.
No, I can't leave.
Please forgive me, Director.
If I have to die, I must die in this house.
Nobody except for Chairman can get rid of me.
Once I marry Chairman, I'll own the house.
It'll be in my right to
fire you and get rid of you!
I shouldn't be the one leaving.
It's you,
Cheon Seo Jin.
What?
I...
have lived with Chairman...
for 20 years.
Goodness.
The way Chairman looks at me,
his breath,
and every hair on his body.
I remember them all.
I can die...
for this man.
Joo Dan Tae is mine.
I won't let anyone take him!
My goodness.
Chairman!
You haven't fixed that habit of yours yet?
I've just let you be
since you've done so much,
but I'll make sure to fix that
crazy habit of yours today.
I have no reason to live if it isn't for you.
"You"?
I...
love...
you to death, Chairman.
Get her away.
No, Chairman! I can't leave.
Chairman! Don't desert me!
Chairman!
- My goodness.
- You can't get rid of me.
I feel a little sad that I can't have...
Ms. Yang's spicy braised monkfish.
DIE!
Who did this, then?
We'll find out.
There's one person...
that comes to mind.
Joo Dan Tae.
What a smart man you are.
Right. Did the PR Team
publish the engagement news?
Why? Is something wrong?
I want them to reword the statement...
that I'll become the CEO
once the two companies merge.
- What do you mean?
- When Cheong A Group is made,
you will be the CEO, of course.
I think I'll be busy...
making Cheong A Art Center
a world-class opera theater.
I'll ask them to fix that.
What are you doing tonight?
Why?
Just curious.
Hello, Chairman.
I thought he passed out
because of his hunger strike.
Why is he sleeping at my office?
You make me come all this way and appear now?
You can't call a civil servant
up as you please like this.
Come on.
Have you forgotten already?
Remember who got you that badge?
Half of your votes were from me.
You know well.
The price of Hera Palace
properties went to dust...
thanks to your wife's death,
and I was the one who
pulled the prices back up.
Remember that?
If I didn't become an assemblyman,
Hera Palace wouldn't have
gotten the prices back up...
to 150,000 dollars per 3.3m².
Isn't that thanks to Seo
Jin's announcement...
of building the second Cheong A
Medical Center in Samseong-dong?
That's true.
But don't you think your
business is doing too well?
You've made it so big out of nothing.
Let's be honest here.
Thanks to Shim Su Ryeon,
your wealth multiplied.
I guess luck follows when
you're a righteous man.
Whatever. Just cut to the chase.
What is it? A complaint?
No, not that. This is very important.
FIGHTING CRIMES TOGETHER,
MAKING A SAFE SOCIETY
RIGHTEOUS POLICE
Surprise!
Congratulations on your marriage!
What's all this?
Dan Tae.
- Here you go.
- What do you think?
I feel like I've finally found my soulmate.
I'd like...
to dedicate the rest of my life to you.
I love you.
He's like a prince!
Did you get Assemblyman Lee
just to propose? He's busy.
Exactly.
I put serving the people
behind and came right here.
What are you doing? Accept it already.
His knees are going to wear out!
Get up.
Put it on me yourself.
This isn't your first proposal.
You're an experienced
one. How can you not know?
Here.
It's beautiful.
I love it.
Thank you.
Joo Dan Tae!
You're being arrested for
Shim Su Ryeon's murder.
What did you just say?
What do you mean?
He's suspected of murder?
What do you think you're doing?
Why would I kill my own wife?
Please come with us to the office.
Let go! Why would I do that?
Dan Tae!
Why would I do such a thing?
I would never!
What's going on?
This will surely be an unforgettable day.
GANGNAM POLICE STATION
We're Chairman Joo's defense counsel.
Why did you arrest him?
There has been a report.
What report?
That Chairman Joo was the one
behind Shim Su Ryeon's murder.
So, who made that nonsense report?
The first witness and Chairman Joo's maid,
Yang Mi Ok.
Yang Mi Ok!
You brought me all the way
here just with her report?
You're ready to face the consequences, right?
I can't stand this inhumane investigation.
You'll be sure to suffer the consequences.
Where's Yang Mi Ok right now?
I'd like to request a cross-investigation.
Ms. Yang...
has died.
What did you say?
Ms. Yang...
was found dead at her home an hour ago.
We believe she poisoned herself to death.
I have loved Chairman
Joo Dan Tae all my life.
If I can't have him, I will destroy him.
That way, nobody can have him.
It is Joo Dan Tae who killed Shim Su Ryeon.
I'm sorry to Oh Yoon Hee.
Ms. Yang pointed to you...
as the murderer.
What?
She also made an apology to Ms. Oh Yoon Hee.
It sounds like she had a grudge against you.
I don't believe this.
Ms. Yang doesn't have the guts to break me.
- It's her.
- Sorry?
All of this was plotted by Oh Yoon Hee.
I bet Oh Yoon Hee killed Ms. Yang.
Make sure to apply for an
autopsy as soon as possible.
We need to confirm that it's a suicide.
If there are traces of people
having gone into her home...
and if her suicide note was forged...
Hold on!
Oh Yoon Hee?
Why is...
Oh Yoon Hee here?
INVESTIGATION DIVISION
Oh Yoon Hee!
Tell me. Why are you here?
What happened?
Where have you been hiding?
Why are you pulling all of this nonsense for?
Ma'am, please stop.
You did this, didn't
you? You killed Ms. Yang!
You plotted all of this nonsense!
- Tell me right now!
- Please stop.
Ms. Oh has already turned herself in.
Turned herself in?
Let's go.
I didn't kill Shim Su Ryeon.
You can ask me over and over again,
but my answer won't change.
I can bet my daughter's life on it.
My goodness!
Ms. Yang left a suicide
note and killed herself?
How can Chairman Joo be the murderer?
Does that mean Oh Yoon
Hee isn't the murderer?
Just one suicide note can't
make someone a murderer.
That's horrifying.
There's no way Chairman
Joo would've done that.
She was his wife!
That means Oh Yoon Hee was
wrongfully imprisoned...
and became a fugitive.
So you are saying, Ms.
Yang from the penthouse...
named Chairman Joo as the
murderer and killed herself.
Right?
I never said this before,
but it never made sense
that Oh Yoon Hee killed...
Shim Su Ryeon.
Chairman Joo makes sense.
He took her entire fortune...
when she died.
Oh Yoon Hee had requested...
a meeting with Ms. Yang, the
first witness at the scene.
And when the police went to her home,
Ms. Yang was dead already.
That witch Oh Yoon Hee killed her.
Or she paid someone.
I suspect the same, but
things look bad right now.
Since Ms. Yang named you
as the murderer and died,
they'll reopen the case.
You will be the new
suspect. It's unavoidable.
If word gets out that your
people assaulted Ms. Yang,
you may be accused of murdering her as well.
Then what?
Should I just take it?
One good thing is,
they found photos that prove
Ms. Yang stalked you...
and defamed Madam were found in her home.
That psycho.
She never understood her place.
This is...
an opportunity.
Let's do this.
I'll say that...
Breaking news. The real murderer...
of the Hera Palace murder was revealed.
The murderer, Yang, was the
maid who worked for the victim.
She had been stalking Chairman
Joo, the victim's husband,
and had a deep grudge against
her regarding her pay.
This was revealed after Oh Yoon
Hee, who had been on the run...
for a year after being accused of the murder,
- turned herself in.
- No way.
- Ms. Yang killed her?
- Yang left a suicide note...
apologizing to Oh Yoon Hee...
and died in her home.
What happened?
The police state Yang...
Is it true?
Did Ms. Yang really kill our mom?
- The police...
- Did she?
will reopen the case and
investigate thoroughly.
Since the murderer Yang...
POLICE TO REINVESTIGATE HERA PALACE MURDER
What happened?
Ms. Yang is the killer?
How could you frame her for it?
Stop talking. I haven't slept a wink.
Explain yourself!
I'm going crazy too.
I was about to become the target.
We were able to resolve it this easily...
thanks to her mental illness.
Do you know how much money I spent...
on five lawyers making sure
Ms. Yang was the murderer?
Yoon Hee is alive.
So?
This was the only way to get rid of Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee is innocent again now.
What do you want from me?
If I didn't frame Ms. Yang for being crazy,
I would've been found guilty of murder.
Must I go to jail? Will that make you happy?
That's not what I mean.
If...
Ms. Yang didn't kill herself...
Even if Oh Yoon Hee killed her,
it'll only hurt me if we dig into it.
I'm grateful beyond words...
that Oh Yoon Hee isn't obsessed
with finding Su Ryeon's real killer.
Even the public sentiment is
moving in Yoon Hee's favor.
Someone must be helping her.
Who?
The suspicions about the
Hera Palace murder...
do not end here.
The police did not find Oh
Yoon Hee's fingerprint...
on the forged family
picture found in her home.
Is this for real?
She was framed?
She's innocent?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you watching TV here?
- What's your problem?
- When did you come?
Yang was jealous of Shim.
Storeowners in the area
stated that she went around...
acting like she was...
the owner of the penthouse.
What's more shocking is,
the last person she spoke
to on the phone was Yang.
Why did the police ignore
this big piece of evidence?
GANGNAM POLICE STATION
Oh Yoon Hee, who was branded
a murderer for a year,
has requested a retrial.
Since the real murderer has been revealed,
it is presumed that she
will be found not-guilty.
The police and justice
department will be unable...
to avoid being criticized...
for being incompetent both in
their investigation and decision.
I saw you every day in my dreams.
My baby looks the same.
You too.
I...
knew you didn't do it.
I'm sorry, Ro Na.
I'm so sorry.
Mom...
Are you home?
We spoke earlier.
You said you were looking for a gig worker.
Just a minute.
Hello.
This is all your mom's fault.
The chairman is angry because your mom fled!
If you die, your mom will show her face.
If her daughter dies because of her,
she'll show up for sure.
Die! Die!
Die!
You were alive, Oh Yoon Hee.
Wasn't it enough that you framed me?
Why are you trying to kill my
innocent daughter too? Why?
That way, you'll show up.
If your daughter dies because of you,
you'd show your face even if
it were from the underworld.
Did Joo Dan Tae tell you to kill me?
Goodbye,
Oh Yoon Hee.
- Logan.
- I said not to go anywhere alone.
Why did you show up without my permission?
I had no choice. Ro Na was in danger.
I'll protect Ro Na.
I'll kill everyone who hurt children.
Ms. Yang!
What are you doing?
Ms. Yang.
Ms. Yang!
I should've...
taken her with me.
I'll go ahead and wait for you, Chairman.
I'll...
Is she dead?
Go to the police station and
turn yourself in right now.
Ask for a cross-investigation with Ms. Yang.
I'll take care of the rest.
I HAVE LOVED CHAIRMAN JOO DAN TAE...
ALL MY LIFE. BUT...
IT IS PAINFUL TO LOVE SOMEONE
WHO DOES NOT LOVE ME BACK.
IF I CAN'T HAVE HIM, I WILL DESTROY HIM.
DIE!
I HAVE LOVED CHAIRMAN
JOO DAN TAE ALL MY LIFE.
IT IS JOO DAN TAE WHO KILLED SHIM SU RYEON.
I HOPE HE WILL BE EXECUTED
AND SENT TO ME SOON.
Mom...
Is that right?
Make sure that she leaves the country. Okay.
She's fleeing abroad?
Oh Yoon Hee?
What if she comes back?
You can forget about her now.
She's been through so much.
She must want to leave everything behind.
We can finally get on with our lives.
We'll have an engagement
ceremony as planned...
and establish Cheong A Group.
You'll take over the musical
world as the greatest prima donna.
We'll build a happy family
that everyone envies...
and love each other for the
rest of our lives, okay?
What's wrong?
Nothing. Eun Byeol's
lesson will be over soon.
I should get going.
She's not a kid anymore.
Don't you think you're
a little overprotective?
If you're being jealous, please don't.
How we raise our own
children is off-limits, okay?
I must be out of my mind.
You're out of your mind, Cheon Seo Jin.
Get it together.
3 MONTHS LATER
- Oh, my.
- My goodness.
Ms. Cheon, you look stunning.
Who'd think you're getting
married for the second time?
Everyone would think you're 20.
How can Chairman Joo be so lucky?
At your age, you could have
gotten married right away.
Why bother to get engaged?
It's an important time for our children.
Also, with all my upcoming
concerts, I couldn't find the time.
Don't you get it?
Marriage is a business deal too.
It has to be handled carefully.
When their companies are merged,
there will be stock problems.
And it'll be complicated
to calculate alimony.
Do you know how much money...
Dr. Ha ripped off her when they got divorced?
Why would you bring that up today?
There's no one else here anyway.
Let's face it, Chairman Joo
doesn't deserve Ms. Cheon.
Is there anyone in this country who
doesn't know Cheong A Foundation?
Chairman Joo totally lucked out this time.
So when are you getting married?
Nothing's been decided yet.
I want to take my time
and get to know him well.
Maybe I'll end up not marrying him after all.
You look beautiful.
- Congratulations.
- Why do you look so tired?
- Congratulations, Mr. Joo.
- Thanks.
It's a beautiful thing to watch.
What's that?
Well, how have you all been?
Are you in the middle of something?
Why do you look so surprised?
Am I not allowed here?
Oh, I'd like to introduce my wife,
Oh Yoon Hee.
It's been a while.
Congratulations on your engagement, Seo Jin.
THE PENTHOUSE 2
Are you saying you really got married?
Watch how you speak about my woman.
You're not the same Ha Yoon Chul of old.
It's an honor to be invited to Hera Club.
Are you here to see Ro Na?
Did you forget who died in the penthouse?
Let's both be happy with
our respective families.
You may never sing again.
This concert must be perfect...
no matter what.
How long will you talk about Ha Yoon Chul?
He isn't your man anymore.
I predict a storm coming.