ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Hey, wake up.
She's not breathing. Hey!
One, two, three, four, five…
Hey, breathe!
Come on, breathe!
You're alive. Thank goodness!
Gosh.
SISYPHUS
I feel like I'm going to pass out.
Darn it.
I hope this works.
ACCESS
-Security has been disabled.
-Nice!
It worked!
Thank you, Seo-jin!
Don't move.
Damn it.
My back. Gosh, I feel like I'm dying.
Hold on.
You must be cold. Here.
She had a wound somewhere here.
Gosh.
It has to be disinfected.
Hold on.
Darn it.
Where is it?
Here it is. I found it.
Sorry.
Oh, hey. I'm sorry.
Hey, don't!
Isn't she the one who kidnapped you?
Seo-jin, I'll explain everything.
Hey, hold on.
It's very complicated,
and you'll find it hard to believe.
How should I put this?
It defies the laws of physics.
It's about the universe we live in.
Can you give me a moment?
Wait. Before that,
can you treat her first?
Or you can write her a prescription.
Who is that woman?
Isn't she the one who kidnapped you?
-No.
-Then who is she?
It's complicated.
Does Eddy know you're alive?
-Not yet.
-Then why are you here?
-Well, let's treat her first.
-Take her to the hospital.
She's a foreigner,
so she doesn't have health insurance.
Just write out a prescription
under your name or my name,
and we'll leave right away.
Darn it, you jerk!
I thought you were dead.
Gosh.
Darn it.
Why are you crying?
Hey.
I'm sorry.
I thought I was going to die too.
I'm sorry, Seo-jin. Okay?
Don't cry.
Go away.
You're all crazy.
Who in the world is she?
It's a long story.
I don't know either.
Is it serious?
Is she badly hurt?
She fell into a river earlier.
Did water get in her lungs?
What is it? Cardiac arrest?
She's malnourished.
Do you expect me to believe that?
It's the most ridiculous and absurd thing
you've ever done.
Hey, I fixed a falling airplane
and came back alive.
Doesn't that sound more absurd?
-Compared to that…
-You said she's from the future.
And you'll supposedly end up
building a time machine later on?
-An uploader.
-It's still a time machine.
And that's why those lunatics
are trying to kill you?
Sigma.
"Sigma"?
Is that someone's name?
I have no idea whether it's a person,
an organization, or an alien.
I see.
Hey.
Don't tell anyone about this.
If you do, they'll think you're crazy.
At least you know that.
Tae-sul, I've been telling you
to stop taking the pills
and get therapy, but I take it back.
You need to be hospitalized.
Honestly, I didn't know
your condition was this serious.
I was not seeing things.
I swear it was Tae-san. I saw him.
Do you realize that you're in danger?
When are you going to call Eddy?
Everyone's waiting for you now.
Is it because of her?
She saved my life.
I want to get her treated first.
From the Control Bureau?
-Yes.
-You're crazy.
Hey.
They're literally everywhere.
It must be a government organization.
They even tap our phones.
If I go out there rashly, I'll be screwed.
-Tae-sul.
-I should start getting prepared.
I'll figure out where Tae-san is
and how to deal with those--
Han Tae-sul!
Do you know who you sound like right now?
You sound just like your brother.
Hey, maybe Tae-san was right.
You saw this earlier.
It was a real gun.
And what about Bong-seon?
Are you saying it's all in my head?
Forget it.
I don't want to make the bed
for you and your new girlfriend.
I'm going home.
You'd better leave by tomorrow morning.
-And--
-Hey, Seo-jin.
Can you lend me your credit card?
I lost my wallet.
I'm going to report her
to the police tomorrow morning.
Hey, wait! Seo-jin.
Darn it.
Thanks. What a loyal friend.
She's a keeper.
I paid 150 million won for this? Jeez.
Don't I have the right
to take a look at what she wrote?
Forget it. I don't want to be so sneaky.
Mom.
Where am I?
I don't want to tell you.
How are you feeling?
-My backpack.
-Just stay there.
But all the things that were inside…
Still… Here.
I managed to salvage these.
What's with that glare?
The diary? I didn't read it.
I said I didn't read it.
I should've just read it.
Then I will kill you.
Hey, here.
Get changed. Let's grab a bite.
Good. Help yourself.
You can eat everything here. Eat this too.
This too. You need to eat well, okay?
Hey, dip it in the sauce.
That's it.
These are all high in calories.
Who picked these?
Also,
take these to supplement
the nutrients that you may lack.
Yes, drink it. Go ahead and open it.
Not now? Drink your Coke, then.
By the way, is there not enough food
in the future?
I just can't wrap my head around it.
Why were all the people who crossed over
exposed to radiation?
Does the exposure happen
on their way here?
And let's go back
to what you brought up yesterday.
You said you won't let me
make the uploader.
Does it have something to do with it?
There will be a war.
No way. A nuclear war?
Yes, it starts in Wolsong.
That nuclear power plant will be nuked.
By North Korea?
And then,
Seoul will also be nuked.
Everyone will die.
Everyone you and I know.
All the passersby you see now.
But like I said,
I'll protect you.
I was told that it'll prevent the war.
Who told you that?
-What about them?
-The Control Bureau?
No idea. They didn't chase us.
They must be looking for us
with their eyes peeled.
-Are you going to go to that address?
-Yes.
Both the Control Bureau
and Sigma will be there.
Let's go.
Please remove your cash.
All right, let me sum it up.
I'm going to invent the uploader,
a machine that enables time travel.
So all sorts of people
will try to kill me.
That includes the Control Bureau.
And those jerks at Asia Mart
must be mad at me as well.
-And Sigma.
-Yes, Sigma.
But what are they?
An individual or an organization?
Anyway, all sorts of mysterious people
will try to kill me from now on.
You're in danger too. Right?
Then let's go our separate ways.
I've been meaning to say this.
Thank you so much. I mean it.
In Busan and at the Han River yesterday…
If it weren't for you,
I'd already be dead.
But you have no reason
to do all this for me.
You nearly died too.
And I'm not a nice person. You know that.
So with that said,
I'll figure things out on my own now.
Take this.
Come on, take it.
You'll need it to get by.
Find a place to live and look for a job.
Just live your life and be happy.
Only five percent of those
who come here survive.
You risked a lot to come here,
so I don't want to ruin this opportunity.
But I have to protect you.
Yes, I know, to prevent the war.
Does that mean
the war will break out if I die?
That's…
Uploaders, downloaders, war, Sigma…
I can't fully trust you
and will not trust everything you say.
And it'll be a nuisance
for me to have a bodyguard.
You won't even last a day on your own.
-Sigma--
-Okay, who told you that?
My diary.
It said you'll save the world
if I save you.
At PEXCO,
I could've met my brother
had you not dragged me out of there.
No, you would've died,
which would lead to the war.
That's your problem.
Let me ask you something.
Let's say I found my brother again,
but the situation is dangerous.
Then will you stop me again?
Because there will be war if I die?
Yes.
You're unbelievable.
You'll just do what you need to do
even if everyone will die?
You selfish jerk.
Let me help you, please.
I'll do it alone.
You want me to just go back?
You're the only person I know
whether from the past, present, or future.
Do you know what it's like to be alone?
You can't do it on your own.
No, thanks. I prefer working alone.
There's plenty of cash in the future.
We need it for lighting fires.
Hey!
Damn it.
You psychos! Let me out!
Hello,
I'm a police officer
of the Republic of Korea!
Kidnapping a cop?
Have you lost your mind?
Let me call my family at least.
Just one phone call!
My mom is waiting for me!
I have to go see my mom!
Hey! Are you listening?
Let me out at once!
Hey!
-Is he the one?
-Damn it!
Yes.
And he happens to be a cop.
Things got complicated.
I know. What should we do?
Follow protocol?
What did the doctor say?
Even after I remove the cast,
I'll need rehabilitation therapy
for a year.
Darn it.
This is nuts!
THE END IS NEAR
"The end"?
Where am I?
The Control Bureau.
It's sort of like the Immigration Office.
The Control Bureau?
Well, what do you "control"?
Illegal entrants.
Look.
The guy you caught the other day
is one of them.
Where are these people from?
That's not important.
What matters is "when."
Back in the old days,
people knew everything
about their neighbors.
They even knew how many spoons
their neighbors had.
So if there was a newcomer,
you'd notice right away.
But these days, people don't even know
who lives next door to them.
They don't even care.
That's the world we live in now.
But we aren't the only ones in this world.
The uninvited are living among us.
You got promoted early.
-A special recruit?
-Yes, for gunnery.
In 2021, the uploader was invented.
It's a time machine.
We catch people who travel to the present
from the future through the uploader.
LIST OF ILLEGAL IMMIGRANTS
UNDER EXAMINATION
SUCCESSFULLY INVESTED IN STOCKS
REALIZED MASSIVE REAL ESTATE PROFITS
ELIMINATED
A time machine?
Then what about the lottery?
They'd all win the lottery.
Right, everyone is curious about that.
Upon encountering
the very first illegal entrant in 2002,
the government established
the Control Bureau.
What did they do first?
Here.
The lottery.
LOTTERY COMMISSION
2020 REPORT
They founded the Lottery Commission
to take care of all the expenses
for catching the illegal entrants.
Okay. So what?
So what do you want me to do?
You don't have to believe me.
I don't expect you to anyway.
I'm sorry to say this,
but while you were here,
your mother passed away.
What?
Hyeon-gi.
Mom!
Where have you been?
Mom.
Mom!
That woman is the prime suspect.
She's an illegal entrant.
She broke into your house,
stole your gun and car, and ran away.
She shot and killed your mother,
who couldn't even fight back.
By the time we arrived at the scene,
the suspect had already fled.
You see, they all say the same thing
at the beginning.
That they came here
because they missed the clean air,
they missed their late parents, and so on.
They also say
that they'll stay out of trouble.
But once they get here,
they get greedy.
Have you ever thought about
how strange it is?
Some people keep making a fortune
in the stock market or real estate.
So why does nothing in life work out
for ordinary people like us?
Some people act as though
they can foresee the future,
so why are ordinary people like us
struggling to just make ends meet?
We no longer have the opportunity
to become successful
by pure chance and luck.
Do you want to fix it?
Tae-san!
What's going on?
Damn it.
They all look dumb.
What do you mean?
They're smiling,
not knowing they'll all die soon.
-No!
-it's dangerous!
-What's she doing?
-My gosh!
Hey! What are you doing?
-Are you crazy? Move!
-Out of the way!
-Move!
-You're blocking the road!
-Get out of there!
-Hey!
-Hey, move!
-Have you lost your mind?
What is she doing over there?
The red light is on.
I certainly know
what it's like to be alone.
I've been feeling so alone
ever since my brother died.
He said the same thing.
"Don't worry about money.
Study as much as you like,
do everything you want to do,
and be happy."
He was always covered in oil,
working himself to the bone
at an auto shop,
but he just wanted me to be happy.
Then he suddenly died.
I must find my brother.
So no matter
how dangerous the situation is,
don't drag me out like you did last time
when my brother is right in front of me.
Can you do that?
If your answer is yes,
I want you to protect me from them
and save the world.
Okay.
We're different from the police.
You may shoot and kill
any illegal entrant.
Don't breathe in the air. It's toxic.
I took it off for a second to tie my hair.
-What about you, Dad?
-I'm fine.
Nice! Incredible!
My gosh, they're so handsome.
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH HAN TAE-SUL,
CEO OF QUANTUM & TIME
"Young Asian Tycoon,
New Paradigm of Quantum Transmission."
Whatever.
Nice!
Look what I've got!
Oh, no.
I'll take them all with me.
I don't see any fruit cocktail.
What you see is all there is,
so just grab everything.
Let's have some fun!
Hit the target and score ten points!
How dare you come into our turf?
Ready or not, here we come.
We'll kill you!
Darn it!
Hey, will I win against you
if I catch them both today?
No, it'll be a tie.
The current score is 149 to 147.
So I'll be beating you!
Are you an idiot?
Darn it, those rotten little punks.
Gang Seo-hae!
Damn it! What the hell?
Hey! Everyone follow me!
Looks like I'll win today.
How many are there?
About nine or ten?
Darn it.
Let's just leave the things here.
More of them will come
because of the gunshots.
-Behind the post.
-Behind the post?
I see.
Hey, you two!
If you wrecked our turf,
you should pay for it.
Come out at once!
You come here, you punk!
What a lunatic.
Damn it! Boss, they're not here!
Where are they hiding?
By the tool board.
Darn it.
Hey, tell the rest of our guys
to come here!
Here.
I grabbed it earlier.
Yes! Nice!
-Did you get hurt?
-No.
Dad!
Catch that girl first!
Please don't kill me.
How old are you?
I'm 18.
Why didn't you shoot him?
He was going to shoot you--
-Because he'll die anyway.
-Gang Seo-hae!
Once you get soft,
you'll lose something even more precious.
Dad.
I'm fine. I was just grazed by the bullet.
Let's go.
Dad, are you okay?
Of course.
By the way, what is this place?
A sauna?
What did people do here?
People used to come here
for sauna bathing.
What is that?
Oh, it's like a room
where people relax in dry heat,
take baths, or lie down and watch TV.
So this place used to be warm.
-Dad.
-Yes?
Which one tastes the best?
Jjajangmyeon, of course.
It was your favorite when you were little.
I don't remember.
Which one do you want to eat the most?
TTUKBAEGI BULGOGI
Ttukbaegi bulgogi.
What's that?
Soupy bulgogi
cooked in a ttukbaegi.
What is a ttukbaegi?
It's an earthenware pot
used for making stew.
And bulgogi?
Bulgogi is
sliced beef
marinated in soy sauce, then boiled.
-Is it good?
-Yes, it's delicious.
Your mom made delicious bulgogi.
Seo-hae, which one
do you want to eat the most?
Tteokbokki.
Mom made it for me as a snack
whenever I had a short school day.
It was so good.
Dad.
Yes?
What would you do
if you could go back in time?
SAUNA
Darn it.
There's so much water here.
It tastes good too.
We were always short of water.
The water tastes good?
Yes, it did.
You drank the bathwater?
Yes. Why?
Nothing. Well done.
Damn, this place is packed with people.
Did we really have to come here?
It's safer here.
They can't shoot us here,
and it's easier to spot suspicious people.
Right. The water tastes good too.
It's really warm here.
Obviously! We're in the sauna.
Did you expect it to be cold?
I didn't know.
You have a lot to learn.
CAFETERIA
What? Are you hungry?
I want…
The special tonkatsu. I'll get that.
Pick what you want.
I'll get…
TTUKBAEGI BULGOGI
Ttukbaegi bulgogi.
What's wrong?
It's good.
What's this?
You'll tag along everywhere I go,
so you'll need it.
SEO-HAE
Good. That's my number. Save it.
Hand it over. Goodness.
Are there no cell phones in the future?
HAN TAE-SUL
"Tae-sul."
Don't answer calls from anyone else.
I don't even know anyone else.
Your diary got all wet and crumpled.
I bought a similar one for you.
So it was from you.
-By the way…
-What?
You said when your brother came,
he brought the suitcase
and a key Mr. Park is after.
Yes, the key to the safe.
What's in the safe?
Some research documents.
About topological changes of space-time
and the inflection points…
What is that?
Hey.
Maybe that's the uploader.
Speaking of which,
let's go to my place after we finish this.
We need to figure out what to wear
when we sneak into the chairman's party.
Besides, that key is at my place.
Hey!
Darn it.
Are you kidding me?
You left that important thing at home?
I didn't know it was important,
and I thought
my house would be the safest.
I hid it well.
-Where's the key?
-It's in my lab.
Did someone already ransack your place?
It always looks like this.
It looks messy,
but I'd say it's an orderly mess.
-Where did you put it?
-In a drawer.
Hey! You said you hid it well.
Jeez, look.
Watch.
Are we good now?
Hey,
the party is tomorrow evening,
so let's get some rest today.
-Wait.
-What is it?
What happened?
The alarm system was turned off
for a moment.
-Was there no power outage?
-No.
Take a look around.
Don't stand so close to me.
Be quiet.
Yes, sir.
I stopped by Tae-sul's place for a moment.
No, it's nothing serious.
The alarm system shut down for a moment,
but it's back up now.
Yes, we're checking it now.
I don't think it's anything serious.
The thing is,
the police said
they'll stop searching for him now.
They search for missing persons
for up to two weeks.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to just let it go.
Yes.
Okay, I will.
All clear, sir.
Have a few guys stand guard here
until tomorrow morning just in case.
Is this the police?
Yes, last night…
They're literally everywhere.
It must be a government organization.
They even tap our phones.
Go ahead.
No, it's nothing. I'm sorry.
HAN TAE-SAN
PSYCHIATRIST KIM SEO-JIN
Do you still see things these days?
They're not hallucinations.
I'm serious. Those people…
They live among us in hiding.
Those jerks will kill Tae-sul.
Who are "they"?
Sigma.
HAN TAE-SAN
You idiots! Are you kidding me?
Find them and bring them here, okay?
Go find them at once.
They're gone.
Darn it.
-Have you checked his place?
-We did.
But we couldn't go in
because of tight security.
Find them no matter what
and bring them right here. Okay?
Okay?
Jeez, I shall rip these rats to pieces.
Find them, okay?
Go find them yourself if it's that urgent.
That's why I'm heading out now!
Darn it.
Is there a back door?
There is a secret door I built
to avoid paparazzi,
but they're guarding
in front of that door as well.
-"Paparazzi"?
-Yes.
Tabloid reporters.
It was because of a girl I briefly dated.
What? Is that important now?
-Let's just wait.
-Until when?
Until tomorrow morning.
They'll go on patrol at 9 a.m.,
so we'll leave then.
I know where all the security cameras are.
Don't stand so close to the window.
But you've been standing here
this whole time.
-Happy birthday to you
-Happy birthday, Dear Seo-hae
-A cell phone?
-Do you like it?
Yes! It's awesome.
Save my number.
Call me if anything happens, okay?
Okay.
You told me not to stand by the window.
The moon has risen,
so they can't see us from outside.
I got nothing to drink except for this.
Do you want one?
What? Is there no booze in the future?
There is,
but my dad never let me have any.
Oh, dear. Your dad is way too strict.
Go on.
Look. That's the N Seoul Tower.
So that's what it looked like originally.
What does it look like in the future?
It's collapsed to the side.
How serious is this war?
The future is
very different from now. There's nothing.
Have you contacted your family?
-No.
-Why not?
Because I can't.
Because of the Control Bureau?
Will it endanger them?
That's my brother.
See that area over there?
The shantytown on the hill.
We used to live there.
My brother and I lived
in a semi-basement room there
until I graduated from middle school.
His job was…
While working as a mechanic,
he learned how to repair trains.
Do you know what a train is?
He worked for a train maintenance company.
Every time I called him,
he'd be at a different train station.
Maybe that's why he's so good at hiding.
Let's talk about something else.
Are there any places
you've wanted to go to?
Places I've wanted to go to?
An amusement park? Why?
To ride the pirate ship.
You don't know how to have fun.
I don't know what it's like in the future,
but Yeonnam-dong is
the most up-and-coming area at the moment.
There are many good restaurants and bars.
-No.
-Why not?
-Then go to a water park.
-Where?
It's a swimming pool.
-I don't like swimming pools.
-Why not?
You see good-looking men and women
checking each other out and chatting away.
Then they'll go eat churros together.
I'll go to an amusement park.
To ride the pirate ship?
I went to an amusement park
with my mom on my ninth birthday,
but I was too short to ride it.
Only by two centimeters.
I promised my mom I'd grow taller
so I could ride it the year after,
but the war broke out.
But the pirate ship is no big deal.
Whenever I think about it,
it brings back
these bad memories that I have.
Was it during the holidays?
My brother and I picked up
this high-paying part-time gig there.
Our job was to check the equipment
and clean the site.
I was waiting under the ride
while it was in operation
when vomit suddenly fell from the sky.
That smell.
No matter how many times
I washed my clothes…
THE LATE KIM JEONG-HYE
I'm sorry for your loss.
It's okay.
Just put it to good use.
I'm sorry you had to forgo her funeral.
No one would come anyway.
-I've reported you missing.
-Okay.
We're family now.
We received a report overnight.
Here, you see the trails of
illegal entrant 250811 and Han Tae-sul.
After contacting the illegal entrant,
Han evaded our pursuit,
then met her again in Busan
and fled with her help.
After that, they disappeared
for about three days.
Then they broke into a home in Imun-dong,
killed an innocent civilian,
stole some money and a car, and ran away.
That was six days ago,
and their trail has gone cold.
The report is
a reconstruction of statements
made by several illegal entrants.
We know where Han Tae-sul
and the suspect are headed.
I know you're still in mourning
and in training,
but if you want to join this operation,
I'll let you--
Yes, I want to.
Okay.
I just have to go inside?
We're just going to find out
where my brother is.
Shoot the woman dead on sight.
You were all in it together?
Goodbye.
Where's Seo-hae?
It's a typical delusion.
You knew about people
coming from the future!
Please stop!
Seo-hae.
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs