19 YEARS AGO
AUGUST 6, 2001
Hello?
Are you still alive?
I thought you were dead.
Why weren't you picking up?
What time is it?
It's past nine. Almost ten o'clock.
What?
I asked you to wake me at eight!
I kept calling you,
but you wouldn't pick up.
I told you I have to get the results
before meeting the investors tomorrow!
You couldn't do me that one favor?
Hey. I work so hard
enduring the smell of oil
just to support you.
How can you talk like that to me?
Anyway, I'm almost done.
I'll be home at around 12.
How about some beer later?
Sounds nice.
Oh, can you pick up
a box of Bacchus energy drinks
on your way home?
Don't get the fake ones
just because they're cheaper.
Only Bacchus, okay?
All right. I get it.
Jeez. I'm screwed.
So how is it going?
Wow.
Is it going to work this time?
Come on. Work.
No! What the heck?
Darn it.
I messed up.
-What?
-What's going on?
What's happening?
Gosh! Isn't that a man?
-Where?
-Oh, my gosh!
Sir, there's someone
on the rails over there!
-Move away from the rails!
-Is he dead?
Stay back, everyone!
-What's he doing?
-What's going on?
Sir, it's dangerous to be here.
The train is going to come soon.
Sir? Hello?
What?
Is he drunk?
Hey! Get up. Are you okay?
You shouldn't be…
What's this?
What? Why does he have
a photo of Tae-sul and me?
RECORDS OF ATTACKS ON HAN TAE-SUL
JULY 15, 2020: PLANE CRASH
AUGUST 15, 2020: CONFERENCE SHOOTING
Hey. What is this?
What does this all mean?
Who are you? How do you know Tae-sul?
Who are you?
What?
Hey, wait!
Hey, you! Who are you?
SISYPHUS
You're up.
You seem to have a lot of nightmares.
I do, too.
Let's go. Everyone's gone now.
Okay.
BANK TRANSFER FORM
THREE MILLION WON
"Kim Jin-hui."
RESIDENT ID CARD
PARK JAE-UK
-"Park Jae-uk."
-Sir!
You startled me!
What are you doing here?
What about the store?
It's payday today.
I came to get everyone's money.
Just use your phone for stuff like that.
Go back to the store.
Illegal immigrants can't use
mobile banking. That's too risky.
Anyway, who are you sending that to?
Three million won kept disappearing
from the account book. Is this it?
Just go, will you?
-Who are you sending it to?
-Hey!
Jeez. I work so many hours every day,
but I only get 1,8 million.
I provide you guys
with board and lodging as well.
Plus, you get additional incentives
for every successful deal.
Do your best.
Then I'll pay you three million won.
Just go and find Han Tae-sul!
Jeez. Aren't you going?
Do you want me to cut your pay?
What a horrible boss.
Fine. I am, so just report me
to the Ministry of Employment and Labor.
Sue me.
What will she do about it?
Stop staring at me.
You look fine. We're attending a party.
You look pretty.
Where should I hide my gun?
Don't even use that.
And let's not get shot, either.
Put that away.
Why aren't you dressed up?
I told you. Everyone will recognize me,
so I can't go in.
I just have to go inside?
Yes. I got your name on the list.
-What…
-Grace Park.
You have to pronounce it properly.
You're listed as
a foreign investment firm employee.
And if they ask questions,
pretend you don't understand Korean.
But I can't speak English.
It's fine. They'll get fooled
by anyone who's dressed up like this.
-I look stupid.
-No, you don't.
Besides, you have to hide
in the crowd of fools.
All right. I'm going through
the back door.
I'll look around the back
and the second floor, and you…
I'll check the first floor.
The entrance to the banquet hall.
Right. Okay.
Hold on. Let's check one last time.
We're just going to find out
where my brother is.
No commotion, okay?
No hitting people,
twisting their joints
or knocking them out.
You're dressed elegantly today,
so don't do that.
Whether it's Sigma or someone else,
don't fight with anyone.
-We'll see.
-Hey!
Fine.
Hang on.
Do you hear me?
Say something.
Stop it.
Here. This is an EMP.
If something happens,
push this red button.
Then it'll cause a blackout
in the whole building,
and we won't be able to communicate.
Got it?
Gang Seo-hae.
We got the approval.
Shoot the woman dead on sight.
To your positions!
Welcome. May I ask your name?
-Grace Park.
-One moment.
Okay. Welcome, Ms. Park.
Ms. Grace Park is entering.
I'm in.
Is everything going okay?
People keep staring at me.
I told you not to draw their attention.
I didn't do anything.
-What about my brother?
-I don't see him.
But what are all these people doing here?
Well, they're all celebrating
my death together.
But they're your company's people.
Well, to be exact, it's a stock company.
I only have five percent of the stocks,
so the remaining 95 percent
are having a party to celebrate my death.
It hasn't been officially announced yet,
but since this is a special occasion,
you can all greet him first.
This is the new CEO of Quantum & Time,
Edward Kim.
Eddy, come and greet them.
Thank you.
It's nice to meet you, everyone.
You must have been worried and anxious
due to the unfortunate events
that happened to our company.
It's not official yet,
but as the next CEO,
I want to tell you something today.
From now on, Quantum & Time
will be a company
that is defined by the two words,
trust and stability.
I want to use this opportunity
to ask for your support and encouragement.
You're all so excited, aren't you?
Hey.
After this is over,
let's go to an amusement park.
I'll be your guide.
But you hate amusement parks.
Did you hear me?
Well, you said you wanted to go.
I can just wait in line there.
So
be careful.
You too.
Team A, clear.
Team B, clear.
Sniper Team, clear.
Starting communication jamming.
Excuse me.
We've met before, right?
You look familiar.
Did we
meet at a conference?
Atlanta? Sydney?
There's no way I'd forget
such a beauty like you.
No.
You really don't know me?
I don't.
Then I can be honest with you.
I did over a hundred handshakes
with all these people here.
Everyone here apparently came
to congratulate me,
but the problem is
I can't trust any one of them.
To these people here,
I'm just a playing card
they'll discard after one use.
Just like my friend.
Han Tae-sul.
You know him, right?
I must've lost my mind.
He was a jerk,
but he was a good jerk. Damn it.
You're the only one I don't know here,
so let's clink our glasses.
Tae-sul,
I'll meet you in hell.
Why are you here?
I came with a friend.
Which friend? I know everyone here.
Well…
We're just going to find out
where my brother is.
Excuse me.
Han Tae-sul. I found Han Tae-san.
Yes, I'm patrolling the second floor.
Yes, it's clear.
Han Tae-sul. I found your brother.
What? Seo-hae?
Seo-hae? Gang Seo-hae!
What?
What did you say? Seo-hae!
Darn it. What did she say?
What is this?
"Technology transfer agreement"?
QUANTUM TELEPORTATION TECHNOLOGY
TRANSFER AGREEMENT
QUANTUM & TIME WILL SHARE
TECHNOLOGY WITH SIGMA
"Sigma."
Han Tae-sul, answer me.
I found your brother.
Hey!
Get that woman!
Find her!
I know who you are. Listen to me.
Stay away from Tae-sul. Understand?
What? Tae-sul, what happened?
Mr. Kim. What the hell is this?
Who the hell is Sigma?
-Our investor.
-Since when?
What do you mean?
Since the beginning. I reported it to you.
CEO: HAN TAE-SUL
The Control Bureau's operation
starts in a minute.
You should've attended our meetings.
I told you so many times
to pay attention--
-I'm going to tell everyone.
-Tell them what?
A crazy guy named Sigma is trying
to kill you and take over the company?
Or that there's a time machine,
and people are coming from the future?
What? Did you think you were
the only one who knew?
What?
-You were all in it together?
-Who would believe you now?
I'm sorry, but please stay quiet.
-Or you'll end up like your brother--
-What?
He can easily send people
to the mental ward.
Don't bother trying.
The Control Bureau has you surrounded.
Everything's over.
I'll kill you! I'm going to…
I got Han Tae-sul.
The girl. Start the operation.
Gang Seo-hae,
daughter of Lieutenant Gang Dong-gi.
You're putting Tae-sul in danger.
This is my last warning.
If I ever see you again,
I'll kill you.
We found her.
It's the Control Bureau. Han Tae-sul.
Han Tae-sul!
Catch her!
-What's going on?
-Crazy wench!
-Hey!
-Get it open! Hurry!
Hey, where are you?
Han Tae-sul, you idiot. Answer me!
This is an EMP.
If something happens,
push this red button.
Then it'll cause a blackout
in the whole building,
and we won't be able to communicate.
Goodbye.
Let's not cause a commotion.
People are watching.
You have nowhere else to go, anyway.
Don't go outside. There's a sniper.
My first mission was to kill you.
Get in!
Put your guns down. Check the plate!
Aren't you glad to see me?
You remember me, right?
What are you doing here?
Aren't you glad to see me?
Turn the car. Han Tae-sul…
What? Is that blood?
Are you okay? Did you get shot?
-Han Tae-sul…
-Are you okay?
Hey! Stay with me!
Are you okay? Stay with me!
Hey!
Darn it.
Han Tae-sul! Get down!
I said, get down!
Darn it.
Tae-sul!
How are you feeling? Are you okay?
-Tae-sul, look over here.
-What are you doing?
Are you okay?
-Of course not.
-How much do you remember?
What?
You got shot at the conference.
Fortunately, it was just a graze.
It just barely missed your artery
by a centimeter.
We got the culprit. He must've had
issues with our company.
-Tae-sul, let me see.
-Stop it.
-You can't get up yet. Stay in bed!
-Tae-sul!
Let me go!
Hey, you got shot!
We thought you were dead!
-You've been in a coma until--
-What the hell are you talking about?
Han Tae-sul! Get down!
What…
What are you two up to?
Tae-sul.
Where's Seo-hae?
-Who?
-Where's Seo-hae?
The girl who ran out
of the conference hall with me.
-Tae-sul.
-She saved my life.
And we went into hiding together.
And Sigma. What happened to Sigma?
And my brother?
Where's Tae-san?
-Tae-san is dead. Calm down.
-Tell me, Seo-jin.
I visited your place.
I went to your hospital. When was that?
It was four days
after the PEXCO incident, so…
August. August 19th.
Where's that girl you treated?
-Tae-sul.
-What?
Today is August 19th.
What are you talking about?
AUGUST 19, WEDNESDAY
-How dare you lie to me?
-Tae-sul.
-Tae-sul, stop it.
-Tae-sul, please!!
-Tae-sul!
-Move.
AUGUST 19, WEDNESDAY
What?
What's going on?
Why are you doing this to me?
You're all trying to fool me, right?
Hey, Kim Seung-bok.
You said on the phone
that you'll hold a funeral for me.
And you were all excited
after taking over my management rights,
held a party to celebrate
and drank yourself silly!
Tae-sul, what's wrong?
Tae-sul! It's okay. Breathe slowly.
Give me my phone.
I need to contact Seo-hae.
-Tae-sul, please stop!
-Right back at you, you jerk!
You jerks.
Do you think you can fool me?
Who ordered you to do this?
Seo-jin. Did your father
put you up to this?
-Tae-sul. Calm down.
-Calm down.
-I know everything.
-What?
I know you were all in on it.
How? I saw and heard everything
at your place.
You were going to hand over
my technology to Sigma.
It's the uploader, right?
Tell me. Who ordered you to do this?
Is it Sigma? Or the Control Bureau?
And you!
You already knew about people
coming from the future!
-Tae-sul!
Don't run!
What's going on?
What's the date?
August 19th? Damn it!
Let go of me!
Let me go, you jerks!
-Tae-sul.
-It's okay, Tae-sul.
-Stay still. It's going to be okay.
-No, don't do it.
No! Don't do this!
-Tae-sul.
-Don't do this.
Don't do this.
Don't
do this.
Don't…
Next news.
Quantum & Time's CEO, Han Tae-sul,
miraculously gained consciousness
this morning.
Reporter Choi Ji-eun.
Quantum & Time's CEO, Han Tae-sul,
gained consciousness
this morning at 11 a.m.
It's been four days
since he fell into a critical state
after the shooting incident at PEXCO.
The medical staff stated
that his life is not at risk,
but he is still recovering,
so he may not return
to his position as CEO yet.
This is all my fault.
No, it's his fault
that he's gone mad like that.
No. I should've treated him
properly since the beginning.
When he said strange things
and had hallucinations--
You know how stubborn he is.
I should've stopped him
from going to the conference.
There's this thing called confabulation.
It usually occurs in alcoholics.
When the frontal lobe is damaged,
you suffer memory loss.
And you start making up things
to fill in those gaps.
Then you start believing they're real.
What's more,
you were addicted to drugs before that.
And when you were shot…
I told you, remember?
You had an epidural hemorrhage.
It's this spot right here.
I think you're getting such symptoms
from the aftereffects.
You may have certain delusions
or sometimes confuse dreams with reality.
You're finally home.
Vitamin B will help you recover.
They're tranquilizers.
Please don't waste your energy.
Drink the juice too.
I saw Tae-san.
It's true. It was Tae-san.
I saw him when I was making the speech
at the conference.
He was standing among the reporters,
looking around for something.
And then I got shot,
and a woman saved me.
-Seo-hae?
-Yes, Seo-hae.
You probably don't believe me,
but it's true.
We're not the only ones
living in this world.
They say I'm going to build
a time machine.
They call it the uploader.
Some people from the future
are taking it to come here,
And there's a bureau that catches
such people. There are brokers, too.
And one of those people
is trying to kill me.
-Like The Terminator?
-Yes.
And this woman named Seo-hae
is protecting you?
She says the world is going to end.
To be exact,
a nuclear bomb will go off in Korea, and…
Never mind.
It sounds crazy even as I'm saying it.
Seo-jin told me to listen to you,
whatever you say.
She says you shouldn't use the internet.
I disconnected the Wi-Fi.
Just hang in there for a while.
When Seo-jin says it's okay, I'll--
Seung-bok.
What?
Be honest with me.
You're lying, right?
-No.
-Are you sure?
Yes.
Then have I really lost my mind?
You've just had a rough time.
Things were too--
You and I
have been friends all along, Seung-bok.
Swear on our friendship,
look into my eyes and tell me.
You're lying right now, aren't you?
I'd rather wish I were.
Get some rest. I'll get going.
Right.
Those pills could give you
a slight headache.
Get some rest.
Is your head hurting again?
It's because you're low on sugar.
It's inevitable for people
who use their brains all the time.
You should have some chocolate.
It's been a while.
I've always been by your side.
Shut up, please!
That's the N Seoul Tower.
So that's what it looked like originally.
What does it look like in the future?
It's collapsed to the side.
The future is
very different from now. There's nothing.
But I have to protect you.
You're the only person I know
whether from the past, present, or future.
Do you know what it's like to be alone?
-You should've visited more often.
-Sorry. I was busy.
Mom, are you feeling better now?
I'm always doing great.
Take care of yourself, all right?
Okay. I'll take good care of myself.
-So don't get sick, Mom.
-Okay.
You're here.
Hello.
Come to my study.
-Go on.
-Okay.
How's Tae-sul?
I guess he's still feeling confused.
He must be.
He's taking a lot of drugs.
How much?
Take this.
It'll help with your headaches.
Does your head hurt a lot?
And your hallucinations?
Which hallucinations?
The ones I used to have, or the new ones?
I heard you told Eddy everything.
It was real.
I don't know.
I don't know if it was real or not,
but that situation, those feelings…
I remember everything. I mean it.
That's what your senses are like.
You said it's a nuclear war, right?
There have been news reports
in the last two months
about talks with the US
and nuclear missiles in North Korea.
You must've made up stories in your head
with things like that
in your subconscious.
A time machine?
I guess you want to go back to the past.
It's a typical delusion.
Tae-sul.
Let's get you treated properly this time.
If you don't recover fully,
you'll have to get hospitalized.
Then you know
you'll have to step down as CEO.
Doctors aren't supposed to go along
with the patient's delusions,
but we can try this method
if they don't show any progress.
Look at this.
This is what you told Eddy.
Maybe you should think
about why you have such delusions
and why you've been making up
these stories in your mind.
You're smart.
Is it guilt?
Or is it anxiety
about losing your company?
Stop.
Or is it pressure
about having to be better than others?
I told you to stop!
Or is it a kind of defense mechanism?
Is it hard to build relationships?
Is that why you treat others badly
before you get hurt by anyone?
Hey. What did you give me?
You…
I read everything you said,
but there's one thing that doesn't add up.
What?
The key.
Where's the key?
By the time this is over,
Tae-sul won't be able to recover
because of the drugs.
I got a locked ward prepared for him.
What about Eddy?
He thinks it's just a treatment.
The only thing on his mind
is taking over the management rights.
And the key?
I'll find it soon.
We have to find that key.
Your mom won't survive
without the medicine they give us.
SATURDAY, FRIDAY, THURSDAY, WEDNESDAY
TUESDAY, MONDAY, SUNDAY, SATURDAY
Where's the key?
If what you said is true,
you had the key on you
before the party at our house.
But you don't have it now.
Did you hide it?
Or…
does the woman named Seo-hae
from your delusions have it?
Hey. Where's the key?
You made a promise, you know.
I don't know.
You little jerk.
You have no sense of ethics.
Shoot him.
If you keep insisting, you'll get hurt.
Not just you, but everyone you know.
So don't waste your energy and tell me.
Where's the key?
I told you I don't know. I swear!
Seo-hae.
Seo-hae?
What?
The time.
It's 22:00.
The moon.
The moon's azimuth.
It's 315,9 degrees.
Then the date is…
September 15th.
A month after we first met
at the conference.
Right.
A month after we first met.
That's right. I remember everything.
I remember everything about you.
Five.
What?
Four. Three. Two. One.
My goodness.
That startled me.
What was that? It suddenly dropped.
I'll clean that up later.
Tae-sul!
Be careful. You'll hurt your feet!
This isn't mine.
What?
Tae-sul, let's pick up where we left off.
Do you remember where the key is now?
Is that important right now?
I made it up, anyway.
Or did it all happen in real life?
This is an EMP.
If something happens,
push this red button.
Then it'll cause a blackout
in the whole building,
and we won't be able to communicate.
I DON'T WANT TO GET MARRIED, EITHER
-What is it?
-Nothing.
-What's that?
-I gave this to someone.
But it's right here.
What are you doing, Tae-sul?
Bring all the guards in.
Tae-sul, that's enough.
Just stay still, okay?
If you don't, you'll get hurt!
Seo-jin.
Let's stop now.
And watch your feet.
-Get him!
-What? Turn the lights on!
Tae-sul!
Han Tae-sul!
Darn it!
Tae-sul.
He can't have gone far.
Why are you here? I said I'll take care--
Where is Tae-sul? What about the police?
It'll complicate things.
I didn't report it.
Just call the cops.
EMERGENCY SERVICES
Who are those people?
I'm going to send Tae-sul to the hospital.
-You said he'll be okay.
-No.
He's in a risky state.
That's my opinion as a doctor.
Seo-jin.
Why are you doing this?
Is there something I don't know?
No, there isn't.
Just do as you're told,
like you've always done.
Then you can become the CEO.
Got that?
Anything else you want to ask?
The operation was going to fail anyway.
It could've been because of the wind,
or the EMP.
Or because your hand
suddenly started shaking.
Whatever the reason, it was bound to fail.
PERFORMANCE REPORT
OPERATION EXPECTED TO FAIL
Why did you tell me to do it, then?
Would you not have done it if you knew?
-I still would.
-Let me offer you some advice.
Don't try too hard.
You need to do your best,
but don't overdo it.
Some things work out,
and some things don't.
Just memorize that
if you want to keep working here.
"Some things work out. Some things don't."
That woman. Her!
Can I catch her?
You said you know what happens.
If I say you can't, will you give up?
-No.
-Then why do you ask?
You'll catch her.
So just trust me and wait.
CEO HAN TAE-SUL'S RETURN
TO MANAGEMENT POSITION UNCLEAR
How did things get so messed up?
Spread out and find him.
Make sure to block all the exits.
Darn it.
A telephone? There's no cord.
Okay!
Ringing tones are set at 2,600 Hz.
Please work.
Come on. Please work.
Yes! It's working!
-Hello?
-Hello? Is it you, Seo-hae?
-Is that you?
-Yes.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Did you manage to escape that day?
Yes. I saw the news.
You seemed to be doing fine.
Me?
I'm telling you this because you should
adjust to the modern society.
You shouldn't believe everything
the media says.
The world isn't that honest.
-What's going on?
-Seo-hae, listen carefully.
You're the only person I can trust
whether from the past, present, or future.
I ran away from home,
and I'm in huge trouble right now.
Can you help me?
Where are you?
I'm at Hannam Tool Market.
I'm a bit busy right now, though.
What? What are you doing?
-I'm just busy.
-Hey, you can't do this to me!
-Get down.
-What?
-I said, get down.
Hello? Seo-hae?
Oh, my gosh. What the heck?
What was that?
Darn it.
Hey. Why are you here?
You said you were busy.
What can I do? You said
I was the only one you could trust.
What?
This part is my favorite.
It's romantic.
Don't you agree, Mr. Han Tae-san?
Help me save Tae-sul.
You think you can change the future?
I can change it.
Who is Sigma?
I met your brother.
I figured out who Sigma is.
He was right next to us all along.
You must not turn off the downloader.
And the other person who's watching this.
You just stay put,
because I will find you.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs