Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
DONATION BOX
HANKUK UNIVERSITY MEDICAL SCHOOL
JUNE 2010, SUMMER OF TWENTY-ONE
Thank you.
All right. Everyone did a great job today.
-Thank you!
A toast to the med students' hard work
and everyone who attended
the medical school's pub today! Cheers!
-Cheers!
MEDICAL SCHOOL
ONE-DAY PUB
Nice.
I wanted to ask you,
what's your name?
I'm Shin Sol-i.
Your name is as pretty as you look.
Are you a freshman? What's your major?
Who invited you?
Well, I…
Why do you have so many questions?
Oh, you're Heon's friend.
There's hard liquor on that table.
Heon, I can hold my drink.
Why don't we play a game?
Playing a game will liven up the mood.
Yes, let's play a game.
How about the Game of Truth?
All right.
My bad. I'll spin it.
Goodness, it's Ji-hui.
Hey.
Okay, pay attention. I'll ask a question.
"There's someone I like here." Yes or no?
Come on. Say it.
Say it.
-Say it.
-Say it
No way.
Well, I…
You like someone. Who is it?
Sol-i. Help me.
-Love shot.
-Okay.
I like
-Cha--
-Ouch!
I have
a sudden stomachache.
-Right now?
-Yes.
My girlfriend isn't feeling well.
We'll get going.
Let's go.
-What?
-She's his girlfriend?
Heon,
I have a question.
What is it?
Earlier…
I mean,
by any chance, did you
really just call me your girlfriend?
I mean, I'm not sure if I heard it right.
I did.
Since when?
Since when was I your girlfriend?
I don't know.
Heon. My boyfriend.
Wait for me!
Sol-i, are you that happy
that you're Heon's girlfriend now?
Yes, I am.
I'm so happy.
All your hard work paid off.
You finally made it.
Ha-young.
Heon and I
even held hands.
That's great.
"Hands"?
-You've only held hands so far?
-Yes.
Sol-i.
You're still a baby.
What do you mean?
How far have you gone with Heon so far?
What?
Then, you and Jin-hwan…
No way!
Baby, you have so much to learn from me.
Let's take care of those clothes first.
Let's go.
-Now?
-Finish your drink.
What are you doing tonight?
What? Tonight?
Nothing much.
In that case,
don't go back to your dorm tonight.
Stay with me.
All night?
You and I together?
But I'm not mentally prepared.
Sol-i.
What are you imagining?
What?
I'm going to do my assignment
in the library.
I was asking you to stay with me
if you weren't busy.
I see.
That's what you meant.
Heon, the night air feels
nice and cool these days.
Right?
Right.
Sol-i.
Yes?
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
Come here.
Why?
Okay.
Excuse me.
You're so my type.
May I have your number?
Hey! Who do you think you are?
Who are you?
He's my boyfriend.
What?
You know what?
We should stay together all day.
Don't go overboard.
How did you know I was here?
I'm your boyfriend.
I will go and find you,
no matter where you are.
Really? You're amazing.
Study.
What's this?
"Do you have a boyfriend?
You're a goddess."
"Can we meet if you have time? 010-53…"
What's this? A poem?
"Kang Ha-young, you're my black hole.
You make me fall for you.
I will love you forever"?
He must be crazy.
How dare he? Who is this?
Hey, look at me, poet.
Who wrote this poem?
I'll throw them all out.
Forget it. I'll go home.
We're done.
Great. Thank you.
Thank you.
Let's go straight to Seongsu-dong.
You have a commercial shoot soon.
Okay. Let's go.
Sorry about the tight schedule.
You have to finish everything
before the season starts.
I know. Don't worry.
Hi, Dae-sung. I'm a huge fan.
May I have your autograph?
Sure. What's your name?
-It's Ji-hye.
-Ji-hye?
DECEMBER 2012, WINTER OF TWENTY-THREE
WAITING FOR YOU ON A WINDY DAY
Read.
Jin-hwan, don't you have
any classes today?
I only called Ha-young.
I don't. We're a couple, anyway.
Heon!
Oh, hi.
You and your girlfriend are famous now.
Look at this.
See you. Let's go.
Bye.
Sol-i. You should've told us about this.
How could you do the photoshoot
without us?
I'm so disappointed.
Jin-hwan, you don't even attend
Hankuk University.
I practically do because my girlfriend
and my friends go there.
Heon, you look great in this picture.
Right?
Sol-i.
Yes?
You knew, didn't you?
Yes.
Actually, a reporter
from the school newspaper contacted me
and said he'd give me this.
I'm sorry. Are you angry?
He said we looked so good together,
so he took the photo without realizing it.
Take us with you.
It's just for two people.
You disloyal jerk.
When did you become a romantic?
You're so ungrateful.
Yes, we'll go on our own.
Get lost, Jin-hwan.
Ha-young, look at them.
HANKUK UNIVERSITY HOSPITAL
CARDIOVASCULAR CENTER
Mr. Jeong Jin-hwan, please come in.
Yes.
Are you really okay?
Of course.
Aren't you going to tell Ha-young?
No, I won't.
That means
you should keep this a secret.
Why did you call me?
I was focusing on my studies.
I'm really busy because the first draft
of my master's thesis is due today.
Is something wrong?
Let's break up.
What?
We've been going out for too long.
We're getting sick of each other.
Jin-hwan, are you kidding me?
I'm sorry.
This isn't funny at all.
What the hell are you doing?
You said you were busy. You should go now.
I'll get going.
Hey!
-Heon, you're here.
-Hi.
Why do you have so much in your bag?
Isn't it heavy?
-No.
-Do you want me to carry it?
No, it's okay.
When did you get here?
Why didn't you call me?
He's really handsome.
Is she his girlfriend?
-He's way too good for her.
-I agree.
Don't listen to them.
I didn't hear anything.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Jin-hwan will go into surgery.
What?
He told me not to tell Ha-young.
But the surgery's quite risky,
so I think we should tell her.
No wonder.
Ha-young is really shocked
because Jin-hwan suddenly
broke up with her.
You should talk to her
so that she doesn't get upset.
Okay, I will. Don't worry.
Good.
THE 100 GREATEST SPORTSMEN
Dae-sung is on a roll!
He took first place again.
I heard he's famous abroad, too.
He's a superstar now.
Did you guys see his automobile advert?
He looked so cool
with the convertible car.
Mr. Jeong Jin-hwan,
prepare for your surgery in 30 minutes.
Jin-hwan.
Ha-young.
Are you stupid? Did you think
I wouldn't know if you didn't tell me?
I was sorry.
-So…
-Don't be sorry.
It's okay as long as you survive.
I'll be waiting. See you after surgery.
Okay.
JUNE 2014, SUMMER OF TWENTY-FIVE
Okay. Who's next?
-Me!
-Hey.
I've been looking for you.
It's a scary lady. Run away!
Go back!
Goodness.
Take my love.
No, thanks.
JULY 2015, SUMMER OF TWENTY-SIX
Heon!
Heon, shouldn't you be at the hospital?
I came here to see you.
Aren't you tired?
Part-time jobs are always hard.
Here.
Thanks.
Sit down. I'll do it.
Really?
Thank you.
-He's so cute.
-Thank you.
-I'd like one, too.
-He's so handsome.
-Thank you.
-You're so good-looking.
-Me, too.
-Thank you.
-Give me one more, please.
-Let's ask for one.
-Give me one, please.
-Thank you.
-Me, too.
You'll get sunburned. Put this on.
It's hot.
I know. Just put it on.
Why?
Just put it on!
Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Why are you already here?
I said I'd go to you after work.
You're always busy,
so I don't mind coming to see you.
Haven't you heard?
I'm the best mentor you can find.
Heon, are you busy?
Your boyfriend's a doctor.
You should call him right now.
I recommended you
for the training program in the US.
Dr. Cha will go to the States, won't he?
Kim U-hyeon, male, 53. TA.
-V-tach!
-A hundred and fifty joules.
I can't take it anymore.
Let's break up.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-hyun Yang