♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 12=
(Apart from you like stars in the sky)
(Jingnv Pavilion)
We're playing polo
against Luming Pavilion?
We're all ladies.
I've never even ridden a horse before.
How are we going to play polo?
That's true.
It's the family affair between
the Commandery Prince of Julu,
and Xiaoman anyway.
If we take part hastily,
it's not appropriate.
That's right.
We're all ladies.
Could Xiaoman be sold
and someone's happy about it?
In this world,
there are too many injustice
towards us ladies.
Are we not going to help
other ladies?
Help her if you want.
I can't do it.
I was angry with him.
Who knew
it's as if he was born to play polo.
My bad.
I'm not as bright as the city people.
I'm such an idiot.
Xiaoman.
Oh, right.
About what happened before this,
how did it go?
It's solved.
Don't worry
about me.
Since Yanniang has decided to do so,
I should be responsible
for your matters anyway.
You're my junior,
and also the most hardworking
student in Jingnv Pavilion.
I'm like your teacher.
There's no way I'll ignore you.
Don't worry.
Zhao Xiaoqian can't do
anything to me for now.
I'm
not just a powerless scholar.
Xiaoman.
Teacher.
I've heard about what happened.
I've disgraced you.
How is that disgrace?
As a concubine,
your fate isn't up to you.
I heard you're going to
have a polo match
with the Commandery Prince
at the old academy.
Actually,
I couldn't even ride a horse properly.
I made that decision in a rush.
Please forgive me.
How do I forgive you?
Since such misfortune is set,
compromising
will be unfair for ourselves.
Confucius compared ladies to villains.
So, as ladies,
all the more we should
always remind ourselves
of the way of gentlemen.
We must keep our word.
For our own destiny,
we must also achieve
something for our future.
Hopefully we'll have a clear
conscience towards heavens,
towards the world,
and ourselves,
understand?
Teacher, may I ask,
what's the meaning of have a clear
conscience towards ourselves?
In the past, Lady Hao went to the
battlefield in her husband's place,
and Princess Zhao of Pingyang
guarded Niangzi Pass.
The two of them never relied
on their father or brothers.
People always say
ladies depend on others throughout their
lives, akin to climbers on trees,
and the tree here means the
male members of her family.
But ladies in this world
are no different from men.
The only difference is
ladies neither compete,
nor dare,
thinking submitting will
mean an easy life in future.
However, easy life or not,
it depends on others.
Food handed out in
contempt is tasteless.
Heavens help those who help themselves.
Today,
if you stand forth for yourself,
even if you failed in future,
you won't regret it.
But if you admit defeat
or give in,
then your destiny
is no longer up to yourself.
Teacher, do you mean
I should fight for my own destiny?
A just cause attracts much support,
an unjust one finds little.
If you're firm-minded,
yours will be a just cause.
I understand now.
Teacher, you're broad-minded and bold.
I'll go and take a look at her first.
Xiaoman.
Ladies.
I know.
Perhaps all of you are thinking.
What did Xie Xiaoman do
to be loathed by the Commandery Prince
and even offered to sell her to others?
In fact...
In fact, I also want to know why.
What exactly happened that
Xie Xiaoman has to end up in this state?
Today,
I'm not afraid of being
embarrassed anymore.
I'll tell you the entire story.
I thought about living in
Yuyangli my entire life.
Plant mulberry trees during
peak farming season,
and study during off-peak season.
Find a good husband,
and lead a stable life
as long as we're safe and secure
for the rest of our lives.
But the current era
is so harsh towards ladies.
I won't hide it from everyone else.
That day,
I indeed spent the night
with the Commandery Prince.
It was an accident.
But my entire life
was changed since that night.
The times we're in now,
ladies have to obey
their father's orders at home,
and after they get married, they'll
obey their husband's orders.
When their husband pass away,
it's the sons.
I've always enjoyed studying
because it'll bring us knowledge.
But if I can't even determine
my own fate,
what good will knowledge do?
If we keep living in the lessons
of "Admonitions for Ladies",
we'll only suffer more and more.
For us ladies,
a concubine like me,
or a female servant,
or even courtesans,
none of us is an object.
We shouldn't be trampled by others
or thrown around.
What's the purpose of studying anyway?
I've been thinking about this question
ever since I joined the academy.
Now,
I seem to have understood a little.
Perhaps it takes this kind of suffering
and tribulations
for us to understand that
like men, we're also humans.
I'm not afraid to fight with anyone.
I just want Xie Xiaoman
to live on with a sense of pride.
Today, the person who is
asking for your help
isn't your classmate, Xie Xiaoman,
but a lady
Xie Xiaoman.
I'll help you.
It's not easy for ladies anywhere.
We're not those kind of
ordinary short-sighted ladies.
Let's show those guys
from Luming Pavilion
that
we can also play polo with them,
fair and square.
Count me in!
We'll also help you.
Of course.
I'll help you, too.
Zhao Xiaoqian,
what are you doing?
All of us are friends.
In future, when we meet,
it'll only make things
difficult for all of us.
Jingnv Pavilion has promised Xiaoman.
But even if that's the case,
it's also very unlikely they'll win.
You shouldn't be doing this.
I agree.
Hanchen.
Don't let yourself regret this.
I'm already regretting
marrying her.
Master.
This rascal.
What happened to you this time?
Did you come and have a drink with me?
Or you're here for archery?
That shot
was full of determination.
But you've been visiting
the army camp often lately.
What are you up to?
Are you planning to join Xiongjie Camp
or remain at Wujiang Prefecture?
Master, you've heard of it?
Of course.
Commandery Prince of Julu's
selling his concubine.
Everyone in Wujiang Prefecture knows.
So, Master,
what do you think I should do?
When I first taught
you horseback archery,
I told you,
for us men,
if you have high ambitions,
you need to be broad-minded.
Attachment to the self
brings about trouble.
Self-centeredness is
a no-no for soldiers.
If you have high ambitions,
you'll have to let go of certain things.
Master, do you mean
you want me to let go?
Men should be
adaptable to circumstances.
If you want to leave
Wujiang Prefecture itself,
then nothing at this place
should hold you back.
Squire Wang, will you really redeem me?
Certainly.
Then I'm willing to marry you.
I hope you're not lying to me
and are indeed planning to
make me your wife.
You're really agreeing to it?
Yanniang,
don't worry.
I'll definitely treat you well.
I guarantee
I won't get any concubines.
When we get your contract,
I'll make you
my wife openly.
Magistrate Yan,
about redeeming Courtesan Zhu,
I need your help.
(Capital)
(Kunning Palace)
(Crown Prince, Zhao Xiaoze)
Lady Shen again submitted a
memorial to the palace today,
(Eunuch Wang Xian)
saying she wants to meet Your Highness.
How many times has she done
that in this month alone?
It must be about
(Empress)
Commandery Prince of Julu.
I don't understand
what Shen Zunfu is thinking.
Zhao Xiaoqian got
a concubine in Wujiang,
embarrassing Shen Family.
Yet, he's still thinking of
letting Lingniang marry him.
Maybe Lingniang is the one
who couldn't forget him.
Did you forget?
Lingniang and the Commandery Prince
grew up in the palace together.
His Majesty
verbally granted their marriage before.
What Commandery Prince has done
is known all across the capital.
Lingniang would rather
compromise her dignity
than change her mind.
Perhaps...
Perhaps she's unwilling to enter
the imperial palace as a concubine.
Lingniang is entering the palace?
His Majesty is here!
You may rise.
Yesterday, Xiaoze said
he's almost memorised "Mencius"
by heart,
and yet you still haven't
tested him on it.
What were you writing?
(Emperor)
"To be able to celebrate with the people
as one's happiness."
What does it mean?
It's talking about
King Wen of Zhou was
building the astronomy tower.
He said to the people,
"take your time to build the tower."
The people thought King Wen
was concerned about them,
so they put even more effort into it.
However, when it's completed,
King Wen of Zhou was found
relaxing in the astronomy tower.
It was then the people realised
King Wen of Zhou's aim
was to enjoy himself in the tower.
So, this sentence implies that
King Wen...
King Wen wants to
celebrate with the people.
It means the king should apply
the policy of benevolence,
share weal and woe with the people,
and celebrate together.
It's better to have a solid foundation
when it comes to studying.
Don't be restricted in vision
and shallow in understanding.
In the past, when Hanchen
studied "Mencius",
it took him great painstaking effort.
Not only must you memorise it by heart,
you have to understand what it means.
Learn from your brother.
I understand.
I received many memorials again.
I need to leave.
The osmanthus tree at the backyard
is going to bloom soon.
You and your son should go
have a look when you have time.
No need to see me off.
Revise with the Crown Prince.
Take care, Your Majesty.
Take care, father.
Your Highness,
regarding Lady Shen...
I won't meet her.
Entering the palace or not
isn't up to her.
(Residence of the Shen Family, Capital)
Her Highness wants us to send
Lingniang to the palace.
How can I let them ruin our Lingniang?
His Majesty is much older
than Lingniang.
No, this won't do.
I married you
not to let our daughter suffer.
I don't care.
Go to the palace and tell His Majesty
that Lingniang's already engaged.
What are you talking about?
Zhao Xiaoqian has got himself a
concubine in Wujiang Prefecture.
It's an act of humiliation towards us
as well as Lingniang.
You've been
my wife for years.
Why don't you understand
such a simple theory?
(Madam Shen)
Why won't Her Highness meet Lingniang?
Do you know why?
(Minister of Bureau of Military Affairs,
Shen Zunfu)
Her Highness has decided
to bring Lingniang to the palace,
but the current situation within
the palace is very complicated.
Noble Consort Zhang and Her Highness
are fighting over His Majesty's favour,
but she has no child.
Her Highness has Crown Prince,
yet Chancellor Xu's clinging
to Crown Prince for his power.
The forces in the capital
are intertwined and complicated.
Our Junfu is coming back next year.
Her Highness' idea
is to let Shen Family settle down first.
You won't let Lingniang enter
the palace.
Do you want to let her enter
the East Palace?
(Lingniang, Shen Zhaowen)
Do you mean
you want my Lingniang,
to set the path for Shen Family?
We're a family of high officials,
not some unknown people
who climbed up to this status today.
We
can't afford to fall.
It's the last 15 minutes.
Don't give up.
Hang in there.
Although those from Luming Pavilion
are natural horse riders,
we mustn't lose to them.
I'll remember
the kindness you all show today.
In future,
if any of you
are treated unfairly by the society,
I'll be the first to stand up for you.
Why don't we
recite "The Ballad of Mulan"
to boost our morale?
Sure!
Sigh.
Mulan sat at home weaving,
but the loom's resonant sound
could not be heard
over the girl's sighs,
but my father has no son,
and I have no big brother.
I want to go to buy
a saddle and a horse
to serve in my father's place.
The night air moved
the watchman's rattle,
the cold light glinted on her armour.
A hundred generals died in battle,
in ten years she returned
as a great warrior.
Mulan said, "The male rabbit
normally hops and runs
while the female sits and stares.
But both flee fast
when danger threatens.
How can one tell whether they
are male or female then?"
Sister,
did something happen within the mansion?
Lady Xie,
well...
I still have something on.
I don't know anything.
(Lotus Garden)
Wick,
come closer.
Try again once more.
What's wrong?
What's she doing?
This afternoon,
she bought a few books on polo.
I guess she's practising now.
Your Highness,
a married couple's fights don't last.
Why don't you just go in?
Maybe if she's happy,
the misunderstanding between
you two will be solved.
What's there to solve?
She's already made her decision.
It's already been said.
If all the misunderstandings
in this world
can be solved so easily,
then I...
Wick, don't sleep.
Help me see
if my action just now
was correct or not.
Yes.
This is the page.
Why does it feel strange though?
Is that so?
What are you doing?
Leave us first.
Let me tell you.
Many of the students at Jingnv Pavilion
are skilled in polo.
We won't lose to
you all from Luming Pavilion.
You've been practising polo
the entire evening?
That's right.
It's going well.
Do you want to leave me so badly?
Speak.
What are you doing?
You're the one who
was planning to sell me.
You abandoned me first.
I sold you?
Don't you know why I did that?
Let go of me!
Let go!
You're my concubine
yet you secretly helped Li Su.
What do you take me for?
I'm the Commandery Prince, you know.
Speak!
Let go!
Yes,
that's right.
It's because I was worried something
might happen to Congwen.
That's why I copied the intelligence.
It's because Congwen helped me before.
Be it Congwen
or Teacher Liu,
they're the ones who told me that
ladies can also study and
know the rules of propriety.
Ladies can also have their own path.
And you?
Zhao Xiaoqian,
I'm thankful for what you did for me,
and I'm also trying to repay that.
However, am I mere nothing to you?
What unforgivable mistake did I make?
When you're unhappy,
you just sold me to others?
Zhao Xiaoqian,
you were going to sell me.
So tell me.
Why should I be in love with you?
Why should I be in love with
a person who decides
my destiny as he pleases?
Let go!
Please let me go!
Do you hate me so much?
In future, when you've left my side,
take good care of yourself.
Don't try to step up for others anymore.
If you come across someone
other than me,
who knows
you might even get killed.
Did you know?
I also hate myself.
There're so many ladies in this world.
Why does it have to be you
of all people?
You heartless Xie Xiaoman.
Your Highness.
Su Family sent someone here
to bring Lady Xie back.
Chase them away.
That'd be inappropriate.
After all, it's Lady Xie's family.
Do I need to teach you all these?
If they cause a ruckus again,
just seal Su Chang Ji.
I want to grow old.
Please have a look.
There's a 200-tael note inside
as well as a deed.
Xiaoman will go with you
after the polo match.
Let her leave
and return the deed to her.
Tell her not to return to
Wujiang Prefecture anymore.
♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step
on the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey has rendered
my longing, rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are
far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
Xie Xiaoman's been playing
the entire day.
She hasn't eaten anything yet until now.
Yes.
Xiaoman hasn't eaten?
Could it be the same for Minggu, too?
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures find
right companions and become a pair♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
(Apart from you like stars in the sky)
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures find
right companions and become a pair♪
I scored!
(Bailu Academy)
Principal.
It's you, Xingzhou.
It's late. You haven't gone home yet?
I purposely came to look for you.
Principal,
I guess the polo match will
go on as usual tomorrow.
But if we
don't want things to get more
serious than it already is,
the polo match mustn't
have a final result.
Therefore, I'd like to ask you
to think of a way to
terminate the match tomorrow.
I know what to do
to solve the issue.
Since you're solving the issue,
problems shouldn't arise
from it further.
You must consider carefully.
I understand.
Sister! Sister!
Careful.
(Bailu Academy Polo Tournament)
Fellow students,
this time's polo match as a test
is a first for male and female
students to fight in opposing teams
ever since the establishment
of Bailu Academy.
It'll set a precedent.
I hope everyone will strictly
follow the rules
by competing in fairness and
win with your techniques.
Don't overdo it.
The match begins!
Whoever scores a goal gets a point.
The team who gets three points
first wins.
Let's begin.
Hanchen, catch this!
Minggu!
Careful! Don't fall!
Don't talk nonsense!
It's none of your business!
Luming Pavilion gets a point!
It's all right. Don't give up.
Let's carry on.
Okay.
Careful.
Careful, sister!
Xiaoman!
The rein!
Are you all right?
Stay out of this.
I'm going to pass this examination.
I...
Great!
They scored again.
Minggu,
I didn't do it on purpose.
Minggu!
Luming Pavilion, second point!
You're the one who wanted to sell me.
You abandoned me first.
Did you know?
I also hate myself.
There're so many ladies in this world.
Why does it have to be you
of all people?
You heartless Xie Xiaoman.
Xiaoman,
stop spacing out.
It's going to begin soon.
One more goal.
One more goal
and we'll separate.
Hanchen.
What are you doing? It's starting soon.
(Mulan)
Should we continue with
the match tomorrow?
Wait.
It seems like it's raining heavily.
Take a rest, all of you.
Keep the scores in mind.
We'll break the part of incense
to where it's burned to now,
and continue the match tomorrow.
Come on.
Let's go.
Sister,
our parents told me to bring you home.
Where's Wick?
She's been sent back
early this morning.
I have a way. Let's go.
All right.
Let's go.
You cried just now?
Minggu!
Why is she so grumpy today?
I just scored a goal, that's all.
Seriously.
Hanchen,
it's raining so heavily.
Let's go.
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪