♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Sausages.
You want a sausage? Oscar sausage.
Two are in Level 29.
One is in Level 26, one is in Level 27.
Do you still have comments?
This year, we have students for the fourth exam.
And four students.
Not much time left.
You have to come out
with a strategy against him.
Or else, let alone half an hour,
you wouldn’t even be able
to take his first attack.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 14]
Teacher Zhao’s Martial Soul is Supreme Bear.
It’s a powerful beastly Martial Soul.
He’s completely flawless.
Its defense is extremely terrifying.
Even the soul masters at his level...
can hardly hurt him.
Flawless.
Speed was Teacher Zhao’s weak point.
But there’s a big difference between
your soul power and his,
so this weak point is worthless to you.
Teacher Zhao has a nickname
in the school, Acala.
He’s Acala?
What? You have heard about him?
Many years ago,
Acala offended Martial Soul Hall.
He was surrounded by 16 bishops
of Soul Emperor level.
But they didn’t succeed.
Acala fought against 16 people.
He survived the surrounding attack.
Since then, he disappeared
in the world of soul master.
Turns out he’s teaching here.
[Shrek School]
So great.
Back then, Teacher Zhao was just a Soul Emperor.
I haven’t seen Teacher Zhao gave his full effort.
So pray for yourself.
Get to know each other...
to see how you can work together.
So you can endure the fight a little longer.
I’m Tang San. My tool soul is Blue Silver Plant.
A soul master of Level 29
from Controlling Branch.
Xiao Wu, my beast soul is Rabbit.
A soul master of Level 29
from Storm Attack Branch.
Zhu Zhu Qing. My beast soul
is the Cat of Netherworld.
A soul master of Level 27
from Keen Attack Branch.
Ning Rong Rong.
My tool soul is the Qibao Amber Pagoda.
A soul master of Level 26
from Assisting Branch.
You’re from the Qibao Amber Tribe?
Is that the tribe with the most powerful
assisting tool soul of the land,
Qibao Amber Tribe?
Stop staring. I’m no difference from others.
I sneaked out from my home.
Let’s talk after this test.
Two souls rings of mine can increase
our speed and strength.
The increment is about 30%.
It can last for half an hour without problem.
30%?
That’s great.
I think the combination
of your Martial Souls are good.
Come out with a strategy quickly.
Ning Rong Rong assists the three of us.
Xiao Wu is the main striker.
I’ll control Teacher Zhao’s attack.
Try my best to limit him...
to help Xiao Wu attack.
Zhu Zhu Qing, pin him down from the flanks.
I’ll go there first, then you...
How is it? Are you done discussing?
Teacher. We can start now.
When the Qibao spins, there will be amber.
Good fellow. Turns out one of the
candidates is from Qibao Amber Tribe.
Not bad.
Frander is going to be excited about it.
If you meet a soul master
from Qibao Amber Tribe,
you must defeat him/her immediately.
Not good.
I’ll play with you guys today.
You aren’t strong enough, little girl.
Xiao Wu.
Let me show you my power then.
It’s still not strong enough.
Oh, really?
Rise.
What’s going on?
Are they destroying the school?
Delightful. Again.
Little girl, good timing.
Qibao gives the power.
Qibao gives the speed.
Spinning is also fun.
You’re truly the number one Martial Soul
of Assisting Branch.
[Soul Land]
Little San, are we fighting too harshly?
No. Teacher Zhao hasn’t used his soul skill.
The master is defeated by the newbies.
It seems I have to be more serious with you guys.
Mu Bai. What are you laughing at?
See me tomorrow for practical class.
Kids, come on.
Let’s continue.
Xiao Wu, Human Meteor Hammer.
Blue Silver Plant. Intertwine.
That’s not good.
Xiao Wu.
Great. There’s puzzling soul skill.
Sadly, you forgot that my nickname is...
Teacher Zhao’s nickname is Acala.
Puzzling skill is useless to him.
Besides, if the level difference is too big...
Xiao Wu.
She’s fine.
Puzzling soul skill is good,
but the gap between
her soul power and mine is too great.
She’s attacked by her own soul power.
That’s the natural result.
Just like the poison on your Blue Silver Plant...
is useless against me.
Let her sleep for a night.
She’ll recover tomorrow morning.
I don’t need to fight again, right?
Little girl from Qibao Amber Tribe, you lose.
The gap between us is too big.
You can’t even fight me for half an hour.
Can you please take care of Xiao Wu?
What? You want to carry on?
I’m afraid you may not even
take one attack of mine.
My second soul skill, Supreme Palm,
is not so easy to handle.
I don’t want to continue
the current exam with you.
That means you’ve surrendered?
No.
I hope to fight you seriously.
We’ll start from the beginning.
If I can withstand more than half an hour,
then please allow the four of us
to join Shrek School.
What if you fail?
Just now the four of you fought together,
you lost.
Tang San, we’re comrades-in-arm.
Worst comes to worst, we’ll leave together.
If I lose, we’ll leave together.
Okay, as you wish.
[Xuan Tian Records. General principle.]
[Don’t try to defeat your opponent
by pretending to be weak.]
[Or else, you’ll really lose.]
If the one we were facing just now was an enemy,
Xiao Wu might have been harmed.
As your older brother, I couldn’t protect you.
Unexpectedly, this little boy
made me feel a little uneasy.
Teacher Zhao, beware. Twenty-Four Moonlight Bridges.
Soul guiding tool?
Tang San’s skill...
Which clan is this attack from?
I haven’t seen this before.
It’s really flawless.
Not right.
Flawless is the flaw.
If the power is focused in front,
once the back is relaxed,
that’s the point where my chance stands.
Good kid.
Turns out Blue Silver Plant can reach such level.
Supreme Palm.
Good monkey, you’re really keen.
This is how you want to buy time.
It won’t be so easy.
Increase gravity.
What a strong soul skill.
What a strong sense of pressure.
My body is sucked to the ground.
Where can you run?
The famous Acala...
can’t even defeat a 12-year-old kid.
Dangerous.
If this is spread, it’ll be the joke
of other teachers.
I’ll surely take this child.
But this exam should end now.
What does this mean?
It’s about to end.
Could this be Teacher Zhao’s...
Little monkey.
This is my fourth soul skill.
[Next Episode]
How’s Xiao Wu?
Come out. I know you’re here.
Who are you?
I meet Acala in such an insignificant place.
I want to fight against with you.
Let’s begin.