♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
It’s bad, Little San might be in trouble.
I didn’t expect that
I’ll be killed by someone who uses useless poison.
I’ll give you one day.
If you can cure my poisons with your antidotes,
that means you’re qualified.
Or else, you will die.
Whether Dugu Bo keeps his promise,
I have to hedge my bet.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 49]
Octa Dark Frost, a unique winter flower.
Even it’s a great item, but it’s poisonous too.
It causes freezing chill and numbness.
Even my Xuan Yu Hand is badly burnt.
This Fiery Soft Apricot is extremely poisonous.
It’s important to understand the nature
and prescription of these herbs.
It tastes good.
I hope they’re not too fiery.
Xiao Gang, we’ve been searching for him for a day.
No matter how well San Pao smells,
if we continue to do it,
it’s struggling for it.
Get some rest.
Don’t worry, Xiao Gang.
Dugu Bo might not kill Tang San.
Or else, he could have done it in our school.
Why took him away?
No, you have no idea.
Dugu Bo abducted Tang San
surely because what he did to Dugu Yan
and the poison casting skill Tang San has shown.
I guess,
Dugu Bo must be eager to know
about Tang San’s poison.
He wants to know what poison Tang San has.
I’m pretty sure
Dugu Bo won’t spare his life.
Those useless Great Soul Land Masters
from Tian Dou Imperial School!
They only know Dugu Bo
stays in this Sunset Forest,
but don’t know in which mountain.
They told us about Sunset Forest,
that means they have already offended Dugu Bo.
Even if they know his exact location,
they can’t tell us.
If anything happens to Tang San,
what are we going to say to him?
Him? Who is it?
In Xuan Tian Records,
in order to enter the Ice Fire Mouth Spring,
one must consume Octa Dark Frost
and Fiery Soft Apricot simultaneously.
Both herbs grow by the two extreme
spring water in Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
Only they can restraint the great force
from both spring water.
If Dugu Bo breaks his promise,
I can even hide in the Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
But, I’m feeling unwell.
Brother, hang on!
You’re heading a new route.
You can’t die, alright?
Little San, remember we’re brothers.
- Brother, it’s me.
- Little San, Grandpa is here to pick you up.
This power...
It’s a Grand Soul Land Master.
If he can cure the poison of
my granddaughter and me,
I won’t let this best chance slip away.
Is the kid dead yet?
I’d better go and have a look.
I’ll get him out if he’s still alive.
How dare someone challenge me?
Alright, I would like to see who is that.
Two Saints of Soul above Level 70.
and a soul master under Level 30.
Do they have death wishes?
You’re here for me?
Dugu Bo, where’s Tang San?
Where did you hide him?
Who are you to question me?
You!
Senior Dugu, Tang San is our disciple.
We’re not sure how he offended you,
but since you’re a Grand Soul Land Master,
we beg you to let him go.
That kid, I’ve already killed him.
Want to take revenge?
Even though three of you are weak,
but I still can take it as warming up.
Dugu Bo, you’ll regret killing Tang San.
Come, show me
what you have got to challenge me!
Before that, let me tell you.
I have a thousand ways
to put you in a living hell.
[Soul Land]
Sun Moon Golden Shine.
What soul skill is this?
Luo San Pao.
There’s even a trinity Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
It can even be summoned on the host?
Could this be the legendary Dragon Chief?
Sacred Dragon.
So what if it’s Sacred Dragon?
It looks like the Golden Dragon.
It can beat me with that oppressive force.
Even the Golden Dragon isn’t as powerful as me,
but its ability to fly makes it more flexible.
My skill is overbearing.
If I ruin it here,
then the game’s not worth the candle.
The key to Martial Soul Fusion Skill
goes back to the soul masters.
They aren’t dodging?
It’s bad, he’s trying to attack the three of us.
Farting like thunder.
Thunder Flame of Luo San Pao.
Do you wish to die?
It’s soul bone. This isn’t Dugu Bo’s soul-ring skill.
It’s an additional ability by soul bone,
and it is about the head.
Farting like thunder. Blasting Luo San Pao.
What skill is this?
It can turn my power into stones?
This is the Medusa Gaze.
Then his soul bone should be the top
among snake-type soul beasts.
His soul bone is only produced
by the queen of snake, Medusa.
It must be fallen from one of the
Decade Millennium Medusa.
You were lucky to dodge it,
but will luck favour you again?
Medusa Gaze is too strong.
Once he’s being hit, San Pao will be in danger.
One of the strongest strike by Golden Dragon,
Sacred Dragon True Form!
Medusa Gaze!
What? It is devouring the Medusa Gaze?
The eighth soul skill,
Time Freeze.
Break!
You all are great.
This is the most extraordinary
Martial Soul Fusion Skill I’ve seen.
Too bad, you all are still weak.
Break!
Just one attack, and I’ve used up my soul power.
Recover!
So what? You win at last. Just kill us.
It would be easy to kill you.
Wait. Dugu Bo, Tang San is my disciple.
This has nothing to do with them.
Let them go, I’ll stay.
Leave this between only you and me.
Do you really think you can bargain now?
Senior Dugu, indeed we don’t.
But, did you realize
what our Martial Souls are?
Xiao Gang and I come from
the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe.
Yes, we might not worth to be your opponent.
However, do you dare to offend our tribe?
Er Long, stop.
You’re from the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe?
Good, that’s great.
Even if I can’t defeat the dragon from your tribe,
but when I kill all of you,
your family won’t have any proof to accuse me.
It’s a piece of cake for me
to get rid of your bodies.
[Next Episode]
As a disciple in Tang Clan,
if I can’t even handle the poison,
I don’t deserve to be in the clan.
If I drink his blood, maybe...
Time’s up.
If you fail my test, I’ll still kill you.
Just right, I can kill them all and save my trip.
How dare you, Dugu Bo?
Tang San.