♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Do you want to discuss it?
Yes, I’m here.
Are you convinced?
What are you doing?
Isn’t this a friendly fight?
Hit your right shoulder.
Left calf, right calf.
How dare you hit me with stone!
You lose this time.
Come again!
You still want?
All right.
Come again!
Master, where can we find soul beasts?
This is for you.
Thank you.
I’ve been using this belt for thirty years
but I never gave it a name.
You give it a name.
I’ll call it Twenty-Four Moonlight Bridges.
Not everyone can enter the Soul Hunting Forest.
Only soul master who receives warrant
from Martial Soul Hall...
can enter the forest and hunt for soul beasts.
From now on,
don’t leave my side, not even a single step.
Yes.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 7]
Come out,
Little San, this is my Martial Soul.
Luo San Pao.
You can call it Luo San Pao.
You can also call it San Pao.
Master, this is your Martial Soul?
Isn’t the usual expression of
Martial Soul possession?
Why is it...
Because my Martial Soul
is a Mutated Martial Soul.
Do you remember
the Mutated Martial Soul I told you?
San Pao is the one.
But its mutation is towards a bad direction.
When it just awakened,
my soul power was only at half rank.
Otherwise, it wouldn’t be like this.
No matter how hard I try,
my soul power would never exceed Level 30.
After all, I can only study Martial Soul in theory.
Master is so persistent on Martial Soul
but San Pao...
Master, I’m sorry for mentioning your sadness.
It’s all right. I’m used to it.
Let me introduce San Pao to you.
It was called San Pao...
because of the sound it produces.
Its attack can only be launched three times.
San Pao. Lead the road.
It’s just a ten-year-old tabby cat.
San Pao. Don’t disturb it.
This is a ten-year-old solitary bamboo
which features toughness.
Its attack is weak but it’s very defensive.
It suits your Blue Silver Plant.
Then...
But, its age is still too short.
Let’s continue to look.
If there is no other choice.
How can I identify its age?
Mainly, you have to observe
the color of them when they attack.
The color of soul beasts is the same
as their soul ring when they attack.
Ten-year soul beasts have white soul power.
A hundred-year one will be yellow.
So on and so forth.
However,
although 100-year and 900-year
have same soul ring color,
the additional attributes gap is huge.
According to my studies,
the acceptable limit of the first
soul ring should be 423 years.
Within this area,
I hope that your first soul ring can
get to this limit as close as possible.
This is a required course
for every outstanding soul master.
Yes, Master.
Only that,
you can use power of
the soul ring better in the future.
Do you know why I let you sprinkle the powder?
It’s to mask our odor and get rid of
the snakes, worms, rats and ants.
That’s right. That’s snake repellent.
In the Soul Beast Forest, try not to use fire.
Although most of the beasts and
soul beasts are afraid of fire,
there are also some huge
soul beasts that like fire.
If we meet them,
unless your soul power is huge enough,
or you’ll surely die.
It is Ghost Wolf.
Little San, stay here and don’t move.
How dare a pack of Level 10 wolves
come to disturb!
San Pao!
Farting like thunder. Blasting Luo San Pao!
Wolves and dogs have similar body structures.
They are said to have a bronze head,
steel bone and weak waist.
Their waists are the weak point.
Look. The soul rings are going to appear soon.
Like this.
Draw the soul rings to yourself
using the soul power.
Then, start meditating to absorb
the energy of the soul rings.
My soul power now is unable to be advanced.
So, I can’t absorb it.
The soul rings will fade away in two hours.
Little San, give me two radishes.
San Pao can reduce my soul power
consumption by eating.
It’s because it can only launch three attacks.
So, it has to replenish after every attack.
Does San Pao only eat radish?
You saw it too. San Pao’s attack is farting.
It’s very rare that any other food
can beat radish in inducing fart.
With two radishes,
after one hour,
San Pao can recover one attack
that has been launched.
This works too?
To own a Martial Soul that attacks by farting.
Master is an arrogant person. He...
There’s poison.
Master, it’s there!
It’s Datura Snake.
Why could this kind of soul beast
appear outside of the forest?
Hopefully its age is not too old.
It’ll be difficult if it ages
more than 100 years.
It doesn’t attack...
because it is waiting for the timing.
Master, what are we going to do?
Datura Snake’s venom is very toxic.
It not only has paralytic effect
but also damages the nerve system.
It is one of the most terrifying beings
of the poisonous soul beasts.
Moreover, it’s incredibly fast.
Its body is also extremely tough.
It’s hard to hurt it with an ordinary sword.
Only its mouth and eyes are the weakness.
But, it always protects these two parts very well.
Stay behind me.
[Soul Land]
I am teaching you a theory now.
When there are more rings,
there are more bones. Attack with power.
When there are fewer rings,
there are fewer bones. Run away.
I’ll explain about soul bone next time.
If your soul rings are more than your opponent’s,
then you can defeat your opponent
with your soul skill and soul power.
If fewer, just run without hesitation.
Farting like thunder. Blasting Luo San Pao!
Run!
Before Datura Snake evolves
up to thousand years,
it will grow 1 centimeter long every year.
This Datura Snake is already 4 meters long.
It’s been nearly 400 years.
This snake is just unharmed.
Farting like smoke. Hypnosis Luo San Pao!
Most beasts like the Datura Snake are impatient.
Let’s hang on there.
It will give up very soon.
San Pao. Stop it!
Come back, San Pao!
Little San, I’ll stop it later.
You find a chance to escape.
Good tactic!
Little San!
This snake’s defense...
Oh, no! What if Master goes deep...
Little San, how are you?
Master, it’s so scary. Where’s the snake?
Why did you let go of your hands just now?
Do you know how dangerous it is?
Luckily, Master didn’t realize it.
It slipped all of a sudden.
Master. I simply waved the stiletto
you gave me just now.
I think I stabbed the snake.
You may have stabbed on its weakness.
Let’s wait for a while.
Snake-type soul beasts have tenacious vitality.
It won’t die so easily.
That was close.
I have to get more hidden weapons
as soon as possible.
Little San, it’s great.
You finally got your soul ring.
It’s great, Little San.
Master, what did you say?
You aren’t talking about this snake, are you?
Yes. It is.
This snake is nearly 400 years old.
It’s about the limit for a soul master
to absorb the first soul ring.
Due to your inborn soul power,
it’s not a problem to absorb it.
But, Master,
my Martial Soul is a plant. Wouldn’t it conflict?
It isn’t a must to absorb a plant soul
beast’s ring for a plant Martial Soul.
It isn’t necessarily beast Martial Soul
can’t absorbs plant soul ring.
Under certain circumstances,
both of them are mutually absorbable.
A few years back, I’ve mentioned...
one of the ten core competitiveness
martial soul mimicry theories.
I’ve told you before.
One of the great advantages of Blue
Silver Plant is its non-exclusiveness.
As it is too weak,
It doesn’t reject the additional
attributes on any soul ring.
It will only integrate passively.
Do you remember what kind of soul rings
are we looking for?
With additional toughness
and preferably toxic.
That’s right. Datura Snake has
these two characteristics.
Regardless of an ordinary soul master...
or the people from the Martial Soul Hall,
they despise and don’t believe...
my ten core competitiveness theories.
No soul masters absorb different kinds
of soul rings to strengthen himself.
Little San, are you willing to try it?
Although I have absolute certainty
in my theory,
no one has tried it before.
Practice is the sole criterion
for testing the truth.
The ten core competitiveness that I’ve proposed...
is only a theory but not a truth...
because no one is willing to practice it.
Master.
Let me be the one who practices it.
I believe you.
Little San, let us start.
Sit cross-legged. Concentrate on Martial Soul.
Come on, my first soul ring.
You will decide if I can practice
Tang Clan’s peerless talent.
You also decide if I can pass on Master’s hope.
No matter how the power of the soul ring
pounds on your body,
you must stay awake.
So hot. What a strong power.
Is this the inner sight realm?
I did it.
The first bottleneck of Xuan Tian Strike
is finally broken.
Master!
What happened?
Poison!
[Next Episode]
Boss Xiao, are you afraid?
Who do you think I am?
Level 11 one-ring tool soul master.
I can attack anywhere within 50 metres.
A Century Soul Ring?