♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Fourth soul skill, Fire Dance Dazzling Sun!
The victory is ours.
Too bad.
My Blue Silver Plant...
is immune to fire.
Blue Silver Cage!
As long as you can defeat Tang San,
I will agree to be with you.
This round is against Cang Hui School.
Grandmaster, please let me join it.
Have you found Teacher Shi Nian?
Little San, you’ve shown too many abilities.
Displaying too much is not advisable.
Master, why not let me join for this round?
No way. Your ability is very special.
Plus the grudge they have with our Shrek School,
This time,
let’s end
our grudges with Cang Hui School.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 77]
Are you from Shrek School?
Yes. Who are you?
I am Feng Xiao Tian. We’ll meet in a match later.
You must do your best to destroy Cang Hui School.
Well, of course.
You must be Tang San.
You mustn’t lose before fighting our school.
I can’t let anyone else
defeat Shrek School before me.
Otherwise,  Huo Wu might be a girlfriend
of someone else.
Something’s wrong with him.
After identification, he’s crazy.
The twelfth match is about to start.
Participants from Shrek School
and Cang Hui School,
please be prepared.
Welcome to the twelfth preliminary.
I am your old friend, Dou Dou.
As we all know, Shrek School has
won for eleventh round straight.
However, Cang Hui School has only
got 8 wins for 11 games.
This group of jerks!
There may be no suspense for this game.
But let’s anticipate
how long Cang Hui School can hold on.
Next,
let’s welcome the participants
from both teams with applause!
No matter what’s the price to pay,
we must kill them.
The formation of Cang Hui School is quite weird.
Such a formation hasn’t been shown,
since the preliminaries started.
Shrek’s formation hasn’t changed.
Keen Attack Branch’s Jing Ling who’s in
charge of fast attack hauled to the end.
Are they ready to make a quick battle?
Today, Shrek sends Soul Sect,
Zhu Zhu Qing
to replace soul master
Jiang Zhu of Support Branch.
Does it mean Cang Hui is more powerful
than Chi Huo School in their mind?
Tang San, we are at feud with each other.
Next, let’s have a look
at the information of both teams.
[Shrek] vs. [Cang Hui]
[Dai Mu Bai] vs. [Zhang Jing Yang]
[Tai Long] vs. [Dong He Guang]
[Xiao Wu] vs. [Zhu Zi Zhang]
[Huang Yuan] vs. [Lin Zi Ping]
[Jing Ling] vs. [Liu Hao Si]
[Zhu Zhu Qing] vs. [Lian Xue Feng]
[Tang San] vs. [Shen Xin Shui]
I announce the twelfth preliminary
between Shrek School and Cang Hui School
begins.
You come over.
Too arrogant. Let’s go!
Don’t be reckless.
Listen to my order. Stay focus.
Master San, just let us go and fight to end this.
Today, four players of Cang Hui School
make their debut.
That’s a big difference from Master’s list.
Good. It seems that Little San also realized it.
What did he realize, Grandmaster?
The participants that Cang Hui School sent
are mostly new here.
This means two possibilities.
First, Cang Hui School is preparing to give up.
Second, they have hidden their strength
in the previous matches.
They purposely retained their strength
until the battle with Shrek School.
So, you from Shrek School
are a bunch of cowards.
You!
Don’t act rashly.
What happened?
Why hasn’t Shrek School attacked?
Theoretically, they should pre-empt
and subdue quickly.
Is Shrek School afraid of Cang Hui School?
They can still calm down
under this situation. Good.
The most taboo in a battle
is to take the enemy lightly.
In your opinion,
why aren’t they starting yet?
Tang San must have realized
something is not right.
So, he didn’t let his teammates start.
He has a calm mind.
He doesn’t seem like only have...
Awful. They’re still not starting
even I provoked.
You are really steady.
But all tactics and skills are futile,
when facing absolute strength.
Finally, you’re not pretending anymore.
Seven Shura Fantasy!
It’s Seven In One Martial Soul Fusion Skill!
Seven In One Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
What a terrify power.
No. It’s not Seven In One
Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
No one can complete
Seven In One Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
This could be only the use of a fusion skill.
This year’s Advanced Soul Master School Contest
has really opened my eyes.
You are the first ones who experience
our Seven Shura Fantasy.
You’ll also be the ones who die
from Seven Shura Fantasy.
Close your eyes.
What an amazing power.
Both teams have disappeared!
Cang Hui!
Kids!
No. We must stop this match immediately.
The kids will die.
Calm down. That is not Seven In One
Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
It’s a Seven In One Fusion Skill.
Aren’t they the same?
One is the sublimation of skill
by fusing the Martial Soul.
One is fusion skill activated by the
assistance of respective soul skills.
They’re different.
Can Little San and the others block it?
Shrek. Today you will be dead!
Shrek.
Reincarnate endlessly in this painful abyss!
[Soul Land]
Brother.
Brother San.
Little San.
Master San!
Everyone. No!
Why are you talking nonsense?
This is deadly.
He’s just joking. He treats Little San as his son.
How can he not worry, if anything happens?
You...
Didn’t you see how Cang Hui control it?
Purple Demon Eye.
Comparing with Shi Nian’s nightmare,
you’re still far behind.
You really met Teacher Shi Nian.
Seems like it’s right.
That thing is with you, right?
I got it this easily.
Do you want to kill me? Aren’t you
afraid of the punishment of the contest?
In the Shura Fantasy,
your death will only be an accident
under my tactic.
Shrek. Goodbye.
Impossible.
Is this the motto of Cang Hui School?
How did you do it?
Fantasy is a lie to the vision.
If the lie is seen,
how would the person who lied be punished?
My body can’t move.
Everyone...
Students of Cang Hui School fell down.
Tang San...
What happened?
Little San is injured.
So, this is it.
What actually happened?
This is the most tragic match,
since the preliminary started.
Shrek School won!
Shrek!
Little San, how do you feel?
Teacher Qin, don’t worry. We’re just pretending.
Little San, you’re too cruel.
I’m afraid seven of them are going to be disabled.
They’re destined not to be our friends.
The fantasy may be real the next time.
Brother San, I support you.
Being kind to the enemy is cruel to yourself.
Little San, come here.
Students from Cang Hui School
are mentally injured.
The medical experts have confirmed that
they can’t recover.
Xiao Gang has taken cover
with the other members who participated.
You have to accept an interrogation
as the only person
who stood on the stage.
If the investigators ask
what happened on the field,
what shall I do?
Don’t know.
What?
You really don’t know anything, right?
Just like the audience.
You didn’t see what happened...
Dean, you’re saying that
Boss Fu is the expert in this field.
Don’t let me down.
Little San, did you get it?
Yes. I got it.
Okay. Regulate your breath in the lounge first.
I will ask someone to call you
when needed.
Okay.
Dean. The organizing committees are here.
This is fast. Who are they?
Ning Feng Zhi and Salas.
The Martial Soul Hall and imperial family
are involved in the investigation.
Let’s meet them.
Dean Frander.
You should know our purpose being here.
Shrek School has badly injured students
from Cang Hui School in a match.
How can you explain?
What? Students from Cang Hui School
have become stupid?
Lord, students from Cang Hui School
are badly injured.
Aren’t students from Shrek school
badly injured too?
Please don’t be unfair.
Don’t act silly!
For this kind of killing behaviour,
it’s not allowed in the contest.
Call the students
who participated in the contest!
I want to interrogate every one of them.
[Next Episode]
Starts.
It’s said that Tian Shui School has all girls.
How can we fight?
Anyways, we just pray not to meet them so soon.
Dai Mu Bai from Shrek School is so handsome!
Seems like Little San has met his opponent.
Boss Dai and others, I’m sorry.
How can you jump to conclusions?
Salas!
You asked for it.
How dare you still have contact with that woman!
Are they looking down on us?
I announce
Shrek School is removed from this contest!