♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Brother!
Little San!
Thank you, Xiao Wu.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 67]
Little San, what is your fourth soul skill?
Show us.
It’s nothing special.
It’s similar to the skill
used by the Burrow Demon Spider.
But there are some changes.
Do you want to see it?
Of course.
You are the first one to get
the Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
Come on, show us.
The Blue Silver Plant turned black.
- When did you get this?
There was no energy surge
when it was triggered.
This is my fourth soul skill.
This is the Spider Web Cage
stemmed from the Burrow Demon Spider.
This cage is formed by Blue Silver Plant.
So I named it the Blue Silver Cage.
It doesn’t seem very sturdy.
It’s not even as strong as
Constraint of Spider Web.
Brother San, this is all your
Decade Millennium Soul Skill can do?
Is that so?
Crowd-control skill?
But only soul master from Controlling
Branch above Level 50 can do this!
This is terrifying.
A mere cage may be nothing,
but it takes time to break it.
And during that time,
the partners of Controlling Branch
soul master can do many things.
Brother San, can you combine
this skill with my move?
Of course.
Blue Silver Cage is a pre-emptive skill,
your Phoenix Strike restrains opponents
during the battle.
If we can use it optimally,
our attacks will be maximized
to their greatest potentials.
I think the champion mission given to
them might have been too easy.
Their strengths are off the charts.
Cut it off. Are you amazed by their power
or are you applauding yourself?
Shut it, Er Long.
I just helped you and now you are mocking me?
I shouldn’t have treated you so well.
We need to head back to Shrek School soon.
The Continental Competition
is only five days from now.
Get some rest once you got back.
Tomorrow morning,
we will gather in the forest
at the back of the school building.
Is that clear?
Yes!
What is taking the teachers so long?
Where is everyone?
These four over here are your
substitute teammates.
You may introduce yourselves now.
War soul master at Level 35
from Storm Attack Branch, Huang Yuan.
from Keen Attack Branch, Jing Ling.
Tool soul master at Level 35
from Healing Branch, Jiang Zhu.
I don’t have to introduce myself,
you all know who I am.
They are the elite students
mentored by Er Long.
If it wasn’t for the competition,
they would have graduated long ago
with their strength.
I think the substitutes need to work
on teamwork with us.
Substitute members are compulsory
to form a team for the competition.
The competition will be difficult
far beyond your imagination.
With only seven members,
whether it’s stamina or
skill combinations,
you will fall short in face of obstacles
and the number of opponents.
Everyone, have a seat.
In a few days,
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament will begin.
I will explain the rules to you now.
Take this seriously.
The rules can be limitations,
but also be your advantages.
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament,
which is organized by royalties of
Tian Dou and Xin Luo
and the Martial Soul Hall,
is the greatest
Martial Soul competition of all time.
The strengths of the participants
are second only to the elite members
of Martial Soul Hall qualifiers.
As per the rules,
the participants from each school
must be under the age of 25 years old.
Each round will be participated
by seven members.
No death is allowed during the competition.
Grandmaster, that doesn’t sound fair.
What if we killed someone from a misfire?
You are certainly right about this.
But you must understand,
the two empires hold this competition
to hand-pick the best of the best.
It’s never meant to be a fight to death.
During the competition,
you cannot consume any item not made by
the Food or Healing Branches.
Any weapon other than the Martial Soul
is not allowed either.
Which means traps and hidden weapons
can’t be used.
You must bear these rules in mind.
Breaking them will only mean disqualification.
[Soul Land]
I will explain the tournament system.
These two rocks represent the two empires.
This rock here represents the Martial Soul Hall.
All teams will be divided into
the main and secondary teams.
The main teams will represent
the two great empires.
They will advance into the finals directly.
The secondary team will join
the preliminary with other soul masters.
Tian Dou has six main regions
for the preliminary.
There are more than one hundred teams.
All will be eliminated
except for 15 soul masters.
For the region of Tian Dou,
there are too many advanced schools,
only five soul masters can advance.
Preliminary and qualifying rounds
are not the same.
You battle as a team in preliminary rounds.
But seven soul masters will be bid
against each other in qualifying rounds.
The 33 teams in the finals will
battle in draw elimination rounds.
Grandmaster, there are two seed teams.
30 teams will advance through
the qualifying rounds.
There should be 32 teams.
Where is the other team?
I forgot to mention.
There are three seed teams, not two.
The third team is from the Martial Soul Hall.
They’re much stronger
than the Emperor Battle Team.
The finals will be elimination rounds.
The first round will be a bye
for the three seed teams.
In the second round, the two best
qualifier teams will be in a bye.
The same rules apply to
the third round as well.
After the third round,
only the best six teams will remain.
In the fourth round, each team will
draw lot to determine the opponents.
The top three will be battle in
both team fight and eliminations.
As long as you win every round,
none of these will matter.
Only three of you will battle
in the preliminary rounds.
Rong Rong won’t battle,
I have special training for her.
Only three of us can battle?
If you expose your strength
too early in the competition,
the path afterwards will be difficult.
I understand, Master.
You will be in charge of the strategies.
Tai Long and Huang Yuan are both
from Storm Attack Branch.
They can be our vanguard.
Jing Ling is from the Keen Attack Branch.
His Skeleton Martial Soul
will be unpredictable to the opponents.
Jiang Zhu’s healing sceptre is not
as powerful as Little Ao’s or Rong Rong’s.
But she is one of the best in Support Branch.
Tai Long and his friends haven’t
reached Level 40 yet,
but they are the best candidates to
hide our true strength.
That’s why they were picked by Grandmaster.
Who will battle tomorrow?
You, Xiao Wu and me.
Little devils.
For the Advanced Soul Master School Contest,
I designed a new batch of cool
and dashing uniforms for you.
I hope it’s not the last one we had.
We will be the champions!
We need to be strong and cool looking!
Could it be...
This is even more hideous
than our previous outfits.
So? Aren’t they cool?
This uniform is so ugly, it’s like...
Dean, don’t you have a sense of aesthetic?
And the product placement is so embarrassing.
That is for our school budget.
But...
I have other works to do.
Try out your new uniforms.
Brother San, I don’t want to wear it.
Master...
Consider this an ordeal for your minds.
No!
Wow! So many people!
What school are they from?
Did they come out from
the sewer or something?
There is even an advertisement on their backs!
Nothing is too weird nowadays!
Shut it, they are soul masters.
But they do have a fat guy with them.
He is round like a ball.
I don’t want to wear this uniform anymore.
This is ruining my image!
We’ll talk to the Dean about this later.
At least, we can remove the advertisement.
Why do you have to choose
a place so remote out here?
Pull yourselves together.
We are here to be the champion!
Champion?
Even losers want to be a champion?
Did you just call us losers?
Who else are wearing that ugly green uniforms?
I will show you who is the real losers here!
Where do these mutts come from?
Did you just call us mutts?
Aren’t them from the  Cang Hui School?
Why are they picking a fight on us?
What do you think you’re doing?
[Next Episode]
It’s starting, let’s go.
His Majesty of Tian Dou Empire
will officiate the competition!
So he is Emperor Xue Ye?
Look up there!
I know a team,
they might win this competition for the empire.
The Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament,
will begin its first-round battle!