♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I haven’t been here for a while.
Everything is rusted.
An artisan doesn’t create
excellent tools with excellent iron.
Instead, they use common iron
to create excellent tools.
Brother San, what great things
did you make this time?
I call it Flying Godly Claw.
As the Dean,
I must be responsible for every student.
Actually, it’s good to be tired.
So that I have an excuse for you
to massage my legs.
You haven’t fought for two months.
Tonight, you shall exercise
in the Silves Soul Arena.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 44]
Ladies and gentlemen.
Coming right up, our 9th group battle today.
It’s also the most eye-catching battle
of this month.
Xiu Ren versus Luo Ji.
Why?
Sorry, fellow respected soul masters.
We don’t have a Gold Soul Battle Team
at Level 30 here.
I’m afraid you can’t join the group battle tonight.
Silver Soul Battle Team can also do.
Didn’t you see that
only one of them achieved
the gold soul level?
The battle you mentioned is obviously unfair.
I’m sure you understand.
Someone’s plan is going out of the window.
Is there no other way?
If you challenge those higher ranks,
the level of soul badge wouldn’t matter.
That means
you may choose to challenge
any soul battle team at Level 40.
Level 40?
Forget about it then.
No, I think that’s okay.
Are you kidding?
You want them to challenge
a soul battle team at Level 40?
Are you sending them to death?
You said we may choose any opponent we like.
Right?
Is there a team at Level 40,
which is especially cruel?
Those who injure or kill
their opponents will be the best.
The more formidable, the better.
What?
Xiao Gang, are you insane?
Don’t worry. I know what I’m doing.
Is there such a team?
Yes, the Fiend Battle Team.
It’s the lethal weapon
among soul battle teams at Level 40.
After they achieved the silver soul level,
they won 31 fights out of 46.
They’ve killed 63 opponents,
injured 98 opponents.
Okay. We shall challenge this Fiend Battle Team.
Grandmaster.
But, is this good?
Frander, this is an experience to toughen them.
They’ll meet such situation one day.
When they face it today,
at least we’re here to guide them.
It’s better than having them
endure it alone in the future.
Alright. I hope you’re right.
Fellow respected soul masters,
this way, please.
Get some rest and be ready.
We’ll have a look around.
It’s especially happening today.
Who are they betting on?
They’re betting on Fiend Battle Team.
What? It’s them?
They’re insane, cruel and wicked.
Aren’t they boycotted by all
silver soul battle teams at Level 40?
This time, a team is challenging them.
They’re called Shrek Seven Devils.
I haven’t heard about them before.
They aren’t famous.
They dare to challenge Fiend Battle Team.
Shrek Seven Devils is a
Gold Soul Battle Team at Level 30.
Although they have reached the gold soul level,
according to what I found out,
there’s only one of them who has a gold soul badge.
And some of them haven’t reached
Level 30 in the team.
They’re challenging a higher rank.
But the gap is...
Shrek Seven Devils will surely lose.
No, they’ll surely die.
That’s right.
The captain, Meng Li, upholds that
the brutal are afraid of the fierce,
the fierce are afraid of the desperate.
He instilled his motto to his entire team.
How many soul masters at Level 40
lost their lives to their insane attack?
Even if they lose,
they’ll let their opponents become
disabled or even dead.
Those who want to bet on Fiend Battle Team,
get in line,
lest you can’t make it before the soul battle.
I’ll bet 30,000 gold soul coins
on Shrek Seven Devils.
What? How much?
I’ll bet 30,000 gold soul coins
on Shrek Seven Devils.
Is it not allowed?
Are you sure?
I’m sure. Just swipe the card.
I’ll bet 10,000 gold soul coins
on Shrek Seven Devils.
Things are especially odd recently.
The result is obvious.
Yet more than one simpletons
gifted us their money.
Brother, did you see it correctly?
Shrek Seven Devils and Fiend Battle Team
have such a huge gap
between their soul power and soul rings.
Yet you’re still betting on them?
You don’t know this.
I’m a businessman.
I have businesses in Barak Kingdom
and Silves Kingdom.
Not long ago, in Suo Tuo City of Barak Kingdom,
I saw an extremely splendid group soul battle.
The winner was Shrek Seven Devils.
Don’t look down upon them
because their levels are low
and soul rings are few.
Brother, if you believe me, bet it as I do.
You’ll surely gain profit.
I see. I believe you.
I didn’t expect to meet their fan
in the capital of Silves Kingdom.
But he’s supporting them blindly.
If there’s no special reason,
even if little monsters have
outstanding Martial Souls,
they can’t defeat an opponent
that is much more powerful than them.
The reason I made this decision
is to help Frander,
and to let you test your weapon.
In this group soul battle,
I permit you to use the hidden weapons
that Tang San made.
But, Master, this is...
The team I chose is very cruel and fierce.
They have plenty of debts of blood.
You don’t have to feel bad in the fight.
The opponents are stronger than you.
Remember, if you want to defeat them,
you have to take them by surprise.
Keep being on their heels.
Don’t give them a chance to breathe.
Little San, do you understand?
Master, I understand.
Alright. You shall arrange the fighting tactic.
[Soul Land]
They’re cruel and fierce.
Don’t have mercy on them.
Settle it as fast as possible, get it?
If anything unexpected happens,
jump off the stage immediately,
surrender yourselves, and don’t get injured.
Remember that.
Fiend Battle Team is marching in now.
Silver Soul Battle Team at Level 40.
The team who’s challenging them
is Shrek Seven Devils.
Gold Soul Battle Team at Level 30.
Both sides release their Martial Souls.
Boss Dai, if they charge forward,
with Rong Rong’s help,
can you hold on?
No.
Curse you.
How can you be lack of confidence
in Little San’s precious tools?
I’m not. I mean just in case.
To think I’m a youth with
bright future, good look, elegance...
Xiao Gang.
Won’t these soul masters with soul skills
at Level 40 resist Little San’s hidden weapons?
They’re all from Storm Attack Branch.
Their defence capability
is second to the Defence Branch.
They can resist it.
What did you say?
I’ve studied the attacking power
of Godly Zhuge Crossbow.
Generally,
the first two soul skills of
Storm Attack Branch can’t resist it.
But when they initiate their third soul skill,
they can basically fight it.
If it’s the fourth soul skill,
there will be no problem at all.
Then why did you send them
to the soul battle?
Do you want them to die?
So what if the third and
fourth soul skill can resist it?
It doesn’t affect Tang San
and his teammates to win,
Tang San once told me,
the key to the hidden weapon is being secretive.
If it were you,
when you’re facing an opponent,
who’s far worse than you,
will you consume your energy of third
or even fourth soul skill at the start?
Of course,
such a surprise attack mode can’t be repeated.
But Tang San’s hidden weapon is being
used for the first time at the arena.
When the opponents are
using first and second soul skills,
they can’t resist it.
Be ready.
Tear them apart.
Look at how the girl is shivering.
Look at them.
Shrek Seven Devils challenges
Fiend Battle Team.
Begin.
Release.
I’m going to check Zhu Qing.
Can you announce the result
of this soul battle now?
Group soul battle,
Shrek Seven Devils versus Fiend Battle Team.
Fiend Battle Team lost.
Shrek Seven Devils successfully
challenged them.
I’ve figured it out. 90% of the money
shall be used to help the families
of the victims of Fiend Battle Team.
The rest shall be used
as the backup money of our school.
What do you think?
Little San, just now we...
Master said they’re a group of ruffians.
But, we...
Are we wrong?
As a soul master,
this is a problem that you’ll face sooner or later.
Those in front of you
are the obstacles that you must overcome.
To face it now is better than
on the battlefield in the future.
Or else, the one who falls can be you.
Any strong soul masters
have to go through this.
You have to pay a price for any victory in a battle.
Battles of soul masters are not games.
Fiend Battle Team used soul battle as an excuse
to do violent and illegal things.
Alone in silver soul level battles,
they have killed 64 people,
injured 98 people.
They weren’t punished for the crime,
instead, they earned their income.
They even got the attention and
invitation of some stronger force.
Fiend Battle Team is heavily injured
by hidden weapons.
Although they’re alive,
they have lost their power to fight.
They can’t do any crime anymore.
This is a good thing to fellow soul masters.
If you don’t want to be
the centre of attraction,
you’d better hide your masks
and leave with us right away.
Xiao Gang, is it your plan
to punish the Fiend Battle Team?
So you chose this notorious team
as their opponent?
Yes, indeed.
This is another test for the kids.
Or better said, a training.
At least, if such a thing happens in the future,
they’ll be mentally prepared.
However, they’re still young.
Isn’t this too much for them?
These kids are smart.
They won’t get themselves into a dead end.
I’ve played the role of a bad man.
Then Frander played the role
of a good man to comfort them.
They won’t feel so bad anymore.
I always have a positive image in their hearts.
Of course, I’m the good man.
Wu Ji, don’t worry.
I vomited a lot at my first time too.
This is a stage of life.
It’s okay they went through that earlier.
One sheep, two sheep, three sheep, five sheep...
One dumpling, two dumpings,
three dumplings, four dumplings...
Little monsters, today is a new start.
Our destination is
Tian Dou Imperial School. Let’s go.
[Next Episode]
Here we are.
This is the board of education
of Tian Dou Imperial School.
Get lost.
Tian Dou Imperial School is not a refugee camp.
I heard from Qin Ming,
these kids defeated Emperor Team
from our school.
There’s an excellent soul master
of Controlling Branch.
Who could that be?
That’s enough.