♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I announce Shrek School won!
Well done!
In this match, Captain and Zhu Qing
have won their pride.
Yu Tian Heng, don’t make me look down on you.
if Martial Soul Hall hasn’t come in the way,
this world would have belonged to us.
If you have trouble in the future and you need me,
just one word, I’ll be there.
Today.
Tian Dou Imperial School
and Martial Soul Hall School,
will fight to tell who’s better.
Let’s invite both the teams.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 100]
Just like the last match of Shrek School,
the level doesn’t mean everything.
Can Tian Dou Imperial School strike back?
Are you dumbfounded, kid?
I think there’s no need for this match to go on.
Three of us are sufficient to defeat seven of you.
Just surrender.
How would we know it’s impossible
without trying?
Tian Dou Imperial School remains
confident when facing powerful opponents.
Then, I announce.
Martial Soul Hall School
versus Tian Dou Imperial School,
begin!
Fourth soul skill!
Don’t look into her eyes!
Will you be fine if just avoiding my eyes?
Other people usually call me Sky Fox.
I can’t move. How could this happen?
Her Charm skill
not only launches through her eyes.
What is that?
Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
This is the Martial Soul Fusion Skill
of two, Genie Mesmerise.
The main control has
reduced everyone’s sense,
soul power and action by 50%
within its control area.
The red light is too bright.
I can’t see things clearly.
I think we can’t see how they attack today.
They don’t want the other opponents
to see their strength.
Purple Demon Eye.
It’s Osler. He was just dumped out.
There wasn’t any sound of a fight inside.
There’s also no cry of pain.
It seems that Oslo has fainted
as soon as the opponent attacked.
When Martial Soul Hall School
faces another powerful team,
they have simply defeated
four of their opponents
by just using Martial Soul
Fusion Skill of two persons.
Another person has been dumped.
Now, on the field,
Tian Dou Imperial School has only
Yu Tian Heng and Dugu Yan left.
How long can they persist?
Venom? The efficacy will also
be reduced in our territory.
Dugu Yan.
Your venom doesn’t work on me at all.
See you.
Yan Yan!
I’ll spare your life because of your family.
Never seen this before.
Martial Soul Hall School is the greatest
school team in this Elite Tournament.
Martial Soul Hall School has won
in this game.
This is stunning.
By seeing it today, I just realized how
scary is Martial Soul Hall School.
No doubt.
They must be the champion.
In the previous game,
Shrek School’s performance
was quite eye-catching.
But comparing with Martial Soul Hall School
Do you see it? This is called strength.
Once Genie Mesmerize is out,
the strength of Shrek School is nothing.
Exactly!
I didn’t expect that Martial Soul Hall School
is much more powerful than expected.
After today’s battle, they’re indeed daunting.
No matter when you meet them,
first of all, you mustn’t lose confidence.
After watching today’s battle, I have a thought.
The greatest among them
is the Martial Soul Fusion Skill
of Xie Yue and Hu Liena.
But this also shows their weakness.
What?
Three of their greatest members
seldom cooperate with the other four.
There must be no tacit agreement
between them like Little Devils.
Exactly. In the previous matches,
the three other people didn’t play at all.
If the next match, which is the fourth round,
we are lucky enough
and didn’t fight them,
I will do my best to follow the match of
Martial Soul Hall School
and continue to research.
Okay.
[Fourth-round grand final of Continental
Soul Master Elite Tournament]
[Soul Land]
In the sortition for the fourth round,
three teams with significantly better strength,
Martial Soul Hall School, Shen Feng School,
and Shrek School
didn’t draw the other two schools.
There shouldn’t be a problem for us
to advance to the top three.
This year, Continental Soul Master Elite Tournament
the fourth round of the grand final has ended.
Congratulations to Martial Soul Hall School,
Shen Feng School,
and Shrek School
for advancing to the top three!
Let us anticipate the upcoming matches
for the top three at The Sacred Temple.
I gave him a name.
You have to remember it forever. This is our child.
Go with them! Don’t Sacrifice!
Master. You couldn’t sleep either.
Little San.
Tomorrow will be the match for the top three.
It’s said that the Pope
will watch the match tomorrow as well.
Don’t worry. Focus on the match.
I’ll be your backup on other issues.
This competition is no small matter.
The schools that lost couldn’t watch the matches.
After entering this door,
I can only stay at the rest area.
You guys do your best.
Yes.
The arrival of Her Holiness.
Your Holiness!
Greetings to Your Holiness.
Only Father and Master can make me kneel.
Pope, so what?
The second youngster from the left is Tang San.
What a strong sight. Purple Demon Eye.
My soul seems to be striped.
How dare you be rude to the Pope?
So, you’re Grandmaster’s disciple, Tang San?
Yes, Your Holiness.
Good. You have the style
of your teacher in the past.
I dare not compare with my teacher.
Stand up.
I see hope on you.
At the Sacred Temple,
I would like to see all
your talents and strengths.
The ultimate winner
will get the best gift of Martial Soul Hall.
This brightness. It’s the soul bones!
There are three soul bones!
They’re a right arm bone,
a skull and a left leg bone.
They’re the soul bones.
It’s good to have but is not guaranteed.
There are a few Grand Soul Land Masters here.
Do you still want to get it?
These three soul bones came from
Decade Millennium Soul Beast.
They’re Spiritual Cohesion Wisdom Skull,
Burst Burning Flame Right Arm,
and Fast-Moving Chasing Left Leg!
Among them, Wisdom Skull came from
a soul beast of fifty thousand years.
It was beheaded by the former pope.
It’s the best in the soul bones.
Former pope?
Qian Xun Ji.
The soul bones produced from
the higher level soul beast,
the greater the effect.
These three soul bones are
more than ten thousand years old.
They’re considered the highest class.
Of course, except the attached soul bones.
Your attached soul bones have great attack power.
They can puncture and has poison.
They can also ignore
the terrain factor when marching.
I didn’t expect that you already have
such achievement at this young age.
Attached soul bones?
There are six types of normal soul bones.
The most valuable part is the torso,
second is the skull.
Then, followed by the right hand,
left hand, left leg and right leg.
The value of the attached soul bones
is above the six types.
It’s very rare.
Its strength and growth are extremely valuable.
In the whole system,
it’s second only to soul bones produced
by a hundred thousand years soul beast.
Soul skill of soul rings
will grow stronger along with
the soul master’s strength.
Will the soul bones grow too?
The growth of soul ring
is subject to the age limit of
the original soul beast.
Just like the Century Soul Ring,
it can never have power
beyond a hundred years.
But soul bones are different.
They not only can enhance
the soul master’s strength,
they will also evolve along with
the growth of soul master’s strength.
The earlier you get the soul bones,
the longer the time for them to evolve.
The soul master’s strength will also grow faster.
With the help of Zhi Lin,
the Great Soul Land Master,
Little San has completely fused with
Eight Spider Bone and increased in strength.
If the children can get these three soul bones,
their fighting power
will definitely increase. But...
There’s only one champion.
So these soul bones
will belong to the champion.
I hope that all of you can do your best
and win the honor.
[Next Episode]
You’re right.
This is your rights.
Sorry for asking.
Elder Yu.
Elder?
I didn’t expect that
Martial Soul Hall would play dirty tricks
at such a dominant position.
Do they really think
they can hinder us?
I didn’t get it
why Martial Soul Hall agreed on
the merger of Shen Feng and Chi Huo.
Now it turns out this is what they’ve planned.
I want a showdown between us.
I would rather give up the championship
so as to beat you.
This is...