♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Don’t need to be worried.
Your team is the strongest at this level.
We, the Seven Shrek Devils,
are Gold Soul Battle Team now.
Are you aware of your problem?
You didn’t lose to your rival,
but yourself.
Tian Heng.
If you want to be a great soul master,
set Tang San as a goal then.
Even if they’re from Shrek School,
you can still bring them to the imperial school.
Xiao Gang, thank you for helping me
draw this end to Shrek School.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 43]
I haven’t been here for a while.
Everything is rusted.
An artisan doesn’t create
excellent tools with excellent iron.
Instead, they use common iron
to create excellent tools.
No matter how common the iron is,
if it’s forged for ten thousand times,
it’ll eventually be the king of iron.
What a delight.
Toxin is the only thing I need now.
We haven’t seen Little San for a while.
I wonder how he has been recently.
Little San, you’re finally out.
Our iron man is here.
Iron man, why are you so clean today?
I came out because things are done.
Looking at the time,
there are only a few days left before we leave to
Tian Dou Imperial School.
Brother San, what great things
did you make this time?
Show us, please.
Just some hidden weapons.
But I have made something practical
for everyone.
For us?
Little San, what is this?
Is this a more powerful sleeve arrow?
I call it Flying Godly Claw.
I made it by combining a few types of metals.
Its hardness is enough
to penetrate gold and stone.
This metal claw is its main part.
When the claw is expanded, only with a light touch,
the inner springs and gears will be triggered,
so it’ll contract.
Look.
What other functions does this steel claw have?
If that’s the only function,
my tiger claw would be much better.
Of course not.
After all, it is called Flying Godly Claw.
Look, this is its third function.
The length of the steel cable is 30 meters.
Contractile power is about 150 kgs.
As long as our weight isn’t more than 150 kgs,
we can use it to climb to a certain height.
This is the best tool
for flying from house to house
and for cracking a crib.
You have to beware of your weight.
When you exceed 150 kgs,
this will be useless to you.
Little San, I have no idea what’s in your brain.
You could even figure out such a thing.
Moreover, you created it.
Brother San, you’re really powerful.
This is the essence of Tang Clan’s year-long study.
I only mastered the way of making it.
I’m able to produce so many tools,
all because of my other Martial Soul.
All metals become soft when they contact with it.
However, it costs too much soul power and energy.
As the Dean, I must be
responsible for every student.
Stop looking. Let’s go. We will come back.
Worst come to worst, I’ll come here
with you for our retirement.
Am I very old?
[Soul Land]
Little monsters, you have taken rest
for two months.
From now on, speed up to catch up.
Put me down. I can walk myself.
You’re slow.
I can’t wait to go to the next station.
Even if he wants to reduce expenses,
he shouldn’t torture old people like us.
I’m so tired.
Why are you tired?
Most weight is on me, okay?
But I had to keep making sausages for all of you.
The soul power I used is no lesser than you.
Stop whining.
I’m the most unfortunate one. I’m heavy
and slow.
I really hope I can get a flying soul skill soon.
Little San, come out for a while.
Okay.
Xiao Wu, what’s going on?
After today’s journey, my legs are sore.
Brother, would you massage my legs, please?
Okay. Over here?
Yes, here.
Rong Rong and Zhu Qing have fallen asleep.
If we keep hurrying like this tomorrow,
I can carry you if you can’t make it.
I’ll use my soul bone of Eight Spiders.
Speed shouldn’t be a problem.
No need. I can make it.
Actually, it’s good to be tired.
So that I have an excuse for you to massage my legs.
It’s comfortable, Brother.
Why are your palms warm?
How does this feel?
Very comfortable.
I think my leg isn’t sore anymore.
Alright. Another leg now.
Brother, it’ll be great
if we keep being this.
When you have a wife in the future,
will you ignore me then?
Silly girl, of course not.
No matter when, you are always my sister.
Brother, do you know you’re the best in my heart?
Rong Rong always makes fun of me,
saying we are brother and sister.
That’s right. Aren’t you my sister?
That’s not the same.
I don’t want to talk to you. You’re dull.
Alright now. Go to rest.
We have to keep going tomorrow.
Okay.
After today’s journey, my legs are sore.
Brother, would you massage my legs, please?
Okay. Over here?
Yes, here.
Rong Rong and Zhu Qing have fallen asleep.
Alright. You were eavesdropping.
We weren’t eavesdropping.
But there’s bad soundproof here.
Brother, massage my legs too, okay?
Okay, no problem. I’ll do that
with my soul bone of Eight Spiders.
I heard that some venom can be used medically.
It dredges acupoints and improves circulation.
I wonder if my soul bone
of Eight Spiders can do that.
I’ll let you try it.
No, Brother San. I’m wrong.
Go to sleep.
[Capital of Silves Kingdom]
[Silves]
You haven’t fought for two months.
Tonight, you shall exercise
in the Silves Soul Arena.
Dean.
Do we have to submit the reward
we get from the fight
to the school?
Do you think I’ll take advantage of you?
You may use the income as you like.
It has nothing to do with the school.
Mu Bai, how dare you suspect
that I have an intention?
Hurry away.
Okay, let’s go.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Coming right up, our 9th group battle today.
It’s also the most eye-catching battle
of this month.
Xiu Ren versus Luo Ji.
[Next Episode]
Okay, we’ll challenge Fiend Battle Team.
You? Are you sending them to death?
Are we wrong?
Hold on. Who are you?
You poor fellows?
They’re fierce and cruel. Don’t have mercy.
If anything unexpected happens,
surrender yourselves, and don’t get injured.
Remember that.
Shrek Seven Devils will surely lose.
No, they’ll surely die.