♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
You have to pay for you cheating.
Do you think so, Rong Rong?
Frander,
who do you think you are?
You’re just a Soul Saint!
Depart.
To the Soul Arena.
What’s a Soul Arena?
That’s a place where soul masters
engage in battles,
After registration, each participant...
will receive an iron soul badge.
Before you graduate,
I want all of you to at least get silver soul badge.
Welcome to Suo Tuo City!
Nervous,
exciting,
fair
Soul Arena!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 19]
Look, it’s a little girl!
This isn’t the place you should come.
Go home!
This muscle man seems tough,
can Xiao Wu make it?
We’ll just wait and see.
Ready, go!
Girl, go back!
You look so fragile,
I don’t wish to hurt you.
Stop your nonsense.
Xiao Wu’s first soul skill, Arched Body!
Goodbye.
Wait, what?
That little girl is great!
[Win]
Xiao Wu’s soul skills are indeed ineffective
towards strength type soul masters,
but only when their soul power
is higher than her.
Others are just a piece of cake for her.
Xiao Wu wins!
Score, one win and zero loss.
Qing Bao’s results, twenty-one wins
and fourteen losses.
Girl, you’re great!
I’ve lost.
What girl?
call me Sister Wu.
Now you know who’s more capable?
Oh, Sister Wu.
Master Wu.
Please proceed to point redemption after this.
Iron battle soul Tang San,
please enter the 15th battle stage.
Iron battle soul Zhu Zhu Qing,
Little San.
be gentle later.
It’s 1-on-1 in Soul Arena, the second round.
both are newcomers.
Soul Master Tang San,
with Blue Silver Plant,
versus
Zhu Zhu Qing, with Cat of Netherworld.
Well, the battle...
Please go all out,
I need to know my capability.
Begin!
Blue Silver Plant.
You’re going to miss the chance.
Blue Silver Plant will never catch me.
Zhu Zhu Qing has a nice figure.
Ouch.
Hmm.
Naturally.
Figure is also very good.
My little cat is in trouble now.
Speed is useless as long as she’s in the cage.
Zhu Zhu Qing is being trapped inside.
What’s she going to do?
Blue Silver Plant.
Tang San is going to strike big at our pretty girl,
but she’s rapidly moving.
Tang San can’t even catch her tail.
Nether Spikes.
The pretty girl now counter-attacks!
Tang San is being passive.
Such a waste.
The real motive of the cage is not to limit her,
but to attack from the sky.
The Controlling is effective
against Keen Attack.
Your attack won’t break my Martial Soul’s control.
Zhu Qing.
I’ve lost.
Zhu Zhu Qing admitted defeat,
the winner is
Tang San.
Don’t worry, I didn’t cast the poisonous spikes.
Your soul power decreased sharply...
because my first soul ring...
carries paralysis effect.
Tang San won.
one win and zero loss.
Zhu Zhu Qing has zero win and one loss.
[One win, zero loss]
Keen Attack soul masters
are more used to hiding in the dark.
Assassinations, investigations
and ambushes are your strengths.
If you were in
a more complicated demographic,
Little San wouldn’t win so easily.
[Soul Land]
Let’s go.
Redeem points,
and then take a break.
The 2-on-2 battle should start
in any minute.
The fifth round, 2-on-2.
The Iron Blood versus San Woo.
Please get ready.
Strength type war soul masters again?
Two kids?
It seems San Woo looks promising.
Let the battle begin!
Both of them never feel relaxed
even though we’re younger than them.
It proves they’re experienced.
I’m Iron Dragon.
I’m Iron Tiger.
Be careful.
Xiao Wu.
The Iron Blood!
What a great strike!
Can the San Woo take it?
What a great impact.
Blue Silver Plant got shattered.
His hammering looks similar to
my Skill of Random Hammering.
Even though its rhythm isn’t organized
and not fierce enough,
but its speed is way faster.
What a strange move.
Too bad he’s slow.
What a strong kick.
Look. How Blue Silver Plant
is being used. Marvelous!
Activate Blue Silver Plant’s second soul skill.
Haunted Vine.
My second soul ring, Haunted Vine...
is a terrifying Plant Branch.
It’ll scatter fine seeds during attack...
which parasite on your body.
As long as it has enough power,
the seeds will grow.
It’ll produce a nerve poison that numbs you.
Its spikes are the deadliest.
Once you are spiked, it’ll turn into a pus.
In order to help Little San get this
600-year-old Haunted Vine,
we even involved the Dean of Nuoding School.
It seems to be working well.
We defeated Teacher Zhao with this move too.
Second soul skill.
Stake all on this throw!
What a powerful attack! Can the San Woo take this?
It even has tracking ability.
That’s bad.
You two, how dare you!
No, Xiao Wu.
Little San, what are you doing?
They did what they should.
My injury isn’t severe.
Her sleeve arrow might kill you.
Now that you’re being totally trapped
by Blue Silver Plant,
and your soul powers are much depleted
after using the skill just now.
The numbing poison has further gone
into your bodies.
There’s no way you can escape her attack.
I think we’ve already won the round.
Thank you for saving our lives.
We admit defeat.
San Woo wins!
Luckily, I have Tang Clan weapons.
I underestimated the enemy.
Where’s the Dean?
He has some issues with the shop.
Let’s head back.
You all may leave first.
I have something to do too.
Take things easy.
Boss Dai,
are you not going?
No.
Come on, let’s go together.
Didn’t you say that women are just resources?
What resources?
It’s nothing.
Get lost.
My taste isn’t as bad as yours.
Dirty.
Disgusting.
You!
Stand there!
They...
Is it still hurt?
It’s because of me.
It’s nothing,
I’m not that weak.
Let’s go.
Hurry up,
or else we’ll lose them.
[Next Episode]
Your task today...
is to eat special made sausages by Oscar,
at least one piece.
They’re from the Cang Hui School, right?
Fight?
I love it!