♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] The background of
Emperor Team is overwhelming!
During the battle,
we must focus on
the soul master of Assisting Branch
of the opponent.
This is an almost perfect combination.
This time, you’re going to
encounter a strong opponent.
We can win.
In the previous battles,
we won by defeating the strong opponents.
We, Shrek Seven Devils
are never afraid of anyone else.
Yes, Shrek Seven Devils will surely win.
Win!
Soul battle begins.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 40]
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
He is indeed powerful.
Remember.
Only by combining all your strength,
you can make up the gap
between the capability difference.
It’s odd.
How can he control every strand
of Blue Silver Plant like his limbs?
Pulling requires strength.
It isn’t easy to control it well.
Let alone controlling six teammates
at the same time.
It’s hard to control Blue Silver Plant
only by strength.
But I have the skill from Tang Clan,
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
I have the whole situation in control.
Teacher is right. You should
be paid more attention.
Thunder Dragon Claws.
Purple Demon Eye.
Oh, no, I’m tricked.
Our opponent’s level is too much higher than ours.
Therefore, we can’t have a head-on fight.
Brother San, what idea do you have?
The key to victory is on him.
Yu Tian Heng?
His strength is very mighty.
He’s the captain of Emperor Team,
and the sharpest spear of Emperor Team.
If we can first break this spear,
the scale of victory and defeat will be tilted.
But how should we defeat him?
Yu Tian Heng is from
the clan of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
He must be very arrogant.
We can take advantage of this.
Little San, you’re indeed an expert in tactics.
Using Mu Bai’s attack as a bait,
and Blue Silver Plant is used to
help Mu Bai neutralize his attack.
That’s not just for saving Mu Bai,
most importantly, it is to attract
Yu Tian Heng’s attention
to yourself.
Lure the enemy into depth.
As the captain of Emperor Team,
you’re indeed calm, reliable and strong.
However, in your heart,
while facing this obviously weaker team,
you’re indeed a little reckless.
You’re tricked eventually.
Tian Heng, the pride of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
makes you belittle your opponent.
Intertwine.
Excellent combination.
How can Yu Tian Heng overcome this plight?
I’m waiting for this moment.
I don’t have to retreat.
Your joint attack
is the chance for me
to destroy all of you in a blow.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Fury of Thunderbolt.
Is this really a soul battle among Soul Honors?
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
shouldn’t be looked down upon.
Powerful. Blue Silver Plant
doesn’t conduct electricity normally.
But the energy of Fury of Thunderbolt
is too humongous.
Blue Silver Plant can’t take it.
The tactic of luring enemy
of Shrek Seven Devil was effective,
but it has also put them in crisis.
Fury of Thunderbolt of Tian Heng
can double the power of lightning.
His second soul skill,
Mighty Thunderbolt, has a bursting attack.
It can injure Shrek Seven Devils
in all dimensions.
Pretending to progress while retreating.
However,
Shrek Seven Devils can win all 27 battles
in Suo Tuo Soul Arena,
they won’t be defeated so easily.
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Martial Soul is brutal,
but you’re fighting alone after all.
Mighty Thunderbolt may be frightening,
but it attacks in all dimension.
Mu Bai’s attack is monosomic.
In coherence of soul power,
White Tiger Intense Light Wave is more superior.
But Yu Tian Heng has only fallen
one step further back than Mu Bai.
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
is apparently very overbearing.
Due to the fire wall,
teammates of Emperor Team can’t help.
Although Xiao Wu’s soul power is eight levels
lower than the opponent,
Tian Heng’s body condition is at its worst.
Xiao Wu has an increment of 30%
with the help of Qibao Amber Pagoda.
Tian Heng can’t resist Xiao Wu’s Rou Skill.
First soul skill, Arched Body.
From Tian Heng overtook
Black Martial Turtle to attack,
to Shrek Seven Devils completed the surround
to inflict Tian Heng,
all of these only are done within little time.
However, this is the key moment.
I’ll kill you all!
No, Yan Zi.
Do not use Jade Phosphor Serpent Venom.
Dugu Yan’s best skill,
Jade Phosphor Serpent Venom.
The venom of Jade Phosphor Serpent
is extremely venomous.
Even Tian Heng is strong, he wouldn’t touch it.
Let alone that she released the venom
with third soul skill,
the toxin will be in effect very quickly.
Once touched by the venomous fog,
that part will be inflamed immediately.
It’s indeed Jade Phosphor Serpent Venom.
This girl is just like him, cruel and vicious.
Don’t know if Little San...
Get back.
Yan Zi is a little lazy normally,
but when someone hurts Yu Tian Heng,
she’ll be infuriated.
Now she has forgotten my deploy.
The lives of Shrek Seven Devils are at stake.
Are the little monsters okay?
It’s just the Jade Phosphor Serpent
of the Five Toxins Jade Phosphor.
See how I neutralize your venom.
Boss. Fatty.
Pointless struggle.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Phoenix Firing Line.
It’s alcohol.
No, this is impossible.
How could you neutralize
my Jade Phosphor Purple Venom?
Jade Phosphor Serpent Venom
is just an insignificant skill.
Venom is the unique skill of Tang Clan.
I added realgar powder into the alcohol.
Then it’s ignited by Fire of Phoenix.
Although the serpent venom is strong,
it can be neutralized.
Turns out there’s such an intelligent way
to neutralize it.
Do these small obstacles
make you afraid of the opponents?
Nine Heart Flowering Apple.
We’ve neglected
the existence of this soul master.
That’s not good.
Shrek Seven Devils could strike first,
because they took advantage
of their recklessness.
But this time, we’re the reckless ones.
Shrek Seven Devils have good teamwork.
But Emperor Team isn’t half a penny worse.
Ling Ling is usually cool and detached.
In fact, she cares about her partner
more than anyone else.
Because of the recovery power of
Ling Ling’s Nine Heart Flowering Apple,
Tian Heng and the others
can charge forward without worries.
You’re reckless. Though Jade Phosphor
Serpent Venom lost its function,
it has gained the most crucial time.
Oh, no.
Ling Ling is right.
What are we waiting for? Fight!
The favorable situation
that Little San established is useless now.
The real battle starts now!
It’s venomous gas. Oscar!
His body isn’t recovered to his best condition.
Although his wounds are healed,
his soul power isn’t recovered.
His fractures didn’t heal completely either.
The Black Panther soul master
is faster than Zhu Qing.
Besides, his attack is fierce.
He wants to use up Zhu Qing’s soul power
with continuous attacks.
Osler may be arrogant,
but his tactic is implemented thoroughly.
Especially when he faces
opponents of the same type.
His nature of breaking the opponent completely
is released.
The angle of attack is cunning.
This person looks smiley.
Why is he so cunning?
The opponents that Zhu Qing and Hong Jun
face have way higher soul power.
Despite the help of Qibao Amber Pagoda,
the gap of a soul ring can’t be made up.
An extra soul ring isn’t just about
an extra soul skill.
When the soul ring is absorbed,
everything is improved comprehensively.
Black Martial Turtle soul master
has undoubtedly the shell as defence.
Now that the shell is here,
their defence will decrease greatly.
The turtle shell is cutting Silver Blue Plant.
Black Martial Turtle and Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
are both top Martial Souls.
It seems the Shi Brothers
are stronger than imagined.
All along, the most eye-catching
one in Emperor Team
is the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon soul master,
Captain Yu Tian Heng.
But in terms of the combat ability,
Shi Brothers aren’t much worse than Tian Heng.
Without turtle shells,
how will you defend yourself?
Xiao Wu, watch out!
Oh, no! Xiao Wu can’t move in the air.
No!
I promised you, I’ll protect you forever.
Brother.
Xiao Wu.
No!
Brother.
Don’t talk.
Xuan Tian Strike has protected
your cardiopulmonary arteries.
The blood has been stopped.
How dare you injure Xiao Wu?
What’s going on?
Surprisingly, I feel a unique pressure from him.
Third soul skill, Raging Storm.
[Next Episode]
The toxin is getting near the cardiac artery.
That’s the fact.
Comparing your actual strength,
you’re no match to Emperor Team.
Alright, Frander. That’s enough.
The kids have worked hard lately.
You are...
Frander, I’ve repeated many times.
I have nothing to do
with Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe anymore.