♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
We’re not humans, but monsters.
Let me teach you how to be a human.
Nether Spikes.
Intertwine.
Dark Water.
Don’t you dare!
You didn’t even use your Martial Soul.
So arrogant.
Beating up people without
using Martial Soul is really enjoyable.
Star Dou Forest is
different from
other forests with reared soul beasts.
Watch out. Something is
heading to us in a high speed.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 22]
Watch out. Something is
heading to us in a high speed.
It seems to be a flying snake.
It’s flying two or three meters
above the ground.
It has a red crown on its head.
What does its tail look like?
Its tail is
shaped like a fan.
Zhu Qing,
how long is the snake?
What is the color of its wings?
It’s about six to eight meters long.
Wings are pale red.
Six to eight meters,
red.
This is a Millennium Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent.
Probably 1,300 to 1,800 years old.
Its age and type are suitable.
Millennium Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent is rare.
We’re lucky this time,
Oscar.
Really? That’s awesome!
The attack of Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent
is predictable,
it only uses its body to strangle the enemy.
But it is extremely fast.
Especially its meat crown...
stores nutrition to help it speed up
to escape when it senses danger.
So it’s quite hard to hunt.
How do we do then?
Snakes are afraid of birds.
Fatty’s Martial Soul is Phoenix,
maybe it can restrain this snake.
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent is not good at attack.
We only need to
prevent it from escaping.
Good.
You know this soul beast well.
You’ll lead this battle.
Okay, Teacher.
Get ready.
Fatty.
It’s here.
That’s fast.
Be careful.
Are you okay?
Well done, kid.
Eat my...
sausage.
After eating this, surrender.
I can’t hold it anymore.
Retract.
Fatty, now!
Teacher Zhao.
Want to escape?
Not so easy.
Gravity Squeeze.
Orientated pursue.
Fourth and fifth soul skill are used at once.
This is Teacher Zhao’s real power.
Teacher Zhao held back during the exam previously.
Oscar, come here.
Okay.
Do we need to kill the soul beast?
Can we don’t kill it?
The weak is the prey of the strong.
This is the law of survival.
If this snake was stronger than us,
do you think it would let us go?
Let’s not delay anymore, do it.
Stab at its meat crown.
Then the soul ring will be yours.
Stop.
I’m Chao Tian Xiang.
Chao Tian Xiang?
Sounds familiar.
Six soul rings.
Seems like she’s a Soul Emperor above Level 60.
Compared with Teacher Zhao’s
Soul Saint level with seven soul rings,
her ability is lower.
The soul rings are swaying,
but their body has not change.
That means their Martial Souls...
are the sticks in their hands.
What’s the matter?
Teacher Zhao’s attitude towards this old lady...
Good day, respected Soul Saint.
You can’t give this
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent to this kid.
Why?
Because we found this snake first.
You found it first?
How can you prove that you found it first?
When we found it, we didn’t see you.
Kid,
don’t be impatient.
You can check its stomach.
There are three wounds made by my stick.
[Soul Land]
My granddaughter has just reached Level 30.
She needs this soul ring.
It’s her.
Is this Unrivaled Dragon Serpent,
The Serpent?
Do you know me?
You’re famous,
of course, I know you.
Unrivaled Dragon Serpent,
who is that?
Why...
Boss Dai, who is this old lady?
Why is Teacher Zhao so polite to her?
The Dragon, Meng Shu,
The Serpent, Chao Tian Xiang.
A famous couple among the soul masters.
It is rumored that this couple is
inseparable and connected to each other.
Thus when their Martial Souls
combine, their power is great.
Probably stronger than a Grand Soul Land Master.
Is that so?
That means Little Ao’s soul ring is gone?
It isn’t for sure.
The Dragon is not here.
Only the Serpent herself is...
no match to Teacher Zhao.
The Serpent is here,
The Dragon may be nearby too.
This old lady is very alert.
If we attack hastily and let her escape,
once The Dragon arrives,
we’ll all die here.
I can’t let this old lady delay anymore.
I’m Zhao Wu Ji.
Oh, it’s the famous Acala,
Zhao Wu Ji.
No wonder.
I’m wondering why I met
such a young Soul Saint.
You’re exaggerating. It’s just a bad title.
You said your granddaughter
need this soul ring very much.
Theoretically,
I should give it
to you in courtesy,
but...
What?
We found this snake first.
If it isn’t for us to have injured it,
can you catch it?
Return it to us now.
If not, we won’t be easy on you.
That means,
you’ll not return this
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent to us.
Your words are not appropriate.
The soul beasts in
Star Dou Forest don’t have any owner.
How can you use the term, return?
You may have found it first,
but we’re the ones who have caught it.
You said it’s suitable for your granddaughter.
But it’s suitable for my student too.
You mean these kids are Level 30 as well?
Oscar.
Yes.
Tell this elder what level your soul power is.
Senior,
my soul power is Level 30.
This kid is younger than Yi Ran.
Yet his soul power is already at Level 30.
Senior,
if there’s nothing else,
then we’ll leave first.
If that so,
we’ll deal with it by the soul master rules.
Soul master rules?
Please state it.
Battle with my granddaughter.
The loser will not get the soul ring.
I don’t think so.
What?
Zhao Wu Ji,
I’ve taken a step back.
What else do you want?
Are you bullying us because
my husband is not around?
Of course not.
But my student is
a Food Branch soul master.
What? Food Branch?
He’s a Food Branch soul master?
Kid, which clan are you from?
I don’t have a clan.
He doesn’t have a clan...
and he’s so young.
If I can convince him to help Yi Ran,
that will be perfect.
Kid,
you...
Teacher Zhao,
I’ll fight on behalf of Little Ao.
If we delay this further,
what if The Dragon appears...
I’m at Level 29,
it’s not a cheating.
Senior.
Is this okay?
Is this okay, Senior?
Okay.
Meng Yi Ran,
Serpent Stick Martial Soul.
War soul master
with two soul rings at Level 30.
Tang San,
Blue Silver Plant Martial Soul.
War soul master
with two soul rings at Level 29.
You first.
Blue Silver Plant?
A useless Martial Soul.
First soul skill.
Intertwine.
Poisonous Thorn Paralysis.
This battle ends here.
What happened?
the poison is not working.
First soul skill,
Serpent Blade.
No wonder.
She uses poison too.
Darn.
I’ll end this fast then.
[Next Episode]
Don’t let down your guard.
Star Dou Forest is very dangerous.
Teacher Zhao,
we may not go back to school yet.
Well...
Promise me that
you won’t laugh at me.
I’ll show you my third soul skill later.
Don’t be surprised.
Be careful of your surroundings.
Prepare to fight.