♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
She’s Liu Er Long.
She’s the one who followed Master and me
wandering around the soul masters’ world.
She’s the third in the Golden Iron Triangle.
I don’t care about the secular viewpoint.
I just wish to be with you.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 48]
My Xuan Tian Strike is at Level 4,
I’m immune to frost and heat.
Could this freezing feeling be...
Who is it?
That’s bad, Little San might be in trouble.
Hurry and have a look.
Stop pretending if you’re awake.
Kid, you’re Tang San?
Yes, I am.
I heard that you broke
my granddaughter’s third soul skill
and even suppressed it with poison.
How did you cure the venom?
I believe there’s something
else other than liquor.
How dare you call yourself the Grand Venom Master
if you don’t know realgar powder
can cure snake venom?
It has been years since
someone talked to me that way.
Kid, you’re bold!
How dare you suspect my poison?
Your poison is mere rubbish.
Your poison is indeed effective,
but still it’s useless.
Poison strike is to attack others.
Now that you’re poisoned too,
what are you if you aren’t useless?
You mean I was poisoned by myself?
I’m 78 years old.
Only I can cast poison to others,
never at once I have been poisoned.
Is that true?
Tell me, when it’s cloudy or raining,
do you ribs feel numb?
It happens once at noon and 11 p.m..
From what I see,
every time it’ll last for at least two hours.
Besides, during midnight,
your head and feet
will have prickling pain, right?
That overwhelming pain,
you won’t feel that if you aren’t poisoned.
Not only you’re poisoned,
the venom has also entered your marrow.
Blue Silver Plant’s first soul skill, Intertwine.
An attached soul bone?
No wonder Yan lost.
I didn’t expect that
I’d be killed by someone who uses useless poison.
It’s so unworthy.
Not reconciled?
Didn’t you say that my poison is useless?
Yet you’re still defeated by me.
That’s my biggest regret!
If I was given time,
even if I won’t use Martial Soul,
I’ll kill you too.
Your poison
not only harms yourself,
but also ruins your descendants.
You’re an ultimate rubbish!
What did you say?
You know exactly what I mean.
You can cure my poison?
I won’t even if I can.
You’ll only suffer more than I do.
Just kill me. Maybe you’re not afraid of death,
but your dearest pretty granddaughter
may won’t hold as long as you.
She’ll only be severer when the poison attacks.
Since she was in her mother’s womb,
she already got in touch with the poison.
Dugu Yan’s unique semblance
and her Jade Phosphor Serpent Venom
must be inherited from Dugu Bo’s Martial Soul.
Even she has a great ability to poison,
at the same time, she inherits
the counter charge of her own poison.
Why should I believe that
you can cure my poison?
Do I even have to prove it to you?
You’re killing me anyway.
Having you alive is a threat to the world.
Saving you is just like holding
the candle to the devil.
I’ve been living with poison all my life,
yet I can’t even cure the poison within my body.
But my granddaughter...
Alright, if you can cure our poison,
I won’t kill you,
and I can promise to help you with three things
that don’t violate my base line.
You’re not killing me?
Why should I believe you?
People like you
always repay kindness with ingratitude.
Isn’t my fame enough to prove it?
Stop making empty promises,
unless you make a vow.
Alright then.
As long as you can prove that
you can cure my poison,
I can make a promise.
How do you want me to prove it?
Prove that you can cast poison better than I do,
then I’ll believe you.
I have nothing with me now,
how do I prove I’m stronger than you?
Easy. This is my house.
All herbs are widely grown here.
I’ll give you one day
to figure out all sorts of antidotes yourself.
After that, I’ll cast three types of poison on you.
If you can cure my poisons with your antidotes,
that means you’re qualified.
Or else, you will die.
Bring me to your herb garden.
Don’t disturb me for a day.
[Soul Land]
I can smell sulphur.
Is there a hot spring here?
Your herb garden is near a hot spring?
It’s a great place.
The hot spring itself
isn’t suitable for plant nourishment,
but some special plants are different.
They need minerals and heat
from a hot spring.
Follow me.
Kid, aren’t you arrogant?
Let me see how you get down.
That’s how he uses attached soul bone.
This is
Ice Fire Spring Mouth.
Both ice and fire which restrict
each other in one spring mouth.
It’s one of the Three Treasures
of hidden weapons in Xuan Tian Records.
I can’t believe the rare
Ice Fire Mouth Spring appears here.
No wonder this old creature can still survive
even he’s severely poisoned.
He even trains himself to
the Grand Soul Land Master.
Ice Fire Mouth Spring?
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
I just didn’t expect such a great place exists.
If I was 30% confident to cure your poison,
now, with this Ice Fire Mouth Spring,
it can be raised to 50%.
What? Only 50%?
Kid, you’ve been lying to me all this while?
You’ve been soaked with poison for years,
50% is already my best to cure you.
But, even if you’re not fully recovered,
it’ll ease your pain too.
But I’m positive to cure your granddaughter.
All my herbs are planted here,
you may use them.
If you dare to ruin my place,
I’ll make sure you go through living hell.
I’ll give you more time.
If you can’t pass my test
the morning after tomorrow,
it’ll be your doomsday.
This is a famous soul beast forest.
Except this mountain is being
sealed by my poison formation
and the soul beasts dare not enter,
Millennium Soul Beasts are out there.
If you run away, before I find you,
the soul beasts will tear you apart.
Kid, remember, don’t touch those two hot springs.
Even I can’t withstand the heat
and frost for too long.
No one can save you by then.
Of course, I’m aware of it.
That’s the coldest and hottest place in the world.
Humans or beasts
who stay by the Ice Fire Eyes
will be hurt by the extreme
heaven and earth auras in a short time.
Their bodies will explode
if they don’t leave immediately.
But, for someone who is poisoned like Dugu Bo
this is the greatest place.
Extreme frost or heat
is effective against the venom.
Not to mention this treasured place
of Ice Fire Spring Mouth,
there’s no sense of temperature
on the surface of the hot spring.
Is this snow silkworm?
It’s the ultimate herb of
the winter worm and summer grass.
The Vermillion Lotus can grow up to this size?
This is
the Fragrant Silk Woven Flower?
That’s right, that’s it.
It’s the best antidote recorded in the
secret list of the Xuan Tian Records.
Within its range,
none of the poison is effective.
Its fragrance can
neutralize all sorts of poison,
too bad it can’t cure it.
Whether Dugu Bo keeps his promise,
I have to hedge my bet.
Octa Dark Frost, a unique winter flower.
[Next Episode]
Two Saints of Soul above Level 70.
and a soul master under Level 30.
You’ll regret killing Tang San.
Even though three of you are weak,
but I still can take it as warming up.
Sun Moon Golden Shine.
There’s even a trinity Martial Soul Fusion Skill?