♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Bastards, how can they sell her as a pet?
I come to see
who dares to beat my son.
Brother, isn’t that our Malicious Attack?
It’s in my interest.
Tai Long, are you still not convinced?
Tai Long, if we also beat your father up,
is your grandfather coming too?
You troublesome woman.
How dare you insult Xiao Wu!
Supreme Orangutan!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 57]
First soul skill, Boost.
My first soul skill, Boost
can boost my soul power up by 25%!
Intertwine!
His power is still increasing.
Second soul skill, Focus!
Focus, it can boost his power
by 20% after his first skill.
He’s 50% stronger now.
You’re quite slippery.
Third soul skill, Source of Power!
Now, he’s two times stronger than he was before.
So strong.
Still evading my blows?
I’ll increase my power until
the point you cannot evade.
Fourth soul skill, Power Slam.
Brother?
Look up!
A parachute?
Godly Zhuge Crossbow! Watch out!
Power boost times three!
Fourth soul skill, Power Slam!
You used poison.
Poison is one of my original ability.
Do you still want to continue?
You!
Father.
Tang San, I’ll kill you!
Ghostly Trace!
Tai Long, if you don’t want your father to die,
you’d better stop now.
If not, I can’t save him.
He’s too strong.
I’ve purged the poison.
Your father will feel weak for some time.
Let him rest for three days.
Don’t be angry and don’t use any soul power.
He’ll recover after that.
And your father made this pit.
You two should handle it.
Brother! Wait for me!
I rarely come back. My father is not around.
Grandpa Bone,
do you think my father is avoiding me on purpose?
My little princess, don’t be angry.
I think he’ll be back soon.
I don’t care! When he’s back,
I want some rewards from him.
Grandpa Bone, you must help me.
I heard that my little daughter is back.
Let me have a look.
My little lass. Why are you turning
your back to me? It’s been almost a year.
I miss you so much.
Miss me? Don’t lie.
You hoped that I wouldn’t come home.
Come, little lass. Let me hug you.
Grandpa Sword! I miss you!
Good girl. You’re finally back.
I miss you too. Very much.
Is that so?
Of course. You can ask your Grandpa Bone
if you don’t believe it.
But just now, he said
he misses me more.
He’s lying. I miss you more.
You’re the one lying!
Not happy? Come, let’s fight one by one.
Okay. Uncle Sword, Uncle Bone,
you have fought each other all the time.
Rong Rong just came back. Call it off.
Uncle Sausage is not in the dorm again.
Although I’ve trained myself
in the Ice Fire Mouth Spring,
and consumed the Octa Dark Frost
and Fiery Soft Apricot,
the power differences of 21 levels
are too hard on my body.
But, I confirmed one thing
because of the battle today.
The other ability of Eight Spider Bone.
Devour.
The Eight Spider Bone can
devour the opponent’s soul power.
And it can last for one hour.
Brother, what’s wrong?
It’s nothing. It’s just some minor injuries.
How can that be?
Tai Nuo is a Soul King.
Brother, you just fought with a Soul King!
And you won!
Tai Long and his family
love to justify their faults.
Brother, you defeated his father this time.
Will his grandfather come for you next?
I wonder where Uncle Sausage is.
He’s never around when we need him.
Xiao Wu, you should go back and rest.
I want to meditate to recover for a while.
No, I won’t leave. I will stay with you.
What if other troublemakers turn up?
Brother, you can meditate. I’ll protect you.
[Soul Land]
I can prove who misses me the most.
Rong Rong, stop fooling around.
I finally came back,
but you are not at home.
My grandpas are better than you.
Grandpas, how about this?
Both of you can send me a gift.
If I like your gift,
it means that you miss me the most.
Rong Rong, that’s enough. Come here.
I miss you too, you know?
I’ve prepared a gift for you.
Gift? What did you prepare?
- That was quick!
Rong Rong, what’s your soul level now?
Dad, I’m not talented.
I only gained ten levels
even though I’ve worked hard.
Only ten levels? Rong Rong,
you need to work harder.
Wait, what? Ten levels?
Yeah. I was at Level 27 when I left.
Now, I’m at Level 37.
Level 37? Rong Rong, don’t lie to me.
Dad, you don’t believe me.
Although I have the help of the
Silk Woven Tulip,
I did train very hard too.
Silk Woven Tulip?
Half a month ago, Brother San
gave me that mysterious flower.
With its help,
I gained six levels within one day.
Six levels in one day?
What kind of plant is that?
I think only Dugu Bo knows about it.
This can’t do. Feng Zhi,
we need to check Rong Rong’s body condition.
It’ll be bad if she sacrificed her
life force to increase her soul level.
Grandpa Bone, Dad, don’t worry.
Brother San said that flower is a sacred grass.
It doesn’t hurt my body.
Look at this if you don’t believe me.
Qibao, with the power of Amber,
with nine stories and colours,
Jiubao Amber Pagoda!
With nine stories and colours,
Jiubao Amber Pagoda?
Dad, do you feel better?
My son, I knew why you lost.
Even I was defeated.
It’s no wonder you can’t defeat him.
Do you know about his background?
He came to the school for the first time today.
He was sitting next to Xiao Wu!
That’s why I fought with him.
You know that I like Xiao Wu, right?
Look at you.
You’re just like the past me.
Dad, you...
No. I’m saying that you’re useless!
You can’t even defeat a man younger than you.
But Dad, you were defeated by Tang San too.
You scoundrel. Are you asking for a beating?
No! I don’t mean that.
I’m just saying that Tang San is too strong.
Does he belong to one of
the Seven Major Tribes?
Let’s talk when we get back.
I remembered that
no tribe uses the Blue Silver Plant
as their Martial Soul.
Let’s ask your grandfather.
Perhaps he knows something.
Grandpa? Dad, there’s no need for that.
We’ve disgraced ourselves.
If Grandpa knows about this,
he’ll surely beat us up.
What if he went to my school as you did?
What? Do you have any objections?
No.
Dad!
Qibao Amber Pagoda
is the strongest martial soul of Support Branch,
but it has a major flaw.
It can only accommodate seven soul rings.
Although I heard about
the Jiubao Amber Pagoda before,
it is hard for me to believe that
I got to witness it today.
Dad, Grandpa Bone, Grandpa Sword,
now do you believe me?
Rong Rong, that Brother San of yours,
who exactly is he?
Dad, why do you have so many questions?
Where is my gift?
I bought this at the auction house today.
Although they are not very powerful,
they can protect you.
Malicious Attack? Soundless Arrow?
Dad, why do you have the
hidden weapons of Brother San?
Your Brother San made them?
So, it’s him.
Look, aren’t they the same?
I have some more powerful weapons.
By the way, I want to ask you...
can the direct descendants of our tribe
use these hidden weapons?
They are powerful if we use them well.
I really wanted to know...
What kind of a genius your Brother San is.
Brother San? He’s just one of
my classmates in Shrek School.
Classmates.
If he’s really outstanding,
he may be our grandson-in-law.
Uncle Sword, it’s not what you think.
Brother San likes someone else. And I...
How about we go outside?
I’ll show you how to use hidden weapons.
[Next Episode] - Who’s Tang San?
- I am Tang San.
You’ve revealed your identity.
Playboy.
Tomorrow, I’ll go to Shrek School with you.
Why is Little San fighting with him?
Let’s make a bet.
What’s the bet?
Tang Clan!
Regarding his strength, he’s stronger
than most Grand Soul Land Masters.
What? He’s stronger than you?
Teacher Zhao, go and stop them.
This is...