♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I’ve grabbed it, so others don’t
have to keep thinking about it.
Tang San.
We’re fighting Lei Ting School today.
The only match they lost
was the one against Shen Feng School.
Shrek, wins!
In order to defeat them,
you must have faith in your partners.
- Fourth soul skill, God Locking Ring.
- She escaped Lei Ting’s attack just now.
She hasn’t experienced
the power of lightning.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 88]
We surrender.
Ninth round, Lei Ting School won.
Cool. Let’s do this in the next round.
Xiao Wu.
Let’s go.
Mu Bai, it’s your turn.
Boss Dai, count on you now.
Shrek School is sending the captain.
A Soul Sect at Level 44
of Storm Attack Branch, Dai Mu Bai.
The strength of Shrek School’s
captain is powerful.
I’ve depleted much energy in the last round.
I must settle this quickly.
The situation is exciting.
Who will take the first move?
Tenth round, begins.
Fourth soul skill, God Locking Ring.
First soul skill, White Tiger Shield.
Using first soul skill to
resist my fourth soul skill?
You’re belittling me.
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum.
Unbreakable and resilient.
It’s so stunning.
Dai Mu Bai has defeated his opponent
with just one soul skill.
Tenth round, Shrek School won.
Teacher.
Don’t be reckless.
Don’t stop me. I want to report that
Shrek School has attempted a murder.
They were battling just now.
Lei Dong didn’t surrender either.
Dai Mu Bai has only hit him off the stage.
He didn’t intend to kill.
The judge will not disqualify them.
But
Lei Dong’s shoulders are nearly broken.
With such a heavy injury,
let alone the qualifying rounds,
he won’t even be able to join the finals.
How can we just take this insult?
Let me fight them.
Shrek School is at their climax point.
If Lei Ting School loses one more participant,
Shrek School will have the final victory.
Are you okay?
However,
this person will be representing
Lei Ting School next,
Captain Yu Tian Xin.
A Soul Sect at Level 43 of Storm Attack Branch.
His Martial Soul is
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
Why did the weather change so suddenly? Xiao Gang.
Tian Xin?
Dai Mu Bai, you have to pay for what you’ve done.
We shall see if you can do that.
The ultimate battle between two captains.
Who’ll have the victory?
Begin!
I’ll show you today,
who has the strongest beast soul.
I would like to see it too.
It’s finally here. Rain.
Did you bring an umbrella?
Rain can conduct electricity.
Mu Bai is in trouble.
Wind and rain come as clouds cover the sun.
Dragon in heaven. Jade Lightning.
Remember, the dragon is the strongest.
I don’t agree with you.
[Soul Land]
My strength is similar to my cousin Tian Heng’s.
Only because he’s younger than me,
the family values him more.
I have to defeat you in this match,
to prove to my family that I’m the best heir.
I left home to Tian Dou Empire,
to Shrek School,
so I can make myself stronger.
I can’t lose.
Second soul skill,
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Mu Bai and Tian Xin have similar strengths.
They have the same style,
and even the same ambition.
That means...
What does that mean?
It won’t take long until the result is clear.
Come on. We’ll decide who wins.
The person who last stands will be the winner.
Okay.
Fourth soul skill,
Blue Lightning Divine Dragon.
White Tiger Meteor Strike.
Fourth skill.
Both parties are using their fourth soul skills.
This is the last decisive strike.
No gimmick, only a battle between strengths.
This is a battle of equal strengths.
No matter victory or failure,
they’ve both tried their best.
He will win.
You’re very strong. I lost.
No, you didn’t lose. You might have lost the battle,
but your heart wasn’t defeated by mine.
Looking forward to the next strike with you.
Alright.
Qualifying match between
Shrek School and Lei Ting School.
Shrek School won.
Boss Dai.
Mu Bai.
Zhu Qing, did you come
to Tian Dou Empire to monitor me?
I promise, I’ll never court other girls anymore.
You wouldn’t dare. Let me tell you.
If you aren’t strong enough
to reach my expectation,
I will not marry you in the future.
You’ve agreed on the engagement?
Zhu Qing.
Mu Bai.
You two...
Little San.
Master.
The opponent that we drew surrendered just now.
We have only one opponent left.
Shen Feng School.
That’s right.
Tang San.
What’s the matter?
Our opponent tomorrow has surrendered.
When both our teams cross swords,
I’ll be the first one to fight.
I hope you’ll be the first one as well.
Oh.
Let us decide who the champion
of the qualifying rounds is.
If I lose, Shen Feng School will surrender.
Sorry, I can’t agree.
Why?
Could you be afraid?
We’re a team.
I can’t make the decision
for my teammates with my own will.
Tang San, don’t be a sissy.
I just want to fight with you fairly.
Just like the battle between
Dai Mu Bai and Yu Tian Xin today.
Little San, agree with him.
Give him a battle of men.
If I’m right, you’re doing this for Huo Wu, right?
However...
If that’s the case, we’ll decide
the victory with one match.
Don’t have regret in life.
Don’t worry. Everyone trusts you.
Okay. I accept your challenge.
If you lose,
I don’t want to see you
around Huo Wu anymore.
I’m never related to her.
Who would you wish to win this battle?
This is the last qualifying round.
Both competing teams
have the results of 13 to 0.
But there will be only one winner today.
You can do this, boss.
You can do this, Brother San.
Both schools suggested one match
to decide the champion of the qualifying rounds.
After discussion, the organizer has
approved the request.
Feng Xiao Tian of Shen Feng School
defeated many strong opponents.
Same goes to Tang San
from Shrek School, who has
shown miracles with his persistence.
So,
what kind of battle
will these two bring us?
Continental Soul Master Elite Tournament,
the climax qualifying round,
begins now.
His Martial Soul is Gale Devil Wolf,
it’s even a double-headed wolf.
Could it be Mutated Martial Soul?
Tang San, I admire you.
But I have to defeat you today.
No matter what it takes.
[Next Episode]
Wow, Little San is so powerful.
- No.
- I must win.
The strength is way stronger than the last time.
I’ve already...
Could I really be defeated this time?
Brother.
The Pope means...
Fellow Elders.
Our teacher doesn’t wish
to see this person in Martial Soul City.