♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Since you decided
to assassinate Tang San
without empathizing my feelings,
the affection between us had ended.
Yu Xiao Gang, since I can’t have you,
I’ll destroy everything that you care about.
Xiao Wu!
Tomorrow is the first round of the final
of the tournament.
Seven of you will duel together this time.
Martial Soul Hall,
I’ll definitely settle it with you.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 96]
Dean, who is our opponent in the first round?
One bad news and one good news.
Which one do you prefer to listen to first?
Bad news first.
The bad news is
your opponent is Chi Huo School.
Why is Chi Huo again?
What are the odds?
Frander, what about the good news?
Right, what about it?
The good news is
Chi Huo School gave up the finals.
What?
So, we’ve skipped the first two rounds.
Are we entering the top ten without dueling?
Huo Wu had fought fiercely
in the qualifying rounds.
How could she give up so early?
The fight between Shen Feng School
and Long Kui School is going to begin.
Please be on the field.
What?
- This...
- How could it be?
Why did students from Chi Huo School
and Shen Feng appear together?
What’s going on?
I’m going to ask the committee.
Sister Huo Wu, regarding things about us...
Get on the cart.
Brother Feng, I called you
as I have something to discuss with you.
Sister Huo Wu, do we have to
be so polite to each other?
Do you think we can defeat Shrek
only by Chi Huo School
or Shen Feng School?
It’s hard.
Do you want a breakthrough?
Chi Huo School and Shen Feng School
combine to become New Shen Feng.
New Shen Feng?
I’ll negotiate with the committee.
As for you, you just have
to communicate with your members.
Brother Feng, will you promise me?
How can I refuse?
Sister Huo Wu.
Whether you wish to win in the finals
or you just want to defeat Tang San,
I’ll definitely help you.
The committee approved
their personnel transfer.
As expected.
They went around the rules.
It doesn’t allow schools to change
their participants during the fight.
But this doesn’t mean participants
can’t change their school temporarily.
Martial Soul Hall must have
a secret agreement with New Shen Feng.
Hence, they allowed New Shen Feng to do so.
Darn it.
Wouldn’t it be difficult if we encounter them
in the future?
Please remain silent.
Let’s look at both team’s fighting position.
We can see that
the distribution of the combat power
of Long Kui School is even.
It’s a conservative formation.
While New Shen Feng’s formation
is more aggressive.
It shows that Shen Feng is full of confidence.
Long Kui has four Soul Sects,
and they distribute evenly.
It seems like Long Kui
is going to fight firmly.
All Shen Feng members have reached
the level of Soul Sect.
With such a strong lineup,
can Long Kui fight with them?
Brother, Brother Feng. Settle them quickly.
I hereby announce,
Shen Feng School versus Long Kui School,
starts
now.
Second soul skill,
Blazing Flames Burning Lights.
It’s too powerful.
One more.
Fourth soul skill, Stormy Sand.
That was close.
Third soul skill, Vertigo Aroma.
I can’t avoid it.
Got him.
Wind.
Fire.
Darn it. Leader and I can’t fight over them.
Victory belongs to us anyhow.
Third soul skill, Gale Wings.
First soul skill, Threadlike Sparks.
Fourth soul skill, Menacing Waves of Clouds.
No, that’s a feint. His target is...
How cunning.
Third soul skill, Coagulate...
Right now.
When did...
Did they win?
Isn’t this too fast?
Did they pass three strokes?
Is this the strength of New Shen Feng?
Shen Feng School won.
Feng Xiao Tian only used three soul skills.
Huo Wu Shuang used two soul skills.
While Huo Wu didn’t even use her first soul skill.
Even though there’s a slight gap
between both teams,
but Shen Feng defeated their rivals
within a few minutes.
This happens rarely in finals.
I wonder who are our next opponents.
Could it be New Shen Feng?
[Soul Land]
Next round, Xing Luo Imperial School.
Xing Luo?
Xing Luo.
The seeded soul masters from Xing Luo Empire.
Their strength should not be underestimated.
Boss Dai, what’s wrong?
I know that it’s important
for you to reserve your strength.
But I’d like to request everyone
to do your best in this round.
For Mu Bai and me,
this isn’t just a battle of soul skills.
but
a life-and-death duel.
Welcome the first match in the third round
of the finals.
Shrek School
versus Xing Luo Imperial School.
Now standing on the field is Shrek School.
They didn’t join the
first two rounds in the finals.
How would they perform today?
How far can they go?
Let’s wait and see.
Now here comes Xing Luo Imperial School Team.
As the best seed of Xing Luo Empire,
what surprise will they
bring to us today?
Mu Bai, I’ve never expected
you can reach the finals.
But you should know that
it’ll make my desire stronger to attack you.
Dai Wei Si, stop being pretentious.
When have you ever stopping striking me?
Today, we’re enemies.
Oh, our playboy has changed.
How dare you talk so rudely to me?
It seems like their relations
are worse than what Boss Dai described.
Their situation
is totally different from Yu Tian Xin
and Yu Tian Heng.
The competition between Yu brothers is healthy.
But theirs are cruel.
Because of their tribe’s rules,
losers are not worthy of living.
I didn’t expect that Zhu Qing
followed you to Tian Dou Empire.
Are you going
to fight us till the end?
Give up, Brother. You’ve lost.
Not yet.
Brother, you’re just my junior forever.
Second soul skill,
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
For Zhu Qing, I will not run away anymore.
Zhu Qing, you’ve reached top ten
in the finals. Just end here.
Dad and Mom miss you a lot.
But they can’t go against the tribe’s rules.
Go back with me after this tournament.
Zhu Zhu Yun, stop being pretentious.
If I didn’t leave home,
I might have been killed by you.
They miss me?
Does such affection
exist in our family?
My life would be under your control.
Zhu Qing, what are you saying?
They are all aggressive in the first meeting.
All participants, please be ready.
Now, let’s look at their information.
Friends, initiate our martial souls.
Give them a surprise.
Well, I wonder what you’ve learnt
after leaving home.
[Dai Mu Bai]
All members of Shrek are Soul Sects.
[Zhu Zhu Qing]
Besides, this is a well-prepared team.
[Ma Hong Jun]
They’re difficult to deal with.
[Oscar]
There is a new face
[Ning Rong Rong]
in Shrek’s team,
she has been hiding her strength since then.
[Xiao Wu]
Is she the trump of Shrek?
[Tang San]
Tang San, as a soul master of Control Branch,
stands at the second row.
He’s still being prudent as usual.
Let’s look at
Xing Luo Imperial School’s information.
Dai Wei Si, captain of Xing Luo Imperial School
has reached Level 49.
[Da Wei Si]
Just one more step to be a Soul King.
Dai Wei Si and Zhu Zhu Yun
as the strongest members of the team
[Zhu Zhu Yun]
stand in the first row. What an aggressive aura.
Are they going to defeat Shrek
with their advanced soul power?
[Dong Hui]           [Yang Ming Ming]
Besides,
in the team,
two members whose soul powers
ranked the third and fourth
[Tang Hong Ning]
is similar to Dai Mu Bai,
the strongest soul power in Shrek.
[Ying Wei]
In Xing Luo Imperial School’s formation,
they stand in three rows.
Constructive for attacking and defence.
It seems like they have full confidence.
Are you looking forward to
this exciting match?
I hereby announce
Shrek School versus
Xing Luo Imperial School,
Start
now.
[Next Episode]
Dai Mu Bai and Dai Wei Si,
Zhu Zhu Qing and Zhu Zhu Yun,
have the same Martial Souls?
We’ll deal with Dai Wei Si and Zhu Zhu Yun.
Mu Bai, it’s been a long time.
Today, I’ll teach you a lesson.
Let’s duel first.
I’ll settle you then.
Strategy adjustment.
We’ve underestimated them.
Seven Devils Riot.
Ghost Shadow Doppelganger.
White Tiger Obliterate Spirit.
Phoenix Lava Dash.
Tempestuous Waters.
Invincible Golden Shield.
Nether Fantasy.
The assassin was indeed you.
Which occasion are you talking about?
Stop resisting. You’re the next.