♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Forget about your sausage,
Big Sausage Uncle.
What Big Sausage Uncle?
I’ll shave my beard tomorrow.
Why did you break up with you?
Stop!
I’ll show you what is actual strength.
Is there such a fat phoenix?
I think he looks more like a chicken.
Who are you calling a chicken?
Let me do it.
How is it, Fatty? You want to fight again?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 17]
Little Rabbit, come on!
Stop fighting.
Hong Jun is a good person.
But we don’t suit each other,
so we had to break up.
You all may leave, I’ll talk to him.
Don’t mind my business, go away!
Tang San.
Fatty.
What are you all doing here?
What are we doing?
Ask him!
This Fatty bullies a girl in broad daylight.
Xiao Wu,
I think you misunderstood.
I’ll do it myself.
Miss Cui Hua, you...
What’s going on?
Are you going to say it,
or I say it?
Go on.
Do you remember that I told you...
there are three students
including me in our school?
You mean...
Yes, Fatty is the third one,
and he entered the school latest
before you both did.
Even though I didn’t see what happened,
I still can guess it.
We can’t blame Fatty,
we can only blame his chicken.
Nonsense,
it’s not a chicken!
My Martial Soul is a phoenix!
Even if my parents’ are chickens,
mine is still a phoenix!
Haven’t you hear of
“golden phoenix among the bush”?
Phoenix?
Alright,
phoenix then.
Tang San,
Fatty’s Martial Soul looks weird.
The Dean said he has a Mutated Martial Soul.
Mutated Martial Soul?
Which two Martial Souls mutated?
I have no idea,
Let alone me,
not even Fatty himself.
People from his village...
get poultry-type Martial Souls
without attack ability.
Who knows,
when it’s his turn,
his Martial Soul is mutated,
and he was born with the ability of flame.
Fatty’s flame is strange too,
not only it’s always over-heated,
it’s also adhesive and hard to put off.
The Dean said
after his Martial Soul mutated,
it might really be a phoenix.
But...
his Martial Soul also has a flaw.
What is it?
It always loses control...
and harm the others near it.
Everything around will burn up
if he is being careless.
What’s that got to do with the break up?
You know nothing!
Fatty has been dumped a few times before.
This time, the girl has accepted him.
Fatty’s emotion is a little fluctuated,
especially in some aspects.
So, she can’t take this.
Nonsense,
when I lose control, all I have to do is to eat.
I don’t need anything else.
Yes,
control by eating.
That’s why people call you “Fire Chicken”.
It’s “Fire Phoenix”!
I can’t even believe this people actually exists.
I’m unlike you and Little Ao,
you both look like boy toys.
Don’t think that I don’t know you would go places...
and date with different girls every day.
Fatty,
you can’t say nonsense.
in front of them.
Don’t you always feel proud
and never feel humiliated?
What’s
wrong with you today?
Stop that.
if you spoil my reputation again
I won’t spare you.
What about our training in the future?
What else can we do?
Turn our anger into appetite.
Little San, I’m hungry.
Let’s go,
I’ll bring you to eat something.
You’d better
calm your fire down.
Why?
Are you going to tackle them?
Boss Dai,
even if you’re the boss,
you have to leave something for us, right?
Little Ao must be overslept again.
Let me introduce,
this fatty is another student from our school,
Ma Hong Jun.
and his Martial Soul is Chic...Phoenix!
Isn’t that Uncle Sausage?
Hi, Uncle Sausage!
Hey, Boss Dai, Fatty.
Good morning, everyone!
You overslept again?
Morning, Uncle Sausage.
Pretty girl, please call me
The Sausage Oscar.
Your beard...
Look at the new pretty girls.
If I don’t touch up a bit,
how would they ever look at me?
The Dean is here.
[Soul Land]
Little San, isn’t him the profiteer?
What profiteer?
He’s our Dean.
The founder of Shrek School,
Frander, the Four-Eyed Owl.
A Soul Saint of Level 78,
even stronger than Teacher Zhao.
He owns a flying-type beast soul,
that’s quite rare among the war soul masters.
I can’t believe he even said that...
he only accepts “monsters”, not the ordinary.
Luckily, he’s only at Level 78.
Uncle Sausage,
does our school have soul master
with highest soul level?
Please call me
The Sausage Oscar.
You mentioned Great Soul Land Master?
Great Soul Land Master
isn’t easily found here and there.
There are less than a hundred masters
who have earned this title.
They’re all supported by the Empire
and subordinate kingdoms.
And the Grand Soul Land Master,
there are only around ten in both Empires.
It’s not that easy to meet them.
Great then.
Xiao Wu, what’s wrong?
Dealing with this profiteer is insulting us.
If you don’t have enough money,
I can only collect 200 gold soul coins first.
You can pay the remaining later
with 10% interest.
Profiteer, why don’t you get lost?
It’s nothing.
Little San, do you think if he remembers us?
It has only been two days,
he surely still remembers it.
But since he’s the Dean,
I think he won’t care about it.
You’re wrong.
Dean Frander is a grudge-holding person.
Of course, it’s his strong point is
to justify his faults.
That’s bad.
I think he heard me.
I think I’m in trouble.
It’s great this year,
we have another four small monsters.
I, Frander, Dean of the Shrek School,
welcome you all on behalf of the school.
Later on, every one of you hand in
a hundred gold coins to Teacher Li.
For assisting-type soul master,
it’s dangerous once you’re
unprotected in battlefield.
Therefore,
you must learn how to flee.
Oscar.
Ning Rong Rong.
Twenty rounds...
starting now.
Forget about your lunch
if you can’t finish before that.
Yes!
Oscar leads the way.
Yes.
Go!
Mu Bai.
Dean.
Tell the newcomers about the school rules.
Alright, Dean.
Your first lesson will start at night.
You,
come with me alone.
How’s Grandmaster doing?
Master is fine.
His student?
No wonder...
Oh, right.
He asked me to pass this to you.
You old man!
Prove? Why must he prove it?
Since you’re his proof,
don’t disappoint him.
Tribe Chief,
Miss Ning has been selected
by the Shrek School.
How’s it in Shrek?
There are a few strong soul masters
in Shrek School,
and at least one Soul Saint.
I can’t enter for more investigation.
But their teacher has passed
your letter to the Dean.
Alright,
got it.
Feng Zhi,
aren’t you worried about Rong Rong alone outside?
Uncle Sword.
Can the Shrek School
teach her better than us?
Super Invincible Big Sausage!
Here.
Take it.
You won’t be able
to finish without eating it.
It’s ok. Eat it.
Well, I have super red bean bun.
Back off.
Uncle Sword.
Don’t worry,
The Shrek’s Dean is
the top master of the Golden Iron Triangle.
Rong Rong is going to be fine.
No way,
I’m going to fetch her.
I feel worried that she’s out there.
Uncle Sword,
you and Uncle Dragon
have spoiled her to much.
Now she doesn’t even listen to us.
Sending her to school
might change her.
Who said we spoiled Rong Rong?
I need to talk to him.
Uncle Sword,
you have to listen to me this time.
Let our devil girl gain
some experience out there.
We can’t let her do whatever she wants to do.
Hmph.
You are to blame
if anything happens to her.
[Next episode]
Frander, who do you think you are?
Since you look down at this place,
then please leave.
How dare you, Frander!
Depart. To the Soul Arena.