♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Your fire-resistance Blue Silver Plant is useless to me.
Ghostly Trace.
Tang San has defeated six members
from Chi Huo School continuously.
No matter what, I must win.
Rings Fusion.
No!
Huo Wu, no.
She’s going to kill herself
along with the opponent.
Chi Huo School will not allow
anyone to damage its honor.
Face your first defeat.
He’d better not join the battles.
Or else it will be bad if his wound bleeds again.
Why are you here? Go away.
We’re here to visit Tang San
and express our gratitude.
Leave here at once.
Or else, don’t blame us for being rude.
I’m here to thank Tang San for saving my life.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 86]
The winner is, Shrek School.
[School of Florals vs. Shrek School]
Shrek School’s next participant is
[Mu Yun Teng vs. Tai long]
Supreme Orangutan, Tai Long.
Hopefully, you can hold on longer
than your teammates.
School of Florals has won two rounds in a row.
- Can they defeat Shrek this time?
- Huang Yuan and Jing Ling have lost.
- We shall wait and see.
- Did you notice?
They’re all soul masters of Controlling Branch.
They’ve only sent three people
at most for the previous matches.
School of Florals is really one of a kind.
Is it about their Martial Souls?
Their Martial Souls are normal.
But these normal plant Martial Souls...
- Third round, starts now.
- can maintain their victories.
But why?
The point is to control.
There is no gorgeous soul skill or fierce attack.
But they can control their opponents.
Even if their levels are lower
than their opponent,
they can still restrain their power.
Even the strongest
soul master can’t continuous this kind of fight.
Moreover,
they have three soul masters
above Level 40 of Controlling Branch.
Third round, School of Florals won.
Three loses in a row!
Is this still Shrek?
Not that easy.
This is the sixth day.
The previous five matches,
Shrek only sent two people per match.
Maybe,
they’re just being restrained
by their opponents today.
As long as Tang San
from Controlling Branch isn’t here,
soul masters of Controlling Branch
can restrain other soul masters.
It’s highly probable that we’ll win.
Shrek School isn’t that good after all.
Do you know what a tactic is?
It’s individual in the Qualifying rounds,
but the key to success is teamwork.
To let one member to remain
on the arena till the end.
This is Grandmaster’s motive.
Watch me.
Did you see how she attacks?
This is your first time on the arena.
Fatty, come on.
He...
is also a member of Shrek School?
Is there information about him?
Seems like Shrek has given up on this round.
They’re either to train
their Soul Honor or a newbie.
It’s really despicable to have all control.
He’s never been on the arena.
Is he from some clan
who uses relation
to get him in to gain experience?
If so, it’s disrespectful to the tournament.
Little Fatty, my vines are very fast.
You’d better go down.
What if I hurt you?
Your target is to defeat all of them.
However, my teacher sent me up.
If I go down like this, I’ll get punished.
Why not...
young lady,
you beat me down?
But please be gentle.
No problem,
I won’t bully a...
Fatty...
This Fatty is a Soul Sect?
Shrek School’s fourth participant
is a Level 41 Soul Sect
of Storm Attack Branch.
This participant has never been
on the arena before.
What surprise will he show us?
[Fire Phoenix]
Ultimate Fire Element Martial Soul.
Fourth soul skill,
Vines Fortress.
Since this kid ate the Cockscomb Phoenix Flower,
- his Phoenix power has been purified.
- Save...
- His explosiveness is the strongest among them,
- Save me!
We admit defeat for this round.
Fourth round, Shrek School won.
How can a Soul Sect who has never
been on the arena before,
is a fire element which
restricts the plant Martial Soul?
This is too easy.
If she’s in her best condition,
maybe she can hold on longer,
but now...
This is Martial Soul restraint.
Five wins already, Shrek School is indeed strong.
Your opponent for this round, is me.
[School of Florals vs. Shrek School]
School of Florals’s sixth participant is
their leader.
A Level 44 Soul Sect
of Controlling Branch.
This level is considered as the top
among the participants.
During the qualifying rounds,
she has performed well.
She has won for countless times.
Among them,
there are Fire Element
Martial Soul soul masters as well.
Too bad! My Fiery Thorns are resistant to fire.
Too bad!
My Blue Silver Plant
is fire resistant.
No wonder that Huo Wu keeps on targeting you.
It’s really annoying listening to this.
Huo Wu, where are you going?
You’re injured, you should rest.
None of your business.
[Soul Land]
Third soul skill, The City of Thorns.
Against the Ultimate Fire Element Martial Soul,
The fire resistant power
of Fiery Thorns has decreased.
But as long as she holds on longer,
she can defeat the soul master
of Storm Attack Branch.
Second soul skill, Thorns Bound.
Third soul skill, Flying Phoenix.
Good.
Ma Hong Jun
has chosen a position
that is hard to avoid attacks.
Does he
try to directly face his opponent’s attack?
Fourth soul skill,
Thorns Shower.
His Martial Soul is powerful,
but he lacks experience.
Yao Zi is luring him to the air.
Shrek School almost has another
monster who can defeat six.
Xiao Gang, is he okay?
Second soul skill, Firing Bathing Phoenix.
Fire has different functions.
Some can only light up the wood,
yet some can melt the steel.
If his fire can’t restrain Fiery Thorns,
then his Fire Phoenix Martial Soul
is not the ultimate one.
Fourth soul skill, Phoenix Strike.
What?
Fatty, please show some mercy.
Fortunately, Ma Hong Jun has stopped
his second attack of Phoenix Strike,
Phoenix Lava Dash.
Or else the opponent will either die
or be severely injured.
Her thorns have blocked her retreat.
She trapped herself.
Six wins in a row.
Shrek School has again recorded six wins in a row.
School of Florals has one last member.
Can she stop Shrek School?
Fortunately, she’s just unconscious.
But his soul skill’s power is
greater than this for sure.
Last round,
we admit our defeat.
School of Florals has given up
for the last round.
The winner of this qualifying round is
Shrek School.
They’ve won seven times in a row.
Fatty,
well done!
Of course, Boss Dai.
It is enjoyable to win seven times in a row.
Okay,
we can leave now.
Tang San.
Miss Huo Wu,
what’s up?
Tang San,
I would like to talk to you.
Can’t you say it here?
I want to talk
to you in private.
Go,
you can go back later.
Grandmaster,
didn’t she hurt Tang San enough?
Child,
trust
is the foundation of a relationship.
You must believe...
what is yours,
will always be yours.
Today, Huo Wu spoke to me again.
Tang San.
Why is Huo Wu with him?
Are you okay now?
I’ve recovered.
That’s great.
You called me out
just to ask about this?
You don’t want to talk to me then?
Not really.
I just don’t know what to talk about between us.
After all,
we’re opponents.
Why are you so dumb?
Are you normal?
Shrek School is famous for monsters.
If there’s nothing else, I’ll go first.
You.
Wait,
are you that impatient with me?
You can leave,
but answer my question first.
Go on.
That day,
why did you save me?
Why did you use your body to resist the strike?
That strike was to attack you.
This is your question?
And also the reason you called me over?
Yes.
We’re opponents,
but not enemies.
You attacked me to win.
We didn’t have any deep grudges.
Your death will elevate
the conflict between our schools.
If I endured that strike,
I wouldn’t have any danger.
That’s it?
Yes.
Tang San.
Be careful.
[Next Episode]
The last three rounds will be very tough.
Their overall strength is
higher than Chi Huo School.
They’re no doubt the strongest team.
The flying ability of Lei Tian
can restrain soul masters who attack close.
Third soul skill, Wings of Lightning.
What do you mean?
With that person, how is this a coincidence?
I shall leave now.
You can’t run away from this.
What should we do?
Fourth soul skill, Lightning Eagle.
Using first soul skill to
resist my fourth soul skill?
You’re belittling me.
Don’t stop me.
I want to report that Shrek School
has attempted a murder.