[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Soul Land]
[Episode 1]
Nineteen voices were heard when the stone fell in deep streams,
an additional level compared to hell.
So here’s the Devil May Cry.
I don’t know if Tang San is down there
and the stone fell.
What’s the difference?
It’s Shadowless Needle from the Second Elder.
Purple Demon Eye! What a talented kid.
This is the Ghostly Trace.
Let’s see how’s he going to dodge this.
Freezy-jade like and invincible, it’s the Xuan Yu Hand.
Did he just block my Pear Blossom Shower
with his bare hands?
How dare he! All of you, attack.
Don’t ever let him go!
He’s heading to the Devil May Cry. After him!
Finally, this day has come.
Tang San, that’s enough.
Just give up.
I’m aware that entering inner clan secretly...
and learning its martial arts is unforgivable...
and impermissible.
But I swear...
that I’ve never leaked any of what I’ve learned.
I don’t say this...
to get your forgiveness,
but I wish you all know...
that I never forget my roots.
I didn’t, and I won’t.
Everything I have was given by the Tang Clan.
Be it my life or abilities,
they’re all given by the Tang Clan.
He even made the ultimate hidden weapon of the Tang Clan.
No matter at what time,
I’ll always belong to the Tang Clan, even if I’m dead.
I know you don’t allow...
the body of an outer disciple who broke the rules to stay in the clan.
If that so,
let my remains spread over Ba Shu.
He even learnt the greatest inner martial arts in Xuan Tian Records.
I’ll leave naked as I came.
Tang’s Lotus of Buddha’s Rage would be my final present for the clan.
Now, besides my own body,
I won’t bring anything belonged to Tang Clan with me.
The secret books are all in the first block in my room door.
I give everything now
back to Tang Sect.
Wait!
Tang San, why did you have to do this?
You’ve given us too many surprises.
Brother, why do you have to be grief over a traitor?
Who said he’s a traitor?
Have you seen a traitor who still stayed after learning our greatest power?
Have you seen a traitor who would die to prove his sincerity?
Have you seen a traitor who had the greatest weapon to kill us...
but ended up giving it as a gift to our clan?
Tang San isn’t a traitor,
he’s the most excellent genius we ever had for two hundred years.
However, he secretly learnt our...
If you can make the Tang’s Lotus of Buddha’s Rage,
I can close one eye on whatever you steal.
You were wrong, so was I.
Just right before this,
the chance of the clan’s glory has slipped away in front of us!
Say no more, pass my order!
All members, out you go!
Look for Tang San around Devil May Cry.
I want to see his body unless he’s alive.
From now on,
Tang San will be my inner disciple.
If he’s alive,
he’ll be my sole successor of the Chief.
Yes, Chief.
- Taking her away? Over my dead body.
- Let them go.
- I’ll follow you all.
- No!
You may try if you still can stand up.
Don’t cause any more trouble, let’s end this earlier.
Don’t leave me!
Seventeen, eighteen, nineteen...
Where’s this?
[Soul Land]
I’ve been here after that day...
and become an infant.
I practiced the Xuan Tian Records again but am now in a bottleneck.
This world is called Soul Land.
When everyone grows up,
there’ll be an awaken ability,
called Martial Soul.
Failed again.
I still can’t pass through
the first level of the Xuan Tian Strike.
It has been this for three months.
Why is that so?
Even the Purple Demon Eye which depends on...
Purple Air from East, it’s improving.
Yet, my Xuan Tian Strike hasn’t broken the bottleneck.
Same goes to my Xuan Yu Hand.
When I trained this in my past life,
I never encountered this before.
There’re nine levels for Xuan Tian Strike.
Why is it so troublesome in the first level?
Could it be...
this world is different from the previous one?
It’s time to go back.
Old Man Li, are we going to Nuoding City again?
That’s right.
I have to deliver the order I got yesterday.
I’m so envious of you.
What for?
There are three hundred families in Soul Saint Village.
Which of our grains and vegetables ever had bad sales?
You’re right.
There was even a Soul Saint from our village before this.
Soul Saint?
What does it have to do with the sale of the villagers?
It’s because of the strategic place of Nuoding City...
in between the Tian Dou and Xing Luo Empires.
Traders just come and go all the while.
Or else, to whom should we sell our vegetables to?
You’d better lower down your voice...
in case the village head hears it.
Just let him be.
The Soul Saint incident has happened over 100 years ago,
yet he’s still mumbling it.
The village head is here.
Where?
Hurry up and send them. Stop mumbling every day.
- Yes.
Dad, let’s eat.
Little San, Grandpa is here.
Go, come back before lunchtime.
I’m six years old and going to be awakened today.
They say Martial Soul can be anything,
what would mine be then?
Kids,
this is the handprint left by the Soul Saint in our village.
It represents the glory of our village!
♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine, hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪