♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Were you fighting someone for a woman?
That’s why you were hit, right?
What are you saying?
I was just helping someone
in need of justice.
But if it’s to punish the evil,
and defend peace,
it shouldn’t be refused.
Where are you creeping to?
His Martial Soul looks like two claws.
They are pitch black.
That’s so disgusting.
Hello, little girl.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 35]
Uncle, where is the candy shop?
It’s dark here. I’m a little scared.
Little girl, don’t be afraid. I’ll protect you.
Uncle, you should protect yourself.
Where are you running to?
It’s Xiao Wu’s Charm and her third soul skill, Teleport.
It seems we don’t have to be worried.
Bu Le can’t escape her Eight Flinging.
What is Eight Flinging?
That’s the most brutal flinging skill
of Xiao Wu’s Rou skill,
flinging for 8 times continuously.
One can barely fight back
after the first flinging.
Have a look.
A soul master of strength type may have a chance.
But Bu Le is from Controlling Branch.
His Martial Soul couldn’t be released. He can only...
First soul skill, Arched Body.
You evil rotter.
You took advantage of a young lady.
Let me give you a lesson
with my Flinging of Circling Soaring.
Eight Flinging is done.
Xiao Wu, could you have killed him?
Killing him would make my hands dirty.
But he needs to recover for 3 months.
We said we would punish the evil together.
You have flung him to this condition,
what shall we do then?
However, Xiao Wu, your Eight Flinging
is really mighty.
The thing is, her Teleport is ridiculously good.
Once she’s 5 meters away from the someone,
that one can’t escape.
Furthermore, Xiao Wu,
you can use your Arched Body consecutively?
Don’t you need to recharge
your soul power in between?
Back then, yes.
But since I’ve achieved Level 30,
I can use it consecutively.
Even if I have to recharge soul power,
the gap between every Arched Body
would be enough.
My Eight Flinging doesn’t work
on soul masters of strength type.
But to a soul master
of Controlling Branch like him,
if I can attack him secretly, he would suffer.
Xiao Wu.
You shouldn’t lure an enemy in that way.
That’s too dangerous.
Alright now. Let’s go.
The fellow can’t do any harm for a while.
We’ve punished the evil, haven’t we?
Actually, it’s not good that we do this.
Not good? Little San, are you being softhearted?
I have a way to punish such a villain.
Hey, Xiao Gang.
Although I don’t want to interrupt you
in teaching those little monsters,
I’m sorry to tell you that
you have used up the money our school had.
The tuition fee that the students paid
was supposed to be enough for a year.
But your teaching method is too different.
Besides the increase in food expense,
the herbs mixed in food
and bath every day are very expensive.
In just three months,
the finance is already collapsing.
I got it.
You got it? We have to figure out a way.
After these few days,
I’ll guide them to
the second phase of the training.
Don’t you worry about this.
The expense problem will be solved by then.
If the kids aren’t so excellent,
I wouldn’t want to maintain this anymore.
Those time we traveled around
Soul Land was the best.
Perhaps,
one day, we’ll resume the happiness.
Being wretched is also a crime. He knows himself.
[Confession Letter]
Finally, someone has revenged for us.
He who hurt others finally got hurt by himself.
Bu Le promised to take us to have some fun.
Until now, he hasn’t shown up.
Would he take it all for himself?
This fellow insisted on taking action alone.
Now we have to look for
him everywhere. That bastard.
What’s going on there?
Isn’t that Bu Le?
Old Goose, Tian Ya, save me!
Turns out he’s a Soul King. Run!
Confession letter. I, Bu Le,
though being a soul master,
am notorious as a ruffian.
I’ve committed an endless crimes,
but they can be categorized into two.
I’m born wretched, immoral and unkind.
I’m lawless and very violent.
There’s karma. All the ruffians
are advised to take me as an example.
Change bad habits to be a good person.
Bu Le, what happened to you?
All your limbs are dislocated.
Five ribs are broken.
Three fractures at your cervical vertebrae.
What a swift and fierce move.
I want to revenge!
I want them to suffer worse than being dead.
[Soul Land]
For the past three months,
with the help and supervision of all teachers,
you have built your bodies a little.
However, to be an excellent soul master,
this is still far from enough.
Hence, starting from today,
I’ll start the phase-two training.
I heard it from Frander
you had been to Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
That place
will be the place
that you learn in the coming time.
This training has no time limitation.
As soon as you get a silver soul badge,
your training will be done.
If you have the capability,
the income you’ll get from the soul arena
will be very handsome.
Joining the soul battle
seems to be relaxing than the training.
However, besides getting
a silver soul badge in a single battle,
you have to get a silver
soul badge in the group battle.
You’ll battle as Shrek Seven Devils.
Group battle can help everyone collect points
and contribute points to the group.
This is what double soul fight lacks.
Of course, who wants to progress faster,
may form a team to join the double soul battle.
You have to remember
a few restrictions beforehand.
First, don’t reveal your appearance and your name
during the soul battle,
always fighting with mask and nickname.
Second, including Tang San,
no one is allowed to use hidden weapons.
Third, whether to win or lose,
each one of you has to fight twice a day.
Grandmaster, Rong Rong and I are
soul masters of Assisting Branch.
Do we have to get a silver soul badge as well?
Or you may train as before
until everyone else gets their badges.
Grandmaster.
I suddenly realize your decision
to have us compete in the soul arena
to gain experience is very wise.
I’ll take back my words.
Okay. If there’s no question, you may depart now.
The competitions in the soul arena
are separated to singles, doubles
and group battle which starts the latest.
You may team up freely.
But you must join a group battle and a single
or a double battle every day.
I wouldn’t disagree,
if you want to join three battles.
The term is,
that you must know your soul power well.
Boss Dai, let’s join a double soul battle together.
My assisting capability may help you.
Or else,
I wouldn’t know how I can earn points
to get a silver soul badge.
Alright then.
Brother San, are you willing to help me?
But Xiao Wu and I have formed the San Woo.
Rong Rong, what about me?
You? Forget about it.
No. I suggest that you should form
a team with Ma Hong Jun.
Why?
In a double soul battle,
when one of the soul masters
achieves a higher level,
you have to join a battle of higher level too.
That means,
when you team up with Little San,
you’ll face opponents at Level 30 and above.
Your chance of winning will decrease.
While Hong Jun is at Level 28,
your team will face opponents within your range.
Hong Jun’s Martial Soul is superior.
In addition to your assistance,
the winning chance is 70% and above.
Little Sister, let’s team up.
Okay.
Rong Rong, this is discrimination. I disagree.
Fourth Brother, since you’re so strong,
you’ll win even if you fight alone. Right?
You can decide how to join the soul battle.
I have one more thing for you.
This is for you.
Wear it when you’re battling.
Talk fewer words on the stage.
Try not to reveal your age to the opponents.
During the group battle,
your team name will be Shrek Seven Devils.
In the single soul battle,
I’ve figured out nicknames for each one of you.
Use the nickname to register.
So your real name will not appear at the soul area.
What are our nicknames?
Mu Bai shall use his own nickname,
Evil Eyes White Tiger.
Evil Eyes White Tiger, Dai Mu Bai.
You’ll still be The Sausage Seller.
The Sausage Seller, Oscar.
Little San shall be called Thousand Hands Silver Plant.
What do you think?
This isn’t good. It’s not cool at all.
Silver Plant sounds horrible.
What should he be called then?
Little San may look well-behaved.
But when he’s angry,
he’s more murderous than anyone of us.
What about Thousand Hands Asura?
What do you think?
Master, you shall decide.
Then you shall be called Thousand Hands Asura.
Hong Jun, I’ve thought up a nickname for you.
You’ll be called Evil Phoenix.
This is good. Thank you, Grandmaster.
Thousand Hands Asura, Tang San.
Evil Phoenix, Ma Hong Jun.
Grandmaster, what am I called then?
You have to give me a nice name.
You use Rou Skill. You’re very flexible.
In addition to your rabbit Martial Soul
and Charm skill,
what about Flexible Charming Bunny?
Flexible Charming Bunny, Xiao Wu.
That doesn’t sound too bad.
Rong Rong’s Martial Soul is Qibao Amber Pagoda.
Nothing describes you better than Qibao Amber.
As for Zhu Qing,
her Martial Soul is the best name for her.
Cat of Netherworld.
Qibao Amber, Ning Rong Rong.
Cat of Netherworld, Zhu Zhu Qing.
[Next Episode]
Welcome to Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
Next up, we shall welcome
the most-awaited climax battle.
Rip them apart.
Young lady, you have such a nice figure.
Get lost.
She told you to get lost.
I would like to see who’s going to be injured.
Countdown! Five, four, three, two, one.