♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] Welcome to
the twelfth preliminary.
Seven Shura Fantasy!
Today, you’ll be dead!
Reincarnate endlessly in this painful abyss!
Purple Demon Eye.
If the lie is seen,
how would the person who lied be punished?
You really don’t know anything, right?
Dean, you’re saying that...
Call the students
who participated in the contest!
I want to interrogate every one of them.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 78]
Call the students
who participated in the contest!
I want to interrogate every one of them.
No way. These kids are badly injured.
If they weren’t rescued immediately,
I’m afraid their entire soul master’s
career will be affected.
Do you want to spoil
their soul master’s career
because of an interrogation?
Since there are six injured out of seven,
wasn’t there one still standing?
He was Tang San, right?
Call him.
The...
Salas is so determined to make it hard to Shrek.
All right. Er Long, get Tang San here.
Let Grandmaster get some desserts
from our school here too.
Okay.
How can our school have money
for dessert? Could it be...
Lords, you don’t know.
This time, Shrek School’s students
are seriously injured.
I’m afraid we can’t participate for
the coming preliminary.
Are the casualties of Shrek School so serious?
Even they’re serious,
they wouldn’t become idiots like Cang Hui School.
As the organizing committee,
I have a reason to doubt Shrek School
for maliciously aiming at Cang Hui School.
How can you jump to conclusions?
You haven’t understood the truth yet.
You’re so eager to charge Shrek School?
You asked for it!
Salas!
Humph!
Little San, how do you feel?
Dean, are you looking for me?
They are the organizing committees
of the contest.
You explain it to them
what has happened during the battle
with Cang Hui School?
Shrek! Goodbye.
Purple Demon Eye.
My body can’t move!
Fantasy is a lie to the vision.
If the lie is seen,
how would the person who lied be punished?
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
Boss Dai and others, I’m sorry.
Facing with Seven In One Fusion Skill,
we must be seriously injured.
I don’t know.
What? You don’t know?
I couldn’t see things clearly at that time.
I had to release soul skills at random.
When I could see clearly,
they had already fallen to the ground.
How dare you...
What? You don’t know?
How could you not know?
At that time, there were only you and them.
Dean, I really didn’t know.
Maybe Cang Hui’s students were
backfired by their own soul skills
and lost their mind.
Enough!
Stop echoing and supporting each other!
Tang San! You refuse to be interrogated!
Shrek School is suspected of covering up a crime!
I announce
Shrek School is removed from this contest!
Lord, you’re arbitrary. I’m afraid
it doesn’t conform to the rules.
This is my authority!
Pope token?
Salas. You’re not worth being
the Martial Soul Temple Platinum Chief.
Greetings to you, Elder.
One who has this token, just like the Pope is here.
No wonder Salas is so respectful.
Elder, please take it back.
Elder, I acted rashly.
We’ll exempt this interrogation.
We’re leaving.
Chief, don’t go in a hurry.
Come and try some of our desserts.
That is a well-known specialty of our school.
Chief!
I’m leaving too.
I am sorry I cannot escort you farther.
Yu Xiao Gang!
How dare you still have contact
with that woman!
No.
Er Long, you’ve misunderstood.
Misunderstood? That woman
even gave you the Pope token!
What is the misunderstanding?
The Pope token was not given by her.
Who else?
Little San’s father gave it to me.
Little San’s father?
The Grand Soul Land Master, Hao Tian.
[Soul Land]
Twenty-seven rounds of the preliminary
are coming to an end.
Today is the last match between
Shrek School and Tian Shui School.
It’s said that Shrek School had
2 loses out of 26 matches.
Tian Shui School had
3 loses out of 26 matches.
Let’s hurry and have a look.
Hasn’t that Shrek School lost before?
Why did they lose 2 matches?
Last time, it’s an internecine game
between Shrek and Cang Hui.
Cang Hui’s team members became idiots.
Shrek’s team members had also
injured badly and gave up two games.
My God! Cang Hui School is so pitiful!
Exactly. Soul skills have no eyes on the field.
Let’s go. It’s going to start.
Brother Tang. Today is the last game.
You have to do your best.
Why did he come to see us
before every match?
Since Senior Feng is so anticipated
to meet us in the finals,
then you’d better not lose.
So, you’re saying that
Shrek School’s goal is the champion.
Shen Feng School doesn’t want it?
Of course not.
Who wants to confront
those from Martial Soul Hall?
Anyways, we just pray not to meet them so soon.
I’ll go first.
Feng Xiao Tian must have
known something.
Master has told me before.
Martial Soul Hall is much more powerful
than anyone expected.
Look. Dai Mu Bai from Shrek School
is so handsome.
Don’t you be too obsessed with him
until you throw the match.
Okay. Stop the nonsense.
Shrek School is a powerful rival.
We must do our best till the end, understand?
Yes, Captain.
Although the match is going to end
after one more round,
the actually qualified teams
have already been determined
according to the match situation.
The sequence is
Lei Ting School,
Shen Feng School,
Shrek School,
Chi Huo School and Tian Shui School.
This is the last game for the preliminary.
We couldn’t get the first place,
But we must at least get into the top three.
We must not lose to Tian Shui School.
It’s said that Tian Shui School has all girls.
How can we fight?
Don’t ever look down on Tian Shui School.
Tian Shui is the veteran strong team.
They beat Chi Huo School in the previous battle.
You must know that Chi Huo defeated
Shen Feng at the second place.
Teacher Qin is right.
Tian Shui School must not easy to be defeated.
But Shrek School never fears any enemy.
That’s right. Shrek never fears any enemy.
Shrek! Must win!
Finally, we’ve come to the
last match of the preliminary.
Let’s welcome teams from Shrek School
and Tian Shui to enter the field.
The formations of both teams are quite similar.
How big is the gap in the data?
First, let’s look at Tian Shui School.
Tian Shui School team captain, Shui Bing Er.
Controlling Branch War Soul Sect at Level 43.
She led Tian Shui School
to enter the top five of the preliminary.
What kind of wonderful performance
will there be today?
Other than the captain,
Tian Shui School has also sent
another two Soul Sects.
Their strength shouldn’t be
underestimated either.
The opponent has also sent
three Soul Sects.
Moreover, this captain is also
a soul master of the Controlling Branch.
I’m afraid Little San has met his opponent.
Besides, four Soul Honors
owned ferocious Martial Souls.
Tian Shui School’s determination
to win is shown here.
What kind of lineup did Shrek School send?
Shrek School’s Captain, Dai Mu Bai.
The strength is quite powerful.
Vice Captain, Tang San.
Today, he meets a soul master of
Controlling Branch, who has a higher level.
Can he still win as always?
It’s really surprising.
Shrek School chooses the same formation
as the first round of preliminaries.
Do they also
prepare to defeat their opponent
in one minute this time?
The two other Soul Sects
didn’t participate at all for this time.
Are they looking down on us?
Which team will win
and get the third place
to enter the qualifying rounds?
Both teams get ready!
Start!
[Next Episode]
At least, buy some time for Little San.
It’s still early to be happy.
Shui Bing Er’s skill seems to have restricted Little San.
It’s bad! It’s Martial Soul Fusion Skill!
Little San, can you resist it?
But I can’t be defeated.