♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
King of Forest, Titan Giant Ape...
is like the overlord of soul beasts.
It has the same wisdom as human.
Its strength, speed, attack and defense...
are almost flawless.
No, let go of Xiao Wu.
Little rascal, come back!
Faster, even faster.
No.
Brother.
Sorry, everyone.
I have to look for Xiao Wu.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 25]
It’s Human Faced Demon Spider.
The nightmare of small soul beasts.
Swallowing the existence of life.
The common enemy of every soul beast.
A scarily evil slayer.
Oh, no.
Human Faced Demon Spider
appears at this moment.
Master once mentioned,
it has a hard shell and moves fast,
and its venomous legs are penetrative.
The scariest thing is...
the spider web that it spits.
Its venom can kill most soul beasts.
This fellow seems to be a millennium one.
Human Faced Demon Spider is one
of the targets of your third soul ring.
But it’s also the hardest to obtain.
So don’t force yourself.
Weird.
The first thing this spider does to its prey
is spitting spider web.
It can do it three times a day.
Yet this fellow is...
only attacking with its legs.
Could it has used up its quota?
My soul power
can’t defeat a fit Human Faced Demon Spider.
But when it’s injured,
as long as I can absorb its soul ring,
my body condition will recover completely.
Xiao Wu is still waiting for me.
Blue Silver Plant.
Intertwine.
Now it is the time.
Blue Silver Plant can’t control it for too long.
I have to solve this as soon as possible.
Besides,
Blue Silver Plant’s paralyzing effect...
is useless against it.
It is venomous itself.
This is...
What a strong venom.
Blue Silver Plant is being corroded.
It can’t take any longer.
This is not good.
So fast.
Could it be...
That’s indeed its weak point.
Goodbye.
This is...
It seems you’re fine now.
This voice...
is...
I’m back?
Tang San,
outrageous!
How can you be so rude to Chief?
Please,
forgive me, Chief. I...
Second Brother.
Could you have forgotten...
that I’ve said,
if he came back alive,
he would be my sole successor?
Let alone...
Tang San is badly injured,
he was finally saved.
Should he be exhausted by your red tapes?
Well.
You’re right.
Chief,
I...
Devil May Cry was dangerous.
You were fortunate.
In addition to your Xuan Tian Strike,
you’re able to survive.
God blesses the Tang Clan.
How was it?
Are you feeling bad?
I feel like
there’s something...
important that I need to do.
However,
I can’t recall it.
Don’t think about it then.
You should rest in Tang Clan.
Everything will be better.
I didn’t discover your talent in time,
that’s why you had to suffer.
That was really my sin.
I don’t dare to blame you.
I, Tang San,
only wishes to live for Tang Clan
and die for it as well.
I’ll not
disappoint Tang Clan.
Good.
Remember your words.
Have a good rest.
There are a lot to do.
Second Elder and I will leave now.
Okay.
Who are they?
[Soul Land]
Hello, Senior San.
Don’t call me that.
You’re an inner disciple.
I...
Don’t regard yourself as an outsider.
Since you’re saved,
The Elder has abolished the rule
of inner and outer disciples.
The ranking depends
on the sequence of enrollment.
Really?
But...
Isn’t this breaking the rules?
No, Senior San.
You really shouldn’t call me Senior San.
It sounds weird.
Why don’t you
call me Brother San?
Senior San, what’s going on?
I recall...
Brother.
I recalled something...
What did you recall?
Xiao Wu,
Master,
and...
This is not Tang Clan.
I want to go back.
Tang San,
what are you doing?
Chief.
Tang San,
no matter how Tang Clan did you wrong,
I’ve decided to make up for you.
Can’t you forget about the resentment?
Yes,
I can’t forget it.
That’s why I’m seeing you,
seeing Tang Clan
and being here again.
What are you talking about?
I think the past is too important.
I’ve lived here for more than 20 years.
Everything here has imprinted in my mind.
It’s hard
to forget it.
But
I have to move on.
I don’t belong to this world.
In another place,
someone is waiting for me to rescue her.
Xiao Wu,
I’m coming.
Turns out it has neurotic venom...
which causes syncope.
Activate...
the inner power of Xuan Tian Strike.
Indeed.
The spider values its abdominal eyes.
However,
with the spider’s alertness,
the hidden weapon can hardly injure it.
I’ll stake all I have.
Although I don’t have the soul ring
of Iron’s Brothers,
I have the skill of hidden weapon.
Perhaps...
Second soul skill has no complimentary skill,
but its weight increases with Martial Soul.
There’s only one opportunity.
Now.
You’re finally dead.
Although my strength is weak,
when I pour in all my soul power,
this little hammer
can weight tonnes.
It’s enough to elevate you
to expose your vulnerability.
And then I killed you with hidden weapons.
Absorbing its soul ring is dangerous.
I have to squeeze out the venom quickly.
No.
My Demon Spider.
Who did this?
What a coincidence.
I killed it.
You?
You again.
You’re Tang San?
Do you know...
Human Faced Demon Spider is
rarer than Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent?
In order to hunt this Demon Spider,
we have been chasing it for a whole day.
If it weren’t for the annoying spider web,
the soul ring would be obtained by our Yi Ran.
I get what you mean.
But
I had to protect myself.
This Human Faced Demon Spider
appeared in front of me suddenly.
Should I give up my fate to it?
You mean,
you killed this Human Faced Demon Spider alone?
Thank you for depleting...
its three times web-spitting capability.
Grandpa,
please help me find justice.
I, Meng Shu, have been a soul master for years.
I’m not an unreasonable person.
In the face of Human Faced Demon Spider,
everyone would protect himself.
So it’s understandable that you killed it.
However,
you’ve interrupted my granddaughter
twice in getting her soul ring.
We can’t let it go easily.
Tang San,
you have two choices.
Although Godly Zhuge Crossbow
can’t injure the two of you,
Meng Yi Ran won’t be able to withstand it.
If you go too far,
then don’t blame me for using
your granddaughter as shield.
[Next Episode]
Since you want to die,
I’ll fulfill your dream.
What a strong fluctuation of soul power.