♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Grandmaster.
Tang Hao!
I wish to entrust Little San to you.
Please always remember that he is my son.
Xiao Wu, would you like to be my sister?
I’m just a peasant.
I can give you neither wealth nor power.
But I can give you my promise.
I’ll protect my younger sister forever.
I won’t let her get hurt.
Brother.
I don’t know what’s the Grandmaster thinking.
There are several intermediate schools
that want to recruit us unconditionally.
However, he kept asking you
to enroll in Shrek School....
which has no rank at all.
This room should belong to me, right?
Buddy, I think we came first.
So what?
Nothing. We just want you to get out.
I’ll give you a chance to get me out.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 11]
Please.
Very strong.
Great! Able to hold my punch!
You’re qualified to be my opponent!
To no avail to hit hard.
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
My body is being absorbed toward him.
Ghostly Trace.
So fast!
Ouch! Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
Oops!
Shall we continue?
Sure!
You did force me to use soul power.
I lost this battle.
However, how can I let it be
if I don’t battle once again?
White Tiger Shield Body.
Millennium soul ring.
Dai Mu Bai. White Tiger Martial Soul.
War Soul Master of Level 37. Please.
Tang San. Blue Silver Plant Martial Soul.
Tool Soul Master of Level 29. Please.
Blue Silver Plant.
Are you looking down on Blue Silver Plant?
Martial soul is wasted with a waste soul master.
You’re right!
Show me how peculiar your Blue Silver Plant is.
Inseparable.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Tang San. The attack power of a beast soul
is always stronger than a tool soul.
The power of your Blue Silver Plant
is beyond my expectation,
but it can’t trap me at all.
That’s not a must.
The Blue Silver Plant is poisonous.
While you launched strong soul skill
to break my intertwine,
the toxin has already penetrated into your body.
You might feel paralysis all over now.
You lost this battle.
What a great Blue Silver Plant.
If I have only two soul rings,
indeed I did lose.
But...
Just let me show you the skill
of my third soul ring!
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Is this the millennium soul ring?
The toughness of Blue Silver Plant
is indeed beyond my expectation.
Even my normal soul power can’t cut it all at once.
But I’m now using the skill of my third soul ring,
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
The White Tiger Vajra Transformation
can retain for half an hour.
In this half an hour,
the attribute of all aspects will be doubled.
With my soul power of Level 37...
and the strengthening of
White Tiger Vajra Transformation,
the toxin won’t hurt me.
Even you own subtle soul skill...
and great martial soul of controlling branch,
you’re still not my opponent.
This shows the great
differences of our strengths.
I think that we will meet again soon.
If there’s someone troubles on you...
in Shrek School,
you can tell them my name,
Evil Eyes White Tiger — Dai Mu Bai.
How did you know we’re going to Shrek School?
I’ll wait for you in Shrek.
Huh! This person is inexplicable!
He’s not a good guy.
Little San, when we get into Shrek School,
we don’t mingle with him.
I think this person is pretty good.
Although a bit cold on the surface,
he is straightforward.
What I see as bad cannot be mistaken.
You said he took two girls to rent a room at the hotel.
Still capable of what good deed?
What Evil-Eyes White Tiger?
I think it’s more like Lewd Tiger.
Xiao Wu, I find you understand more and more.
Of course.
Don’t forget that I was
the boss of Nuoding School.
I’m not going to evaluate
Dai Mu Bai’s personal preferences.
But about the battle just now,
he’s good at every aspect.
His strength is beyond us,
but he didn’t bully us.
He shows his intention on
taking care of us before he left.
Take care of us?
Oh, yes! He did mention that he lost.
What does it mean?
Him? If I got it right,
he is also a combative person.
What does it mean?
Nothing. Let’s check in first.
Brother, if you lost the battle just now,
would we really get out of here?
Even so, I would be the only one who leaves.
That’s why I didn’t allow you to get involved.
He said it right. One soul ring apart...
did keep an enormous difference
between our strengths.
When he used
White Tiger Vajra Transformation,
we’re still not his opponent
even we joined hand together.
Don’t you worry.
If he insisted on getting you out,
I’d fight against him deadly.
If I got to fight against him again,
I have 70% certainty to put him to death.
Fight against him deadly?
This hotel...
It seems to be exclusively for couples on dates.
It doesn’t matter to stay here.
[Soul Land]
Why didn’t you... move forward?
It seems that I got it right.
No wonder Dai Mubai wants to bring a girl here.
Xiao Wu, if don’t like it,
I’ll ask the waiter to take away these flowers.
Brother, how stupid you are!
There isn’t any girl who dislikes roses.
If you’re doing this, how can you get your wife then?
It’s still too early to talk about this now.
This room is really well decorated.
I realize that I’ve fallen in love with this place.
Brother, can we come here again in the future?
How good is it? We are siblings.
What good is it to come to this place?
We have a long journey.
Let’s have a rest.
Xiao Wu, I think it’s a mistake to
listen to you and come here.
You rest here. I’ll rest on the sofa there.
The golden light ray seems to be radon.
Tang Clan has several hidden
weapons that can destroy it.
Unsure whether it’ll work.
You’re from Blacksmith Clan.
Why are you coming to Tang Clan?
Do you believe if I say that
I’m here to enjoy the scenery?
Anyone who breaks into Tang Clan...
will be killed without pardon.
This is a hair crystal.
Little San, why are you looking at this poor crystal?
Are you planning to buy this thing?
Yes, but I don’t know how much is it.
It’s not expensive. 100 gold soul coins.
This poor crystal costs 100 gold soul coins?
It’s better to snatch!
100 gold soul coins is the lowest price here.
If you want to buy, pay it. Or, please leave here.
All right. I’ll buy it.
Little San, are you all right?
That is not enough.
This is 100 gold soul coins. No wrong.
I’m selling it for 200 gold soul coins.
You’re cheating!
You said 100 just now,
and now it turns to 200.
No wonder you have no dealing.
Little San, don’t buy it. Let’s go.
Are you going to change your mind?
Okay, 500 gold soul coins.
No change.
Let’s go.
We should have left earlier.
Dealing with this dishonest trader
is really insulting.
If you have no enough coins now,
I can collect 200 gold soul coins first.
You can pay the remaining
for 10 coins monthly with 10% of interest.
Dishonest trader!
Why don’t you go to hell?
10 coins per month?
He knows that I’m a soul master.
- I didn’t feel the soul power of him.
- Money makes a person blind.
[Next Episode]
Xiao Wu, hurry!
Help me collect all the gold granules quickly.
Don’t miss even one.
Mu Bai, someone is claiming for
a refund. Settle it.
Fully refund if he can defeat me in a battle.
Did your family know that you’re here?