♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Little San...
What did happen just now?
Tell me in detail.
The ultimate practice of
Heart Separation Control
is to grasp every change
of the surroundings.
Preliminary second round, first match.
Shrek School won.
All of you are well-known now.
Yet, being your dean,
this will never be enough for me.
The first six rounds of Preliminary are over.
Why there are no more decent opponents?
Since you’re keen to battle,
I’ll find an opportunity for you in the future.
Let’s go and watch the battle.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 74]
Cang Hui School.
I’m looking forward to fighting them.
They can’t even take down
Elephant Armored School in the first match.
How dare they act so arrogantly.
They’re not the opponents that
you all should concern about.
For the Preliminary,
your biggest rivals are those Five Elements Schools.
Five Elements Schools?
Shen Feng, Chi Huo, Tian Shui, Lei Ting
and also Elephant Armored School
from the earth element.
They’re collectively known as five great
elemental schools in Tian Dou Empire.
From their names, you’ll know
the team members use martial souls
of corresponding elements to battle.
These five great schools have deep backgrounds.
Thus, they might have hidden abilities.
Huyan Li’s soul bone is the best example.
Grandmaster, is Lei Ting School supported by
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon’s family?
Yes.
I don’t know much of the backgrounds
of Shen Feng, Tian Shui and Chi Huo.
But, I can sense that
they are difficult to deal with.
Shen Feng and Tian Shui Schools
will have battles today.
Master, why do these five schools
have soul masters of
the same element in a team?
Even though this can boost particular aspects,
the weaknesses also become obvious.
Like Elephant Armored School,
it has strong defense and strength,
but it has low agility and
monotonous attack formula.
It also lacks abilities to assist and control.
This is a struggle between balanced and
extreme factions in the soul master’s world.
The extreme faction believes that
a soul master should develop his abilities
in a single direction
to an extreme.
However, the balanced faction believes that
a soul master should develop his abilities
in balance between attack and defense.
It’s different from the balanced nature
of Xing Luo Empire.
Most soul masters of Tian Dou Empire
are the supporters of the extreme faction,
just like the Li Tribe from Tai Long’s family.
Then, how about Martial Soul Hall?
Martial Soul Hall should be
the fusion of both streams.
It is the fused stream of extreme individuals
and balanced teams.
After many years of investigation,
I found that
this is the most suitable method to cultivate.
It’s right.
The individual strength is preferred
to go to an extreme.
Weakness can be complemented by teammates.
The teams of Martial Soul Hall
did the same in every batch.
The champions of previous batches
were also taken by them.
With the authority of Martial Soul Hall,
they can encourage the fusion of both streams
to make everyone advanced,
but why did they hide it confidentially?
The story behind is very complicated.
You’re still young.
It’s unnecessary to go deep on that.
What you must do now is
to improve your strength as possible as you can.
If you wish to obtain the champion,
your only opponent will be
the team of Martial Soul Hall.
Their strength is
certainly far beyond Emperor Team
and the five great elemental schools.
Martial Soul Hall is much
stronger than what you expect.
Martial Soul Hall.
Master, I’d like to go back to school first.
My Heart Separation Control is not skillful yet.
I have to practice it more.
You’re right.
It’ll be better to strengthen myself,
rather than investigating others.
All right then.
Be careful on your way back.
603, 604, 605...
There’s something amiss.
I’ve taken 605 steps since I started
to walk from stopping just now.
Why am I still far from the school?
Please show yourself.
Worthy of being the most
outstanding disciple of Shrek School,
you’re vigilant.
Unfortunately, it’s too late.
Oh, you’re a teacher from Cang Hui School.
Are you stopping me for some advice?
I have no advice. I just need you to disappear.
Do you think that my absence
can make Cang Hui School defeat Shrek School?
If killing one doesn’t work,
I’ll keep killing more of you.
I’ll target Dai Mu Bai as the next.
Are you going to kill me here? Not afraid...
You thought we’re still in Tian Dou City?
[Soul Land]
Your weapon is pretty good.
Unfortunately, you’re not in reality now.
This is
my Brutal Dreamland.
The greatest pleasure in my lifetime
is watching my opponents
become insane in my Brutal Dreamland,
until they die.
Soon, I’ll see a youth who is known
as a genius to become like this.
I’m already excited.
Defense?
Do you think that you can resist
my seventh soul skill of Nightmare?
Tang San, such a monstrous sin of you
stealing the Xuan Tian Records!
Tang Clan raised you and taught
you the skills. But, you are ungrateful!
Elders, please listen to me.
How sinful you are!
You will have the clan’s most severe punishment.
You will be held here
for seven days and nights,
and be killed by
the eagles and falcons on the cliff.
Xiao Wu.
Brother, rescue me.
No. Don’t...
No.
This reddish light...
The bloody disaster?
Where did my brother go?
Little San went back to practice first.
There must be something happened to brother.
What’s going on to Xiao Wu?
Grandmaster said Brother San
went back to school, right?
Nothing could happen in
Tian Dou City during the day.
Anyway, let’s check it out with her.
You’re a genius, so what?
You will die in pain in my Brutal Dreamland.
Unfortunately,
I haven’t reached the level of
a Grand Soul Land Master,
otherwise, I can see what he
experienced in the martial soul.
It will more perfect then.
Purple Demon Eye.
No. It’s impossible.
You just reached Level 40.
There’s nothing impossible. You’ve lost.
Have I lost?
Brat, you’re still young to aim high.
You’re impossible to conquer
my soul power at Level 72.
Even if you can conquer
my seventh soul skill of Nightmare,
the ending will never change as well.
However, I’ll give you a chance
to tell me how you broke the Nightmare.
At least, I can make you die in less pain.
Before die, I’ll let you know it clearly.
My Purple Demon Eye
has reached the Surreal level.
It obstructs any kind of illusions.
Even it’s the 9th soul skill,
yet it couldn’t hide from my sight.
Starting from the street illusion that you set,
I had used my Purple Demon Eye to observe.
I just kept pretending not to reveal it.
Why didn’t you break the Nightmare
when you launched the weapon in hands?
You’ve missed the golden chance to escape.
Although it’s tough...
I didn’t want to escape. I was just waiting for it.
Waiting?
There’s a huge gap between you and me.
Though I’ve discovered you earlier,
yet I can’t attack you directly.
Hence, I just kept waiting
until the moment you believed
that I had been controlled.
So that you aren’t in vigilant anymore.
Hilarious. A tiny ant couldn’t fight
against an elephant.
But I’ve made it.
You thought that Blue Silver Plant
was protecting myself?
Your sight is hindered, aren’t you?
You missed my action.
The Yama’s Invitation that I launched
by coagulating soul power
has undissolvable poisons.
It also spreads instantly.
You feel a slight tingle
as it enters your body without pain.
In just a few words, you will die.
You...
[Next Episode] Don’t tell anyone
about Shi Nian’s incident.
including Shrek Seven Devils.
What’s the thing that keeps shining?
Grandmaster.
Is Shrek School’s opponent
for this round confirmed?
Their abilities may be higher than
Elephant Armoured School.
If you can’t do this, you’d better give up.
since this is just a Preliminary.
Grandmaster, please let Little San join the battle.
Little San is the soul of Shrek Team.
We can’t proceed without him.
It’s now!
It comes to an end.