♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Look at you, all poor and pathetic.
Your hick smell stinks.
Get lost.
The third rule of the Tang Clan’s
Xuan Tian Records,
after confirming your enemy identity,
as long as you’re able to kill,
show no mercy.
Or else, it’ll only cause trouble to you.
Alright, enough.
Please accept me as your disciple.
You’ve become a Master’s disciple?
Who are you? Why are you attacking me?
I’m Wang Sheng, the boss of this dorm.
You’ve defeated me,
from now on you’ll be
the boss of this Dorm Seven.
Boss.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 5]
Me? I’m here to study, not to be your boss.
This is the rule. Whoever wins the battle leads.
Right, this is the rule.
By the way, did you use soul skill just now?
Is this Dorm Seven?
Mixed-gender housing is allowed here?
We’re still kids.
Our school’s dorms are gender-neutral.
We’ll only be divided by gender during
Intermediate Soul Master School.
This is weird.
Last year we didn’t have an apprentice.
Yet this year we have two.
Boss, go on! Show her some colors.
Me?
There’s a newbie, we must test her abilities. Go!
I don’t think it’s necessary.
Hello, I’m Xiao Wu, the “Wu” from dance.
Hi, I’m Tang San.
I’m the chief of this dorm.
You can call me by my name.
May I ask about your Martial Soul?
My Martial Soul is a rabbit,
a very cute little white rabbit.
What about you?
Yours restrain mine perfectly.
My Martial Soul is your
Martial Soul’s food, Blue Silver Plant.
That’s interesting, can I come in?
Here is the thing.
Dorm Seven has a rule.
The new apprentice must
show their Martial Soul’s ability.
So, I want to have a friendly fight with you.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Okay.
Come on.
Are you okay?
Come on, boss!
Gosh.
I think I might be the
shortest-lived boss of Dorm Seven.
Tang San, are you alright?
I have lost.
Can you tell me,
what skill you used just now?
I used Rou skill.
It’s a skill which utilizes the softness
and flexibility of our body.
Rou skill.
Of all the famous clans in
the martial world including Tang Clan,
I’ve never seen any martial art like this.
This skill is powerful, yet it is full of risk.
Just now she caught me off guard.
If I had a quicker response,
At that close distance, it’s easy to attack her.
Why are the apprentices
for this year so skillful?
According to the dorm’s rules, you win.
From now on you’ll be
the dorm leader, which is our boss.
That’s right.
Boss, sounds interesting.
Okay, then I’ll be your boss from now on.
It’s not bad being an apprentice after all.
Good, dismiss.
Boss, have a seat.
Tang San, what level is your soul power?
When we fought just now,
I feel that you’re quite strong.
I’m born with full soul power,
that’s why I’m more powerful.
Born with full soul power?
No wonder he’s more powerful than me.
Who is Tang San?
I am.
I’m Teacher Mo. This bedding is from Grandmaster.
Thank you, Teacher Mo.
Tang San and Xiao Wu is year one apprentice.
You’ll be in charge of the south side
of the garden beside the field.
You’ll get ten copper soul coins daily.
If you slack, you’ll be expelled.
Okay.
Tomorrow is the school opening ceremony.
You’ll start working after the classes
start on the day after tomorrow.
I’ll check on you randomly.
If you have questions, ask Wang Sheng.
Okay.
Boss, you can use my bedding.
Boss, use mine.
Boss, use mine instead.
Don’t call me boss, just call me Sister Wu.
Alright, Boss. Oh, it’s Sister Wu.
Little San, let’s discuss this matter.
Little San?
Your bedding is huge,
it’s enough to cover two people.
What about this?
Let’s move our beds together and
share the bedding together, okay?
Together? Is it appropriate?
It is improper for us to get too close.
I’m a girl, if I don’t mind. Why should you mind?
What are you waiting for? Hurry.
Move the bed near you.
I thought you are strong?
Put your bag here too.
From now on, this will be the border.
If you pass the border, I’ll not be easy on you.
[Soul Land]
Wow!
How huge!
This canteen can fit three hundred
students and teachers to eat at once.
Of course, it is enormous.
Let’s go in, I’m starving.
Well, aren’t these Wang Sheng and his poor gang?
If you’re poor, you’re forever poor.
It will be impossible for them
to go to the second floor to eat.
Who are you?
What’s so great about the second floor?
Wow, such a pretty little girl.
Too bad you’re just an apprentice.
The second floor is a place where you can
order and have your meals personally.
The price is high, we can’t afford it.
Wang Sheng, I’m going to eat now.
I’ll let you go for this time.
Darn it.
When did he...
Never mind, we’re here to eat.
You’re afraid of trouble.
Rules of Tang Clan.
All Tang Clan’s disciple are
not allowed to look for trouble.
Never mind, let’s eat first.
We’ll teach them a lesson soon.
But if someone attacks first,
we’re allowed to fight back with all might.
Master, you’re here to eat too.
Have you done tidying all your things?
Thank you for the bedding.
Follow me to the second floor to eat.
I’ll show you around.
Wang Sheng, isn’t this meal on you?
I’m going to eat this.
No, thank you. I’ll eat with my dorm mates.
Good. You’re not acting like a maverick.
Wait for me at the
canteen’s entrance after your meal.
Do you know the Grandmaster?
He is my Master.
Oh no, you’ve acknowledged
Grandmaster as your Master?
His ability is just average.
It is rumored that
he’s in good terms with the Dean,
so he stays here as a guest teacher.
In other words, he’s a freeloader.
I heard that Grandmaster’s almost fifty,
yet he’s stuck in the Great Soul Master level.
There are only twenty-nine
levels in Martial Soul.
He probably can’t go higher than this anymore.
This is the first time, and I hope it’s the last too.
If you don’t want to fight me again,
don’t bluntly comment on my Master.
Thank you for your kind intentions.
I think, there’s no need
for you to pay for my meal.
Dad, can you give me this piece of steel?
Dad, it’s mealtime.
Dad, I’ve done it for ten thousand times.
Dad, practice makes perfect.
Dad, I’m leaving.
Eat first, you’re growing up.
You must eat well.
Master...
Hurry up and eat. Eat it while it’s still hot.
After the meal I have something to tell you.
Don’t waste your time.
Come, show me your the other Martial Soul.
Tang San surname is Tang...
Okay, withdraw it back.
Don’t simply show it in front of others.
Without my permission,
don’t add a soul ring on this Martial Soul either.
My father said this too.
I want you to promise me,
no matter how you practice your soul power,
never add any soul ring to that hammer.
Moreover, never show it in front of others.
And never tell anyone that...
you have Twin Martial Soul.
Can you do this?
What’s your father’s job?
The blacksmith in the village.
Blacksmith?
Blacksmith and hammer are quite a pair.
Why can’t I add a soul ring to this Martial Soul?
Now it’s not the time to tell you yet.
You just need to keep this in mind.
It’s all for your future, remember.
Dad said this. Master said the same thing.
I will.
Good, if that so,
tomorrow morning, I’ll bring you
to look for a suitable soul ring.
For you to level up to a soul master.
With the soul ring,
I can make progress in Xuan Tian Strike, but...
Tomorrow is the school opening ceremony.
I’ll settle the school for you.
Come, tell me your views about Blue Silver Plant.
Everyone thinks that
it’s a useless Martial Soul.
But I think that
everything has its own specialty.
Even if it’s a commonly found Blue Silver Plant.
It surely has its reason to exist and ability.
Good. It’s rare for you to have such insights.
Let me tell you about the
development path of the Martial Soul.
The development path of the Martial Soul?
Let’s start from
the categories for Martial Souls.
We divide Martial Soul into two categories.
Which are beast soul and tool soul.
Beast soul is a merge of human and Martial Soul.
It utilities the beast’s power on our own...
to reach the state
in which the soul and body are one.
We call that Martial Soul Shield Body.
Whereas tool soul is different.
Most tool souls need to leave the body to be in use.
Tool souls are more like
an auxiliary compared with beast souls.
Furthermore, some Martial Souls
can be seen as food.
Can we eat Martial Souls too?
Of course.
All Martial Souls in the Food Branch are edible.
You can think of
the soul power as a type of energy.
Living things eat to obtain energy.
That means, tool souls are for support,
right?
This is not exactly correct.
There’s similarity and difference among
tool soul master and war soul master.
Some tool martial soul can be war soul master.
Every soul master has his path.
For instance, Food Branch, Investigation Branch,
Combat Branch, Healing Branch,
Controlling Branch and so on.
Once we set our path for Martial Soul,
when we’re obtaining soul rings,
there will not be a clash
between the ring and the soul.
Master, which path should I go to?
Many think that the Blue Silver Plant is useless.
But after years of research,
Blue Silver Plant has its strength too.
First, it consumes little soul power.
Second, it’s found everywhere and deceitful.
Third, it has various paths to develop.
It doesn’t repel the soul ring easily.
Repel?
That’s right.
If your Martial Soul
doesn’t match with the soul ring,
adding the soul ring on the Martial Soul...
will result in a repulsion.
And the fourth benefit only works on you.
Me?
[Next Episode]
What are you doing?
Didn’t I come?
Convinced or not?
I’ve found a way to fight with you.
Hit your right shoulder.
We’re preparing to enter the forest.
From now on,
don’t ever leave my side, not even a single step.