♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face,
hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
A black Decade Millennium Soul Ring?
Is this the result of
Little San’s cultivation these days?
Blue Silver Cage has mutated.
Nothing can be better than
battling against Teacher Er Long.
Do your best, guys!
To protect the soul masters’ privacy and safety,
Only teams that joined the preliminary
are allowed to watch the game.
If you don’t mind,
just call me Brother Xue.
Okay, Brother Xue.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 83]
Nice to meet you, Chief Ning.
He’s my disciple, Xue Qing He.
This way, please.
In fact, we come with a bold request.
Oh, please go ahead.
Under the tutelage of you and the teachers,
Rong Rong has improved a lot.
If possible,
I’d like to send some of our youth
to study at Shrek School.
Pardon?
I wonder if it’s feasible?
I think this is inappropriate, Chief Ning?
How can our school compare
with your prestige education?
Nothing is inappropriate.
I believe Grandmaster’s capability in teaching.
It must be the top among the entire continent.
Thanks for your high regards,
I’ll put in my utmost effort.
Having support from Qibao Amber Tribe,
Shrek School no longer has
to worry about school funds.
The teaching materials could be renewed,
and to recruit more teachers.
Becoming the first-class school
is now within our reach.
Dean, what are you smiling about?
We’re greatly honoured...
and we deeply appreciate.
Regarding the details of cooperation,
let’s discuss further after...
the Continental Soul Master School Elite Tournament.
Everyone, good luck in the qualifying rounds.
Shrek will do our best.
Teacher, it’s late. We have to leave.
Dad, why are you leaving so early?
It’s too bad I’m from the Support Branch,
I can’t be in the qualifying rounds.
Otherwise, I’ll show you my current strength.
Not necessary.
I believe Frander’s tutelage.
After graduating from Shrek School,
I’ll officially announce you
as the next tribe chief.
You’re my only daughter,
this is your inborn duty.
With my current health condition,
I’m still able to lead the tribe for years.
Isn’t this period enough for you
to enjoy yourself?
Little Ao has been working hard since I told him.
What if...
What will happen to Little Ao?
It’s late, Qing He and I would take our leave.
Goodbye.
Tang San, see you.
Looking forward to your performance
in the qualifying rounds.
Sure, I’ll do my best. See you, Brother Xue.
Little San, this Xue Qing He...
is that Xue Qing He, right?
Dean, you’ve realized it?
I think I’m right in my guess.
I promised Brother Xue
not to reveal his identity.
Perhaps, he has his reason.
Great, Shrek School is going to be developed.
I didn’t see him for a short while,
and Tang San’s aura has greatly improved.
I’m sure his soul power has developed too.
He’s noteworthy.
Yes, you’re right.
Everyone, the drawing result
for tomorrow’s game is out.
The first-round opponent is Barak School.
Barak?
I remembered that Shrek School
was located at Barak in Suo Tuo City.
They entered the qualifying rounds too?
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament...
consists of preliminary rounds,
qualifying rounds and finals.
Tian Dou Empire has six preliminary divisions.
They’re Tian Dou City Branch,
the four great vassal kingdoms,
and one vassal duchy
wield a preliminary division each.
Tian Dou City Branch
possesses five quotas.
And vassal kingdoms and duchy
possesses two quotas each.
It makes up a total of 15 quotas
to the qualifying rounds.
While the Barak Kingdom...
is one of the four biggest
vassal kingdoms of Tian Dou Empire.
Shrek had also fought for a quota
of Barak Kingdom,
however, due to the suppression of royals,
we failed to get the quota to enter
the qualifying rounds.
Meanwhile, I had missed
Advanced Soul Master School Tournament.
This has become my greatest lifetime regret.
Barak.
Teacher Qin, please be rest assured.
Shrek Seven Devils will do our best...
to defeat Barak School.
Yes.
But, the rules of qualifying rounds
is much different from the previous one.
Both teams send out seven members.
Each member has to fight until they’re defeated.
If they win, they will have to fight the next rival...
until all seven of the rivals are defeated.
It means it’s a one-on-one battle
rather than a team battle?
Yes.
Master, please let me duel.
I’m good in melee, I’ll surely win.
Little San, please don’t be anxious.
All teachers have decided...
to send Xiao Wu first.
Okay.
I hereby announce...
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament,
Qualifying Rounds.
officially begins.
[Soul Land]
Looking forward to your excellent performance.
Long live the Emperor.
Little San, it seems like you’ve
offended many beauties.
One is Huo Wu, another one is Shui Bing Er.
Do you think others
would consider you as a playboy?
I was wondering who they are?
It’s Shrek, the losers of Suo Tuo City.
Lofchy.
You’re just as annoying as your father.
What’s going on? Does Dean know him?
Frander, I think your Shrek is the annoying one.
I advise you and your losers
to out of the field as soon as possible.
Please don’t disgrace our Barak Kingdom.
Barak? They’re from Barak School.
We from Shrek are ethical and with integrity.
The one smeared the good name
of soul masters is you.
Frander, my father kindly advised you years ago.
How dare you didn’t accept it.
I heard you’ve ridden
on Lanba School’s coattail.
What’s more, it’s a woman’s school.
Frander,
if I were you, I’d feel so ashamed.
Scoundrel.
Teacher Zhao, you’ll be against the rules
if you beat him here.
Come on. I’m here for you.
Frander, you’re such a coward.
Let’s leave.
Dean, Teacher Zhao, what exactly has happened?
It was because Shrek lacked
new student recruits,
therefore, the royals of Barak
weren’t able to gain profits.
Hence, they’ve always belittled us.
If without the support of alumnus,
Shrek wouldn’t be able to survive till now.
Does Barak have such great power?
Among the four kingdoms of
Tian Dou Empire,
Barak Kingdom possesses
the most powerful military power.
It can be considered as
the portal of Tian Dou Empire.
They wield absolute power.
Except for necessary tributes,
they’re fully autonomous.
Who’s that Lofchy?
How could he address
your name disrespectfully?
Lofchy’s father is in charge of
the education department of Suo Tuo City.
He always instigates those royals
to go against us.
He’s like a thorn in the flesh.
There’re so many people living under
their suppression in Suo Tuo City.
Xiao Wu, in this duel,
you must put them to shame.
Teacher Zhao, Dean, don’t worry.
I’ll definitely win this duel.
Next,
Shrek School versus Barak School.
Let’s look at their data.
Fighting!
It’s Xiao Wu’s turn now,
hopefully, she won’t be hurt.
Lofchy is at Level 42.
No wonder he’s so arrogant.
Will Xiao Wu...
I believe Xiao Wu and Master’s judgment too.
Barak School first participant, their captain.
A Soul Sect at Level 42.
Perhaps, they want to win in the first round.
But their opponent is Shrek,
who aced in the preliminary.
It must be an exciting game.
Does Shrek like to swagger around?
By sending a little girl?
It’s must be the worthy student of coward Frander.
Fatty, what’s wrong?
Have you forgotten that Bu Le?
He was beaten by Xiao Wu’s Eight Flinging...
Start.
Brother, I think you’re right.
Here’s a place I shouldn’t come.
Brother, please give way to me.
I’ll treat you gently...
See you.
Nice. That arrogant Barak School deserves this.
How could they not know of our Shrek?
Suppressing people. They ask for that.
Next.
What are you doing?
Judge, I report they purposely take revenge.
Why? You’re not convinced?
You...
Or do you want a gang fight?
Are you keen to die?
[Next Episode]
You have to pay for what you have done.
This is a competition. What are you doing?
What is Little San doing?
I never expect that Shrek’s student
has a soul bone.
Tang San, remember what you’ve said.