♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Dean, please help me.
I want the Burrow Demon Spider.
You want to escape? No way!
Dean, it’s here!
This soul beast is something!
If I let you escape again,
I won’t be the Four-Eyed Eagle Owl!
Xiao Wu!
Mother!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 66]
You should never let her down.
If not, no matter who’s your master,
you will suffer the same fate
as that King of the Land last time.
I, Tang San, swear to God,
I will never let Xiao Wu down.
Little San, the Burrow Demon Spider
is holding on to its last breath.
You should go and absorb its soul ring.
Dean, you’re right.
I feel much better.
Later, I will absorb its soul ring
in the Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
It’ll speed up the process.
Before I’m done with it,
you all should not go near
the Ice Fire Mouth Spring,
in case you guys will get hurt.
Xiao Wu, no matter if his decisions
are right or wrong,
you need to support him.
You should be happy for him
if he made the right decision.
Mother, you’re right.
I should always support him.
Xiao Gang, come with me.
I need to speak to you.
Xiao Gang.
Luckily, I have a daughter now.
I do understand why you took
Tang San as your disciple now.
At least we can place our emotion on them.
Even if we can’t lead a happy life together,
I hope they can be happy.
Brother San.
My son!
Xiao Gang, do you wanna continue
this state with Er Long?
I don’t know.
You don’t know?
Er Long has waited for you for 20 years.
She spent a long time waiting for you!
Although you’re my brother,
I want to beat you up right now!
Actually, I want to beat myself up too.
It’s all my fault.
But Er Long is suffering because of me.
Xiao Gang, are there no other ways?
If this continues, both of you
will suffer until the end.
You should know that
Er Long only like you
and no one else.
I shouldn’t stay by her side,
and make her suffer again.
Xiao Gang, do you love Er Long?
Of course.
That’s good. I’m sure that
Er Long has always loved you too.
Since that’s the case,
both of you are together already.
Can I say that?
You!
Since both of you love each other,
Why can’t both of you
be united in the mental state?
You don’t need any recognition.
You just need her approval.
Both of you can be together mentally.
Frander, I don’t understand.
It’s easy.
You guys can be a couple.
Just don’t change the way
you address each other.
If you two love each other mentally,
nobody can talk about it.
Is that really okay?
Why not?
At least, both of you will feel better.
You two love each other.
There’s nothing wrong with that.
Frander, why didn’t you say that earlier?
[Soul Land]
Boss Dai, it’s going to rain.
Why isn’t he back yet?
He’ll return to us. He’ll surely return to us.
Er Long.
Is being together with me
that hard for you?
God, why are you punishing me like this?
I’ve let you down.
Let’s be together.
Xiao Gang, do you know how long
I’ve waited for you?
How many days and nights?
Do you know how I got through every day?
You’re not escaping anymore?
Are you willing to be with me now?
Er Long, I swear,
I won’t ever try to escape from you again.
Although we can’t be a normal couple,
I will still love you forever.
Okay. Everything is fine
as long as you return to me.
Brother?
Xiao Wu.
Let’s believe in Little San.
Brother.
Brother, comb my hair.
Little San.
Brother, please return to us.
Xiao Wu, thank you.
Brother!
Little San!
The wind is coming.
We’re flying!
Look, it’s beautiful.
Brother,
you are my hero.
Let’s go.
[Next Episode]
Crowd-control skill?
This is too scary!
They are the elite students
mentored by Er Long.
The competition will be difficult
far beyond your imagination.
You have five days left.
They’re much stronger
than the Emperor Battle Team.
Little devils,
Could it be...
Wow! So many people!
What school are they from?
Did they come out from
the sewer or something?
We are here to be the champion!
Champion?
Do you think you can be the champion?