♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Mr. Team Leader.
On behalf of Suo Tuo Soul Arena,
I hereby invite Shrek Seven Devils
to join the group battle
at the Central Soul Arena.
Here are the details of the opponent.
I can make some guess
about the origin of Emperor Team.
You have to pay the most attention to two persons,
who are their Captain and Vice Captain.
It’s only with a 30% probability.
You must not admit defeat until the last moment.
Xiao Gang,
I think that you shouldn’t
promise them in a hurry.
I’ve never heard of any other
soul masters of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon yet.
Are you saying...?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 39]
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
is known as the
beast soul with the strongest attack power.
Its status in beast soul
is similar to the status
of Rong Rong’s Qibao Amber Pagoda
in Assisting Branch of Martial Soul.
So, is their captain
from the family of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon?
Apart from the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon family,
I’ve never heard of any other
soul masters of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon yet.
The background of Emperor Team is overwhelming!
Not only both captains,
but the Black Martial Turtle also has
the same level as Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
They are the top in the
Defense Branch of Martial Soul.
As for the soul master of
Jade Phosphor Serpent,
she makes me think of a person.
Frander, do you still remember him?
Jade Phosphor Serpent?
Are you saying...?
I’m talking about him.
Jade Phosphor Serpent is similar
to that of several big families.
It’s a rare martial soul.
School Dean, Grandmaster,
who are you talking about?
Among the soul masters who own the martial soul,
there’s only a famous one.
He’s being known as
The Grand Jade Phosphor Master.
Are you talking the Poison Master?
The most difficult to tackle one,
The Grand Jade Phosphor Master.
There’s no one else other than him.
The vice captain of Emperor Team
is having the same surname of Dugu
as The Grand Jade Phosphor Master.
Master, the soul master of Jade Phosphor Serpent
is in Controlling Branch.
I wonder how she controls it.
It’s not easy to control if using the serpent martial soul.
Poison.
Poison?
If that is the case,
we’ll have a chance to defeat them!
Little San, never underestimate the opponent!
Oscar’s Detoxifying Small Sausage
is only in its second soul ring.
It may not bear with the
poison of Jade Phosphor Serpent.
Yes, Master.
Grandmaster, may I say something?
Yes, go ahead.
During the battle,
we must focus on
the soul master of Assisting Branch
of the opponent.
Oh? Why?
I know the martial soul of
Nine Heart Flowering Apple.
It has only one ability of
general healing in the scope.
General healing in the scope?
The degree of healing is
controlled by soul master’s intentions.
The higher the level,
the more the soul ring,
the more the healing power can be used.
My father said,
if there’s a soul master with
Nine Heart Flowering Apple,
it’ll not be easy to die even if you want.
This is an almost perfect combination.
We can win.
Mu Bai, Little Ao, Fatty, Xiao Wu, Rong Rong, Zhu Qing.
Have you forgotten that
we’ve already achieved a winning streak of 27?
In the previous battles,
we won by defeating the strong opponents.
We have Mu Bai’s top martial soul
of Storm Attack Branch,
Little Ao’s capability of
holding the battle continuously,
Fatty’s top Mutated Beast Soul,
and Xiao Wu’s magical Rou skill.
Rong Rong, do you think your Qibao Amber Pagoda
is not comparable with
Nine Heart Flowering Apple?
And Zhu Qing...
You’re the most speedy
among those of Keen Attack Branch
at the same level that I’ve ever seen.
Although the opponent is strong,
we aren’t weak.
If we lose the confidence to win,
why should we participate in the battle?
Little San, you’re right.
We, Shrek Seven Devils
are never afraid of anyone else.
Yes, Shrek Seven Devils will surely win.
Win!
Let’s guess
what kind of opponent will be
arranged by Soul Arena for us tonight?
Any opponent will be useless.
No one can compete with us.
Ling Ling, if we get hurts,
you have to cure me first.
Teacher.
This time, you’re going to
encounter a strong opponent.
Here is your opponent tonight.
[Participant Information]
Team of Shrek Seven Devils.
Seven team members with iron soul badges.
They’re already qualified
to obtain a silver battle soul.
- Please.
- Suo Tuo Soul Arena has
already decided to grant them
the Silver qualification in advance.
This comes at the time to battle with you all.
Being granted silver battle soul in advance?
Does Suo Tuo Soul Arena have no more
silver battle soul team to battle with us?
Never underestimate the opponent!
Shrek Seven Devils team won
the Frenzy Battle Team before.
Frenzy Battle Team?
How can they make it?
This is the key person.
A soul master with Blue Silver Plant.
Moreover, pay attention to the
soul master of Qibao Amber Pagoda too.
As well as the captain of the team.
He won’t be the captain if he’s not outstanding.
This battle is indeed a tough one.
I have a request for every one of you.
No matter how the battle goes,
never hurt the opponent.
Especially you, Yan Zi.
If they got poisoned by you,
you have to detoxify them immediately
after the battle.
Why?
I’ll tell you when the battle is over.
Welcome to Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
It’s my honor to see everyone again.
I’m the host of tonight’s soul battle, Dou Dou.
Next, let’s welcome the members of both teams.
Look! Look!
Purple hair and green eyes.
Does such color of eyes and hair
exist in this world?
The Central Soul Arena is very magnificent.
This is the highest-standard stage
of Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
The diameter of this soul battle stage
is up to 70 meters.
The auditorium is large enough
to accommodate 20,000 spectators.
It’s a retro and ancient style of an auditorium.
This is a tribute to the ancient soul masters.
Do you know the leader of the opponent?
I’ll tell you when the battle is over.
It’s not easy to battle with this guy.
Attention, please.
You have one minute from now
to initiate your martial soul.
The battle will begin once I announce.
The battle will end when either team
admits defeat or falls off from the battle stage.
Initiate your martial soul now.
[Soul Land]
This... Is this...?
You’ve finally seen it?
This is the third tribe in the world.
The only martial soul owned by
the tribe of Blue Lightning.
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon is the top martial soul.
It’s different from the other martial souls.
The soul ring of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
can only be the soul beast of
toothed-dragon species.
This means its soul skill is superb.
Master said, the soul master
of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
is the most terrifying soul master of
Storm Attack Branch at the same level.
As expected,
he’s absolute confidence in his own strength.
Soul battle begins.
First soul skill,
White Tiger Protection Barrier.
The best soul ring combination
of 2 yellow and 1 purple
brings a great pressure indeed.
Either the quality of martial soul
or the configuration of soul rings,
Shrek Seven Devils are indeed at a disadvantage.
However, this is their advantage of
encountering the other soul battle teams.
The advantage might turn into a disadvantage.
Little San, what are you going to do?
I’m forcibly blocked by two of them at the front.
I can’t exert pressure on the other
members of Emperor Team behind them.
I’ll tackle two of them first.
They’re retracted!
Up there!
Unexpectedly, the Black Martial Turtle is tough.
You got into my trap!
First soul skill, Thunder Dragon Claws.
Oh, no!
I exert power in the air.
You have nowhere to hide.
It’s you who got into the trap.
[Next Episode]
First soul skill, Intertwine.
The favorable situation
that Little San established is useless now.
The real battle starts now!
I’ll kill you all!
The lives of Shrek Seven Devils are at stake.
No!