♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] I’ll give the
apprentice position to Little San this year.
Don’t stop him...
from becoming a soul master.
Come and look for me if you change your mind.
There are three months to go
before the registration starts.
It’s the same as hers.
No.
My son!
Remember,
you must protect your plant with the hammer.
Forever.
Pack your things,
Old Jack will bring you to Nuoding City tomorrow.
Don’t let others know that
you have Twin Martial Souls.
Can...
you do it?
Dad, I’m leaving with Grandpa Jack.
Take good care of yourself.
Don’t forget to eat the porridge in the pot.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 4]
Little San,
I’ll leave after sending you to the school.
You must listen to the teachers,
don’t leave the school without permission.
When the term ends, I’ll come and fetch you.
You’re leaving so soon, Grandpa Jack?
We can’t afford a hotel here.
- This way please, Mister.
- You must put efforts into it.
When I meet you next time,
I hope you’re already a soul master.
The whole Soul Saint Village
will be so proud of you.
I will, Grandpa Jack.
Good boy.
Fine fresh fruit selling cheap!
Special sale! Fine fresh fruit!
What would like to buy?
Excuse me, how do I go to Nuoding School?
Just go straight to the end.
Oh, thank you.
Mister, what would you like?
Don’t worry.
Didn’t I tell you before? Look.
Excuse me, how do I go to Dorm Seven?
Dorm Seven is at...
We don’t know!
What? Does she have to be so rude?
Let’s go.
What are you doing?
Are villagers even allowed to be here?
I’m sorry.
I’m late.
Little brother, we come from
the Soul Saint Village.
He’s the apprentice from our village this year.
Are there any procedures to follow?
Someone is trying to aim at the moon here.
Even a villager can have soul power?
It has been years since we had an apprentice.
You’re not fakers, are you?
This is the letter from the officer
of Martial Soul Temple, Su Yun Tao.
Blue Silver Plant but has full soul power?
Funny, that’s hilarious.
I’ve been working here in the school
for four years,
and I’ve never heard of a student
born with full soul power before.
Let me guess, you fake this letter.
You!
You’re making things difficult for us!
Alright, you wait here.
I’ll look for the officer
from Martial Soul Branch Hall.
Little San, let’s go.
Soul Saint Village,
I think Beggars Village suits you more.
What did you say?
What? You don’t agree?
I said you come from Beggars Village.
Am I wrong?
Look at you, all poor and pathetic.
Get lost!
Go somewhere else if you want to beg.
Nuoding School isn’t
a charity association. Get lost!
Little San, you...
The third rules of the Tang Clan’s
Xuan Tian Records,
after confirming your enemy identity,
as long as you’re able to kill,
show no mercy.
Or else, it’ll only cause trouble to you.
Alright, enough.
You’re back, Grandmaster?
Old Mister,
can you show me the letter
from Martial Soul Temple?
It’s genuine.
Old Mister,
I apologize on behalf of the school
on what happened just now.
Hand this kid to me.
There’s no need to say sorry.
We’re at fault too.
I’ll leave this kid to you then.
Little San, follow this Grandmaster.
I’ll fetch you once the term is over.
Goodbye, Grandpa Jack!
I’ll put efforts in studies!
I’ll excuse you, but for the last time.
If you get caught again, just leave.
[Soul Land]
Thank you, Teacher.
Teacher? I’m not a teacher here.
You’re not? Didn’t you say that
on behalf of the school?
Who said that only teachers
can represent the school?
I got it.
You must be the Dean,
or leader.
You’re indeed a smart kid.
But, wrong guess.
You are...
I’m just a guest here who enjoys free meals.
You can call me “Grandmaster” as everyone else does.
Everyone here calls me the same,
I even have forgotten my name.
The letter states that your name is Tang San?
Tang San, you must understand.
Grandmaster and teacher has big differences,
don’t get it wrong next time.
Unless you really want me to be your Master.
Are you going to teach me Martial Soul training?
Are you willing to learn?
Great, you’re indeed a smart kid.
Gifted and clever.
It seems like I need to be persistent this time.
Since you’re the third person who has
Twin Martial Souls in this century.
First rules of the Tang Clan’s Xuan Tian Records,
never allow someone you can’t fully trust...
to know your exact capability.
You might ask, why I know
you have Twin Martial Souls.
Because of this letter.
I’ve investigated 647 people
with Blue Silver Plant.
Only 16 of them have soul powers.
Among them, none has more than
a Level 1 soul power,
but your soul power is at Level 10.
According to one of the
10 Core Competing Power of Martial Soul,
comparing your soul power amount
and Martial Soul’s quality,
Blue Silver Plant clearly can’t satisfy it.
So I’m pretty sure...
that you have another Martial Soul,
and a very strong one.
There’s always an exception.
Why can’t I be the one?
You’re right, there’s always an exception.
In these hundred years, even if
Tian Dou and Xing Luo Empires...
only have 2 people with Twin Martial Souls,
but there are 19 born with full soul power.
I’ve gone through each of their Martial Souls,
and all of them are strong masters.
Even the youngest one...
has reached the level of Great Soul Master.
There are still five who are exceptional.
They have Mutated Martial Souls.
Well, according to my research
on Mutated Martial Soul for years,
none of them mutated with Blue Silver Plant.
Since your Blue Silver Plant is just a normal one,
that’s why, I’m positive that...
my prediction is right.
Mutated Martial Soul, what’s that?
That has to begin from
the inheritance of Martial Soul.
Under normal situation,
we’ll inherit one of our parents’ Martial Soul.
But some might be exceptional.
Mutated Martial Soul can be much stronger,
some even born with full soul power.
But most of the Mutated Martial Soul...
will only be weaker.
Mutated Martial Soul is just like
the product of near-kin marriage,
there’s a big possibility of getting retarded.
But there could be an extraordinary man too.
What are you doing?
Please accept me as your disciple.
Silly kid, why did you have to kowtow?
Don’t you know this only can be used
towards the emperor and your parents?
You only need to bow.
Master for a day, father for life.
You deserve my kowtow.
What a rare guest, Grandmaster.
These teachers will help you with registration.
I’ll have to leave now,
I’ll look for you again.
Goodbye, Master.
Kid, you call him “Master”?
He’s not a teacher from our school.
But he’s my Master.
You’ve become a Master’s disciple?
Is there anything wrong, Teacher?
Nothing.
I didn’t expect he’ll take a disciple.
Tang San, right?
As a school teacher,
I need to remind you that...
you can’t simply take a man as your master.
Oh, you’re born with full soul power.
What? Born with full soul power?
Too bad your Martial Soul is
just Blue Silver Plant.
Blue Silver Plant, I see.
Every soul master can only choose
one master for his lifetime,
or else people will look down on you.
Do you really think he suits you?
What’s the matter?
Maybe he’s a little strange,
but come to think of it,
he’s invincible in Martial Soul’s knowledge.
Since you only have Blue Silver Plant,
it’s fine to take anyone as your master.
Alright, that’s it.
This is complimentary by the school.
You’ll be staying in
the seventh floor of the dorm.
There’ll be a teacher over there
to take care of your work as an apprentice.
Thank you.
That Grandmaster is invincible,
but that’s just theoretically.
His theories have to work right with practices.
Director, I heard of his
10 Core Competing Power of Martial Soul.
Indeed, I find it very funny.
Enough.
He’s a friend of our Dean, stop criticizing.
Even though no one can prove him right,
but that doesn’t mean he’s wrong.
He has great reputation
in the world of Martial Soul.
No, Director.
He’s only a famous clown,
people are just taking him as a joke.
He knew that I have Twin Martial Souls
by just looking at my letter.
How is he a joker?
Let’s see who’s laughing till the end.
Who are you? Why did you attack me?
I’m Wang Sheng, the boss of this Dorm Seven.
Thank you for showing mercy.
Since you’ve defeated me,
you’re the boss of Dorm Seven from now on.
Boss!
Me? I’m here to study, not to be your boss.
This is our rule,
whoever wins the battle leads.
Yes, that’s the rule.
Oh, right. Did you use your soul skill just now?
Soul skill?
Is this Dorm Seven?
[Next Episode]
Hello, I’m Xiao Wu.
Boss, it seems fun.
Born with full soul power?
It’s so huge!