♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Ah Yin, here is the place we bade farewell.
Tang Hao, you can’t escape.
Give her to me. I’ll let you live.
If you want to hurt her,
step over my corpse first.
Farewell, my love.
I’ve given him a name.
[San]
Little San might not withstand
this Human Faced Demon Spider.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 28]
Yi Ran, what are you thinking?
I’m thinking of Tang San’s words.
Gift it to you.
Grandma,
do you think if I should
use that Bone Piercing Needle?
Use it if you think it’s useful.
Tang San is gifted.
He’s a rare talent.
Unfortunately, he refused to join our family.
Otherwise, in less than twenty years,
he can definitely lead the family to a new level.
You’ll never find a golden carp in a pond.
Not only Tang San,
but also the other children are outstanding.
But, why I’ve never heard of Shrek School?
All these are unimportant.
Although those kids are outstanding as well,
there’s still a difference from Tang San. Yi Ran...
Huh?
How do you think of Tang San?
Him? I think he’s just a mature kid.
No. I’m asking your feeling towards him.
Grandpa, are you pairing us together?
I’m three years elder than him.
Age is not a matter.
Grandpa, you...
What? Aren’t you willing?
Do you think that he looks too ordinary?
Indeed he has an ordinary look.
Obviously, he isn’t from a famous clan.
I don’t understand how he practices
the poor martial soul of Blue Silver Plant.
My girl, never judge a book by its cover.
Tang San is not as common as you say.
How do you know that he isn’t from the famous clan?
Have you ever seen a soul master who
practiced Blue Silver Plant to Level 30?
And the hidden weapon that he used.
All of these are enough to prove
that he’s extraordinary.
Grandpa, don’t be mad.
Let’s talk about it later.
It’s uncertain whether I’ll meet him again.
Yi Ran, you’d better think properly.
It’s now or never.
No worries, my dear. She’ll have her own happiness.
We’d better help Yi Ran to find
an appropriate third soul ring first.
Let’s figure out the Shrek School
when we return home later.
Brother San, where did you go?
Brother, Xiao Wu is back!
Teacher Zhao, if Little San carries on,
he may be in danger.
I knew it. But it’s
inappropriate to disturb him now.
Everything depends on his willpower.
Who?
Xiao Wu, you’re still alive!
Are you expecting me to die?
What happened? This mist...
What happened to Little San?
Xiao Wu, please wait.
Little San is absorbing his third soul ring.
Don’t disrupt him.
Third soul ring? How come...?
How can this happen during
absorbing the third soul ring?
This is Human Faced Demon Spider.
The soul ring of Human Faced
Demon Spider that Little San is absorbing
far exceeds the limit of his third soul ring.
How do you know it?
Grandmaster did say
the limit of a third soul ring
is about 1,700 years.
The legs of this Human Faced
Demon Spider is longer than 3 meters.
It had undergone at least 2,000 years of practice.
I see.
But it’s too late to stop him now!
Hopefully Little San can withstand until the end.
By the way, how did you
escape from the Titan Giant Ape?
I don’t know what happened either.
The Titan Giant Ape caught me
and ran into the forest.
Before running further,
we heard a cow roaring from far.
The Titan Giant Ape looked nervous.
It threw me aside and ran away.
Cow roar? What kind of cow can
make Titan Giant Ape nervous?
Titan Giant Ape roared before leaving,
so I fainted.
It had disappeared when I awoke.
By the time,
my soul power was upgraded to Level 30.
What? You’re reaching Level 30 now!
Who’s elder between Tang San and you?
I’m a few months younger.
At the time, a few Millennium Soul Beasts fainted as well.
Coincidentally, there’s one suit for me!
So I hunted it. It’s such a coincidence!
Ah! How can it be?
I thought I would be dead.
Unexpectedly, I survived.
I was physically recovered
after absorbing the soul ring.
So I came to you all at once.
Xiao Wu, I’ll definitely rescue you!
Brother, please stay well!
It’s all my fault. My bad.
Please wake up.
Don’t you worry, Little San can overcome it.
[Soul Land]
Have you been returned home?
Do you think I still have a home?
You have to return one day
since they are your family.
It’ll not be now even if I return.
Before I prove myself,
I won’t make myself a joke to them.
Xiao Gang, you’re too stubborn.
Otherwise, you and she would not be...
Shut up! Don’t mention her in front of me!
I’m here just for one purpose.
All right. Not mentioning her.
Isn’t Tang San your purpose to be here?
Zhao Wu Ji was beaten
a few days ago because of Tang San.
I can guess who is the person.
You know?
Do you think Little San’s Martial Soul
is only Blue Silver Plant?
He made it.
He has overcome the danger.
He’s undergoing the transformation
process of soul power now.
Tang San is a miracle!
He can even withstand the
Human Faced Demon Spider of 2,000 years.
The Unrivaled Dragon Serpent
should be grateful that
their granddaughter didn’t
absorb this soul ring.
If not, she might have already
died of body explosion.
Let’s step back.
Little San’s power has just upgraded.
His soul power is out of control now.
Teacher.
This is very common. Don’t worry.
Brother.
This shouldn’t happen.
This...
Isn’t this the leg of Human Faced Demon Spider?
It’s my first time to see this condition.
Look!
Teacher Zhao, what happened to Little San?
This...
Is Little San becoming a big spider?
It’s impossible! How can Little San become a spider?
The mutation must have occurred
when he absorbed the soul ring.
He’ll be all right.
Teacher Zhao, what should we do now?
Now? Perhaps we can only wait.
Xiao Wu, don’t. Please don’t leave me.
An outer disciple is not allowed
to enter the inner clan for a whole life.
Scriptures of Tang Clan are never be propagated.
An outer is always an outer.
You can only be trash.
How dare an outer disciple
peep at the inner practice!
Give him a lesson!
Tang San has already mastered the outer skill.
I know well that
the journey of learning is infinite.
I beg Elder to teach me the inter martial art
and allow me to enter the Scriptures Library.
Scriptures Library is an
important place of Tang Clan.
The inner disciples never dare to think of that.
You’d know your place.
Tang San would like to learn
deeper of the hidden weapon.
I’ll develop the hidden weapon.
If you still have improper thoughts,
I will definitely report to
Grandmaster Tang Lan
to expel you from the clan.
[Next Episode]
If you insist to enter,
you will be chased out from Tang Clan.
Death is the only option.
Rebellious! Never let go of him!
Brother, keep it up!
I am not dreaming, right?
Xuan Tian Records?
Tang San, you may try it boldly.
Who?