♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face,
hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
If possible,
I’d like to send some of our youth
to learn in Shrek School.
I hereby announce
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament, Qualifying Rounds,
officially begins!
I wonder who they are?
It’s Shrek, the losers of Suo Tuo City.
Many people are living under
their suppression in Suo Tuo City.
- Xiao Wu, in this duel...
- See you.
You must put them to shame.
Next.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 84]
Why? You’re not convinced?
You...
Or do you want a gang fight?
Are you keen to die?
This is a competition.
What are you doing?
Platinum Chiefs, please calm down.
We just want to bring our member out.
We mean nothing.
Remember your identity.
If participants who are not involved
enter the stage again
will be expelled from
the tournament immediately.
I hope you’ll leave safely
in the next round.
After the accident happened just now,
the competition continues.
[Barak School: Jakes] vs. [Shrek School: Xiao Wu]
Start.
Shrek School won.
[Winner: Xiao Wu]
[Scott] vs. [Xiao Wu]
Shrek School won.
What’s wrong?
Why is Barak so lousy?
Barak sent another Soul Sect.
How will he perform in this round?
Let’s wait and see.
You have to pay for what you have done.
Raise your fist then.
Start.
First soul skill.
Flower Bloom.
What a Level 40 Soul Sect.
He’s able to control the arena instantly.
With such firm manipulation,
Barak School has got the upper hand this round.
Although Olby’s control never stops,
with Xiao Wu’s speed,
she could have escaped from it.
Second soul skill, Flower Turbo Spread.
This...
What’s going on?
It’s Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
Darn it.
Since the sunflower attacks Xiao Wu,
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet
considers it as an offence.
As the king of flower, how could it endure?
Are we going against the rules?
Even Master can’t figure it out,
not to mention those judges.
Besides, it isn’t Xiao Wu who used it.
It can’t be considered a violation.
What’s going on?
It seems I have to...
Third soul skill, Spurting Sun.
You next opponent’s martial soul is Sunflower.
You don’t have to resist his attacks.
After winning, if somebody asks you,
you don’t have to answer.
OK.
I never expect
one of Shrek’s student has a soul bone.
Maybe they have covered up their strength.
But isn’t this soul bone too powerful?
It can make its rival’s martial soul
wilt instantly.
Your Majesty, if I’m not mistaken,
Xiao Wu’s soul skill must be very targeted.
Only martial soul from Plant Branch
can be restrained.
I agree with Chief Ning.
This should be a common soul bone.
It just worked at a certain time.
What ability did you use?
In this round,
Shrek School won.
Although Xiao Wu’s soul power
is temporarily behind,
she’s excellent in melee.
Xiao Wu has won five rounds consecutively.
I’m afraid she will be hurt, if she continues.
Yes.
Barak School seems to
have no rivals worth dueling with.
Settle the rest as quickly as possible.
Send Little San to duel with them.
So that we can cover up
our strength as much as possible.
OK.
Little San,
next round is your turn.
Yes.
Shrek changes their participant.
[Shrek School]
Brother, what’s wrong
with the glow around me?
How could a sunflower
challenge the king of flower?
Blue Silver Cage.
We lost.
No, we lost.
Tang San,
I’ve worked so hard
and finally made a breakthrough.
Xuan Tian Strike.
I’ll definitely defeat you
next time.
[Soul Land]
Blue Silver Plant.
Little San, what is he doing?
No,
how could Little San...
Duelling with Barak School,
I think Little San is using a good one.
Shrek School won.
Let’s talk privately.
Tang San, when it’s our turn to duel,
I hope you can duel with me.
Let’s fight fairly.
Sorry,
I can’t promise you.
You don’t dare to fight with me?
The sequence of the duel
is arranged by our teachers.
I don’t have the right to decide.
You...
But if we meet in the duel,
I’m willing to have a fair fight with you.
Good.
Remember what you’ve said.
Your rival for tomorrow is Chi Huo School.
Why is Chi Huo School again?
Fourth soul skill, Fire Dance Dazzling Sun!
Qualifying rounds are
a round-robin competition.
It isn’t a bad thing to fight them early.
What formation do you think
should be used in this fight?
Grandmaster, please send me first.
You can punish me if I lose.
Grandmaster, only Huo Wu Shuang and Huo Wu
are considered strong in Chi Huo School.
Judging from today’s competition,
just send Little San and me to duel,
our victory is guaranteed.
I suggest Tang San going first,
and you’ll wrap it up.
Why?
Isn’t it better to start with
a soul master from Storm Attack?
Yes,
that is a commonly same tactic,
so we’ll act reversely.
Little San as a soul master from Control Branch,
his nature resists those
from Storm Attack Branch.
I see.
Since Fatty strongly requested it,
I think he can be the second to duel.
We knew Fatty has been training so hard,
it’s time to check his results.
Your analysis is correct.
Hence, tomorrow we’ll send
Little San, Ma Hong Jun,
Zhu Zhu Qing, Xiao Wu, and Mu Bai.
But I have to remind you that
even in the qualifying rounds,
all teams may not use their full strength.
You have to hide yours too.
Rest early then.
Any problem?
There’re seven quotas reserved to fight,
but Grandmaster only mentioned five.
Isn’t that insufficient?
Senior is right.
They first sent Huo Wu Shuang
from Storm Attack Branch.
It seems like the first round
is quite easy.
This round may be difficult for Little San.
Why?
We’ve won Chi Huo School
in the previous team battle.
Only unexpected tactics can defeat rivals.
But Little San’s ability to fire resistance
isn’t a secret anymore.
It’ll be slightly difficult for him to win.
Grandmaster, let’s believe Little San.
Brother, come on.
Next,
Chi Huo School versus Shrek School.
Both teams sent their main force
in the first round.
Huo Wu Shuang and Tang San.
Start.
Third soul skill, Constraint of Spider Web.
It’s useless to me.
This...
Little San is being suppressed.
Now I got it.
It seems Huo Wu Shuang has prepared
for Blue Silver Plant’s fire resistance.
Even Blue Silver Plant can immune
to both water and fire,
but Huo can compress
and condense his soul power
to produce an explosion.
Huo Wu Shuang has completely
got the upper hand.
How will Tang San deal with this?
I did mention that your fire-resistance
Blue Silver Plant is useless to me.
Do you think you can win?
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
How could it be?
It’s like hitting on a soft barrier,
I can’t feel my force.
[Next Episode]
What’s going on?
The Five Elements Schools
are comparable in strength.
She must have other intentions
in exhausting soul power substantially.
I never expect Tang San
could be so mean.
The competition is over.
It’s better not let him duel again
in the qualifying rounds.