♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Tang San, would you wish me to be your teacher?
I have too many poisons in my body.
I can’t store all poisons in the soul bone.
So, just stop the treatment now.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 52]
What is this?
These are two iron balls.
But they can save your life.
With these two little things?
You don’t believe it?
I’ll show it to you.
Watch closely.
This pair of iron balls is named as
Cluster Soul Chasing Life Taking Balls.
Once they suffer
external pressure or collision,
they will explode immediately
and release the poisonous fog.
Common people inhale a little bit of it,
they will sleep for ten days.
Even a powerful soul master
who thoughtlessly gets affected
will be forced to slow down his action.
After two balls collide,
hundreds of Bone Piercing Needles
inside it will be emitted,
to break radon protection barrier.
Extremely poisonous.
Once the needle is pierced,
the poison will spread quickly.
The bone will be ossified as it passes through.
The poison is held as core in the iron ball.
These Cluster Soul Chasing
Life Taking Balls are superb.
Little Freak, you can even create such a thing.
I really wonder what’s in your brain.
You’d gift me hundreds of it as respect.
Are these the jelly beans?
How can I have hundreds of it?
I only have two of it.
I’ve shown its power to you
as you didn’t believe me.
What? Only two? Then why did you try it?
Why didn’t you just tell me verbally?
Seeing is believing.
All right. Actually, I did make four of it.
I’ll give you two more then. Catch it.
Little Freak,
the battle of soul master will start soon, isn’t it?
You’d leave now.
If you’ve no enough experience,
how can you be The Grand
Soul Land Master in the future?
The outside world is much broader.
That’s the place where you should go.
You still owe me two wishes, right?
I’ll agree if it doesn’t go against my principles.
I’ve already thought it through.
Please, don’t regret it.
Thought it through?
Little Freak, stop there!
You allowed me to take the herbs.
Never break your promise!
For the second wish,
I want to take the herbs that I need from here.
You can’t stop me from doing it.
Just this one? This is too simple.
I can promise you.
Unbelievable.
I allowed you to take it.
But it doesn’t mean to take all of it.
I did leave the roots and seeds for you.
They’ll grow in a few years.
Since you’re going back to Shrek School with me,
you won’t need many herbs.
I’d have to think well of the third wish.
Stop the nonsense. Hurry up.
The third wish is
to invite you as a senior adviser in Shrek School.
No, I can’t. I hate to be restricted.
This is a matter of principle.
I can’t agree with it.
No one will restrict you.
You can come and go as you wish.
It’s just a title for you.
At least, I still can meet you
in a proper way.
Forget it. I’ll keep my promise
instead of arguing with you Little Freak.
You’re not mad anymore?
I hope you’ll not do it again.
Old Freak,
you’re suitable for our school.
Our Shrek School is also known as Devils School.
It’ll be wonderful to see
Old Freak teach Little Freak.
Stop the nonsense.
Hurry up and lead me the way.
When I arrive at the school later,
I’ll take Yan Yan over there for you to cure.
[Shrek school]
[Frander]
Please help me to make an inform.
Master.
Teachers, I’m back!
Little San, how are you?
Did he treat you badly?
No, he didn’t.
Senior Dugu treated me kindly.
Dean Frander,
Senior Dugu is willing
to be a senior adviser of our school.
What?
[Soul Land]
Can’t he?
Really?
He said, he’ll not stay at school.
He’ll just be an advisor here.
Dugu Bo has been very arrogant,
but he always keeps his promise.
Hi, Senior Dugu.
I promised Little Freak to be here as an adviser.
I’m not sure if you’re willing to accept me.
Of course, we’re much delighted.
Your presence will definitely
make Shrek School be more marvelous.
Since all of you have agreed,
you’d find me a quiet place then.
I’ve brought Tang San back to you all.
I’m tired now. Please take me for a rest.
Senior, please follow me.
Little San, how did you do it?
This old freak is willing to come to our school?
This is unbelievable!
Maybe we’re well connected.
With a Grand Soul Land Master here,
it’s a good thing for our school too.
Master, how’s everyone?
Xiao Wu, are you fine?
Everyone is fine. They’ve made great progress
for the past six months.
I told them that you’ve been
cultivating in seclusion.
You’re back at the right time!
Dai Mu Bai is in his progress to Level 40.
Perhaps in two days, we’ll hunt the soul beast
for his fourth soul ring together.
Master, I want to see them.
You just came back,
don’t you want to rest?
I’m not tired.
I brought some gifts for them.
Let’s go then. I’ll go with you.
Er Long, you may leave to the works first.
Master, you and Aunt Er Long...
You little kid, don’t ask so much!
Let’s go.
Your partners are cultivating
in virtual environments.
Little San,
what’s going on between you and Dugu Bo?
Dugu Bo sounds owing you a favor.
At first, it was Dugu Yan telling him
that I defeated her.
So, Dugu Bo took me away as he was interested
in my soul bone of Eight Spiders.
Later on, I found that there were
some flaws in his poison abilities.
He let go of me as I had helped him.
He even taught me something on using the poisons.
I see.
Little San, you’ve been studying poisons
with Dugu Bo for the past six months,
did your soul power keep it up with that?
All of your partners are really talented.
If you’ve fallen too far behind them,
it’ll be tough for you to catch up.
What’s your current soul power level?
I’m at Level 37 now.
Level 37...
What did you say?
Your soul power has reached Level 37?
Yes. Last time at Tian Dou Imperial School,
under the board member’s pressure
my soul power has reached Level 34.
Later, I cultivated at Senior Dugu Bo’s place,
I’ve advanced three more levels.
There are a lot of precious plants
at Senior Dugu’s place.
Maybe the environment
is suitable for me to cultivate.
My soul power was advanced fast.
It seems that my worries are unnecessary.
In less than half a year,
the Continental Competition of
Advanced Soul Master Schools will begin.
You probably have the chance
to reach Level 40 by the time.
By the time,
Shrek Seven Devils will be famous.
Xiao Wu, look who’s coming.
Grandmaster, you’re here.
Brother!
Brother, you don’t want me anymore?
How can you leave for such a long period?
Do you know how much I miss you?
It’s my bad to make you worry.
Please promise not to
leave me anymore.
You have to bring me along,
if you need to go for cultivation.
All right, I promise you.
Brother, please swear that
you’ll never leave me.
I swear. I’ll never leave you
unless I die.
I also swear that I’ll not leave Brother.
I’ll never leave even if you die.
This time, I won’t be afraid of you anymore.
Anyway, we have to settle all the past debts.
[Next Episode]
Brother San, where are the gifts?
Hurry and show us.
Xiao Wu, I promised to protect you forever.
No! Xiao Wu!
Brother.