♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this
when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] Tribe Chief,
the hidden weapons are powerful indeed.
We must ask the maker to join our tribe.
Tai Long is here again!
Did his father come too?
Not just his father,
his grandfather is here too!
So strong!
He is at a different level from Zhi Lin.
Is he a Great Soul Land Master?
Is that a soul bone? It’s an attached soul bone!
This kid is indeed awesome. Since it came to this...
[Soul Land]
[Episode 59]
Am I losing? Will I lose here?
You mustn’t let people know that
you are born with two Martial souls.
Do you admit your defeat?
No!
This is...
Rong Rong!
Qibao Amber Pagoda,
The Six Supplements!
I thought who is that.
It’s Grand Soul Master Bone and Tribe Chief Ning.
Greetings.
Old Ape, give me some face.
Call off the bet.
Fine. I’ll agree with that.
We’ll call off the bet.
You actually did that?
Old Ape, this is unlike your style.
Old Bone, look at what he’s holding.
This is Hao Tian...
It’s good you know that.
I’m just asking for embarrassment.
You will be the same too.
What a gentle strength.
My damaged body is recovering. Not just that,
with the combination of the
soul pressure and this gentle strength,
the Yangwei Meridian in my
Eight Meridian has been unlocked.
Brother, how do you feel?
I’m fine now.
It’s you?
We meet once again.
Dad, do you two know each other?
Greetings, Tribe Chief Ning.
You can just address me as Uncle.
You’re Tang San? Is your father Tang Hao?
How did you know that?
I’m Tai Tan. Greetings, Young Master.
Young Master? Senior, what are you doing?
Please get up.
My guests, welcome to Shrek School.
I’m the Deputy Dean, Zhao Wu Ji.
Please come in.
It’s you. I’ve been looking for you for a long time.
We can talk about that later.
Find a quiet room for us.
I need to talk to the Young Master.
You have a point.
Everyone, please.
Who asked you guys to come?
Go to your class immediately!
Little San, go and change your clothes first.
After that, come to the meeting room
on the 4th floor.
I’m completely healed
even though I am seriously injured.
Qibao Amber Pagoda is the strongest
Martial Soul of Support Branch indeed.
Senior Tai Tan is really strong.
He’s at least a Great Soul Land Master.
He knows my father. And...
I’m Tai Tan. Greetings, Young Master.
All of my questions will be answered.
I’ve arranged two rooms for both of the tribes.
You can decide which room you want to go first.
Remember to keep calm
no matter what they are going to say.
Thank you, Teacher Zhao.
I know what to do.
I’ve hurt you, Young Master.
Please punish me.
Senior, please get up.
I’m not your young master.
I’m just a normal civilian.
Your father is Tang Hao. He’s my master.
Young Master, you have Hao Tian Hammer.
I’m sure you’re my young master.
What did you say? Hao Tian...
I’m sure I’m not mistaken.
Young Master, you were holding
the unique Martial Soul that belongs
to the Hao Tian Tribe,
Hao Tian Hammer.
This is Hao Tian Hammer?
Come.
Unleash the other Martial soul that you have.
You’re Tang San? Your surname is Tang?
Don’t show this to anyone else.
So, Master knew about this a long time ago.
Why did he ask me to hide it?
Senior, can you tell me
who exactly is my father?
Did my master tell you nothing?
Young Master, can you tell me
your experiences with my master?
If my master didn’t say anything,
I wouldn’t dare to tell you.
My father and I lived
in the Soul Saint Village.
He was the only blacksmith in the village.
Besides working,
he only likes to drink.
A blacksmith?
Master, what happened to you?
In the past, you were the...
Senior, do you recognize these words?
[Soul Land]
When I was six,
my father left this letter for me
and he never came back.
Little San,
I would have been gone already
if you’re reading this letter.
Don’t come and find me. I’m useless.
You’re growing up.
I need to take back the things
that belonged to me.
Yes. These words are my master’s.
One day, we’ll be reunited.
I hope you grow strong.
But I hope you won’t grow strong too.
You must choose your own path.
If one day, you think to be a soul master is not good,
you can return to Soul Saint Village.
And be a blacksmith like me.
Don’t miss me.
Tang Hao.
Master.
How can you say you’re useless?
In my heart, you’re an honorable man.
Is my father really from Hao Tian Tribe?
Why did we end up living in that village then?
What exactly happened?
Please tell me!
Young Master, I’m unsure about
what happened to Master.
You only need to know
Master is an honorable man.
He’s the greatest man alive.
That’s all you should know.
The Li Tribe,
we were under the Hao Tian Tribe once.
We left the tribe because of Master.
We created our own tribe in Tian Dou City.
Now that you’ve appeared,
the Li Tribe will be under your command.
We have 217 soul masters in the tribe.
We’ll die for you.
We’ll die willingly for you, Young Master!
Senior, you’re Tai Long’s grandfather.
I’m his classmate.
I’m younger than him.
If you don’t mind,
I’ll address you as Grandpa Tai.
But...
Grandpa Tai, please don’t reject me.
I’ll meet Tribe Chief Ning right now.
Farewell.
Please keep my background a secret.
Young Master,
please be wary of Ning Feng Zhi.
Master once said that
Ning Feng Zhi is an ambitious man.
Grandpa Tai, don’t worry. I know what to do.
Hello, Uncle Ning. Sorry for the wait.
It’s nothing.
Have a seat.
Can I address you as Little San?
Of course. You’re Rong Rong’s father.
I heard about you from Rong Rong.
You impressed me
when we met at the auction house.
I didn’t expect you to be my friend’s son.
You know my father?
He’s the youngest Grand Soul Land Master
in Soul Land.
I believe almost all the people in this world
have heard of him.
Grand Soul Land Master?
He has been missing for many years.
I wonder where he is?
I don’t know about his whereabouts either.
He disappeared eight years ago.
Senior Tai Tan said my father
is from the Hao Tian Tribe.
He may be with the Hao Tian Tribe now.
No. That’s impossible.
Why?
I don’t know the reasons
and I can’t tell you why either.
Only your father has the right to tell you.
Little San, I came here today
because I wanted you to join our tribe.
But since you’re the son of my friend,
that’s impossible.
However,
I’m interested in your hidden weapons.
Are you willing to sell the method
of making the hidden weapons?
You can give me a price.
Impossible.
I won’t sell the methods to you.
But I promised Rong Rong that
I’ll sell the hidden weapons to her tribe.
You can be in charge of the process.
But the final step of assembling
must be completed by me.
Oh? But why?
Firstly, I spent a long time figuring them out.
I don’t want to sell it.
Secondly,
I need a few years at least
to teach the blacksmiths
how to make them.
But I need to train. I don’t have much time.
You have a point.
Uncle Ning, which hidden weapons
are you interested in?
We’ve seen Rong Rong’s hidden weapons.
I want a set just like hers.
I want 500 sets. I’ll give you
10,000 gold soul coins for each set.
What do you think?
The price is fine. But I need to say this first.
For the set of hidden weapons,
it does not include the
Flying Godly Claws on Rong Rong’s hand.
I can change it into Soundless Arrow.
Because the Flying Godly Claws
is not a hidden weapon.
And it’s made from prime materials.
It’s hard to make one.
Flying Godly Claws?
Rong Rong didn’t show it to us.
It looks like he knows how to
make more weapons.
Okay. Besides that, I’ll give you
one million gold soul coins.
As a sign of gratitude for
giving Rong Rong the Silk Woven Tulip.
Do you still have that plant?
I’ll buy it with a huge sum if you have it.
The Silk Woven Tulip is a rare grass.
It’s hard to find one.
That is a gift,
so I don’t need any rewards.
These are the blueprints of Soundless
Arrow, Shoe Crossbow, and Hidden Knife.
Let me say this first.
I’m only in charge of the final steps.
Regarding the initial steps,
Uncle Ning, please think of something.
I heard that your tribe has your own blacksmiths.
I don’t think this is hard for you.
Kid, you’re a good businessman.
You don’t even need to make the parts yourself.
Isn’t it too easy to gain 50,000 gold soul coins?
Uncle Bone.
[Next Episode]
Are you saying that my father
came to see me before?
Uncle Bone, please don’t say that again.
If we continue to let him grow,
he’ll be a threat to us.
What are you guys doing?
Are you saying that
my father would hurt Brother San?
No. I need to clarify things with Oscar.
We only have one goal.
Since you want to be a soul master,
you mustn’t stop.
Why did you think I wouldn’t come back?
Do you guys want to ask me something?