♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Teacher Zhao.
Want to escape?
Fourth and fifth soul skill are used at once.
This is Teacher Zhao’s real power.
Teacher Zhao held back during the exam previously.
If that so,
we’ll deal with it by the soul master rules.
Battle with my granddaughter.
The loser will not get the soul ring.
I’ll fight on behalf of Little Ao.
Tang San,
Martial Soul is Blue Silver Plant.
Blue Silver Plant?
A useless Martial Soul.
Intertwine.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 23]
Little rascal,
there is poison all over my snake scepter.
You’re seeking death!
Unfortunately, your poison is useless on me.
How dare you!
A battle of soul power?
Come on then.
They’re battling on soul power.
How much soul power do you have
to battle with me?
Teacher Zhao.
This kid should be no problem, right?
Little San is...
quite amazing.
Her soul power is higher than mine.
However, Xuan Tian Strike is the inner
martial arts of superior sect.
To grow and multiply without end.
She’s not my opponent if we continue.
Why am I not winning yet?
She’s anxious.
Little San has the upper hand.
No.
I cannot lose.
Since you’re so persistent.
Fine.
Let’s see who falls first.
We lost.
How about both of us fight together?
Okay!
Ready!
Let go!
Madam Chao,
what do you think?
I admit that I lost.
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent is yours now.
Little rascal! Hurry up!
Grandma.
We lost.
Let’s talk about it after we meet your grandpa.
I’ll remember what happened today.
Acala,
see you.
Beware.
Let’s leave immediately
after both of them wake up.
Oscar. You’re awake.
Little Ao, you’re awake.
Hurry!
Show us what the skill of
your new soul ring is!
Fatty, go farther.
You’re too close.
Little rascal.
Tell us what your new soul skill is.
Forget about it. Let’s talk when we go back.
Why? Are you afraid that
we will laugh at you?
Little rascal,
don’t hide it.
Don’t keep us guessing.
We won’t laugh at you.
Okay, promise.
Don’t laugh at me.
We won’t laugh.
Hurry up.
You guys step aside.
Let me show you.
Flying
Mushroom Sausage!
Didn’t you promise not to laugh?
Little Ao,
why is your curse so weird?
It’s none of your business.
I’ll show you my third soul skill.
Don’t be frightened.
Oscar, this is...
This is Flying?
Beware of the surroundings.
Little Ao,
this skill is awesome.
How long can you fly?
It’s about 1 minute.
Only 1 minute?
It’s as short as your sausage.
It’s impossible.
The soul ring on Phoenix Tail
Crest Serpent is so useless.
I haven’t finish my words.
What?
Flying for one minute...
couldn’t even pass a slightly wide river.
If flying for 1 minute in
the Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent’s speed?
What?
Oh,
that’s not bad.
Little Ao,
are you sure?
I’m sure.
It may be even faster.
That is
so amazing!
Great.
At least what we did paid off.
Little Ao,
with your current soul power,
how many of such Mushroom Sausages can you make?
For one time...
it should be less than 10.
Ten is already good.
When your soul power increases,
it will increase.
Okay.
Go and get ready.
We’ll go back immediately after Little San wakes up.
Teacher Zhao,
we may not go back to school yet.
[Soul Land]
Little San,
you’re awake!
Hey, Little San is awake.
Little San,
you’re awake.
What do you mean that we can’t go back to school?
This Star Dou Forest is not for fun.
Since Little Ao has got his soul ring,
we must go back as soon as possible.
Otherwise,
I couldn’t explain...
if anything happens to you.
But...
I need a soul ring too.
There’s no such thing as but.
What?
What did you say?
Well.
I have also reached Level 30 just now.
Little San,
you’ve reached Level 30?
Level 30?
Teacher Zhao,
can we stay on to search for
a suitable soul beast for me?
Of course, we can.
Little San,
congrats for being
the youngest Soul Honor in Shrek.
Little San,
you’re really the best among the Shrek’s monsters.
Little Ao,
pinch me...
to see if I’m dreaming.
Congratulations.
Brother, congratulations.
But I’ll catch up with you soon.
Okay.
It’s getting late.
Let’s move on.
Let’s depart to get a soul beast for Little San.
Don’t let your guard down.
The danger of Star Dou Forest...
goes far beyond this.
Yes, Teacher Zhao!
Brother,
what happened?
Nothing.
Is it an illusion?
Tonight, let’s cultivate and regulate.
We’ll continue to help Little San
find his soul beast tomorrow.
Little San,
are you anxious?
It’s all about luck to find a soul beast.
Teacher Zhao, you can rest assured.
I am patient.
In the past, there were many
Millennium Soul Beasts...
even at the outer part of the Star Dou Forest.
Now,
I wonder if they have gone to
the inner part of the forest...
or there is any other reasons.
No matter what the reason is,
it’s caused by us human beings.
Although soul beasts are ferocious,
human are even more ferocious.
Soul master kills soul beast indiscriminately.
Even if there are more soul beasts,
they will decrease or even disappear.
Human cultivation can only last a few decades.
Soul beasts cultivate
for a century
up to thousand years.
Soul masters aren’t many.
But, every soul master could have to
hunt for at least 5 to 6 soul beasts.
Besides that,
how many people out there...
hunt soul beasts indiscriminately for living?
So,
maybe one day the profession of soul master...
would have no soul rings to use.
You are right.
But you and I can’t control that.
All we can do is...
to find soul rings for the cultivation
and avoid indiscriminate killing.
Teacher Zhao,
previously...
Prepare to fight!
Teacher Zhao, what happened?
Prepare to escape.
No matter what happens later,
just leave me alone.
Escape the forest with all your strength!
Mu Bai. Protect them.
Understand?
Yes, Teacher Zhao!
Little Ao, get the Mushroom Sausage ready.
Flying Mushroom Sausage.
Flying...
[Next Episode]
This is...
King of Forest, Titan King Ape.
How could Titan King Ape appears at
the outer part of Star Dou Forest?
What can I do?
Mu Bai.
Bring them out.
Hurry!
Little Ao,
I beg you.
I have to go get Xiao Wu.
If I don’t go now,
I will regret for life.