♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
As long as Tang San
from Controlling Branch isn’t here,
soul masters of Controlling Branch
can restrain other soul masters.
Shrek School isn’t that good after all.
The winner of this qualifying round is
Shrek School.
They’ve won seven times in a row.
This is Martial Soul restraint.
Tang San, I would like to talk to you.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 87]
Brother, just now...
Huo Wu insisted that I have saved her,
and she wanted to return me a favor, so...
Brother, look at me.
I’ve grabbed it, so others don’t have to
keep thinking about it.
Tang San.
Coming right up, Shrek School.
They have won ten times consecutively.
Up to this point, we have won
11 times consecutively.
We’re in the first place
together with Shen Feng School.
But the last three rounds will be very tough.
Especially two strong opponents,
Shen Feng School and Lei Ting School,
which we didn’t meet in preliminary rounds.
We’re fighting Lei Ting School today.
Their overall strength is
higher than Chi Huo School.
They can even specifically restrain
Tian Shui School and School of Florals.
The only match they lost,
was the one against Shen Feng School.
Master, let me join the match today.
Little San, your Blue Silver Plant
is immune to water and fire,
but it’s not immune to lightning.
It’ll even be restrained
when facing Lightning Martial Soul.
Because your Blue Silver Plant
isn’t completely insulated.
If you’re injured or defeated today,
if we face Shen Feng School tomorrow,
the chance of victory will be greatly reduced.
So I’ll be kept to fight Shen Feng School?
I’ve observed the strength
of Shen Feng School in detail.
Among the Five Elements Schools,
they’re no doubt the strongest team.
In order to defeat them, you have to give your best.
You must have faith
in your partners in today’s match.
I’ll announce the list of participants.
The sequence is Tai Long, Jing Ling,
Huang Yuan, Xiao Wu, Dai Mu Bai,
Zhu Zhu Qing, Ma Hong Jun.
Is there any question?
No.
Don’t worry, Little San.
Let us handle this round.
We’ll count on you
to fight Shen Feng School.
Alright.
Shrek, wins!
This is the first match between
Shrek School and Lei Ting School.
Under Lu Chen’s strong attack,
can Tai Long only defend passively?
Tai Long, the trick for you
against Lei Ting School
is one word, delay.
Use your defence skill
to delay until the opponent’s
soul power is exhausted.
The attack of lightning is so strong.
Can Tai Long take it?
What an awesome attack.
Congratulations, Shrek School.
Second round.
[Lei Ting vs. Shrek]
Lei Ting School is sending Xiao Yun Ju.
Can he win this round for Lei Ting School?
Seal!
The weather is worsening.
Tai Long is trapped by him again.
Could this be...
Kill!
Tai Long.
Trust him. Tai Long is a descendant of Li Tribe.
Such an insignificant Soul Honor
defeated two of my teammates.
[Lei Ting vs. Shrek]
Third round. Tai Long of Shrek School
versus Lei Jiu Chong of Lei Ting School.
[Lei Ting vs. Shrek]
Tai Long is defeated.
Congratulations, Lei Ting School.
Fourth round. Shrek School is sending Jing Ling.
What would he bring into play?
Tai Long’s performance
is more outstanding than I expected.
Although he has won,
Lei Jiu Chong’s soul power has been depleted.
Start!
Jing Ling, as a soul master
of Keen Attack Branch,
has the biggest advantage of speed.
Your trick consists of only one word,
hide.
Let’s see how long you can hide.
Fourth round, Shrek School won.
Curse you.
For the next round,
Lei Ting School is finally sending a Soul Sect,
Lei Mie.
All four Soul Sects of Lei Ting School
are arranged to enter the arena later.
Jing Ling and Huang Yuan
have lower soul power levels.
The chance of victory isn’t high.
Lei Mie has defeated Jing Ling and Huang Yuan.
For the seventh round,
Shrek School is sending a Soul Honor
at Level 39 of Storm Attack Branch, Xiao Wu.
After six rounds of exciting and speedy matches,
the one who’s left on the stage is
Xiao Wu from Shrek School.
The next one who’s representing Lei Ting School
is a Soul Sect at Level 42
of Storm Attack Branch, Lei Tian.
They’re planning to deplete our strength
with a few Soul Honors.
This match is the key.
I can’t lose, and I have to settle this quick
to keep my strength in order to fight Dai Mu Bai.
[Soul Land]
What kind of performance would Xiao Wu have,
after defeating a Soul Sect at a higher level?
Seventh round, begins.
Third soul skill, Wings of Lightning.
Fourth soul skill, Lightning Eagle.
The flying ability of Lei Tian can
restrain soul masters who attack close.
Such height is beyond
the attacking area of the opponent.
Yet the opponent is still not taking action.
When Lei Tian is done reserving
the energy and lock the target,
you can’t escape even if you try.
Lightning Eagle Shield Body.
My Lightning Eagle has covered
the range of your Teleport.
You can’t escape.
- Eagle eyes locked on.
- Third soul skill, Teleport.
What? She’s gone?
Rapid speed. I can’t lock in time.
Lei Tian is surrounded by lightning.
I can’t get close.
Let’s see how you can hide
from my attack in the air.
Second soul skill, Charm.
The opponent is using
the strongest soul skill right away.
He probably wants to settle this quick.
But it’s too energy-depleting. He’s tricked by Xiao Wu.
The guidance I gave Xiao Wu is the word, dodge.
Xiao Wu has handled the match quite well.
She unsparingly used
her third soul skill, Teleport.
It forced Lightning Eagle
to be distracted.
Hence, she was able to mesmerize the opponent.
Shrek School won the seventh round.
Good one, Shrek School.
I didn’t expect them to defeat
Lei Ting School so easily.
Your Majesty, could you tell
why Shrek School can win continuously?
Of course, because of their strength.
Your Majesty, you’re half right.
Strength is surely important.
But one can’t achieve
such level just with strength.
The key to Shrek’s advantage
is their strategy and team arrangement.
According to what you two said,
this is no coincidence.
With that person, how is this a coincidence?
The choice of the Pope is indeed right.
That person has studied
Martial Soul profoundly.
No wonder he’s made the Honourary Elder.
Chief Salas, what do you mean?
Why don’t Your Majesty ask Chief Ning?
I shall leave now.
Your Majesty, this person is Tang San’s teacher.
The Grandmaster from the tribe
of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
He has become the Honourary Elder of
Martial Soul Hall at about Level 30.
His profound study of Martial Soul
made me ashamed of my inferiority.
Chief Ning is giving high praise to the Grandmaster.
Your Majesty, those who have Grandmaster
have the world.
It seems like I should meet this Grandmaster.
Chief Ning, please arrange it
after the qualifying rounds.
Your Majesty, if you would like
to solicit Grandmaster, start with Tang San.
Only this disciple
that he cares the most
can decide his direction.
Next, Vice Captain of Lei Ting School,
Lei Dong.
A Soul Sect of Controlling Branch at Level 43.
A very strong opponent.
How would Shrek School respond?
Eighth round, begins.
Little San, pay attention to Lei Dong’s battle.
He has spider type Martial Soul.
Since your third and fourth soul rings
are originated from spiders,
so is your soul bone,
his battle method may inspire you.
He closed eyes.
It seems he’s taking precautions
against Xiao Wu’s Charm.
Third soul skill, Web of Lightning.
From the look of its form,
Lei Dong’s Martial Soul, Lightning Spider,
is similar to Eight Spider Bone.
Eight Spider Bone is venomous.
It works well with Blue Silver Plant.
It has a balanced attack and defence power.
Lightning Spider is controlled
with the help of current flow.
Its attacking power is stronger.
The Web of Lightning is like his eyes,
having the movement of the arena in hand.
Xiao Wu, you must be careful.
What?
How can this be?
The Web of Lightning is sort of sucking.
But my soul power isn’t enough
for continuous Teleport.
What should I do?
First soul skill, Silk of Lightning.
I finally get the chance.
Take my first soul skill, Arched Body.
She escaped from Lei Tian’s attack just now.
She hasn’t experienced
the power of lightning.
Impossible. You’ve penetrated
the Web of Lightning.
Your body should be numb.
Your Web of Lightning can
attack strongly but defense weakly.
The core is the weakest part
of the lightning.
If this keeps going, I’ll be screwed
when she closes up.
I have to use my fourth soul skill.
Activate. Fourth soul skill,
God Locking Ring.
[Next Episode]
Boss Dai, count on you now.
Don’t stop me.
Dai Mu Bai, you have to pay for
what you’ve done.
I left home to Tian Dou Empire,
so I can make myself stronger.
I can’t lose.
We surrender.
If that’s the case, we’ll decide
the victory with one match.
Everyone trusts you.
Tang San, I admire you.
But I must defeat you today.