♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Looks like
he acquired a great skill
for his fourth soul ring.
God, why are you punishing me like this?
Xiao Gang, you are here,
but I still feel distant from you.
How dare you interrupt me!
I’ll make you regret your actions!
This is not miasma. They’re Pink Lady!
What? More than a thousand?
I’m sure a Pink Madam is leading the group.
We’re surrounded.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 63]
What’s a Pink Lady?
Pink Lady is a scorpion-like soul beast.
They stay in groups.
They rarely attack humans.
Because their bodies are
pinkish and transparent,
they’re known as Pink Lady.
A group of Pink Lady consists
of around 100 of them.
The strongest one leads the group.
How do they attack?
Do they only use poison?
Yes. Although their poison is not very strong,
it’s a stimulant.
If you inhale too much of it, you will die.
I’m sure
there’s a Pink Madam in this group.
Pink Madam?
Pink Madam is a mutation of Pink Lady.
It should have lived for 3,000 years.
It has consumed at least 100 men.
But I don’t understand.
Why are they so hostile towards us?
It seems like they’re ambushing us.
Master, do you think
the King of the Land yesterday is the reason?
It is a scorpion-like soul beast
as the Pink Lady.
Maybe they’re connected.
Don’t tell me
the King of the Land yesterday
was the Pink Madam’s mate?
Soul beasts communicate in their ways.
Before The King of the Land died,
it may release some scent
to alert the Pink Madam.
You tortured her husband.
Now, she wants her revenge.
Revenge? Fine, I’ll face her head-on.
I’ll let them die together.
The poison mist of 1,000 Pink Lady is no joke.
You mustn’t be careless.
Little San, you know more about poison.
What’s your suggestion?
The safest way is to
escape this forest by using
Little Ao’s Flying Mushroom Sausage.
Okay. We’ll follow your order.
Okay!
No! I can’t stand this!
Let’s follow her.
Don’t kill them!
Pink Madam? Er Long, come back!
Little San, join her.
But don’t kill the beast.
Brother San, assist me!
Third soul skill, Flying Phoenix!
Go!
Constraint of Spider Web!
Fourth soul skill,
Phoenix Strike!
Oscar, kill it now!
The eyes are her weakness.
Kill her and absorb her soul ring.
Don’t be smug. Sit down and meditate.
Grandmaster, why are you asking Oscar
to absorb the Pink Madam’s soul ring?
Although it’s quite old,
it’s not very strong.
There are no strong or weak soul beasts,
if it is suitable for us.
After he acquires his fourth soul ring,
your team’s capability will be improved.
Master, are you saying that
after Little Ao acquires his fourth
soul ring from this beast,
he can produce the same poison?
Yes.
Soul masters of Food Branch
won’t produce any poison
even if they absorb
venomous soul beasts.
That’s why,
after Oscar absorbs the skills of Pink Madam,
his skill will change
into increasing our boost with his sausages
in an all-round way.
Just like the bloodlust effect of
the Frenzy Battle Team.
An all-round boost?
I think Oscar is in pain.
I think the grudges of the Pink Madam are deep.
Xiao Gang, what do you think
of Hong Jun’s attack just now?
It’s pretty good.
Regarding explosive strength,
Fatty is the strongest among Shrek Seven Devils.
He’s even stronger than Mu Bai.
Phoenix Flame is included in his strike as well.
It has extremely high temperature
and it can latch onto opponents.
We need to thank Er Long for that.
If she killed the soul beast directly,
Fatty wouldn’t get to enjoy this special perk.
Frander,
did you see Fatty’s weakness just now?
Weakness?
[Soul Land]
Are you talking about his continuous attack?
His explosive strength is strong,
but he used too much soul power for that.
At the same time, there’s a problem.
His fourth soul skill, Phoenix Strike,
is an adaptation of the
King of the Land’s Lava Strike.
There are two parts to it.
First, it stuns the opponent
using its air pressure.
Second, it unleashes its strongest strike
while the opponent is stunned.
Yeah.
Because of that,
Fatty has the same weakness
as the Land of the King,
the attack range.
Hong Jun’s Phoenix Strike needs to
get close to an enemy to stun them.
He can’t lock an opponent and stun them.
But his opponent wouldn’t let him
stun them that easily.
Although Flying Phoenix provides him
with a short flying time,
it boosts his fire ability and overall strength,
not his speed.
Because of that,
he needs a partner to land his strike
even though it’s very strong.
Are you saying that
someone needs to restrict
his opponents for him first?
Only then, he can deliver
his devastating Phoenix Strike?
Exactly.
As for their coordination,
we need to research that.
We can’t afford to let him waste his soul power.
These children are so talented.
All of them can be considered geniuses.
By the way,
when do you plan to allow Little San
to train his second Martial Soul?
We must at least wait until he’s at Level 80.
When the contest is over,
I’ll need to visit The Sacred Temple.
You want to see her? Aren’t you afraid
Er Long would get angry?
You need to help me by then.
For Little San, I need to see her.
Wait, you...
Little Ao, what’s your fourth soul skill?
My fourth soul skill is Stimulate.
Stimulating Sausage!
Those who consume it will get a
10% boost in all stats for five minutes.
10% boost only? For five minutes?
Your soul skill...
Boss Dai, listen carefully.
It’s a boost for all your stats.
It means that after you consume it,
your overall strength will be
instantly increased by 10%.
It’s not as easy as you think.
He’s right. 10% may not
sound like a great boost,
but you can fight with
110% of your strength right away.
And it has no negative effects.
You guys can unleash your greatest
strength in a short time.
During battles,
you’ll understand the usefulness
of his fourth soul skill.
But Grandmaster, this skill has two flaws.
First, the duration is too short.
Second, it can’t last long.
After I summon it,
it needs to be consumed within one minute.
But there are some benefits to it too.
I don’t need to use much soul power for this.
It’s almost the same as Flying Mushroom Sausage.
And there are no side effects.
Based on that point,
it’s much stronger than most
of the supporting skills.
Okay. Let’s move on.
Only three people are left
without their soul rings.
I hope you can find what you want.
Let’s rest here.
Although there are many soul beasts
in the Sunset Forest,
not many of them are powerful.
We’ve been searching for two days.
If this continues,
I’m afraid we can’t make it for the contest.
Dean Frander, I have an idea.
But it’s quite risky.
You should’ve told me earlier.
What’s your idea?
This is the Fragrant Silk Woven Flower
that I used two days ago.
With its natural aura,
it’ll attract powerful soul beasts.
Since that’s the case,
we’ll surely get our soul rings then!
But, under this circumstance,
powerful beasts will come
and they’ll come in huge numbers.
Little San, do you still remember where Du Gu Bo lived?
Master, are you saying that
we can use the poison
that the Old Freak left to protect us?
Yes.
Outside the Ice Fire Mouth Spring
that Du Gu Bo lived in the past,
there’s a poison trap guarding the place.
We just need to put the Fragrant Silk
Woven Flower near the poison trap.
If the beasts are too strong for us,
we can retreat to the poison trap.
Little San, what is this? It stinks!
This is to get rid of soul beasts
that are 2,000 years old and below.
Old Freak set up an extremely
poisonous trap around here.
Consume either one of these,
you’ll be protected for one day.
Consume another one tomorrow.
I think two days are enough for us.
It’s coming.
Dragon summons clouds, tiger summons wind.
I think it’s a tiger-like soul beast. Be careful.
I didn’t even lift a finger
and it’s defeated already.
Brother San, a Millennium Soul Beasts
is not that strong after all.
This is bad!
[Next Episode]
Er Long, there are kids here.
Don’t spill too much blood.
I know that!
If you have time to think of that,
you should think about yourself!
Soul shock will destroy a person’s mentality.
It may cause that person to become an idiot.
Soul shock?
Retreat to the poison trap!
Third soul skill, Nether Slash!
This is bad!
That tiger picked the weakest spot to attack us.
What a strong defense!
The left one is the real one! Mu Bai! Be careful!
Fourth soul skill, White Tiger Meteor Strike!
Zhu Qing!