♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Both teams, get ready.
Begin!
What?
If you think of taking advantage of these girls,
you will be wrong.
They would have...
It’s bad. It’s Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
It’s the Mighty Beast Soul, Ice Phoenix.
Ice Phoenix is a Mighty Beast Soul that
is comparable with Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
Little San, can you resist it?
I can’t be defeated.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 80]
Brother!
What did happen just now?
The snow is so heavy that we can’t see clearly.
The stage is totally frozen.
How could Tian Shui be forced to this degree?
Boss, Shui Bing Er was not injured at all.
But why do they look very weak?
Nonsense. The power of
drifting snow is so strong.
Shui Bing Er and Xue Wu are worn out.
This is terrifying. But why haven’t
Tang San get defeated yet?
This is the scary part of Tang San.
Can you tell me the reason?
I have ice immunity. You can’t restrict me.
Then, why were you restricted
by me earlier?
My ice and fire immunity is
only effective in energy form.
The physical form and energy shock
will still hurt me.
I see. We’ve lost.
No. It should be us who lost.
It was my mistake that led to this ending.
My ice and fire resistance
don’t originate from cultivation.
And I was forced to use Eight Spider Bone,
which should be used only in the final match.
You two finished the battle?
I’ve lost.
It’s a tie match.
We’ve already used up the soul power.
All right.
I announce that the match between
Shrek and Tian Shui Schools
ended in a tie.
Finally, both of you are back.
Let me have a look at the qualifying certificate.
[Qualifying Certificate]
[Reward: 10,000 gold-soul coins]
Sorry, Master. It’s my fault.
I underestimated the opponent
before the match.
Hence, I didn’t deliver relevant tactics in time.
Little San, you’ve done a good job.
No one would blame you.
It’s more important that
we could find the root of defeat.
It’s right, Brother San.
Because we have to hide our strength this time.
Next time, I’ll show them my Phoenix Flame.
Who knows I can burn seven of them at once.
Failure is the mother of success.
In other words, we’ve not lost,
but a step closer to the triumph.
It’s a pleasant thing to discover
your deficiencies in advance.
There’s still a long way
to go for you guys.
You still have plenty of time
to change yourself.
Master, Empire and Martial Soul Hall
seems to have conflict.
Each qualified team for the coming
tournament are the Empire’s future hope.
I’ll confer the title of viscount
to both captains of the team
and also the title of baron
to the other teammates.
The fiefdom will be allocated
after you graduate.
Your Majesty, this seems to be inappropriate.
There’s no precedent of
awarding the title of nobility.
Moreover, the awarded title seems to be too high.
Your Mightiness, Platinum Chief,
conferring the titles of nobility
is an internal matter of the Empire,
unrelated to Martial Soul Hall.
If there’s any team from Tian Dou Empire
can obtain the final victory,
everyone’s titles of nobility in the
team will be promoted one more level.
And its school will also be
given the prefix of Imperial,
receiving financial support from the Empire.
Shen Feng School, Lei Ting School,
Shrek School,
Chi Huo School, Tian Shui School,
you are the top five outstanding schools
among the many.
I hope that all of you can perform
your best in the qualifying rounds.
By the time, three of
the most outstanding students
will obtain the soul beast furnished by
the Empire for your next advance level.
You can choose any soul beast
of below 30,000-year cultivation.
Brilliant, Your Majesty.
They even promise to furnish
Decade Millennium Soul Beast.
Obviously, they want you
to choose between the Empire
and Martial Soul Hall.
Master,
do you think that His Majesty
is just showing his protest to Martial Soul Hall
or
their conflict has already
reached an irreconcilable state?
It will certainly become unpeaceful soon.
What do both of you discuss?
Little San, don’t be sad.
By being able to place
before Chi Huo and Tian Shui
is a pride of our Shrek School.
I don’t have to worry about
the advertising costs anymore.
Wait!
Tang San.
Stop there.
Do you dare to have a battle
with me without the martial soul?
I’m not available.
You go to hell!
[Soul Land]
Tang San, I want to kill you.
Let’s go.
Disgusting!
Don’t waste your energy. You’re not his opponent.
Brother!
My silly sister, if you really want to defeat him,
then you’ve to cultivate ceaselessly.
We still have a chance in the qualifying round.
Encountering an opponent
who can fully restrain our attribute,
we have to come up with new solutions.
Count me on, Sister Huo Wu.
I didn’t encounter him in the preliminary.
I’ll help you defeat him in the qualifying rounds.
Master. Everyone.
There’s still one month to go
to the next tournament.
I need to have self-seclusion.
You can go. I’ll train them.
This is just a temporary defeat.
The more challenging battles
are yet to come in the future.
In one month,
I’ll conduct a
strengthening training for all of you.
I’ll also help with supervision and guidance.
If there’s anyone who dares to be lazy,
I don’t mind doubling the training.
Oh, no.
Due to my carelessness,
I caused the entire team to lose.
Without Eight Spider Bone,
without Fiery Soft Apricot
and Octa Dark Frost,
without Decade Millennium Soul Ring,
what else do I have?
Perhaps, Blue Silver Plant
is not worth of cultivating,
should I choose a more powerful
martial soul to cultivate?
What else do I have?
I possess poison abilities.
Perhaps, the poison ability of Tang Clan
has the potential to develop
in this Soul Land.
It’s been ten years already.
Do you finally admit your fate?
Ten years ago, I was nearly
killed by you and Old Ghost.
Today, it is time for me to take revenge.
Taking revenge?
You were fortunate enough to
encounter Prince Xue Xing’s patrol team.
Xue Xing forced us to withdraw
by Tian Dou Empire’s military power.
If not, you might have died already.
Because my life shouldn’t be ended yet.
Ju Hua Guan, I’ll take you down today.
Old Venom Freak,
you have no Prince Xue Xing’s help for this time.
Fifth soul skill,
Frosty Gather.
This broken flying knives only deplete my power.
I have to find a chance
to approach Ju Hua Guan.
Third soul skill,
Jade Phosphor Enchanted Formation.
How fast his speed is!
Wasn’t he deeply poisoned?
Maybe his poison was...
Luckily, Little Freak helped me
detoxify my poison.
My speed has been greatly improved.
Ju Hua Guan, go to hell.
Jade Phosphor Serpent King Venom.
Clouds of Golden Pistil.
I used the method of Little Freak
to store all the poisons into the soul bone.
Unexpectedly, Jade Phosphor
Serpent King Venom
works well with Medusa Soul Bone.
Thus, a more formidable
Serpent Venom was produced.
Even if your Serpent Venom became stronger,
how could you surpass the oppression of
three-level soul power?
Moreover, I’m
the Grand Soul Land Master at Level 95.
[Next Episode]
Once a soul master reaches Level 90,
every level will be vastly different.
Not to mention three levels.
Everyone’s cultivation has
made progress recently.
You’re awesome, Xiao Wu.
I’ve already reached Level 39.
I wonder how about Brother’s cultivation.
Tang San.
Tang San’s soul power improvement is too fast.
It’s not that I have no confidence in you.
Instead, you have no chance at all.