♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Little San, I’m still alive.
Master, you’re alive well.
I can attack anywhere within 50 meters.
Intertwine...
is the feature of
Controlling Branch’s soul master.
Keep this book.
It’s about my study on the training of soul power.
I heard the apprentice and Boss Xiao
are starting a fight.
Come on!
Fighting against the wolf’s claws of Boss Xiao?
He’s asking for death.
Blue Silver Plant. Intertwine!
Hello, Mr. Su Yun Tao.
He’s the child I’ve mentioned to you.
Please verify him.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 9]
Here is the lowest-level of Martial Soul Hall.
It’s also known as Martial Soul Branch Hall.
No matter how small a city is in this land,
there will be a Martial Soul Hall in this size.
In the branch hall, there’s a sub-hall.
The level higher is Martial Soul Main Hall.
The level of Martial Soul Main Hall...
is only available in big cities.
In the capital of both kingdoms,
there are the Martial Soul Temples of 4th level
The 5th level is the Sacred Temple.
That’s the holiest place of Martial Soul Hall.
Actually, above the Sacred Temple,
there’s the legendary Soul Land Shrine.
But only soul masters that achieved
the highest soul level...
are qualified to go there.
That’s the dream of every soul master.
Thank you for telling me all these,
Grandpa Ma Xiu Nuo.
Can we start now?
Nowadays, youngsters are so impatient.
Okay, we may start now.
This is Blue Silver Plant.
Is there a problem, Grandpa Ma Xiu Nuo?
It’s a century soul ring.
No wonder even the Blue Silver Plant
has such a big change.
It seems like you had a good teacher
in Nuoding School.
Sadly, the Blue Silver Plant
has low potential to develop.
Focus your soul power in it.
Show me which level you’ve achieved.
Accordingly, you should be 11...
This is...
Level 13 of soul power.
Level 13 of soul power?
That isn’t right. How could you skip 2 levels?
Child, can you tell me...
which soul beast you hunted to get this soul ring?
Datura Snake.
What?
Datura Snake?
Datura Snake from Animal Branch?
How can Plant Branch use soul ring
of Animal Branch?
It’s possible, Grandpa Ma Xiu Nuo.
It can be done under certain circumstances.
My master called it
the Theory of Martial Soul Mimicry.
Who is your master?
Everyone calls him Grandmaster.
Grandmaster?
He’s the Grandmaster who came up with
10 Core Competing Power of Martial Soul,
and then was expelled by Martial Soul Hall?
Turns out he was from Martial Soul Hall.
Tang San, are you willing
to join Martial Soul Hall?
Grandpa Ma Xiu Nuo, am I not here for registration?
No, this isn’t the same.
Joining Martial Soul Hall...
meaning you’ll be an exclusive
soul master of Martial Soul Hall.
The training of soul masters will
start directly in our special school.
That’s impossible.
I’m already learning in Nuoding School.
It’s indeed too late.
Even if we’re the Martial Soul Hall,
we can’t snatch you from another school.
I’m afraid the Grandmaster wouldn’t agree
with you joining us either.
It’s all Su Yun Tao’s fault.
He should have brought you
to Martial Soul Hall directly.
You can’t say that.
If I were to come here first,
I wouldn’t get such a good soul ring.
That’s right.
Alright. Welcome to the team of soul masters.
From now on,
you’re an honored soul master of Tian Dou Empire.
Boy, it’s dangerous here. Get out.
Get an adult if you want to buy something.
Hello, Uncle. Do you need an apprentice here?
Stop it. Get off.
Look at you, you don’t look like
a blacksmith at all.
Sorry, Uncle. I’ll be back later.
Uncle, can I be an apprentice now?
Boy, are you making fun of me?
Uncle, I’m an apprentice of Nuoding School.
I have time every afternoon.
My father is a blacksmith.
I have been learning to forge from him.
If you’re willing, you may come.
You may serve as a handyman.
The salary isn’t high.
But you’ll be fed. How about that?
No problem.
Stop staring, start working.
I’ll treat all of you to wine tonight.
Okay. Keep it up, brothers.
You said you had learned to forge
from your father.
What did your father teach you
when you were so young?
Forging, of course.
I might look small.
But I’m strong. Forging isn’t a problem for me.
Brothers.
Our new worked claims he can forge.
Let me try it if you don’t believe it.
What about this?
If you can carry this hammer, I’ll believe you.
[Soul Land]
You’re trying to remove the impurities
of this pig iron, right?
Uncle, please pull the bellows. It’s not hot enough.
Hold on.
If you keep hammering like this,
it wouldn’t be small even after a year.
What should I do then?
Tell me.
Which part of your body do you use
when you wield the hammer?
It should be waist.
From waist to back to move the hand.
Besides the brain,
what’s the most important organ?
Heart.
How many hearts does one have?
Ah?
Answer me.
One.
No, you’re wrong. Not one.
It’s three.
Your calf muscles...
are your second and third hearts.
When one...
wants to release all his power,
all three hearts must be functioning
at the same time.
You shouldn’t start from your waist
when you work hard.
The three hearts should be your starting point.
Start from the hearts,
use your back as an axis. Look.
This is...
Try it.
Dad, did I do it right?
Do you know the function
of the hearts now?
The most used muscle is calf muscles.
Calf muscles are the source of power.
When you use the power of calf muscles well,
your power will be increased.
Here.
Do as I did.
Pay attention to my next action.
Right. It’s taking advantage of another power.
Such a beautiful skill of hammering.
Do you understand now?
Take advantage of another power.
I understand the theory.
But this doesn’t look simple.
If you want to achieve my level,
you have to practice more.
The key is to control your power when you forge.
Carry on practicing.
Don’t increase your power and speed blindly.
Accuracy is also important.
You need to know the aim of your hammer.
Start from the calf muscles, to the heart.
Waist as axis, pass the power up.
Powerful. You’re really the son of a blacksmith.
Could this be...
the Skill of Random Hammering?
The most powerful continuous hammering skill.
What’s that?
Skill of Random Hammering is
a skill of continuous hammering.
Taking advantage of another power.
It can release the power
of a blacksmith perfectly.
I heard the most powerful one...
can hammer 81 times continuously.
The pig iron can be hammered
into the desired shape directly.
Skill of Random Hammering is the best
way to remove the impurities of metal.
I thought it’s lost.
[One year later]
Little San.
When will we arrive at your place?
Soon. I’ve told you,
my family is poor. I have nothing to serve you.
It’s okay.
My father has a bad temper.
I’ll be good.
I hope so.
What? You don’t want me to go
to your house?
No, that’s not what I mean.
Dad, I’m back.
It’s just as messy as before.
Grandpa Jack.
Little San, why did you come back alone?
I came back with Xiao Wu.
Hello, Grandpa Jack.
Hello.
Grandpa Jack. Where is my father?
I wanted to pick you up
with your father.
He left this.
Little San.
When you read this letter, I’ve gone.
Don’t look for me.
You’ll never be able to find me.
An eagle can only fly high when it’s independent.
I’m useless. I can’t help you.
You have to choose your path.
I have to get back something that belongs to me.
Don’t be worried about me.
One day, we’ll meet again.
You’re as exquisite as your mother.
I believe, you’ll be the pride of your mother.
If one day, you think soul master
isn’t a good occupation,
then go back to Soul Saint Village.
Be like me, be a blacksmith.
Don’t miss me.
Tang Hao.
My father has left.
Thank you, Grandpa Jack.
[Next Episode]
Hurry. Call me Sister Wu.
Hello, Grandmaster.