♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Zhu Qing’s Millennium Soul Skill is quite strong.
Yeah. Under Rong Rong’s boost,
I think
this is her strongest attack yet.
Rong Rong!
This is her first time supporting
soul masters that are stronger than her.
It’s normal for her to be exhausted.
Retreat to the poison trap!
Little San, have you made your choice yet?
I’ll choose the Burrow Demon Spider.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 65]
Okay. You can go.
But you must remember this.
Brother, if you die,
I’ll follow your steps.
Dean, Teacher Zhao, please help me.
I want the Burrow Demon Spider.
Little San, have you thought it through?
You know what will happen
when you absorb the soul beast.
Dean, I will surely be successful.
Good! You’re determined!
I wish you luck then.
This sly spider!
Fatty!
First soul skill,
Phoenix Firing Line!
You want to escape? No way!
Seventh soul skill,
Eagle Owl’s True Form!
The Burrow Demon Spider is sly.
Don’t let the other soul beasts distract Dean.
Xiao Wu, take this Fragrant Silk Woven Flower.
And take care of yourself.
Okay, Brother. You can go now.
Teacher Zhao, please throw me into the battlefield.
This is troublesome.
Damn! It didn’t leave any marks behind.
Dean, it’s here!
Little Ao, are you okay?
I’m fine.
Teacher Er Long is too brutal.
I mean she’s too strong!
First soul skill,
Farting like thunder!
Blasting Luo San Pao!
First soul skill,
Phoenix Firing Line!
Second soul skill,
Charm!
Constraint of Spider Web!
This soul beast is something.
If I let you escape again,
I won’t be the Four-Eyed Eagle Owl!
Come up! Little San, let’s return.
This is bad. The Human-Faced
Demon Spider is using all its strength!
Xiao Wu!
What?
It’s ineffective!
I managed to kill the Human-Faced
Demon Spider last time,
because I had the Godly Zhuge Crossbow.
Compared with this 6,000-year-old soul beast, Xiao Wu
is way more behind it.
This is bad!
First soul skill,
Intertwine!
I must reach her in time!
[Soul Land]
No!
Xiao Wu!
Brother.
The spike punctured her left breast.
And with the poison
of the Human-Faced Demon Spider,
Xiao Wu will never survive this.
Seventh soul skill, Dragon Form!
Go to hell! Flying Phoenix!
The dragon flame is extremely dangerous!
Don’t go near it!
Tang San!
He’ll be fine. Let’s save Xiao Wu first.
Xiao Wu, how do you feel?
Why did this happen?
Dean, can Xiao Wu be saved?
Dean, is Xiao Wu going to...
Xiao Wu!
Don’t worry. Xiao Wu will be fine.
Dean, don’t lie to us.
She was struck by the spider’s poison.
How can she be fine?
What’s going on?
Xiao Wu actually survived the poison
of the Human-Faced Spider Demon.
I guess I’m lucky.
When the spider struck me with its spike,
it struck the Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
Luckily, I didn’t consume it.
If not, I would’ve been dead.
The Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet
is a tough plant.
Even after suffering that blow,
it remained undamaged.
Where’s Little San? Where is he?
First soul skill, Super Recovery Big Sausage!
Little San is fine.
His Eight Spider Bone is
ending the soul beast’s life.
Tang San, Xiao Wu is fine!
Xiao Wu is fine?
The energy that Little San is absorbing
is transformed by his attached soul bone
for itself.
I didn’t expect my indecisiveness
to save my life.
Good girl. I’m around.
Nobody will bully you again.
What?
Teacher Er Long.
Xiao Wu.
I don’t know why,
but I feel warm when
Teacher Er Long is holding me like this.
Xiao Wu, are you willing to be my disciple?
Teacher, I’m willing to be your disciple.
Teacher Er Long, honestly speaking,
you’re just like a mother to me.
Is that true?
Yes. My mother left me a long time ago.
I’m not married. I may not
have any children in this life.
Xiao Wu, if you don’t mind,
you can address me as your mother.
I... Teacher Er Long,
are you willing to be my mother?
Mother!
Er Long, congratulations.
Brother, I have a daughter now!
Do you know that I have a daughter now?
Fatty! This is so touching!
Yes, I know.
From now on, you won’t be lonely.
You have a daughter now.
Xiao Wu!
You’re loyal to her. This is a rare sight to behold.
You should never let her down.
If not, no matter who’s your master,
no matter how strong you are,
you will suffer the same fate
as the King of the Land last time.
I, Tang San, swear to God,
I will never let Xiao Wu down.
I feel much better.
Little San, the Burrow Demon Spider
is holding on to its last breath.
You should go and absorb its soul ring.
Dean, you’re right.
[Next Episode]
Why isn’t he back yet?
Brother!
Brother?
Why didn’t you say that earlier?
I want to beat you up right now!
I shouldn’t stay by her side,
and make her suffer again.