♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Your target should be me.
You’re smart.
But smart people usually don’t live long.
I’d like to know,
how you overcame the difficulties
of Twin Martial Souls.
Is it worth for you to call over these many
to trouble these youngsters?
How dare you Soul Emperors challenge
the Grand of Soul Land Master?
Ju Hua Guan!
Tang San is my brother.
If you want to kill him,
you have to get through me first.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 93]
It’s said that Shrek has a disciple
from Hao Tian Tribe.
He’s broken through Level 40
at a very young age.
Twin Martial Souls. Owning the fourth
soul ring of Decade Millennium
and even the soul bone.
Such a young talent.
Yet, he’s close to
Qibao Amber Tribe and Tian Dou Empire.
Since he can’t be one of the Martial Soul Hall,
I’ll just kill him.
Bibi Dong, don’t go too far!
He’s just your disciple.
For your disciple,
do you want to fight against Martial Soul Hall?
I’ve had no child in my lifetime.
He’s like my son.
Bibi Dong, listen to me clearly.
If there’s any unpleasant happening to Tang San,
I’ll destroy Martial Soul Hall at all costs.
Just by you?
Yu Xiao Gang, you will also get anxious.
I’ll never forget those past stories forever.
I want to torture you.
I want to make you suffered.
I want you to go through
the sufferings that I experienced.
My endings?
I advise you to think about
your own funeral first.
I don’t believe that you don’t know
the person behind Tang San.
Since you attacked him,
you have to be ready for
the revenge from the person.
Recalling back then, even...
Shut up, Old Venom Freak!
Both you and I have reached
the level of Grand Soul Land Master.
We did understand the difficulties
that we suffered to get here.
Although there’s resentment between us,
I don’t wish to see you sacrifice over this matter.
If you know what’s good for you,
leave here quickly.
Ju Hua Guan, Tang San is my brother.
If you want to hurt him,
you have to get through me first.
Even if your soul power
is slightly higher than mine,
yet it’s not such a big deal
to sacrifice you with me.
By Old Venom Freak’s capabilities,
I’m worried that our thousands of
soul masters will be defeated by his poisons.
By then, I’ll have to deal with him alone.
Moreover, two of Golden Iron Triangle
help to attack.
What a great Old Venom Freak.
I can’t. My soul power is depleted greatly.
Once the martial soul form is disappeared,
I’ll become worthless in this mission.
I’d attack them in advance.
What an idiot to act rashly!
It’s only the ghost shadow
and no soul ring is seen. He is...
Old Ghost.
Old Ghost, you’re here as well!
You’ve spent too much time.
Get them quickly!
I block the Old Venom Freak.
You complete the mission.
Then, we could head back
to have a feast.
Another Grand Soul Land Master!
The total of Grand Soul Land Master
in the entire continent
is just a dozen people.
And, three of them are here now.
For the last battle,
Ju Hua Guan’s martial soul already
can’t resist my Serpent Venom.
It’ll be better to attack him first.
Seventh soul skill, martial soul form.
Old Ghost, if you dare to touch Tang San,
just wait for the revenge of death!
Is this your revenge on me?
If you’re dissatisfied with me,
why do you aim at Tang San?
Just come to me directly.
You thought that
I dare not to touch you?
[Soul Land]
Purple Demon Eye.
Jiubao Boosts!
First, Strength! Second, Speed!
Third, Soul! Fourth, Defense!
Fourth soul skill, White Tiger Meteor Strike.
Fourth soul skill, Phoenix Strike.
Such an awesome eye function!
Unfortunately, the gap of soul power between us
is really far apart!
Purplish golden light.
Oh, no. He interrupted
the lock of Purple Demon Eye.
Third soul skill, Breath Enchantment.
The air is frozen. Unbreathable anymore.
Rong Rong.
Brat, goodbye.
Sixth soul skill, Clouds of Golden Pistil.
Brother!
Little San!
Xiao Wu.
Fifth soul skill, All-Around Massive Quake.
Sword Sect Chen Xin.
Another the Grand Soul Land Master!
Nine soul rings. The Grand Soul Land Master.
The direction is Shrek School.
Chen Xin, are you sure
to involve yourself in this matter?
Tang San is our Qibao Amber Tribe’s friend.
Hit!
This is indeed Sword Sect
Chen Xin’s power of attack.
Fifth soul skill, Frosty Gather.
Sixth soul skill,
Myriad Sword Returning Tribe.
The Grand Sword Master can even fully suppress
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
in his attack.
Let the rain to be heavier.
Frosty Gather is just a sword
formed by the plants.
It’s incomparable to the real sword.
Ju Hua Guan has already
used up his soul power.
In addition, his level is below of Chen Xin.
If I don’t show up now, he’ll definitely lose today.
Ju Hua Guan, fusion!
Bipolar Static Field.
[Next Episode]
I wish
that you can return to
Qibao Amber Tribe with Uncle Sword,
to avoid from the danger.
It’s been 20 years.
Bibi Dong, you’re still very beautiful.
Now, we’re in danger.
Everyone must be extra careful.
Xiao Wu, what has happened?
Xiao Wu.
They’d attack you so quickly.
They even dare to attack
at Martial Soul City.
Martial Soul Hall,
I’ll definitely settle it with you.