♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[Previous Episode] Shrek School versus
Elephant Armored School,
officially begins!
Retreat.
These kids are taught by
the Wisdom Vertex, Master.
Master!
Forget about Shen Feng School. Set up the fort!
Boss Dai, defense quickly!
Great! It’s now!
The fourth soul skill, Blue Silver Cage.
Pay attention, everyone!
Defeat Huyan Li within 20 seconds.
Let’s attack together!
A helmet?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 73]
Oscar, Pink Sausage.
Li!
While everyone was focusing on
White Tiger of Netherworld,
the Pink Sausage was released.
Little San chose the right timing to do so.
What a great move!
Tribe chief, you’re absolutely right!
In team battles, a soul master
of Controlling Branch...
did bring a powerful impact.
Strengths can be weaknesses as well.
Fortunately, Huyan Li is safe...
even though his arms were fractured.
He’s just fainted over due to the pain.
Then it’s good.
Don’t you worry, Chief Huyan.
Elephant Armored School
still left four members.
The game might have its turn around.
Let’s continue watching.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Brother!
They broke the cage.
Start the countdown!
Five, four, three, two,
Now, I announce the result of
Preliminary second round, first match.
Shrek School versus Elephant Armored School.
Shrek School won.
Little San has a well-planned tactic.
He clearly knew that...
Huyan Li is the captain of
Elephant Armored Team...
as well as the core of the team.
This is the opponent’s most powerful strength,
and also the utmost important part.
Once Huyan Li is entangled,
the opponent’s perfect defensive formation...
would be ruined immediately.
We’ll meet very soon.
Sure, you’re welcomed at any time.
Xiao Wu, please give me a hand.
Jiubao Boosts! Third, Soul!
Shrek School! The winner!
Rong Rong said,
to grasp Heart Separation Control,
one should have a strong observing
ability of the overall condition.
At the meantime of flying knives
hit the fallen leaves,
release Blue Silver Plant
to entangle these three stakes.
The introductory practice...
is to hit precisely
on different targets simultaneously.
It requires multi-tasking
as well as aiming precisely.
This is really hard.
It requires a very high mental strength...
and also excellent response.
What? Can’t grasp the feeling yet?
Master.
In order to grasp Heart Separation Control,
you need perception rather than controlling it.
Perception?
Right. Relax yourself.
Think of what did Rong Rong
and I told you yesterday.
Provide corresponding assistance precisely...
to the targets that
require different auxiliary effects.
This can further maximize
the auxiliary ability of...
Qibao Amber Pagoda.
Little San, feel the changes
in surroundings with your heart.
The martial soul can
strengthen your attributes,
including your perception.
Three Aperture Governing Heart.
Ventilated Nine Deficiency.
It’s no good.
Martial soul at each level will initiate,
while using Heart Separation Control.
It means that I’ve to distract
my mental power to control soul beasts.
It also means to initiate
and control simultaneously.
It will require a more powerful
mental power to control than the usual.
If not, I’ll be attacked by
the soul power itself.
Little San...
[Soul Land]
Perception is in prior to controlling.
Each Blue Silver Plant seems to be
the extension of my mental power.
By the feedback of Blue Silver Plant,
I can control the overall condition accurately.
So that I can adjust my
soul power and mental power precisely.
The ultimate practice of
Heart Separation Control...
is to grasp every change
of the surroundings.
Other than observing it,
I will have to bring it under my control as well.
Little San seems to be fully
integrated into the surroundings.
Is this so called the top
mimicry environment of cultivation?
But this can only be done by...
those at Level 70 and above, isn’t it?
Little San is only at Level 41.
Have his spirit power developed
to such a high level?
Brother San, finally you wake up.
You scared us.
Little San, what did happen just now?
Tell me in detail.
I think I have quite a big breakthrough.
According to you,
these Blue Silver Plants are familiar to you,
without showing any rejection.
I’ve met a few soul masters of Plant Branch.
But no one can attract the same plants as you do.
You seem able to control them...
by your own martial soul.
I’m sure that it’s beneficial and harmless to me.
But I couldn’t say why either.
Since there’s no harm,
why do you insist on finding the reason?
Brother San, you’re a freak
in the eyes of others.
A bit more freakishness doesn’t matter.
Anyway,
how’s your progress of
Heart Separation Control?
Do you need me to guide you in further?
You’ve achieved...
such a great outcome by just one day!
I admit that I was slacking off before.
Brother San, do you know?
Sometimes, I really feel like
dissecting your brain...
and take a look at the inside.
By your side,
none of us deserves to be a freak.
Fine, Rong Rong. You have to keep it up as well.
I wish that you’ll be succeeded to cultivate...
Four-Aperture Fortitude before the final match.
So, the real power of
Jiubao Amber Pagoda can be exerted.
Little San also.
Keep up with your practice too.
Yes.
The first six rounds of Preliminary are over.
Other than Elephant Armored School,
why there are no more decent opponents?
All my sausages are useless now.
Since you’re keen to battle,
I’ll find an opportunity for you in the future.
But it’s not today.
Why?
Your opponents of today,
Othello School has abstained.
It seems that your fame has been well spread.
Shrek School...
All of you are well-known now.
Yet, being your Dean,
this will never be enough for me.
You know it well, right?
Don’t get defeated by the others.
Dean is right.
We shouldn’t take it lightly!
Coincidentally,
Lei Ting School will be the team
in the central arena of today’s battle.
This team is a powerful opponent that
all of you have to be extra careful.
Let’s go and watch the battle.
Shrek School!
I love all of you very much!
Xiao Wu! Tang San!
Cang Hui School.
[Next Episode]
Martial Soul Hall
is much more magnificent
than anyone can imagine.
What’s the thing that keeps shining?
There must be something happened to Brother!
I have no advice. I just need you to disappear.
Xiao Wu!
No! Don’t!
No!