♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Stop!
You’re going back to Shrek School with me.
You won’t need many herbs.
This old freak is willing to come to our school?
This is unbelievable!
With a Grand Soul Land Master here,
it’s a good thing for our school too.
Master, I want to see them.
You just came back,
don’t you want to rest?
I’m not tired.
I brought some gifts for them.
What did you say?
Your soul power has reached Level 37?
I swear. I’ll never leave you
unless I die.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 53]
Little San, you’re finally back.
If you take longer, Xiao Wu will be worried.
I’ve been away for a long time,
I’ve made you worry.
Brother San, where are the gifts?
Hurry and show us.
I’ve brought Boss Dai this
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum.
Eight Petal Fairy Orchid is for Little Ao.
Cockscomb Phoenix Flower is for Fatty.
Rong Rong, yours is Silk Woven Tulip.
You’re giving them the herbs
that you got from Dugu Bo.
For your ability,
you don’t need a shortcut like this.
Don’t worry, Master.
I’ve picked these premium herbs
according to their characteristics.
Mainly to solidify their body
and remove impurities.
It won’t do them any harm.
Okay, I believe that
you know what you’re doing.
Little San,
although Dugu Bo is in favor of you
he’s willing to be our school’s adviser,
we still have to stay vigilant as he’s weird.
Brother, Grandmaster,
are you saying that Dugu Bo has come to our school?
Master, Xiao Wu, and all, don’t worry.
Dugu is a nice senior.
Besides, he has promised me
that he won’t hurt anyone from Shrek School.
You can rest assured.
Zhu Qing, this ultimate premium herb for you.
It can raise the dead, grow flesh from
bones and seize the world’s fortune.
However, to consume this premium herb,
you need to pay a price.
I hope that you’ll be prepared for this.
I understand, thank you, Brother San.
This herb is named as
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
There’s a lovely yet sorrowful story about it.
Once upon a time, there was a young man.
He was placid and he loved to
care for the flowers and trees.
His garden was full of green lotus,
which was a beautiful sight.
He sang to the flowers
and drank with the moon.
If he saw a flower withered,
he would mourn for it.
He would collect the petals,
bury and mourn for them.
It is said that
emotions touch Heaven and earth.
His love for flowers
touched the Flower Fairy.
She descended to earth and married him.
But their good time don’t last long.
God knew about this and was furious.
As fairy and human can’t be together,
he ordered Flower Fairy back to Heaven.
Since the young man lost his wife,
he was in deep sorrow and
didn’t take care of the flowers.
Thus the walls and fences
fell apart and the flowers withered.
It was a miserable sight in the garden.
One day, an old man came.
He told the man that his favorite
white peony in the garden
was the incarnation of his wife.
If he ruined the flower,
Flower Fairy would lose her fairy form
and descended to earth again to be his wife.
But he must not give up caring for his garden.
After saying those,
the old man disappeared into thin air.
The young man woke up.
He regretted his actions,
so he cared for the flowers again.
Yet, although he loved his wife,
he can’t afford to ruin the peony.
So he cared for it more than usual,
and cried to the flower day and night.
Lovesick and heartbroken took away his life.
When he died, he bled on the petals.
The blood stained on the petals
is the young man’s heart blood.
Lovesick and heartbroken,
two parallels never meet.
This flower is extraordinary,
and it chooses its owner.
When you pluck it,
you must think of your loved one.
Drop a drop of blood on the petal.
If you change your mind,
even if you bleed to death,
you can never pluck the flower away.
The stone under the flower
is the Dark Absolute. If you ruin it,
this Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet
will lose its healing ability as well.
After plucking the flower,
as long as it stays with its owner,
it will never wither.
But I...
Zhu Qing, although I know little
about your affairs with Boss Dai,
among the seven of us,
you are the only couple.
That’s why I bring this to you.
I hope that you can be the fateful one.
Let’s go together. Didn’t you say...
I’m sorry, Brother San.
I’m not single-minded.
I have no fate with this flower.
Zhu Qing, there’s no need to say sorry.
Master, you’re in love with Auntie Er Long,
maybe you can try this.
What can it bring to me even if I eat it?
If there’s a fate, I’ll keep it with me forever.
[Soul Land]
Er Long, my wife,
is my second uncle’s illegitimate daughter,
which means she is my cousin.
Seems like I still can’t let it go.
Xiao Wu hasn’t moved her gaze away from Brother San.
That gaze is focused, true and pure.
Xiao Wu!
I can’t believe that I’m the fated one.
Brother, I’ve finally understood.
Brother, that legend must be true, right?
I don’t know either.
Xiao Wu, eat it then.
It will help you.
No, Grandmaster is right.
This premium herb,
how can I bear to eat it?
Didn’t you say that
after it chooses its owner,
it will never wither?
I want it to accompany me,
I’ll care for it with my love.
But...
Brother, don’t worry, I’ll work hard.
I’ll keep improving.
Then you shall protect it.
It will protect you as well.
Should I leave him?
If I don’t,
I’m afraid that the Grand Soul Land Master
with him will harm me.
No, I can’t leave.
I’ve sworn that I won’t leave him.
Only with him,
I can feel the happiness
that Mom has mentioned.
Great, this is awesome.
Five levels, my soul power
has increased by five levels!
Why are you so excited?
It’s just five levels.
I’ve increased by six levels.
This premium herb is so wonderful.
Why should we work hard then?
We should just eat this every day.
Stop daydreaming.
Little San has said previously,
everything has their limits.
Herbs are harmful if we overeat it.
I’m just saying.
Rong Rong, look.
One, two, three, four.
Your Qibao Amber Pagoda has nine levels now!
It has turned into Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
Is it that Silk Woven Tulip
is the secret key to
breaking the limits of my tribe?
You’ve all done absorbing?
Brother San.
Brother San, thank you so much.
I have no idea how I can repay you.
Brother San, my Qibao Amber Pagoda
has turned into Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
That means I’m no longer restricted by
my tribe’s inherited constraints.
You’re welcome, we’re teammates.
Did he notice anything?
Brother San, what is this skill?
Why did I lose my sight just now?
Rong Rong, are you okay?
I’m sorry, I didn’t control my vision power just now.
This is my Purple Demon Eye.
All thanks to the Eager Gaze Dew,
I’ve grown to the Surreal level.
In Tang Clan, Surreal level
Purple Demon Eye only exists in legends.
Out of my surprise,
it can see through all disguise.
Xiao Wu...
Brother, congratulations.
If you eat this Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet,
you’ll improve better than us.
No, I can’t bear to.
I want to keep it with me forever.
[Next Episode]
I’ll entrust Xiao Wu to you.
You’re leaving?
About my ability, we’ll see on the ring.
If there’s another round, I’ll hit him hard.
I’m afraid that you don’t have the chance.
You’re new here, don’t you know
about our advance class’s rules?
Rules? People like them,
how can they be a Grand Soul Land Master?
The enemy who wants to take
your lives away will not show any mercy.
Be careful, everyone.