♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this
when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Is he really Tang Hao’s son?
I’m sure of it.
Soul Land will experience a massive change soon.
For that, the Seven Major Tribes must be united.
Master, you knew about my background?
You must prove to your father that
you’re capable enough to help him
with your achievements.
I won’t disappoint you.
Rong Rong, can you give me your answer?
Little San, if you look at this from another perspective,
perhaps your father didn’t leave you at all.
Why didn’t you two allow me
to use Hao Tian Hammer?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 61]
Is it to hide the fact
that I’m from the Hao Tian Tribe?
This is a simple question.
Because we want you to get stronger.
The biggest advantage of having
Twin Martial Soul is
you can master one Martial Soul at a time.
Although your Hao Tian Hammer
doesn’t have any soul rings,
your soul power is already at Level 37.
Think about this.
When your Blue Silver Plant is as strong
as a Grand Soul Land Master’s,
you acquire soul rings
for Hao Tian Hammer after that,
how powerful would that be?
There’s no mistake. Your father and I
are trying to create a supreme being with
Decade Millennium Soul Rings.
Now, I’m only worried that
your Twin Martial Soul
will clash when you’re
trying to master the hammer.
In our history,
you’re the third person with Twin Martial Soul.
We’re not the only smart ones.
The first soul master with
Twin Martial Soul led a poor life.
When he was acquiring the third soul rings
for his second Martial Soul,
the two Martial Souls clashed and he died.
The second person with
Twin Martial Soul was successful.
Master, did you ask me to train my body
because I have Twin Martial Soul?
Yes. When you acquire more soul rings,
you’ll get stronger in every aspect.
But when your body can’t stand the enhancements,
it’ll become a disaster.
In the future, if this method won’t work,
we’ll need to try a special method
to separate all the elements.
How do you do that?
By using attached soul bones.
When you reach a certain level,
it’s best if you have more soul bones.
When your body can’t stand it,
the extra elements will be absorbed
by your soul bones.
But if it is known by others,
many people will try to hunt you down
for your soul bones.
Even after knowing all these facts,
I hope you can keep a normal attitude.
Can you understand why I’m doing this?
Master, I understand.
You know that I like freedom.
Actually, I would rather be a blacksmith’s son.
My identity to me is meaningless.
I’m relieved.
You have six months left.
The Advanced Soul Master School Contest
is coming soon.
This is the best time for you to train.
I’ve already discussed this with Frander.
When the contest ends,
you guys can graduate from school.
Graduate? Master, isn’t this too fast?
No, not at all.
For a normal advanced soul master school,
you can graduate when you reach Level 30
as a top student.
Little San, come.
For you guys,
the training in the school is only a minor part
of your lives.
Facing the real world is more important.
That’s the true test.
Master, I understand now.
Okay, you can return now.
There are six months to go.
I won’t give them any special training anymore.
You guys can train on your own.
But I’ll guide you guys
through the battle strategies.
I hope you guys can break your limits
within six months
for the contest.
Okay.
But, Xiao Wu didn’t consume the
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
I’m sure her progress will be delayed.
I’m worried...
Worried about what?
Why do you stop talking?
Are you worried that I will delay the progress?
Never mind. We’ll see when the time comes.
If Xiao Wu cannot catch up with us,
for her safety,
she will not join every round of the contest.
Xiao Wu, it’s late now. You should return.
Brother, we will hunt soul beasts tomorrow.
What beast do you want to hunt down?
I am not sure.
It all depends on our luck.
I hope everyone is lucky.
Brother, you guys reached
Level 40 within these six months.
I’m the only one below Level 40.
Are you disappointed in me?
I’m not, Xiao Wu.
We must go through the training
step-by-step. We mustn’t rush.
Now, our group is quite strong.
You don’t need to overthink.
I’m sure...
if you consume this
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet,
your soul power would
be the strongest among all of us.
Brother, don’t you believe in my strength?
I...
What? Are you worried that
I’m not strong enough?
And I’ll drag you down during the contest?
Let’s fight then.
I didn’t mean that.
You didn’t mean that?
Let’s have a fair fight then.
I will prove to you that I’m strong enough.
Fine. I won’t have mercy.
Brother, be careful!
Xiao Wu has improved a lot!
She unleashed her Arched Body multiple
times even though she’s trapped!
Brother, now you know that I’m strong, right?
Yeah. It’s unnecessary to worry.
Brother, can you comb my hair for me?
My hair is messy.
Comb your hair? But you need to sleep anyway.
Won’t your hair be messy when you sleep?
You’re so dumb!
I’ll just train until tomorrow morning.
[Soul Land]
This comb is made of quality wood.
My mother gave it to me.
She made the comb personally.
She made this with the best rosewood out there.
Although it’s not fancy,
it’s the last thing my mother left for me.
Brother, please comb my hair.
Xiao Wu, you’re really beautiful.
Mom! This comb is pretty!
Why is the wood purple in color?
Silly girl. This is made of rosewood.
Since you’ve made your choice,
I will give this comb to you.
In the future, if you do find someone you love,
ask him to comb your hair with this comb.
A woman’s hair,
it can only be combed by
the most important man in her life.
I pray for you. I hope
you can find that man one day.
I found him.
We’ve checked our equipment.
Xiao Wu, your braid is not straight.
This...
Little San, don’t tell me you...
It’s not what you think!
Yeah, it’s not what I think.
You don’t need to explain.
We understand.
Stop your nonsense.
What are you guys doing?
We’ll depart to Sunset Forest now.
Although the four of us are with you this time,
I need to say this first.
For your hunt today,
you will complete them yourself.
We won’t help you.
Tonight, the Seven Devils will keep watch.
You guys can arrange the shift.
Little San, although we didn’t meet any
large soul beasts this afternoon,
it doesn’t mean that we won’t meet them at night,
You must be cautious.
Master, I understand.
Xiao Gang?
Move aside!
I’ll sleep at the far right.
I’ll...
I’ll sleep here. Mu Bai and I
have discussed it.
He’ll take the first shift, and I’ll take the second.
Mu Bai will sleep here when we change our shift.
I’ll sleep here then.
Xiao Wu, I think you’re nervous.
Should we exchange our place?
You’re annoying. No.
I knew you wouldn’t change.
I’m a girl! And I don’t care at all!
Why are you so scared?
This is our border.
I’ll have no mercy if you exceed the line.
Grandmaster, you should rest.
I’ll patrol the area.
Okay, go. I’ll sleep later.
Aren’t you tired? I think you should rest.
We need to continue our hunt tomorrow.
Yeah, I’m tired. I should sleep.
The smell of Xiao Wu’s hair...
So that’s the case.
It smells just like
the Fragrant Silk Woven Flower.
In the Xuan Tian Records,
if this smell appears on someone,
it is called as Silk Fragrance.
It’s good for the body
and it can even extend our longevity.
I didn’t expect Xiao Wu to have this smell.
Emergency! Everyone, be careful!
[Next Episode] This soul beast
is 4,000 years old at least.
I’ll kill you!
Frander, I can’t believe this.
I didn’t believe you when you said
your sister has a bad temper.
But, I think you’re right.
I made these Cure Pills myself.
You will be safe from the miasma
if you consume them.
Everyone, be careful!
The mist is poisonous!
This is not miasma!