♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] Facing with
Seven In One Fusion Skill,
we must be seriously injured.
I couldn’t see things clearly at that time.
I had to release soul skills at random.
When I could see clearly,
they had already fallen to the ground.
Shrek School caused severe injuries
to students of Cang Hui School during the battle,
who is unconscious now.
I announce that
Shrek School is removed from this contest!
We’ll exempt this interrogation.
We’ll leave first.
That’s right. Shrek never fears any enemy.
Shrek, must win!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 79]
Both teams, get ready.
The battle starts now.
Attack!
In prior to knowing the opponents’ abilities,
let’s test by using the first soul skill first.
First soul skill, Intertwine.
First soul skill, Ice Bound.
Her soul skill is amazing that
it can aim four people at the same time.
I’m restricted by the opponent now.
It’ll be hard for me
to control everyone precisely.
Little San failed to restrict Shui Bing Er.
Instead, Shui Bing Er managed to restrict Little San.
I’d withdraw Blue Silver Plant first,
and observe how it goes.
Little San is forced to give up
Human Meteor Hammer for the first time.
Tian Shui School is indeed a strong opponent.
Brother, Shui Bing Er’s skill
seems to have restricted Little San.
Look at his embarrassing look.
Your Repelling Fire Ring can restrict
Shui Bing Er to a certain degree only.
Tian Shui School of this batch
is indeed strong,
especially Shui Bing Er and Xue Wu.
I’d find a way to defeat the opponent’s
soul master of Controlling Branch.
At least, buy some time for Little San.
Second soul skill,
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Second soul skill, Ice Ring Armour.
Team defense.
The Ice Ring Armour
can be enforced to her teammates.
What a powerful attack!
Ice Ring Armour can’t resist it anymore.
Little San, it’s now!
Want to hide? It’s not easy.
Ice Bound.
It’s the first soul skill again.
She’s having priority
as her soul power is stronger.
How to break this passive circumstance?
Jing Ling is a soul master of
Keen Attack Branch. He’s quick response.
Xiao Wu owns third soul skill of Teleport,
yet she can’t hide from it either.
Is this Soul Skill Lockdown?
Third soul skill, The Pressure Kill.
Tai Long, hurry up! Amplify your power.
First soul skill, Firm Rock Defense.
He broke the Ice Bound.
First soul skill, Fish Transformation.
Second soul skill, Burst Enormous Power.
Second soul skill, Jade Wave.
What a strong power!
Obviously, their attacks are weakened greatly.
But they still caused me severe injuries.
Her defense is as hard as an ice cube.
It can even resist my second soul skill.
As long as Tang San is being controlled,
Shrek’s tactics will be restricted as well.
And I can attack them one by one.
The victory will be ours soon.
What?
As there’s a concentrated focus,
there’ll be a neglected blind spot too.
You’ve just focused on me.
but you didn’t notice that my teammates
have already broken the Ice Bound.
It’s still early to be happy. Xue Wu.
[Soul Land]
As there’s a concentrated focus,
there’ll be a neglected blind spot too.
While you launched the tactics,
Xue Wu’s soul skill has been ready as well.
Tang San, how about the taste of your own medicine?
Is that satisfying for you?
Ice Snow that weakens the battle power.
The tool soul master
can even control the weather.
This snow is a soul skill
of General Support Branch.
However, it’s not supporting her teammates,
but it keeps exhausting
the opponents’ soul power
even the auditorium is encaged as well.
We have no chance to win
if we keep going on like this.
Fourth soul skill, Blue Silver Cage.
He is using massive soul power
to initiate the fourth soul skill.
Little San has to do in this way.
Now, they are fully suppressed.
Especially Jiang Zhu, she can’t resist it for long.
Even Blue Silver Cage can’t hinder her soul skill?
First soul skill, Ice Bound.
It’s Ice Bound again.
Shui Bing Er can initiate
her first soul skill instantly.
And once targeted by her soul skill,
we can’t escape.
It seems that I can
use an impulsive force of pulling back
the Blue Silver Cage
to break the Ice Bound.
This is the only feasible way for now.
Since it’s difficult to deal with
Xue Wu and Shui Bing Er...
Mu Bai. Meteor Strike
binds with Blue Silver Cage
and attacks from both sides.
All right.
Fourth soul skill,
White Tiger Meteor Strike.
Great! The situation is reversed.
How wise Tang San is.
He even attacks his own cage
as to weaken our team by the impulsive force.
Four people of Tian Shui were attacked.
Is Tian Shui defeated?
Little San, hurry up!
First soul skill, Intertwine.
It’s late. Third soul skill,
Repelling Light.
It’s similar to Huo Wu’s Repelling Fire Ring.
It breaks all of our skills instantly.
Moving forward?
No, she’s moving backwards.
What’s she doing?
If you think of taking advantage of these girls,
you will be wrong.
Last time, I could barely blow them away by wind.
Boss,
I thought you were full of dirty thoughts.
You know nothing.
If I didn’t blow them away,
they would have...
fused!
It’s bad. It’s Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
Gather!
They’ve been ready for this
Martial Soul Fusion Skill
since Little San is fully restricted by Shui Bing Er.
Healing sceptre. Hurry up!
It’s radius attack!
Its attack scope is really exaggerated.
And its destructive power is really strong.
He even uses the Blue Silver Cage
that restricts the opponents
as self-defense.
Tang San’s tactics towards
the battle are really beyond expectation.
Martial Soul Fusion Skill that performs
by both Level 40 soul masters
is comparable with a Level 60 soul master.
Blue Silver Plant is tough,
but it’s just a vine
evolved from the grass. It can’t resist it.
Why can’t I see anything all of sudden?
What’s going on?
Who will win at the end?
Martial Soul Fusion Skill has been
hidden by Tian Shui School
in the preliminary.
They finally use it today.
Finally, someone can teach Little San a lesson.
But I still wish to defeat him by myself.
Don’t be anxious. To win or to lose is uncertain yet.
Although it’s a radius attack,
the power mainly focused on Tang San.
Let’s see if he can resist it.
There’s something amiss.
Why there are different degrees of defense
even with the same cage?
He can even...
What a terrifying response of him!
What happened?
Qibao Amber Tribe,
Three-Aperture Governing Heart.
Little San, provide corresponding
assistance precisely
to the targets that require
different auxiliary effects.
This can further maximize the
auxiliary ability of Qibao Amber Pagoda.
Little San can release so many Blue Silver Cages at once.
It doesn’t mean he has greatly
improved his soul power,
but his ability to use the soul power precisely,
while releasing each of his soul skills.
In other words, although those
Blue Silver Cages look similar,
it’s sturdier if using more soul power,
and weaker if using less soul power.
This saves much soul power.
Yes.
That’s why Little San can protect everyone
while encountering Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
If this carries on,
our soul powers will be depleted.
We couldn’t break Tang San’s defense formation.
It’s the Decade Millennium Soul Skill.
Though it’s only defense, it’s too powerful.
We did even use Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
If we can’t win in this tournament,
the reputation of
Tian Shui School will be ruined.
What’s happening?
This frozen ability is too powerful!
Go to initiate the defensive cover quickly.
It’s the Mighty Beast Soul, Ice Phoenix.
Frozen Ice with Flying Phoenix.
She owns the top martial soul, Ice Phoenix.
The Ice Phoenix is
supported by both fusion partners.
We have no extreme strength.
How can we compete against them?
Extreme strength?
There’s only one method now.
Our soul powers are exhausted greatly. Little San.
All of you get down first. I have my trump.
Brother, be careful.
Ice Phoenix is a Mighty Beast Soul that
is comparable with Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
I’m worried...
Ice Phoenix is indeed a Mighty Beast Soul.
Little San, can you resist it?
Get away quickly. The Phoenix is too powerful.
I can’t control it anymore.
You’re such a kind girl.
But I can’t be defeated.
[Next Episode]
Can you tell me the reason?
Without Eight Spider Bone,
Without Fiery Soft Apricot and Octa Dark Frost,
Without Decade Millennium Soul Ring,
What else do I have?
Failure is the mother of success.
We’ve not lost,
but a step closer to the triumph.
Master,
Empire and Martial Soul Hall have
already reached an irreconcilable state.
It will certainly
become unpeaceful soon.
It’s been ten years already.
Do you finally admit your fate?