♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Fourth soul skill, God Locking Ring.
You have to pay for what you’ve done.
Dragon in Heaven. Jade Lightning.
Tang San.
Let us decide who the champion
of the qualifying rounds is.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 89]
So fast.
Xuan Yu Hand.
Feng Xiao Tian is from Storm Attack Branch.
Why is he as fast as Keen Attack Branch?
Actually, he can be considered as
Keen Attack Branch too.
Gale Double-headed Wolf. I see.
Second soul skill,
Double Wolves Shield Body.
Such Mutated Martial Soul
like Gale Double-headed Wolf
has a keen attack characteristic
on top of the storm attack foundation.
I believe Little San has realized that too.
Brother San will surely find a way
to defeat him.
Up to now, without using
his third and fourth soul skills,
he has led his team to continuous
victories. Don’t look down on him.
It’s indeed a battle between
two teams of complete victory.
Tang San pretended to be weak
to lure Feng Xiao Tian to his trap.
He’s so thoughtful at such a young age.
It’s indeed rare and commendable.
First soul skill, Aero Sword Formation.
Turns out Feng Xiao Tian is risking himself,
in order to release Aero Sword Formation.
Just for the first soul skill?
Feng Xiao Tian’s first soul skill has
a boundary limit. It isn’t precise.
Despite so,
Feng Xiao Tian chose to continue releasing it.
It must be very powerful.
Especially with the help
of Double Wolves Shield Body,
the power of Aero Sword Formation
has greatly improved.
It won’t be easy for Little San to react.
Second soul skill, Parasite.
First soul skill, Aero Sword Formation.
First soul skill, Intertwine.
Although Little San was tricked by
Feng Xiao Tian just now,
a direct attack is just to feign.
Planting Blue Silver Plant
is his real aim.
Right. Then enclose him with Blue Silver Plant
to have a series of attack.
Little San is doing really well in this battle.
Wow, he won. Little San is so powerful.
This battle is far from done.
How is that possible?
Up until now,
Feng Xiao Tian has only used
his first and second soul skills.
That means he hasn’t done his best.
Third soul skill, Gale Wings.
Besides forming wings of wind,
my third soul skill
can also bring my body condition to the top.
So, you’ve been planning this since the beginning?
Tang San, you’re stronger than I imagined.
Despite so, I’ll defeat you.
The strength of Feng Xiao Tian
is much more powerful than mine.
This time, Little San...
The tougher it is,
the better it can help him grow.
This battle has brought us too much.
Your Majesty,
the battle is only just about to start.
Oh?
I’ll defeat you with my self-created soul skill.
You’ll have a moral victory.
Gale Devil Wolf with 36 continuous chops.
Self-created soul skill
isn’t like given soul skills,
which can form naturally.
It’s formed through continuous
trials and training.
It’s more practical
than common soul skills.
It’s more powerful.
His talent is frightening.
The strength is way stronger than last time.
That’s not good.
What happened, Dean?
Look. Feng Xiao Tian’s 36 chops
work through leveraging.
Speed and strength
are superimposed continuously.
Superimposed continuously?
This is only the fourth time,
yet Little San is already injured.
If there are 36 times...
Brother, you must be careful.
I can’t await death without doing anything.
Fourth soul skill.
It’s Blue Silver Cage again. You’re out of ideas.
Blue Silver Spike Formation.
Is this a self-created soul skill too?
This is the mutated version
of his fourth soul skill.
The activation speed of Blue Silver Cage
is much faster.
This can be considered as
Little San’s last trick. However...
I can’t run away anymore. I have to...
Fourth soul skill, Storm of Devil Wolf.
It has been broken through.
The attack coverage is everywhere.
I can’t escape by Ghostly Trace.
Xuan Yu Hand is at its extreme.
I’ve already...
Could I really be defeated this time?
Brother.
No.
Weapon?
Could this be...
- That is...
- Hao Tian Hammer? How is it possible?
Yes, Your Majesty. He is the son
of Grand Hao Tian Master.
Grand Hao Tian Master?
Could this be Hao Tian Hammer?
You still recognize Hao Tian Hammer.
Do you know what you’ve missed then?
Hao Tian Hammer.
Little San wants to fight directly.
Hao Tian Hammer is the number one
tool soul in the world.
Even without an additional soul ring,
it weighs 500 Jin.
But when facing the self-created
soul skill of Feng Xiao Tian, I’m afraid...
Random Air Hammer Skill.
Little San is...
The only thing they can compete now
is the persistence.
I believe in him.
For Sister Huo Wu,
I have to win.
[Soul Land]
You’re the first person who persists
until the 36th strike.
How can they...
Twin Martial Souls, right?
The hammer is called Hao Tian.
Hao Tian Hammer?
It seems I can’t complain about my defeat.
Actually, you didn’t lose.
It’s just that your self-created
soul skill was limited by me.
Besides, there’s nothing
between Huo Wu and me.
If you like her, that’s your business.
Please don’t involve me.
Awesome.
Random Air Hammer Skill is done so adeptly.
They’re indeed the team
that Chief Ning thinks highly of.
They can make the empire proud.
My daughter
will only be seen fighting
in the final round.
Well, good one, Hao Tian Tribe and Tang Hao.
I’ll show you who’s the master of Soul Land.
Let’s go.
After a few days of competition,
15 teams of Tian Dou Empire
have performed distinctively.
Special congratulations to Shrek School.
They have obtained complete victory
by winning all 14 battles.
- Great. Awesome.
- Not bad.
In this year’s competition,
the Crown Prince, Xue Qing He,
will be the envoy of the empire,
in joining the jury.
Moreover, Royal Cavalry Troop of
500 strong will be assigned as an escort.
I hope all of you can make
the empire proud.
Aren’t you ready? We’re departing soon.
Xiao Gang isn’t found yet?
Xiao Gang said in his letter that
he’s going to look for her.
You have to help me then.
For the sake of Little San, I have to see her.
Xiao Gang has no choice.
You knew about it?
Why did you let him go?
He...
Dean Frander, Deputy Dean Liu Er Long.
Royal Cavalry Troop of Tian Dou is pressing.
He said he must see her for
something urgent. Don’t you trust him?
It’s not that I don’t trust him.
I just don’t understand.
It’s been so many years.
Why would he still need to see her?
Er Long, have faith in yourself and Xiao Gang.
Okay. Let’s go
to Martial Soul City for the final round.
Hooray.
Alright, just stop here.
Class will start soon.
Don’t hold up the curriculum of the kids.
Don’t worry, Dean.
Handle the kids in the school to us.
It won’t be held up.
We, the teachers who can’t join the final round,
wish the Little Devils
good results in this trip.
No problem.
Yes. No problem.
Just count this on Fatty alone.
That’s not what I mean.
I just wanted to ease the atmosphere.
Holy Lady, the Pope means...
Fellow Elders.
Our teacher doesn’t wish
to see this person in Martial Soul City.
Don’t worry, Teacher.
The honour of this competition
belongs to Martial Soul Hall.
[Next Episode]
Little San, what are you thinking about?
Regarding us...
Get into the cart.
Shh. Keep quiet.
Something is happening.
Right now,
the most important thing
is to protect the children.
It is indeed so.
There are so many of them.
They’re obviously prepared.
Qin Ming.