♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face,
hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Brother!
Failure is the mother of success.
Little San, don’t be sad.
It is a pride of our Shrek School.
Due to my carelessness,
I caused the entire team to lose.
Empire and Martial Soul Hall
seems to have conflict.
It’s been ten years already.
Do you finally admit your fate?
Ju Hua Guan, go to hell.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 81]
Even if your Serpent Venom became stronger,
how could you surpass the oppression of
three-level soul power?
I am...
The Grand Soul Land Master at Level 95.
Ju Hua Guan is at Level 95.
I’m only at Level 92.
Once a soul master reaches Level 90,
every level will be vastly different.
Not to mention three levels.
Hidden weapons.
I still have hidden weapons.
However, a hidden weapon is still a hidden weapon.
When I meet a powerful opponent,
I can’t counteract with it.
Is this the ninth soul skill?
Even the most deadly poison,
I just have to pull away.
What?
It’s Medusa Gaze!
Medusa Gaze can never stop my action!
I only need this moment of the loophole.
Medusa Gaze is just a disguise.
Cluster Soul Chasing Life Taking Balls
is the unexpected blow.
How dare you make a sneak attack?
It’s so mean.
You lost.
Just wait and see.
Thanks to Little Freak’s
Cluster Soul Chasing Life Taking Balls.
I wonder how Little Freak is going on.
Do my efforts these years go in vain?
Do I have to give up Blue Silver Plant?
Little Freak!
Old Freak?
What happened?
Little Freak. What happened?
What exactly happened?
Old Freak. If the soul power of
my peers and me
are above Level 70,
would I still get ahead before them like now?
Why do you ask so?
I don’t know what I should do.
As the level increases,
the weakness of Blue Silver Plant
is getting more obvious.
I think you already knew
my second Martial soul, Hao Tian Hammer.
I just need to match the right soul ring.
It’s more powerful than Blue Silver Plant.
Follow me.
Old Freak. Where are you taking me?
You’ll know it later.
Come on. Release your Blue Silver Plant.
What does Old Freak want to do?
This is an ordinary Blue Silver Plant.
Try touching it.
Tell me what’s the difference.
Comparing with a normal Blue Silver Plant,
my Blue Silver Plant is stronger.
Its top part is more aggressive.
Moreover...
What is it?
Moreover, I think they’re warmer.
To an ordinary person,
having a Blue Silver Plant as Martial Soul
is no way for cultivation.
You not only could cultivate,
you also have innate full soul power.
The most unbelievable thing is that
you actually have Twin Martial Souls.
Master said it before.
Martial Soul inheritance is about
choosing the stronger one among parents.
However, Hao Tian Hammer is more powerful
than Blue Silver Plant.
Why do I...
I accidentally saw it in an ancient book.
There are two conditions for
the birth of Twin Martial Souls.
First.
There’s a big difference in nature of
Martial Soul between the parents.
Second.
The nature of Martial Souls of parents
is very similar.
That means
your mother’s Martial Soul, Blue Silver Plant
is quite similar to the nature of
Martial Soul of your father.
Little San.
Mother. Blue Silver Plant.
Do you still think that
your Blue Silver Plant
is just an ordinary one?
I got it. Thank you, Old Freak.
Rest assured. Based on your
current cultivation speed,
you’ll break your father’s record to
be the youngest Grand Soul Land Master.
The Grand Soul Land Master.
I have decided.
I will never give up on cultivating
the Blue Silver Plant.
It’s good that you understand this.
[Soul Land]
I’ve reached Level 39.
Xiao Wu, you’re great!
Congratulations, Xiao Wu.
Everyone’s cultivation has
made progress recently.
I’ve also reached Level 39.
I wonder how about Brother’s cultivation.
Even the best blacksmith in Tian Dou City
couldn’t beat you, Little Freak.
Oh, right. Little Freak.
Do you still have the Cluster Soul
Chasing Life Taking Balls with you?
I gave you two last time.
Have you used them?
I fought with an old man.
This thing is quite useful.
I used to be beaten up by him.
Finally, he was ashamed this time.
Is he the Grand Soul Land Master too?
But the Cluster Soul Chasing
Life Taking Balls is not that toxic.
How did you defeat him?
Jade Phosphor Serpent Venom.
How’s it? Do you get it, Little Freak?
A hidden weapon can only attack secretly.
Combining with poison
can have excellent effects.
Old Freak, as the Grand Venom Master,
when you use a hidden weapon,
you also use the soul skill and soul
power of your Grand Master level,
the effect would be a big difference
compare with only using
a normal hidden weapon.
Can I
combine the Blue Silver Plant
and a hidden weapon?
I know how I should cultivate
the Blue Silver Plant.
Thank you, Old Freak.
Finally, I know what I should do.
It’s getting late.
Let’s go. Let’s have a walk around.
That’s it for today’s practise.
Everyone has improved a lot.
Go back and rest well today.
The practise for tomorrow will be very tough.
I wonder what we will face tomorrow.
As long as we don’t have to battle with Teacher Zhao.
Little San is not around.
It’s tough for us this time.
I mean
Little San’s cultivation will make a breakthrough.
Xiao Wu, since you’re so worried about Brother San,
why don’t you go and see him?
This is the Martial Soul Branch Hall of
Tian Dou City.
How do you think about it?
A branch hall built in the capital of
Tian Dou Empire.
It’s just a branch hall,
yet the momentum is superior to
the power of the Tian Dou Empire.
So its strength is unfathomable.
The strength of Martial Soul Hall
can even control lives in the
Advanced Soul Master School Elite Tournament.
Old Freak. Why did you say that?
I heard that you also joined the
Advanced Soul Master School Elite Tournament?
How are the results?
We’ve passed the preliminary.
We’re going to fight in the qualifying rounds.
Having you, Little Freak,
it shouldn’t be a problem
for Shrek to get the third place.
The third place?
You’ve no confidence in me.
Shouldn’t you wish us
to get the first place?
It’s not that I have no confidence in you.
Instead, you have no chance at all.
Because there’s always
the only champion of this tournament.
Who?
Martial Soul Hall.
Why?
The strength of Martial Soul Hall
is all over the land.
They predominate most of the masters.
The person who battled with me
was one of them.
It’s said that they have
some amazing juniors in recent years.
Even the Pope called them as
the Golden Generation of Martial Soul Hall.
That means
Martial Soul Hall is bound to win
the champion of this tournament.
Do you know the prize for the champion of
Advanced Soul Master School Elite Tournament?
Why don’t you guess
the most important thing for a soul master?
Could it be a soul bone?
It’s three soul bones.
Three soul bones?
Tang San.
He reached Level 40 earlier than the
Golden Generation of Martial Soul Hall.
Blue Silver Plant? Useless Martial Soul.
It’s interesting.
Tang San’s soul power improvement is too fast.
I heard that
Dugu Bo is a guest teacher of
a soul master’s school in Tian Dou City.
[Next Episode]
Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
What happened?
Boss Dai. Fatty.
Is this the result of
Little San’s cultivation these days?
How can I be eliminated as they wanted?
Who is it?
Fine! How dare you scheme me?
I am not Liu Er Long
if I don’t beat till you cry!
You wouldn’t have the chance to win.
But I have the strength to fight with them.
Guys, are you ready?