♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face,
hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
It’s Medusa Gaze!
I only need this moment of the loophole.
You lost.
Just wait and see.
A hidden weapon can only attack secretly.
Combining with poison
can have excellent effects.
Can I
combine the Blue Silver Plant
and a hidden weapon?
Tang San’s soul power improvement is too fast.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 82]
These three soul bones are the relics
of the late elders of Martial Soul Hall.
The Pope uses them
as the prize for the champion.
They must be very confident in the participants.
Do you still feel lucky now?
Old Freak.
Do you know the level of the participants
from the Martial Soul Hall?
What are their Martial Souls?
Little San. You still don’t get it.
You wouldn’t have the chance to win.
A black Decade Millennium Soul Ring?
Now, do you think I can compete
with those from the Martial Soul Hall?
Give up the tournament of this year.
At your age, you can still join
the tournament next year.
At that time, no one can be your rival.
But I have the strength to fight with them.
Do you know how troublesome you will be
if your fourth soul ring is of decade millennium?
If I’m not wrong,
your information is now on the table of
Platinum Chiefs of Martial Soul Hall.
They’ll either subdue you
or get rid of you on the field by chance.
The tournament rules are just a game
to the Martial Soul Hall.
How can I be eliminated as they wanted?
Let me tell you.
The soul powers of participants from
Martial Soul Hall are above Level 45.
One at Level 51, two at Level 52.
They’ve recorded the youngest
in the Martial Soul Hall.
They’ve also...
met the age of the participant.
I suggest that you give up.
At your age,
you still have big chances
to overtake them in the future.
Old Freak.
If I really drawback, I’ll lose confidence.
Only that I fight with all my strength,
then I can know the gap between our strengths.
I will not give up.
Fine. Younger generations
will do all right on their own.
Take care.
I’m going.
Who is it?
You want to fight again?
Xiao Wu, how did you do it?
Your melee ability seems
to be strengthened a lot.
Soul skill does not necessarily have to
be given by a soul ring.
We have a lot of potentials.
It’ll be a kind of soul skill when we develop one.
It’ll be more practical after understanding it.
By cooperating with the soul skill,
the overall strength will be
significantly improved.
Xiao Wu. You can actually see it so thoroughly.
We happen to hold the same view.
That is the direction of Shrek School.
What happened?
Teacher Er Long is too mean.
You didn’t cooperate well.
You couldn’t even pass three rounds under me.
I wonder when Little San and Xiao Wu are coming back.
If this continues,
my Evil Eyes White Tiger is
going to be a burnt tiger.
Master and guys, we are back.
It’s good to be back.
These days, your partners have been
practicing with Er Long.
The battle is quite tragic.
You guys must have suffered a lot.
After both of you return,
hopefully, you won’t do worse than them.
Rest assured, Teacher Er Long.
Shrek Seven Devils never fear of difficulties.
Guys, are you ready?
Yes!
Come on, Teacher Er Long!
Teacher Er Long comes from the family of
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
There’s the thunder property in her Martial Soul.
It’s likely to have a paralytic effect.
Boss Dai. Fatty.
When you meet head-on later,
don’t go on fighting and retreat quickly.
I will let Xiao Wu and Zhu Qing
distract Teacher Er Long’s attention.
Okay.
Xiao Wu. You cooperate with Zhu Qing.
Entangle Teacher Er Long
according to your melee advantage.
Remember. Teacher Er Long’s
soul power is far too terrifying.
Once the soul power in her body surges,
you must retreat immediately.
Otherwise, there’s no way we can fight back.
In short, as long as you retreat,
just leave the rest to me.
First soul skill, Phoenix Firing Line.
Third soul skill, Furious Fire Shocking Thunder.
Second soul skill,
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Nine Layers of Colours. Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
Jiubao Boosts! Second, Speed!
Purple Demon Eye!
Third soul skill, Teleport.
Second soul skill, Charm.
Fourth soul skill, Ghost Shadow Doppelganger.
You, little rascals!
Flying Mushroom Sausage!
Fourth soul skill, Blood Eater Flame!
Fifth soul skill!
Fourth soul skill!
Blue Silver Cage is not going to trap me!
Soaring Flame!
Blue Silver Spike Formation!
[Soul Land]
Teacher Er Long. You’ve lost.
This is...
Is this the result of
Little San’s cultivation these days?
Blue Silver Cage has mutated.
Facing this sudden attack of
Blue Silver Spike Formation,
even Teacher Er Long has been
caught unprepared.
Little San. How did you do this?
Blue Silver Cage has actually mutated.
Luckily, Xiao Wu helped me.
I have a new level of insight into
the Blue Silver Cage.
Okay, Er Long. You lost.
I don’t accept it. Why did I lose?
I must be the one to win
if we continue to fight.
The Martial Soul Fusion Skill of Mu Bai
and Zhu Qing hasn’t been used yet.
Little San has also retained his Eight Spider Bone.
You still lost.
You were set up.
When you were caught by Little San’s Purple Demon Eye,
you had no chance anymore.
Today, even Frander
couldn’t handle their bombardment.
Fine! How dare you set me up?
I am not Liu Er Long if I don’t beat till you cry!
We still have something to do.
Nothing can be better than
battling against Teacher Er Long.
Do your best, guys!
Er Long. You shall go easy.
It’s indeed the Imperial Hunting Ground.
It’s so stylish.
Sooner or later,
Shrek will also be as stylish as this.
Please show me your card.
Welcome.
I am Luo Ke Sen,
Third Team’s captain of the Imperial Knights.
Please come with me.
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament qualifying rounds
will be held in the camp.
To protect the soul masters’ privacy and safety,
ordinary audiences are not allowed
to watch the game.
Only teams that joined the preliminary
are allowed to watch the game.
To avoid unwanted troubles,
teams entering the qualifying rounds are
arranged to rest in different places.
This is Shrek School’s rest camp.
There won’t be any opening ceremony tomorrow.
Qualifying rounds will start right away.
Please rest early.
Thank you, General Luo Ke Sen.
No problem. I’ll leave first.
This rest camp looks good.
Hello, Uncle Ning.
Your Highness, why are you here?
Brother Tang. I came to visit you.
How is it? Can you adapt here?
The conditions here are very good.
Thanks for your concern, Your Highness.
Brother Tang.
Don’t call me that anymore.
I’m a few years older than you.
If you don’t mind,
just call me Brother Xue.
Can I just call your name?
Why are you stunned?
Hurry and call Brother Xue.
Okay, Brother Xue.
I’ll call you that in the future.
Where’s Rong Rong?
It’s been a while since I last met her.
I quite miss her.
Dad! Why are you here?
Hello, Chief Ning.
This is...
He is my disciple, Xue Qing He.
[Next Episode] Everyone, the drawing result
for tomorrow’s game is out.
We come with a bold request.
We from Shrek are ethical and with integrity.
The one smeared the good name
of soul masters is you.
I advise you and your losers
to out of the field as soon as possible.
Don’t you shame our Barak Kingdom.
Frander. You are a coward.
What happened?
Scoundrel.
Master, it’s getting late.
We shall go now.