♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
He’s the War Soul Master from Nuoding City.
I’m going to awaken your Martial Soul one by one.
Lone Wolf,
join me!
It’s a useless Martial Soul.
No attack,
no defence...
or assisting ability.
No soul power.
Something in my body...
seems to be unlocked.
Blue Silver Plant is considered
standard for useless Martial Soul.
I’ve never seen anyone with Blue Silver Plant...
who has the soul power.
He’s born with full soul power!
Born with full soul power,
but with Blue Silver Plant.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 3]
Little San, what’s your Martial Soul?
It’s Blue Silver Plant, Dad.
Is he...
Even though it’s Blue Silver Plant,
But Little San was born with full soul power.
I’ve decided...
to give the only apprentice position
in our village to Little San...
to learn at Beginner Soul Master School
in Nuoding City.
We’ll take care of the travel fee.
Blue Silver Plant.
No way.
What?
You should know this is a precious chance.
We get our this apprentice position...
because there was a Soul Saint
here in our village.
Others have to fight for a position
among two or three villages.
Are you aware of that?
By grabbing this chance,
Little San might be a successful person in the future.
What’s the use of being successful?
Who’s going to make me meals after he’s gone?
What can he train with Blue Silver Plant?
It’s just a useless Martial Soul.
But Little San was born with full soul power.
As long as he gets a soul ring,
even the worst can be trained as a soul master.
Soul master, you see?
It has been years since we had a soul master.
This is your motive behind all this, right?
I said no.
Alright, you may leave now.
Tang Hao!
I can still hear, you don’t have to shout.
I said, you may leave.
You!
Grandpa Jack, don’t be angry. My father is right.
Blue Silver Plant is just a useless Martial Soul.
I think I’d better not learn
those soul masters’ abilities.
Thank you for your kindness.
Good boy, I’m not angry.
Alright, I shall leave.
Tang Hao, you may have already given up,
but Little San is still young.
Don’t you think...
he deserves to learn some surviving skills?
Don’t stop him...
from becoming a soul master.
At least he won’t look down-and-out like you.
Come and look for me if you change your mind.
There are three months to go
before the registration starts.
Little San, get me the beer.
Are you disappointed?
You want to be a soul master?
It’s alright, Dad. I’m fine with being a blacksmith.
We can still survive with that.
Didn’t you promise...
to teach me to make farm tools?
What’s the use of being a soul master?
Not to mention a useless Martial Soul,
even the best Martial Soul...
and the strongest soul master...
are merely useless.
Don’t be angry, Dad.
I’m not going to be a soul master.
I’ll always accompany you and make meals for you.
Release your Martial Soul.
Alright.
It’s the same as hers.
Dad?
Stop bothering me!
But I still have another Martial Soul.
Let them go, I’ll go with you.
No.
No, Ah Yin!
No!
Ah Yin!
No.
This...
Is there anything wrong?
It’s Twin Martial Souls!
Son, my son.
Dad.
This is the first time Dad hugs me.
It feels so warm.
Wait, why is my inner power
decreasing drastically?
I’ll hurt Dad if this goes on.
Dad, I can’t hang on any more.
Withdraw it back.
Remember, in the future,
you must protect your plant with the hammer.
Forever.
Dad, I will. Promise.
It’s extremely rare to witness
Twin Martial Souls in this world.
Hang on.
If you continue to knock like this,
you won’t make it even after a year.
What should I do?
Look.
[Soul Land]
Finally, the hidden weapon of Tang Clan is done.
Too bad, I’m lack of iron samples now.
Or else it would be perfect
if I can add a hook at the arrow tip.
For the past three months, Dad has been
teaching me the hammering skill,
I can strike twenty-four times continuously now.
Even the other strikes have great improvements.
It’s time to think about
Xuan Tian Strike’s problem.
The porridge is ready.
Dad, let’s eat!
Normally, Dad will come out by now,
has he fallen sick?
Where did he go this early?
Dad, let’s eat.
Alright.
You don’t have to train to hammer today.
Pack your stuff,
and Old Jack will bring you
to Nuoding City tomorrow.
Nuoding City?
For what?
Don’t you want to learn to be a soul master?
Old Jack will bring you to
the Beginner Soul Master School.
You’ll learn what you want there.
Dad, why did you change your mind?
Are you going or not?
So Dad went out this morning
to look for the village head.
But no one will make meals for you then.
Do you think I really need you? Just go.
You chose this path.
Just use the hammering method I taught you...
to be an apprentice in a blacksmith shop there.
It should be enough to cover
your school fees and meals.
I won’t let you go to Nuoding City so easily.
Promise me something before you go.
I promise.
You didn’t even ask what I want,
yet you’d already agreed.
As a man,
you must mean what you say.
Don’t break your promise.
No matter what you ask, I’ll say yes.
It’s definitely for my own good.
Alright, I want you to promise me,
no matter how you train your soul power,
never add any soul ring to that hammer.
No one should know about its existence,
and the fact that you have Twin Martial Souls.
Can...
you do it?
What about Blue Silver Plant?
You can use that whenever you want.
For Twin Martial Souls,
you can proceed training
even you only have one soul ring.
Any problem with your soul power will be solved.
That means...
I can only use Blue Silver Plant, right?
Unless it’s a life-and-death matter,
never use the hammer!
Alright, got it.
Alright, let’s eat.
Little San, have you packed up?
That’s too loud, Grandpa Jack.
My dad is still sleeping.
He most dislikes being disturbing
while he sleeps.
Kid,
you’re still worrying about
your dad’s breakfast upon leaving?
Grandpa Jack, give me another minute.
Dad, I’m going with Grandpa Jack.
Take care of yourself.
Don’t forget the porridge in the pot.
Little San, will you miss the village...
or your drunken dad more?
Both.
Grandpa Jack, can you tell me about the school?
Of course, what would you like to know?
Dad asked me to work with a blacksmith
after getting into the school.
Working in a blacksmith shop?
Is he kidding?
Tang Hao must be crazy.
You’re too young for that.
Just study hard at school.
If you really are capable,
you should ask your dad
to earn some money for you.
We don’t have any more position
for Intermediate Soul Master School.
That costs quite some amount of money.
There’s Intermediate Soul Master School?
Of course!
[Next Episode]
Are villagers even allowed to be here?
Get lost.
The third Twin Martial Souls in a hundred year.
What?
Born with full soul power?
People will just laugh at him.