♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I’m back.
You looked fine.
It seems that there’s
something important for me to do.
I get it.
Tang San, can’t you let go of these resentments?
Someone is waiting for
my rescue in another place.
Xiao Wu, I’m coming.
It’s you again.
I, Meng Shu has been a soul master for years.
I’m not an unreasonable person.
I’ll give you two options.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 26]
Although Godly Zhuge Crossbow
can’t injure the two of you,
Meng Yi Ran can’t withstand it. If you go too far,
then don’t blame me for using
your granddaughter as a shield.
Appreciate for more details.
The first option is to join my family.
Join your family?
Yes.
If you become one of my family,
either killing Yi Ran’s hunted soul beast
or wasting the soul ring of
Human Faced Demon Spider
I’ll just let go of them.
Once a soul master joins into a family,
one can never betray it
and is controlled by the family.
Sorry, Senior. I’m used to freedom.
I dislike being constrained.
It’s a great offer for you.
How dare you turn it down.
I’m sorry for obstructing your granddaughter
to obtain the soul ring.
But, you’re wrong for one thing.
If you don’t appear, I must have
absorbed the soul ring of it.
It’ll not be wasted.
What?
You should know that without my permission,
you can’t absorb the Human Faced Demon Spider.
If so, this great soul ring will be wasted.
However, if you join us,
you can absorb the soul ring,
and I’ll protect you personally.
Otherwise, even it’s wasted,
we won’t give it to you either.
How about the second option?
Leave an arm as compensation
to my granddaughter.
I can join your family,
if you can fulfill my request.
What makes you qualified to bargain with me?
What is it? Say it.
We met a powerful soul beast before.
It has caught my friend.
If you can help rescue my friend
or take revenge for her,
I promise that I’ll join your family.
Only to hunt a soul beast?
Aren’t you together with Zhao Wu Ji?
Can’t he fight against the soul beast?
If Zhao Wu Ji can’t, it doesn’t mean that I can’t.
With our Fusion Skill,
there are few soul beasts in this Star Dou Forest
which can compete with us.
Tang San, what kind of soul beast is it?
It’s a Titan Giant Ape, above Decade Millennium.
Titan Giant Ape?
We can’t make it.
With your abilities,
can’t you fight the Titan Giant Ape?
You know nothing.
Titan Giant Ape is an ancient
peak-level soul beast.
Not to mention us, even the
Grand Soul Land Master might not beat it.
As far as I know, there’s only
one Titan Giant Ape here.
It is at least 60,000 years old.
A real overlord of the forest.
Moreover, it has a more terrifying brother.
Unless all Grand Soul Land Masters
of two empires gather,
otherwise, no one dares to hunt them.
Unexpectedly, Titan Giant Ape
appeared in forest periphery.
This is not a good omen.
Luckily, it doesn’t initiate a killing feast.
If not, Tang San can’t stay alive until now.
My old man,
Emm.
We should leave here quickly.
Has Xiao Wu...
No. That won’t happen.
Surely there must be a way.
Tang San.
Are you making fun of me with a Titan Giant Ape?
Don’t waste my time.
Tell me about your decision!
You can’t fulfill my wish,
so I won’t join your family.
If you want my arm, take it yourself.
Ha.
Since you want to die, I’ll fulfill your dream.
Senior Dragon Duke, please wait!
Senior Dragon Duke, I’m Zhao Wu Ji.
Nice to meet you, Acala.
Stealing Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent first,
then Human Faced Demon Spider.
You’ve taught them well.
Should you give me an explanation?
Senior, there are some misunderstandings.
And I’m a teacher in their school.
Tang San’s master is someone else, not me.
Oh!
Senior, can we talk over there?
Is it real?
Oh, you’re Grandmaster’s disciple!
Unexpectedly, he got a chance
to realize his theory.
Today, I’ll let go of you for the sake of your master.
However,
bear it in mind, if the same things happen again,
I won’t care who your master is.
Thank you, Senior.
Can Master’s fame deter
the Unrivaled Dragon Serpent?
Let’s leave.
Grandpa! Grandpa! He has snatched my soul ring
for twice. How can we just let him go?
How do you want to deal with it?
Grandpa is old. I shouldn’t bully the weak.
All right. Since Grandpa doesn’t help,
I’ll do it by myself.
Tang San.
Em.
If you’re a real man, battle with me.
Battle again? Have you forgotten
you had lost to me?
I’ll defeat you this time.
Your soul power is insufficient.
Let’s have a different kind of battle.
How’s the bet?
If you win, you can have
the Human Faced Demon Spider.
If you lose, you’re not allowed to absorb it.
All right.
Wait! This is unfair.
The bet is not fair. If Little San defeats you,
you should do something as well.
What do you want?
Apart from not hindering Little San
to absorb the soul ring, you need to...
What should I do?
Kiss him.
What?
Little Ao!
All right. Let’s carry on.
Grandpa!
Young people should have a little passion.
Let’s begin.
Let’s do it quickly.
How’s the battle go?
[Soul Land]
I’m having 32 soul knives here.
We’ll have 16 respectively.
Later, my grandpa to shake a tree 20 meters away.
We’ll throw the soul knives
at those falling leaves simultaneously.
The one who impales the most leaves will win.
No matter how many leaves are impaled,
the soul knives must be stabbed
on the tree trunk. If not, it won’t be counted.
All right.
Do you need to rest?
I’m not taking advantage of you.
I still have things to do. Let’s start now.
You!
Why do these kids seem confident?
Interesting!
Ready!
Begin.
Didn’t you throw?
I have done it.
What?
It’s such a magical moment! Yi Ran...
[Fifteen seconds ago]
Yi Ran, you lost!
It’s unnecessary to see the result! Let’s leave.
No, I don’t believe it.
My girl, admit your failure!
Even I can’t perform Tang San’s technique,
16 soul knives were thrown simultaneously
and stabbed on the tree with only one sound.
Each knife has ten leaves on it.
Besides, he was not facing the tree.
He didn’t use his eye at all.
It’s such a magical technique.
Miss Meng,
your soul knife.
Are you here to tease me?
I don’t.
Then, why are you here?
You don’t need to be sad about your failure.
I’ve been
practicing hidden weapons for nine years.
Nine years? Hidden weapon?
Yes. Nine years.
No. I’m asking you what the hidden weapon is.
Hidden weapon means the weapon to use in secret.
The weapon to use in secret?
What is this?
This is Bone Piercing Needle,
with powerful penetration.
It’s 20% lighter than your knife.
It’s convenient to carry it.
What do you mean?
Gift it to you.
To me?
It should be more suitable that the knife for you.
If you’re willing to, I can tell you
the practice method.
It should be better than your technique now.
What? You want to teach me?
Yes, are you willing to learn?
Can I?
Of course!
Just now, I could perform it precisely
without using my eyes.
It’s the basic technique of using hidden weapons.
It’s known as sound track identification.
Identifying the location
of the target through sound.
There’s no blind zone
when the hidden weapon is shot.
It’s great concealed as well.
I won’t say thanks to you.
I don’t expect it. Just take it as
a compensation for snatching you twice.
This is the bet. Bet is bet. I don’t break it.
Please don’t think much.
Little San, are you feeling good?
Give me one more recovery sausage.
Xiao Wu’s life is uncertain. No more delay.
I’m sorry to bother all of you.
Are you sure not to rest first?
No. Teacher Zhao, please help me.
What a strong soul power wave!
How old is this Human Faced Demon Spider?
Teacher Zhao. This...
Little San might can’t bear this Human Face Demon Spider.
There’s a great gap in their power. It’s vicious.
Little San is more likely going through
a life-or-death challenge.
Grandmaster, join us. Several students are
celebrating their breakthrough.
Xiao Gang, will you be back?
Martial Soul Hall, I’m back!