♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Is this dorm seven?
Hello, I’m Xiao Wu, the “Wu” from dance.
I want to have a friendly fight with you.
Are you sure?
Gosh.
Little San, your bedding is huge. Let’s share it.
Together?
Many think that the Blue Silver Plant is useless.
But after years of research,
Blue Silver Plant has its strength too.
First, it consumes little soul power.
Second, it is commonly found and deceitful.
Third, it has various development paths.
It doesn’t repel the soul ring easily.
Repel?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 6]
That’s right.
If your Martial Soul
doesn’t match with the soul ring,
Adding the soul ring
on the Martial Soul...
will result in a repulsion.
And the fourth benefit
only works on you.
Me?
Yes.
The soul masters who own the Blue Silver Plant...
has too little soul power when they’re awakened.
That’s why they’re progressing slowly.
There’s never been a powerful
Blue Silver Plant master in Soul Land.
But you’re different.
You are born with full soul power.
This is what people are lacking.
To conclude,
I suggest that you go to the Controlling Branch.
Controlling Branch?
Controlling Branch uses
Martial Soul to restrain the opponent.
And gain control of the situation.
Right,
after thorough research,
the Blue Silver Plant Martial Soul
can change its form freely.
No doubt it is perfect for Controlling Branch.
But the Blue Silver Plant breaks easily.
How can it tie people up?
That’s your development path.
Your soul ring should focus on two areas.
Firstly, its tenacity and the other one is poison.
As your soul power elevates,
your Martial Soul will be more powerful too.
After you channels in more
soul power into the Blue Silver Plant,
naturally, it will become tougher.
In addition to the supporting effects
of the soul ring,
It’s easy to tie up the enemy.
Whereas the poison will restrain the enemy.
A combination like this
is enough to attack the enemy.
That means from now on
I must use the hidden weapon
on a fixed target.
That’s all for now.
Alright.
You may go back first.
I’ll pick you up tomorrow morning.
Okay.
Master.
The school has just started
yet you’re leaving?
What about the apprentice’s job?
If you leave, I’ll have to do the work alone.
You’ll have to work harder for these few days.
After I’m back,
I’ll settle the work for the rest of the semester.
You’ll still get the wages.
How is it?
Well,
I’ll accept this then.
Okay,
it’s a deal.
Let’s go back.
But,
I still want to fight with you.
Fight again?
That’s right.
I hit you first.
It’s considered as a sneak attack.
It’s unfair even if I win over you.
And you were not satisfied with the result.
I’ll give you another chance.
Come on, then.
Don’t cry if I hit you later.
Are you ready?
Come on.
What are you doing?
Isn’t this a friendly fight?
Yes.
I’m coming to you.
How about it?
Convinced or not?
Not convinced. Try again.
Try again?
I won’t give you an opportunity.
If you have any skills,
then struggle free.
What are you doing?
In a public place?
Get off!
You two...
What do you have to say?
Teacher.
- We were having a friendly fight...
- Please let me explain...
Friendly fight?
Friendly fight by lying on the ground
and learning how to flirt at a young age.
What about when you’re grown up?
Teacher.
If you don’t believe me,
I’ll have a friendly fight with you too.
Teacher.
Are you okay?
What was your technique just now?
It seems pretty awesome.
That’s my favorite technique.
It’s called Rabbit Kicking Eagle.
Rabbit Kicking Eagle.
I did not use my hand.
Otherwise, the result will be more serious.
Why are you asking so clearly?
Thinking about a counter measure?
You are gauging the heart of a gentleman.
Dare you say I’m a base person?
I’ve found out the way to fight you.
Speaking of speed, I’m not afraid of you.
Hey, you’re cheating.
We’re having a friendly fight, not hide-and-seek.
You can’t just dodge around!
You can attack me if you want.
Okay, be careful.
Hit your left shoulder.
Hit your right shoulder.
This rascal is bluffing me.
Left leg, right leg.
Hey, how dare you to hit me with rocks?
Is using rocks not allowed?
No, this doesn’t count.
This time, you lose.
Again.
Again? Okay then.
Master, where are we going to find the soul beast?
Why are you so tired? Are you sick?
Maybe I didn’t rest well yesterday.
It’s okay.
Please continue on
the information about soul beast.
Okay, listen carefully.
Normally, soul beast is divided into five levels.
Decade Soul Beast, Century Soul Beast,
Millennium Soul Beast...
Decade Millennium Soul Beast and
Century Millennium Soul Beast.
Each of them corresponds to
white, yellow, purple, black, red,
the five colours of the soul ring.
The longer the soul beast
has been practicing, the stronger it is,
and the soul ring that it produces will be better.
Soul Hunting Forest at
the north side of Nuoding City.
That is where the royals rear their soul beast.
Decade or Century Soul Beast
are mostly found there.
It’s rare to find any soul beast
above the Millennium Soul Beast.
But judging from your current situation,
Decade or Century Soul Beast will be enough.
Master, how is the soul ring powerful?
This is a good question.
Soul ring not only can add into
the soul master’s characteristic,
it can also add special skills on the soul master.
For instance,
if you get a matching Decade Soul Ring.
Your control on
Blue Silver Plant will increase by ten.
If Century Soul Ring,
your control will increase by hundred.
The add on skills for Century Soul Ring...
is normally stronger than Decade Soul Ring.
That means powerful nobles can use their
family’s power to hunt strong beasts?
Great. It seems that
you’ve thought about this.
The nobles have advantages
on hunting soul beasts.
But the soul ring’s adding terms are strict.
First, the soul ring exists shortly
after the soul beast dies.
The soul ring created will only be
gained by the soul master who killed it.
Besides, soul beasts are prideful.
They won’t allow themselves to be held captives.
If they are seriously injured,
they’ll self detonate so that the
soul master can’t get their soul rings.
Moreover,
soul masters must persevere
while absorbing the soul ring.
Or else, they’ll be unable to withstand
the power of the soul ring and explode.
I got it.
Little San, this world is fair. This is for you.
Thank you, Master.
Youngster shall not refuse gifts from an elder.
Good, this belt has been with me for thirty years.
It hasn’t also been used for thirty years.
Hopefully in the future,
it can be useful as it should in your hands.
Master, what is this belt for?
It is a soul guiding tool for storage.
Every piece of jade can provide
a storage space of a cubic meter.
To use it, channels your soul power into it.
Each piece of jade has
one cubic meter of storage space.
Twenty-four cubic meters in total.
The storage for hidden weapons is settled.
This belt has been with me for thirty years,
yet I’ve never named it.
You should name it.
I’ll name it as
Twenty-Four Moonlight Bridges.
It’s a nice name, but a bit too lengthy.
Considered it as a memory from Tang Clan.
[Soul Land]
I have the token!
A team to hunt for strength type soul beast.
We still need two more persons.
Hunt for agility type soul beast.
Token for seven. Ten gold soul coins.
Master, why is here so busy?
These are due to benefits.
Soul masters are rich.
These people are here to earn their money.
What about those who are calling for a team?
You have to kill the soul beast
to absorb the soul ring.
But some powerful soul beasts
are not easy to hunt.
Thus they need to form a team and work together.
But a temporarily formed team like this...
can’t be considered as a real team.
A truly superior hunting team...
needs to form by five parts.
Food Branch tool soul master
is in charge of replenishment.
Healing Branch tool soul master on
condition’s and soul power’s recovery.
Agility Branch war
soul master on the investigation.
Strength Branch war soul master on defence.
Attack Branch war soul master
on killing the opponent.
A team with these five factors...
is a team that is considered complete.
Besides, teamwork...
can’t be formed in a few days.
More importantly,
the teammates in the same team,
must trust each other.
Otherwise, when encountering danger,
the team will fall into pieces easily.
Trust?
Maybe you’ll join such a team in the future.
While choosing a team,
you can even not
considering your teammate’s ability.
But you need to keep this in mind.
The team that you choose
is a team that you can entrust your back with.
Soul Hunting Forest is not for anyone to enter.
Only soul masters with
token issued from Martial Soul Hall...
are allowed to enter the forest
to hunt for soul beasts.
These soldiers are
just defensing on the outer area.
In the Soul Hunting Forest,
law enforcement officials
from Martial Soul Hall
will check the token at any time.
They are merciless.
Master,
the Soul Hunting Forest is
owned by Martial Soul Hall or the country?
Don’t ask a question like this in public.
The relations between
Martial Soul Hall and the country,
I’ll tell you later.
It isn’t hard to get the token.
First, you need approval from Martial Soul Hall.
To confirm that your skills
has reach a certain peak of a level.
And you need a soul ring to level up.
Next, you need at least
three nobles to vouch for you.
Remember this logo.
This is the logo of Martial Soul Hall.
There are six types of the logo in Martial Soul Hall.
You need to differentiate
the token by its pattern.
The lowest ranking token has a sword on it.
It symbolises a late chief executive
officer of Martial Soul Hall’s temple.
The token with a rank higher
has a hammer beside the sword.
It symbolizes an extremely powerful elder
of Martial Soul Hall in the past.
Master.
These two persons must have
important positions in Martial Soul Hall.
I heard that beast soul
is stronger than tool soul.
But both of them are tool souls, right?
Those who said that
beast soul is stronger than tool soul,
apparently have little
understanding about Martial Soul.
The strength of a Martial Soul
depends on two things.
First, it’s the soul power
when the Martial Soul’s awaken.
Another one is hard practice.
True strength depends on own’s practice.
Let’s go.
This token,
is Martial Soul Hall’s third-ranking warrant.
It can be owned forever.
Unlike the two previous tokens,
they need to be returned to
the Martial Soul Hall after the hunt.
With this,
you can enter any forest
without Decade Millennium Soul Beast
in Tian Dou.
Compared with the two other tokens,
my token has a Blue Lightning T-Rex on it.
It is considered as
a top creature among the beast souls.
Although its master is
not from Martial Soul Hall,
the family it’s representing is
respected by Martial Soul Hall.
There are three higher ranking tokens.
Each has an additional logo, right?
That’s right.
Six logos of Martial Souls.
Each represents six powerful soul masters.
It also represents six powerful families.
Three of them are in Tian Dou Empire.
Another three are in Xing Luo Empire.
Master, the soul masters
represented in the tokens,
what are their titles?
Soul Saint, Great Soul Land Master,
or Grand Soul Land Master?
Grand Soul Land Master.
The six most powerful
Grand Soul Land Masters.
Most powerful?
Same level, different soul rings,
different Martial Souls.
Their strengths are totally different.
These six Grand Soul Land Masters
are the best of the best.
Even there are other soul masters
who reach above Level 90,
and enter the Grand Soul Land Master level,
their status remains unchanged.
But, this is still too distant for you.
Okay, we’re going to enter the forest.
From now on,
don’t leave my side, not even a single step.
Okay.
[Next Episode] It’s the scariest
among all poison soul beasts.
And it is extremely fast.
Come on, my first soul ring.
Farting like thunder. Blasting Luo San Pao!