♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Why did Martial Soul Hall turn all out for it?
Yet they returned with nothing,
and even might lose their pope.
If it’s a soul bone,
Martial Soul Hall wouldn’t lose.
Diamond Mammoth.
Please.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 72]
I heard that the captain of
Elephant Armoured School Team
has some relations with Chief Huyan.
Li is the most outstanding one among
all youths in Elephant Armoured Tribe.
He’s my eldest grandson.
His innate talent is even better than mine.
I’m hoping he can be the first
Grand Soul Land Master in my tribe.
Congrats Chief Huyan for having such a grandson.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Our tribe aims to get top three in finals.
For now, let’s see how he performs today.
However,
your grandson is battling with
four soul sects above Level 40 this time.
One of them has possessed a 10,000 aged soul ring.
He is Tang San, right?
Chief Ning.
Do you know who could
teach such a brilliant disciple?
Your Majesty,
do you remember the Golden Iron Triangle?
They’re now in charge of Shrek School.
The dean, Frander is the Flying Vertex.
These kids are taught by
the Wisdom Vertex, Master.
He’s the only direct disciple of Grandmaster.
Grandmaster? How could it be him?
Chief Salas,
do you know him too?
No one hasn’t heard of the Golden Iron Triangle.
Martial Soul Hall and Grandmaster are well-connected.
I never expected that he went to Shrek School.
No wonder those young students
are very outstanding.
Salas thinks highly of himself,
why is he shocked upon hearing
Grandmaster’s name?
It must be something behind it.
Since both of you think highly of this Grandmaster,
I’d like to meet him in person.
Let’s watch the game now.
Preliminary second round, first match.
Shrek School versus Elephant Armoured School,
officially begins!
First soul skill.
Impregnable Fortress.
Retreat.
First soul skill, Intertwine.
Brother San’s Blue Silver Plant is tough.
How could he break it so easily?
It seems like their strength is
beyond our expectation.
Moreover,
apart from having powerful strength,
they’re so good at using their merits.
They use their physical strength
to replace the consumption of soul power.
Furthermore, combining soul power
and physical strength
to stimulate more powerful strength.
Even though Blue Silver Plant is tough,
but a small amount of winding
can’t restrict their movement.
I didn’t expect that Shrek has several Soul Sects.
So, it’d be better to attack soundly,
instead of acting impulsively.
What we have to do now is
to maintain this formation.
If we could take down those
aren’t from Keen Attack Branch,
we’ll win.
The more space they occupy,
the more power they can exert.
Little San, right now!
Advance, three steps.
First soul skill, Intertwine.
I know this.
This formation derives from Meteor Hammer.
With the help of Blue Silver Plant
to control their movement precisely.
I name this Human Meteor Hammer.
Little Ao.
Third soul skill,
Flying Mushroom Sausage.
Lighten yourselves.
Xuan Tian Strike,
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
Tang San has a flying ability as well?
I’d say this ability comes from
the assisting soul master.
That’s why that sturdy
Supreme Orangutan was replaced.
This is what he aimed to do.
With this formation,
everyone lightens their body
within the weight
that the Flight Mushroom Sausage could cater.
Tai Long is too heavy.
Otherwise, he could do better
than Xiao Wu with this strategy.
How come they’re airborne soul masters?
Since flying in the sky,
they could avoid our strong defensive bodies,
and directly attack our heads.
They even disrupt our pace
for attacking.
This Tang San...
Brother, should we use that skill?
No.
No way.
that’s for dueling with Shen Feng School.
They must have greater attack tactics behind.
Don’t panic, maintain our formation.
Their formation is well-guarded.
I’ve no chance to use the fourth soul skill.
Air combat is indeed our only weakness,
but we’re invincible when it comes to defence.
Let’s see who will start first.
Little Ao.
Brother, come up here.
Childish,
you only know how to evade us.
Why don’t you call yourselves as Tortoise School?
Secret snack.
Brother.
Darn it!
What a fool.
Forget about Shen Feng School. Set up the fort!
Mammoth Spiral Bomb.
Load.
Speed up, turbo charge.
What are they doing?
Oh no!
Fire.
Boss Dai, block it!
White Tiger Protection Barrier.
I can’t stand such a strong power.
Trigonal Defense, please.
First, defence break.
[Soul Land]
Xuan Yu Hand.
Right now.
Second shot, sneaky attack.
What a little devil.
How dare he takes
the blade wheel barehanded.
Mammoth Wheel isn’t that simple.
His hand is beyond recovery.
Dismantle the blade wheel.
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon,
Four Liang Lifting A Thousand Jin.
It’s quite tough to take down the blade wheel.
Watch out!
Mammoth Triple Bomb.
Bring Tang San
out!
Lock him down.
Darn it, I can’t move.
Great! Right now!
No! It’s Huyan Li.
Come on, Brother.
Bash him, Li!
Go to hell!
How could you be so foolish?
Oh, that time.
Secret snack.
Taste good?
I want to kill you.
No, save Brother.
Second soul skill, Parasite.
This...
These seeds are actually
when we were fighting...
They made it.
Forth soul skill, Blue Silver Cage.
Shrek School! Knock them down!
Defeat them!
Super Recovery Big Sausage.
He used Parasite and Blue Silver Cage
to fight for time?
Their first soul ring is defence.
Second soul ring should be
strength amplification.
Even the third soul skill is
strength type as well.
In order to get rid of
Blue Silver Plant,
Huyan Li, the strongest one
takes about four seconds.
while the slowest one
takes seven seconds.
If Blue Silver Cage is used...
If there’s no mistake,
that means
20 seconds
is the longest period
I could control the rest of them.
Pay attention, everyone!
Defeat Huyan Li within 20 seconds.
Shrek,
how could you use that tiny booger
to ruin my perfect plan?
He has lost his mind.
Xiao Wu!
I can’t stand this shame...
Where’s she?
Look here.
Let’s attack together!
Beat him!
Brother,
bear it!
This hit is really terrifying.
Huyan Li is in danger.
That’s...
What a tough face.
Chief Huyan, it seems like you’ve broken the rules.
I don’t get you, Chief Ning.
What have I done?
What did he tell his grandson?
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Martial Soul of Skeleton.
Martial Soul of Bloodthirsty Wolf.
Third soul skill, Nether Slash.
Done.
No.
This...
A helmet?
No, it’s a skull bone.
What the heck? Aren’t contestants allowed
to use implement?
Poor thing, this is a soul bone.
Having such a skull bone at this young age,
your grandson is really outstanding.
Is your attack ending here?
It’s our turn then.
What a clumsy stumblebum.
Third soul skill, The Pressure Kill.
What a strong pressure.
Zhu Qing.
My legs are immobilised.
This is Soul Skill Lockdown.
Mu Bai!
No, Huyan Ba and Huyan Shan’s time is ending soon.
Zhu Qing!
White Tiger of Netherworld, hurry up.
White Tiger of Netherworld.
Come on, Shrek.
[Next Episode]
Let’s continue watching.
They broke the cage.
Have his spirit power developed
to such a high level?
Little San only at Level 41.
Little San, you’re finally awake.
You really make us worried.
What happened just now? Tell me in detail.
Xiao Wu, please give me a hand.