♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
During the preliminary，
your biggest rivals are those Five Elements Schools.
Martial Soul Hall should be
the fusion of both streams.
It is the fused stream of
extreme individuals and balanced teams.
It is much stronger than you expect.
We are not in Tian Dou City.
You’re a genius, so what?
You will die in pain in my Brutal Dreamland.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 75]
Purple Demon Eye.
In just a few words, you will die.
Even the hardest jewel
will lose its shine under the
corrosion of Yama’s Invitation Poison.
What’s the thing that keeps shining?
Soul bone.
Soul bone is indeed a premium treasure.
But it must be suitable for you.
If you don’t understand the soul bone’s function,
don’t rush to absorb it in.
Or else,
you may waste one of
your six soul bones position.
Purple Demon Eye.
Brother.
Xiao Wu, is Little San feeling better now?
He’s still unconscious.
But his condition has become more stable.
I think he should be okay.
Great. I shall have my meal first.
By the way, Grandmaster said that after Little San is awake,
he wants to see him.
I’m okay now, I’ll go and see Master.
Master, I’m here.
Sit down.
Yesterday, did someone attack you?
Tell me in detail.
It’s Shi Nian from Cang Hui School.
Nightmare Shi Nian?
Yes.
He has let you go?
Shi Nian is always cruel.
Moreover, he has a unique Martial Soul.
Whether to attack or escape,
his opponent is at a disadvantage.
He’s dead.
I killed him with the Yama’s Invitation.
Besides, I’ve got his soul bone.
Hurry and show me.
You’ve got this soul bone,
yet you still remember what I’ve said.
You didn’t absorb it immediately.
This shows that you have
an extraordinary temperament.
Now I can rest assured.
After this contest, I’ll let you graduate.
Don’t tell anyone about Shi Nian’s incident,
including Shrek Seven Devils and Frander.
[Soul Land]
Shi Nian is missing.
But it has nothing to do with you.
Even for this soul bone. Do you understand?
Yes, Master. What is the use of this soul bone?
This soul bone should be
under the jewel category.
It’s suitable for soul masters
of Support Branch and Illusion type.
Thus, it doesn’t suit you.
Ideally,
we can use it to trade for a suitable soul bone.
What kind of soul bone will suit me?
Soul bones of Plant Branch
and Strength Branch will do.
is certainly beneficial for you.
As for soul bones of Strength Branch,
it will strengthen your body.
So that you can withstand higher pressure.
This is also a preparation
for your second Martial Soul.
Then when can I trade this soul bone?
Don’t worry.
Soul bone is a sensitive issue
among the soul masters.
If you’re not powerful enough,
you can’t trade for a suitable soul bone,
you may even lose your life.
Recently,
a guard was killed at Tian Dou Auction.
The treasure is gone.
There is no fatal wound on the body.
But it seems like
he has suffered before death.
It may be Shi Nian’s doings.
Do you mean that
this is the stolen auction item
of Tian Dou Auction?
We can’t pass this soul bone
to Tian Dou Auction.
Or else you’ll be suspected for
killing the guard and stealing the item.
The death of Shi Nian may be investigated too.
Forget about what happened today.
Understand, Master.
If your father is here,
no one can harm you.
Or if you’re supported by Hao Tian Tribe.
Okay, let’s discuss the upcoming matches.
[Participant Information]
Little San, how do you feel?
I’m fine now.
Grandmaster.
Is Shrek School’s opponent
for this round confirmed?
Our opponent for the next round
is Chi Huo School.
Chi Huo School?
Is it the one like the
Elephant Armoured School,
it’s also one of the Five Elements Schools?
As expected,
the extreme faction is starting to overcome
their weaknesses with their strengths.
According to the data,
the members of Chi Huo School’s team
consist of soul masters of Storm Attack,
Keen Attack, Controlling,
and Support Branch.
Their teamwork will be ingenious.
Their abilities may be higher than
Elephant Armoured School.
If you can’t do this, you’d better give up.
There’s no need to be persistent.
Since this is just a preliminary.
Even if Chi Huo School is very powerful,
we should give it a try too.
There’s no harm if we lose.
Our Shrek School is fearless.
Shrek School, fearless.
Qin Ming, you’ll lead for this contest.
Rest assured, Grandmaster.
Master, aren’t you going to be our leader?
I will still be your leader.
But there are many participating teams
for this tournament.
I can’t possibly study all of them.
I’ve invited Qin Ming to be
Shrek School Team’s vice leader
He’ll assist me to arrange battle strategies.
We’ll count on you, Teacher Qin.
It’s okay.
I’ve not joined this tournament
when I was a student.
It can be considered as I’ve achieved my dream.
Grandmaster, what about Dean Frander?
Frander? He needs to settle the new sponsorship.
He has no time for tactical analysis
before the battle.
You’ve changed your uniform and your
advertisement fees have reduced by half.
Frander blamed these on me and
wants me to be responsible for it.
Welcome to the Central Arena of
the eleventh preliminary.
I’m your old friend, Dou Dou.
Today, Shrek School will
fight against Chi Huo School.
Let’s invite both teams into the arena
with a big round of applause.
Come on, Chi Huo.
Previously Shrek School
has defeated one of the School of Five Elements,
Elephant Armoured School.
If they can defeat Chi Huo School again,
their ranking will be upgraded.
Come on.
Shrek will win again!
Whereas Chi Huo School has never lost
since its participation.
These two teams,
which team will maintain their victory?
We shall wait and see.
Before the battle,
according to the rules,
we shall take a look
at both teams’ members
and positions.
- Chi Huo.
- Chi Huo School is famous for fire
and their attack.
The two Storm Attack Branch soul masters
should not be looked down on.
Shrek School has used the same
guarding formation as before.
I wonder how they will
fight against Chi Huo this time.
Let’s take a look at the members.
I hereby announce, the eleventh
preliminary will start in...
Three, two, one.
Start!
If your Controlling Branch soul master
is not a Plant Branch,
maybe you’ll have a chance to win.
But now...
We’ll wait and see then.
That being said, but Little San...
First soul skill.
Threadlike Sparks.
This team has great teamwork.
At the very beginning,
they’re building up their superiority.
[Next Episode]
What a good support and control.
Gosh, I’m being tricked.
It’s a double trap.
Tang San, you’re the only one left now.
Grandmaster.
Our opponents are too powerful,
it’s hard for us to win.
Are you trying to perform suicide?
You’ve come just in time.
You’re indeed powerful, yet...
It’s over, Tang San.
The victory is ours.
Skip the next match.