♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Fifth soul skill, Gravity Squeeze.
Such a small hammer. I’ll give you a lesson.
Teacher Zhao, did we pass?
Yes, you passed.
The Grand Soul Land Master.
You hit the young one.
The older one will of course ask for justice.
Let’s begin.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 16]
Zhao Wu Ji,
do you understand now?
Thank you
for your guidance, Lord Hao Tian.
Consider that
as your compensation.
Thank you in advance.
Frander,
you’re a non-loyal friend.
If it weren’t for
the Lord’s kindness...
What do you know?
If he were to mean harm,
even if I fought alongside you,
do you think we would escape death?
He dares to attack the Pope,
he has no fear.
You don’t even understand that.
I just didn’t expect
him to be...
I understand you.
You just didn’t want to infuriate him.
But
I was so badly hit,
can’t you just let me whine?
His power is really scary.
Perhaps...
not many people in this land...
can be his equal.
No Grand Soul Land Master
should be triggered.
Where is this?
You’re awake.
This is our dorm.
I heard you fought Teacher Zhao alone today.
You made Teacher Zhao suffer great loss.
I didn’t expect you to be so fierce.
That was Teacher Zhao.
You’re called Tang San, right?
I’m Oscar.
Soul master of Level 29.
My Martial Soul is Sausage.
My nickname is The Sausage Ocar.
You may call me Little Ao.
Where’s Xiao Wu?
How is she?
Xiao Wu?
Oh, Xiao Wu is fine..
She shares the same room
as the pretty Ning Rong Rong.
She should be fine after sleeping.
Sadly she didn’t eat my sausage.
Or else she would be awake by now.
Ning Rong Rong from Qibao Amber Tribe
is gorgeous.
Forget about your sausage.
Uncle Sausage.
What Uncle Sausage?
I’ll shave my beard tomorrow.
I’ll show you my handsome,
elegant,
and cool side..
There are some pretty juniors
in our school now.
I can’t be so dispirited.
Mu Bai obviously likes the beautiful cool girl.
Xiao Wu is yours.
So I’ll have no choice
but to pursue Ning Rong Rong.
Xiao Wu and I
are just friends.
Alright,
stop pretending.
We’re both men.
I understand.
At a young age,
you have such a pretty girlfriend.
The two of you came to the school alone,
and nothing happened in between?
Boss Dai said,
just because Xiao Wu is injured,
that’s why you fought Teacher Zhao so hard.
Who would believe that
the two of you are just friends?
But don’t you worry.
I have my principles.
Don’t be polite with your friend’s wife.
No.
I mean be polite
with your friend’s wife.
I will not fall for your Xiao Wu.
Rong Rong.
Tang San.
The defence skill of Teacher Zhao
is stunning.
Fortunately, he wasn’t fast enough.
If not,
I wouldn’t have no chance at all.
I have to figure something out.
Or else, when I meet such an opponent
in the future...
Maybe,
I should make some machinery hidden weapon,
in order to fight strong opponents like Teacher Zhao.
Angered Buddha’s Lotus.
Pear Blossom Shower.
Peacock Plumes.
However,
the production of these weapons is difficult...
The material required
is also hard to get.
It’s impossible to make them
in such condition.
It seems I have to train harder.
Find the opportunity
to make some poison.
Little Ao,
get up.
What’s going on?
Let me sleep.
Get up.
It’s late now.
Don’t you know that morning
is the best hour?
I’m different from you guys.
You guys are war soul masters.
I’m a tool soul master.
I’m even from the Food Branch.
I don’t need to train
as hard as you guys.
Brother,
please stop making a row.
Let me sleep a little longer.
Then tell me where Xiao Wu is living.
I want to see if she has recovered.
Go left when you’re outside of our dorm.
In about 30 meter,
there’s a wooden house.
That’s where Xiao Wu and Ning Rong Rong live.
But
I have to remind you.
The school rules specify that...
male students aren’t allowed
to disturb female students.
The school rules are strict.
Shrek School takes up
a third area of this village.
The other side is where the villagers live.
Don’t go there.
Xiao Wu,
are you feeling better?
Rong Rong is training.
Don’t disturb her.
Let’s talk elsewhere.
It was my fault yesterday.
I didn’t protect you well.
The teacher was too powerful.
How can I blame you?
This place is different from Nuoding.
It seems that everyone is powerful.
Luckily,
no one with the highest soul level has appeared.
How do you know if there’s no one
in the school with highest soul level?
Teacher Zhao is just the Deputy Dean.
Maybe the Dean has the highest soul level.
I was just guessing.
After all,
why would a Grand Soul Land Master
stay quietly in such place?
Let’s go.
Go to find some food.
Okay.
[Soul Land]
Ma Hong Jun,
stop seeing me.
I’ll not be with you anymore.
Cui Hua,
am I not nice to you?
Why are you breaking up with me?
You’re nice to me,
But...
Your Martial Soul is...
The Dean said,
there would be a way soon.
Give me a little more time.
No.
Don’t.
I have to consider my family’s safety.
Stop.
What a beautiful girl.
What?
You want to be my girlfriend after her?
Okay,
no problem.
I agree.
No way.
You little rogue.
You’re young and yet doing bad.
Are you trying to...
seize this girl in public?
This is our matter.
Stop being busybody.
Since you don’t want to be my woman,
leave then.
You...
You’re called Ma Jun Hong, right?
Please stop disturbing this lady.
Who do you think you are?
How dare you interrupt your “father’s” business?
Are you looking for trouble?
Whose father are you?
I’m the father of
those who’re busybody.
So? You can’t hit me, right?
This fatty has
similar soul power as mine.
This isn’t so easy.
You’re a soul master too.
No wonder you dare to interrupt me.
I’ll show you what is actual strength.
The Merging of Phoenix.
Phoenix?
Grandmaster has mentioned,
there are some
very powerful soul beasts.
One of them
is phoenix.
Phoenix is also called seven-color bird.
Other than giving the owner flying ability,
it also has strong fire attacking power.
It’s the best of the combat type Martial Soul.
Is there such a fat phoenix?
I think he looks more like a chicken.
Who are you calling a chicken?
First soul skill, Phoenix Firing Line.
Be careful.
What’s that?
Have a taste of
the undying bird’s fury.
That’s not good.
Little San.
Don’t worry.
According to my observation,
the temperature of his flame is high,
but the attacking distance is only 5 meter.
If we limit his mobility...
Blue Silver Plant?
Oh, no.
He recognized the shortcoming
of Phoenix Firing Line.
But the next one...
Oh, no.
Although my Blue Silver Plant has 2 soul rings,
as a plant,
it’s still afraid of fire.
His Martial Soul,
is my nemesis.
Let me do this.
Xiao Wu.
Second soul skill,
Fire Bathing Phoenix.
Rascal,
how dare you say that I’m a chicken?
This is my second soul skill.
Besides having complete defense,
it can also attack.
If I don’t give you a lesson,
I won’t be called the Devil Phoenix.
But she’s quite pretty.
It’s better not to burn her.
The flame has gone weaker.
Is the fatty showing mercy?
Okay, I’ll be gentler to you then.
That was my first soul skill,
Arched Body.
The Arched Body of Xiao Wu...
can increase
her waist power up to 100%...
and her body tenacity up to 50%.
Besides,
after her soul power achieved Level 10,
every level of increment
can raise the effect by 1%.
I’m at Level 29 now.
That means...
my waist power has increased to 119%.
If I can get near to someone,
those below Level 50
won’t be able to handle it.
Although your Fire Bathing Phoenix
is powerful,
when I release my soul power,
there is no problem to defense
when I pass the firing line.
How is it, Fatty?
You want to fight again?
Stop fighting.
How are you?
Miss Cui Hua, you...
I’m not dead.
Little Rabbit.
Let’s fight again.
[Next Episode]
The Dean is here.
Little San, do you think this profiteer
uncle still remember us?
My master told me to give you this.
Okay, I get it.
Uncle Sword.
Well, I have super red bean bun. Back off.
What’s going on?