♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Now, he’s two times stronger than he was before.
You used poison.
The power differences of 21 levels...
are indeed hard on my body.
What’s your current soul level?
Look.
With nine stories and colours,
Jiubao Amber Pagoda!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 58]
Malicious Attack? Soundless Arrow?
Dad, why did you have
Brother San’s hidden weapons?
Your Brother San made them?
Let me show you how to use hidden weapons.
Let’s go outside.
Rong Rong, how do you plan to show it to us?
Grandpa Sword, why don’t you have a try?
You’re so powerful. I’m sure
you wouldn’t be hurt by them.
I think your Grandpa Bone is stronger.
He should do it.
You coward. I’ll do it.
Do you really think I meant that?
Stay away.
Both of them are Grand Soul Land Masters.
They are at Level 95 and 96 respectively.
But they still act like kids
when they throw their tantrums.
Let me do it for you, little princess.
Little lass, use whatever you have.
I’ll block them off.
If so, Grandpa Sword, you have to be careful.
This is the Soundless Arrow.
That is a feint attack!
Sword Aura!
Godly Zhuge Crossbow!
Aura Sword!
That’s powerful.
Malicious Attack!
Here’s the poisonous weapon.
Sword Aura!
Uncle Sword, you’re so strong!
The hidden weapons are powerful indeed.
Especially the crossbow.
It has a strong impact.
Soul masters under Level 40...
can’t block it if they’re not cautious.
Of course!
We defeated a team of soul masters at Level 40
in the soul arena with it.
Shoe Crossbow, Hidden Knife!
You haven’t done yet?
That’s fast!
One with the sword!
Grandpa Sword, you’re so strong!
You’re strong too.
You forced me to use my Martial Soul.
This hidden weapon is really something.
Yeah. Brother San said
hidden weapons should be used
when the opponents are unaware.
So it can be used to its fullest potential.
Back-tightening Crossbow!
Grandpa Sword, you...
Rong Rong, on your knees!
Feng Zhi, what are you doing?
It’s the old fellow’s fault. He’s too weak.
How can you blame Rong Rong for this?
Grandpa Sword, I’m wrong.
Please punish me.
Rong Rong, be a good girl. Don’t cry.
How is this your fault?
We agreed to test hidden weapons out.
You didn’t do wrong.
And I’m fine now.
Tribe Chief, the hidden weapons
are strong indeed.
If possible, we must ask the maker
to join our tribe.
Rong Rong, regarding this,
don’t tell anyone in our tribe yet.
Tomorrow, I’ll go to Shrek School with you
to meet this Brother San of yours.
Dad, are you not angry at me anymore?
Why would I be angry at you?
Just now, I was too anxious.
The pain inside my body
has disappeared completely.
In the Ice Fire Mouth Spring,
the Octa Dark Frost and Fiery Soft
Apricot did increase my endurance.
[Brother, Oscar is back. I’ll go back first.]
[Eat this sausage when you wake up.]
[I’ll visit you tomorrow morning.]
[From Xiao Wu.]
My Purple Demon Eye is stronger now.
I’ve reached the Surreal level now.
Not only my Purple Demon Eye has improved,
my Xuan Tian Strike has improved too.
If I follow this progress,
I can attain the
highest level in Xuan Tian Strike.
Brother!
The class is so difficult.
I can’t understand them at all.
Look.
It’s Tang San.
What’s going on?
Good job, Tang San!
You defeated a Soul King.
Of course, everyone would notice you.
Look at those girls’ loving eyes.
I’m so jealous.
Uncle Sausage, you’ve revealed yourself. Playboy.
Don’t speak nonsense. I only love Rong Rong.
Two words for you.
Be sincere.
Be sincere?
You can only feel the sincerity from others...
if you treat them sincerely.
Little Ao, you may not notice...
the way Rong Rong looks at you is different.
If you’re sincere enough,
you will earn your rewards.
Tang San, go and have a look!
It’s Tai Long! They’re back!
They still want to fight?
Did his father come again?
Not just his father,
even his grandfather is here!
- What?
At this time?
The Dean and the others
all went to hunt soul beasts for Boss Dai.
Xiao Wu, go and find Teacher Zhao.
Little Ao, let’s go and have a look.
Super Recovery Big Sausage!
Just in case.
Yeah.
Look.
[Soul Land]
Grandpa, I beg you. Please go back.
If you create a mess again, I’ll be expelled.
Shut up.
Who’s Tang San?
I am Tang San.
I’m Tai Tan, the head of Li Tribe.
Did you injure my son and my grandson yesterday?
I did.
Okay.
You managed to injure them,
because they’re weak,
but it doesn’t mean that my tribe is useless.
I won’t bully you.
Let’s make a bet.
What’s the bet?
The pillar is made from reinforced steel.
That incense can pierce through the pillar
form long distance
and without any damage.
This old man is scary.
I won’t use any skills or use my Martial Soul.
You win if you can withstand my soul
pressure until the incense burns out.
And I’ll ask them to kowtow
and apologize to you.
If not, you’ll have to join my tribe.
This is unfair!
If you lose,
they just need to kowtow and apologize to him.
Although it’s a disgrace,
they won’t lose anything.
I should delay this as long as I can.
If Little San loses,
he has to join your tribe and will be restricted.
What kind of bet is this?
What do you propose then?
It’s easy. If you lose,
they have to join Tang San’s tribe.
Oh, you have a tribe too?
Yes. I’m from Tang Clan.
Tang Clan? I didn’t hear of that before.
Maybe it’s a small tribe.
Okay, deal. If I lose,
both my son and my grandson
will join the Tang Clan.
Little San, that’s all I can do for you.
Senior, please.
I heard Tai Long’s grandfather is here.
Come, let’s have a look.
You can do it!
So strong!
He is at a different level from Zhi Lin.
If Zhi Lin’s soul pressure were like river waves,
This old man’s soul pressure is like a flood.
Is he a Great Soul Land Master?
This kid, he actually withstood my first wave.
Is he really at Level 37? If that’s so...
Teacher Zhao, please stop them!
The battle began.
We’ll have to wait until the battle ends.
Why is Little San fighting with him?
You know him? He’s Tai Long’s grandfather.
Of course, I do.
In the past, I hit his disciples accidentally.
And he hunted me down.
That’s why I joined Frander to set up Shrek School.
He’s stronger than you?
Yeah. That old man is over Level 80.
I can face the other Great Soul Land Master.
But he’s all about strength.
Regarding his strength,
he’s stronger than most
Grand Soul Land Masters.
Eight Spider Bone!
Is that a soul bone?
It’s an attached soul bone!
This kid is indeed awesome. Since it came to this...
You mustn’t let people know that
you are born with two Martial souls.
Am I losing? Will I lose here?
[Next Episode]
Do you admit your defeat?
Remember to keep calm...
no matter what they are going to say.
who exactly is my father?
What exactly happened?
Please tell me!
What happened to you?
You must be wary of Ning Feng Zhi.
Ning Feng Zhi is ambitious.
Kid, you’re a good businessman.
Are you willing to sell us the method
of making hidden weapons?