♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this
when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Is your father Tang Hao?
How did you know that?
I’m Tai Tan. Greetings, Young Master.
Now that you’ve appeared,
the Li Tribe
will die for you.
We’ll die for you, Young Master!
I’m interested in your hidden weapons.
We’ve seen Rong Rong’s hidden weapons.
I want a set just like hers.
I want 500 sets. I’ll give 10,000
gold soul coins for every set.
I’m only in charge of the final step.
For the initial steps,
Uncle Ning, you need to think of something.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 60]
Isn’t it too easy to gain 50,000 gold soul coins?
If Uncle Ning finds the price unreasonable,
you can lower the price. I have no objections.
No need for that. Although I’m not a great man,
our Qiber Amber Tribe will keep our promise.
[50,000 gold soul coins]
If there’s nothing else, I’ll leave now.
Rong Rong, you can follow Little San back.
Okay.
Feng Zhi, what do you think?
Is he really the son of Tang Hao?
I’m sure of it.
I didn’t expect Tang Hao
to have an outstanding son
after he left the Hao Tian Tribe.
The Hao Tian Tribe is higher in statue
than our Qibao Amber Tribe.
If he continues to grow,
he’ll be a threat to us.
Uncle Bone, please don’t say that again.
Although the Hao Tian Tribe
is higher in statue than our tribe,
the Upper Three are friendly with each other.
We have no reason to sabotage his tribe.
But if this kid becomes a Grand Soul Land Master,
our Qibao Amber Tribe
can never make a comeback.
Compared with the condition in Soul Land,
the feuds of the tribes are nothing.
Tribe chief, are you saying that...
When I was young,
many soul masters were fighting
each other to be the very best.
But now,
this kind of fighting almost disappeared.
And the Soul Land is tranquil.
Are you saying...
Although I’ve only got some clues,
these clues show that
Soul Land will experience a massive change soon.
For that, the Seven Major Tribes must be reunited.
Do you guys want to ask me something?
Nothing.
You can handle your own affairs.
I only know that you’re Little San
from the Shrek Seven Devils.
I still don’t understand what’s happening.
I don’t know what to ask.
You never asked us about our background before.
Everyone has their own privacy.
I won’t ask anything.
We’re only concerned about your well-being.
We’re relieved now that you’ve returned safely.
Xiao Wu,
are you saying that
my father would hurt Brother San?
Here’s a secret.
My father bought 500 sets of
hidden weapons from Brother San just now.
He paid him 5 million gold soul coins on the spot.
- What?
What are you guys trying to do?
What are we trying to do?
We’re robbing you
of course!
Rong Rong, you returned earlier than I expected.
I was worried that you couldn’t return.
I said I would return, didn’t I?
Why did you think I wouldn’t come back?
It’s because...
What’s wrong? Tell me.
Let me give you two words.
Be sincere.
Rong Rong, can you give me your answer?
Answer?
You have a feeling for me, am I right?
You!
If you do, it means that I have a chance.
I will work hard!
I will work hard to gain your father’s permission!
Rong Rong? Why are you here?
Dad, are you leaving?
I still have many things to handle.
You must listen to your teachers.
And train hard.
Teacher Zhao, I’ll leave her to you.
If the school needs any help,
our Qibao Amber Tribe will help you gladly.
Tribe Chief Ning, don’t worry.
We will take good care of Rong Rong.
Farewell. I’ll stop here.
Rong Rong, why is your face so red?
Are you sick?
It’s nothing. I’m fine.
Dad, can’t you stay longer?
Silly girl.
I’m proud of your results.
Not only did you grow stronger,
you grew up as a person too.
You should talk to your Brother San more often.
You can learn many things from him.
Okay.
No. I need to clarify things with Oscar.
He must know about the rules
of the Qibao Amber Tribe at least.
If I tell him about the rules now,
will he give up?
But if I don’t tell him now, he’ll...
Never mind. I’ll wait until the
Advanced Soul Masters’ meeting is over.
I’ll tell him then.
No. No. No.
[Soul Land]
Boss Dai!
Little San, thank you.
Boss Dai,
I thought you would hug Zhu Qing first.
Little Ao, are you asking for a beating?
I hugged Little San because he helped me.
After I got my soul ring,
I felt the improvement of my soul power.
Now, I’m are Level 43.
It’s all because of the
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum.
Everyone must work hard now.
We mustn’t let Little San’s treasures go to waste.
Before the competition starts,
you all must get to Level 40 at least.
We only have one goal.
We must be the champion!
Yeah! Champion!
Little San.
Follow me.
Grandmaster is trying to persuade Little San.
I’m a bit worried.
I’ll follow him.
Okay.
Master, you knew about my background?
I knew that.
I knew that a long time ago.
What?
You don’t need to be surprised.
When you first came to Nuoding School,
I accepted you as my disciple.
Because I saw your potential
of the Twin Martial Soul.
But I can’t confirm that your other
Martial Soul was the Hao Tian Hammer.
Until one day, your father came to see me.
And he gave me this.
That’s why, I hope I can leave Little San to you.
He’s my son.
Is this the badge of the highest rank
in Martial Soul Hall?
Only then, I knew who your father was.
He’s famous in Soul Land.
He’s my idol too.
He’s Tang Hao, the youngest Grand Soul Land Master.
Hao Tian as his title.
Grand Hao Tian Master?
I don’t know him well.
He just asked me to take care of you.
There are six icons on this badge.
There are two parts.
The first part contains the three
Grand Soul Land Masters in the Martial Hall.
For the second part,
it contains the three Grand Soul
Land Masters of the Seven Major Tribes.
The sword on the badge
represents Master Luo Chen Xin
from the Qibao Amber Tribe.
The dragon
represents the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
from my tribe.
The hammer represents the
Hao Tian Hammer from the Hao Tian Tribe.
The Hao Tian Tribe had two
Grand Soul Land Masters.
Tang Xiao and Tang Hao, the two brothers.
They were the strongest in Soul Land once.
When your father received the title,
he was only 44 years old.
According to rumors,
he got to Level 90 all by himself.
And he defeated two Grand Soul
Land Masters from the Martial Hall.
They’re represented by the chrysanthemum
and the human figure on the badge.
Master Ju and Master Gui.
Why did my father fight with the two of them?
I think this is a secret between the
Hao Tian Tribe and the Martial Hall.
However,
why didn’t Dad come to see me?
Little San, if you look at this from another perspective,
perhaps your father didn’t leave you at all.
Why?
I heard this from Frander.
When you first came to the school,
Zhao Wu Ji was itchy to fight.
He tested you and your gang personally.
But you used your hidden weapons to defeat him.
You were hurt too, right?
Did you discover
what happened to Zhao Wu Ji after that?
Did you forget that
Zhao Wu Ji was covered in bruises the other day?
Frander said
a man with a black attire came that night.
And he beat Zhao Wu Ji up.
That person didn’t even release his Martial Soul.
That person was your father.
Are you saying that my father
came to see me before?
If I’m not mistaken,
I think he didn’t see you because
he’s afraid it’ll affect your training.
The other reason is
he’s afraid that he can’t bear to leave you
once he meets you.
I think,
he must have something to do.
Dad actually did the same thing to protect me.
I’m telling you all these things because
I want you to understand...
since you want to be a soul master,
you mustn’t stop.
Your father needs your help too.
You must prove to your father that
you’re capable enough to help him
with your achievements.
Dad, are you really looking after me
in the shadows?
Okay then. I will not disappoint you.
Master, I have two more questions.
Tell me.
For the first question,
do you know who’s my mother?
Your mother’s identity is mysterious.
I’m afraid only a few people
in Soul Land know about her.
Judging from the Blue Silver Plant,
it seems that she does not
belong to any of the major tribes.
Blue Silver Plant is a useless Martial Soul.
But your Blue Silver Plant
is different from others.
Master, for the second question,
Why didn’t you two allow me
to use Hao Tian Hammer?
[Next Episode]
Even after knowing all these facts,
I hope you can keep a normal attitude.
You have six months left.
Actually, I would rather be a blacksmith’s son.
This identity to me is meaningless.
But Xiao Wu didn’t consume
the Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
I’m afraid that...
Brother, don’t you believe in my strength?
I didn’t mean that.
Let’s fight then.
My mother gave it to me.
Mom, this comb is pretty!