♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Soul Land]
[Episode 27]
Ah Yin, here is the place we bade farewell.
Martial Soul Hall.
Be careful.
Your doom is due.
Tang Hao, you can’t escape.
His soul ring can’t be seen, only the shadow is here.
What a Grand Soul Land Master.
Ah Yin.
No.
The Strike of Ling Tian.
Bright light can stop him for a while. Let’s go.
Go? Where are you going to?
Oh, no.
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum.
Another Grand Soul Land Master.
Wilted chrysanthemum brings pain.
Falling flowers bring misery.
Shield of Hao Tian.
Sixth soul skill, Clouds of Golden Pistil.
Hang in there, Ah Yin.
I’ll surely take you and the child
out of this valley.
Hao.
I’m here.
Thank you.
Finally.
Hao.
Almighty Pope.
Challenging is the soul hammer,
lofty is Hao Tian Tribe.
The heir of the world-best tribe
is going against God’s will.
This will be a disaster.
Going against God’s will?
Am I going against God’s will?
Or are you assuming yourself as God?
How dare you?
Three Grand Soul Land Masters.
Martial Soul Hall.
You only have 8 soul rings.
Why ask destruction to yourself?
Tang Hao, Martial Soul Hall doesn’t want
to be enemy of Hao Tian Tribe.
Give her to me. I’ll let you live.
If you want to hurt her,
step over my corpse first.
What a stubborn one.
The Sword of Angel Light.
Hammer of Hao Tian.
Skill of Random Hammering.
Unexpectedly, Skill of Random Hammering
is so powerful.
You’re indeed a rare genius of Hao Tian Tribe.
Bipolar Static Field.
I can’t move.
Combination of Martial Soul.
No one can stop Martial Soul Hall
from getting what it wants.
The Holy Sword of Angel.
This is the end, Tang Hao.
Your anger is the stepping stone to my peak.
Despicable.
Blue Plant doesn’t belong anywhere.
Fortunately, it was cared for
by the east wind during a hard time.
Ah Yin.
Hao, I have no regret loving you.
Always remember, this is our child.
No, Ah Yin. No.
Ah Yin.
No.
I know,
I can never survive in Martial Soul Hall.
That’s my fate. I can’t complain.
But before submitting myself to fate,
I want to have a deal with you.
You want to offer a sacrifice?
Do you know you’ll be destructed?
Ah Yin, no. Go with them.
Don’t offer a sacrifice.
Stop her. Take action, everyone.
Farewell, my love.
No.
[Soul Land]
Hao, you have to live on for him.
I’ve given him a name.
[San]
Little San might can’t withstand
this Human Faced Demon Spider.
Their levels are too different. It’s dangerous.
Little San has faced a situation of life and death.
Xiao Wu.
Brother.
It was just a dream.
Ah Yin, I’ve seen our son.
He has grown up. He looks more and more like you.
The girl called Xiao Wu is cute as well.
If you see her, you might like her too.
I hope they can live well. Not like us.
Don’t worry.
As long as I’m around, no one can harm them.
It’s enough to have our tragedy once.
Little San has met a trustworthy companion.
He also has a teacher who’s more
responsible and better to care for him.
I can do what I want to and must do without worry.
I have to pay back what I owed the tribe.
I also have to ask back
what Martial Soul Hall owed us.
I like this place a lot.
I wanted to stay here with you forever.
But I think it’s not possible now.
Don’t stop me, Ah Yin.
I promise you, I’ll be back soon.
To be able to meet you and have Little San with you
are the biggest happiness in my life.
Martial Soul Hall, I’m back.
[Next Episode]
Tang San
is a rare talent.
Yi Ran, what do you think of Tang San?
Grandpa, are you pairing us together?
If Little San carries on,
he may be in danger.
Do you think
Little San’s Martial Soul is only Blue Silver Plant?