♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
The battle has ended. San Woo won!
Stop.
Don’t be fooled by his appearance.
Kuang Xi and his teammates of Frenzy Battle Team
are all above Level 35.
Every time they take action,
their opponents will either die or get hurt.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
next will be our fourth round group battle today,
which is also the most awaited last match.
At this critical moment...
[Soul Land]
[Episode 37]
Three, two, one.
The fourth round of Group Soul Battle, begins!
Friends, initiate your martial souls.
Martial Soul Shield Body.
Kuang Xi’s Martial Soul is a rhino
with great strength.
He’s a typical soul master of Storm Attack Branch.
Boss Dai can handle him.
These two are probably
soul masters of Keen Attack Branch.
Xiao Wu and Zhu Qing can handle them.
These two seem fast, we need to be careful.
Surprisingly, the only one
with a top-level soul ring
is her!
Lucky Disc Defensive Light Blossom.
Lucky Disc Attack Halo Blossom.
Frenzy Battle Team doesn’t
have a soul master of Food Branch.
This means that their strategy is to
end the battle as quick as possible.
They’re confident with
the soul power amplification of
their soul master of Assisting Branch.
You need to pay attention to
this Lucky Disc soul master.
Frenzy Battle Team’s previous battles,
he had played an important role.
Come on.
Frenzy Battle Team.
Such a sturdy net.
Fatty, in the air. Phoenix Firing Line.
First soul skill, Phoenix Firing Line.
Qibao famously said...
At this small difference of level,
Qibao Amber Pagoda’s amplification effect
is far greater than other Martial Souls.
It’s the most powerful Martial Soul
of Assisting Branch.
What? Gosh, assisting position is vacant.
Rong Rong and Oscar are being attacked.
They target them since the beginning.
Attacking the weakest soul masters of
Assisting Branch and Food Branch at the beginning
to eliminate all uncertain factors,
is the ultimate law of battle.
Speaking of the ultimate law of battle,
that means we can use this same factor
to create a trap.
Second soul skill,
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Third soul skill, Constraint of Spider Web.
Twin Monkey retreats, protect
Lucky Disc. Twin Sheep withstand it.
Blue Silver Plant.
Let’s break this spider web first.
Your opponent is me.
In terms of poison,
my spider poison has never met an enemy.
Unbelievable, Shrek Seven Devils
are leading the battle.
Is Frenzy Battle Team’s
seven-victory record going to an end?
Fatty.
Oh, attack the soul master of Assisting Branch.
Who is this Lucky Disc?
Little San, Zhu Qing.
If there’s a chance,
eliminate this Lucky Disc at once.
We must not let him use that skill.
Third soul skill, Fanatic.
Oh, no.
It’s here!
The key to Frenzy Battle Team’s
countless table-turning-success,
Fanatic.
- Release.
- Can Shrek Seven Devils
endure this counterattack
from Frenzy Battle Team?
Second soul skill, Trample.
Boss Dai!
Their power has amplified greatly.
Their speed has elevated immensely too.
Gather.
Admit your defeat.
In the state of Fanatic, we don’t feel pain.
Every attribute increases by fifteen percent.
Admit defeat? In your dreams.
If there is no Qibao Amber soul master,
do you think I’ll waste my time talking?
If that so, don’t blame us for being cruel.
Airborne.
They’re able to fly too?
Master is right.
We must take down Lucky Disc
soul master since the start.
We’ve misjudged.
You thought we can’t perform
the long-distance attack?
Everyone, disperse.
Smart.
Little San, what shall we do now?
Mushroom Sausage is only valid for a minute.
Moreover, Little Ao can only fly for half a minute.
Purple Demon Eye.
Ghostly Trace.
Nice.
This degree is too mere to hurt us.
Try this then.
Dangerous!
Rong Rong.
[Soul Land]
Gather.
Fatty.
If only one or two of them can fly,
that means they have an airborne soul master.
But seven of them to fly at once,
means that they use a soul master’s soul skill
of Assisting Branch or Food Branch.
This soul skill can’t last long.
Their abilities have amplified greatly,
probably due to the soul master’s
millennium soul skill of Assisting Branch.
But you see, except for the female soul master,
everyone has lost their mind.
According to Master’s research,
their Fanatic state won’t last long.
After the Fanatic state ends,
they’ll undergo negative feedback.
We can’t handle them in the current state.
Little Ao, how many Mushroom Sausage can you make?
I don’t have much soul power left,
I can make one at most.
You can’t hold on.
Later, after your flying ability ends,
Go down immediately.
I’ll do it, Little San.
No, I should do this.
I still have my trump card.
Even if their Fanatic state
can last longer than I thought,
I can still leave the battle site.
Since I’m leading this battle,
you should listen to me.
Little San is betting,
he’s betting that Oscar’s Mushroom Sausage
can last longer than Fanatic.
Frenzy Battle Team is betting too.
But what if when we land,
they’re still in this state?
We can only bet.
We’re indeed hoping for a victory.
But everyone’s safety is more important.
Their flying ability has ended.
If they land outside the ring, they will lose.
Flying Mushroom Sausage.
I’m sorry, I’ll go down first.
Only one left, we’re going to win for sure.
The flying time has ended.
You have no chance to win.
In a group battle, a defeat means
every team member is taken down.
Now, Shrek Seven Devils have one member left.
One against six, does he hold a chance?
Aren’t you leaving?
Although I’m the only one left,
yet to win or to lose is uncertain.
Their Fanatic state has ended.
One against six, you don’t stand a chance.
In Frenzy Battle Team,
you’re the only one to fight, right?
The negative feedback from Fanatic
has made your teammates
lost their fighting abilities.
Shrek Seven Devils are going to turn the table.
Turn the table? You?
After the Fanatic state,
their abilities have become weaker.
I still stand a chance.
Even with my human body,
I can easily crush you into bits.
Ghostly Trace.
It’s time.
I just need to sweep you off the ring.
I’m being pulled in, how is this possible?
Why?
My third soul ring is
Millennium Human Faced Demon Spider.
Human Faced Demon Spider?
This battle has ended.
Shrek Seven Devils won!
Can you tell me your name?
One of Shrek Seven Devils,
Thousand Hands Asura.
Brother, you’re so cool!
Xiao Wu, get down.
Today, we have a great victory.
We must have a good meal.
Let’s go. Meal on me.
Brother, how generous you are!
Let’s go.
Let’s go, catch up.
[Next Episode]
To be honest,
three days ago, a soul master team came
and caused a big loss to the Soul Arena.
This Silver Soul Battle Team
is like Shrek Seven Devils,
they’re a team with top-level soul rings.
Sir,
I hereby invite Shrek Seven Devils
to join the group battle
at the Central Soul Arena.
Xiao Gang,
you shouldn’t promise them this quick.
You must not admit defeat until the last moment.
[Participant Information]
Do you have any problem?
The battle starts now.