♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Such Mutated Martial Soul
has a keen attack characteristic
on top of the storm attack foundation.
Third soul skill, Gale Wings.
Brother, you must be careful.
I can’t await death without doing anything.
Brother.
No.
Random Air Hammer Skill.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 90]
Work hard. Must win.
It seems
15 teams of Tian Dou Empire
who are qualified for the final round
are joining the troop gradually.
Little San, what are you thinking about?
I’m thinking that
to us, they are not threats.
The real threat will be the chosen team
from Martial Soul Hall.
Only by defeating them,
we can be the final champion.
Indeed. Challenging them
is going to be the biggest trial
for Shrek Seven Devils.
Oh, right, Dean.
How is the competition venue, Martial Soul City?
Martial Soul City almost belongs
to Martial Soul Hall.
It’s located at the border
of the two empires.
However, neither empires have its ownership.
Most importantly,
one of the two noblest symbols
of Martial Soul Hall,
the Sacred Temple
is located in Martial Soul City.
It seems there are a lot of things
to eat and to explore.
After the tournament,
we must have fun in Martial Soul City.
Martial Soul City.
However, the venue for the final round was
not supposed to be in Martial Soul City.
For reasons unknown,
Martial Soul Hall made a sudden decision
of having the final round in Martial Soul City.
Sudden decision?
Please hold on.
I would like to go to Chi Huo School.
Please allow me.
Brothers of Chi Huo School, may I come in?
Brother Xiao Tian, what’s the matter?
Nothing. Is Sister Huo Wu here?
I’m here to apologize.
For what?
You didn’t do anything wrong.
Sister Huo Wu, sorry.
I couldn’t fulfill your request.
I was defeated by Tang San.
Stop it. You’re not wrong.
Since he’s the descendant of Hao Tian Tribe,
everything is reasonable.
It’s okay that you lost.
Right now, I just want to see
how he defeat other opponents
in the final round,
and which place he will get.
SIster Huo Wu, regarding us...
Get into the cart.
There are so many crows in this lousy place.
Why isn’t there anything else?
Let’s get back into the cart.
Boss Dai, why are you keep staring
at the cavalries?
Do you want to be a warrior too?
War soul masters have always
been the best warriors.
There’s nothing to be envious about.
I was just observing them.
Royal Cavalry Troop is indeed
the trump card of Tian Dou Empire.
Besides being disciplined,
they’re very well-trained.
What’s so good about them?
Isn’t that natural for cavalries?
Boss Dai, why don’t we get out
and have a look in the troop?
Brat, what a weird idea do you have?
Boss Dai isn’t the same when Zhu Qing is around.
Shut up.
Everyone, keep quiet.
Keep quiet. Something is happening.
Commander, everything is normal.
Why are there maple leaves here?
Stop.
Everyone, be alert.
What’s going on?
What’s happening?
There’s nothing to be worried about.
There are so many Tian Dou
Royal Cavalries. They can handle it.
Not to mention the leading teachers
of every school.
It may not be.
Enemy attack!
Formation.
The cart is an obvious target. Let’s get off.
[Soul Land]
Boss Dai, you’re indeed right.
They’re really well-trained.
Who dares to attack us sneakingly?
Er Long, hold on.
Boss Fu, why are you stopping me?
These stupid thieves.
Let me just beat them up.
It isn’t that simple.
Right now, the most important thing
is to protect the children.
It seems the Cavalry Troop is starting
to be threatened.
Children, activate your Martial Souls.
How many more rocks are there?
Hide if you can. Reserve your soul power.
But don’t run away. Try to stay together.
Besides trying to deplete our soul power,
they are using the rocks to separate the schools.
Hong Jun.
Qin Ming.
Thank you, Senior. Are you okay?
I’m fine.
Super Recovery Big Sausage.
Be extra careful.
It seems there are quite some prowlers.
That’s not good.
Assembly of Power.
Attack.
That’s not good.
That’s extravagant of them to send so many people.
I’m not afraid.
It’s indeed so.
There are so many of them.
They’re obviously prepared.
Four versus one.
A pack strategy. I’m still not afraid.
Why don’t most of them
activate their Martial Souls?
In order to hide their true identities.
That’s good.
Spare your soul power. Smash the enemies.
Er Long, remember to take care of Qin Ming.
Don’t worry, Boss Fu.
That’s not good.
Fourth soul skill, Blade of Eagle Claws.
Fifth soul skill, Abyss of Tiger Roar.
Fire Dragon Strike.
Fifth soul skill, Carapace Shield.
Third soul skill,
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Who told you to not activate your Martial Souls?
Second soul skill, Nether Claws.
Don’t look down upon soul masters of Food Branch.
Third soul skill, Flying Phoenix.
Nine layers, nine colours. Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
Soul masters of Controlling Branch are
never afraid of group fights.
First soul skill, Intertwine.
Godly Zhuge Crossbow, wind up.
Release.
Don’t move. Defend yourself.
Purple Demon Eye. Xuan Yu Hand.
Little San is demonstrating his power in all angles.
He is oppressing. He’s a Great Soul Land Master.
[Next Episode]
Handle these children to me.
Sadly,
you have to die young here.
Guys, let’s fight or die trying.
Let’s see how I destroy you.
Eagle Owl’s True Form.
The kids are in danger.
Let’s get rid of the opponents soon
and help the kids!
Why?
Why wasn’t me the one who got
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet?