♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this
when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Your father and I
want to create a supreme being with
Decade Millennium Rings.
After the contest,
you guys can graduate from school.
Graduate?
That’s the real test.
Emergency! Everyone, be careful!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 62]
Emergency! Everyone, be careful!
You make me angry!
Here’s a suitable beast.
Little San, this soul beast is 4,000 years old at least.
How dare you interrupt me!
I’ll kill you!
This is the King of the Land, Bloodthrist.
Its element is fire.
It’s around 4,000 years old.
It’s suitable for us.
Seventh soul skill, Dragon Form!
It’s just a Millennium Soul Beast.
Teacher Er Long needn’t release
her seventh soul skill at all.
And she’s the one fighting now.
Master, Teacher Er Long, she...
God, why are you punishing me like this?
Why?
Xiao Gang, you are here,
but I still feel distant from you.
Er Long.
Is it that hard being together with me?
Er Long, let go of me first.
This is one of its strongest technique,
Lava Strike!
The scariest part is the flickering aura
before its attack.
It can confuse its enemies.
The next moment,
it’ll unleash a heat ray that’s
as hot as lava to kill its enemies.
She’s undamaged?
Be careful of the tail!
How dare you interrupt me?
I will make you regret your actions!
Poor creature.
Squat! Everyone, squat!
I’m the Evil Phoenix...
I always thought Tigress is the fiercest being.
Now, I know that the female dragon
is the fiercest being.
Dai Mu Bai, who are you
referring to as the tigress?
Of course Zhu Qing...
No! Zhu Qing! I’m not talking about you!
I can explain myself!
I’ve decided!
So black!
From now on, Teacher Er Long will be my idol!
My goddess has returned!
Fatty, it’s yours.
It’s mine?
Your element is fire too. It’s suitable for you.
Frander, I can’t believe this.
I didn’t believe you when you say
your sister has a bad temper.
But, I think you’re right.
I’ve decided. I’ll keep watch next.
I will stand guard. No objections.
Fatty is absorbing the soul rings.
As a teacher, I need to guard him.
Xiao Gang, go to sleep now.
Wu Ji and I will stay here.
Teacher Er Long is my idol.
No wonder she’s known as the
Killing Point of the Golden Iron Triangle.
I think you guys don’t need
to keep watch anymore.
Let’s go to sleep.
I’ll skip that. I don’t want to
squeeze with you guys.
I’ll stay outside and accompany the teachers.
Fine.
[Soul Land]
Dean Frander, is Fatty not finished yet?
He finished absorbing the soul rings.
I wanted him to continue his training.
Looks like he acquired a great skill
for his fourth soul ring.
Who’s playing with fireworks
so early in the morning?
Fatty!
Everyone, prepare yourself.
We will move out after breakfast.
Fatty and I have acquired our fourth soul ring.
Did you guys think about your next soul ring yet?
But the soul ring that Fatty absorbed yesterday,
Grandmaster said that is the best soul ring for him.
Fatty, how do you feel now?
How’s your fourth soul ring?
It’s easy. I absorbed it within half an hour.
This is strange.
Was the King of the Land
giving up its life because of Teacher Er Long?
And it thought I can end it suffering?
So it allowed me to absorb that quickly?
That is possible.
Master did some research on this.
There are two scenarios where
it’s the best for soul masters to
absorb soul beasts after their death.
First, the soul beast must be filled with grudges.
Second, the soul beast must die willingly.
Not only can you absorb
their soul ring completely,
their age will not restrict us
from absorbing them.
And they will most probably drop a soul bone.
Even if we’re only at Level 40,
if a Decade Millennium Soul Beast
is willing to let us kill it,
won’t we suffer any backlashes?
Is that great?
Not at all. Do you think it’s easy?
Do you think they would die for you,
and give you their soul rings?
That is the ideal scenario.
It’s quite impossible.
Nothing is impossible.
Under the right circumstances,
miracles will happen.
So,
that means I did not fulfill
both of the conditions then.
If the King of the Land was killed by Teacher Er Long,
it would be the first scenario.
It’s hard to fulfill the other scenario too.
If you want a soul beast
to have grudges against you,
you need to hunt them yourself.
You can’t ask others to hunt them for you.
It’ll split up their grudges.
But normally,
soul beasts that a soul master wants to hunt
are usually stronger than the soul master.
It’s hard for us to beat them flawlessly.
No wonder it’s hard to find a soul bone.
These conditions are too extreme.
By the way, Fatty, what’s your fourth soul skill?
I’ll show it to you when I have the chance.
I think it’s great.
But the area of effect is small.
And I can’t lock my target
before unleashing the skill.
I made these Cure Pills myself.
Miasmas are poisonous.
You will be safe from the miasma
if you consume them.
It’ll boost your energy too.
Everyone, be careful.
Our vision is obscured.
Stay closer to each other.
Go to the back. Let’s swap.
The mist is poisonous!
This is not miasma.
Little Ao, Detoxifying Small Sausage!
Everyone, stay in this field.
I’m using the Fragrant Silk Woven Flower.
Any poison
is useless in its field.
Everyone, stay in this field for now.
Be careful! The soul beast is coming!
I think it created the thick mist.
We’re surrounded.
Little San, can you see the soul beast from here?
I’ll try. Purple Demon Eye.
Master, it’s the Pink Lady.
There are more than a thousand of them.
What? More than a thousand?
How is that possible?
What’s a Pink Lady?
Pink Lady is a scorpion-like soul beast.
They stay together in groups.
They rarely attack humans.
Because their bodies are
pinkish and transparent,
they are known as Pink Lady.
A group of Pink Lady consists
of around 100 of them.
The strongest one leads the group.
Pink Madam is the mutation of Pink Lady.
It has consumed at least 100 men.
I’m sure there’s a Pink Madam in this group.
Pink Madam?
[Next Episode]
Why are they so hostile towards us?
Er Long! Come back!
Frander, do you see the Fatty’s weaknesses now?
Brother San, assist me!
Oscar, hurry!
When are you going to allow
Little San to train his second Martial Soul?
You want to see her?
Aren’t you afraid Er Long would get angry?
Actually, I have an idea.
But it’s quite risky.
Everyone, be careful.
It’s coming.