♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] Brother!
Why are they attacking Little San suddenly?
Dai Wei Si, your target is here.
You’re rather brave.
But you’re asking for death.
Next, who will be the key to breaking the ice?
White Tiger of Netherworld has grown wings?
It seems the victory and defeat
can obviously be told.
We haven’t surrendered.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 99]
Second soul skill, Parasite.
First soul skill, Arched Body.
Judge,
we surrender.
It’s indeed a surprising and exciting match.
I announce
Shrek School won.
At the point of Blue Silver Spike Formation,
the seeds of Blue Silver Plant
have been placed on her.
No wonder Master San didn’t activate Parasite.
Well done.
In this match, Captain and Zhu Qing
have won their pride.
At the last part, when Mu Bai fought the opponent,
he has shown mercy.
If he would have attacked his chest,
the two of them would have died.
Shrek has once again defeated a stronger team.
That isn’t easy.
The other party is the strongest team
of Xing Luo Empire after all.
Shrek only made use of
their opponent’s underestimation.
to win the match.
In the next match with Martial Soul Hall School,
could we...
Tang San.
I didn’t expect you to become so strong.
You aren’t too bad.
I could tell
you’ve improved by leaps and bounds.
I planned to fight you well in this tournament.
It seems there’s no chance now.
Tomorrow,
watch our match with Martial Soul Hall School.
Even if we lose,
we’ll try our best to make them
show their actual strength.
Is Martial Soul Hall School
really that strong?
Don’t forget to revenge us.
Yu Tian Heng.
Don’t make me look down upon you.
How would you know it’s impossible
before you try?
If you lose your confidence,
then you’re unworthy to be my opponent.
Wait and see.
Your performance today was very good.
I’m very proud of you.
Dean,
the medical staff of the tournament informed us,
that they have treated Little Ao and Hong Jun.
They’re mentally injured.
They’ll recover
after treatment and night sleep.
That’s good.
This match wasn’t easy for you.
You don’t have any match in the next two days.
You may relax a little tonight.
Who is that?
It’s me.
Boss Dai,
why don’t you rest to recover your soul power?
Why are you here?
To chat with you.
OK. Come in.
Little San,
thank you for today.
You should
thank everyone.
Today’s victory
is the result of our hard work.
Not to mention that brothers
needn’t thank each other.
You knew about it, right?
Except the imperial family,
I can’t think of
any family fight would
develop to such intensive extent.
Even brothers are trying to kill each other.
What do you think? Your Highness.
You have guessed it right.
That’s right.
I’m the third prince of Xing Luo Empire.
Dai Wei Si who I defeated today
is my eldest brother.
Is there only victory or death
between you and your brother?
Zhu Qing exaggerated it a little.
If I lost,
perhaps, I wouldn’t die.
But my soul power will be scrapped,
I’ll be exiled and imprisoned for life.
That’s just like death.
Why is the imperial battle so cruel?
Little San,
look at this grand Martial Soul City.
This side of Martial Soul City
that you see now is Tian Dou Empire.
[Martial Soul City]
The other side
is Xing Luo Empire.
[Tian Dou Empire vs. Xing Luo Empire]
But what you don’t know is,
if Martial Soul Hall
hasn’t come in the way,
this world
would have belonged to us.
In term of national power and military power,
Xing Luo Empire is much better
than Tian Dou Empire.
The main reason for that is
the special competition of the imperial family.
This method may be cruel,
but the emperors who grew up like this are
all remarkable.
Tian Dou Empire is no match to that.
Indeed.
The only advantage of Tian Dou Empire
is the Upper Three in it.
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe
and Hao Tian Tribe
are never involved in the politics battle,
but Qibao Amber Tribe always
supports Tian Dou Empire.
[Soul Land]
Only until recent years,
the development of Tian Dou Empire has sped up.
The internal of Xing Luo Empire
is also facing some problems.
That’s when the strengths
of both empires start to be balanced.
That’s what Martial Soul Hall desires.
You don’t understand politics,
but you’re very keen.
Indeed. If Xing Luo Empire
defeats Tian Dou Empire,
both empires will be combined to a strong empire.
Then Martial Soul Hall can no longer exist.
After all,
no imperial power would allow
such a powerful organization to exist.
Hence, Martial Soul Hall has
always been balancing both sides.
Turns out there’s such complicated relation.
Although Martial Soul Hall is powerful,
they’re not strong enough to dominate Soul Land.
So they’re balancing both empires secretly for now.
Where are they? That way.
Little San,
you’re in great danger.
As you know,
Martial Soul Hall will not let you go easily.
Chief Ning may protect you for now,
but he can’t follow you forever.
What you mean is...
After the tournament,
Zhu Qing and I will return to Xing Luo Empire.
You and Xiao Wu
should come with us.
I’m officially qualified to fight
for the throne with my eldest brother.
In Xing Luo Empire,
the imperial family is stronger
than that of Tian Dou Empire.
Martial Soul Hall wouldn’t dare to come close.
Boss Dai, I appreciate that.
But regarding this,
I must listen to Master’s suggestion.
Soul masters must train continuously.
If I go to Xing Luo,
I’m afraid...
In my territory,
no matter what kind
of training environment you need,
[Xing Lou Empire]
I can provide it to you.
We’ll work together.
If I succeed the throne,
you’ll be my chief commander,
imperial military adviser.
Xue Qing He has been trying to recruit you.
[Tian Dou Empire]
But the imperial power
of Tian Dou Empire is too dispersed.
When I’m at the throne,
I’ll be the only one
deciding for Xing Luo.
Boss Dai, I understand what you mean.
If I really have to choose a side to depend on,
your side will always be my first choice.
If you have trouble in the future and you need me,
just one word,
no matter how far away I am,
I’ll be there for you.
Alright.
Let’s swear.
After a while,
the final round of Continental
Soul Master Elite Tournament
will be held here.
Yes.
Sadly, non-participants aren’t allowed to watch.
I heard that in today’s match,
three from Martial Soul Hall,
who got Badge of Purple Record, will show up.
There are always talented young people.
Just like the tournament we joined
when we were young.
There were also many elites.
- I wonder who would be rising in this tournament.
- Thank you. Thank you.
In the future,
they will be the leaders
of soul masters in Soul Land.
So exciting.
Today, two out of three seeded teams,
Tian Dou Imperial School
and Martial Soul Hall School,
will fight to tell who’s better.
When two heroes fight, who will be the better one?
Let’s invite both the teams.
Martial Soul Hall School surely wins!
- Have a look.
- So cool.
The three from Martial Soul Hall
who got Badge of Purple Record are here.
Martial Soul Hall School
will surely win this round.
In their previous match,
they won easily
without having these three fights.
That’s right.
As long as my goddess, Hu Liena, is around,
they’ll always win.
Pay attention to these three.
The overwhelming imposing manner
and confidence of these three
are rare to be seen.
Only those who had countless victories,
defeated countless opponents,
would have such a psychological advantage.
This is the most-cheered match of the final round.
The exciting moment is coming again.
Both parties, please be ready.
Martial Soul Hall School has
3 Soul Kings who are beyond Level 50.
They’re the participants
at the highest level in this tournament.
You must have heard about these three Soul Kings.
They’re assigned with the five best soul rings.
These three are hailed as
the three geniuses of the Golden Generation.
After activating her Martial Soul,
Hu Liena became beautiful.
Hu Liena is Xie Yue’s younger sister.
They inherited each of their parents’
surnames and Martial Souls respectively.
Since it’s Fox Martial Soul,
does she have Charm Skill like Xiao Wu’s?
That’s right.
She has a very strong Charm Skill.
Compared with Xiao Wu’s Charm,
her Charm has a very different side.
Two Soul Sects of Storm Attack Branch,
who are achieving the level of Soul King.
The last Assisting Branch member
from Martial Soul Hall School,
has the best assisting tool,
Golden Scepter, as Martial Soul.
The powerful scepter is domineering.
The formation
of Martial Soul Hall School is simple.
Xie Yue, as the captain, is leading.
It has highlighted their strong will to win.
Next, let’s look at the info
of Tian Dou Imperial School.
The captain, Yu Tian Heng.
As a member of
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe,
He is at Level 43.
That’s not a bad level.
But compared with Martial Soul Hall School
captain at Level 52, Xie Yue,
it’s rather distanced.
Dugu Yan.
As the granddaughter of one of the
Grand Soul Land Masters, Soul Land Venom,
she’s good at using venom
and shouldn’t be underestimated.
Shimo and Shi Mo are
two Soul Sects of Defence Branch.
Compared with the four Storm Attack Branch
members of Martial Soul Hall School,
only their captain
is from Storm Attack Branch.
Tian Dou Imperial School’s condition
in this match doesn’t look optimistic.
In general,
Tian Dou Imperial School
is weaker in soul power level.
The members are evenly dispersed.
Their strategy must be about
flexible attack and defence.
However, just like the last match of Shrek School,
level doesn’t mean everything.
Can Tian Dou Imperial School
strike back?
Bibi Dong,
is this your test for me?
[Next Episode]
I think there’s no need for this match to go on.
Just surrender.
How would we know it’s impossible
without trying?
It’s said that the Pope
will watch the match tomorrow as well.
Don’t worry.
Focus on the match.
I’ll be your backup on other issues.
That’s a soul bone.
Only Father and Master can make me kneel.
How dare you
be rude to the Pope?
Pope, so what?
Purple Demon Eye.