♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
You took advantage of a young lady.
Let me give you a lesson with
my Flinging of Circling Soaring.
I have a way to punish such a villain.
Old Goose, Tian Ya, save me.
I want them to suffer worse than being dead.
Starting from today,
I’ll start the phase-two training.
You’ll battle as Shrek Seven Devils.
I’ve figured out nicknames for each one of you.
Use the nickname to register.
What are our nicknames then?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 36]
Guys, I’ll go to the thirteenth arena with Xiao Wu
to join the double soul battle.
We’ll meet again later.
Go ahead.
Okay.
Alright.
Okay, I’ll go along too.
Okay.
Welcome to Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
This double soul battle will be joined by
San Woo team against
Cat-and-Mouse which has won four times
in a row in double soul battles.
Cat-and-Mouse.
If they can win their opponent, San Woo,
they’ll get five victories in a row.
Maybe they appear in the Suo Tuo Soul Arena next,
they’ll be in the Central Soul Arena.
Acting mysteriously in purpose.
Now, the second round of double soul battles
in Thirteenth Sub Soul Arena, begins!
Martial Soul Shield Body.
First soul skill, Speed Up.
Using high speed to dodge, failing your attack.
Grasp the advantage at the beginning.
This is our strategy.
Unbelievable, right? I’m faster.
She’s a soul master of Keen Attack Branch?
First soul skill, Intertwine.
You thought a soul master
of Controlling Branch is slow?
When did you...?
It’s time for that skill.
Coming. Cat-and-Mouse’s
classic combination skill.
Third soul skill, New Whirlwind.
Second soul skill, Silver Claw.
This skill can defense and
attack at the same time.
Their defense is impenetrable.
It’s hard to breakthrough
from the outside. Be careful, Xiao Wu.
Bloody tornado.
We’ll do it from the inside.
What? Blue Silver Plant can be used like this?
Second soul skill, Parasite.
I’ll lock the Fat Mouse’s actions inside.
He can’t use his skill anymore.
Soul skill, Teleport.
First soul skill, Arched Body.
The battle has ended. San Woo won!
I can’t believe that today’s battle is this easy.
I only used a little bit of soul power
to provide a Mushroom Sausage for Boss Dai
and nothing else, and then I got the points.
The plan to use on the ring
to dodge the opponent,
I didn’t even get to use it.
Little Sister and I, Qibao and Civet Cat
also won easily.
Five battles of single, and
three battles of double, all win.
Our Shrek School is not bad.
It’s time to go for the group battle.
You’ll come onto the stage at a later time.
Remember, you’re going to face
teams above Level 30.
Group battle is unlike single or double battles.
Your cooperation is
more crucial than dominance.
Grandmaster, don’t worry about our cooperation.
Little San, you’re a soul master of Control Branch.
You’ll lead the battle later.
Okay.
Alright.
Later, Mu Bai, Xiao Wu, Zhu Qing,
three of you will attack.
I’ll be in the middle, controlling
the opponent and supporting you.
Fatty, you’ll stay behind
and attack from a distance
and protect Little Ao and Rong Rong.
Little Ao, start preparing.
Give everyone your three types of sausages.
Is there any problem?
No problem.
Rong Rong, be careful and protect yourself.
You and Little Ao must not leave Fatty’s side.
I’ll aid Fatty to protect you both.
Okay.
Don’t worry.
Frenzy Battle Team, Shrek Seven Devils,
please gather at group battle lounge.
Alright, let’s go.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
next will be our fourth round group battle today,
which is also the most awaited last match.
The fourth round, group battle.
The two opposing groups are
Frenzy Battle Team and Shrek Seven Devils.
Frenzy Battle Team has won seven times in a row.
If they can keep this valorous spirit,
they may create Suo Tuo Soul Arena’s
record of the fastest team
to reach Bronze Battle Soul.
Frenzy Battle Team, rip them apart.
Frenzy Battle Team!
Now, let’s take a look at their opponent.
What is this look?
Right.
It’s really hideous.
If you want something nice,
we’ll surprise you later.
This team just registered today.
This is their first round of group soul battle.
Unfortunately, they are
going to fight Frenzy Battle Team.
They are Shrek Seven Devils.
Why are you so close to me?
What if someone attacks you,
I can be your human shield.
Maintain the position.
This is our first group battle.
Thus before the fight, we must set a strategy.
Later, Mu Bai will be in charge of storm attack.
Young lady, you have such a nice figure.
Why are you covering your face?
Get lost.
Do you know who I am?
How dare you to talk to me like this?
She told you to get lost.
Can’t you hear that?
Darn you.
Stop.
You’re not allowed to fight
at the soul battle preparation area.
Or else, you’ll be disqualified.
Director Ao, it’s my fault,
I didn’t hold back my anger.
Kuang Xi, if you create trouble again,
it won’t be just a warning.
Okay, I won’t do this anymore.
You’re Shrek Seven Devils,
the team which registered today, right?
You don’t need to fight here.
Kuang Xi is your opponent
on the soul battle arena.
Don’t get fooled by his appearance.
Kuang Xi and his teammates of Frenzy Battle Team
are all above Level 35.
Battling at soul arena for seven days,
they’ve won Soul Honor level
of seven victories in a row.
Seven days, seven victories.
With their ability,
even among the Level 30 teams
at Bronze Battle Soul,
they’re one of the best.
Every time they take action,
their opponents either die or get hurt.
Bless you all.
If you sense danger,
admit your defeat immediately.
Either die or get hurt?
I would like to see who’s going to be injured.
Boss Dai, don’t get fooled by their appearances.
Just now the director was reminding us,
Kuang Xi is not as rugged as he looks.
To lead a team to win seven times in a row,
he can’t do that with pure strength.
I think this person was trying
to test our ability just now.
That’s possible.
Little Ao, you’re being so calm today.
Hey, me, Oscar has always been...
Stop.
We need to be cautious.
Everyone, listen carefully.
If the situation gets worse,
use Little Ao’s mushroom sausage
to fly off the ring.
Everyone’s safety is our top priority.
Time is running out, let’s go now.
This Kuang Xi is named as a rhino.
His Martial Soul can be a rhino.
He’s a soul master of strength type,
focusing more on defense.
During the battle, we need
to avoid facing him directly.
We’ll attack other
soul masters with weaker defense.
Leave this Kuang Xi to me.
I’ll try my best to hold him back.
He’s on you, Little San.
Countdown. Five, four, three, two, one.
- The fourth round of Group Soul Battle, begins!
- Friends, initiate your martial souls..
Lucky Disc Defensive Light Blossom.
Lucky Disc Attack Halo Blossom.
Shrek Seven Devils have four Soul Honors?
- They’re all top Martial Souls.
- Qibao famously said...
- Their soul master is Qibao Amber Tribe!
- First Strength Second Speed.
The result of the group battle,
- not only depends on ability but also momentum.
- Qibao Amber Tribe, till now...
at this critical moment,
there is no turning back.
Frenzy Battle Team obviously lose to
Shrek Seven Devils regarding soul rings.
Their momentum is weaker.
But that lady in the opposing team
is the only one with a top-level soul ring.
[Next Episode] If that so, don’t blame us for being cruel.
Tell me how you all feel
for today’s battle soul?
One against six, you don’t have a chance to win.
I was a burden to all during the group battle.
On behalf of Suo Tuo Soul Arena,
I hereby invite Shrek Seven Devils
to join the group battle
at the Central Soul Arena.
Oh, this seems inappropriate.
[Participant Information]