♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Chi Huo School and Shen Feng School
combine to become New Shen Feng.
Did they win?
For Mu Bai and me,
this isn’t just a battle of soul skills.
but
a life-and-death duel.
Mu Bai, I’ve never expected
you can reach the finals.
Dai Wei Si, stop being pretentious.
When have you ever stopping striking me?
For Zhu Qing, I will not run away anymore.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 97]
What’s going on?
Dai Mu Bai and Dai Wei Si,
Zhu Zhu Qing and Zhu Zhu Yun
have the same Martial Souls?
- Could they be brothers?
- Sisters?
Xing Luo Imperial School surely wins!
This girl was only at Level 20
when she left home.
In just two years,
she has broken through Level 40.
Tang San has a Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
Decade Millennium?
Isn’t that leapfrog absorbing?
Aren’t we all excited to see
the splendid competition?
I hereby announce,
the battle between Shrek School
and Xing Luo Imperial School
begins now.
Rong Rong, Little Ao.
Jiubao Boosts! Third, Soul!
Fourth soul skill, Stimulating Sausage.
Fight Tang San.
Second soul skill, Nether Claws.
Third soul skill, Tempestuous Waters.
Third soul skill, Nether Slash.
Jiubao Boosts! Second, Speed!
With the help of
Qibao Amber Tribe chief’s daughter,
Shrek School is even stronger.
Why don’t we compete first?
Fourth soul skill,
Ghost Shadow Doppelganger.
Then I shall get rid of you first.
Mu Bai, it’s been a long time.
Today, I’ll teach you a lesson.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
White Tiger Shield.
Are you trying to tickle me
with such strength?
Glare Cutting Line.
This is a self-created soul skill.
After so many years,
your soul skill remains at the original state.
What trash.
White Tiger Meteor Strike.
Did he swallow all the meteors?
Break.
What? The meteors are still around.
Reverse Meteor.
He can aggregate
the released soul power in such a short time.
I’ve underestimated this rascal.
Reverse Meteor Shower.
Aggregate.
Self-created soul skill?
Comet Burst.
Such a beautiful strike.
We haven’t seen Boss Dai use this style before.
Not bad. I’ve underestimated you.
Third soul skill, White Tiger Earthquake.
The floor has become like waves. I can’t leverage.
This is your strongest strength, right?
Not bad. You managed to hurt me.
You’re like a clown now,
shaking in front of me ridiculously.
I shall end your show now.
Second style, White Tiger Ground Pulling.
Extrusion.
You have to be careful.
Third soul skill, Nether Fantasy.
My mind is exhausted.
Father.
Zhu Qing, Zhu Yun is so nice to you.
How would she have assassinated you?
Mother.
Zhu Qing, stop fooling around
with your sister. Come home.
Zhu Qing, you’re seven years
younger than me.
No matter how hard you try,
you’ll not surpass me.
Why do you try so hard?
Zhu Qing’s attacking speed slowed down.
Her expression changed too.
It looks like she’s in illusion.
Zhu Qing.
Doppelganger?
Meteor.
Can Boss Dai listen to me?
Last strike.
Fourth soul skill,
White Tiger Obliterate Spirit.
He has escaped.
They should buy Little San some time now.
I’m very vigorous. You’ll get hurt.
You’re fast. However, you’re not strong enough.
Xiao Wu, buy me some time.
I’ll break free soon.
If we work together...
Meteor Enhancement.
Boss Dai, you silly. Why did you remind him?
I almost forgot about you.
Boss Dai, use that skill right away
when you get out.
White Tiger Ground Pulling.
White Tiger Obliterate Spirit.
Don’t you touch her.
Good timing.
Why don’t you stay obedient in it?
Instead you’re looking for death.
Fourth soul skill, Invincible Golden Shield.
When Xiao Wu activates her Invincible Golden Shield,
all attacks at any level will be voided
in three seconds.
Besides, her power will be doubled.
That is Xiao Wu’s new fourth soul skill.
What golden flare is that?
Reversed vibration? My hand.
Golden tornado?
Combined skill, Whirlwind Supreme Drill.
That’s not good.
Unbelievable.
Xiao Wu at Level 40 has knocked out
Dai Wei Si at Level 49.
[Soul Land]
Done.
Dai Wei Si has underestimated his enemy.
No. Self-denial is an excuse of the weak.
- Not giving up...
- Sister Zhu Zhu Qing, give up.
is the quality of the Shrek Devils.
Zhu Qing, come home.
Zhu Qing, why can’t you let go of the grudge?
Nether Slash.
I didn’t expect Zhu Zhu Qing to reverse the defeat.
What’s going on?
That’s weird. Since the competition started,
others from Shrek School
haven’t intended to attack.
Besides, what’s Tang San doing,
who always controls the fight?
Why isn’t he fighting at all?
The assassin was indeed you.
Sister, which occasion are you talking about?
Strategy adjustment.
We’ve underestimated them.
Alright.
They’ve changed their strategy.
Tang San is taking action.
Seven Devils Riot.
Alright.
Fourth soul skill, Blue Silver Spike Formation.
What is that?
In tomorrow’s competition,
the opponent will take you lightly.
Therefore,
they’ll not show their true power
at the beginning.
You should make use of this point,
to go all out at the beginning.
Okay.
We can’t make it in time.
Captain, I’ll send you out.
Third soul skill, Magical Mirror Escape.
Oh, no. Dai Wei Si disappeared.
Disappeared?
This must be a passage.
The mirror can distort space,
to create an alien space.
Dai Wei Si isn’t found.
We were careless.
How can Blue Silver Plant be so strong?
Fatty, original plan.
Okay. Third soul skill, Flying Phoenix.
Second soul skill, Firing Bathing Phoenix.
What’s going on?
Why did they lose their mobilization together?
Could it be Tang San’s new skill?
Except for Dai Wei Si who disappeared,
the others are like...
Little San studied his mutated fourth soul skill.
If he influxes all his soul power
into Blue Silver Plant,
what effect would it have?
Increasing dizziness.
It seems the desired effect is achieved.
But Blue Silver Spike Formation doesn’t
hold as long as Blue Silver Cage.
That’s enough.
I’ll let you feel
even stronger dizziness.
Fourth soul skill, Phoenix Strike.
The scene is spectacular.
They can’t even escape at this point.
The strength of Xing Luo Imperial School
isn’t even released yet.
Jiubao Boosts! First, Strength!
It’s my turn.
Fourth soul skill,
White Tiger Meteor Strike.
Second stage of Phoenix Strike,
Phoenix Lava Dash.
Fatty, behind you.
Fourth soul skill,
White Tiger Obliterate Spirit.
Fatty.
The attack is interrupted.
Dai Wei Si chose Hong Jun,
in order to reduce the injury
on the other teammates.
Such a good captain.
However, if he attacked Little San first...
It’s too fast. I can’t estimate his direction.
Purple Demon Eye.
Fatty, how are you?
How is Fatty?
What’s going on? There’s no wound on Fatty.
This...
First soul skill, Intertwine.
Master San’s Blue Silver Plant
isn’t as fast as Dai Wei Si.
It seems his speed increases in the alien space.
First, get rid of these two supporting ones.
Rong Rong, watch out.
Little Ao.
Should we just let him attack us?
My head aches.
Rong Rong, don’t move.
I’m not injured. Just headache.
Little Ao saved me. But he...
This child.
I see.
Dai Wei Si’s attack may look like a physical one.
Actually, it’s a psychological attack.
Hiding an invisible psychological attack
in a visible physical attack.
Who will he attack next?
You’re the next.
Since it’s a psychological attack,
there’s nothing to be afraid of.
Brother.
[Next Episode]
I must leave.
Coward, I hate you.
The crucial time of victory and defeat
has arrived.
Oh, no, my soul power isn’t enough.
Master San.
Victory belongs to us.
It belonged and still belongs to us.
Yet he can keep fighting?
Shrek School is getting
more and more surprising.
Since I have made a promise,
even if I have to pay the price with my life...