♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Exchange in our school?
You poor fellows?
Get lost!
Why is the quality of the students
of Tian Dou Imperial School so bad?
I’m the President
of the Board of Education, Meng Shen Ji.
Vice President of the board,
Bai Bao Shan.
Second Vice President of the board, Zhi Lin.
He is testing my strength.
Level 42.
Level 43.
Level 44.
Soul bone.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 46]
Uncle, here they are.
He is The Grand Soul Land Master.
Is President Meng Shen Ji around?
Your Highness, you are here.
Why don’t you, the committees
of the Board of Education,
introduce the guests to me?
Your Highness, let me introduce to you.
This is the Dean of Shrek School, Frander.
He is here to discuss collaboration with us.
Dean Frander.
This is Prince Xue Xing of Tian Dou Empire.
Imperial School is managed by His Highness.
I’ve never heard of Shrek School.
It must be a lousy school.
President Meng Shen Ji.
How could you let people
with unknown origin enter our school?
Your Highness.
Shrek School is not a lousy school.
Teacher Qin in our school
was graduated from Shrek School.
It’s our pleasure to invite Dean Frander
and fellow teachers of Shrek School
to teach in our school.
President Meng Shen Ji.
According to the school rules,
assessment is needed to hire teachers.
Teachers from Shrek School have
the ability of Tian Dou level teachers.
Don’t need assessment.
Your Highness.
Did you come here for this?
Tian Dou Imperial School is
the pillar of the empire.
It is here to bring in talents for the empire.
I don’t hope that the school would hire
some arrogant and bossy people.
President Meng Shen Ji.
I heard that people from
Shrek School has just arrived today
and yet has humiliated my nephew,
the fourth prince of the empire,
Prince Xue Beng.
He is the fourth prince of Tian Dou Empire?
So how will Your Highness settle this matter?
I don’t know if you have asked Prince Xue Beng
why he was humiliated?
I’ve always been kind to talents.
Since you are here to collaborate
with Tian Dou Imperial School,
let’s put aside Xue Beng’s humiliation.
However,
you have to prove to me that
you’re really talented.
Okay. How does Your Highness want us to prove it?
Very simple.
As long as you can hold on
under Mr. Dugu for 5 minutes,
I’ll agree that you’re talents.
Otherwise, please get out of my school.
You!
He defeated Mu Bai with a simple glance.
Your Highness, don’t go too far.
President Meng Shen Ji, don’t you forget...
in the Tian Dou Imperial School,
I am the direct manager.
I have the rights to decide the personnel.
You...
Mr. Dugu, please.
So, it is him.
You guys come together.
[Soul Land]
The Grand Soul Land Master.
My surname is Dugu. My body smells fishy.
If I’m not wrong,
you must be Grand Venom Master, Dugu Bo.
Since you knew my name, hurry up and get lost!
Okay. Let’s go.
Xiao Gang.
I cannot let Shrek School suffer this shame.
You can’t defeat The Grand Soul Land Master.
Even if we are not afraid of death,
do you want the kids to die with us?
Let’s stop here today.
We will never forget the warm hospitality
of the three seniors. See you next time.
Wait.
Dugu Bo.
Let the three of us experience your venom.
Fellow committees, what are you doing?
Prince Xue Xing, you are stubborn
and act arbitrarily.
After today,
we’ll report what happened today
to His Majesty,
and let him decide.
Fine.
Shrek School doesn’t want to trouble you.
Since Tian Dou Imperial School
doesn’t want us to stay,
how can I force?
Let’s bid farewell here, fellow seniors.
Dean Frander!
Grandpa!
It’s her.
Yan Yan. Not bad.
Your strength has improved.
It’s him.
Grandpa, last time we...
Fellow committees,
I’m thinking to leave here too.
Teacher Qin, you can’t do this.
We will definitely report
this incident to His Majesty.
Let His Majesty uphold justice.
I appreciate your kindness.
Since the imperial family hates
people from Shrek School,
how could I stay on shamelessly?
I was alone when I came here.
Today, I’ll leave alone too.
Three of you take care. Bye.
Your Highness, you’re silly.
Do you know how talented they are?
At this point, it’s useless to talk more.
You!
If the three of you want to
complain to His Majesty,
I have nothing to say. Bye.
Yan Yan, I’m leaving now.
You stay here and study well.
Xue Beng. You’ve brought me
so much trouble this time.
I’m afraid these three old fellows
won’t let this matter drop.
If I didn’t create this trouble,
I wouldn’t be the arrogant and bossy
Prince Xue Beng.
At this point,
it’s useless to talk more.
Unfortunately, the three committees
are your brother’s men.
Dean, let us expand Shrek School.
You’ve always rejected students’ sponsorship.
I understand.
But at this time, even if we are
to strive for vindication,
we can’t stop here.
I agree. Boss Dai is right.
Frander, I’m sorry. It’s my fault.
It’s nothing to do with you.
It’s just our bad luck.
I’m not in the mood to re-run the school at all.
Maybe I’m too tired.
What shall we do now?
Why don’t we go to my palace now?
It’s not far from the Qibao Amber Tribe here.
Thanks for your kindness, Rong Rong.
But, I don’t want to feel
being under someone else’s roof anymore.
Dean, it’s my fault. Please punish me.
Qin Ming. What are you doing now?
It’s not your intention.
I should have said sorry.
We have ruined your future.
If it wasn’t your teaching,
I wouldn’t have a future.
Dai was right.
Let’s re-run Shrek School.
None of us would want to see it end like this.
Yes.
Okay. Shrek School will not end.
But before that,
let’s find a place to stay in Tian Dou City.
Recruitment. Lanba Advanced Soul Master School.
Due to expansion, we would like to hire
for the following positions.
Ten Soul Sects at Level 40 and above.
Ones with high soul power are preferred.
Once hired, treated favorably.
Why is a school’s advertisement attached
on the city gate’s bulletin board?
How much does this need?
Lanba School. I know something about it.
[Next Episode]
We don’t have to waste time.
Go!
This voice.
Xiao Gang. When can you stop avoiding?
Xiao Gang.
Our pay requirement is quite high.
Can you bear it?
[Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon]
When you love someone, you don’t have to own her.
I hope she could live happily.
But, at that time...