♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Remember. Only by combining all your strength,
you can minimize the capability difference.
As the captain of Emperor Team,
you’re indeed calm, reliable and strong.
I’ll kill you all!
However, in your heart, while facing a weak team,
- you’re a little reckless.
- How could you neutralize my Venom?
Venom is the unique skill of Tang Clan.
You’re careless.
- Jade Phosphor Serpent Venom lost its function,
- No.
but it has gained the most crucial time.
Xiao Wu!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 41]
How dare you injure Xiao Wu?
Third soul skill.
Raging Storm.
Zhu Qing, White Tiger of Netherworld.
It’s Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
No way, it’s Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
You know what, among martial souls,
it’s difficult to meet a martial soul
that complements each other.
But if they meet and collaborate,
the strength of one’s martial soul
will be doubled.
This is the so-called Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
Don’t let them do it.
Third soul skill.
Fury of Thunderbolt.
Leopard Shadow Doppelganger.
Boss Dai.
Little Sister?
Mutated Martial Soul.
Shimo, Shi Mo. Be careful!
Second soul skill.
Shield Form.
Down.
What a deceiving stroke!
Yu Feng!
You just used the third soul skill.
It has depleted your soul power.
No more energy left to perform
those strange moves.
You’ve no way to hide.
Captain!
Let go of her.
We’ve lost.
Cure my teammate.
Little San, your soul bone of Eight Spiders is poisonous.
Don’t hurt others.
The poison is about to reach the heart.
Luckily, it’s detoxified in time. Otherwise...
Save my teammate.
Or else, they will die.
Should we announce the result
of this soul battle?
The battle is over. Shrek Seven Devils won.
Little San, it seems like you would become Asura
only when Xiao Wu is in danger,
Your team is robust.
But, we didn’t lose to you completely.
You’re right, it’s because
your cooperation is flawed.
Otherwise, it would still anyone’s guess.
We’ll be flawless for the next battle.
The victory will still belong to us,
Shrek Seven Devils.
It’s impressive your toxin can break my venom.
I’ll keep this shame in my heart.
You’ll be defeated by my venom one day.
I’ll look forward to it.
We’ve won!
[Soul Land]
Sorry, Teacher. We’ve lost.
It was my fault for today’s failure.
I was overzealous and fell into their trap.
Please punish me.
No, Captain. It was not your fault.
We never expected they were so cunning.
No, Osler. Being cunning is also part of strength.
We’ve lost the battle. Don’t find any excuses.
Tian Heng, it’s not your fault, but mine.
As the soul master of
Controlling Branch, our team’s soul,
I didn’t lead everyone well enough.
Captain...
It’s a failure to all of you,
but it isn’t bad at all.
Why?
You all have been through
very smoothly so far.
This failure came just in time.
It makes you learn from failure.
You all must learn to progress from failure.
Progress from failure?
You may go back to rest. I have an appointment.
Great, you’ve won.
You’ve defeated your rivals and yourselves.
Today’s group battle
is counted as a test of the second phase training.
You all have passed.
Grandmaster, would you give us a break
after going back?
Don’t be too proud, young fellows.
You can’t compete with Emperor Battle Team,
when it comes to the fight of strength.
But Dean, you’ve taught us that
luck is also part of our strength.
Little brat, don’t get smart with me.
Enough, Frander. Stop it.
They have been working so hard this time.
Grandmaster, are you going
to give them a break after going back?
They do need to rest.
After this trip, you can have a break for 15 days.
I’ll think about the third-phase training.
What? The third-phase?
Why? Do you have any problems?
No, absolutely no.
You’re the wisest.
Besides having the third-phase training,
we’re welcoming the forth, the fifth to come.
Dean Frander, Deputy Dean Zhao, how are you?
You’re the leader of Emperor Battle Team?
Qin Ming here greets my teachers.
I thought you little brat had forgotten us.
Little brat, you’ve improved a lot.
It seems like you’ll catch up with us very soon.
Regardless of the time,
you are always my teachers.
I’m always the disciple of Shrek School.
Disciple of Shrek School?
You’re still as polite as before.
Come, I’ll give you introductions.
This’s Grandmaster.
He’s the teacher of Shrek School.
Greetings to Grandmaster.
Not necessary.
You’re his nephew’s teacher.
You both are considered peers.
That’s why he didn’t accept your courtesy.
Nephew’s teacher?
Why are you still hiding it?
Do you want me to tell them that
Yu Tian Heng is your nephew?
What?
Frander, I told you repeatedly
I have no relation with
Blue Lightning Tyrant Tribe anymore.
I have said too much.
I didn’t expect that he still minds it.
You must be curious about
why Qin Ming is here?
It’s simple. He was once a student
of Shrek School like you all.
Moreover, he was once an outstanding student.
Hello, juniors.
Nice to meet you, senior.
Dean, it seems like Shrek School
has developed better than it was.
What progress is better?
They’re the last batch.
Haven’t the financial problems been resolved?
That’s the reality. We’re getting old.
We’ve lost the impetus we used to have.
After their graduation,
we’re going to live our own life.
Shrek Seven Devils are
younger and better than the students
of Tian Dou Imperial School.
You may go to settle your credits.
Brother San, thank you.
What are you thanking him for?
I know I’m not smart enough,
but I’m definitely not a fool.
During the battle, when Little San faced
the shield attack,
he didn’t use Oscar’s
Flying Mushroom Sausage to dodge it.
It’s because Oscar, Rong Rong, and I
were behind him.
Didn’t you say that we are a team?
I can’t betray my teammates, right?
By the way, what kind of school is
Tian Dou Imperial School
mentioned by Qin Ming?
Little San, are you kidding?
You know nothing about Tian Dou Imperial School?
I really don’t know about it.
Me neither. Are they famous?
The school is way more than famous.
Tian Dou Imperial School,
the greatest Advanced
Soul Master School of Tian Dou Empire.
Previous deans of this school
were in charge by the emperor of
Tian Dou Empire.
However,
the first requirement to enter it is
the student must be of noble birth.
Many outstanding
civilian students can’t join.
That’s why only few famous soul masters
have been fostered.
Tian Heng, do you still recognize me?
You are...
[Next Episode]
Please come with me.
Even though Tang San is strong,
when it comes to one-to-one battle,
I’ll definitely defeat him
by Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon’s martial soul.
Little San, what brings you here?
Uncle,
why are you here?
Even though they are from Shrek School,
you can bring them to the imperial school.
No, I don’t consent to it.
They belong to Shrek School.
I’ve put painstaking care into
Shrek for two decades.
Too bad!