♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] I, Emperor Xue Ye of
Tian Dou Empire, on behalf of my empire,
and on behalf of the organizer
of this competition, announce that
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament
now begins!
Shrek School versus
Tian Dou Imperial School Second Team!
Since you have the confidence,
I will give you another challenge.
Secure victory within one minute.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 69]
A bunch of losers.
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament,
preliminary round one, match three,
Tian Dou Imperial School Second Team
versus Shrek School!
They indeed are a bunch of losers.
Who would cheer for losers?
Shrek School, go for it!
Just admit your defeat, losers!
Rong Rong.
Shrek School wins
not with our popularity, but with our strength.
This is my flower?
Shrek Seven Devils, fighting!
Greetings to each team.
[Tian Dou Imperial School] vs. [Shrek School]
Countdown to start!
Three!
Two!
- Go for it!
- One!
- Win the round!
Preliminary round one, match three!
We’ll proceed with plan A.
We must defeat them within one minute.
- Starts!
- Trigger your martial souls.
Decade Millennium Soul Ring?
This should have been the glory
of Tian Dou Imperial School.
The Decade Millennium Soul Ring?
Is this the team that gained your favor?
Yes, Your Majesty.
My daughter is in that school as well.
In that case,
Shrek School is mentored
by your tribe personally?
They were meant to join
Tian Dou Imperial School.
But Prince Xue Xing expelled them.
Then the Shrek School was founded.
What?
Attack.
Hurry up! We need to make the first move!
Third soul skill,
White Tiger Vajra Transformation!
Sirius Morph!
Third soul skill, Berserk Lion Roar!
Second soul skill,
Bronze Ring Confine!
You fell for it!
- Victory for Tian Dou!
Third soul skill...
You fell for it.
Fourth soul skill, Blue Silver Cage!
What?
It’s a crowd control skill.
Tang San just unleashed a crowd control skill!
- My goodness!
- That is awesome!
This is bad.
Fourth soul skill!
Impossible!
They can’t break my skill so easily!
Fourth soul skill,
White Tiger Meteor Strike!
War soul master at Level 44
with White Tiger Meteor Strike!
The power is at the level of a Soul King!
This is not a competition.
This is utterly...
They are killing people!
Shrek School...
Stop it! Referee, this is not a battle,
they are killing!
This is against the rules.
I request to hold them...
Referee, are they dead?
Our Support Branch soul master
specializes in healing.
She triggered her Martial Soul
to heal the enemy team.
Do you mean they don’t need our healing?
Curse you! You won’t get away with this.
We admit the defeat.
Preliminary round one, match three,
Shrek School won!
They surrendered? That was barely
a minute. This match is rigged!
Maybe the hideous uniform
injected fear into the opponents.
Let’s go.
[Soul Land]
I’ll take my leave now.
Where are you going?
The little devils are doing so well.
I must get more sponsors for them.
Brother San, that was great!
I don’t want to wear this uniform ever again.
This is embarrassing.
Boss Dai, even Xiao Wu hates the outfit.
We boys don’t care much
about our appearance,
but Xiao Wu and Rong Rong wear that ugly thing,
Boss Dai, don’t you feel bad at all?
He has a point, Boss Dai.
You should figure something out for us.
Boss Dai.
Even if you don’t care about these brats,
what about Xiao Wu, Zhu Qing, Jiang Zhu, and me?
Don’t worry about it.
I will come up with something.
Let’s go back to the campus.
I don’t want to be watched as an animal.
Rong Rong.
Father.
Hello, kids from Shrek School.
Greetings, Chief Ning.
For now, I am just Rong Rong’s father.
I am just an elderly man,
I am not your chief.
Congratulations, Little San.
You got the Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
I am flattered, Uncle Ning.
Rong Rong got her fourth ring as well.
I discussed with His Majesty just now.
Tian Dou Imperial School welcomes you.
We’re doing good in Shrek School.
Thank you, Uncle Ning.
I should thank you.
The hidden weapons you made
for us are very handy.
Rong Rong, go on with your friends.
Otherwise, I might be said to abuse authority.
They can gossip all they want.
We won with our own effort.
Before you leave,
introduce your friends to me.
This is Miss Jiang Zhu.
She is a Tool Soul Master
at Level 35 from Healing Branch.
Miss Jiang Zhu’s Martial Soul is very special.
Focusing on healing
will bring you a bright future.
Senior Huang Yuan’s Martial Soul
is the Lone Wolf.
He is a storm attack soul master.
Senior Jing Ling uses Skeleton
Martial Soul, Keen Attack Branch.
You’ve met Brother Tai Long,
pure strength type soul master.
This is the boss of Shrek School.
He is also our captain.
Dai Mu Bai the Evil Eye White Tiger.
He is already a Soul Master at Level 44
at such a young age.
I saw your battle just now.
You’ve achieved much at this age,
I am sure you’ll have a bright future.
Are you interested in visiting
the Qibao Amber Tribe someday?
I appreciate the offer, Uncle Ning.
We will visit the tribe
if we ever get the chance.
Evil Eye White Tigers? I see it now.
He is Oscar, his Martial Soul is sausage.
He is the second person in charge of us,
a Tool Soul Master at Level 41 from Food Branch.
Food Branch?
Level 41?
Uncle Ning, I admire the Qibao Amber Tribe.
I wonder if I have the honor
to join your cause?
You don’t admire the Chief.
You admire his daughter.
I would like to recruit you.
With your talent, boy,
the door of Qibao Amber Tribe
is always open for you.
Dad, you can’t call him “boy”.
That would make you much older.
The joy got messed with my head.
Little Ao has a great future in the Food Branch.
You know Brother San well.
Over here is Brother Ma Hong Jun.
His Martial Soul is Phoenix,
Level 41 from Storm Attack Branch.
Phoenix?
Are all of you above Level 40 already?
Xiao Wu hasn’t reached Level 40 yet.
But she didn’t use the premium herbs.
Otherwise, her level would be much higher.
Hello, Uncle Ning.
Do you have another daughter as
beautiful as Rong Rong?
If I could marry your daughter,
I’ll join Qibao Amber Tribe right away.
But Rong Rong is
the only daughter I have.
If she is willing to do so, I have no objection.
Perhaps I should get myself
a pretty wife instead.
You said it yourself.
The door of Qibao Amber Tribe will
always be open for us.
Yes, the Qibao Amber Tribe
welcomes you at all time.
Zhu Qing is a soul master
at Level 41 from Keen Attack Branch.
She is working tag-team with Boss Dai.
Be sure to visit the Qibao Amber Tribe next time.
I am glad to meet talented
young people like you today.
You may go back now.
I need to have a word with Little San.
That is not fair.
You care more about him than me.
I do wish I could have a son like Tang San.
Dad, did I make you proud as well?
Uncle Ning, is there anything
I can do for you?
I need you to meet someone.
Your father went missing right after
becoming the Grand Soul Land Master,
This person knows some information.
[Shrek School]
I wonder how the tournament
is going.
[Next Episode] Even if you will become
the Grand Soul Land Master,
you won’t be a qualified
soul master from Support Branch.
Three seconds?
Grandmaster, how do you know the secrets
of Qibao Amber Tribe?
But all the clues are connected to one location.
Where is the place?
After this battle,
the Hao Tian Tribe faded
from people’s attention.
What about my mother?
In that case...
The question lies with
what the secret item actually is.
Your father wouldn’t offend
the Martial Soul Temple for a beast.