♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Come out, Luo San Pao!
This is my Martial Soul.
You can call it Luo San Pao.
You can also call it San Pao.
How dare a pack of Level 10 wolves
come to disturb!
There’s poison.
Farting like thunder. Blasting Luo San Pao!
Run!
San Pao. Stop it!
Little San, it’s great.
You finally got your soul ring.
You aren’t talking about this snake, are you?
What a strong power.
Master! How are you?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 8]
Poison! How did Master get poisoned?
Master, you are awake. How do you feel?
Water...
Little San, I’m still alive.
Master, you’re alive well.
You saved me, right?
My father has taught me some simple ways
to treat poisonous wound.
I saw that you had fainted.
So, I gave it a try
and treated a dead horse like a live one.
So rude. How can you say I’m a horse?
Master. You are still weak.
Rest for a while.
I’ll make some meat broth for you.
Wait. Did you make it, Little San?
How’s the toughness? What is soul skill?
Master, look.
I can attack anywhere within 50 metres.
Interwine.
is the feature of Controlling Branch’s
soul master. The toughness is good.
If I’m not wrong,
it should also be accompanied by
the toxicity of the Datura Snake.
Master, you’re right.
But, only with the paralytic effect of
Datura Snake.
The toxicity is not lethal.
The combination of winding
and paralysis is enough.
Unless your opponent has two soul rings
more than you,
it’s impossible to get rid of
the intertwining skill at once.
Let’s hurry up and get back to school.
Master, your injury...
I’m fine.
Master, don’t tire yourself lately.
You can order me on anything.
I didn’t expect to survive this time.
I’ll recover sooner or later.
But, your practice cannot be interrupted.
Bring me the second book from the left
on the third row of the bookshelf.
Keep this book with you.
This book records some of my studies
on soul power practise.
You do it first.
Besides that,
Register at the
Martial Soul Hall in Nuoding City.
After that, you will receive
soul master allowance every month.
You don’t have to be an apprentice anymore.
You rest well. I’ll go now.
Class is over. Let me go and visit Xiao Wu.
I heard that the apprentice is going to
fight against Boss Xiao!
Oh, really? Let’s go and have a look!
Little girl, you can regret it now.
Boss Xiao, are you afraid?
Be my follower if you’re afraid.
Will I be afraid? Who do you think I am?
Wang Sheng, is this apprentice out of her mind?
This little girl is going to fight against me?
Stop the nonsense. How do you want to fight?
I heard that your Martial Soul is a rabbit.
Since you want to die,
I don’t mind to have a rabbit as a pet.
Rest assured. I won’t bully you.
You only have ten people.
We will also send ten people.
Enter the playing ground by turn.
The winner can continue to battle
with the next opponent.
Until one of them is defeated.
- Come on. Who is coming first?
- Sister Wu...
Little girl. Even if you’re strong,
the rest are trash.
Continuous battling will consume your energy.
Sister Wu, let me go first.
Is it okay?
Go!
Loser.
Wang Sheng. My surname is not Liu
if I don’t defeat you today.
If you lose,
you shall be called fallen angel
in the future.
Wang Sheng is too impulsive.
He can’t get close by fighting face-to-face.
He can only beat his opponent by getting close.
Little San, you’re back.
What? Do you want to say that I’m impulsive?
You’re right.
Being apprentices, we can’t be bullied
all the time.
However, you should wait for me to come back.
Why should I wait?
Who knows when are you coming back?
They’ve already come to bully us.
That brat called Boss Xiao...
let me be his rabbit pet.
If I can stand it, I am not Xiao Wu!
I won!
[Soul Land]
What a fallen angel he is!
Boss Xiao, what do you think?
We lost for the first battle. Ling Feng, you go!
Wang Sheng, come back.
Let Little San go for this battle.
Please.
What is this?
Next.
How is it, Boss Xiao?
You got a problem with that?
Tang San didn’t use his soul power.
You shall just admit defeat.
So that you don’t suffer.
Xiao Chen Yu, sixth grader.
Martial Soul is Wolf.
Level 11, war soul master with one soul ring.
Tang San, first grade apprentice.
Martial Soul is Blue Silver Plant.
What? Blue Silver Plant?
Level 11 tool soul master.
What did you say just now?
Level 11 soul master with one soul ring.
Century Soul Ring.
How could this be?
A first grader practiced to a soul master?
Boss! Defeat him!
It’s just a Blue Silver Plant.
What can be more powerful in the soul ring?
Stupid! Shut up!
What is the background of this kid?
The first soul ring is already
a century soul ring.
Is he from any big family?
The belt on him can’t be afforded by an apprentice.
Are you really an apprentice?
Start it.
Be careful!
Head on. Come on!
It’s courting death to fight with Boss’ wolf paw!
This kid wants to fight with me face-to-face!
If I crush his palm,
will the person behind him...
So tough!
Oh, no!
I still have something to do. Let’s end this here.
Blue Silver Plant! Interwine!
Boss!
Is this kid normal?
What is this?
Don’t have to try.
You won’t be able to break free.
My Blue Silver Plant has
the toughness of Datura Snake.
Of course, it also has
some toxicity of Datura Snake.
If you think you can still fight,
I don’t mind to let you try it out.
No. I admit defeat.
Boss Xiao admitted defeat. Brother San won!
Since you’ve lost it,
you should do what you agreed with Xiao Wu.
So, shall I take you or her as the boss?
Of course, it’s Xiao Wu. I can’t beat her.
Otherwise, I’ll be the leader of Dorm Seven.
Little San, you did well. Thank you.
I got to go.
You handle the rest on your own.
In the future, you’re the Big Sister in the school.
Go.
Why? You have a problem with it?
Okay. Let me introduce myself.
I am Xiao Wu, a first grade apprentice.
Martial Soul is a Rabbit.
Level 12, war soul master with one soul ring.
What?
Sister Wu, I admit it.
In the future, you are the Big Sister
in Nuoding School.
Come here! Greet Sister Wu.
Greetings to Sister Wu!
Don’t you have something to do?
Why aren’t you going?
Only you are allowed to have
inborn soul power? Can’t I do it?
Xiao Wu, you are really a rabbit?
What? I’m getting angry!
Finally, the practice of
Xuan Tian Strike is solved.
I’ve also got the soul ring.
Master said that there are
many clans in this world.
I wonder if I could build
a new Tang Clan in this land.
Stand there, kid!
This is Martial Soul Hall. You can’t enter.
Hello. I am here to evaluate for my Martial Soul.
Get in. Go to the reception at the first floor
and see Master Ma Xiu Nuo.
Hello, Mr. Su Yun Tao.
He is the kid I mentioned to you
with inborn full soul power...
but owned Blue Silver Plant as Martial Soul.
Yun Tao. Are you sure that this kid
is here for advanced identification...
and not Martial Soul awakening?
I’ve awakened the Martial Soul of this kid.
So, he is the one?
Yes. Please identify it for him.
I have to go to settle some matters.
Tang San. Master Ma Xiu Nuo
will lead you to the identification.
Bye, Master.
I’ll go first.
Tang San, come with me.
Sorry for bothering you, Master Ma Xiu Nuo.
Don’t call me master. I’m not a master.
Okay. Grandpa Ma Xiu Nuo.
[Next Episode] Kid, it’s dangerous here.
Hurry up and go out.
So, this is...
How long will it take to reach your house?
Soon.
My family is poor. I have nothing to serve you.
I will be good.
I hope so.
Little San. Why do you come back?