♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Ju Hua Guan, fusion!
Bipolar Static Field.
Feng Zhi’s involving.
The fusion is interrupted.
This guy’s speed is really incredible.
Since when did Shrek become
so close to Tian Dou Imperial?
Yu Xiao Gang.
everyone in this world is
eligible to criticize me,
except you.
The Upper Three is on the same boat.
Yue Guan, don’t you even know this?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 95]
It’s been 20 years.
Bibi Dong, you’re still very beautiful.
But I’ve grown older.
If you were in danger now,
I would worry about you too.
Because I loved you.
Do you deserve to say love?
Since you decided to assassinate Tang San
without empathizing my feelings,
the affection between us had ended.
The two elders have retreated
and the rest are severely injured.
Call doctors, hurry up.
Bibi Dong.
Affection? The affection between us...
Yu Xiao Gang, since I can’t have you,
I’ll destruct everything that you care about.
This is Martial Soul City.
Martial Soul Hall,
I’ll definitely settle it with you.
Finally, we’ve reached.
This journey is too dangerous.
You’re right. Luckily, Qibao Amber Tribe helped us.
Otherwise, we were doomed.
Do you think you’re safe
even in Martial Soul City?
Really, Dean? But this’s where
the Sacred Temple is located.
Do they have the guts to kill us
in Martial Soul City?
Isn’t this too impudent?
Not really.
Now we’re in the tiger’s den.
You all should stay alert.
I think this tournament is going to be fierce.
I wonder where is Grandmaster right now?
I believe that Xiao Gang went away
because he has something important.
Don’t worry. Grandmaster will be back soon.
We’ve less than three days before
Continental Soul Master Elite Tournament?
We have to race against time
to prepare ourselves.
We must show our improvement to Master
when he returns.
Sure.
[Soul Land]
Finally, I’ve reached Level 40.
Congratulations, Xiao Wu.
Xiao Wu.
You’re great, Xiao Wu.
Congratulations, Xiao Wu.
Xiao Wu, ask Teacher Er Long to bring you
to hunt for a soul beast
before the tournament begins.
I don’t...
Right. The day’s still bright.
I’m taking you to hunt for a soul beast now.
My Xiao Wu is great.
Xiao Gang will be very happy
once he knows this.
That’s strange.
Someone helps her hunt a soul beast.
Why did Xiao Wu look so reluctant?
Maybe she misses her dad?
Look, Xiao Wu’s back.
Thanks for Teacher Er Long’s help.
Xiao Wu finally have her fourth soul ring.
In fact, I didn’t help her at all.
We were losing each other
after entering the woods.
Xiao Wu?
I freaked out and tried to find her.
Xiao Wu! Where are you?
Xiao Wu!
Finally, I found Xiao Wu, she wasn’t injured.
And she has got her fourth ring as well.
Xiao Wu, what has happened?
How did you get your fourth soul ring?
I was just lucky.
I found an injured soul beast
and then I absorbed its soul ring.
Really, Xiao Wu?
Of course.
How lucky you are, Xiao Wu.
Next time, please bring me with you.
It seems like you’re working hard
since I was away these days.
Master, you’re finally back.
Xiao Gang.
Grandmaster, where have you been to?
So many things happened on our journey.
We almost can’t see you again.
The journey was hard. Are you okay?
Are you okay, Little San?
Master knew everything.
Yes, Master. I’m fine.
Tomorrow is the first round
of the final of the tournament.
Brace yourself and be prepared.
Sure.
Let me repeat the rules.
There are 33 teams in the finals.
Including three seed teams sent by
the two empires and Martial Soul Hall.
For us, the most threatening
is the team from Martial Soul Hall.
If we win and enter the second round,
champion of qualifying rounds
from two empires will draw a bye.
It’s better for teams to get the free pass earlier.
Then, we’ll have time to rest.
The final is tough.
Tai Long, Huang Yuan,
Jing Ling, and Jiang Zhu.
You’re the substitute members.
Little devils, seven of you will
duel together this time.
Finally, we can fight as a team.
Little San, you control the team tomorrow.
Remember, you must hide your strength
in the first round.
Understood, Master.
Go back and rest.
Be ready for tomorrow.
Sure.
How is it?
Now, she’s the Pope.
No longer Bibi Dong of those years.
We’ll find the training methods
for Twin Martial Souls.
Don’t be anxious.
Actually, I’ve found something.
As long as Bibi Dong make any movements,
I can be sure of my thoughts.
That’s great.
Martial Soul City is a dangerous place.
I’m afraid she’ll harm you.
Promise me.
Don’t leave me no matter what happens.
Just let her be.
As long as she can’t take you away,
I fear nothing.
She couldn’t, I’m sure.
[Next Episode]
Why did students from Chi Huo School
and Shen Feng appear together?
Sister Huo Wu.
Whether you wish to win in the finals
or you just want to defeat Tang San,
I’ll definitely help you.
Right now.
Is this the strength of New Shen Feng?
They miss me?
Does such affection
exist in our family?
Mu Bai.
I’ve never expected
you can reach the finals.
Boss Dai, what’s wrong?
A life-and-death duel.