♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Fatty’s Martial Soul is strange,
he was born with the ability of flame.
After his Martial Soul mutated,
it might really become a phoenix.
He’s our Dean,
Frander, the Four-Eyed Owl.
A Soul Saint of Level 78,
Dean Frander is a grudge-holding person.
Aren’t you worried about Rong Rong alone outside?
Can the Shrek School teach her better than us?
Well, I have super red bean bun!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 18]
Oscar, have you both
finished running twenty rounds?
Dean, I’ve done.
I asked about both of you.
Not only you.
Yes, we’ve done it.
Good.
come over.
Since you make such a good teammate,
what about you run another twenty rounds?
I’ve sealed your soul power.
Go.
You have to pay for cheating,
no matter what the reason is.
Do you think so, Rong Rong?
Tell me...
if you have completed your morning task.
No,
the distance was too long.
I was hungry,
I couldn’t hang on.
So, you went into the city
to eat and walk around.
You just got back and found Oscar, right?
You were spying on me?
As a Dean,
I’m responsible for every student.
Oscar is forgivable to lie because
he was afraid that you might be punished.
And you...
disobeyed your task
leaving without permission,
yet you allowed your senior to cover it.
If any of your mistakes
happened in the battlefield,
you would be punished by the military law,
which is death.
This is not a battlefield,
it’s just a school.
Right.
but this my Shrek School.
You have two options now,
either you pack your things and leave,
or prove to me that you’ll never repeat mistakes.
Frander, who do you think you are?
You’re just a Soul Saint.
That’s right.
I’m just a Soul Saint.
Since you look down at this place,
then please leave.
Chase me out?
It’s not that easily.
Frander, I warn you not to mind my business.
If not, you can’t bear the consequences.
Mu Bai, help this lady pack her things.
How dare you, Frander!
I’m in charge in my own territory.
Mu Bai.
Yes.
Ever since young,
you’re the first one to treat me like this.
Even you’re the precious daughter
of the Qibao Amber Tribe,
you’re merely a Great Soul Master for me.
Any student here is stronger than you.
Nonsense,
I’m now at Level 25.
I’m the most outstanding genius
in the tribe in a hundred years.
The Qibao Amber Pagoda is the best in the world,
No one can beat us!
Mu Bai has already reached Soul Honor.
Tang San’s and Xiao Wu’s soul powers
are already at Level 29.
Talking about genius,
they’re all better than you.
Although Ma Hong Jun’s Martial Soul isn’t perfect,
he’s blessed with the top beast soul...
that only a few in this land can compete him.
Although Zhu Zhu Qing
has similar soul power as yours,
her staunch persistence
is far beyond your reach.
Zhu Zhu Qing,
why did you come to Shrek School?
To turn myself stronger.
I’m an assisting type soul master,
of course, I can’t compete with them.
I’ll be much more useful in battlefield.
Useful?
Without any willpower,
you’ll be the first one to get killed
in the battlefield.
You!
With your arrogance,
you seriously think
someone is going to cover your back?
You...
What about Oscar?
I’m sure I’m stronger than him!
Have you seen a Food Branch soul master
born with full soul power?
You mean...
That’s impossible!
How can a Martial Soul of Assisting Branch
have full soul power?
Oscar is unprecedented.
His achievement can be boundless.
One day,
he might be able to replace
your Qibao Amber Tribe.
Have you realized it?
Among these students,
You’re the weakest!
The weakest.
If I can’t handle a little girl,
I’m not worth of the title Golden Iron Triangle.
Dean,
should I go and help her to pack things?
Do you wish her to leave?
Tell Oscar not to run anymore,
tell him to go and comfort Ning Rong Rong.
Yes, Dean.
He dares to scold the little princess
from Qibao Amber Tribe.
Our Dean is really something.
In this school, my words are orders.
Those who disobey...
Depart. To the Soul Arena.
Dean, you’re bringing them to there
on the first day?
All of you are monsters.
so let’s train in a monstrous way.
Let’s go.
[Soul Land]
What’s a Soul Arena?
That’s a place where soul masters
engage in battles,
and where gamblers bet.
For all of you,
that’s the best platform to improve
your actual combat experience.
You mean we’re going to put on a monkey show?
You’re wrong.
even though I dislike it too,
but I have to admit that...
Soul Arena is a place to show soul masters’ value.
It has complete system,
and independent influence.
What’s more important is
it’s rather fair.
Fair?
At here,
even if you’re a successor from a noble family,
you’ll still face a test of life and death.
After registration, each participant...
will receive an iron soul badge.
One point for each winning,
every loss, you’ll lose a point.
A hundred points will advance you
to bronze battle soul.
Before you graduate,
I want all of you to at least get silver soul badge.
Yes, Dean.
Mu Bai,
bring them to register.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Which rank is silver battle soul?
There are eight ranks of badges.
From bottom to top is,
iron, bronze, silver, gold,
purple-gold, sapphire, ruby and diamond.
Silver battle soul is at third grade,
so it’s not that hard.
It’s not as easy as you think.
What?
I’ve been in the battle when I was in Level 29.
Now I have 29 wins, 27 loses.
Only two points.
Mu Bai, how’s this possible
with your capability?
Nothing’s impossible.
It’s not easy in
Suo Tuo City’s Soul Arena.
Fatty, tell us your results.
21 wins, 12 loses. Nine points.
Why is your score higher than Mu Bai’s?
The battles here are arranged
according to your level.
I joined when I was at Level 29,
I won a few rounds and rose to Level 30.
Then I met opponents with Level 38 or 39...
and lost many rounds. That’s why my points dropped.
I see.
There are three types of battles here,
normal battle, death battle and gambling battle.
The last two might cost your life.
We’re now going for the normal battle
just to test your capability.
As for the battle mode,
you can choose either 1-on-1,
2-on-2 or group battle.
Done?
Yes.
You can only take part
in one normal battle per day,
but you can register for different battle modes.
Do you want to go for 2-on-2?
Alright.
Over there.
Ten gold coins for registration.
Your group name.
Let’s call it San Wu.
Hey, you spelled it wrongly!
It’s Wu, not Woo!
You may change the name,
ten gold coins then.
You!
Forget it. San Woo then. It’s just a name.
Iron battle soul Xiao Wu,
please enter the 14th battle stage.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome to Suo Tuo City!
Nervous, exciting, fair Soul Arena!
The first 1-on-1 battle tonight,
War Soul Master, Xiao Wu.
with her beast soul, Jade Rabbit.
Versus war soul master, Qing Bao
with his beast soul, Iron Horn Bull!
[Versus]
Look, it’s a little girl!
This isn’t the place you should come. Go home!
[Next Episode]
Ning Rong Rong.
Don’t ever test my patience!
This is Shrek School, not your home!
If you make me angry, I’ll kill you!