♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Friends, initiate your martial souls.
Admit your defeat.
In the state of Fanatic, we don’t feel pain.
Airborne.
They’re able to fly too?
Although I’m the only one left,
yet to win or to lose is uncertain.
Brother, you’re so cool!
Xiao Wu, get down.
Let’s go. Meal on me.
Brother, how generous you are!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 38]
Tell me how you all feel
for today’s battle soul?
I felt good in a single battle.
But we didn’t cooperate well in the group battle.
I was a burden to all during the group battle,
making less contribution to the team,
which is harder for us to
defeat a strong opponent.
All of you are wrong. What I want to tell is that
all of you have done a good job today.
I’m very satisfied.
You are still lack of some tacit bond,
but this is the very first group battle of you.
Plus, the opponent is a team
with the members’ levels at above 35.
They have gained seven-victory in a row,
But all of you did perform well
and won the battle.
What you have all done today
was beyond my expectation!
Little Ao, you shouldn’t undervalue yourself.
You’ve never given up in contributing to the team.
It’s your Swift Flight Mushroom Sausage
that turned danger into safety
at the crucial moment.
Each of you did play an
essential role in the group battle.
Shrek Seven Devils is a team.
Each of you is indispensable.
Hey, Grandmaster!
Are you coming back purposely to praise the kids?
Of course, I’m not.
I just want to tell them that
they’re the best.
Yet, they’re still imperfect.
I allow all of you to rest for a day tomorrow.
But, you have to analyze
today’s performance together
and tell me before the soul battle
day after tomorrow.
And never stir up any conflicts
when we’re away,
especially in between soul masters.
Grandmaster is right. Don’t stir up troubles.
However, if someone gets on your nerves,
don’t let down of Shrek School either.
There’s one who got on our nerves not long ago.
Xiao Gang, these kids have brought me
more and more surprises.
It’s a good idea to hand them
over you for training.
They’re talented as well.
Their opponents are
five levels higher than them,
and the total soul rings are three more,
yet they still won the battle.
This proved their extraordinary talents.
But I’m still lost.
Compared with Tang San,
the Fatty Hong Jun is still far behind.
Even I’ve been teaching for years,
but I’m still not as good as you.
This is very obvious. You rarely admit it.
Am I someone who doesn’t admit the defeat?
It seems to be right. You did bet with me last time.
You lost ten gold soul coins to me.
- And, you never admit it!
- You...
Frander, I feel like having some beers now.
Since you admitted the defeat, treat us then.
All right! I’ll make both of you drunk.
Register for Shrek Seven Devils, please.
Schleck?
Shrek!
Shrek.
Let’s start the battle.
[Zhu Zhu Qing vs. Gong Lei]
[Zhu Zhu Qing won]
[Dai Mu Bai vs. Xiao Niao]
[Dai Mu Bai won]
[San Woo vs. Li Yang & Ying Wei]
[San Woo won]
[Ma Hong Jun vs. Bruce]
[Ma Hong Jun won]
[Qibao Tomcat vs. Xiao Cao Combination]
[Qibao Tomcat won]
[Shrek Seven Devils vs. Bare Soul]
[Shrek Seven Devils won]
We’re the team of Shrek Seven Devils.
Let’s start the attack with me!
- I’ll have my bet on Shrek Seven Devils.
- Me too...
[Soul Land]
Hurry! It’ll begin soon!
Did you know that there’s a team of seven
keep a clean sweep for the past one month?
Clean sweep? Am I getting it right?
It’s said to be the first team
who makes the quickest and
most clean sweep in Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
The team is...
Excuse me. Register for a group battle, please.
Shrek Seven Devils!
It’s you!
Please hurry up.
Sir, please wait for a while.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Nice to meet you, Honorable Mr. Team Leader.
Is it okay for us to have a talk?
I won’t spend too much time.
Is it representing you personally?
Or representing Suo Tuo Soul Arena?
Of course, representing Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
Mr. Team Leader, I’ll get straight to the point.
On behalf of Suo Tuo Soul Arena,
I hereby invite Shrek Seven Devils
to join the group battle
at the Central Soul Arena.
Oh, this seems inappropriate.
According to the rules of Soul Arena,
only masters above silver battle soul
can battle at the Central Soul Arena.
But, Shrek Seven Devils
are just iron battle souls now.
You don’t have to be humble.
With the records achieved by
Shrek Seven Devils in this month,
all of them will get silver soul badges
after today’s soul battle.
There’s nothing wrong if they gain
silver battle souls one day earlier.
If that’s the case,
you shouldn’t care if it’s one day delay either.
To be honest,
three days ago, a soul master team came.
All of them are silver battle souls.
They’re probably invited
by several nobles in Suo Tuo City.
In these two consecutive days,
the nobles put a lucrative bet on them.
And they won the battle as expected,
which caused a big loss to the Soul Arena.
You’d have known that
the masters with silver battle soul
are generally above Level 40.
But, all of these team members are Soul Honors.
We can’t break the rules,
asking the Soul Sects at Level 40
to battle with them.
If this continues,
Soul Arena can’t sustain the loss.
As Soul Honors, they have reached
the silver battle soul.
It seems that they are a very strong team.
What team did...
Soul Arena used to battle
with them these two days?
Since Suo Tuo Soul Arena
doesn’t have Soul Honors of silver battle soul,
so we can only
send the Soul Honor of
copper battle soul to battle with them.
One of the team is Frenzy Battle Team.
But they were defeated.
Among the Soul Sects,
Frenzy Battle Team is one of the highest level.
Is that because of the level of silver
battle soul team higher than them?
The problem is not about the soul power level,
but the soul ring.
This silver battle soul team is
the same as Shrek Seven Devils.
they’re a team with top-level soul rings.
Top-level soul rings?
The first soul ring is around 100 years.
The second soul ring is above 500 years.
The third soul ring is 1,000 years.
There will be 2 yellows and 1 purple
if it manifests on soul masters.
Why does Soul Arena think Shrek Seven Devils
can win in the soul battle then?
Moreover,
we only have four soul masters
with a level above 40
and the other three don’t reach Level 30.
You’re too humble for this.
Shrek Seven Devils have kept a clean sweep
in the past 27 soul battles.
This is unprecedented in our Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
They must be capable
to compete with this silver battle soul team.
If I remember well,
there will be extra rewards if participating in
the battle at the Central Soul Arena.
Of course, to those who participate,
each of them will obtain
direct rewards of 500 gold soul coins.
In addition, since you’re invited by Soul Arena,
we’ll give you an extra of
10,000 gold soul coins as rewards
if your team can win in the battle.
A team that makes Suo Tuo Soul Arena
put so much attention
and the best soul rings the team owned,
this is beneficial for Shrek Seven Devils.
In order to cope with this battle,
please allow Shrek Seven Devils
not to participate today’s
single and double soul battles.
So that they can concentrate on tonight’s battle.
Here are the details of the opponent.
[Participant Information]
Xiao Gang,
you shouldn’t promise them this quick.
If we negotiate it,
they probably will reward us more.
If we win the battle, the reward
is already enough.
10,000 gold soul coins is a great amount.
I’ve thought it through.
1,000 coins for each kid is more than enough.
The remaining 3,000 will
be reserved for the school.
I’ll spend it on their third-phase training.
Do you have any problem?
No, we have none.
All right. Have a look at
the opponent’s information.
This could be a tough battle
for all of you.
Captain – Yu Tian Heng.
Martial Soul – Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
War soul master Level 39 of Storm Attack Branch.
Soul rings – 2 yellow, 1 purple.
Vice Captain – Dugu Yan.
Martial Soul – Jade Phosphor Serpent.
War soul master Level 38 of Controlling Branch.
Soul rings – 2 yellow, 1 purple.
Team member – Osler.
Martial Soul – Haunted Leopard.
War soul master Level 36 of Keen Attack Branch.
Soul rings – 2 yellow, 1 purple.
Team member – Ye Ling Ling.
Martial Soul – Nine Heart Flowering Apple.
Tool soul master Level 35 of Assisting Branch.
Soul rings – 2 yellow, 1 purple.
Team member – Shi Mo.
Martial Sou – Black Martial Turtle.
War soul master Level 37 of Defense Branch.
Soul rings – 2 yellow, 1 purple.
Team member – Shimo.
Martial Soul – Black Martial Turtle
War soul master Level 38 of Defense Branch.
Soul rings – 2 yellow, 1 purple.
Team member – Yu Feng.
Martial Soul – Wind Chime Bird.
War soul master Level 36 of Keen Attack Branch.
Soul rings – 2 yellow, 1 purple.
The team is so strong!
I can make some guess
about the origin of Emperor Team.
Little San.
Master.
This time, you aren’t allowed
to use the hidden weapon.
But, you are allowed to use
the soul bone of Eight Spiders.
You must not admit defeat until the last moment.
Master, can’t we defeat the opponent?
It’s only with a 30% probability.
And it mainly falls on
you, Mu Bai and Zhu Qing.
Based on the details given,
the opponent of 7 persons in a team
is a very great equipped team.
You have to pay the most attention to two persons,
who are their Captain and Vice Captain.
Soul masters of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
and Jade Phosphor Serpent.
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon?
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon is known as the
beast soul with the strongest attack power.
Its status in beast soul
is similar to the status of Rong Rong’s
Qibao Amber Pagoda
in Assisting Branch of Martial Soul.
So, is their captain from the
family of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon?
Apart from the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon family,
I’ve never heard of any other
soul masters of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon yet.
The background of Emperor Team is overwhelming!
Not only both captains,
but Black Martial Turtle also has the same
level as Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
They are the top in the
Defense Branch of Martial Soul.
As for the soul master of Jade Phosphor Serpent,
she makes me think of a person.
Frander, do you still remember him?
Jade Phosphor Serpent?
Are you saying...
[Next Episode] This time, you’re going
to encounter a strong opponent.
This is the key person.
I’ll tell you after the battle is over.
The Central Soul Arena is very magnificent.
Next, let’s welcome the members of both teams.
I’ll tell you after the battle is over.
You got into my trap!
Thunder Dragon Claws.