♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Zhu Qing, White Tiger of Netherworld.
It’s Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
Be careful!
We’ve lost.
We’ve won!
I’ll think about the third-phase training.
Qin Ming here greets my teachers.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 42]
Hurry up! Come here.
Please come with me.
Credit System is over there.
This is 10,000 gold soul coins that
Soul Arena had promised your leader.
This black card is accessible
in all banks on the continent.
This is the credit list of each member.
Please check it.
Evil Eyes White Tiger, Dai Mu Bai.
26 wins 2 losses in the one-to-one soul battle.
609 points earned.
Dual Winged White Tiger Combination.
17 wins 11 losses in the double soul battle.
24 points earned.
Captain of Shrek Seven Devils.
28-bout winning streak in the group battle.
18 bouts with over 10 winning-streak.
1,855 points earned.
The total credit is 2,491 points.
And he is promoted to silver soul badge.
For now, my total credit is 2,491 points.
How about you, Little San?
Thousand Hands Asura, Tang San.
28-bout winning streak
in the one-to-one soul battle.
1,855 points earned.
San Woo team.
28-bout winning streak in the double soul battle.
1,855 points earned.
Addition to the 1,855 points earned
in the group battle.
The total credit is
5,565 points.
I’m afraid that you’re the only one
who has such a promotion
in all Soul Arenas in the continent.
Too bad!
What is that?
Since Brother San has a gold soul badge,
that means we’re going to fight against
a team with gold soul badge
in the next group battle.
How could we compete with them?
We just won Emperor Battle Team
who is at silver level by a narrow margin.
Don’t need to be worried.
There’s no other team
with gold soul badge at 30th level
in all Soul Arena of Tian Dou Empire.
Hence, your team is
the strongest at this level.
We, Shrek Seven Devils are
a gold soul battle team.
Tian Heng, do you still recognize me?
You are...
Uncle.
Why are you here?
Let’s talk privately.
Uncle, you’re here...
It seems like you’ve been doing well these years.
You have reached Level 39.
you’ve finally grown up.
Uncle, please come back home with me.
Actually, Grandpa misses you a lot.
And my father as well.
How’s your grandpa and father?
They’re doing great. Since Grandpa is aging,
my father is managing most of the tribe’s affairs.
Uncle, do you know that
I always found Grandpa dazing at your portrait.
He must want you to go home...
Stop it, Tian Heng.
Tian Heng, perhaps we will meet again very soon.
Don’t be discouraged by today’s failure.
Failure is nothing to fear.
The only fear is that you don’t learn from failure.
Your team is strong.
But from watching the battle today,
you didn’t perform the best.
Uncle, you watched the group battle too?
I’ve disgraced our family.
Are you aware of your problem?
You didn’t lose to your rival,
but yourself.
The reason why you fell into their trap
is the arrogance of
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe you’re holding.
Arrogance?
Uncle, don’t worry.
I’ll never lose to them again
in the next battle.
You’ll have the chance.
Because I’m the leader of Shrek Seven Devils.
You’re curious about it, right?
But, among the Shrek Seven Devils,
I only have one direct disciple.
He’s the soul master of
Controlling Branch in the team.
It’s him? Tang San,
who controlled the entire battle.
Tian Heng, I’m leaving. Remember my words.
Uncle, could you please teach me too?
Tian Heng.
If you want to be a great soul master,
set Tang San as a goal then.
If you can surpass him one day,
you’re the top soul master
in the continent by then.
Uncle, why?
Even though Tang San is strong,
I think the information must be wrong.
His soul power should be the same as mine.
Besides, his martial soul is Blue Silver Plant.
I’ll definitely defeat him
with my martial soul of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
in the one-to-one battle.
No, the information is correct.
He’s only on at Level 32.
But...
Well, you’ll know later on.
There’s wine here.
Teacher, we’ve won today.
Shouldn’t you give us a treat?
You? You’re the flaming fatty
in Shrek Seven Devils.
That’s right.
We were wearing a mask before,
so you can’t recognize us.
I know why you all wore masks now.
You really surprised me.
I always thought Emperor Battle Team is gifted.
But if you all are at the same age,
they wouldn’t have any chance to win
before you.
Senior, by any chance, may I ask
what your soul power level is?
Level 62. I’m quite lucky.
[Soul Land]
Fine, stop flattering each other.
Sit down, little monsters.
Order your food as you wish.
Today, your stingy dean will treat you.
This, this, and this.
Good. Worthy of being my disciple.
He still truly letting me save money.
And this too.
Except what I have pointed out just now,
bring me every dishes on the menu.
Two more kegs of ale, please.
Teacher, what’s wrong with you?
Why there is blue in your face?
Didn’t you sleep well last night?
How could I let Dean pay for it?
I finally come back after years.
My teachers,
please give me a chance
to thank you for your teaching.
Little Ming, you’re still so thoughtful.
I wanted to see Frander buy them
a marvelous meal.
What a pity.
If you aren’t from Shrek School,
I’ll try every possible means
to recruit you into the imperial school.
If with your presence, perhaps...
Even though they’re from Shrek School,
you can still bring them to the imperial school.
Grandmaster, are you here to undercut me?
They belong to Shrek School.
Can’t we give them the best education
in Shrek School?
Grandmaster, what you meant was...
Teacher Qin, if I’ve not mistaken,
Tian Dou Imperial School possess two seats
to the pageant one year later, am I right?
I can allow them to join the pageant
representing Tian Dou Imperial School.
No, I don’t consent to it.
They belong to Shrek School.
Grandmaster, don’t forget that
I’ve put painstaking care into
Shrek School for two decades.
Frander, I’ll pose you several questions.
If you can solve them,
it doesn’t matter whether
these kids go to Tian Dou.
First,
can you provide them with
mimicry training environments?
Second, can you provide
the qualifications to enter
the Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament in one year?
Lastly,
what’s your intention
when you established Shrek School?
I...
Mimicry training environments
will speed up their soul power cultivation.
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament
only allow a qualified school to join
after passing a preliminary competition.
Yet our school haven’t registered,
so it isn’t a qualified school.
Your intention of establishing Shrek School
was to cultivate genius soul masters.
What I’ve chosen for them
is to make their paths smooth
in every possible.
Moreover, I haven’t finished talking.
To allow these kids to join
Tian Dou Imperial School,
I have one condition.
The school must admit all teachers from Shrek School
and let us teach them personally.
Tian Dou Imperial School
is not allowed to interfere.
But
Shrek School is the brainchild of
Dean Frander, I’m afraid that...
All right, let’s follow what Xiao Gang said.
He’s right.
I shouldn’t only consider my pride.
Everything should be for the good of the kids.
Shrek’s teachers can also have a place to retire.
It’s a deal.
You talk it over then.
Xiao Gang and Wu Ji will represent me.
Although Frander is quite stubborn,
he isn’t an unreasonable person.
I believe he’ll think it through clearly.
Teacher, don’t feel sad.
I’m not sad,
just frustrated, that’s all.
All this came too fast for me.
Don’t try to convince me, I want to be alone.
Teacher, actually this is like
borrowing a chicken to lay an egg.
To be honest, I don’t know why you’re depressed.
Borrowing a chicken to lay an egg?
Yes, that’s it.
Borrowing that imperial school’s
facilities to train,
and we help them fight
as paying them a fee.
Borrowing a chicken to lay an egg. That’s great.
Maybe I’m too stubborn.
Why should I care about when it happens?
Shrek School will end after all.
But what we have done will never change.
[Shrek School]
Xiao Gang, thank you for helping me
draw this end to Shrek School.
[Shrek School]
Finally, we’re back.
In two months,
you will head on to Tian Dou Imperial School.
Within these two months,
I won’t start the third-phase training,
but with two conditions.
First, deal with your own problems.
Second,
assimilate the battle experience
obtained from soul battle recently.
And focus on cultivating soul power.
Go and rest then,
you have worked hard recently.
Go back and rest.
So tired.
Me too.
I wouldn’t have thought that
when we were in Suo Tuo Soul Arena
I feel tired once coming back.
This must be the fatigue period
mentioned by Grandmaster.
It’s me.
Little San, what brings you here?
I’m here for Rong Rong.
We’ll travel to Tian Dou Imperial School
in two months.
I’ve promised Rong Rong to provide
her family with mechanical concealed weapons.
Hence, I’d like to confirm it with her.
Brother San,
although you’ve given everyone
a Godly Zhuge Crossbow,
only my father can decide this matter.
How about
I’ll ask Dean Frander for leave to go home.
Actually, my home, Qibao City
isn’t far from Tian Dou Imperial City.
Later, I’ll go directly from home to
Tian Dou Imperial School to meet you all.
If that is the case,
let’s talk about it after
reaching Tian Dou Imperial School.
That’s even better.
Since we don’t have to train now,
we have much time to play.
Xiao Wu, any place of fun?
Brother San, will you go with us?
No, I have a lot of things to do.
Go ahead and be careful.
[Shrek School]
[Next Episode]
Brother San, what a good thing
did you make this time?
Little San, could you come out for a while?
Right here. Rong Rong and Zhu Qing
have fallen asleep.
Set off!
Fiend Battle Team.
Xiao Gang, are you insane?
Let them fight with a soul master team at Level 40,
do you want them to get killed?