♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Since he can’t be one of the Martial Soul Hall,
I’ll just kill him.
Bibi Dong,
listen to me clearly.
If there’s any unpleasant happening to Tang San,
I’ll destroy Martial Soul Hall
at all costs.
This is indeed Sword Sect
Chen Xin’s power of attack.
If you dare to touch Tang San,
just wait for the revenge of death!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 94]
Ju Hua Guan, fusion!
Bipolar Static Field.
Oh, no. Once the bipolar field is formed,
everything in the area will become static.
Nobody can escape from it.
Third soul skill, Flying Sword Wings.
It’s too late.
Qibao, reinforced with Amber!
Qibao Boosts! Second, Speed!
Feng Zhi’s involving.
With the great assist of Qibao Amber,
- the fusion is interrupted.
- This guy’s speed is really incredible.
Ning Feng Zhi!
We’re glad to have Chief Ning and
the Grand Sword Master today.
Luckily, you’ve asked them to be here.
What a horrible speed.
What a terrifying increase.
Will Rong Rong’s power the same as him
after reaching Level 70?
You Qibao Amber Tribe,
are you planning to
fight against us until the end?
The Upper Three is on the same boat.
Yue Guan, don’t you even know this?
It’s us who admit the defeat today.
Old Ghost, let’s go.
Finally, they withdraw.
It’s great! We’re safe now!
Brother!
I was scared.
Didn’t I say that
no one can disturb me without my orders?
Your Holiness,
the two elders didn’t complete the mission.
They’re waiting for your instructions.
Your disciple is quite lucky.
You sent someone to murder Tang San
because of his father, right?
By the strength of Martial Soul Hall,
even if Tang San has extreme talents,
you won’t be afraid of this
tiny soul master, will you?
You’re still smart as usual.
Martial Soul Hall won’t forgive
Tang Hao for his crime easily.
The clean-up here is almost done.
I’ll get two persons to repair the carts.
Wait.
Look at there.
Chief Ning from the Qibao Amber Tribe.
Why is he here?
Kids, you’ve done a great job today!
Dad!
Ning Rong Rong. Ning Feng Zhi.
No wonder...
Unexpectedly, Shrek School
has the daughter of
Qibao Amber Tribe’s chief.
It seems that it’s Chief Ning
from Qibao Amber Tribe
who forced the Grand of Soul Masters to withdraw
and resolved the crisis of Shrek School.
Boss,
Chief Ning is just
a soul master of Support Branch.
How could he force the
Grand Soul Land Masters to withdraw?
You know nothing.
Qibao Amber Pagoda is
the strongest martial soul of
Support Branch
in the entire continent.
Ning Rong Rong hasn’t appeared
in the previous rounds.
She must be the secret trump of Shrek School.
Qibao Amber Tribe has helped them out.
It must be the instruction from the Crown Prince.
Since when did Shrek become
so close to Tian Dou Imperial?
[Soul Land]
Tang San thanks to all seniors for saving my life.
I’m not here to protect all of you.
I was entrusted by His Majesty
to protect the Crown Prince.
He is indeed the Crown Prince!
By having today’s lesson,
they’re not going to act rashly anymore.
All of you should continue the journey now.
I didn’t even expect that
They’d attack you so quickly.
Why didn’t you reveal their identity just now?
Presumably, you know that
they’re the people of Martial Soul Hall.
Martial Soul Hall’s influence is powerful.
Once I reveal their violence act,
I’m afraid that every one of us
will suffer a mortal disaster.
But I have no rancour with them.
Why do they insist on attacking me?
Little Freak, you’ve forgotten what I told you?
Just because of my talent?
I think that it’s something to do with my father.
Martial Soul Hall has been arrogant
for some times.
In recent years, the outstanding juniors
are forced to surrender themselves.
Otherwise, most of them
have been settled in secret.
They can just send
the Grand Soul Land Master to assassinate me.
It’s more convenient, isn’t it?
The people of Martial Soul Hall are arrogant.
Assassination would ruin their prestige.
Thus, they would not do it.
But their action of attacking the young ones
by relying on the strong ones
ruins their prestige as well.
The two Grand Soul Land Masters
that appeared were...
The one in golden armour was the
Grand Chrysanthemum Master, Yue Guan.
Soul power at between Level 94 and 95.
The dark shadow that appeared later
was the Grand Ghost Master, Gui Mei.
His level is almost the same as Yue Guan.
His martial soul is very unique.
It’s Gui Mei.
The Old Ghost is indeed incredible.
If we carried on the battle just now,
I may not able to fight them.
Martial Soul Hall sent
the two Grand Soul Land Masters
as they presume that
Uncle Sword and I would help out.
Fortunately, we’ve Senior Dugu today,
making them be in disadvantaged.
Little Freak, you don’t have to thank me.
There’re still many peculiar tricks
that you’ve never seen.
I don’t wish you to die.
All right, Old Freak.
If you need any hidden weapon,
just request it from me will do.
Luckily, you’re safe and sound today.
I wish that you can return to
Qibao Amber Tribe with Uncle Sword,
to avoid from the danger.
Uncle Ning, Grandpa Sword,
thank you for your kindness.
There’ll be a great loss if I give up to it now.
And, I’ll feel sorry to my friends.
Do you know how powerful the Martial Soul Hall is?
Now, the number of soul masters in both empires is
less than half of Martial Soul Hall.
The Pope herself is unfathomable.
She’s known as the most powerful
leader of Martial Soul Hall ever.
Even so,
you still want to participate in
Continental Soul Master Elite Tournament?
Thank you, Uncle Ning.
But this tournament
is a very important phase in my life.
I can’t give up.
All right. Since you’ve decided,
I’ll try my best to keep you safe.
Tang San was still small
when the matters happened.
And he’s still very young now.
How could you be cruel to kill him?
The resentment between
Tang Hao and Martial Soul Hall
shouldn’t be intervened
by you as an outsider.
Yu Xiao Gang,
everyone in this world is
eligible to criticize me,
except you.
Please leave. Go back to protect
your precious disciple.
I don’t wish to see you anymore.
[Next Episode]
She’s now the Pope,
no longer Bibi Dong of those years.
Just let her be.
As long as she can’t take you away,
I fear nothing.
Yu Xiao Gang, since I can’t have you,
I’ll destruct everything that you care about.
Xiao Wu. Xiao Wu.
Martial Soul Hall,
I’ll definitely settle it with you.