♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
For eternal life, I will never change until death.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 30]
Finally, we’re back.
You must be tired after walking for a whole day.
Get some rest first.
I’m starving to death.
Let’s go and have a meal.
It’s not your fault.
Even if we led them,
I’m afraid we wouldn’t be spared
when we encountered Titan Giant Ape.
This is true.
This time, Titan Giant Ape appearing
at the outer part of the forest
might be a coincidence.
However, the bull roar that Xiao Wu mentioned is...
I’ve never heard about a bull roar
that could frighten the Titan Giant Ape.
The bull roar you’re saying
should be the Azure Bull Python.
The person who knows about it is here.
Come on, Wu Ji. Let me introduce him to you.
He is my old partner, Yu Xiao Gang.
He’s also Tang San’s master.
You can call him Grandmaster.
Oh, so you’re the Grandmaster.
Hello. I am Zhao Wu Ji.
Acala, nice to meet you.
Take a seat.
Grandmaster, do you know about me too?
Tang San should have come back with you, right?
Is he all right?
You are on a new and long journey.
Yes, how about you?
Are those memories in the past
and even you
only my illusions?
Every memory is a wave in the long journey of life.
Staying alive is the best proof.
Do I still have a chance to go back?
You’ve already decided it, haven’t you?
If you can’t forget me,
then bravely walk out of your own way
on this land
with our common wish.
Our common wish?
That’s right. A way of my own.
I want to build a Tang Clan
that belongs to me on this land.
It’s threatening but not dangerous this time.
I didn’t expect that we can all return
after encountered Titan Giant Ape.
Xiao Gang, what do you mean by the Azure Bull Python?
Azure Bull Python is a more powerful soul beast
than the Titan Giant Ape in Star Dou Forest.
It’s more powerful than Titan Giant Ape?
If Titan Giant Ape is the King of Star Dou Forest,
then Azure Bull Python is
the Emperor of Star Dou Forest.
I heard about it
from a Grand Soul Land Master.
He entered the core of Star Dou Forest before.
It’s a lake like a fairyland.
A lake?
Yes.
The core of Star Dou Forest is not a forest,
but a lake.
that Grand Soul Land Master
was confident with his ability.
So, he wanted to go deep into the forest
and search for King of Forest,
Titan Giant Ape for a battle.
Finally, he found the Titan Giant Ape.
However, he didn’t manage to
battle with Titan Giant Ape.
Is it because of the Azure Bull Python?
Yes.
When that Grand Soul Land Master
reached the core of the forest,
he saw Titan Giant Ape
was drinking water by the lake.
When he was ready to battle
with Titan Giant Ape,
the lake suddenly boiled.
Next, a huge bull head appeared
from the water surface.
A sudden pressure made him unable to move.
Then, the bull head continued to rise.
Finally, a giant with a bull head and
python body appeared on the lake.
The most terrifying thing was the giant
bull python could speak human language.
Human, it’s not easy for you to cultivate.
Leave this place.
That giant is the Azure Bull Python.
Do you know how the Titan Giant Ape reacted
when the Azure Bull Python appeared?
How?
Titan Giant Ape was like a child being punished.
It seems you were really lucky this time.
Talking about this, we have to thank Tang San.
I’ve read through the details of these students.
What kind of soul ring has the child
from the Food Branch found?
You can’t wait to work.
Since I’ve promised you,
I will definitely do my best.
Don’t you forget about your promise.
Teacher Zhao.
This time, it’s quite lucky.
Oscar has got a soul ring of
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent.
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent has a mild nature.
But it’s very cunning and good at running away.
It’s more outstanding than
any other soul rings I expected.
If I’ve not mistaken,
speed should be the skill of
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent’s soul ring.
You’re right.
Oscar’s third soul skill is
a mushroom-like sausage.
By eating it, he can fly at the Phoenix
Tail Crest Serpent’s speed for 1 minute.
Fly at the Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent’s
speed for 1 minute?
Yes.
The child’s talent is unprecedented.
Our Shrek School only accepts monsters.
Too bad it’s the last batch.
However, it’s lucky to have your help.
As long as we work together,
we can surely train these children well.
In no more than 10 years,
the soul masters’ world will shake
because of Shrek.
I stay on for Little San.
Don’t forget your promise.
You can rest assured.
We’re brothers for so many years.
When do I break my promise?
Moreover,
we’ll have to wait for Little San to reach
Level 40 for his next soul beast hunt.
You’re saying that he has reached Level 30?
I believe Little San’s future will
surpass the owner of this token.
[Soul Land]
Is it true?
Master.
Master, you’re here.
Go back to the team first.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Little San, who’s that uncle?
My master.
Your master?
Is he the master that you’ve always mentioned
who knows everything?
Little monsters, look over here.
Let me introduce. This is Grandmaster.
He will be responsible for guiding
your cultivation in the future.
I’ve read your details.
Next, I’ll guide your cultivation.
I hope all of you can be prepared.
We’ll start the training tomorrow morning.
I’ll announce the content of training
tomorrow before class.
Such a short spoken person.
Okay. Little monsters.
Make ways, everyone!
Both of you don’t touch them.
Teacher, Little San...
Xiao Gang, this is...
Carry Ma Hong Jun to the house.
Little San, can you hear me?
Relax and take a deep breath.
Try to imagine that your soul bones
are retracted into your body.
How is it?
Little San, it’s all right. Try again.
Let the air flow.
Take the soul bones as part of your body.
Just like your limbs.
Don’t try too hard.
Let it be natural. Just like breathing.
Little San.
Little San, you remove the toxins for Ma Hong Jun.
Master, can I?
You can retract the soul bones
according to your consciousness.
Believe in yourself. You should feel it.
Control your soul bones and
draw the toxins from Ma Hong Jun’s body.
Just like retracting the soul bones
into your body.
But, if...
Don’t think about any other things.
Just think that soul bones are part of your body.
You can easily draw the toxins
out of Ma Hong Jun’s body.
But...
It’ll be too late if the toxins enter the heart.
Control the soul bones and
penetrate Ma Hong Jun’s wound.
Mind freely. It’s not hard to do it.
How is it?
He’s fine. He’ll wake up in a while.
I’ll go in and have a look.
Little San, remember. An innocent man
gets into trouble because of his ability.
Brother. How do you feel?
I’m all right now.
Maybe I was not getting used to the soul ring.
Master said that it’s all right.
Is it really okay?
It’s all right. You guys should go in and check Fatty.
Just now...
Let’s go and check Fatty.
Little San, you must tell us if there’s any problem.
Remember that we are brothers.
I will. Go on in.
Brother, are you all right?
What did Teacher mean just now?
I’m really all right. Don’t worry.
Do you know about
the externally attached soul bone?
Master said the one at your back is...
[Next Episode]
Xiao Wu, we would be are together forever, right?
What do you need?
I’m afraid you couldn’t make this decision.
Great Soul Master?
From tomorrow on,
you’ll be greeted with the life of hell.
Super Invincible Sausage!
Dai Mu Bai, dequeue.
Defeat them one by one.
What?