♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
From now on, you should start training.
Keep on absorbing to strengthen your power.
Don’t eager for quick results.
Understood.
Be careful!
Xiao Gang, I lost.
Seems like if they join forces,
they can defeat Zhao Wu Ji.
Little Freak, my wish has come true.
It’s time to leave.
Old Freak, take care of yourself.
Don’t forget about the two iron balls.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 55]
What’s the matter?
Brat, are you new?
Don’t you know the rules of the advanced class?
Rules?
Don’t you know that
no one is allowed to sit next to Xiao Wu?
Who allows you to sit here?
Me.
Nothing else to do now? Get away.
Otherwise, don’t blame me for being rude.
Xiao Wu, it’s our guy’s matter.
Don’t get involved.
I give in to you,
it doesn’t mean I’m afraid of you.
Do you think me as the school chief
could just back down?
School chief?
Who’s this hick?
Doesn’t even know our school chief.
He’s the most...
The most outstanding student in the school.
I see.
Is he even stronger than Boss Dai?
I must be more alert.
Brat, you have two choices now.
First, fight with me, one-on-one.
If you win,
I’ll admit that you’re qualified to sit here.
Second, get off now.
Find another place to sit.
One-on-one? Right now?
Do I have to pick a place
to duel with you little kid?
Don’t worry, I don’t bully kids.
I’m not using my third soul skill.
One may escape an untoward act of God,
but never the evil of their own.
Then come on.
Tang San, Martial Soul of Blue Silver Plant.
War soul honor of Controlling Branch at Level 37.
What? You’re at Level 37?
Is he afraid?
Tai Long, Martial Soul of
Supreme Orangutan.
War soul honor of Storm Attack Branch at Level 37.
He’s doomed.
If his level is higher,
he’d have more bouts to fight.
Come on, boss.
Humph, such a fragile Blue Silver Plant.
Quiet! Class is going to begin.
Little San, are you bullying your classmate
on your first day?
I’m sorry, Teacher Shao.
I’ll release him now.
Teacher, it’s me who wanted
to challenge Tang San.
Tang San, I disclaim it.
Let’s duel again.
Can you stop it?
A strength-type soul master challenging
a soul master of Controlling Branch.
Are you out of your mind?
But I...
Let’s fight physically,
instead of fighting with our martial soul.
Sure.
Enough, here is not the soul arena.
It’s time for class now.
Find a place to settle your problem after class.
I’ll wait for you after class.
Brother, Tai Long keeps pestering me.
Sort him out properly later.
He pesters you?
He’s always approaching me.
Hump! I don’t care about him.
Why do I feel annoyed about
Xiao Wu gaining attention from others?
Finally, class is over.
It’s finally over.
Brother, there’s a lot of good food in Tian Dou City.
Let’s go stroll.
Great, let’s go.
Let’s ask Fatty and Little Ao too.
Why do you bother bringing them along?
They’re so boisterous.
Forget about them, just two of us go.
Xiao Wu, even if you’re afraid of us
bothering your date,
it’s not necessary to mock me.
I’m so handsome, charming, and talented.
How could I be boisterous?
Tang San, follow me.
He’s still not finished!
Brother San, do you want me to deal with him?
No, you go first.
[Soul Land]
Haven’t we arrived after walking so far?
Right here then.
Let’s start.
Are you convinced now?
No!
I’ll beat you till you concede.
Tai Long is tenacious though.
He didn’t want to stop
even you’ve thrown him away many times.
If I didn’t dislocate his joints,
the fight won’t be ended.
It’s good though.
He shouldn’t dare to pester you.
Let’s go eating.
Brother, look. What’s that?
What a strange giant hemisphere.
It seems to be an auction house.
The symbol above should be the gavel
dedicated to the auction house.
An auction house?
Can we go take a look?
I remember Grandmaster said that
only the capitals of
two imperial empires possess
auction houses with the highest standard.
They even sell soul bones.
Let’s go eating first though.
But, it seems like every restaurant is full.
It’s all because of Tai Long
who wasted our time.
Brother, there’s fast food.
Let’s eat it before we go to the auction house.
Boss, what do you have?
Little girl, my meal is delicious yet cheap.
2 copper soul coins for 1 set.
Do you want?
Give me two then.
By the way, give all the meat to him.
How could it be? You should eat more.
Never mind.
You’re growing now.
Grandmaster said that boys should eat more meat.
Or else you won’t have strength.
Xiao Wu, no matter what happens in the future,
I will be by your side as I am now.
You’re always my precious Xiao Wu.
I know you care for me very much.
Let’s eat quickly.
There’s some soul power left here.
Purple Demon Eye.
How pitiful.
Brother.
What kind of treasure is it
that those didn’t hesitate
to kill the guards of the auction house.
Could it be a soul bone?
Stop there. Loiterers keep away.
This is the auction house. We want to go for a look.
I’m sorry, my guests.
Do you have
the bidding qualification certificate?
Bidding qualification certificate?
You don’t even know that.
Do you want to break in?
Only guests with
a bidding qualification certificate
are allowed to enter the auction house to bid.
The threshold of having the certificate
is 10,000 gold soul coins.
As it can avoid malicious bids.
I hope you understand.
Is there any other way to get in?
You may enter if you’re here to sell something.
But the items must be appraised by
our appraisers at Tian Dou Auction.
And the value must exceed 1000 gold soul coins.
We’ll sell this then.
What’s this?
A weapon.
This way, please.
Appraiser, these two guests would like
to put this item up for auction.
What an intricate creation.
May I ask what it is?
Could you please show me?
I named it Malicious Attack, and it’s poisonous.
It’s poisonous?
This weapon is potent,
is there any suitable place for a demonstration?
Please.
[Next Episode]
The coming lot
is a nonpareil among all.
This lot is starting at
100,000 gold soul coins.
It’s in my interest.
Sold.
I come to see
who dares to beat my son.
It’s meaningless to save those
who’ve lost their soul.
How could I not save one with soul?
Are you going to save them all?
The two of you, who’s Tang San?
I am.