♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I have reached Level 30.
Good, Oscar.
If that so,
tomorrow morning,
Teacher Zhao Wu Ji will lead you...
to the Star Dou Forest.
to help Oscar to get his third soul ring.
Unless you meet a Millennium Soul Beast,
or else I’ll not interfere.
You have to think of strategies on the way.
How arrogant you are!
Teach them a lesson!
A fight? I love it.
Our turn!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 21]
I’m Ye Zhi Qiu, head of foreign affairs
department of Cang Hui School.
Which clan are you from?
We’re from Shrek School.
Shrek? Never heard of it.
Because you’re ignorant.
These little monsters don’t
look like a clan’s disciples.
Soul King ranking above Level 50.
I have to use my hidden weapons.
Black Turtle Beast Soul.
Where is your teacher?
Let the adults settle this.
You’re just an old tortoise,
how dare you ask to see our teacher?
We can settle you easily.
What did you say?
Good, I’ll teach you a lesson
on behalf of your teacher.
Respective customers,
please do not fight in the shop...
I’ll wait for you outside.
His Martial Soul is Black Turtle.
I’m certain that
he’s a defense type war soul master.
Strong in defense, weak in attack.
We may win.
Zhu Qing, Mu Bai and me.
Three of us are fast, we’ll pin down him.
Xiao Wu will support us.
Black Turtle corresponds to water.
Fatty’s Phoenix Fire restraints it.
Water restraints fire,
vice versa, fire restraints water.
You’ll attack at the outer area.
Sausage Oscar will aid Fatty.
We’re outnumber.
Let’s play a protracted fight.
Tang San,
what about me?
Well...
your Martial Soul is special,
you’ll play by ear then.
Let’s go.
If you want recognition,
then prove it to them
with actions that you belong to Shrek School.
Come on, Teacher.
I’ll give you another chance.
It’s still not too late to apologize.
Beat us first then.
Let me teach you how to be a human.
Remember, we’re not human,
but monsters.
Come on, Teacher.
First soul skill,
White Tiger...
Intense Light...
Wave.
First soul skill,
Intertwine...
Ma Hong Jun.
He’s great.
It’s over already?
Grilled tortoise.
No, there’s cold air.
First soul skill,
Black Turtle Protection Shield.
Stop him.
White Tiger Intensive Light Wave.
Black Turtle’s defense is really powerful.
Second soul skill, Dark Water Ice Bound.
He uses two soul skills from the start.
I’ll not let you end this fight so soon.
Nether Spikes.
Black Turtle Protection Shield.
What is this?
He shrinks into his shell.
Unbelievable, right?
My hand is stuck.
Third soul skill, Dark Water...
Don’t you dare!
Intertwine.
Dark Water Rage.
- He’s trying to isolate my coldness.
- Dai Mu Bai.
Too bad your soul power
is at least ten levels lower than mine.
Oh, really?
White Tiger Protection Barrier.
My body is totally numb with cold.
Intertwine.
Darn it.
White Tiger Protection Barrier.
Oh, no, I’m freezing.
Fatty.
Boss, well done.
I’ll kill you both!
Is it that I’ve made a false judgment?
This Black Turtle is
not a defense type Martial Soul?
These scoundrels...
At this late hour,
why are you out here instead of sleeping?
Go back to sleep now.
Wait.
What’s the matter?
You’re their teacher, right?
Just now, your students
humiliated our school, Cang Hui School.
You need to give us an explanation.
Explanation?
What is there to explain?
Cang Hui School always
bullies the weak and creates troubles.
In my opinion, it’s a sucking school.
You’re really useless.
You can’t even handle a tortoise.
I’ll settle you once we get back to school.
Teacher Zhao,
behind you.
Get back to sleep.
We’ll talk using our strength.
[Soul Land]
You didn’t even use your Martial Soul.
So arrogant.
Teacher.
Beating up people without
using Martial Soul is really enjoyable.
Teacher, are you okay?
You are...
really embarrassing.
I’ll note this down.
After we’re back you’re going
to undergo a special training.
Why didn’t you use
Martial Soul to aid the others just now?
It wasn’t the right moment, I was waiting...
Rong Rong...
was waiting for Mu Bai’s
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Right?
Yes.
Catch him off guard.
Good.
Remember,
once you entered Shrek School,
you’re a team.
Okay,
get back to sleep.
Okay, Teacher Zhao.
Star Dou Forest is much greater
than those forests with reared soul beasts.
We’ll meet Millennium or Decade Millennium..
Soul Beasts at any time.
Upon entering the forest,
you must stay at least twenty meters close to me.
Especially for Ning Rong Rong and Oscar.
Both of you must be careful.
Without my permission,
no one is allowed to attack the soul beast,
understand?
Understand.
Good.
Let’s go.
Mu Bai, Tang San, clear the path.
Stop.
What’s the matter?
There are many low-level soul beasts here.
Let’s take another way.
Soul beast grows slowly.
Let’s avoid them if we can do so.
If we kill or hurt them accidentally,
in just a few years, no more soul beasts
will be here in the forest.
Make sense.
We shall take another way.
One more reason,
If we fight,
the smell of the blood and the sound
may attract powerful soul beasts.
We’d better be careful.
You’re quite knowledgeable.
These are all taught by my master.
Let’s put our guards up.
Watch out. Something is
heading to us in a high speed.
Oscar, Ning Rong Rong, move closer.
I’ll go on the tree to check.
Did you see it?
It seems to be a flying snake.
Flying snake?
What does it look like?
I can’t see it clearly.
It flies closely to the ground,
two or three meters to the ground.
It has a red crown on its head.
What does its tail look like?
Its tail is
shaped like a fan.
It’s a Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent.
Haha.
Oscar, you’re lucky.
But we don’t know how old this snake is.
Watch its direction carefully. Prepare to hunt.
Zhu Qing,
how long is the snake?
What is the color of its wings?
It’s about six to eight meters long.
Wings are pale red.
It’s coming.
[Next Episode]
Stop.
We found this snake first.
Return it to us.
Or else, we’ll not be easy on you.
A battle of soul power? Come on then.