♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
The core of Star Dou Forest is not a forest,
but a lake.
So, you’re the Grandmaster.
It seems you were really lucky this time.
We’re finally back.
Is he the master that you’ve always mentioned
who knows everything?
Next, I’ll guide your cultivation.
Little San, you remove the toxins for Ma Hong Jun.
Believe in yourself.
Do you know about
the externally attached soul bone?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 31]
When did you come?
I came a few days ago and found that
you had entered Star Dou Forest.
You gave me a surprise.
You’ve achieved Level 30 in a short time.
It’s because of your good guidance.
Did I teach you to absorb the soul ring
from a soul beast at unknown age?
No.
How dare you act rashly?
You should know the danger of
Human Faced Demon Spider.
If anything happens to you, how am I
going to explain it to your father?
You are my only disciple.
You’re not allowed to die without my permission.
Do you understand?
Master, I’m sorry.
Little San, you have a very bad weakness.
In the future, it will always bring you problems.
What is it? Tell me and I’ll correct it.
This is your weakness as well as your advantage.
You’re so serious about the feelings,
even greater than your life.
You already knew it?
If it was not because of Xiao Wu,
you wouldn’t be out of your mind and act rashly.
I rebuking you today is to remind you that
at any time and any where,
you must remain calm and think.
Even if someone important to you is in danger,
you need to be calmer in this case.
Only if you save yourself first,
you have the chance to save others.
There are lots of things
that can’t be solved with impulse.
Do you understand?
Master, I got it.
Show me what you’ve gained after this impulse.
Blue Silver Plant has become thinner.
It looks shinier than before.
This faint sweet smell appears
due to the absorption of toxins
from Human Faced Demon Spider.
Little San, wind the tree over there.
Try to pull hard.
Although your Blue Silver Plant is thin,
its toughness is definitely
better than before. It’s good.
Okay, Little San. Come here.
Master, what is it?
Although you took a great risk
for this absorption,
your gain was also great.
Human Faced Demon Spider
has enhanced Blue Silver Plant.
It not only strengthens
the toughness of Blue Silver Plant,
but also its toxin has made
Blue Silver Plant corrosive.
However, I have to remind you again.
Don’t make the same mistake for twice.
I don’t want you to die before me.
Master, I promise.
I’ll never act rashly again.
Okay. Good boy.
Come on. Show me your third soul skill.
The income of Tang Clan mostly relied
on the hidden weapons made by the outer disciples.
The disintegration of parts drawing
can guarantee Tang’s crafts won’t be known.
After experiencing your Godly Zhuge Crossbow,
if available, I wish
to order a batch of machine-like
hidden weapons from you through my clan.
At least I can let my clansmen
have self-protection ability.
If I can start up the business here,
the income shall not be a problem.
In this way,
I just have to find a stable
blacksmith shop to cooperate,
I can concentrate on practicing
and invent more powerful hidden weapons.
The glory of Tang Clan
will definitely reappear on Soul Land.
[Blacksmith Shop]
Look at our forged weapons.
Those are created by one of the best blacksmiths.
May I know is this the biggest
blacksmith shop in Suo Tuo City?
Young Mister, what do you need?
I want to customize a batch of goods.
What do you want to make?
You can just tell me.
I’m afraid you can’t make the decision.
Kid, can you please explain
what is this?
You don’t have to know.
Just tell me if you can do it.
I want 20 sets.
You must use high-grade iron,
preferably refined iron.
Refined iron? It is costly.
Ask your boss to talk to me.
Uncle, are you a soul master?
You are one of them too?
Can we talk privately?
Please come with me.
A strong physique, focused eyes, calm gestures.
It seems that they are experienced blacksmiths.
Why are they here too?
I am Iron Dragon.
I am Iron Tiger.
Be careful!
They are my twin sons, Iron Dragon and Iron Tiger.
Although they’re young,
they also got my authentic skills.
They’re the best blacksmiths in the shop.
If possible, I want them to make these weapons.
If the cooperation is successful,
there’s no problem.
Please.
Well,
how are you going to cooperate with us?
Iron Uncle. How about this?
I will pay 100 gold soul coins as deposit.
Please make one set.
If the quality is all right,
then just proceed to make them.
Money is enough. But I want another guarantor.
Since you’re a soul master,
can you show me your soul master’s card.
Soul master’s card is a symbol of
a soul master’s identity and level records.
It’s as important as a soul master’s dignity.
Normally, it isn’t presented easily.
However, if I want to show my sincerity...
In 2637 of Soul Calendar,
registered at Nuoding City.
Martial Soul Branch Hall.
Martial Soul, Blue Silver Plant.
It’s a useless Martial Soul. What a waste.
Wait. This is...
[Soul Land]
Great Soul Master?
That’s right.
You became a Great Soul Master in only three years.
I got my third soul ring not long ago.
I haven’t had time to register.
So, there’s no record of me
being a Soul Honor in my card.
Three? You have three soul rings?
This child is so young.
Father! I heard that there’s big business!
We meet again, Iron’s Brothers.
It’s you.
Dragon and Tiger, you know Soul Honor Tang San?
Father, do you remember
we lost to two youngsters at the Soul Arena?
One of them was Tang San.
If Tang San had not stopped,
we would have been
seriously injured by his partner.
Tang San, you have reached Level 30?
Are you the one that our worker mentioned
who brought a big business?
Soul Honor Tang San, I’m sorry
for suspecting you before.
I’ll do as you say.
Revive Tang Clan.
Brother! What are you thinking?
I am thinking about our present lives, my father,
and you.
What are you thinking about me?
I am thinking why you reached Level 30 so soon?
You’re only thinking about this.
Of course, not only that.
What else?
Oh, right. You haven’t told me
what Teacher meant by saying an innocent man
gets into trouble because of his ability?
Master told me that
the soul bone on my back is an extremely rare one.
I’ve heard about it.
It’s a thing that appears very rarely
during soul beast hunt, right?
I don’t know specifically.
Master only said that it will only
appear under a special condition.
But no one knows what the special condition is.
The one on my back
is an externally attached soul bone which
is comparable to a premium soul bone.
You can rest assured.
I won’t let anyone snatch your soul bone.
I swear.
I promised you that I would protect you forever.
So, I could also protect myself.
Brother.
Xiao Wu. We would be together forever, right?
Yes.
Little San!
Sounds like Little Ao’s voice.
Rong Rong’s too.
Don’t keep them finding us.
Let’s go, Xiao Wu.
Where did both of you go?
We’ve been looking for you for some time.
We didn’t go any where.
We were just feeling the wind on the cliff.
Just feeling the wind?
Of course.
Oh, I see.
Ma Hong Jun has woken up.
Dean of School said it’s rarely lucky for Shrek
as everyone could return safely
from the Star Dou Forest
and Brother San, Little Ao and Xiao Wu have reached Level 30.
So, he has decided to hold a celebration tonight.
Celebration?
Little monsters.
Enjoy the last night of happy moments!
From tomorrow on,
you’ll be greeted with the life of hell.
Boss Dai, do you want one?
Mr. Zhao.
Do you want one?
Rong Rong.
Super Invincible Sausage!
Little Ao, wake up. It’s time to wake up.
Don’t be noisy. Let me sleep for a while.
Have you forgotten Grandmaster’s words?
I don’t want to see anyone be absent for breakfast.
Otherwise, you will be at your own risk.
It’s so aromatic.
Master.
You are never late. Oscar is here too.
Come on. Try my dishes.
All of you are growing.
You must have sufficient nutrition.
Without a good body,
how are you able to bear a huge soul power?
Thank you, Grandmaster.
Eat while they’re hot.
It’s aromatic. It seems that
there is good food today.
Hello, Grandmaster.
Slow down! Return me my drumstick!
Drumstick!
Today, every one of you has come
for breakfast as promised.
It’s a good start.
But the food needs time for digestion.
You can’t do strenuous exercise immediately.
Next time, I’ll prepare breakfast at 5 a.m..
If you don’t come in 1 hour,
- you aren’t allowed to eat.
- Yes!
Great. Next, I’ll start with
intensive training for you.
Dai Mu Bai, dequeue.
I’ll give you a mission.
From now on, without hurting them,
defeat six of them one by one.
What?
Your soul power is at Level 37.
The highest soul power of them is only at Level 31.
Do you have any problem?
Tang San, dequeue.
You cannot use your third soul skill
and your special weapons.
You can start now.
Wait, Grandmaster. This is unfair.
Tang San’s level is lower than mine.
If you limit his soul skills,
what’s the meaning of battling?
If Tang San uses the third soul skill,
you won’t have any chance.
A soul master of Controlling Branch
is best at one-to-one battling
before meeting any restraining Martial Soul.
But, if you ask for it,
I won’t restrict Tang San’s soul skills.
As partners, you have to know each other well.
[Next Episode] There are no perfect
soul masters in the world.
But there’s a perfect team.
Mu Bai, continue your class today.
Yes, Grandmaster.
Boss Dai! I am not fighting alone.
Is this Little San’s third soul ring?
Let me help you.
Come on!
Xiao Wu, help him fight an opponent.
Okay, Grandmaster.
Xiao Wu disappeared into thin air.
What?