♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
This is Blue Silver Plant.
It’s a century soul ring.
No wonder even the Blue Silver Plant
has such a big change.
Can you tell me...
which soul beast you hunted to get this soul ring?
Datura Snake.
Welcome to the team of soul masters.
From now on,
you’re an honored soul master of Tian Dou Empire.
Brothers.
Our new worker claims he can forge.
Could this be...
the Skill of Random Hammering?
The most powerful continuous hammering skill.
Dad, I’m back.
I’m useless. I can’t help you.
You have to choose your path.
My father has left.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 10]
Little San should be home by now.
Please come in.
Hello, Grandmaster.
You are...
We haven’t seen each other
for about 20 years, right?
I can’t blame you for not recognizing
my current appearance.
I’m Tang Hao.
Tang Hao?
You...
You’re Hao Tian...
Let’s not mention the past designation.
Seems like I was right.
You’re Little San’s father.
He went home. Why are you here?
Exactly because he’s home, that’s why I came here.
I know you took him as your disciple.
I should have come earlier.
I have to go. He’s my only worry.
So I wish to entrust Little San to you.
You’re leaving? To where?
Leave?
No. I’ve decided to come back.
There’s something that I have to do.
He’s your son. How can you just leave him?
He’s your disciple..
I know you’ll take good care of him.
He won’t be happy with me.
He should make his own choice in his life.
Even if it’s an unusual path.
I believe in him.
I don’t know what happened to you.
But I can tell Little San can’t bear to be parted with you.
Don’t you think it’s cruel to him,
if you just leave him?
Being with me is crueler to him.
Okay, that’s all I want to say.
No matter what, please remember that he’s my son.
Xiao Wu, thank you.
What for?
Thank you for accompanying me.
Don’t be upset. Your father left temporarily.
You’ll see each other eventually.
Maybe he left...
so you can grow better...
and be stronger.
If you keep being like this,
aren’t you letting him down?
Perhaps.
But why did he just leave like that?
My father is my only family.
Without him, home is no longer home.
Even without your father,
you have me as your friend.
If you really want a family,
I don’t mind being your older sister.
Call me Sister Wu.
Everyone calls me that, except you.
I think you’re a few months younger than me.
If you’re willing to be
my younger sister, I’m fine with it.
Dream on.
I only want to be the older one, never the younger.
Xiao Wu, come to the mountain with me.
I want to show you something.
Xiao Wu, here’s where I used to practice martial art.
Let me ask you a question.
I hope you can answer me seriously.
Do you know?
Now you look like those old men in the school.
Xiao Wu, are you willing to be my younger sister?
I really hope that I have a family.
I...
I’m just a peasant.
I can give you neither wealth nor power.
But I can give you my promise.
I’ll protect my younger sister forever.
I won’t let her get hurt.
If one day, many people want to kill me,
but you can’t defeat them, what would you do?
They’ll have to kill me first.
[Soul Land]
Brother.
Thank you, younger sister.
Can I not call you older brother?
Why?
I’m the boss of all the students
in Nuoding School after all.
What would they think about me when they
find out I have an older brother?
Okay, you may keep calling me Little San.
As long as I know you’re my younger sister.
This is for you.
What’s that?
Sleeve arrow. It’s also known as silent arrow.
When you pull the trigger,
the small arrows inside will
be launched under your control.
The sound of launching is soft.
It’s barely noticeable.
Why haven’t I seen you using this...
when we fought each other?
Silly girl. How could I use
such a dangerous weapon against you?
Then I should thank you.
Look, there’s a mosquito.
I can hit its left wing, without killing it.
Do you believe it?
Are you kidding me?
This is a hidden weapon.
Even my father doesn’t know about it.
I want to tell you that...
I have the capability to protect
my younger sister.
It looks fun. Can you teach me?
No.
Brother, teach me, please.
With your violent behavior,
if you learned this, many will suffer.
You should first learn
how to use the sleeve arrow.
It’s also a type of hidden weapons.
Hm, ungenerous.
Dad, are you afraid that
I can’t be strong when I’m with you?
Don’t worry. I’ll train hard...
to be a real man.
One day, I’ll be your pride.
Tang Clan, I’ve left you for 6 years.
But I belong to the Tang Clan forever.
Soul Land.
I’ll carry Tang Clan forward here.
[Five years later]
[Tian Dou Empire, Barak Kingdom]
[Suo Tuo City]
We’re finally in the so-called Suo Tuo City.
I don’t know what’s the Grandmaster thinking.
There are several intermediate schools
that want to recruit us unconditionally.
However, he kept asking you to enroll....
in Shrek School, which has no rank at all.
My master told me to enroll here, not you.
Who told you to come along?
Fortunately, Barak Kingdom
is border to Fassnor Province.
Or else you would whine more.
I wonder if Master has arrived in the capital.
Such a heartless one.
I did this for you,
because you’re my brother.
Since the exam is 2 days,
you have to play with me in Suo Tuo City for 2 days,
to make up for the trauma of my tiny soul.
The boss of Nuoding School has a tiny soul?
I’m tired. Let’s find an accommodation.
Alright.
What about here? Rose Hotel.
Up to you.
Please get two rooms for us.
I'm really sorry, we only have one room left here.
Yes only one left.
The Rose Suite.
Then one is fine.
Didn’t we always live in a dorm when we were in Nuoding City?
Okay, please get this room for me.
Wait a moment.
This room should belong to me, right?
Are you new?
You are...
I want to see your manager.
Buddy, I think we came first.
So what?
Nothing. We just want you to get out.
Alright then.
How dare you talk to me like that?
I think you’re soul masters as well.
Come on, the two of you.
I’ll give you a chance to get me out.
Or...
you may show me how to get out.
Mr. Dai, calm down.
Manager Wang, you are getting better in business.
Mr. Dai, don’t say that.
The new staff doesn’t know the rules.
I’m sorry.
The room is reserved by Mr. Dai.
Please go to another hotel.
We’re not giving in. So what?
You snob who looked down at us.
Don’t you think we can be bullied
just because we’re young.
Even if you want to give in, I wouldn’t let you.
Mr. Dai, you...
My guests, please apologize to Mr. Dai. Or else...
Stop the nonsense. I’ll pay for all the loss.
Let me do this.
Why? I’ll do this myself. I want to hit him hard.
I’ve said I would protect you forever.
Stop fighting. As I said,
you two can fight me together.
Be careful.
Please.
[Next Episode]
You’re qualified to be my component.
So fast.
That’s too soon.
Those who break into Tang Clan...
will be killed.