♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
You lost this battle.
If I have only two soul rings, indeed I did lose.
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Is this the millennium soul ring?
Brother.
There isn’t any girl who dislikes roses.
If you’re doing this, how can you get your wife then?
Xiao Wu, I think it’s a mistake to
listen to you and come here.
This is a hair crystal.
But how much is it?
It’s not expensive. 100 gold soul coins.
Okay. I’ll buy it.
That is not enough.
I’m selling it for 200 gold soul coins.
You’re cheating!
Okay, 500 gold soul coins.
No change.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 12]
If you don’t have enough money,
I can only collect 200 gold soul coins first.
You can pay the remaining
for 10 coins monthly with 10% of interest.
10 coins per month?
He knows I’m a soul master.
I didn’t feel the soul power of him.
Little San!
Deal.
Where did you get this belt?
My master gave it to me. Do you know it?
Do you want to change the price again?
You are his student?
Take the crystal with you.
I will send 10 gold soul coins to you every week.
No need. I’ll give it to you for free.
For free?
It wasn’t something valuable. Just go.
Don’t disturb my sleeping.
Does he know Master?
Little San, let’s go!
Xiao Wu.
Uncle, please offer a price.
Grandmaster. Aren’t you going to
hide from me this time?
Hurry up, Xiao Wu.
Hurry up and help me collect
all these golden granules.
Don’t miss even one.
Brother. What on Earth is this crystal?
You look anxious and excited.
This is not an ordinary crystal.
This is a hair crystal.
Hair crystal?
Some crystals will form
golden silk threads inside...
when they are affected by external forces.
These golden silk threads are so resilient
with strong elasticity, so it’s called hair gold.
The crystal that forms hair gold
is called hair crystal.
Hair gold and hair crystal.
What do they do?
This is...
Without the crystal’s protection,
hair gold will curl up to form granules.
It will revert to hair gold
when the soul power is injected.
Then?
I estimate this hair crystal is
at least 100,000 years old.
It’s the best hair crystal, plate crystal.
So, what can they do?
Don’t worry, look.
I still don’t get it.
Do you remember the hidden weapon
that I told you?
Hair gold is thinner and sharper than needle.
Its puncture ability gets more powerful
after soul power is injected.
Its size is small.
Let’s imagine. If it penetrates into the body,
what is the effect if the hair gold
curls up when it losses the soul power?
If this penetrates into a human body...
When the hair gold penetrates
into the human body,
unless using some special tactics,
otherwise, you’ll have to cut off
the muscles that are curled up...
to take it out.
This is a natural hidden weapon.
I call it Dragon Beard Needle.
The eighth in Xuan Tian Records that
is specialized to break the radon.
Brother. This hidden weapon is too vicious.
In this world, it’s not the weapon...
that decides its vice.
It’s up to the person who uses it.
It’ll be good if it’s correctly used.
It’ll be vicious if it’s violated.
If it’s used to punish the wicked,
it will be perfect.
Xiao Wu, you’ve grown up.
It’s not that you can’t walk.
I don’t care. You are my brother.
Didn’t Grandmaster say that...
Shrek School can be seen not far
from the south gate of Suo Tuo?
We have walked so far.
Why aren’t we reaching yet?
I am carrying you on my back.
When did you walk so far?
Why I don’t know it?
Yes. You walked so far.
Brother. Look in front.
[Soul Land]
It’s impossible. This is a soul master school?
Brother. Did Grandmaster make a mistake?
It doesn’t look like a school here. Is this a deceit?
Since we’re here, let’s have a look.
Is anything wrong? This is
the so-called soul master school?
It even claims that students would
be a viscount after graduation.
People from the Martial Soul Hall said it.
It should be right.
But...this school looks really old.
Father, I don’t want to study here.
It’s so embarrassing!
Let me go to Suo Tuo Intermediate
Soul Master School.
I was also considered a genius
in the Beginner School.
Since we’re here, let’s just wait.
Maybe this is a test.
The real school is not located here.
Teacher, here is 10 gold soul coins.
Reach out a hand.
Your age doesn’t match. You can go now.
Teacher, my son has just passed
the age of admission.
Can you please make an exception?
Based on the school rules, admission is
not allowed beyond the age of admission.
You knew it.
Then, our admission fees...
After registration, admission fees
are not refundable.
Not refundable?
You are cheating for money!
Hurry up and go! Don’t affect the people behind.
No way!
You must make refund!
Otherwise, I’m not leaving!
If we know Shrek School is so poor,
we shouldn’t come!
Mu Bai, someone is claiming for
a refund. Settle it.
You can have a refund.
Fully refund if he can win me in a battle.
It’s purple! It’s a millennium one!
We’re so unlucky! Let’s go!
Failed. You can go now.
Why? My son is perfectly good.
He’s an outstanding student in
the Beginner Soul Master School.
Moreover, he has a century soul ring.
It’s rare to own a century soul ring.
It’s good to own one.
But judged from his soul power,
he’s just an ordinary person.
I don’t understand.
When you register at Shrek School,
you should be clear with the rules.
If you come here without figuring it out,
you’re just paying the admission fees for nothing.
It’s still not too late to leave if you regret.
Do you know the meaning of Shrek?
Shrek is a monster.
It’s extremely weird among the soul beasts.
The meaning of Shrek School...
is a monster school.
We only accept “monsters” but not ordinary people.
Anyone who exceeds the age of admission...
or soul power below Level 21,
you don’t have to waste your time here.
Only accept “monsters”?
He is a Soul Emperor?
Next!
This school looks interesting.
Especially when that teacher said...
they only accept “monsters”
but not an ordinary one. Awesome.
Now, you don’t doubt Master’s order, right?
Shrek School must be unusual.
It’s awesome.
Did I pass the preliminary test?
Do your family know you are here?
Instruction knows no class distinction.
As long as I meet the school requirements,
you have no reason to reject my admission.
Come here.
Teacher, the two of us want to register.
Your ages fulfilled.
Did...
Did you learn any soul skill with your hands?
Yes.
Lift your leg.
Muscle growth is good.
Bone age is suitable.
Okay. Release your Martial Soul.
Rabbit.
Yours is Blue Silver Plant.
You can practice so fast with Blue Silver Plant.
Teacher.
Don’t you only accept monster?
Am I a monster?
Yes, you are.
Mu Bai. Take them in.
Yes.
Come on. Follow me.
Thank you.
It’s nothing.
What?
Nothing.
What are you looking at?
Any girls do you want to tackle?
I felt something just now.
This feeling seems to be supplementary
with my Martial Soul.
Supplementary?
That’s an excuse.
You must take a fancy to a girl.
You know nothing.
In Martial Soul,
it’s hard to find a supplementary Martial Soul.
If you find it and team up,
the strength of Martial Soul
will increase exponentially.
This is called Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
That means...
that girl’s Martial Soul must be a tigress.
Maybe.
You will undergo the second exam here.
The teacher will tell you what to do.
I need to go out and check.
Sausages! Sausages for sale!
Have a look! Oscar sausage!
Delicious and affordable!
There’s also pure and refreshing green tea!
[Sausages for sale]
[Next Episode]
Where is my sausage?
What happened?
Doesn’t the sausage taste good?
Silly.
What is this?
Why can they skip the test
to enter the fourth exam?
Tang San. Show them your soul power.
Teacher Zhao. I bring them here
to undergo the fourth exam.