♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] I heard that you knew
the reason why my father
went into seclusion.
Martial Soul Hall.
If that isn’t a dream, Martial Soul Hall...
I’ll never let go those who killed my parents.
It’s all because of our greedy dean,
he could do anything for money.
Qibao Amber Tribe should have a skill
named Heart Separation Control, right?
I want to return a favour too.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 71]
Theoretically,
what His Royal Highness has said is correct.
The point lies in what exactly the secret item is.
Why did Martial Soul Hall turn all out for it?
Yet they returned with nothing,
and even might lose their pope.
Could it be a soul bone?
The most precious thing for every soul master
must be the soul ring and soul bone.
Soul ring is exclusively specified,
it can’t be taken.
But a soul bone can.
No, if it’s the soul bone,
Martial Soul Hall wouldn’t lose.
Even though your father is powerful,
it’s impossible to fight alone
against Martial Soul Hall.
In fact, apart from the pope
of Martial Soul Hall,
there’re at least
three Grand Soul Land Masters.
I think if they didn’t insist
on getting the secret item,
it’s either damaged
or has lost its function.
Lost its function? Could it be a soul beast?
But how could a soul beast
be related to your father?
Putting aside how high the level of
a soul beast drew their attention,
it’s impossible a soul beast
would be with your father,
due to the unresolved conflict
between human and soul beasts.
Your father wouldn’t have offended
Martial Soul Hall for a soul beast either.
Your analysis makes sense.
Father,
I’d have known the truth,
if only I could meet you again?
Brother San, I knew my father will
certainly agree.
Little San, Heart Separation Control
isn’t a secret skill.
If it’s useful, you could learn it
together with Rong Rong.
How could such a modest skill compare with
your contribution to Qibao Amber Tribe?
Ning Feng Zhi.
I think no one dares to mock us any more.
From now on, those humiliations will vanish.
I suggest you concede defeat in the next competition.
Ah?
I’ve been observing your opponents these days.
Your opponents...
Now, you have three choices.
First, give up this battle
and preserve your strength.
Second, go with the previous formation.
But you have less than 1% of chance to win.
Third, compete with
the best key members of your team.
However, your strength might be revealed
if your team win.
Master, who exactly are our opponents?
Why are you so anxious?
Your opponents are
from Elephant Armoured Tribe.
What? That strongest defensive tribe?
Shrek School.
Only through your fiasco
could glorify Martial Soul Hall.
It’s the Elephant Armoured Tribe
who ranked the sixth
among the seven great tribes.
No, I’m afraid it could be higher than the sixth,
if there’s one
Grand Soul Land Master from this tribe.
It’s said that Chief Huyan Zhen
isn’t merely the Great Soul Land Master,
his defence is stronger than
others from his level.
The hereditary martial soul of
Elephant Armoured Tribe
is Diamond Mammoth.
It’s a super soul with supreme defence.
Mainly on strength and defence.
Your opponents are
the direct disciples of this tribe.
Three of the seven are at Level 40,
While the rest are almost reaching it.
I suggest you all give up this competition
for the ultimate victory.
After all,
top five qualifiers can enter the finals.
It’s nothing wrong
to conceal your strength in the early period.
But if they give up, my advertising fee...
Brother, stop being greedy!
If these little devils got injured
in this competition,
it’ll be hard to handle in future competitions.
Are you aware of it?
You guys make the decision then.
We’ll fight!
Master, we know what you’re saying.
However, we’re competing not only for victory,
but also to train ourselves.
If we keep out those strong rivals,
we can’t progress.
And it’s not worth being
the monster students of Shrek School.
I reckon, we must think of new tactics
and agility in duelling with them.
[Soul Land]
Why did Huyan Zhen come here too?
You’ll know when you see
Elephant Armoured School’s opponents.
Salas invited Huyan Zhen here
maybe because of them.
That’s the chief of Elephant Armoured Tribe,
Huyan Zhen, the Heavenly Elephant.
Could it be Martial Soul Hall?
It should be.
Among the seven great tribes,
Qibao Amber Tribe from Upper Three
always supports Tian Dou Empire.
Hao Tian Tribe secretly supports
Xing Luo Empire.
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe
stays neutral.
Meanwhile, Lower Four are closed
to Martial Soul Hall.
Even they aren’t its subordinates,
they’re on the same boat.
The reason why Martial Soul Hall
is regarded as the strongest among all
and even can compete
with the two empires
is due to the support of Lower Four.
How interesting this
Soul Master Elite Tournament is.
Feng Zhi, you’ve predicted Shrek Seven Devils
will be the great soul masters.
Today, they’re going to duel
with Elephant Armoured Tribe.
Do you still think so?
Why not?
Elephant Armoured Tribe’s flaw
is as obvious as their strength.
With Tang San’s wisdom
and superb guidance from Master,
they’re in no doubt to win
if they fight all out.
Wait, they’re...
Let’s welcome Shrek School Team and
Elephant Armoured School Team.
Captain Dai Mu Bai and
Vice Captain Tang San from Shrek School.
These two soul sects participated
in the first preliminary round.
Their results are excellent.
These three soul honors are familiar faces too.
But they seem to be lower ranked
than Elephant Armoured School.
I wonder how they will make up for each other.
Here comes the new member, Zhu Zhu Qing...
She’s a soul sect too.
From Keen Attack Branch, at Level 41.
Two yellow and two purple soul rings.
Shrek School has four soul sects.
[Tool soul sect from Food Branch]
This is beyond our expectation.
In the last round,
three members from Shrek Seven Devils.
We now sent out five members for this round.
Zhu Qing replaces Tai Long.
Little Ao replaces Jiang Zhu.
It won’t reveal our full strength,
and yet we’ll have the chance to win.
Good. Very targeting strategy.
Little San, why didn’t you send me to duel?
Our opponents are defence and
strength type of soul masters.
At least, I can help to block them head-on.
I’m confident in my ability to resist attack.
He didn’t intend to fight head on,
that’s why he lets Zhu Qing
takes over your position.
Little San, you’ve done the strategy, right?
They didn’t perform their full strength,
when facing such strong opponents
like Elephant Armoured Tribe.
Are they too naive to be fearless
or are they too confident?
Let’s take a look at
Elephant Armoured School Team’s data.
Captain of Elephant Armoured
School Team, Huyan Li.
War soul sect from Defence Branch,
at Level 43.
Two yellow and two purple soul rings.
He’s young and talented.
Let’s look forward to his performance.
The following are two soul sects, at Level 41.
Two yellow and two purple
soul rings as well.
There are three soul sects
in this team of seven members.
It’s really worthy of Elephant Armoured School.
Four soul honours almost reaching Level 40.
This is a robust team.
Their opponents should watch out.
Seven soul masters of defence type
build up a strong fortress.
Will they keep their opponents at bay today?
It seems like the battle between them
aren’t coincidental.
He suppresses Shrek
since he failed to recruit them.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I just found something interesting.
Shrek School Team has changed the uniform.
But who knows whether their luck
will disappear with their previous uniform.
This game must be exciting.
Please don’t miss it.
Huyan Li, captain of
Elephant Armoured School Team.
War soul sect from Defensive Branch, at Level 43.
Please.
Dai Mu Bai,
captain of Shrek School Team.
War soul sect from Defensive Branch, at Level 44.
Please.
Elephant Armoured Tribe!
Shrek fighting! Shrek victory!
Both teams, initiate your martial soul!
Martial soul.
Diamond Mammoth.
Preliminary second round, first match.
Shrek School versus Elephant Armoured School,
officially begins!
First soul skill, Impregnable Fortress.
[Next Episode]
Brother, should we use that skill?
Set up the fort.
Retreat.
Bring Tang San out!
Trigonal Defence, please.
Great! Right now!