♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Brat, are you new?
Are you convinced now?
No!
I’ll beat you till you concede.
There’s some soul power left here.
What kind of treasure is it
that those won’t hesitate to kill
the guards of the auction house.
Could it be a soul bone?
Stop there.
Bidding qualification certificate?
We’ll sell this then.
I named it Malicious Attack.
Could you please show me?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 56]
I’m afraid this steel plate is unbearable.
You may not believe...
this steel plate has been tested
over a hundred times.
It’s sturdy and has never been damaged.
Don’t worry.
Please.
What a powerful weapon.
It might be weaker than Godly Zhuge Crossbow,
but such piercing force isn’t resistible
by ordinary soul masters.
Malicious Attack can shoot 3 times
when it’s fully loaded with steel needles.
Every shooting associates with poisonous mist.
A needle itself contains a paralytic toxin.
Even those above Level 30 would be
tackled if they can’t resist poison.
Honored guest, I’ve ever seen
such a refined weapon.
I’ll put this lot starting at
1,000 gold soul coins.
What do you think?
1,000 gold soul coins?
No problem.
Are we qualified to join
the auction now?
Certainly.
Thank you for coming.
There may be some peculiar treasures in this auction.
I think so.
Wear a mask before entering the auction.
For your safety purpose.
35,000.  35,000 gold soul coins in the white area.
36,000 gold soul coins in the yellow area.
Any higher bid?
36,000 first, 36,000 twice, 36,000...
37,000 gold soul coins in the red area.
This way, please.
What arrogance.
Let’s go.
The attendants all behave in the same manner,
she’s not against you.
In the same manner? What do you mean?
They were bought by the auction house
for training since they were young.
They’re not only the attendants here,
but as a lot for auction too.
They have no expression,
because they’ve lost their thoughts
and soul.
Is that slavery?
But the slave trade has been
banned in two empires.
Nothing can’t be sold here.
How much do they cost?
You want to buy them and release them?
That’s another tragedy though.
Why?
They’re like caged birds
who have no choice but staying here.
They have no survival skills,
neither thought nor soul.
How could they survive after leaving here?
They’ll end up in disillusion and perish.
Soul guiding tool at 43,000 gold soul coins. Sold!
You came to the auction house at this young age,
do you have anything to buy?
We’re not buying, but selling.
The next lot up for auction
is a rare item.
Please draw your attention here,
especially male guests.
It’s a nonpareil among all.
Can anyone give a guess?
It may be a rare treasure.
Well.
I’ll first reveal the starting price of this lot.
100,000 gold soul coins.
Every increase of the bid is not
less than 10,000 gold soul coins.
My honored guests, please pay attention.
Perhaps you may be curious about
why this girl
has the same price as our beauty
fostered by the auction house.
She’s extraordinary if you look carefully.
You’re right, this is a precious cat lady.
Her body mutated when her martial soul awakened.
Hence, she possesses a cat’s figure.
It’ll be extremely great
having a gorgeous cat lady as a pet.
My guests, you can bid now.
Bastards, how can they sell her as a pet?
Even if you’re able to save this cat lady now,
there will be a panther lady or a tigress lady.
Are you going to save them all?
It’s meaningless to save
those who’ve lost their soul.
How could I not save one with soul?
110,000 gold soul coins.
120,000 gold soul coins.
110,000 gold soul coins from this side.
170,000. A gentleman bids for
170,000 gold soul coins from red area.
Any more for it?
I fathom your thoughts.
Ah! 180,000 gold soul coins from the white area.
Let’s me see who dares to fight with me.
[Soul Land]
Aren’t they the Qibao Amber Tribe?
Auction house has its own rules.
Can we continue?
Sure, of course.
180,000 gold soul coins, twice.
Last call.
Sold!
Thank you, Uncle.
It’s a worthwhile trip.
Let’s see the last lot.
Dad, please return. It’s our matter.
You’re making me even more embarrassed.
How could I tolerate that my son got beaten?
I don’t deserve to be called
the Supreme God, Tai Nuo.
I come to see
who dares to beat my son.
Dad, you’re making me difficult.
How am I supposed to staying in this school later?
Your school didn’t even care that you’re beaten.
When I catch that brat,
I’ll have your teacher to judge.
Well, Dad. It’s me starting the fight.
Nothing to do with Tang San.
So embarrassing! Picking up the duel
and yet got beaten by him?
You’ve disgraced me!
Tang San!
Brother, isn’t that our Malicious Attack?
Malicious Attack? Good name.
This lot is an intricate weapon.
Small size, yet it’s potent.
Instantly launch of 36 steel needles
and conceal with mist.
Within 15 meters,
it can pierce through a 1cm thick steel plate.
It’s also quenched with a paralytic toxin.
We’ll start at 1,000 gold soul coins.
It’s in my interest.
10,000 gold soul coins appears now.
Uncle, did you make a mistake?
I can’t let you make a loss.
Perhaps no one will come to bid
after I increased the price.
10,000 gold soul coins, once.
10,000 gold soul coins, twice.
Last call. Sold!
You spent 10,000 gold soul coins
on my Malicious Attack.
I won’t let you have a loss too.
This Soundless Arrow is also for you.
Tang Clan? I’ve never heard of it before.
My brother is the only one of Tang Clan.
That’s why you’ve not heard of it.
You created these two weapons?
If possible,
I’d like to purchase them in large quantity.
Purchase in large quantity?
Do you think I’m making fun of it?
I’ll bring you to visit my tribe
if you’re interested.
Thanks for your goodwill.
But we have some matters today.
We’ll meet again.
Well. Certainly.
Xiao Wu, let’s go.
Tribe Chief, it’s time to return.
All right. Let’s go, Uncle Sword.
Tai Long, are you still not convinced?
Why are you rolling your eyes?
The two of you, who’s Tang San?
I am.
It’s you little brat!
You’re Tai Long’s father?
Yes, I’m the Supreme God, Tai Nuo.
Give me an explanation,
since you beat my son.
Tai Long, if we also beat your father up,
is your grandfather coming too?
Xiao Wu, please don’t take it wrong.
Dad came because he saw my injuries...
But if my grandpa comes, it’d be worse.
You troublesome woman.
I’ll sort you out after settling this brat.
How dare you insult Xiao Wu?
He’s powerful.
He didn’t even use his soul power.
Let me see how many bouts you can take?
Muscle Twisting Bone Grinding.
It’s rare he can resist my attack head-on.
The scary thing is his powerful strength.
Supreme Orangutan.
Brat, are you scared?
I’ll dislocate your legs first
before getting your teacher to judge.
I’ll make you never dare to beat my son again.
Raise your fist to me.
Father fights for his injured son.
Fine.
First soul skill, Boost.
[Next Episode]
Rong Rong, please don’t lie to Dad.
Dad, you didn’t trust me.
Qibao Amber Pagoda
is the strongest martial soul of Support Branch,
but it has a major flaw.
I really want to know what kind of a genius
your Brother San is.
If he’s really outstanding,
he may be our grandson-in-law.
So strong.
Fourth soul skill, Power Slam.