♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven freaks combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode] It’s important
to understand the nature
and prescription of these herbs.
Dugu Bo, where’s Tang San?
How dare you challenge me?
Sun Moon Golden Shine!
There’s even a trinity Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
Too bad, you’re still too weak.
Break!
Yes, we might not worth to be your opponent.
However, do you dare to offend our tribe?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 50]
Even if I can’t defeat the dragon from your tribe,
but if I kill all of you,
your family won’t have any proof to accuse me.
It’s just a piece of cake for me
to get rid of your bodies.
You’re right.
But Frander has nothing to do with our tribe.
It’s fine if you kill us,
can you spare his life?
Even if he goes alone
and tells about us to the tribe,
they might not believe him either.
Er Long, what are you talking about?
Am I a coward?
Just cut the talk and kill me.
I still want to be the matchmaker
for you both, when I was in the underground.
What’s wrong if the Golden Iron Triangle
dies together?
Frander, are you out of your mind?
Hurry and leave,
it’s not the time to show off.
I’ve lived more than half of my life,
it’s fine even if I die now.
Er Long, even though you have no feelings for me,
but in my heart, you’re as important
as how important Xiao Gang means to you.
To me,
I have no regret if I can die with you both.
But Little San will be left alone.
Dugu Bo, I don’t mind letting you know it.
You can’t afford to offend Little San’s father.
If we’re not back today,
my men will look for him.
He’s even more powerful than
the Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe.
Oh, where does he come from then?
People whom I can’t afford to offend,
there’s only few in this world.
Now I’m curious, who’s his father?
Someone with the surname Tang,
and you can’t afford to offend,
who else on this land can he be?
Tang San. That man is also Tang, could it be...
That’s impossible.
His Martial Soul is only Blue Silver Plant.
That’s right, what you see
is only Blue Silver Plant.
What if he has two Martial Souls?
What? Twin Martial Souls?
You’re right.
If that so,
the safest thing to do now
is to kill the three of them
and go back to check if Tang San is dead.
In case he’s still alive, I should kill him too.
That person, indeed I can’t afford to offend him.
But as long as remove the traces leave here,
it won’t be easy for him to find me.
How dare you, Dugu Bo!
Little San?
Of course, I do. What can you do to me?
Purple Demon Eye. Ghostly Trace.
Soul bone of Eight Spiders.
Little San, you’re alright?
Don’t worry, Master. I’m fine.
His attached soul bone has changed.
Just right, I can kill them all and save my trip.
Senior Dugu,
didn’t you promise to do three things for me?
Alright, from now on,
you’ll never hurt anyone related to Shrek School.
Sorry to make you worried, Master.
Actually, Senior Dugu means no harm
for taking me here.
He realized my talent
and wished to teach me something
about Poison Martial Soul.
Why did you start a fight with him?
He said he had killed you.
He was just kidding.
With his nobleness and high status,
why would he kill me as I’m unknown?
Oh, Senior Dugu.
You wanted to tell me about
your granddaughter’s poison, right?
I think there’re still ways
to cure her poison.
I’ll discuss with you later on, alright?
He has already found a way
to cure my granddaughter’s poison?
Well, since you’re still alive,
I’ll let you all go for now.
Great.
Your disciple is quite extraordinary.
Frankly speaking, I would like him
to be my successor.
Normally, I don’t need to explain myself.
But I’m going to do it once today,
just for this kid.
I just wanted to figure out
whether you’re qualified to be his teachers.
You did well.
Master, you may go back first.
I wish to learn from Senior Dugu for a while.
What do you think?
Well...
What? Worried about him?
Or you’re afraid that I might steal your disciple?
Don’t worry.
Since you all are qualified,
I won’t take him from you.
It’ll take not more than a year,
and I promise he’ll be back to you safe and sound.
I, Grand Venom Master, mean my words.
Since you said so,
whatever happened just now
was just a misunderstanding.
I apologize for being repulsive.
It’s his honor that Little San can learn from you.
Take this medicine and you won’t
be affected by my poison formation.
Alright then. We shall be leaving now.
We’ll come and visit you another day.
The brighter the color is,
the more poisonous it’ll be.
Kid, what have you eaten?
Don’t blame me for not telling you
the herbs here are more powerful
than the normal ones outside.
With a potion,
it might cause death too.
Old Freak, you’re worried about me?
Don’t you always want me to die?
That’s right. If you fail my test, I’ll still kill you.
Old Freak, you just promised my teachers
that I would be back to them safe and sound.
Indeed.
But I can keep a corpse safe too.
You!
Xiao Gang, do you think Dugu Bo
is willing to teach Little San?
There must be a problem.
Dugu Bo seemed afraid of Little San.
But, no matter what,
Little San should be safe for now.
Or else Dugu Bo wouldn’t easily let us go.
Especially when he already knew Little San’s identity.
He would ask for trouble
if he still dares to hurt him.
Let’s hope so.
[Soul Land]
Time’s up.
Are you ready for my test?
Bring it on.
Are you sure?
Old Freak, the venom from
Jade Phosphor Serpent is nothing to me.
Forget it.
Hurry up and move on to the second test.
Second test.
Let it try a bite that bleeds.
You’re really evil.
This is the Bamboo Emerald,
the best from the Trimeresurus family.
Once poisoned by it,
in less than three hours,
one will turn into pus and die.
Its body is even harder than steel,
so basically nothing can harm it.
The Fragrant Silk Woven Flower
can only block poison from outside.
Once the poison enters the blood,
the flower is useless towards it.
Are you afraid?
Bring it on.
But, Senior Dugu,
if it bites me and I’m fine,
can you give this Bamboo Emerald to me?
I think you’re a Little Freak too.
Alright, I promise you.
Kid, if you know this Bamboo Emerald,
don’t you know its poison?
Forget it, if I don’t cure him now,
he’s going to lose his life.
What?
That’s right, Senior Dugu.
Do you think I’ve passed
your second test?
Also, this Bamboo Emerald belongs to me now.
Wait.
Kid, how did you do that?
Senior Dugu,
let’s finish the third test first.
You’re really something.
Tang San, think it over.
Even I myself can’t control the next poison.
You can still back out now before it’s too late.
Dugu Bo’s body is soaked with poison
of the level of Jade Phosphor Serpent King.
It’s indeed difficult to block it
in my situation now.
No, as a disciple in Tang Clan,
if I can’t handle the poison,
I don’t deserve to be in the clan.
Let’s try the pollen of
the Fragrant Silk Woven Flower.
Bring it on.
Are you sure?
Even though the pollen can’t
block the poison in my body,
it’s still able to slow down the attack.
With the Octa Dark Frost
and Fiery Soft Apricot in my body,
as long as I use the Xuan Tian Strike
to enhance my blood circulation,
it’ll stimulate the drug effect.
Why am I doing this to him?
If he dies here,
it’ll be really troublesome.
Wait.
Hao Tian Hammer?
Both his Martial Soul and attached soul bone
have changed after he came here.
He must have eaten something.
Luckily, Dugu Bo doesn’t plan to kill me,
he only cast a small amount of poison.
Thank you for having mercy on me.
What herb have you eaten here?
You can even block the poison
of the Jade Phosphor Serpent King.
After you brought me here yesterday,
I thought about it again and again,
so I consumed the Octa Dark Frost
and Fiery Soft Apricot.
What’s that?
Those are the poisonous plant
at both sides of the water spring
which grow by absorbing the Yin and Yang auras.
Those two are edible?
That’s right. Both are highly poisonous plants,
if any ordinary person is ten meters near them,
they would be frozen or turned into ashes
in less than three hours.
Don’t even mention about eating them.
But, since both fire and ice restrict each other,
when these two extreme herbs
are consumed together,
they’ll neutralize and reduce the toxicity.
That’s also the only chance to consume them.
After consuming them,
I used some special ways to absorb the herbs,
so I’m immune to your poison.
Great. Immune, you say?
That was how you cured the three poison just now?
Sort of.
The herb effects must have not
been fully absorbed by this kid.
If I drink his blood, maybe...
Old Freak, after you brought me here,
I finally know why you’re still alive
as you’re soaked with poison.
It’s because of the Ice Fire Mouth Spring, but...
But what?
the reason I ate the Fiery Soft Apricot
and Octa Dark Frost
is not just that simple.
It’s to make sure I can survive in this place.
When these two herbs are combined,
it’s equivalent to a mini
Ice and Fire Mouth Spring.
I have two ways to cure the poison in your body.
Either you eat these two herbs simultaneously,
then use your enormous soul power
to absorb the herbs,
but at the same time,
your poison power will also be neutralized.
Are you willing to do so?
[Next Episode]
This Old Freak is going to fall into my trap.
He does not dare to put a test
on his poison abilities.
As long as you don’t play tricks,
Alright, Little Freak. Let’s wait and see.
Brother.
I can guarantee even if you’re hit by it,
you’ll not stay alive within three breaths.
Look carefully.
This...