♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I hereby announce,
the battle between Shrek School
and Xing Luo Imperial School
begins now.
Jiubao Boosts! Second, Speed!
Nether Slash.
Ghost Shadow Doppelganger.
White Tiger Meteor Strike.
Unbelievable.
Xiao Wu at Level 40 has knocked out
Dai Wei Si at Level 49.
Oh, no, Dai Wei Si disappeared.
Rong Rong, watch out.
Little Ao saved me. But he...
You’re the next.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 98]
You’re the next.
Purple Demon Eye. Mental Shock.
Brother.
Little San could obviously avoid this strike.
If he would have avoided it,
he wouldn’t attack Dai Wei Si in surprise.
Little San is...
Shrek has attacked generously unexpectedly.
But Dai Wei Si did some harm.
With his power alone,
he has greatly harmed Shrek Battle Team.
Who will be the key to breaking the ice next?
Brother.
I’m fine. In terms of mental shock,
Purple Demon Eye won’t lose
in both power and speed.
Little San. Next,
handle Dai Wei Si and Zhu Zhu Yun to us.
Two of three participants
from Shrek School, who were attacked,
are unconscious.
As for Xing Luo Imperial School,
there are also two who are unconscious.
Martial Soul Fusion. White Tiger of Netherworld.
Victory belongs to us.
It belonged and still belongs to us.
Third soul skill, Constraint of Spider Web.
Oh, no. My soul power isn’t enough.
Why are they attacking Little San suddenly?
Master San.
Ghostly Trace.
Fourth soul skill, Unfettered Invisibility.
Mu Bai.
Dai Wei Si, your target is here.
Rong Rong, can you take it?
Little Ao.
Two White Tigers of Netherworld.
I didn’t expect
Dai Wei Si and Zhu Zhu Yun,
who were badly injured,
to still be strong.
Which White Tiger of Netherworld
will be the winner?
The crucial time of victory and defeat is here.
Zhu Qing.
Today, my second brother died.
Because of your eldest brother?
I must leave.
You chose to escape?
If this is the fate I must face,
why shouldn’t I do things I want to do,
before that fate arrives?
Zhu Qing, you may think I’m a coward,
I may not come back,
but so what?
To Xing Luo Empire,
I’m just a chess piece.
To Soul Land’s millions of years of history,
Xing Luo Empire is nothing.
You want to escape? Coward.
Get back.
I hate you.
[Soul Land]
You’re missing him again?
He’s gone for a long time.
Third Sister, I’ve decided to look for him.
Are you insane?
I can’t move on from him.
Do you know
once you leave,
how many assassinations you’ll face
in this long journey?
I know.
Even if you arrive in Tian Dou Empire safely,
he may have changed.
I still won’t regret it.
Mu Bai, I’ll hold on till the end.
Zhu Qing, I’ll not disappoint you again.
Hang on. I’ll be in Tian Dou Empire soon.
I can never lose.
Even if I die in this battle, I can’t lose.
Mu Bai.
What’s up? Just like back then,
you’re hit until you can’t resist anymore.
White Tiger of Netherworld from Shrek School
is greatly injured
by Xing Luo Imperial School.
Can he get up and keep fighting?
Since I’ve made a promise,
I’ll honour it no matter how hard it is,
even if I have to pay the price with my life.
Zhu Qing.
You’re rather brave. But you’re asking for death.
Look. What is that?
What’s going on?
White Tiger of Netherworld
from Shrek School has grown wings.
It’s flying.
Unbelievable.
He has grown wings under the pressure.
Shrek School is getting
more and more surprising.
Such a situation
has never appeared
in previous Elite Tournaments.
Unbelievable.
White Tiger of Netherworld has wings?
Zhu Qing realized Mu Bai’s pledge of life,
so she took the first step.
Although Dai Wei Si can’t counterattack in time,
he could have dodged.
It seems his White Tiger
of Netherworld has low mental strength.
Does it have anything to do with
Little San’s mental shock on Dai Wei Si?
Curse you.
He has a couple of bone fractures.
Yet he can keep fighting?
White Tiger of Netherworld Breakthrough.
The speed of White Tiger
of Netherworld Breakthrough,
in addition to the advantage of flying,
it seems Mu Bai has the hope to win.
It seems the victory and defeat
could obviously be told.
Once I hit her with this strike, she’ll die.
Back then, I would like to
kill her for countless times.
But now I realize,
the hatred is just the desire to defeat her.
We haven’t surrendered.
[Next Episode]
I didn’t expect you to be so strong.
Well done.
Today, two of the three seeded schools,
Tian Dou Imperial School
and Martial Soul Hall School,
will fight to tell who’s better.
When two heroes fight,
who will be the better one?
Yu Tian Heng, you’re unworthy
to be my opponent.
You knew about it, right?
Perhaps, I wouldn’t die.
But my soul power will be scrapped,
and I’ll be imprisoned for life.