♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I’ll play with you guys today.
You aren’t strong enough, little girl.
Let me show you my power then.
You’re still not strong enough.
Xiao Wu.
Twenty-Four Moonlight Bridges.
Teacher Zhao, beware.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 15]
Good monkey, you’re really keen.
This is how you want to buy time.
It won’t be so easy.
Increase gravity.
What a strong soul skill.
Where can you run?
Dangerous.
I’ll surely take this child.
But this exam should end now.
What does this mean?
It’s about to end, little monkey.
Could this be Teacher Zhao’s...
This is my fourth soul skill.
You won’t be able to escape,
Why is there scent of honey?
Orientated pursue.
Second soul skill of Blue Silver Plant.
Parasitic Haunted Vine.
It’s the Haunted Vine.
It grew from inside of the body.
Could this be...
Haunted Vine is
a century soul beast,
but its toughness surpasses
those of thousand years old.
Perhaps Teacher Zhao can’t set himself free so easily.
It’s so strong.
It’s poisonous.
Here’s a good chance.
You...
Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
Fifth soul skill, Gravity Squeeze.
Decade Millennium Soul Skill is so scary.
You can use my skill to strike back.
In such a passive condition,
Tang San can strike back all of a sudden.
What a stunning speed.
You want castrate me? That’s too much.
Are you a hedgehog?
Such a small hammer. I’ll give you a lesson.
Thank you.
Oscar, come here. There’s business for you.
Boss Dai, are you asking for me?
Make us some sausages. They’re injured.
No problem. Five copper soul coin each.
Don’t forget to pay me.
Super Recovery Big Sausage.
Eat it. Although the way he talks is disgusting,
his sausage has great effect.
This will increase the speed of your recovery.
I’m not badly injured, just a little exhausted.
I’ll just need some rest.
Give the sausage to the others.
Oscar,
come here.
Sausage，
little sausage
give me one each.
Who are you?
Why are you in Shrek School?
You even know my name.
Rotter,
are you looking for trouble?
I’m Zhao Wu Ji.
It’s really embarrassing today.
Tasty Little Sausage.
Don’t worry.
I’ll not let you eat his sausages.
How could I?
Teacher Zhao,
did we pass?
[Soul Land]
Yes, you passed.
Hmm.
Teacher Zhao,
hold on.
Little hedgehog,
what’s up?
You’ve passed my test.
Teacher Zhao,
sorry.
I was too reckless.
But your capability is too strong to me.
I have no choice but to give it all in.
Let me help you remove the hidden weapons in you.
Or else,
it may affect your body.
Mu Bai.
You arrange accommodation for them.
The class starts tomorrow.
Don’t touch these weapons
on the floor that Tang San left.
They’re poisonous.
Have him tidy them up when he’s awake.
What’s going on with Teacher Zhao today?
Why is he mad with the new students?
I dare you to speak louder,
so that Teacher Zhao hears it.
He must be very angry now.
Who would he vent it to?
Let’s help them settle down first.
Why are you guys carrying the beauties,
yet I’m carrying a man?
Because you’re Uncle Sausage.
Ah!
I’m really unfortunate
to meet such a little hedgehog.
If it was back then...
Ah...
No more about the past.
It seems
I have to teach him well.
One must be put through the mill
to be successful.
Zhao Wu Ji.
Who is it?
Come out.
I know you’re here.
Who are you?
Meeting Acala in such an insignificant place.
I haven’t stretched for awhile.
I want to fight with you.
The Grand Soul Land Master.
May I know which senior is here?
Stop fooling around with me.
During the day,
didn’t you have fun
bullying those kids?
I realize
that it must feel great to bully someone.
Let me bully you as well.
Of course.
You may think that
I’m bullying the weak.
Who is this person?
Since you are here,
just show up.
One or two,
there’s no difference.
Boss,
this senior...
Greetings, Lord Hao Tian.
Save the courtesy.
I came to look for trouble.
Martial Soul of Owl,
Level 78.
You’re indeed the main attacker
of Golden Iron Triangle, Frander.
Is Shrek School yours?
Yes,
my Lord.
How did Zhao Wu Ji offend you, my Lord?
Can you forgive him for my sake?
Stop the nonsense.
Stand aside.
Or I will hit you as well.
Zhao Wu Ji,
I’ll give you a chance.
I’ll not use any Martial Soul.
If you can withstand for half an hour,
I’ll leave right away.
Or else,
you’ll have to do something for me.
Lord Hao Tian.
I don’t understand how I offended you.
Can you
clear this up, please?
So...
I can die knowing why.
Ha!
Do I even need to explain?
You hit the young one.
The older one will of course ask for justice.
This is an unquestionable principle.
Let’s begin.
Ah...
[Next Episode]
It’s my fault yesterday.
I didn’t protect you well.
The teacher was too powerful.
How can I blame you?
No.
Don’t.
Stop it.
Please stop disturbing this lady.
Who do you think you are?
You’re also a soul master.
No wonder you dare to interrupt me.
I’ll show you what’s actual strength.