♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
A battle of soul power?
Come on then.
I admit that I lost.
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent is yours now.
I’ll show you my third soul skill.
Don’t be frightened.
Flying?
I have also reached Level 30 just now.
Teacher Zhao,
can we stay on...
to search for a suitable soul beast for me?
Little San.
You’re really the best
among the Shrek’s monsters.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 24]
This is...
King of Forest, Titan Giant Ape.
Titan Giant Ape is like the overlord
of the soul beasts.
It has the same wisdom as human.
Its strength, speed, attack and defense...
are almost flawless.
Even if it’s only at a century level,
it can also battle with soul beasts
at decade millennium years old.
The most terrifying is...
they can also use similar skills
like our soul skills.
This is the soul beast
standing at the top of the pyramid.
It is also a nightmare for all soul masters.
This Titan Giant Ape looks so strong.
Its cultivation is obviously
over ten thousand years.
Probably, no soul beast can compare...
with this terrifying king.
It should have existed
in the core of the Star Dou Forest.
Why does it appear here?
Dear King of the Forest.
We don’t mean to offend.
If this is your territory, we’ll get out at once.
Titan Giant Ape understand human language.
Hope it is not malicious.
Is it like Little San said...
the indiscriminate killing...
has created soul beasts’ hatred towards human?
What shall we do?
Mu Bai, bring them out! Hurry up!
Strength enhancement!
Little San, you cover them and leave.
White Tiger Vajra Transformation!
You guys go first! I’ll help them!
Qibao has its name!
First name, strength!
Second name, speed!
The amplification of Qibao Amber Pagoda
ignores the base of soul power.
Mu Bai is at Level 37.
By increasing 30% of its strength and speed,
So does Teacher Zhao at Level 76.
That means Teacher Zhao’s current attack...
has already exceeded soul power of Level 80.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave!
It didn’t work at all.
Let’s do it together!
It’s bad.
Rong Rong, hurry up and hide!
It’s bad!
Xiao Wu, you go first.
Ah!
No! Let go of Xiao Wu!
Real body of Martial Soul!
Supreme Bear!
The real body of Teacher Zhao’s
seventh soul skill Martial Soul.
No one is allowed to come over!
I’ll defeat it!
Is this
the real body of Supreme Bear Martial Soul?
This soul skill is overbearing.
Its side effect is also the strongest.
It can use any soul skills
under Level 7
for 30 minutes unlimited.
The strength is 150% of its initial strength,
while the defense is increased by 200%.
But every time after using
the Martial Soul’s real body,
the soul master’s own attributes
will be weakened by 50%.
They’ll need 7 days to recover.
So, unless there’s no choice,
a soul master who exceeds Level 70...
would no use it.
This is already Teacher Zhao’s last resort.
Little rascal, come back!
I’m Xiao Wu, the “Wu” from dance.
Faster, even faster.
I’ll protect my younger sister forever.
I won’t let her get hurt.
Yes. Brother, you walked so far.
This is called Rou skill.
Little San. Let’s discuss about this.
I am a girl. I don’t care about it. Why do you fear?
No!
Brother.
If one day, many people want to kill me,
ut you can’t defeat them, what would you do?
They’ll have to kill me first.
[Soul Land]
Why would Titan Giant Ape appear
at the outer part of Star Dou Forest?
Sorry, everyone.
It’s my fault as I didn’t stop...
No,
it’s not your fault.
I didn’t take good care of Xiao Wu.
Let’s take a rest...
and decide later.
Little Ao, give me a Mushroom Sausage.
If you still treat me as a your brother,
don’t say it.
Little Ao, I beg you.
Xiao Wu is my sister.
If I don’t go now,
this will be a regret in my life.
As long as I don’t die this time,
I’ll remember your kindness.
Please, Little Ao.
Fine.
My third soul ring...
was got by you risking your life, Little San.
I will surely...
do whatever you want me to do.
Flying Mushroom Sausage.
What are you doing?
Sorry, everyone.
I have to look for Xiao Wu.
Even if she’s died.
Go, Little San.
I support you.
Qibao has its name.
Second name, speed!
You...
Teacher Zhao, sorry.
Blame me if you want.
You’ve also seen Little San’s look.
If I didn’t help him,
I’m afraid he’s going to walk.
What blame?
Hurry up and make me one of your Mushroom Sausage.
Let’s do it together.
Hurry up.
Flying Mushroom Sausage.
Brother.
Xiao Wu.
Er Ming, stay here.
Don’t go anymore.
I need to go back as soon as possible.
Er Ming, you shouldn’t have come out to look for me.
Brother is injured.
I was caught by you.
He must be very anxious.
Er Ming, you shouldn’t have done it.
If you see me next time, you should observe first.
You cannot hurt my friends anymore.
Is Da Ming all right?
That’s good.
Since I was brought out by you,
I’ll simply complete the third soul ring.
Er Ming, you cover it for me.
Xiao Wu,
where are you?
You must stay alive.
I’ve promised to protect you.
Xiao Wu.
[Next Episode]
It’s Human Faced Demon Spider.
No!
Who did this?
You rest at Tang Clan.
Everything will be all right.
Seems like there is something important...
that I need to do.