♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
I just wanted to figure out
whether you’re qualified to be his teachers.
How dare you, Dugu Bo!
There must be a problem.
Dugu Bo seemed afraid of Little San.
Even I myself can’t control the next poison.
I have two ways to cure the poison in your body.
but at the same time,
your poison power will also be neutralized.
Are you willing to do so?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 51]
This...
If you don’t believe that,
my blood contains medicinal
properties of two herbs,
I can give you a little to try.
But don’t blame me if
your cultivation is downgraded.
No need to try. You Little Freak.
How come you know so much!
I found a book when I was small.
There are plenty of exotic matters in it.
There’s a house of gold in the book.
This knowledge is naturally
derived from the book.
How about the other method?
The main reason why you’re
attacked by the poison
is the poison abilities you cultivated.
Since you’re using beast soul,
the poison would fuse itself into your body.
Even though your soul power
can transform and suppress it,
it has already become part of your body.
However, if you own a tool soul,
you only need to accumulate the poisons
of your body into your martial soul.
Then, it’ll not be a problem anymore.
For the second method,
if you want to retain your poison abilities
without causing any harm,
you’d have to find a parasite
as a storage for the poison.
The parasite can be a soul bone.
Do you mean to
store the poison of my body in the soul bone?
So that it’ll not cause harm to myself.
Yes, the same goes to your granddaughter.
If there’s a suitable soul bone for her,
she can store the poison in it
while she’s cultivating.
Just like me now. Although I was poisoned,
yet the poison can be stored in Blue Silver Plant
and the soul bone of Eight Spiders.
So, the poison can’t attack me.
This is the only feasible method.
This will be a long journey.
It can be more than half a year.
Are you willing to try?
Little Freak, I’ve been wanted
to kill you several times.
Do you mean to help me?
Poison and antidote do coexist.
Any poison has its corresponding antidote.
Coincidentally, I’m very fond of the antidotes.
All right, Little Freak.
There are few people who I admired.
But you’re one of them.
I’ll believe you as long as you can
cure me and my granddaughter.
There will be no issues with the
three promises I made to you.
I won’t kill you.
Now, you have to eat this first.
If you kill me in the treatment,
I’ll take you with me.
Having me to eat something you spat out.
This seems a bit nauseating!
Listen up,
this is a Dan Zhu that coagulated by evolving
the Jade Phosphor Serpent into Queen Serpent.
Half of my power is
contained in this Dan Zhu.
If I die,
it’ll be burst inside your body.
The heat seems to be scattered
into my limbs and bones.
Can you feel it?
As long as you don’t play tricks,
this Dan Zhu will be
beneficial to your cultivation.
I’ll remove it once you cure me.
Old Freak, I have a request too.
You can’t peep when I make the antidote for you.
Every night in between 9 p.m. to 11 p.m.,
you have to come here and take the
medicine one hour before you get ill.
All right.
Tang San, would you wish me to be your teacher?
Old Freak, I used to call you in this way.
I don’t feel like changing it.
Moreover, I don’t think you can
teach me anything about poison.
You might have to consult me.
You...
All right. Little Freak, let’s wait and see.
Dugu Bo.
It seems that I’d thank you.
There isn’t any place best than this ever.
It shouldn’t be wasted.
Every each herb here is peerless and precious.
But, I shouldn’t be greedy.
It doesn’t matter. I can’t eat it.
But, it doesn’t mean I can’t take it.
By mixing my blood with Octa Dark Frost
and Fiery Soft Apricot,
its medicinal properties are much milder.
It’ll only have a therapeutic effect
if the dose is lowered.
Old Freak is still fooled by me.
He does not dare to put a test
on his poison abilities.
[Six Months Later]
Little Freak, I’m here.
Little Freak, what are you doing?
It’s successful!
[Soul Land]
What is this?
This treasure can be fatal.
I can guarantee even if you’re hit by it,
you’ll not stay alive within three breaths.
These little things?
Xuan Yu Hand.
This poison can even kill
a Grand Soul Land Master.
Can kill a Grand Soul Land Master?
Are you kidding?
Do you know what’s hidden weapons?
A hidden weapon is a tool that can use in secret.
These three needles have to shot in a special way.
It’s also known as Yama’s Invitation.
Yama’s Invitation?
Yama is the God of Death.
If the God of Death sends you an invitation,
do you know what it means?
Of course, it means
bringing you back to his embrace.
No one dares to keep you,
if Yama wants you to die.
Why are you so mysterious?
There are just a few needles!
You don’t believe it?
Yes, I didn’t expect it either.
It’s a miracle to refine
the third top super Hidden Weapon
of Xuan Tian Records in Soul Land.
Enormous internal strength is required
to launch Yama’s Invitation.
And, I’m still unable to bear with it now.
Old Freak, are you feeling better?
Little Freak, return the Dan Zhu to me!
Aren’t you afraid of me to poison you?
If I’ll be poisoned by you,
how can I be the Grand Venom Master?
Little Freak, I will bring
my granddaughter here later.
You can leave here after you cure her.
But, your poison has not been cured yet.
I can’t trap you here for a lifetime.
I’ve too many poisons in my body.
I can’t store them all in the soul bone.
My body has already adapted to the poison.
If I don’t have any of it in my body,
it might be harmful to me.
You’re right as well.
So, just stop the treatment now.
It’s a waste. If you’re a few years elder,
I’ll marry my pretty granddaughter to you.
Then you’ll have to call me as Grandpa.
Forget about it!
Your granddaughter has well
inherited your genetic.
Moreover, she already has her lover,
the direct heir of Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon’s family.
Regardless of the background or family power,
I lack a lot compared with Yu Tian Heng,
the third tribe’s descendant of the world.
Yu Tian Heng?
Will he be more outstanding than you?
My background?
I have none of it.
I’m just a blacksmith’s son
who was born in a remote village.
Then, how did you grow up all the way?
Tell me about your past.
Oh, I see.
Hold on. So where did you learn
about the poison?
I won’t believe if you got present attainments
by picking up a book.
This is a secret. I won’t tell you.
It’s up to you.
Catch it.
Is this soul guiding tool a bribe?
I already have this Twenty-Four
Moonlight Bridges gifted by my teacher.
You’d keep this for yourself
or your granddaughter.
Yan Yan has no much interest in the herbs.
Giving it to her is a waste.
Your soul guiding tool is pretty good,
but it can only keep dead things.
This Lucky Almighty Pouch
can keep living things.
In other words,
this little creature can be
kept inside without suffocating
as well as the fresh herbs.
You seemed to say you didn’t want it just now.
Then, return it to me.
How can you ask for the gifted thing back?
As you’re The Grand Soul Land Master,
don’t you feel embarrassed?
Little Freak, I promised you that
if you cure the poison in my body,
I’ll realize three wishes from yours.
Firstly, I won’t hurt anyone of Shrek School.
Now, I’ve gifted you this Lucky Almighty Pouch.
Can it be the second wish?
This pouch was gifted by you willingly.
I didn’t request it from you.
You!
I’m not going to take it for granted either.
Here’s my present as a return to you.
[Next Episode]
You still owe me two wishes, right?
I’ll agree if it doesn’t go against my principles.
Please, don’t regret it.
Little Freak, stop at there!
Although Dugu Bo is in favor of you，
we still have to stay vigilant as he’s weird.
Anyway, we have to settle all the past debts.