♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Shrek School wins
not with our popularity,
but with our strength.
Go for it!
Decade Millennium Soul Ring?
This is not a competition.
I wonder how the tournament
is going.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 70]
Uncle Ning, you are here.
Qing He, I told you this is unnecessary.
You are my master.
My father will be upset,
if I don’t mind my manner.
This must be Tang San
that you’ve given much praise.
Is Shrek School short of budget?
Tian Dou Empire can sponsor you.
It’s all right.
We are about to talk to our Dean
about this uniform.
Let me introduce you.
Little San, this is the Crown Prince
of Tian Dou Empire.
Prince Xue Qing He.
So His Highness is here.
Pardon my rudeness.
If Uncle Ning hadn’t told me,
it’s hard for me to believe
you are just a young man.
If you don’t mind,
you may address me as Brother Xue.
It’s all right if you don’t
address me as the prince.
Is this man here really
Xue Beng’s brother?
Their personalities are so different.
All right, let’s sit down for now.
You are just in time to try out
the green tea.
Brother Xue.
I was told you have information about
my father’s disappearance.
He has always been an idol I admire.
I’ve been investigating it for years.
But all the clues are connected to one location.
What is the place?
Martial Soul Hall.
Back then, the higher-ups of
Martial Soul Hall were mobilized
just to search the whole land
for one treasure.
It’ rumored that the treasure
was in your father’s hand.
Soon after, your father withdrew himself
from the Hao Tian Tribe.
Perhaps, he didn’t want to involve his tribe.
Soon after, your father battled
the forces from Martial Soul Hall.
He left carrying injuries and
the treasure lost ever since.
And that very battle
made your father the youngest
Grand Soul Land Master.
After the battle,
the pope passed away
and the new pope took his place.
The Hao Tian Tribe slowly
faded from people’s attention.
Your father’s disappearance
must have been connected
to this incident as well.
What about my mother?
I am sorry, but I couldn’t get
information about your mother.
But Martial Soul Hall is powerful.
Their power is on par with two empires.
What could be the treasure
they are so obsessed with?
What happened during the battle?
If we could find the connection,
we can surely track down your parents.
If the previous pope
was killed by my father,
then it makes sense why my father
chose to raise me with an alias.
But my mother...
If it wasn’t a dream, Martial Soul Hall...
I will avenge my parents.
I’ve sent my men to investigate the case.
But it’s been years, many clues have been severed.
I doubt we could get any progress.
This information is more than enough for me.
Thank you, Brother Xue.
You are most welcome. It’s getting late,
why don’t we have a meal together?
I’ll pass. I should train for the competition.
In that case,
carry this token with you.
If anything happens,
carry it and come to me when you need help.
But...
This token is only Qing He’s personal token.
It serves no other purpose.
Just accept it.
Alright. I appreciate this, Brother Xue.
Brother Xue, Uncle Ning, I must go now.
Master, you are right. He is unique.
He lives up to the name of Hao Tian Tribe.
Hao Tian Tribe didn’t help him much.
He is already a soul master at Level 40
at such a young age.
If he could undo the rebound
caused by Twin Martial Soul,
he will certainly surpass his father.
He will become a legend.
I will keep investigating
his father’s disappearance.
As for him,
he may be outstanding
but too inexperienced nonetheless.
I should just be friendly
for the time being.
Qing He, Tang San is loyal to his friends.
If you really wish to get his help,
you should never try to recruit him,
but become his true friend.
Master, I understand.
Thank you for enlightening me.
This is Shrek School that defeated
the Tian Dou Imperial School?
Their outfit is so “eye-catching”!
With their appearance,
even if they are a dark horse in this tournament,
I just can’t admire them at all.
Look at Shen Feng School and Lei Ting School.
And the strong Xiang Jia School.
They all look much cooler than these losers.
Shrek School is wearing green like manures.
Perhaps that represents good luck.
“Ever so charming, Qixiang Shampoo
for a healthier body!”
This is the Dean’s fault.
He got us this lousy advertisement.
This shampoo is considered
premium by the way.
Half of the shampoo businesses
in Tian Dou are theirs.
That’s why they paid
such a huge sum.
But this doesn’t change how
embarrassing this is.
If we keep winning,
we might get other weirder advertisements.
It could be a toilet advertisement next time.
No!
[Soul Land]
Dean is so stubborn.
Can Boss Dai alone
enough to persuade him?
Little San, you are the smart guy.
Figure something out.
Fine. Let’s observe for now.
Dean said the product placement must stay.
But if we agree on one condition,
he agrees
to change the uniform back
to the previous color.
What does he want?
He wants more share of
the advertisement payment.
He wants 80 percent.
He is so calculating, that stingy old man.
It can’t be helped.
He said the previous color didn’t
match the advertisement.
The contract will be difficult
if we change it.
The budget will be cut.
And he wants to hold us responsible
for the loss.
As long as we don’t need to wear
this green thing,
I can agree on anything.
Then get ready and get changed.
Grandmaster, what is the training you’ll give me?
There is a skill in Qibao Amber Tribe
called Heart Separation Control.
What is your level on that skill?
I managed to control the
Three-Aperture Governing Heart.
I think it’s enough for me to handle it.
There is the Three-Aperture Governing Heart,
Four-Aperture Fortitude,
and Five-Aperture Scattering,
Six-Aperture Will and Seven-Aperture Agility.
Each of the stages
represents the number of skills
you can control at one time,
and the number of releases
you can make.
You’ve been training since a young age
yet made no progress,
how are you supposed to use
your Martial Soul to its maximum?
Master, Rong Rong is already at Level 40.
She is outstanding in supporting skills.
She can buff us for 50 percent
while controlling four other skills.
The impulse she has
can boost our strength to a whole new level.
Are you sure about that?
She can tell you the answer.
If the Shrek Seven Devils move out,
she buffs all six of you at the same time,
how long can she maintain it?
Probably less than three seconds.
Three seconds?
Grandmaster, how do you know the secrets
of Qibao Amber Tribe?
I was born in Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Tribe.
One of the three greatest tribes.
I am not the only one who knows.
Most of the powerful soul masters
know about this.
Even so,
Qibao Amber Tribe is the most powerful
in terms of Supporting Branch.
That’s all thanks to the
Heart Separation Control.
You are right.
The secret of Qibao Amber Pagoda
is the use of soul power.
The stronger the soul power is,
the more soul rings we have,
the more prominent the side effect is.
This is a fair world.
Qibao Amber Pagoda is the best
Supporting Branch Martial Soul.
Its supporting ability is astonishing.
But it also takes a great toll
on the soul power.
If this issue isn’t solved properly,
when in face of stronger opponents,
Rong Rong will have trouble
using her potential to the greatest.
So the solution is Heart Separation Control?
The Hear Separation Control
is to control different skills
simultaneously to have effects.
During a battle,
every fighter will have
different needs for buffs.
With limited soul power,
you must support with precision
to each of your targets.
That is how you utilize the power
of Qibao Amber Pagoda to the greatest.
For example, among the four skills
Rong Rong has right now,
what I need the most is a buff to my soul power.
Boss Dai, on the other hand,
needs attack, defense and soul power boost.
Grandmaster, you are amazing.
What you said is just the same
as my father’s teaching.
But the training is so hard and boring, so I...
Rong Rong, as the direct heir of Qibao Amber Tribe,
you are born with the advantage.
You must hone your mastering of
Heart Separation Control.
Even if you will become
the Grand Soul Land Master,
you won’t be a qualified
soul master from Support Branch.
Do you understand my concern now?
Grandmaster, thank you.
I assure you that from now on,
I will train harder.
I am glad to hear that.
Rong Rong, I have other agenda
for asking Little San here.
If your tribe doesn’t forbid you
from teaching an outsider,
will you let Little San join your training
for the Heart Separation Control?
Master, that is a skill only
the Qibao Amber Tribe can use.
I can’t learn that.
Little San, you are a soul master
of Controlling Branch with Twin Martial Soul.
If you manage to master
Heart Separation Control,
you will gain more control on the battlefield.
After you acquire skills
for your second Martial Soul,
your power growth will become more prominent.
Brother San, we can train together.
We owe you a favour.
I believe my father would agree on this as well.
But...
Brother San.
When you gave me the Celestial Tulip,
did I ever turn you down?
I didn’t, because I do see you as
my big brother.
Shrek Seven Devils are one family.
You have always been so selfless.
So I must repay your kindness as well.
How about this?
I’ll get permission from my father.
I am sure he won’t refuse it.
She is always so rash.
Little San, don’t worry.
Ning Feng Zhi will seize
this chance to get a favor.
As the Chief of Qibao Amber Tribe,
he has a vision.
He holds both you and your father in high regard.
Now tell me,
what Ning Feng Zhi talked to you about?
Shrek School.
Your unsightly defeat
shall bring glory to the Martial Soul Hall.
[Next Episode]
I suggest you surrender on the next round.
Your opponents for the next round will be...
He failed to make friends,
so he chose to oppress.
To battle!