♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Xiao Wu, you’re still alive?
Brother!
Is Little San becoming a big spider?
An outer is always an outer.
You can only be trash.
How dare an outer disciple
peep at the inner practice!
Give him a lesson!
If you still have improper thoughts,
I will definitely report to
Grandmaster Tang Lan
to expel you from the clan.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 29]
Brother, I’m back.
You must hang in there.
You said that you’d protect me forever.
You must not break your promise.
An outer disciple is willing to
never enter the inner.
But I have to study
the secret scripture of Tang Clan.
Hey, it’s time to change shift.
Okay.
In any case, I mustn’t hurt
my schoolmates with hidden weapons.
I mustn’t reveal myself either.
It’s said that there are 3 levels
in Scriptures Library.
On Level 1, guards are enforcing martial law.
Level 2 is guarded by 3 Elders
with the most powerful hidden weapons,
to ensure no fish slips through the net.
Level 3 is the place
that the secret scripture is kept.
Let’s check over there.
This shall be the entrance to Level 3.
Purple Demon Eye.
Looking thoroughly, in details.
Three Elders have a full-round sight.
This is impervious.
Once any object appears,
I’m afraid it can’t escape
the capture of these red lines.
Three Elders would never miss a single sound.
If I want to break through,
death is the only option.
I got it.
It’s Xuan Tian Records.
It’s Xuan Tian Records that record
the strongest skill of Tang Clan.
Who is it?
Grandmaster Tang Lan.
Outsiders know that Tang’s Scriptures
Library has 2 levels highly guarded.
But they don’t know about the core of Level 3.
I have guarded it on my own for years.
Tang San is unfilial.
I’m willing to be punished.
What if you’re to be expelled from Tang Clan?
I was adopted by Tang Clan when I was a baby.
Since then, I have been part of Tang Clan
for eternal life and will never change until death.
Grandmaster.
Tang San, do you know why I saved you?
Grandmaster, you’re kind.
Wrong! I saved you because of Tang Clan.
In the past, Tang Clan reached its zenith.
No one was a match for us.
However, with the fame growing,
the inner has become hierarchical and
more red tape were created.
The outer disciples couldn’t practice
the highest skills.
The inner disciples are not qualified enough.
The pedantic rules have made
many secret scriptures lose.
In this way, Tang Clan couldn’t
escape its fate of falling.
Only the survival of the fittest, being eclectic,
is the core for the prosperous of Tang Clan.
I haven’t seen you today.
You have never been to Scriptures Library.
Tang San.
How will Tang Clan develop in the future?
You might as well try it boldly.
Revive Tang Clan.
Little San, I am leaving.
You will count on yourself in the future.
Grandmaster.
Heinous treason! Don’t let him go!
In the future,
you must use the hammer in your left hand
to protect the plant in your right hand forever.
Brother, you must put effort.
- Soul power transformation succeeded!
- That’s great!
[Soul Land]
Xiao Wu.
Brother.
Xiao Wu, it’s you?
Brother, it’s me.
I am not dreaming, right?
It’s not a dream. I’m back, Brother.
It’s all my fault. I made you worry.
It’s my fault.
It’s my bad for not being able to protect you.
No. It’s not your fault.
Have you got hurt?
Little San.
Who took off my clothes?
You guess.
What is the situation?
No idea.
Has your soul ring mutated?
A soul ring never mutates.
Only Martial Soul does.
I absorbed the soul ring of Human Faced
Demon Spider and got a skill.
Everything is so normal.
But, there’s no explanation for
the 8 spider legs on my back.
Can you control the 8 spider legs on your back
and keep them?
You can’t leave it like this all the time.
You’ll be treated as a monster.
We are monsters.
You, little rascal.
Let me try it.
Tang San! Brother San.
Did you kill Human Faced Demon Spider with that?
Oh, yes. I will show it to you guys too.
Wait. I can feel something.
Something is approaching.
It’s Human Faced Demon Spider.
The size is much smaller than this one.
They’re its descendants.
It’s a big amount.
It’s bad. My strength hasn’t recovered.
My strength is also limited. I’ve miscalculated.
What shall we do now?
There’s a way.
I used the hidden weapon to kill
the Human Faced Demon Spider.
These young Human Faced Demon Spiders
are not powerful.
If we use the hidden weapon well,
we may survive the crisis.
Xiao Wu, this is for you.
Brother, you use it.
I can protect myself.
Do you remember what I told you?
But I can give you my promise.
I’ll protect my younger sister forever.
Little monsters, let’s start the battle!
Yes!
Why is this so difficult?
It’s because you’re too lousy.
Rong Rong, I’m coming!
Rong Rong, are you all right?
I don’t need your rescue.
You’re the ones who put my brother in danger!
Dangerous! Don’t you hurt Xiao Wu!
Are you all right, Xiao Wu?
This hidden weapon is quite useful.
Exactly. We could beat so many of them
without using Martial Soul.
Brother San, can you sell this to me?
Sell it to you?
I am a soul master of Assisting Branch
with self-protection ability.
If...
Forget about selling. I’ll give it to you later.
Isn’t this inappropriate?
It’s all right. If you feel embarrassed,
you can pay for the materials.
Little San, are we good brothers?
I got it. I’ll give you a set too.
I’ll give one to every each of you.
All of them have money.
It’s hard to make this crossbow.
Just collect the money you deserve.
Teacher Zhao is right.
Little San, we can’t make you suffer losses.
Okay, we shouldn’t stay long
at this place. Hurry up and leave.
Let’s talk about it along the way.
[Next Episode]
It’s more important than your life.
I’m sorry.
It’s a lake like a fairyland.
The lake suddenly boiled.
He entered the core of Star Dou Forest before.
A giant.
The lake suddenly boiled.
Make ways, everyone!