♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
You have to pay a price for what you’ve done.
What a Level 41 Soul Sect.
He’s able to control the arena instantly.
It’s Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
When it’s our turn to duel,
I hope you can duel with me.
Your rival for tomorrow is Chi Huo School.
Why is Chi Huo School again?
Why? Why are you the first
to come on the stage?
Next, Chi Huo School versus Shrek School.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 85]
I did mention that your fire-resistance
Blue Silver Plant is useless to me.
Do you think you can win?
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
How could it be? It’s like hitting a soft barrier.
I can’t feel my force.
Ghostly Trace.
It’s Little San’s Martial Skill with
control and power deformation effect.
Explosion against control,
this is no doubt the best option.
The touch of Blue Silver Plant
can trigger the explosion.
Too bad that Little San’s Martial Skill
has power deformation effect.
Xuan Yu Hand.
Even if he reacts quickly...
Explode!
and explode first.
But Little San has already left the explosion scope.
Besides, to explode voluntarily
needs more soul power.
It’s hard for him to
release it again in a while.
As soon as he follows Little San’s rhythm,
he will have no more chance to win.
Unbelievable.
He was still under restraint just now.
But Tang San has turned the table at once.
Now, Huo Wu Shuang is
the one who is under restraint.
He did it again.
If Huo Wu Shuang used up his soul power just now,
and still in the recovering process,
then what is happening now?
How is this possible?
Shrek has found a way to restrict Chi Huo School.
I need to hold it back. I can’t even touch him now.
I need to find a way to go near him
to release the explosion again.
It’s time.
You’ve lost.
First round, Shrek School won!
Brother.
When you’re facing me, you’re not confident.
If a soul master loses confidence,
how can he win?
Brother, are you okay?
I’m fine.
I’ve lost,
and I admit my defeat.
Tang San.
Uncle, this...
You’re young, but you’re acting maturely.
Second round, let’s welcome Huo Yun
from Chi Huo School.
No matter what trick
you used to restrain my leader,
it’s useless to Keen Attack Branch.
Start!
Take this.
Fourth soul skill, Flamingo Prairie Flame.
[Tang San vs. Huo Yun]
[Tang San vs. Huo Lie]
[Tang San vs. Huo Chui]
[Tang San vs. Huo Yu]
[Tang San vs. Huo Jun]
Sixth round, Shrek School won!
Tang San has defeated six members
from Chi Huo School continuously.
This is the sixth one.
Is Brother San going to
defeat seven people on his own?
Has Chi Huo School got weaker?
They’re not weak,
but Little San is too powerful.
Next one is Chi Huo School’s vice captain,
Level 44 Soul Sect
of Controlling Branch, Huo Wu.
[Tang San vs. Huo Wu]
If she loses this round,
Shrek School will create
a record of one against seven.
Will she complete the record of Shrek School?
Five Elements Schools
are comparable in strength.
But this Chi Huo School is going to
lose for seven times to only one man.
It’s fine to lose, but this is too much.
A mere Blue Silver Plant Martial Soul
soul master defeats the whole team.
I don’t think you deserve your school’s title.
How can this possible?
This Tang San is so rude to
the Five Elements Schools.
You need to be worthy of his politeness too.
Boss Dai, do you think Little San can win this round?
Chi Huo School will sure do their best.
Little San must be careful.
Although I’ve saved up
as much soul power as I can
and only used up forty percent of it,
more than half of my mental power has been used up.
Why does the whole Chi Huo School can’t defeat him?
Why do I still having doubts,
when I know he has fought for six rounds?
Because he’s a soul master of Controlling Branch?
Or his fire resistance?
No, not just these.
Her temperament
has become calm.
For my teachers’ teaching,
and friends’ support,
this battle
is not just my grudge with Tang San.
It’s related to our school’s honor.
If I lose,
Among the Five Elements Schools,
Chi Huo School will be a disgrace forever.
Thus,
no matter what, I must win.
Start!
She’s ignoring the skills and defense.
As long as the skills are not
ten levels higher than hers,
all skills within the attack scope
will be temporarily dismissed.
But she needs time to release this skill.
Third soul skill, Repelling Fire Ring.
Her soul skill’s releasing time
is getting quicker.
The width of the arena is only one hundred meters.
But the Repelling Fire Ring
can cover sixty meters.
If I’m chased by the Repelling Fire Ring again...
After the previous battle,
she seemed to practice hard too.
Controlling Branch soul master
is extraordinary.
She has pushed me to
this extent in a blink of an eye.
Her strategy is ingenious.
But Repelling Fire Ring
can only reach up to three meters.
It can’t reach above three meters.
She must have other intentions
in exhausting soul power substantially.
Rings Fusion.
Rings Fusion is not a skill,
it’s a rare talent.
To channel all of her
soul power into a skill at once.
Right now her soul power
outcome is at the maximum rate.
As expected, it’s hard to
avoid her attacks in the air.
This is her intention.
But if it’s just like this...
Third soul skill,
Constraint of Spider Web.
This maximum outcome
of soul power will be suppressed
to produce an explosion.
The effect will be multiplied.
But it is not the scariest part of Rings Fusion.
This little girl is able to use Rings Fusion?
Can you resist this?
[Soul Land]
Oh, no, I’m being targeted.
Once being targeted, unless it hits its target,
- or else it will not stop.
- Brother!
Awesome!
Among soul masters at the same level,
no one can ever resist
my sister’s Rings Fusion skill.
Huo Wu is using a rare talent skill,
how will Tang San react?
Since I can’t run away,
let’s endure this attack together.
Oh, no!
Once her Rings Fusion is initiated,
unless it hits its target,
it can’t be taken back.
She must figure it out to get away from it.
Chi Huo School is falling into their own trap now.
I can’t believe that Tang San is so despicable.
This is a battle.
Even if you can control it to only attack me,
But judging from our distance now,
you’ll be affected as well.
Aren’t you going to stop your skill now?
You’re being tricked.
No, Huo Wu!
No!
She’s going to kill herself
along with the opponent.
I know that Rings Fusion
is not enough to defeat you.
But I want everyone to see that
even if it’s you, Tang San, you can’t get away
from Chi Huo School.
Rings Fusion has used up all of your soul power.
You can’t take this strike.
You too.
Chi Huo School will not allow anyone
to damage its honour.
Face your first defeat.
What?
- Little San.
- Brother San.
Is he nuts?
Foolish, how can he protect his opponent?
Chi Huo School
is a worthy opponent.
The competition is over.
Tang San is unable to fight anymore.
Chi Huo School won!
Hurry and help Little San.
Still not letting me go?
You’ve won.
I’ve won.
I’ve really
won?
This explosion is terrific.
Everyone, please be quiet.
Let’s wait for the next round.
The doctor will enter the arena immediately
to treat the injured participants.
Sister, are you okay?
I’m fine.
Brother.
Silly girl, don’t cry.
I’m okay.
Let’s send Little San back first.
As Huo Wu has given up for this round,
Shrek School won.
Is my brother okay?
Little girl, don’t worry.
He’s fine now.
Normal people will either die
or get injured severely
after a strike like this.
But your brother’s physique is extraordinary.
Thus he’s okay.
But
for the upcoming qualifying rounds,
he’d better not join the battles.
Or else it will be bad if his wound bleeds again.
Thank you, Doctor.
Okay, take good care of him.
I’ll leave first.
Okay,
the others may go to rest first.
You still have competitions tomorrow.
Xiao Wu will stay and take care of Little San.
OK.
Actually, Little San did the right thing.
Grandmaster, how can you say that?
He could have avoided it.
Little San did this to save a life.
I believe
when he used his body to resist the strike,
he must have known his capability
to endure the strike.
Why are you here? Go away.
We’re here to visit Tang San
and to express our gratitude.
We don’t need your pretended act here.
Tang San is still alive.
Dai Mu Bai,
don’t go too far.
I’m here to see Tang San.
I want to thank him for protecting my sister.
I’m not here to see you.
Move aside.
Stop being a hypocrite.
You really think Shrek doesn’t have anyone left?
Leave this place now.
Or else,
don’t blame us for being rude.
You...
I’m here to thank Tang San for saving my life.
My brother’s condition
is your desired results, isn’t it?
You’re not welcome here.
What is this mad lady doing?
You don’t need to risk your life
for a battle between schools.
If we meet Chi Huo School, let’s give up, okay?
Boss,
the hero saves the beauty.
Are you envious?
Please leave.
My brother has slept.
Please don’t disturb him.
Sorry for disturbing.
I’ll come and thank him when he’s better.
No need.
We’re opponents for Continental Soul
Master School Elite Tournament.
Opponents?
[Next Episode]
I want to talk to you in private.
Can’t you say it here?
Shrek School isn’t that good after all.
This is your first time on the arena.
Fatty, come on.
He’s never been on the arena.
Is he from some clan that uses relation
to get him in for experience?
Little Fatty, my vines are very fast.
You’d better go down. What if I hurt you?