♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Meeting Acala in such an insignificant place.
I want to fight with you.
Xiao Wu’s first soul skill, Arched Body.
The Controlling is effective
against Keen Attack.
Your attack won’t break my Martial Soul’s control.
That’s bad.
You two, how dare you!
Xiao Wu, no!
Let’s go.
Didn’t you say women are just resources?
Dirty.
Disgusting.
You!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 20]
Ning Rong Rong.
Don’t you ever test my patience.
This is Shrek School, not your home!
Yo.
You failed it and now we can’t talk about it?
You can’t even handle a young lady.
How useless.
Let me warn you.
Others might be afraid of Qibao Amber Tribe,
but I don’t.
If you make me angry,
I’ll kill you!
I’m so scared.
You!
Mu Bai,
we’re all classmates.
Forget it.
Alright, Little San.
Since you said so.
Stop provoking me,
or else I’ll show no respect!
Tang San!
Kill him!
If you’re willing to help me,
you’ll be the honored guest of Qibao Amber Tribe!
I’ll give you 10,000 gold soul coins!
The Qibao Amber Tribe will
unconditionally support you!
Money and power can’t exchange
everything in this world.
I have no idea what happened
between you and Mu Bai.
But if you continue to be this lofty,
you might as well leave the school.
You!
Aren’t you aware of how powerful
Qibao Amber Tribe is?
Xiao Wu, let’s go.
You!
Oscar, are you willing to help me?
Why?
Don’t you have feelings for me?
I like the Rong Rong when we first met.
Now,
I’m no match for Qibao Amber Tribe’s little princess.
Rather than becoming a servant for someone,
I prefer to remain truthful to myself.
Tang San is right.
Maybe you don’t belong here.
If you’re not changing your attitude,
you’ll never get friends forever.
Friends?
Friends.
I’m not a devil girl!
Where’s Oscar?
He overslept again?
He was still training when I came out.
Maybe he’s still in meditation.
Tang San, bring him here.
He must be here for this lesson.
Yes, Dean.
He’s here.
Oscar, do you wish to get punished again?
No, Dean.
Please listen to me.
I’ve reached Level 30!
What?
Good.
Oscar.
You’re the second one who reached
Level 30 among all.
I was right about you.
Little Ao.
Congratulations.
As a Food Branch soul master,
you’re the most extraordinary genius
I’ve ever met.
Congratulations.
If that so,
tomorrow morning,
Teacher Zhao Wu Ji will lead you
to Star Dou Forest...
to help Oscar to get his third soul ring.
Remember
it will be a training for all of you.
Yes, Dean.
Alright,
we’ll start our lesson today.
Oscar.
Yes.
Be prepared to activate your soul skill.
Your task today...
is to eat the special made sausage by Oscar,
at least one piece.
What? Dean,
what lesson is this?
Adaptability training.
If you can’t eat such delicious sausages,
whenever you’re in trouble,
rats, cockroaches, earthworms,
will you dare to eat them?
Who is the first one?
Me!
I want to stay.
Next.
[Shrek School]
Who did that to Teacher Zhao?
What are you looking at?
You bunch of little rabbits,
do you want to get beaten?
You should say bear cubs.
What did you say?
Hmm.
Get ready.
Mu Bai, you’ll lead.
Yes.
Soul beasts in Star Dou Forest
are numerous and ferocious.
Little San,
you’ll be the vanguard.
Oscar and Ning Rong Rong, follow him.
Fatty and Xiao Wu, take care of the sides.
Zhu Zhu Qing and I will be at the end.
Follow this formation after we enter the forest,
remain on guard at all times.
Let me warn you again,
Unless you meet a Millennium Soul Beast,
or else I’ll not interfere.
You have to think of strategies on the way.
Yes!
Alright, let’s go.
Oscar.
Super Recovery Big Sausage!
Run for around two more hours.
There’s a small town in front,
we’ll stay overnight there.
[Soul Land]
I’m so tired after running for the whole day.
Luckily, we have Little Ao’s sausages.
It’s nothing.
Come on, after stuffing so many sausages,
I’m already getting nausea.
Let’s order for food.
Fatty, you’re always so troublesome.
Why is Teacher Zhao not dining with us?
We have to pay for our expenses outside.
Teachers aren’t allowed
to take advantage of the students.
That’s what I like about the school,
it’s fair and square.
Fatty, go and order your food.
Order, order!
This way, please.
The girl looks adorable, Boss Dai.
They’re from the Cang Hui School, right?
Just a small Cang Hui School,
who are they showing off to?
Something excited is going to happen.
What is it?
It’s a part of our training.
Quote from the Dean,
soul masters who don’t make troubles
aren’t quite qualified.
His quotes can add up to be
a quote for monsters.
Cang Hui School is an
Advanced Soul Master School, right?
Don’t waste the food.
My apology.
I’m sorry, my hand slipped.
It’s so delicious.
Which school you guys come from?
Trying to interrogate us?
You’re still unworthy.
This is good.
Tastes fine, lacking some skills though.
How arrogant you are!
Teach them a lesson!
Fight? I love it.
Hello, brothers.
Hurry and help her,
Xiao Wu is in an unfavorable situation.
Those guys are the one
we should worry about.
Ah!
She’s great!
Our turn!
Xiao Wu, come back.
[Next Episode]
If you want reorganization,
then prove it to them with actions
that you belong to Shrek.
Let me teach you how to be a human.
Remember, we’re not humans but monsters.
Stay on guard.
Be careful!