♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Level 40?
Forget about it then.
No, I think it’s okay.
Is there a team at Level 40,
which is especially cruel?
The more formidable, the better.
It’s the lethal weapon
among soul battle teams at Level 40.
They’ve killed 63 opponents,
injured 98 opponents.
Any strong soul masters
have to go through this.
You have to pay a price for any victory in a battle.
You should understand that
battles of soul masters are not games.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 45]
This is Tian Dou Imperial School?
Yes. My father brought me here when I was a child.
But this is a mountain.
The whole mountain belongs to
Tian Dou Imperial School.
The forest behind the mountain
and the lake at the foot
also belong to the school.
Hold on.
Who are you?
We’re from Shrek School.
We’ve accepted the invitation
of Tian Dou Imperial School
to come for exchange.
Please, guide the way.
Exchange in our school?
You poor fellows?
Get lost.
Tian Dou Imperial School is not a refugee camp.
As our Dean said, please, guide the way.
You...
Why is the quality of the students
of Tian Dou Imperial School so bad?
The soul power of these
students is far worse than Dai Mu Bai,
but they outnumber us.
If they would work together to attack Dai Mu Bai,
they can at least resist it.
But right now...
Are these students of Tian Dou Imperial School?
A bunch of trash.
I’m starting to doubt the decision of coming here.
Don’t ask me. How would I know?
The Emperor Battle Team
that fought with little monsters
was not like them.
Alright, Mu Bai. That’s enough.
Who should get lost then?
How dare you cause trouble
in Tian Dou Imperial School?
You’re provoking our empire.
Wait for it.
Yes, Teacher Qin.
What’s the noise?
Dean, teachers, you’re finally here.
I invited Shrek School here
to have an exchange.
Why did you stop them?
It was them.
That’s enough. No more excuses.
All of you, run around the field 10 times.
Dean, this way, please.
Shrek School?
They just came here to scam us.
Don’t even dream about staying here
as long as I’m around.
Your Highness, that doesn’t sound good.
What isn’t good about that?
Even the empire belongs to us.
Can’t I decide such a small matter?
No, Your Highness.
I mean, if we don’t run now,
we’ll be scolded again.
Let’s go then.
Go? To where?
To run, stupid!
Dean, the main campus of Tian Dou
Imperial School is at the hillside.
Mimicry areas are
at the mountain top and bottom,
and also by the lake.
One of the reasons why the school
is built outside
of Tian Dou City,
is the mimicry training environment.
Construction of mimicry training environment
is to let soul masters train Martial
Souls in a compatible environment.
If it’s in the city,
it’s okay for soul masters
of Plant Branch and Food Branch.
But for Beast soul masters, it’ll be inconvenient.
There are various kinds of mimicry
training environments in our school,
to provide the most suitable
training environment for the students.
How many students are there
in Tian Dou Imperial School?
More than 500 students.
Basically, they’re the nobles from
the empire or the affiliated kingdoms.
There are about 50 teachers.
We have enough qualified teachers.
But the quality of our students...
What do you think?
Not bad. It’s better than what I imagined.
Although the students are not so good.
It seems we really have to retire here.
More than 500 students.
Their actual strength must be different.
Here’s the case, Grandmaster.
The students of Tian Dou Imperial School
are categorize into 3 levels.
Those lower than Level 25 are in Tian Wei Level.
Level 25 to 30 are considered as Tian Zhi Level.
Level 30 and above are
in the highest Tian Dou Level.
Like those in Emperor Battle Team
are the top of Tian Dou Level.
And those who you met at the foot
of the mountain are in Tian Wei Level.
No wonder they’re weak.
The teachers are categorize so as well.
Teachers at Level 40 to 50 are
Tian Wei Level teachers.
Level 50 to 60
are Tian Zhi Level teachers.
Level 60 and above are Tian Dou Level teachers.
The senior is the board of education
formed by the oldest and
strongest Tian Dou Level teachers.
That means
we can also be Tian Dou Level teachers.
Of course.
If you and fellow teachers can be our teachers,
it’ll be our pleasure.
Here we are. This is the board of
education of Tian Dou Imperial School.
[Soul Land]
Shrek School, Frander.
My Martial Soul is Eagle Owl.
Keen Attack Branch,
7-ring Soul Saint at Level 78.
Greetings, Senior.
Dean Frander, don’t be too polite.
I’m the President of the
Board of Education, Meng Shen Ji.
My Martial Soul is Black Genie.
Controlling Branch, 8-ring
Great Soul Land Master at Level 86.
Vice President of the board, Bai Bao Shan.
My Martial Soul is Star Furnace.
Defence Branch, 8-ring
Great Soul Land Master at Level 85.
Second Vice President of the board, Zhi Lin.
My Martial Soul is Azure Vine.
Controlling Branch, 8-ring
Great Soul Land Master at Level 83.
Pleased to meet you.
Meng Shen Ji, Black Genie Martial Soul.
The best Martial Soul of Controlling Branch.
The legend says,
once one is controlled by Black Genie,
he’ll fall into endless circle of dreams.
There’s no way to escape.
Bai Bao Shan, Star Furnace Martial Soul.
The legend says, having Star Furnace
as Defence Branch Martial Soul,
despite being a Great Soul Land Master,
few can break through only by using power.
Zhi Lin, Azure Vine Martial Soul.
Azure Vine and Blue Silver Plant
have similarities.
But in controlling power,
the two of them have huge differences.
In Martial Soul Training, he may help Little San.
Among these three,
there are two Great Soul Land Masters
from Controlling Branch.
Storm Attack Branch soul masters
are no doubt vigorous,
but Controlling Branch
is the hardest to tackle.
Unless the capability is restraint,
or else, in one-to-one battle,
soul masters at the same level can hardly
defeat one from Controlling Branch.
Don’t be extra polite. This way, please.
I heard from Qin Ming,
these kids defeated Emperor Battle Team
from our school.
What a surprise.
The achievement of Qin Ming is already a wonder.
I didn’t expect that your school
has fostered such excellent geniuses.
Shrek School doesn’t exist anymore.
No, Shrek School will never disappear.
Qin Ming has explained it to me.
Your arrival is our pleasure.
Only when you agree,
otherwise, we wouldn’t give you any teaching task.
Over here, you’re free to do anything.
I heard from Teacher Qin,
one of your students is an excellent
soul master genius of Controlling Branch.
Who would it be?
He’s not a genius.
Tang San.
Greetings.
Teacher Zhao.
He’s testing my strength.
Is he testing Tang San’s strength?
Great.
You shall see how great
the student of Shrek School is.
If I’ve not mistaken,
the soul power of this child
is at about Level 33.
Under my pressure,
he has reached his limit.
However,
he doesn’t show that he’s in any pain.
The durability of Little San is extraordinary.
The attached soul bone
of Human Faced Demon Spider
has increased his toughness
to an extreme level.
He’s unexpectedly tough.
This child looks young.
Even his Martial Soul isn’t forced out.
When low-level soul masters bear direct
pressure from high-level soul masters,
few can endure two thirds
of their own level.
If one can endure the pressure
that equals to its soul power,
it can be said as outstanding.
But even then, Martial Soul would be released.
He also needs to be a tough beast soul master.
With the amount of soul power I release,
even a soul honor at Level 35 and above
would use his Martial Soul.
But this child is still so calm.
If Level 35 doesn’t work,
I’ll increase it to Level 36.
Level 37.
Level 38.
Level 39.
Level 40.
My Martial Soul is shifted off.
Moving load with light effort.
Blue Silver Plant has such a power.
Moving load with light effort?
What if it weighs tonnes?
Level 42.
Level 43.
Level 44.
Soul bone?
Thank you for your help,
Great Soul Land Master Zhi Lin.
Help?
Ever since he got the attached soul bone,
although his strength has increased,
he couldn’t combine it truly.
Under your pressure,
his attached soul bone can
finally be combined with his body.
They won’t separate anymore.
Attached soul bone?
Yes. Please keep it a secret.
Attached soul bone is precious.
If this became known,
Little San might get hurt.
Don’t worry. We swear on our Martial Souls,
that we’ll not reveal this to others.
What a surprise.
A genius has arisen in the soul master world.
I don’t claim credit on Tang San’s success.
He’s the apprentice of the Grandmaster.
No, not just the soul bone of Eight Spiders.
Under the pressure
of Great Soul Land Master Zhi Lin,
my circulation of vital energy
has been opened up.
My soul power has increased to Level 34.
As Xuan Tian Records said,
Que Lie of four limbs, Hou Xi, Nei Guan, Wai Guan,
Zhao Hai, Shen Mai,
Gong Sun, Zhu Lin form 8 acupoints.
These acupoints lead to Ren, Du,
Yin Wei, Yang Wei,
Yin Qiao, Yang Qiao, Chong and Dai,
a total of eight arteries.
Under the pressure of the soul power,
What Xuan Tian Strike broke through
should be the Chong artery.
Not only Tang San,
everyone in Shrek Seven Devils
has their own talent.
We come to Tian Dou Imperial School,
so that their talents won’t be neglected.
Dean Frander, don’t worry.
We’ll try our best
to provide these kids
with the best training facilities
and the best training environment.
We don’t ask for anything back.
We only hope,
when they’re at the top of soul master world,
they will have
Tian Dou Imperial School in their resume.
Thank you, Seniors.
This matter is settled then.
Teacher Qin, please make the arrangement.
Is President Meng Shen Ji around?
It’s him?
[Next Episode]
Hold on.
We’ll report what happened today
to His Majesty,
to have His Majesty redress the scales.
Frander, I’m sorry. It’s my fault.
So how will Your Highness settle this matter?
I’m afraid these three old fellows
won’t let this matter drop.
In Tian Dou Imperial School,
I am the direct manager.
Get out of my school.
You guys come together.