♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Little San, you’re finally back.
Brother San, where are the gifts?
Hurry and show us.
This herb is called
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
I’m not single-minded.
I have no fate with this flower.
Seems like I still can’t let it go.
Brother, that legend must be true, right?
Five levels. My soul power
has increased by five levels.
Look.
Your Qibao Amber Pagoda
has nine levels now.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 54]
Zhu Qing, what about your soul power?
I think it has increased by seven levels.
Unbelievable.
Your Daffodil Jade Beauty is better than us.
Little San is right. It suits you very much.
But this is originally for you, I...
It supposed to be yours.
I have Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet with me.
I’m worried that you would envy me.
Did you feel the majestic vibes in my flame?
My Phoenix flame is purer.
I’m finally a true Phoenix Soul Master.
This Fatty is boasting again.
Hey, let me go.
It is doubtless that you care for me.
Are you still leaving?
I’ll not let you go anymore.
Leave these sweet talks to your lovers.
Zhu Qing, didn’t you realize that
I’ve been as pure as Tang San lately?
Until you’re as innocent as Brother San,
then only we’ll see.
Little San, thank you.
I’ve finally broken through
the bottleneck of Level 40.
By the way,
when you’re available can you teach me
how to be pure and innocent?
I’m afraid that you don’t have the chance.
That’s right, Mr. Dai.
Only my brother can be considered
as the pure and innocent Mr. Tang San.
Master, how do you feel?
It has been more than thirty years...
Unexpectedly, the bottleneck
which has haunted my whole life,
I’ve broken through it today.
Grade Nine Purple Mushroom...
Seems like I’ve underestimated
the benefits of the external force.
Master, you’ve broken through Level 30.
Congratulations.
Maybe your practice will
advance in leaps and bounds later.
The practice of a soul master
will be harder as we age.
How many years I have left?
I’ve given up the hope to be a powerful soul master.
You are my only hope.
Okay, from now on, practice properly.
Keep on absorbing to strengthen your power.
Don’t eager for quick results.
Seven days later,
I’ll hunt for a soul beast with Mu Bai
to obtain soul rings.
Okay.
Rong Rong, Little Ao, be careful.
First soul skill,
White Tiger Protection Barrier.
Be careful, everyone.
Scatter.
Fly.
Flying Mushroom Sausage.
Jiubao famously said,
First Strength Second Speed.
First soul skill, Arched Body.
Second soul skill, Nether White Claws.
Second soul skill,
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
First soul skill, Phoenix Firing Line.
Stop, I’m Teacher Zhao.
Third soul skill,
Constraint of Spider Web.
It’s really Teacher Zhao.
Why are you attacking us?
I just want to test your abilities.
Who knows that you would be this fierce?
But, you’ve greatly improved.
As your teacher, I’m very satisfied.
I’m sorry, Teacher Zhao.
Xiao Gang, I lost.
Seems like if they join forces,
they can defeat Zhao Wu Ji.
But I have no money currently,
I’ll put this on credit.
Hey, you’re making a bet on me?
Wait, what do you mean
that they can beat me?
I was just being lenient on them.
If you don’t believe it,
we shall fight again.
Enough, don’t be too carried away.
The enemy who wants to take your lives away
will not show any mercy.
By the way, Little San,
Senior Dugu is looking for you.
Old Freak is looking for me?
[Soul Land]
Little Freak, you’re here.
Little San, I’ll leave first.
Grandpa, why did you call this scum over?
Besides, why are you being an adviser
at this lousy school?
Even so, you should go to Tian Dou Imperial School.
Enough, Yan Yan. Don’t call him scum anymore.
Look at you.
You’ve grown up,
but you’re still acting like a child.
Tang San is younger,
yet he’s more mature than you.
What’s good about him?
I was just too careless previously.
If given another chance,
I’ll hit him hard.
Then you must hurry.
Six months later, there’ll be a
National Advanced Soul Master School Contest.
We’re both in the Tian Dou area.
We’ll meet soon.
You! Wait for it.
Previously you raided Tian Heng,
I’ll not let you get away with this.
Little Freak, I don’t care about the others.
But you must not hurt my granddaughter.
Or else, I’ll not let you go.
Grandpa, how can he hurt me?
You’re encouraging him
and discouraging me.
You’re siding with him.
Did you accept him as your disciple?
Yan Yan, do you know
what level his soul power is currently?
Level 37, it’s just about yours.
In just six months, this Little Freak
may pass the bottleneck of Level 40.
You’re a soul master of
Controlling Branch like him.
But I’m certain that
you can’t beat him.
If you underestimate this Little Freak,
you’ll face great loss.
About my ability, we’ll see on the ring.
Old Freak, this is the medicine that I’ve made.
After obtaining the soul bone for her,
you’ll need to feed her once
around midnight for seven days.
Just direct the poison into the soul bone.
I’ll leave first, I’ll visit you later.
Little Freak, my wish has come true.
It’s time to leave.
You’re leaving?
I need to take care of something.
If I’m back in time, maybe I can catch your contest.
But don’t forget, you must not hurt Yan Yan.
For your sake, I won’t do her any harm.
But, please remind her that
don’t try to provoke me.
Old Freak, take care of yourself.
Don’t forget about the two iron balls.
You must take care of yourself too.
Little San, Frander and Er Long will follow me
and Mu Bai to hunt a soul beast.
We’ll leave the school for a few days.
You’ll study with
the advance class during this period.
Don’t slack off.
Don’t worry, Master. We’ll practice hard.
Little San, I will go home too.
I’ll entrust Xiao Wu to you.
Goodbye, have a safe journey.
Let’s go to class.
They are from Tian Dou Imperial School.
They’re so proud and rude.
They’re really annoying.
During the Advanced Soul Master School Contest,
we must show them
Shrek School’s ability.
Hey, where is my design?
Where is it? It was with me just now.
Gosh, I’ve lost my new school uniform design.
Goodbye, Dean.
Never mind, I’ll design a new one.
Thank goodness that the essence of the design
is all in my mind.
Little San, although our ability is stronger,
we lose in terms of appearance.
That’s right. We’re in a deep pit
in terms of appearance.
Totally trampled and absolutely squashed.
This indescribable colour.
This unimaginable design.
I can’t believe that
Dean Frander has such a poor taste.
Imagine us wearing this new uniform
to the soul master contest later.
In front of thousands of audiences.
By the way, you’ve been practicing in school.
Is there any difference
in terms of teaching methods?
There are no big differences.
But there are a lot of female soul masters.
It is rumored that they’re here because
they admire Deputy Dean Er Long.
There are six classes in the school.
It is arranged according
to the level of soul power.
If you reach a certain level
you can skip grades.
We’re all above Level 30.
We’re all in the advance class.
There are over thirty students
in advance class including us.
But most of them are older than us.
People like them,
how can they be a Grand Soul Land Master?
Okay, Brother.
Let’s not waste time talking to them.
Let’s go, I’ll show you the classroom.
Tai Long.
This...
[Next Episode]
Brother, look. What is that?
Do you want to break in?
Then come on.
Brother, there’s a lot of good food in Tian Dou City.
Let’s tour around, please?
Then we shall put this up for auction.
Brother, Tai Long keeps pestering me.
He pesters you?
Is he stronger than Boss Dai?
Seems like we need to be careful.
If you win,
I’ll admit that you’re qualified to sit here.