♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Show me what you’ve gained from this impulse.
The glory of Tang Clan
will surely reappear on Soul Land.
Soul Honor Tang San, I’m sorry
for suspecting you before.
Xiao Wu, we would be together forever, right?
I don’t want to see anyone be absent for breakfast.
Otherwise, you will be at your own risk.
I’ll give you a mission.
Without hurting them,
defeat six of them one by one.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 32]
Come on!
Mu Bai.
If you can break my third soul skill,
you win.
Tang San, beware.
Blue Silver Plant. Intertwine.
What’s going on?
Although Blue Silver Plant became thinner,
it’s combined with the character
of Human Faced Demon Spider.
The toughness is greatly increased.
Second soul skill.
Parasitic.
Blue Silver Plant is going to be cut off.
No. Tang San didn’t expect to win
with Blue Silver Plant alone.
He is using Blue Silver Plant to limit Mu Bai,
so he can get the time
to activate his third soul skill.
The true meaning
of a soul master of Controlling Branch
is to control the opponent
since the beginning of the fight
until the end of it.
Is this Little San’s third soul ring?
How can Blue Silver Plant defeat me?
Mu Bai, you’re reckless again.
It’s okay now.
Generally, soul masters of Controlling Branch
are weak at attacking.
But they’re strong in controlling.
Below Level 60,
they can defeat an opponent with
10-level differences, if they’re good enough.
This is my third soul skill,
Constraint of Spider Web.
Don’t move.
I’ll reabsorb the venom of the spider web.
Mu Bai, as a soul master of Storm Attack Branch,
Controlling Branch is your enemy.
When facing a soul master of Controlling Branch,
the best way is to not giving him
a chance to control you.
In the situation just now,
you should have kept distance
between you and him.
Every soul master has
his own merits and demerits.
There’s no perfect soul master in this world.
But there’s a perfect team.
The power of a person can’t have
the strongest strength.
But a team with mutual understanding
will be unbeatable.
Right now, the seven of you are a team.
When you face enemies together,
the first thing you should do,
is to make up for each others’ demerits,
and to optimise everyone’s merits.
Mu Bai, carry on with your class today.
Next, you’ll fight Oscar and Ma Hong Jun.
Yes, Grandmaster.
Boss Dai, you wouldn’t release
your anger on me, right?
Stop the nonsense. Let’s start.
Don’t be afraid, Fatty. I’ll help you.
The Merging of Phoenix.
Second soul skill, Firing Bathing Phoenix.
You!
White Tiger Protection Barrier.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
After the battle in Star Dou Forest,
I realize that using Phoenix Firing Line
in Firing Bathing Phoenix
can increase its force.
Although it uses up much soul power,
the effect is great.
Are you alright, Boss Dai?
Hm.
Boss Dai, I’m not fighting alone.
The mushroom sausage of Oscar.
Flying at the speed of
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent for a minute.
You only have one minute.
Get rid of this assistant first.
- After one minute, the fight will end.
- Flying Mushroom Sausage.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Although White Tiger Intense Light Wave
can attack from distance,
the distance is only within 20 meters.
- If it’s extended further,
- Super Recovery Big Sausage.
a great amount of soul power
will be used up.
So much soul power was used in the previous fight.
I’m afraid now...
Since Little Ao achieved Level 30,
he can make Super Recovery
Big Sausage in split second.
[Soul Land]
He keeps giving them to Fatty effortlessly.
With the support of sausages,
Fatty can obviously endure much longer.
Little San.
Yes, Master?
Since you used your
third soul skill to Mu Bai just now,
so help him fight an opponent.
Xiao Wu, show me your third soul skill.
Okay, Grandmaster.
Little San, you have to be careful.
Little San, do you have to be so alert?
Oh, no. That’s Xiao Wu’s
second soul skill, Charm.
I’ve succeeded.
I was silly.
If I had activated Purple Demon Eye
since I started,
I wouldn’t be so passive.
That’s the enemy of Charm.
Since we came to Shrek School,
I’ve not practiced with Xiao Wu.
I’m reckless this time.
Third soul skill.
Constraint of Spider Web.
Xiao Wu disappeared into thin air.
- First soul skill, Arched Body.
- Xiao Wu’s current Arched Body
must have increased up to 120% now.
It can’t be stood up by soul masters
at the same level.
Little San, you’ve lost.
No. Constraint of Spider Web.
Super, Super Recovery Big Sausage.
Okay. You may stop now.
Talk about your feelings.
It wasn’t fair. If my soul power wasn’t depleted,
they wouldn’t stand a chance.
Would your enemy come
only when your soul power is at its best?
You knew Oscar can provide mushroom sausages,
why did you let Ma Hong Jun eat them?
If you stopped him from the beginning,
or tried to save up your soul power,
you would have been the winner.
What a nice feeling.
I didn’t expect myself to defeat Boss Dai.
What a nice feeling I have.
Little Ao, the sausages are effective.
Of course. I’m a Soul Honor after all.
Are you proud of it?
Ma Hong Jun, let me ask you.
When the Flying Mushroom Sausage
of Oscar lost its effect,
why did you let him fall?
If Mu Bai still had the power to attack him,
what would you do?
And you. As a soul master of Food Branch,
most importantly, you should save yourself.
Even if he didn’t help you,
couldn’t you hold on to him to keep flying?
If Dai Mu Bai was an enemy, you would be dead.
Soul Honor?
Even if you’re a soul master
of the highest soul level of Food Branch,
you would be nothing in front of a war soul master.
Little San.
Master.
Talk about your fight with Xiao Wu.
Master, I was wrong. I shouldn’t have been reckless.
I was attacked by Xiao Wu’s second soul skill, Charm,
and was in a passive situation.
Before I knew what her third soul skill was,
I released the spider web hastily,
which caused myself to be
in a more passive situation.
It’s good that you realize your mistake.
Your mistake is the most serious one.
You need full power
even if you’re fighting a weak enemy.
You even made an unforgivable
mistake at the beginning.
Remember, soul masters of Controlling Branch
have to control themselves,
other than controlling your enemies.
Yes, Master.
Your third soul skill should be Teleport, right?
But it’s limited by distance.
If I guess it right,
that should be the power of Lightning Rabbit.
So your third soul ring is
a thousand-year-old Lightning Rabbit.
Teleport is one of the rarest soul skills.
You’ve surprised me well.
The combination of Teleport and Arched Body
will increase your killing effect greatly.
But why did you assume you would win
when you were choking Little San’s neck?
If you could be more careful,
when you saw Little San use Constraint of Spider Web,
you moved away from his attack
before attacking again,
you would have won,
instead of being controlled again.
Are you the so-called Genius Monsters?
Your performance today has disappointed me.
Everyone made unforgivable mistakes.
All of you must be punished.
Here is the punishment.
There are some rocks at the entrance.
Carry them, run to and back from Suo Tuo City.
No soul power is allowed.
You must do it 10 times by noon.
Little San, your mistake is the worst. Do it 12 times.
Got it, Master.
Remember, you’re a team.
If one person doesn’t complete it,
everyone isn’t allowed to eat.
Do it now.
Why aren’t you running?
We have to run as well?
Zhu Qing and I didn’t make mistakes.
Let me ask you. Who are they to you?
Schoolmates, partners.
If you want to be partners
that can rely on each other,
should you watch your partners be punished
while you’re resting?
I...
Turns out Grandmaster was prepared.
Master treats us differently.
Mu Bai, Fatty and I have
the biggest rocks in our baskets.
Xiao Wu, Zhu Qing and Little Ao follow,
while Rong Rong has the smallest.
It seems that Grandmaster isn’t unreasonable.
A couple of hundred kilometers,
without using soul power.
Isn’t this punishment too heavy?
They don’t eat a big breakfast for anything.
Without suffering as a team,
how can they become true partners?
Let’s go.
Up to you. But the fund of our school...
An honorable Soul Saint can’t even
get such little amount of money.
I don’t want to count on others.
Or else, with my strength...
[Next Episode]
Master mentioned just now,
we’re a team.
The aim of this punishment
is to train our collectivity.
Why are you treating me like this?
Second Brother, isn’t mine here?
You...
Boss, save me.
If you defeat the three of us,
I will release this pig.
You’re like a dead dog.
Finally, you’re suffering.
Watch this.