♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend ♪
♪ right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Tang San,
that’s enough. Just give in.
Everything I have was given by the Tang Clan.
Now I’ll return everything to you.
Wait!
Where...
is this?
We have three hundred families here
in Soul Saint Village.
Which of our grains and vegetables
ever had bad sales?
You’re right.
There was even a Soul Saint
from our village before.
Little San, Grandpa is here.
Go, come back before lunchtime.
I’m six years old and going to be awakened today.
They say Martial Soul can be anything,
then what would mine be?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 2]
Kids,
this is the handprint left by
the Soul Saint in our village.
It represents the glory of our village!
Greetings, honored Battle Soul Master.
Sorry to trouble you.
I don’t have much time, let’s begin now.
Alright, kids.
He’s the Battle Soul Master from Nuoding City.
He’ll lead you all to awaken your Martial Soul.
Please be cooperative during the awakening.
I hope one of you can be a soul master too.
Alright, that’s what you said the year before.
Do you think it’s easy to become a soul master?
I’ve been to six villages,
none of them has the soul power,
not to mention the Martial Soul.
That’s right.
Only the clans’ successors
can easily become soul masters.
It’s too difficult for ordinary people like us.
Get into a row, kids.
I’m Su Yun Tao, a Level 26 Great Soul Master,
and I’ll be your guide.
Now, I’m going to awaken
your Martial Soul one by one.
Remember, don’t be afraid
no matter what will happen.
You, come over.
Don’t be afraid.
Close your eyes and feel it.
Lone Wolf, join me!
Don’t move, I said don’t be afraid.
This is my Martial Soul, Lone Wolf.
If any of you become a soul master,
you’ll use the same ability.
Human transformed into a wolf?
No, he owns the ability of a wolf.
It’s amazing to see how a soul master
uses its Martial Soul.
Show me your right hand.
It’s a tool soul.
Sickle as your weapon, that’s quite unconvincing.
Your Martial Soul is Sickle, a tool soul.
Let’s see if you have the soul power.
If you do,
even one who has a tool soul
can be trained as a Battle Soul Master,
since Sickle is good in attack too.
Master, what should I do?
Keep your Martial Soul with your mind.
Summon it with the same way next time.
You have no soul power, you can’t be a soul master.
Go aside.
These are all just useless Martial Souls.
No attack, defence or assisting ability.
The Blue Silver Plant is considered
a standard for useless Martial Soul.
It feels warm.
It’s strange, my Xuan Tian Strike
seems to be absorbed.
Something in my body has been unlocked.
This kid might be...
Blue Silver Plant, another useless Martial Soul.
[Soul Land]
It seems I’ve wasted my time again
in Soul Saint Village.
Alright, kids. You may leave.
Uncle, you haven’t tested my soul power.
Forget it.
I’ve never seen anyone owns soul power
with Blue Silver Plant.
Let me try, Uncle.
This kid seems different.
Alright, since it won’t waste too much time.
What?
As long as my crystal ball has any reaction,
even if it’s just a weak faint light,
which means the soul power exists.
These dazzling lights.
Could this kid be...
Yes, it must be.
Kid, you’re born with full soul power.
Uncle, what’s full soul power?
Besides your form,
the strength of Martial Soul awakened...
also depends on the amount of soul power.
Most of you have no soul power
while your Martial Soul is awakened.
Just like the kids just now,
they’ll never be soul masters.
As long as soul power exists during awakening,
even if it’s just a faint light,
you can train it through meditation.
That’s the soul power we’re born with.
The soul power during awakening
decides the start of a soul master.
The more soul power you have, the faster you train.
While people who born with full soul power,
has the maximum soul power
during Martial Soul awakening.
Maximum soul power?
That crystal ball absorbed
my internal martial arts.
Could the soul power in this world
refers to internal martial arts?
Every ten levels of Martial Soul is given a title.
You’re called a Soul Warrior after awakening.
Those with the lowest soul power
will be a Level 1 Soul Warrior,
and the highest will be a Level 10 Soul Warrior.
Those with maximum soul power are at Level 10,
which are those born with full soul power.
I’ve never met someone who
born with full soul power.
When I was awakened,
it was just a Level 2 soul power.
It can only reach Level 10?
Can’t it be higher?
Of course not.
Without a soul ring,
no matter how hard you train,
you’ll never get the next title.
Soul ring is the light around your body just now?
You’re at Level 26,
so you have two soul rings.
Exactly.
Your case is special.
It’s so rare to see someone
born with full soul power.
But, it’s such a waste.
Even if your Martial Soul is just a farm tool,
it’s much better compared with
the useless Blue Silver Plant.
Then, I can...
It seems like I need a soul ring...
to break through the second level.
However, what’s a soul ring?
Uncle?
Master.
How is it?
Is there any kid in our village
who can be a soul master?
There’s only one,
born with full soul power.
Born with full soul power?
Unluckily, his Martial Soul is Blue Silver Plant.
Do you get it?
Blue Silver Plant.
Born with full soul power,
but has Blue Silver Plant.
This is so...
Master,
can’t we train with Blue Silver Plant?
We can, but...
even if his power increases, what do you think...
a Blue Silver Plant can evolve to?
It’s still a useless Martial Soul.
Such a waste for this full soul power.
Alright, I’d better get going.
I’m heading to another village.
Full soul power, but useless Martial Soul.
Grandpa Jack, what’s a soul ring?
How do I get one?
I have no idea either.
I think you need to hunt for soul beasts
in order to get a soul ring.
That’s very dangerous,
unless you’re a soul master.
Soul ring, soul beast.
Little San.
Are you the one who has full soul power
but with Blue Silver Plant?
I am.
Little San, I didn’t expect that
you’re so extraordinary.
Too bad, your father isn’t putting enough effort...
to inherit a good Martial Soul to you.
Or else,
you might be the second Soul Saint
in our village.
Tell me,
are you willing to join
soul master’s training school?
You can learn exactly every knowledge
about Martial Soul only from there.
My father has to agree first.
Good boy, we should get his permission.
Let’s go, let me send you home.
Tang Hao!
Who’s making a fuss there?
Old Jack, what is it?
It is your son’s awakening day,
don’t you know how important it is?
Other parents sent their kids over,
yet you just treat it like another normal day.
Little San, what’s your Martial Soul?
It’s Blue Silver Plant, Dad.
Is he...
Even though it’s only Blue Silver Plant,
but Little San was born with full soul power!
I’ve decided...
to give the only apprentice position in our village...
to Little San...
to learn at Beginner Soul Master School
in Nuoding City.
We’ll take care of the travel fee.
Blue Silver Plant.
No way.
[Next Episode]
Soul master,
what’s the use of it?
Look carefully.
Tang Hao!
Unless it’s a life-and-death matter,
never use the hammer.