♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
It’s my turn now!
The Grand Soul Land Master.
Who is it? How dare you
intrude The Sacred Temple!
[Soul Land]
[Episode 92]
No! If any one of us is injured,
you will be my enemy.
You should have understood.
With just a few of you,
you can’t beat me.
If you haven’t eaten
the Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum,
you will be dead by now.
Your target should be me.
All right. Let them go and
I’ll let you punish as you wish.
- Brother!
- Brother San!
Kid. You’re very smart.
But smart people usually don’t live long.
Since your friend is willing
to sacrifice himself,
you don’t have to persevere anymore.
I will make it quick.
No! Shrek Seven Devils are always one.
If I can’t face and move forward
together with my brothers,
do you think I can achieve something
in the future?
Achievement?
If you stop here, what can you achieve?
Stop the crap! Just do it!
I’ll handle Tang San first.
Then I’ll take you home.
I don’t believe you won’t succumb to me.
Your talents are quite good.
I want to bring all of you back
and train you well.
Third soul skill, Breath Enchantment!
He can actually seal us instantly.
Brother San, I can’t move!
My soul power can’t be used either.
No!
Er Long, no!
- Mother!
- Teacher Er Long!
Er Long. Even though you want to protect Little San,
you shouldn’t risk your life.
The mutated Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
is nothing great.
If you dare to hurt Little San,
the Golden Iron Triangle will never let you go.
Today, I will settle you as well.
Greetings to Your Holiness.
You may leave now.
Yes!
Bibi Dong.
Please address me properly.
Yes, Your Holiness.
Why do you come to me?
Your Holiness, I’d like to know
how you overcame the difficulties
of Twin Martial Souls.
You don’t have to know about this.
I have a disciple.
He has cultivated under me
for about seven to eight years.
Luckily,
he owns Twin Martial Souls as you do.
I hope to train him to become a strong one.
Why do I have to help you?
Shall I let you train a strong person
to oppose me in the future?
No. Of course not.
If you can tell me how you made it,
I promise that
my disciple will never oppose
the Martial Soul Hall.
Yu Xiao Gang.
Even if I tell you the secret of
Twin Martial Souls now,
your disciple won’t have a chance
to know about it.
Your Holiness. What do you mean by that?
Three days ago,
I sent killers to the path where
the participants head to Tian Dou Empire.
The target is your disciple
who comes from Hao Tian Tribe.
What are you talking about?
[Soul Land]
What’s so great by bullying the kids?
The Unrivaled Dragon Serpent couple?
Oh, right.
The Exotic Beast School where
Meng Yi Ran was in has been promoted.
The Unrivaled Dragon Serpent couple.
It’s been so long since we met,
Unrivaled Dragon Serpent couple.
You’re quite bold.
How dare you appear at this moment?
Is it worth for you to call over these many
to trouble these youngsters?
You should know that
there’s always no reason for us to do this.
Then, there’s no need of reasons
for me to save Tang San.
You’re overconfident.
Fifth soul skill, Frosty Gather!
Mystifying!
Don’t laugh at me if I can’t do it well.
Dragon Tail Wing!
That’s not a big deal.
Old Man.
First soul skill, Serpent Blade!
Scatter.
Although tool martial soul
can restrain plant martial soul,
the Grand Soul Land Master
is so powerful that
he can restrain the Unrivaled Dragon
Serpent couple only with a few moves.
This is a huge pressure caused by the level gap.
The real strength of
this Grand Soul Land Master
should have overtaken most of
the Grand Soul Land Masters.
It’s disgusting. Drop dead!
Serpent Transformation!
Dragon Stick!
Serpent Blade!
Martial Soul Fusion Skill!
Dragon Serpent Joint Strike!
Dragon Serpent is as good as expected.
Wind and sand have a strong restraint on
most of the Plant Branch Martial Souls.
The strength has increased
after the martial soul fusion of Dragon Serpent.
Not only wind and sand.
This tactic is called
Dragon Serpent Joint Strike.
Why is there only strength of dragon
but not coldness of serpent?
It’s the serpent venom that accelerated
the withering of petals.
Serpent venom is concealed in the sand
and scattered invisibly.
And Plant Branch Martial Soul
can double the restraint with the wind and sand.
What a great Dragon Serpent Joint Strike.
What? He actually took over
the head hammer of the dragon.
That is not a head hammer.
Its real purpose is to fool me to touch
the venom on its head.
I was tricked.
Indulge in self-admiration.
Sixth soul skill, Clouds of Golden Pistil!
Dragon Venom!
How dare you Soul Emperors challenge
the Grand Soul Land Master! Don’t...
This odour...
Old Man! The odour in your mouth
made me can’t even open my eyes!
It’s really...
This is...
Don’t vomit in my mouth!
It’s so disgusting!
You asked for it.
Dragon Venom!
Seventh soul skill!
Martial soul form!
What happened? Serpent Venom
didn’t work on him at all.
I understand.
His martial soul form has multiplied
his soul power.
This battle between Venom
and Chrysanthemum
has completely evolved into
a competition of soul power.
But the Clouds of Golden Pistil...
What a frightening power.
He even defeated
the Dragon Serpent Joint Strike.
Yi Ran!
You mean little thing!
I treat both of you as noble
with great virtue and high prestige.
Today, I’ll let you go.
Why don’t you stop it?
Seniors, they are targeting us.
There’s no need for you and your family
to sacrifice for us.
We will repay for your kindness,
if there’s a chance.
Take Meng Yi Ran and leave.
Yi Ran!
Done. This is over.
There are really too many people
who shouldn’t appear today.
Lordiaara. Fight a quick battle.
Yes, Lord.
A Grand Soul Land Master.
A Great Soul Land Master.
Am I really going to die here today?
My friends, Xiao Wu, Old Freak and Dad.
I still have many things to do. But...
Ju Hua Guan!
Do you think there’s no one else in Shrek School?
Old Freak.
Finally, our saviour is here.
Senior Dugu, why are you here?
Old Venom Freak.
When did you become
the lackey of this school?
You are a lackey!
I am a minister elder of Shrek School.
Is that a problem?
Tang San is my brother.
If you want to kill him,
you have to get through me first.
Dugu Bo. You have to think properly.
What’s the result of going against us?
Us? He mentioned us many times.
He seems to have meant something.
Is it...
It’s said that Shrek has a disciple
from Hao Tian Tribe.
He’s broken through Level 40
at a very young age.
Twin Martial Souls. Owning the
fourth soul ring of Decade Millennium
and even the soul bone.
Such a young talent.
Yet, he’s close to
Qibao Amber Tribe and Tian Dou Empire.
Since he can’t be one of the Martial Soul Hall,
I’ll just kill him.
Bibi Dong, don’t go too far!
Yu Xiao Gang, you will also get anxious.
[Next Episode]
For your disciple,
do you want to fight against Martial Soul Hall?
Yu Xiao Gang, you will also get anxious.
I want you to go through
the sufferings that I experienced.
Since you attacked him,
you have to be ready for
the revenge from the person.
It’s only the ghost shadow
and no soul ring is seen.
If you dare to touch Tang San,
just wait for the revenge of death!
Do you think I dare not touch you?