♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
To us,
the real threat will be the chosen team
from Martial Soul Hall.
Is Sister Huo Wu here?
I’m here to apologize.
Get into the cart.
There are so many crows in this lousy place.
Why isn’t there anything else?
Everyone, keep quiet. Something is happening.
Enemy attack!
Qin Ming!
Assembly of Power!
He is oppressing. He’s a Great Soul Land Master.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 91]
The Great Soul Land Master?
You guys go and deal with him.
Handle these children to me.
Go after them!
Senior shall be alright, right?
Looking at his skill,
he must have almost recovered.
It shouldn’t be a problem to deal with
about 10 men in black.
However, our side...
You guys have some abilities at a young age.
Unfortunately, you’re going to
lose your lives today.
Seventh soul skill, Golden Eagle Form!
Purple Demon Eye.
Be careful, guys. There are
two more Soul Kings behind us!
Brother San, what shall we do now?
The opponents are the Great Soul Land Master
and two Soul Kings.
The oppression he gave me
is nothing lesser compared with the Old Freak.
If my Hao Tian Hammer has its soul ring,
there’s still hope.
Guys, let’s fight or die trying.
Master San, I’ll do this with you.
Okay.
Firstly, let’s use Human Meteor Hammer Formation
to break his defense.
Xiao Wu, use your Eight Flinging
if you can get near him.
Tai Long, Jing Ling,
Huang Yuan, Jiang Zhu.
You guys defend
the two Soul Kings behind.
- Okay.
Er Long! The kids are in danger!
Let’s get rid of the opponents soon
and help the kids!
Okay!
Seventh soul skill, Dragon Form!
It’s not that easy to end this!
Sixth soul skill, Gear Blade Armour!
My scales!
You can attack me, but you can’t damage my scales!
You have really got me angry!
Jiubao Boosts!
First, strength! Third, soul!
Fourth soul skill, White Tiger Meteor Strike!
Fourth soul skill, Ghost Shadow Doppelganger!
Fourth soul skill, Phoenix Strike!
Sixth soul skill, Winged Form!
Most of our team members are just kids.
Yet, you make such ruthless act on them!
You’d better take care of yourself!
I won’t let you escape even with wings!
Arrogant! Seventh soul skill,
Martial Soul Form!
Seventh soul skill!
Eagle Owl’s True Form!
I’ve broken his wing that easily?
He must have shown his defense soul skill.
But there’s no effect.
Why is the golden light on him
is getting brighter?
It’s said that there’s
one kind of eagles in Soul Land.
Mother eagle will break their baby
eagles’ wings when they learn to fly.
So, their wings and bones
have a strong regeneration ability.
Is it...
Brother, I’ll go now.
Initially, I wanted to see your skills.
Now that I see there’s no big deal.
It’s my turn now.
Xiao Wu, come back!
Eighth soul skill, Blood Regeneration!
Good chance.
First soul skill, Arched Body.
It’s bad. Time’s up for
Swift Flight Mushroom Sausage!
Come back! Guys, come back!
Xiao Wu!
[Soul Land]
It’s just a lousy flower.
Yet, you want to protect your master.
Let me crush you and your master!
Stop it!
The Grand Soul Land Master?
He is a Grand Soul Land Master.
Lord.
Lord? They are accomplices.
This is Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
You actually got the recognition
from Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
Even if the hope is tiny,
I have to protect Xiao Wu too.
There’s only one chance.
No!
Why?
Why isn’t me the one who gets
the Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet?
If I got the Lovesick
Heartbroken Scarlet,
I could also reach that level.
Lordiaara, you can take the rest.
You cannot harm this girl.
It’s been so many years.
The legendary Celestial Flower King
has finally appeared
and recognized its master.
I am willing to protect her forever.
Girl, show me your
Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
Can you?
Brother. For you, even if I couldn’t be a human...
No.
It’s really celestial.
Okay. I shouldn’t have
offended your nobility.
He really didn’t discover my identity.
Did the Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet
cover my identity?
To keep maintaining at the martial soul form
would deplete our soul power very fast.
We must end this soon.
Fourth soul skill, White Tiger Meteor Strike!
Wait a moment!
Lord!
Boss Dai!
I am alright.
There are seven kinds of heat
flowing in my body.
They’re urging my soul power.
It not only doesn’t cause any discomfort,
I even feel that my soul power
is growing dramatically.
What is actually happening?
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum?
It’s really Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum.
You’ve eaten this celestial flower before.
He knows about Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum.
This is...
Have you eaten anything like this?
Yes.
That’s right.
No wonder there’s such a golden light on you.
Lordiaara. You cannot hurt this kid either.
He has a fate with me.
Kid. Are you willing to take me as your teacher?
With your talent,
plus you’ve eaten Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum,
your future achievement will be
as good as mine.
I knew that this master
has a weird personality.
But he wanted to accept disciple
under this situation.
Teaching from the Grand Soul Land Master
is very tempting to any soul masters.
He can also save his life.
How would the kid reject?
I can take you as my teacher.
But I have conditions.
Okay.
She is my fiancée.
She’s also my partner for
the Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
You cannot hurt her.
Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
Great. I promise.
We are the closest friends.
We’ve always cooperated well.
You cannot hurt them either.
Master! They are the aim of our mission!
I can’t decide when it comes to
the aim of our mission.
But I can promise you
to kill only one person. All right?
Who is it? How dare you intrude
The Sacred Temple!
Pope token?
Greeting to the Elder.
Lead me to the Pope.
[Next Episode]
If any one of us is injured,
you will be my enemy.
Ju Hua Guan!
Do you think there’s no one else in Shrek School?
What’s so great by bullying the kids?
You should have understood.
With just a few of you,
you can’t beat me.
Yu Xiao Gang.
Even if I tell you the secret
of Twin Martial Souls now,
your disciple won’t have a chance
to know about it.
Is this your revenge on me?
Your target should be me.
Let them go and
I’ll let you punish as you wish.