♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
[415 kilometers]
We’ve caught the ugliest one.
Let the second ugliest one save him.
As you wish.
Next time, you’ll be
in worse condition than this knife.
Then leave!
Without suffering together,
how can they be real partners?
[30m left to reach 830km]
[Soul Land]
[Epiode 34]
[Three months later]
Training is done.
Registered as a Soul Honor.
Finally, we’re on holiday.
Malicious Attack. Back-tightening crossbow.
In just 3 months,
most of the machine parts
of the hidden weapon are done.
The craft of Iron’s Brother is indeed satisfying.
Next, I’ll just assemble and give them to everyone,
and teach them how to use it.
Wow, who is this?
Why do you have a pig head?
Super Recovery Big Sausage.
Detestable! That rotter!
Who hit you?
I was hit by a wretched man.
It was embarrassing.
Fatty, were you fighting someone for a woman?
That’s why you were hit, right?
What are you saying?
I was just helping someone
in need of justice.
Fatty, what happened to you?
Boss Dai, you have to help me find justice.
Look at how my handsome face
is distorted.
What actually happened? Tell us first.
I am furious for a beauty.
We’re finally on holiday.
So I contacted the beauty that I met a few days ago.
And then a rogue interrupted.
Registration fee is 10 gold soul coins.
Beauty, may I know
how many gold soul coins my love worth?
Stupid.
Beauty.
This place is remote.
It isn’t safe to be here alone at night.
Let me send you home.
Stupid.
Why are you so annoying?
Do you think you can escape?
What a beauty.
It seems I won’t be lonely tonight.
What are you doing?
Don’t get in my way.
Run.
You rogue.
How dare you harass my woman?
Let’s see if my fist is okay with that.
The Merging of Phoenix.
So you fought with him?
Of course. Neither beauty and delicacy
can be let down.
But who knew that fellow
was a Soul Sect with four soul rings.
So I became like this.
The worst thing is
he crossed over my body in front of everyone.
Boss Dai, Second Brother, Brother San.
You have to do me justice.
What is his name?
Bu Le or something.
Then I found out,
that fellow is a notorious ruffian here.
He’s involved in illegal business
and loves to harass young and beautiful girls.
Normal folks are no match to soul masters.
Bu Le, a Soul Sect.
Just because he’s capable,
he’s doing some villain business.
He’s a black sheep of all soul masters.
That’s right. He even hit Fatty.
As a soul master, he’s bullying the weak.
That’s humiliating.
It seems
this is the time for Shrek School
to do something.
Yes, we have to help Fatty find justice.
Soul masters are unlike common folks.
If we start fighting out of revenge
and act violently, which is an abuse of our talent.
But if it’s to punish the evil,
and defend peace,
it shouldn’t be refused.
That’s right.
[Soul Land]
Hurry up. We may stop him if we go now.
Where are you creeping to?
Fatty, why is your face swollen?
Who’s so cruel to hit you to hits point?
Boss Dai, could it be you?
Would I be so cruel to my brother?
Fatty wanted to be a hero to save a beauty,
but he lost.
We’re going to punish the evil now.
That’s cool. Count me in.
That person is a pervert.
Besides, he has a higher soul power than us.
It’s too dangerous for a girl.
What? That’s a better reason
for me to come along.
I have to do justice for girls.
Alright then. This is dangerous.
But we’ll face it together.
That fellow has higher soul power than us.
Tell us his condition in details.
He’s quite tall.
His face is so black, it’s as if
he just crawled out from a stove.
His Martial Soul is odd.
It feels like it has a similar function
to Brother San’s Martial Soul.
A soul master of Controlling Branch.
I think so.
His Martial Soul looks like two claws.
They are pitch black.
When they’re summoned, they would fly to his back,
like a pair of little wings.
That’s so disgusting.
Two pitch-black claws, flying to his back?
What kind of weird Martial Soul is that?
When he fought me, he used two soul skills.
First, he enlarged the claws,
to block my Phoenix Firing Line.
The second one was to produce some black smoke.
The black sticky liquid in the smoke
limited my body movement.
He then hid in the smoke.
I couldn’t attack him.
So I was entangled by the slime,
wrapped like a dumpling.
And then he hit me like his sandbag.
Soul Sect should have four soul skills.
That means, two are still unknown.
Brother San, the three of you are Soul Honors,
in addition to me, a soul master at Level 27,
would we still be afraid of him?
I have my mushroom sausage.
If we can’t defeat him, we’ll just flee.
If I’m right,
his Martial Soul is born to restrain flame.
So your Evil Flame wouldn’t work on him at all.
Since there are two unknown soul skills,
we can’t plan a strategy, which increases the risk.
Here it is?
That’s right. It’s said that Bu Le
is active around here at night.
This place is remote.
The residents won’t be disturbed.
It’s good to lay an ambush.
Nothing suspicious is found.
That’s bad.
We wouldn’t know when he will appear.
I have an idea.
My beauty, wait right here for me.
Act accordingly.
Hello, little girl.
Hello, Uncle. Is there a candy shop around here?
Xiao Wu would like to have candies.
Xiao Wu, you’re such a cute girl.
Come with me. I’ll take you to buy candies.
Then I’ll send you home, okay?
Thank you, Uncle.
Come with me.
Little San, is that really Xiao Wu?
What is she planning?
This girl doesn’t change at all.
Let’s follow up. Just in case.
Uncle, where is the candy shop?
It’s dark here. I’m a little scared.
Little girl, don’t be afraid. I’ll protect you.
Uncle, you should protect yourself.
Where are you running to?
It’s Xiao Wu’s Charm and her third soul skill, Teleport.
[Next Episode]
Uncle, you should protect yourself.
Hey, Xiao Gang,
those time we traveled
around Soul Land was the best.
Perhaps,
One day, we’ll resume the happiness.
Would Bu Le have it all for himself?
Welcome to Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
The 13th score soul area.
Second round of double soul battle starts now.