♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Every soul master has his own merits and demerits.
There are no perfect soul masters in this world.
But there’s a perfect team.
Are you the so-called Genius Monsters?
Your performance today has disappointed me.
Everyone made unforgivable mistakes.
Now, all of you must be punished.
Let’s go.
Without suffering as a team,
how can they be true partners?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 33]
[Need 830km]
Mu Bai.
Little San, what’s going on?
Master mentioned just now,
we’re a team.
We both are strong enough,
but they may not be.
Perhaps the aim of this punishment
is to train our collectivity.
Collectivity?
That’s right.
We just started but I’m already so done.
This group task is not achievable.
Rong Rong.
Xiao Wu, how can you be so strong?
I’m also at Level 30.
But my burden is the same as Zhu Qing.
Of course, it’s lighter for me.
Why don’t we cheat?
Let’s eat some Recovery Sausage of Little Ao.
Cheat?
Fatty, are you sure Grandmaster
isn’t monitoring us secretly?
If it’s found out...
I hid two eggs this morning.
For us all, let’s split them to seven shares.
Re-energizing isn’t considered
as cheating, right?
How can we split two eggs into seven portions?
Rong Rong and I from Assisting Branch
shall eat them then.
Take it away.
I don’t want to eat your food.
Zhu Qing, a girl should take care of herself.
Why are you treating me like this?
Second Brother, what about me?
Oscar, give me your rocks.
What?
Although we can’t use soul power,
as a team,
as long as everyone finishes
without changing the total burden,
the task is done.
What about this? From now on,
we’ll run at Rong Rong’s speed.
So we’ll save our energy.
When someone can no longer take it,
we’ll help each other.
What do you think?
Little Ao, you are so smart.
Don’t you know I was called
Wise Prince when I was small?
This is nothing.
Look, it’s them from Shrek School.
Are they training?
We’ll give them a lesson.
[83km]
Drink some water before continue.
It’s so salty. Is much salt added to this?
Is it for re-energizing?
Let’s go.
[128km]
[154km]
[166km]
[249km]
[332km]
[415km]
[507km]
Little Ao, rocks.
Thank you.
[598km]
[664km]
[714km]
Which round is this?
The ninth. Hang in there, everyone.
I can’t do this anymore.
Are you from Cang Hui School?
Finally, you’re suffering.
You’re like a dead dog.
Do you want a piece of bone?
We’ve been waiting for you.
Are you exhausted now?
Boss, save me.
We’ve caught the ugliest one.
Let the second ugliest one save him.
If you defeat the three of us,
I will release this pig.
As you wish.
Watch this.
Stop looking. It’s here.
Next time, you’ll be in a worse condition
than this knife.
Do you want more? Then leave!
Noon has passed. We won’t get lunch.
Let’s slow down, or else I’ll die.
Didn’t you realize we’ve been getting slower.
But the temperature of the salt water
Grandmaster prepared remains the same.
Obviously, Grandmaster has calculated our energy.
If we’re back too late, I’m afraid...
Boss Dai, you’re still okay?
Fatty, remember. A man never says he’s not okay.
Give me.
Let me help you, Zhu Qing.
You have to run two more rounds than us.
How will you hold on?
[747km]
They’re from Cang Hui School.
It seems we have to focus on them
on Soul Master Contest.
[Soul Land]
[825km]
Boss Dai.
- Are you okay?
- Mu Bai, how are you?
You’ve shared many of our rocks.
You can’t go on.
Brothers, there’s one last round.
Let’s hold on. No one should be left behind.
Boss Dai, give it back to me.
And me.
I feel better now.
I don’t know why
I feel very energetic.
Since you mention it, it’s true.
[3km left to reach 830km]
Little San, let me take it myself in the last part.
No, I can do this.
Little Ao, you’re like a man today.
Why did you come to Shrek School?
Remember, since you are in Shrek School,
you’re a team.
Without suffering together,
how can they be real partners?
[100m left to reach 830km]
[30m left to reach 830km]
[5m left to reach 830km]
[4m left to reach 830km]
[3m left to reach 830km]
[2m left to reach 830km]
[1m left to reach 830km]
[830km]
12 rounds. There are two more rounds.
Brother, I’ll accompany you.
Little San, I’ll accompany you as well.
It’s a herbal bath.
I was alone in my previous life.
I never knew friendship.
I’m compensated in this life. This is great.
[Have a meal at the canteen
when you’re awake. Grandmaster.]
Have a meal at the canteen
when you’re awake. Grandmaster.
[Train your soul power before sunrise.
Class starts in the morning. Grandmaster.]
Grandmaster is really cruel.
He’s fiercer than Dean Frander.
Little San, did Grandmaster train you like this back then?
This is my first time to have such training.
I’m so hungry. Where’s the food?
Slow down.
Brother, did you complete that two rounds?
No. Mu Bai and I fainted as well.
We woke up in the wooden bucket.
Were you naked as well?
There was a note in our dorm,
saying that women in the village
took off our clothes.
Xiao Wu, you’re so cute when you blush, like an apple.
Oscar and the rest are not awake.
They must be very tired. Let’s train.
Go ahead. Just leave this to me.
Very good.
Someone didn’t complete the punishment.
However,
you have reflected the spirit
of not leaving behind and not giving up.
Before the class starts today,
Tang San, complete that two rounds.
Yes.
Brother, I’ll accompany you,
as I promised yesterday.
Let’s go together. Aren’t we a team?
It’s good to warm up.
I should lose some weight.
It isn’t easy to be this fat.
Stop the nonsense. Keep up.
This group of youngsters
is how privileged people should look like.
[3 Months Later]
Training is done.
Registered as a Soul Honor.
Finally, we’re on holiday.
[Next Episode]
Do you think you can escape?
I have an idea.
What is that person’s name?
Hello, Uncle.
You have to help me find justice.
What’s actually going on?
What a beauty.
It seems I won’t be lonely tonight.