♪ The throne escape its fate ♪
♪ Martial Soul pulls us together ♪
♪ The scars on your face, hidden by your laughter ♪
♪ Finding the lapis lazuli ♪
♪ Looking back at our shattered memories ♪
♪ Courage and belief will bring us to victory ♪
♪ Nothing can replace the seven creatures ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
♪ Life is full of ups and downs ♪
♪ Who will stand for justice? ♪
♪ Our memories together ♪
♪ They should be cherished ♪
♪ The short yet long four seasons ♪
♪ If we must go through it ♪
♪ Five years of separation ♪
♪ Contains all the loneliness ♪
♪ Courage to walk alone to a far distance ♪
♪ It’s written in our teenage dreams ♪
♪ We’ll remember this when we reunite once again ♪
♪ Touching memories ♪
♪ Not giving up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Soul bone.
Brother.
Yesterday, did someone attack you?
It’s Shi Nian from Cang Hui School.
He’s dead.
And I’ve got his soul bone.
Our opponent for the next round is Chi Huo School.
Welcome to the Central Arena
of the eleventh preliminary.
Today, Shrek School will
fight against Chi Huo School.
This team has great teamwork.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 76]
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Third soul skill.
Raining Sparks.
It’s a supporting soul skill that
amplifies its members’ attack.
It’s time.
To win, we must first catch its leader.
Don’t you dare!
They’re luring their opponent.
Brother has fallen into their trap
and has to fight against the five of them.
I’ve been waiting for you.
The previous six teams
have lost to Tang San like this.
I wonder if Huo Wu Shuang can avoid it.
Third soul skill.
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Wow.
Not this easy.
Third soul skill.
Repelling Fire Ring.
It’s a powerful mono-defense type
repulsing soul skill.
What a good support and control.
It seems like they are
two supports and one control.
But we can see them as
three Control Branch soul masters.
They’re controlling using
their supporting skills,
and assisting their teammates selectively.
This is similar to Rong Rong.
Gosh, I’m being tricked.
It’s a double trap.
They even considered
Little San’s Constraint of Spider Web.
Tang San, you’re the only one left now.
Huo Wu Shuang pretended that he’s tricked
to lure Dai Mu Bai
and the other three to attack.
And Repelling Fire Ring was used to strike back.
Next, they only need to fight Little San with all might.
Boss Fu.
I’ve gained another sponsorship.
Xiao Gang, do you think Little San can handle this?
Third soul skill, Raining Sparks.
It’s over, Tang San.
Third soul skill.
Dragon’s Rage.
Flamingo Clone.
Second soul skill.
Seven Star Flame.
Gosh, Little San is all surrounded.
You’re too naive.
How can a soul master of Controlling Branch fight
the one of Storm Attack Branch?
What is he doing?
Oh, is he trying to suicide?
You’ve come just in time.
Third soul skill.
Seven Star Fire Bullet.
Ghostly Trace.
What happened?
Because I’m not just a soul master.
What is that step? Is that a soul skill?
Soul bone?
I don’t think so.
I didn’t detect any soul power from his steps.
This boy is keeping a lot of secrets.
Well done, Master San.
I just need to drag for a while
until the leader comes.
First soul skill.
Fire Roar.
How is this possible?
Xuan Tian Strike.
Awesome, you’ve turned the table immediately.
Third soul skill,
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Third soul skill, Repelling Fire Ring.
Unluckily, no matter how good your tactics are,
you can’t run away from
the repel of Repelling Fire Ring.
Repelling Fire Ring can protect them
for a while, but not forever.
The formation has suddenly changed.
What are they doing?
Fourth soul skill.
Third soul skill.
Raining Sparks.
Under full support of two Support Branch
soul master, this fourth soul skill
may surpass the fifth soul skill
of normal soul masters.
Fire Dance Dazzling Sun.
The fire is implicit
and not outgoing at all.
This Chi Huo girl has great control over her Martial Soul.
Little San...
You’re indeed powerful.
But the victory is ours.
First soul skill.
Intertwine.
Brother.
Xiao Wu, do you think that Little San will do
something that he’s not certain of?
Have you found Teacher Shi Nian?
Two days ago, Teacher Shi said
that he would settle Shrek School.
Is it Shrek School that did something?
If it was Shrek School,
then let them...
They’re targeting Little San the whole time.
They think that if they defeat Little San,
the rest will not be a problem.
But Fiery Dance Blazing Sun is powerful.
Little San may be...
Will he die in the fire?
Controlling such a great power
is still barely manageable for me.
It’s time to reduce the strength.
If he’s dead, I can’t answer the school either...
You’re so naive.
From the start, you’ve been misled by me.
You thought that fire element
Martial Soul would restrain my ability.
Your cooperation and
your Fiery Dance attack are good too.
Too bad.
My Blue Silver Plant
is immune to fire.
After consuming
Fiery Soft Apricot and Octa Dark Frost,
my Blue Silver Plant is
resistant to both water and fire.
Fourth soul skill.
Blue Silver Cage.
[Soul Land]
To release Fiery Dance Blazing Sun,
you’ve used up
three of your supports’ soul power.
Can you still escape from this cage?
You’ve lost in the bet.
Third soul skill.
This rascal...
The game is set.
Chi Huo School’s soul power has been used up.
Darn it.
We admit our defeat.
Well done.
I hereby announce, the winner of this round is
Shrek School!
Shrek School.
We’ll meet again.
Next time, you won’t be this lucky.
I’ll wait for it.
Little San, you’re so awesome.
Now,
Shrek School has won for all eleven rounds.
We’re close to being the Champion Team.
I’ll take revenge for you later.
We can’t do this, can you?
Wu Shuang, you know I didn’t mean that.
Tang San is immune to fire,
but he may not be immune to wind.
Feng Xiao Tian, you want to have
a relationship with me, right?
Yes or no?
Yes, I’ve always liked you.
Great, if you defeat Shrek Team,
defeat Tang San,
I will agree to be with you.
Brother, let’s go.
Tang San, we’ll wait and see.
I, Feng Xiao Tian will beat you for sure.
Little San, you’ve shown too many abilities.
Displaying too much is not advisable.
Grandmaster, you’ve seen it too.
Our opponent is too powerful.
If Little San didn’t act like that, it’s hard for us to win.
Skip the next match.
Grandmaster, please let Tang San join it.
I understand your worries.
But for these children,
Continental Soul Master School
Elite Tournament is a rare chance.
Back then, I didn’t have the chance to join it.
I can only sit and watch at the side.
I still can’t forget that powerless feeling.
Master, please let me join it.
After this tournament, we’re going to graduate.
Let us do something for our school,
and make up for Senior Qin’s regret.
Grandmaster, please let Little San join the battle.
Little San is the soul of Shrek Team.
We can’t proceed without him.
Boss Dai.
You’re like your father,
seems gentle yet tough.
But do remember that
you’ll break easily if you’re too tough.
Your father has suffered from this.
Dad.
If you want to join it, then do it.
After the tournament,
I’ll arrange you to go
for a long term private practice.
Okay.
This round, we’re against Cang Hui School.
Cang Hui?
That loser?
Yes, it’ll be easy to win them.
No matter what kind of the opponent,
you must not let your guards down.
Yes, Grandmaster.
Cang Hui.
Grandmaster, Senior Qin,
why not let me join for this round?
I won’t use my fourth soul skill, okay?
No way. Your ability is very special.
You must save it up during the preliminary.
Grandmaster, Teacher Qin.
For this round, I think we should
let Zhu Qing replace Jiang Zhu.
Oh, why do you think so, Little San?
Yes, Little San.
When we were facing Chi Huo School,
we didn’t send Zhu Qing.
Cang Hui School has only
lost for three rounds till now.
Their ranking is even higher than
Elephant Armoured School.
Their ability should not be looked down on.
And the preliminary have only three rounds left.
They still need at least two more victories
to ensure their ticket to go to the next round.
This round’s victory is crucial to them.
Plus the grudge they have with our Shrek School,
they will surely do their best for this round.
We must be extra careful.
This time,
let’s end the grudges
between Shrek School and Cang Hui School.
[Next Episode]
Are you from Shrek School?
Let’s meet them.
Finally, I don’t need to be in disguise.
Seven in One Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
Don’t let your guards down.
You’re indeed steady and calm.
But all tactics and skills are futile,
when facing absolute strength.
Shrek School,
goodbye.