♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high
even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend
right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Where did you get this belt?
My master gave it to me.
Take the crystal with you.
Does he know Master?
Brother. What on Earth is this crystal?
This is a hair crystal.
Look.
Once the hair gold penetrates
into the human body,
unless using some special tactics,
otherwise, you’ll have to cut off
the muscles that are curled up.
In this world, it’s not the weapon
that decides its vice.
It’s up to the person who uses it.
It’s impossible. This is a soul master school?
The meaning of Shrek School...
is a monster school.
We only accept “monsters” but not ordinary people.
Teacher, the two of us want to register.
Rabbit.
Yours is Blue Silver Plant.
You can practice so fast with Blue Silver Plant.
Am I a monster?
[Soul Land]
[Episode 13]
You will undergo the second exam here.
The teacher will tell you what to do.
I want to go out and check.
Sausages! Sausages for sale! Have a look!
Oscar sausage! Delicious and affordable!
[Oscar Sausages for sale!]
Let’s have one.
Sure.
You queue up first. I’ll buy for you.
Have a look! Oscar sausages!
Do you want a sausage? It’s of good quality.
It’s only 5 copper soul coins for one.
Uncle. Please give me two sausages.
What did you call me?
I called you uncle. Is there a problem?
Of course, it’s a big problem.
I am still so young, yet you called me that.
Are you young?
Of course! I am a student of the school.
Anyone else would know that I am still a student.
A student? It’s impossible.
A young boy...
has such a long beard.
He’s also a weirdo.
For you.
Senior, I’m sorry. I was rude just now.
It’s all right.
Just buy sausages from me more often.
No problem.
Tang San. What are you doing?
Boss Dai, do you want to have a sausage?
Goodness. What a shame of the school.
I remembered that I warned you more than once.
Don’t sell sausages in the school.
Do you want everyone to vomit?
Tang San. You can’t eat this sausage.
Why?
Little Ao, give me a new sausage.
Boss Dai, I don’t think so.
Anyways, we’re classmates for years.
You’ll make the juniors have grudges against me.
I am just reminding Tang San.
Tang San is my brother. You can’t fool him.
Hurry up. Don’t let me do it.
Super Recovery Big Sausage!
I have no choice.
When Food Branch Martial Soul is in used...
to make changes to food,
you have to accompanied with soul curse.
This is a curse. I didn’t mean to shout it.
But, you can rest assured.
The quality of sausages is no problem.
You shall save the sausages for yourself.
Brother Dai. Thanks for reminding.
What a pity to my delicious sausages.
No one wants to eat it.
You’d better be careful.
Do it outside of the school.
Where is my sausage?
Silly.
What happened?
Doesn’t the sausage taste good?
These boys are too bad.
Why is there such a weird Martial Soul?
This is a monster school.
Of course, the Martial Souls are weird.
Don’t judge Oscar from his appearance.
His Martial Soul is the top of
Food Branch Martial Soul.
The top?
After all he provides meat.
You’ll know it in the future.
Oh, right.
He has a nickname in the school.
Uncle Sausage.
Let’s go. I’ll bring you to pass the exam.
Don’t have to queue.
This is not appropriate.
Rest assured. I am not playing favoritism.
This is what you deserve.
Let’s go to the fourth exam straightaway.
What is this?
Why can they skip the test
to enter the fourth exam...
but we have to pass exam by exam?
If your soul power has exceeded Level 25,
you can go directly to the fourth exam.
What?
Their soul powers have exceeded Level 25?
It’s impossible. We’re at the same age.
how can they have such a high level soul power?
Exactly! It must be fake!
Don’t think others can’t do it
when you can’t do it yourself.
When I entered the school,
my soul power was also Level 25.
Tang San. Show them your soul power!
His soul power has already reached Level 29?
Level 29 at our age?
Can this be achieved by a man?
Another Level 29? Goodness! What is this?
I think I can also skip the second and third exams.
How is it? Two of them are at Level 29.
One at Level 26 and another one at Level 27.
Do you still have comments?
[Soul Land]
What?
Your school only have 3 students now?
Yes. There are only 3 students including me.
In the whole Soul Land,
we are the only school
with more teachers than students.
The school was established for 20 years.
There were only 42 students enrolled.
Averagely,
it seems that there are
about two students every year.
How did the school survive?
If there’s no new students,
there won’t be income.
Why do you think the school
is located in this small village?
It’s due to the shortage of funds.
If my family didn’t sponsor,
the school might have closed last year.
If we can’t enroll any students this year,
the three of us studying...
will be the last batch of students
in Shrek School.
Why not loosen the admission requirement?
There are many people who came for registration.
The Dean of our school said,
put quality before quantity.
Even if Shrek School has to be closed,
it won’t accept trash but only monster.
Do you want to know
the graduation requirement?
What is it?
Your soul power has to exceed Level 40
before 20 years old...
and reach the level of Soul Sect
in order to graduate.
Exceeds Level 40?
Yes. Exceeds Level 40.
Ever since the school was established,
only 14 people graduated.
After these 14 people graduated,
all of them are notable figures.
One of the most outstanding person...
is now the youngest elder
in the Martial Soul Hall.
His authority is second to the Pope.
For those who couldn’t graduate,
some of them couldn’t manage
to complete practice to Level 40,
some others passed away
while hunting for soul beasts.
The Dean of our school said that...
don’t go out and shame him
if you can’t reach Level 41.
I am grateful to be here.
Initially, the royal family of Barak Kingdom
wanted to sponsor the school...
with the condition that
graduates need serve the royal family,
which was rejected by the Dean.
Our Shrek School is incompatible
with other schools...
and was excluded.
So, it became what it is now.
What kind of person is the Dean of the school?
We’re here.
Teacher Zhao. I bring them here
to undergo the fourth exam.
This year, we have students for the fourth exam.
And four students.
They exempted the second and third exams.
Four of them have exceeded Level 25.
Not bad.
Seems like there are quite
a number of monsters.
I am Zhao Wu Ji.
Since four of you have exempted
the second and third exams,
let me play with all of you.
I’ll give you half an hour
to know each other and discuss.
Half an hour later,
all of you team up to resist my attack
for half and hour.
As long as one of you
can persist to the end,
you will pass this exam.
But, the last part of the test...
is not that easy to pass.
Teacher Zhao, this is not quite good.
Why?
Dean of the school isn’t here, so I am the leader.
I make the decision.
Teacher.
Don’t say it anymore.
Using this half and hour,
you tell them my strength and characteristics.
I hope that you understand. Don’t try to trick.
No one can escape from my attack area.
At the same time, I can also remind you.
You won’t be able to resist my attack alone.
Coordination is the only chance
for you to succeed.
I didn’t expect Teacher Zhao would do it personally.
Teacher Zhao is the same as
the teacher at the entrance.
He’s also an outstanding soul master of
the Soul Emperor level.
No.
Then, there’s nothing to fear.
Anyway, four of us are almost at Level 30.
Four to one. It won’t be too hard
to persist for half and hour.
You don’t be too happy yet.
I haven’t finish my words.
Teacher Zhao is not a Soul Emperor.
But he is a Soul Saint.
He’s a beast soul, War Soul Saint of Level 76.
In the school, Teacher Zhao’s strength
is second to the Dean.
Level 76?
Level 76, Soul Saint.
Master has mentioned this before.
Soul Saint can survive in an army of
ten thousand people with great ease.
He is at Level 76?
But he looks far younger than
the teacher at the entrance.
Age? Age has never meant anything.
Not much time left.
I’ll briefly tell you Teacher Zhao’s strength.
You have to come out
with a strategy against him.
Or else, let alone half an hour,
you wouldn’t even be able
to take his first attack.
Initially, Teacher Zhao only
takes charge of the fourth exam.
Your opponent should be me.
You just have to persist
half an hour fighting with me.
You will be passed.
But he is behaving abnormal today.
He wants to do it himself.
Teacher Zhao’s Martial Soul is Supreme Bear.
It’s a super power beast soul.
He’s completely flawless.
Its defense is extremely terrifying.
Even the soul masters at his level...
can hardly hurt him.
Flawless.
Speed was Teacher Zhao’s weak point.
But there’s a big difference between
your soul power and his,
so this weak point is worthless to you.
Teacher Zhao has a nickname in the school,
Acala.
[Next Episode]
Ning Rong Rong will assist three of us.
Xiao Wu will be the main attack.
I will control Teacher Zhao’s attack.
Zhu Zhu Qing, pin him down from the flanks.
Unexpectedly, this little boy
made me feel a little uneasy.