♪ The past is buried with farewell tears ♪
♪ Tang’s belief is regained in the Soul Land ♪
♪ Ghostly Trace, from place to place you run ♪
♪ Xuan Tian power burns ♪
♪ Never look down at the shabby wooden house ♪
♪ Create our glorious miracles in the Soul Land ♪
♪ When seven creatures combine,
hope is what we get ♪
♪ Never give up as it’ll be unforgettable ♪
♪ For a hundred thousand years
I’ll search and grow with you ♪
♪ I’ll turn into a sky of bright stars
when I think of you ♪
♪ Life is full of wars, battles, adventures ♪
♪ and I’ll still protect you ♪
♪ I’m still the King no matter
the Black and Blue are awakened or not ♪
♪ The darkness is all released
by clouds and mists ♪
♪ I’ll never forget my promise ♪
♪ even if the sky and earth changes
or the sea roars ♪
♪ I’ll stand up high even the Gods have to look up ♪
♪ My invincible legend right on this Soul Land ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous Episode]
Fine.
Shrek School doesn’t want to trouble you.
Let’s bid farewell here, fellow seniors.
Dean Frander.
Dai was right.
Let’s re-run Shrek School.
None of us would want to see it end like this.
Yes.
Okay. Shrek School will not end.
[Soul Land]
[Episode 47]
Lanba School. I know something about it.
It’s located in Tian Dou City.
I heard that the teaching of
this school is quite strict.
Moreover, it has a specialty.
They only accept civilian students
and reject all nobles.
[Recruitment]
Very soon, they can compete
with Tian Dou Imperial School.
Let’s start.
I am Qin Ming.
War Soul Emperor of
Storm Attack Branch at Level 62.
Martial Soul, Fiery Grey Wolf.
I’m here to apply for a teacher position.
Please advise.
You don’t have to undergo evaluation.
The school rule states
that a soul master above Level 60
can exempt additional tests.
Since there’s no need for
additional tests for above Level 60,
we don’t have to waste time.
Go!
Tool Soul Emperor, Dragon Bar at Level 63.
Li Yu Song from Storm Attack Branch.
Tool Soul Saint with Jelly Bean at Level 71.
Shao Xin, from Food Branch.
Tool Soul Emperor, Othello at Level 66.
Lu Qi Bin, Controlling Branch.
War Soul Saint, Supreme Bear at Level 76.
Zhao Wu Ji, Storm Attack Branch.
War Soul Saint, Eagle Owl at Level 78.
Frander, Keen Attack Branch.
Is that all right?
Of course, yes.
Fellow seniors, please keep your Martial Souls.
In this world, ability still speaks louder.
When we were at
Tian Dou Imperial School before,
once The Grand Soul Land Master appeared,
fellow teachers from Shrek School have
no way but to be suppressed.
Even Dean Frander held patiently
and didn’t fight.
At this point, the strength of
Shrek School’s teachers
has shocked Lanba School.
Strength is still the most important.
I’m Yin Shu. A war soul master of
Storm Attack Branch at Level 54.
I couldn’t rate your grades, fellow seniors.
Why not allow me to lead you to our Dean?
Let her decide your grades and payment.
Let’s go.
Don’t your Dean stay in the school area?
Dean likes peace.
She usually stays alone in the forest.
The daily affairs of the school are
managed by the teachers.
Only big issues need to refer to the Dean.
I see.
This voice.
Xiao Gang. When can you stop avoiding?
It’s been 20 years.
Can you bare that not to visit her?
Dean, these are soul masters
who come to apply for a job in our school.
Six of them have soul power above Level 60.
We couldn’t decide it.
So, we need you to make the decision.
Xiao Gang. Is that really you?
Am I dreaming?
Sister Er Long, I didn’t know you were here.
We haven’t met for years. How are you?
Boss Fu, we haven’t seen for years.
You still look the same.
I’m getting old.
Come on. Let me introduce.
These are teachers and students
from Shrek School.
We saw the recruitment notice of
your school coincidentally.
So, we come here to ask for a living.
She is Liu Er Long.
She’s the one who followed Grandmaster and me
wandering around the soul masters’ world.
She’s the third in the Golden Iron Triangle.
The Killing Point.
Aren’t you letting us in?
Boss Fu.
Can my hut fit so many people?
What happened to you?
Since when have you fallen to this point?
It’s a long story.
What a Tian Dou Imperial School.
How dare they bully Boss Fu!
Boss Fu, don’t say it anymore!
My place is also your place!
Everyone can stay on.
This will be your place.
Our requirements on our part are very high.
Can you bear it?
Payment?
This is your problem now, Boss Fu.
You are the boss of Golden Iron Triangle.
From now on, this school is yours.
Tomorrow I will hold a faculty meeting
to announce that
the school will change its name to Shrek School.
Teacher Yin Shu.
Please announce a meeting to be held
tomorrow with all teachers and students.
These are my friends.
Let the canteen prepare
a feast on the second floor.
Yes, Dean.
No. I am the Deputy Dean now.
Xiao Gang, are you still going to remain silent?
I remembered.
We haven’t eaten for a whole day.
Little San, let’s go out for a walk.
Okay.
[Soul Land]
Aren’t you afraid that he will run away again?
Boss Fu, do you think he can still run away
after I see him again?
Little San, do you want to ask
the relationship between Er Long and me?
Why do we end up this now?
Why did I avoid her for 20 years?
Let me tell you a story.
Okay.
More than twenty years ago,
a young man with a famous background
was rejected by his family
due to his Martial Soul mutation.
In order to prove himself,
he left his clan for studies.
He hoped that he could be recognized by
the world and his clansmen.
When he traveled abroad,
he met a young soul master with good strength.
They became friends and
went out into the soul masters’ world.
One day, they met a pretty girl
in the soul beasts forest.
The girl soon attracted the young men
with a lively and cheerful personality.
Three of them became good friends
and adventured together.
As time went on,
two young men fell for the girl
who owned Fire Dragon Martial Soul.
But, neither of them wanted to show it.
Especially the one who lacked powerful
strength due to Martial Soul mutation.
Soon, they made a name of Golden Iron Triangle
in the soul masters’ world.
Feelings
can be accumulated over time.
The deeper it hid,
the stronger it would be.
Finally one day,
the young man with good strength
proposed to the girl.
The girl rejected him.
She loved the young man with weak strength
who liked to study theoretical knowledge.
You should have guessed it.
The girl was Er Long.
The two young men were Frander and me.
When I heard the true feeling from Er Long,
I suddenly felt the happiness
I had never had in my life.
Frander withdrew from
this relationship readily.
He said that he wanted to be my brother
and Er Long would be his sister-in-law.
Dean Frander is a good man.
This may be the best ending.
If everything went smoothly,
this may be the best ending.
But, fate is always so cruel.
God’s teasing
turned all happiness in vain.
I remembered very clearly that day.
The stars were exceptionally bright.
Frander hosted our marriage.
Er Long and I finally got married.
At that time, we felt so happy.
The story should end like this.
But at that time,
an uninvited guest came to our wedding.
My second uncle, the second owner of
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon Family,
Yu Luo Mian.
However, he didn’t come to me.
He came for my newlywed bride, Er Long.
What? Why?
It’s because Er Long, my wife
is my second uncle’s illegitimate daughter,
which means she is my cousin.
At that time, I ran out crazily.
Er Long wanted to chase after me
but she was forcibly stopped by my second uncle.
At that time, I only wanted to die.
Frander came to stop me.
But, my heart was dead.
Being disheartened,
I could only escape
and leave alone.
After that, Frander told me that
Er Long had fallen out with my second uncle
and went around to look for me.
I wanted to see her so much.
But, I couldn’t see her.
Master, is the secular viewpoint so important?
Aunty Er Long has waited for you for so many years.
If you continue to avoid it,
both of you will only suffer.
No. It’s unfair to Er Long.
When you love someone,
you don’t have to own her.
I hope she could live happily.
He is right.
Xiao Gang, I don’t care about the secular viewpoint.
I don’t need justice.
I just wish to be with you.
[Next Episode]
Who is it?
That’s bad, Little San might be in trouble.
Hurry and have a look.
Stop pretending if you’re awake.
Kid, aren’t you afraid of death?
I didn’t expect that I’d be killed by someone
who uses useless poison.
It’s so unworthy.