[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 17]
Hello.
Why did you answer
the phone call so quickly?
I've been waiting for you.
Do you want to come to my concert?
Sure.
Are you not going to ask why?
You can come now.
Sure.
Have you left home?
Yes, I've left home.
My acting career is coming to an end
yet I still have the mood to doll up.
Boss.
You stayed up all night for the shoot.
You should take a rest today.
Wait for me in the car.
I'll join you later.
Hello.
[The subscriber you've dialled]
[is powered off.]
Hello, Jia Yun.
Yi Qing.
How is she doing?
Are you free?
Let's meet up.
Okay.
Vocal cord polyps?
How is she feeling?
She appears to be fine.
However, the more she pretends,
the more worried I am.
This way, please.
Come in.
Here?
A concert?
This could be
the most special concert
of my life.
Your voice...
Are you okay?
Be good and take a seat.
Take a seat.
Just enjoy
being the only audience in the concert.
Everyone's life
is full of accidents.
Sometimes you're surprised.
Sometimes you feel helpless.
This song, "You Have Me,"
is specially dedicated to
the only member of the audience.
Thank you for witnessing
the most important moment
of my life.
Do you like it?
Yes.
I feel sorry for you.
You might not be able to listen
to such a beautiful voice again
in the future.
Liang Chen.
What did the doctor say yesterday?
What other songs do you want to hear?
I'll sing them for you.
Are you sure I can choose any song?
Yes.
Don't mind if I do.
I wish to listen to all your songs.
In that case,
I'll sing
all of my songs to you.
Sure.
You sang a few songs for me.
It's my turn to sing.
What's wrong?
Was it because I sang awfully?
I'm just wondering,
do I really have to
let other people ruin my songs
moving forward?
I didn't mean to ruin your song.
I'm just kidding.
It's because
moving forward,
I may not be able to sing anymore.
I have vocal cord polyps.
The doctor recommended me
to undergo a surgery.
I'm so scared.
I'm worried that I can't sing anymore.
I just want to sing.
I don't want to go through a surgery.
Don't worry.
Hello.
[The subscriber you've dialled
is powered off.]
Jia Yun.
You have class tomorrow, right?
You should go home now.
I need to talk to Liang Chen
about something important.
I'm done talking with Liang Chen.
Please hold on.
Are you aware of her health condition?
It's so cold.
How could you take her on a walk?
She's a singer.
She's not like you.
If you hadn't interrupted,
I would've sent her home.
Jia Yun, what's the matter?
Why don't you go home first?
Thank you for your time.
Rest early.
It's so cold.
Don't let her stay outside for too long.
I'll get going.
Bye.
Liu Yi Qing came to see me.
I was told
something is wrong with your voice.
Jia Yun, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me.
Liang Chen, you don't have to
pretend to be strong
in front of me.
I'm really okay.
How is that possible?
If you lose your voice,
you will lose your career.
Liu Yi Qing is really worried about you.
Are you really okay
or are you just refusing to admit
that you're not okay?
We tried to reach you the whole day,
but your phone was turned off.
I'm sorry.
My phone ran out of battery.
It's okay.
You must be tired.
Go home to take a rest.
Don't worry about your voice.
We'll find a solution for sure.
Jia Yun.
Thank you.
It's okay.
I'm going up.
Bye.
Jing.
What is the meaning of life?
Why are you reading medical articles?
I'm reading for fun.
Are you thinking of switching careers?
It's too late now.
Our beloved Jing
may very well join the medical field.
"Acoustic observations on voice recovery"
"after vocal cord surgery?"
"Research on"
"vocal cord polyps
and microscopic anatomy?"
If you're so free,
wash my stockings.
If you don't want to wash them, fine.
I'm so scared.
I'm worried that I can't sing anymore.
I just want to sing.
I don't want to go through a surgery.
I want to sing
no matter what happens.
Jing.
Where are you off to in such a hurry?
-I have something to do.
-What is that?
Are you meeting up with
your internet friend?
When are you going to
introduce your internet friend to us?
Don't even think about it.
Oh no.
What's wrong?
Do you think
Lu Jing would fall in love
with someone distasteful?
No way.
Therein lies the problem.
Why does he refuse
to introduce his internet friend to us?
Is he worried that
I might steal his girlfriend?
Zhou Zhou.
Do you have a fever?
Don't touch me!
That's why,
based on my analysis,
Jing might have fallen for a man.
Are you serious?
Let me break it down for you.
Until now, Jing's internet friend
has been using a voice changer.
They might have fallen in love
with each other
before they met up.
When they met up,
they realised that
the other party was a man.
What should they do?
He could only accept it.
Otherwise, why does he refuse
to let us see his crush even until now?
-What should we do?
Let's follow him in secret.
Lu Jing!
Wait for me.
What? Cut to the chase.
Qi Qi and I have become a couple.
So?
Let me buy you some soy milk.
To celebrate my escape from singledom.
Where is the soy milk?
Get it yourself.
Can't you see I'm injured?
It's okay. I'll skip it.
You're just pretending to be injured.
You're wrapping yourself up like a mummy.
What if you get hurt for real one day?
What do you know?
One has to sacrifice
in order to win a lady's heart.
That's enough. Stop following me.
Help me out.
It's difficult to walk like this.
I'm heading out too.
He's doomed.
I was right.
Well...
Are you kidding me?
I knew it.
He talks about Box Spirit all the time.
Have you seen any player
worse than Gu Fei Ming?
You haven't, right?
Hey.
How is it? Are you feeling better today?
I feel so much better.
I...
I still don't want to get the surgery.
I opt for a conservative treatment.
I will recover eventually.
Chen Chen.
You're a singer.
You'll use your voice all the time.
If you opt for a conservative treatment
by taking medicine only,
it won't be fully cured.
What if the condition becomes worse
when the treatment process is prolonged?
If you don't want to get
the surgery right away,
it's okay.
Take a few days off.
We'll go for the surgery
after you've made up your mind.
I have singing classes to attend.
I can't take a few days off.
I've applied for a leave for you.
What about the theme song of the movie?
Forget it. I'm turning it down.
How can we do that?
Why didn't you ask me first?
You're not fit to work.
But you knew
how important this opportunity is to me.
Your health is more important
than anything else.
In the next two days,
you should stay home and rest.
Don't think too much.
Something came up.
I need to go back to the office.
I can't keep you company.
Take good care of yourself.
See you.
Lu Jing!
You bought so much food.
Are you having a feast?
Lu Bao Bei!
Did you miss me?
Why are you here?
I'm here to take it for a walk.
I'm not in the mood.
What's wrong? Did you get rejected?
Can't you show your friend some concern?
What's wrong? Why are you so touchy?
You don't even know that
Liang Chen has fallen sick.
Is that how you treat your friend?
Liang Chen has fallen sick?
What kind of sickness?
What's wrong, Lu Jing?
Lu Jing, are you abandoning your dog?
Lu Jing!
Lu Bao Bei.
It's been a while
since you went on an excursion, right?
Let's explore the world. What do you say?
So it's a deal, right?
Let's go.
Jing.
What are you doing?
The actor next door is sick.
Her throat is not feeling well.
You're lying.
You're pursuing someone, aren't you?
Grandma, actually,
your future granddaughter-in-law
has fallen sick.
I want to make her some soup.
You should have told me earlier.
Here, let me see.
Jing.
You're chopping vegetables
using a boning knife.
What soup are you making?
Radish soup with monk fruit.
I'll make a few side dishes too.
All right, leave it to me.
Wash the vegetables.
Thank you, Grandma.
My goodness, what a mess.
I'm home.
Something smells good.
The food looks good.
Who is it for?
Are you
cooking for your dancing partner?
Don't talk nonsense.
Let me try it.
-Don't touch it.
-I just want a taste.
Jing made this.
Jing made this?
How is that possible?
Our future daughter-in-law
has fallen sick.
After knowing that, Jing
immediately asked me to teach him
how to cook.
I see.
You've grown up.
By the way,
Jing,
bring her some Doubendou Soy Milk.
She must have lost her appetite
since she's sick.
Let her have some nutritious drinks.
It's good for her body.
-Sure.
-Look, he's shy.
All right, I'll leave it to you.
He's grown up. Jing has grown up.
We're off. Take your time.
♫ Let youth bloom ♫
♫ In the sea of dream ♫
♫ Each second ♫
♫ Stubbornness is ♫
Ms Liang, it's time to eat.
Are you home?
Yes.
Open the door!
It's so cold out here!
Why are you here?
Can we talk inside?
It's so cold here.
Come in now.
Come in.
Why don't you take a seat?
Sure.
Ke Ke. Ke Ke.
Do you mind leaving now?
He just came in,
and you're already kicking me out.
I haven't finished the food.
Then take it back with you.
Will you hurry up?
I haven't eaten.
How can I hurry?
Give me that.
All right, you can leave now.
Don't find any excuses to come back.
Why are you back?
Hurry up!
Here.
It's nutritious and healthy.
Thank you.
It's made with love.
Have it while it's warm.
Try it.
Try this.
It's good for your throat.
Have more.
Is it tasty?
Was it made by you?
No.
Did you hurt your hand?
No, Lu Bao Bei bit me.
Your dog sure has huge teeth.
Hold on. Let me dress your wound.
Is it painful?
No.
It's done.
Given your dressing skills,
you should only dress me.
Don't dress anyone else.
Are you okay? Did I touch your wound?
Is it painful?
You lied.
What's wrong?
Chen Chen.
Mind if I look around?
Ms Ma.
You're there, right?
Ms Ma, please open the door.
It's such a beautiful day.
Don't you want to go
on a walk with the dog
and have a chat?
Ms Ma, let's go for a stroll.
Ms Ma.
Ms Ma!
Ms Ma, can you hear me?
If you don't open up,
Lu Bao Bei will pee at the door.
Ms Ma!
Hello, Ms. Ma.
[I'm at the door.]
Just open the door.
You don't have to call me.
Why are you making noise?
We haven't seen each other in a long time.
I just want to catch up with you.
If you don't open the door,
[the neighbours are going to get angry.]
Ms Ma, you...
Ms Ma, why are you eating takeout?
-It's so unhealthy.
-What do you want?
I'm worried, that's all.
Liang Chen is sick.
I feel bad for her.
Aren't you curious
what happened to your university mate?
She should go to hospital if she's sick.
What does it have to do with me?
I'm worried.
I'm here to see
if you have any suggestions.
After all, you were a music major
back in university, too.
When it comes to voice,
you're more experienced than I am.
What happened to Liang Chen?
What else?
She's got the blues.
So her voice is deteriorating.
Her voice?
Is it hoarseness?
It could be itchiness.
It could be a blockage, too.
Well, the doctor said that
her throat...
I mean vocal cord...
Vocal cord polyps?
Yes!
That's it.
See? You do know your stuff.
Liang Chen
must be very sad right now.