Dong Gu.
Yoon Ah, there's something I want to tell you.
What? What is it?
I like you.
I really like you, Yoon Ah.
Dong Gu, this is so unexpected.
I like you, Yoon Ah.
So...
do you want to go out with me?
I don't want to go out with you.
What? Why?
Is it because of your situation?
Don't worry. I asked you out...
because I'm prepared to take responsibility for you and Sol.
I didn't ask you to...
take responsibility for me and Sol.
That wasn't what I meant.
Then do you think that a single mom with a child like me...
should always agree to go out with...
people like you if they ask me out?
- Yoon Ah, that's not what I meant. - Don't.
Let's pretend this never happened.
Yoon Ah.
Here. You left your phone in the car.
Thank you. Take care.
Bye.
- Are you all right? - Soo Ah.
Did she just dump me?
Yes, and it only took five seconds.
Five seconds?
Why?
Chewbacca, what are you doing this weekend?
Trainees have no weekends.
I need to watch all the dramas and reality shows to write reviews.
They always make me do these things.
Gosh.
You really wanted to be a reporter.
Now that you've become one, are you not satisfied?
My ears are itchy.
Chewbacca.
To celebrate on your becoming a reporter, pick my ears for me.
I think there's something big in here.
Take a look.
What are you doing? Pick my ears.
What... What are you doing?
You could've told me if you didn't want to. Why did you push me?
I didn't.
Gosh.
Yoon Ah, please talk to me.
Why don't you want to go out with me?
You can dump me all right, but I want to know the reason why.
What? What?
What? Dumped? What is this about?
Get lost!
Tell me. What's the reason?
I don't want to go out with you.
I don't want to talk about it. Can I go now?
Hey, what is this about?
You like Yoon Ah?
He does.
But he got dumped in five seconds.
What?
Five seconds?
Five seconds? Really?
Dong Gu, where are you going?
Yoon Ah, there's something I want to tell you.
I like you.
I really like you, Yoon Ah.
I don't want to go out with you.
I didn't ask you to take responsibility for me and Sol.
(Night of the Living Dead)
Gosh, it's so noisy.
What are you doing here?
Soo Ah, am I that unattractive?
I'm not that bad, am I?
I look okay, and I'm tall.
I'm tall, and...
I'm tall. That's right.
I mean, I'm not that bad, am I?
Do you want the truth or a sugar-coated lie?
Forget it.
Whatever.
I'm going to the bathroom.
(Brother)
Gosh. He thinks I'm in the US.
Hello.
Hey, how are you?
What's the matter?
I'm your brother.
I couldn't even see you off when you left for the US.
I wanted to hear your voice.
I got back from training today.
That's right. You have a match soon, right?
I'm leaving for Hong Kong in two days.
How's life in the US?
I love it.
Everything is good. Very good.
I'm glad to hear that.
I can't talk long right now.
By the way, it's an overseas call,
but it sounds as if you were right next to me.
Technology has improved a lot.
I'll call you back soon.
All right.
- Bye. - Take care.
- Soo Ah. - Hey.
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be in the US.
The thing is...
- Let me explain. - Soo Ah, let's go home and sleep.
I'm tired.
Wait. Dong Gu.
Soo Bong.
Hold on. "Let's go home and sleep?"
Do you live together?
- You broke up. - Well...
I broke up with Yoon Seok and got back together with Dong Gu.
I didn't want to worry you, so I lied to you that I was in the US.
Really? But why are you living with Dong Gu?
What happened to your apartment?
Well... The thing is...
We're going to get married anyway.
Dong Gu wanted me to move in with him and save money.
Are you two getting married?
Really? Guys, it's cold.
Let's go to your guesthouse. Come on.
- We'll be right there. - Okay.
What are you doing right now?
I'm sorry. You know what my brother is like.
Please help me this once.
Soo Bong will kill me if he finds out I was conned.
Fine.
Wait. Isn't Jun Ki at the guesthouse?
Dong Gu likes Yoon Ah?
Isn't it so unexpected?
What's even funnier is that he got turned down in five seconds.
We should call him...
Five Seconds from now on.
Five Sec for short.
Five Sec.
- 5 Sec, 5 Sec - 5 Sec, 5 Sec
Who is it?
- It's Dong Gu. - Five Sec?
Hello, Five Sec.
Guess what? It's your new nickname.
What?
Soo Bong?
He's coming here?
You mean here?
Gosh.
- What's going on? - I don't know.
I'll run away. Call me when he's left, okay?
If he sees me, he'll kill me.
It's been such a long time.
I'm back! Soo Bong is here too!
Soo Bong hasn't been here in a while.
How long has it been?
- Du Shik, Seo Jin. - Hi.
It's been such a long time.
You guys.
I missed you, sweeties.
- He's in the cabinet. - In the cabinet?
You're strong as always.
You cuties.
It's so nice to see you.
I'm a bit disappointed in you guys.
Dong Gu and Soo Ah are back together,
and you haven't said anything to me?
What? Soo Ah and Dong Gu are back together?
I told him.
I told him we were back together.
I see. Soo Ah wanted us to keep it a secret.
You guys are such good friends.
A man should be loyal to his friends.
- Loyalty! - Loyalty!
Loyalty.
Nothing much seems to have changed here.
What's this?
That's Jun Ki.
Why is it still here?
Why would you keep a picture of a dead person?
Jun Ki.
I still can't believe he's dead.
Who would have known he'd die like that?
How could he get hit by lightning?
Exactly.
I'm sure it was his punishment.
How dare he steal a friend's girlfriend?
My girlfriend at that?
I shouldn't say bad things about a dead person,
but it might be a good thing that he died like that.
If he had been caught by me,
he would have spent the rest of his life...
at the hospital, half dead.
Jun Ki, you have some mails...
Where is Jun Ki?
- No. - No.
What is she talking about?
Yoon Ah, there you go again.
- Jun Ki is dead, remember? - What?
What are you talking about?
- He was here a moment ago. - Yoon Ah!
You didn't take your medicine today, did you?
You should never skip your medicine.
Follow me.
- Throw away this trash. - What are you...
- You haven't come to your senses? - Jun Ki...
Come with me.
What was that all about? Who is she?
She works here.
She is still not over Jun Ki's accident.
She believes Jun Ki is alive.
Really?
That's too bad. She's so young.
Keep quiet.
Does medicine help?
What?
Jun Ki stole Soo Ah's brother's girlfriend?
Yes. Soo Bong was so determined...
to kill Jun Ki.
So you lied to him that Jun Ki died?
We tried to stop him, but it was Jun Ki's idea.
The thing is, Soo Bong is a UFC fighter.
He is a human weapon.
19 wins by KO out of 19.
Still, how could you tell such a lie?
Where is Jun Ki right now?
Why did he have to show up here?
Gosh, it's so uncomfortable.
I hope he'll be gone soon.
What was that noise?
I think it came from there.
Sorry. I have a cold.
Really?
Seo Jin.
- Do you still have a mustache? - What?
I've had it all my life.
I'm so tired.
It's getting late. Shouldn't you be going?
Well, I guess I should get back.
Hello, Coach.
Really?
Okay.
- Gosh, this is not good. - What's wrong?
Our boiler broke down.
What should I do?
I could stay here.
Dong Gu, I'm going abroad in two days.
Can I stay here until then?
What?
Two days?
No.
You have a match in a few days. You should take care of yourself.
With so many people, it'll be noisy and uncomfortable here.
Don't worry.
I'm used to staying with many people for training.
That's right.
But there is no vacant room at the moment.
I can sleep on the sofa too.
I'll sleep on the sofa. Use my bed instead.
I hate causing others trouble.
Let's go grab some beer for old times' sake.
I'm watching my weight for the match. I can't drink.
Also, I want to watch some dramas I couldn't watch during training.
- Please. - Don't worry and go to bed.
Still...
Okay. Make yourself comfortable.
That handgrip is scary.
- Have a good time. - Okay.
- Enjoy. - All right.
It's fun.
It's so fun.
Kim Nam Joo. Goodness.
That's amazing.
What should I watch now?
That's right. "Wife's Desire".
I heard that the twist is shocking.
Why is he still watching dramas? It's so late.
I have to pee, and my legs feel numb.
I'm going crazy.
Gosh, I have to pee.
What should I do?
Did I ask you to be responsible for me and Sol?
Let's pretend this never happened.
I don't want to go out with you.
Dong Gu, I have to pee. Help me.
Du Shik, I have to pee. Please save me.
(News Report, "Female Directors Are Popular Now")
I'm tired of it. It never ends.
Is Jun Ki okay?
Why do I keep caring about him?
Gosh, I must be insane.
Come to your senses.
What is it?
I'm going to pee.
Please help me.
Why do I care about him...
I can start from the eighth episode.
Goodness, I'm so excited.
I'm at the center tonight
It's me
- Why aren't you sleeping? - Pardon?
I'm looking for something.
- I see. - Where was it?
I only wait for you, it's me
Why are you holding a plastic bottle?
Pardon?
I just wanted to hold something.
It feels like something is missing.
I'm the one who will...
steal your heart away
Thank you, Seo Jin.
What's that sound?
Is water leaking?
What sound?
I don't hear anything.
- I heard it. - Let's watch a drama.
The volume is too low.
It's too loud.
It's because I'm a little deaf.
It's overflowing.
Gosh, it's overflowing.
However
That person
It's me, it's me
I'm at the center tonight
Dong Gu.
What are you doing early in the morning?
What are you writing?
What is it?
(Why? No. I Refuse.)
What?
Did you do this all night?
No matter how much I think, I can't understand.
Du Shik, am I that bad?
No, you're great.
You're the best among all my friends.
Right?
Why does Yoon Ah not like me?
Shouldn't she consider it when I confessed to her?
That's true.
How did you confess to her?
In front of the guesthouse yesterday,
I told Yoon Ah that I like her and I want to date her.
I confessed to her like a man.
Wait.
Did you confess to her on the street?
Without even a flower?
Yes. What's wrong with that?
That's not right.
If you confessed like that on the street,
I wouldn't have accepted it.
Really?
Is that why?
- Yes. - Now I understand.
Du Shik.
Even I don't make that mistake.
I thought it was manly, but I was wrong.
By the way, is Jun Ki still hiding?
I fell asleep.
Gosh.
Is it morning?
I can't tell day and night in here.
My legs are asleep.
By the way,
is he still there?
What's going on?
That's amazing.
Why is he...
watching so much drama?
Are you saying that you're my father's daughter?
His daughter-in-law was his real daughter.
That's unbelievable.
I can't believe it.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
You should have breakfast.
No thanks.
I have to watch this, so be quiet.
She was freeloading.
30 years ago,
you abandoned a woman named Geum Nan.
How do you know her?
I'm her daughter.
What? You are?
- Goodness. - Are you my daughter too?
His wife was his daughter?
I love this drama.
This is incredible.
Is he an athlete...
or someone who monitors dramas?
Why does he watch so much drama?
He's a huge fan of dramas.
He spends...
half of his money on watching dramas.
Poor Jun Ki.
By the way, where's Yoon Ah?
She went to class after making breakfast.
She said that she had something to do.
Since when did you like Yoon Ah?
It's been awhile.
I thought about it a lot, so don't order me around.
Okay.
I'm late, so I'll eat at the convenience store.
Wait.
I'm coming with you.
Where are you going?
What about Soo Bong?
Before he finds out,
I need to catch Yoon Seok.
He'll kill me if he finds out.
Dong Gu, take care of my brother.
Let's go.
Goodness.
I can't handle him on my own.
I need to get ready for work.
Take care of Sol.
Have fun.
Fine. See you later.
Sol.
What does your mom like?
How should I confess to her so that she likes me?
What did you say?
You said something.
Say something.
Don't say gibberish and say something.
Please say something.
Why hasn't he appeared yet?
I need to catch him before my brother finds out.
How should they fight?
Are you still writing it?
Do you earn money with it?
- No. - Then why do you write it?
It's because it's what I like.
Your life seems frustrating as well.
What should I write?
Do I have to use the finger jab here?
- What's a finger jab? - Finger jab?
It's...
one of Bruce Lee's technique.
It's a frightening technique of making someone...
lose his sight by poking his eyes.
Poke someone's eyes? That's unfair.
The tactic is to end the fight in the least amount of time.
Why would you let someone poke your eyes?
You don't understand.
Finger jab is very fast.
- Shall I show it to you? - Go ahead.
See? It's fast.
You can't even see it. Can you avoid it?
Why would I avoid it?
Try it on me.
Aren't you afraid?
You'd better not regret it.
Then here I go.
That hurts. My finger hurts.
Goodness.
It makes no sense.
My daughter-in-law and my wife...
weren't my real daughters.
I can't...
- stay here anymore. - Goodness.
I must leave here now.
Sundown.
I should go back to my star.
Goodbye, Earth.
Goodbye.
(Thank you for watching "Wife's Desire".)
Bravo. That was amazing.
He was an alien.
The title was "Wife's Desire", but the father was an alien.
What an amazing twist.
That was the best drama of my life. That was amazing.
I'll have to own a copy of that drama.
How could the writer think up of something like that?
I should come up with a better way to show my feelings to Yoon Ah.
With him here, what should I do?
I'll have to watch that over again.
This is driving me crazy.
Yoon Ah. You're here early.
Hello.
I thought I'd just come early today.
Who...
was that guy yesterday?
He's the owner of the guesthouse.
I see.
- I'm just curious. Yesterday... - Hyun Joon.
I don't want to talk about that.
All right. I apologize.
Soo Ah. I need to go to the restroom.
- Take care of the counter for me. - All right.
Gosh. I'm getting tired of this.
How much longer do I have to be on the watch for him?
Excuse me.
Did you guys get that ramen today?
Pardon? What ramen?
Bba Bba Yen Tom Yum Mutai.
Wait a minute.
I know this voice.
Why don't they sell it here.
Hey. So it is you.
My goodness.
Stop right there.
I'm going to kill you.
- Wait a minute. - Where do you think you're going?
Give me back my money. Where's my money?
Bba Bba Yen. It's that Thai guy.
Move away.
Du Shik. Get him. Get him.
- It's him. It's that swindler. - Move away.
- Get out of my way. - No way.
- What are you doing? - Get out of my way.
Put that down. Someone will get hurt.
If you don't want to get hurt, get out of my way, you jerk.
Get out of my way. You jerk.
Gosh. Gosh. What should I do? What should I do?
- What are you doing? - What is he doing?
You'll really end up getting hurt.
- Finger. Finger. - You jerk.
My finger. It hurts. It hurts.
My goodness.
You swindler. You jerk.
Du Shik. Hurry up and call the police.
Gosh. How could you poke my eyes?
Finger Jam.
It's time for me to...
return to my land, Biratutura.
Farewell.
Unbelievable. Unbelievable.
It's my second time around, and it's still amazing.
The writer's a genius.
After watching dramas all day, my body's aching.
I should go for a run.
My eyes.
My legs. My legs are asleep.
They're killing me. I can't get up.
It's so cold. It's freezing.
Jun Ki.
You're supposed to be dead.
Why are you here?
What's going on? Did you lie to me?
Do you know my brother?
What's that supposed to mean? Your brother?
You must've mistaken me for my brother, Jun Ki.
I'm not Jun Ki. I'm his twin brother,
Lee Jun Gu.
- What? You're his twin brother? - Yes.
Jun Ki had a twin?
What's going on? What's all this noise?
- Dong Gu. - Yes?
- Was Jun Ki a twin? - Excuse me?
Dong Gu. It's been a long time.
It's me Jun Gu. I'm Lee Jun Gu.
Pardon?
That's right. Jun Gu.
How have you been?
Do you mean to tell me that Jun Ki really had a twin brother?
I never heard about you.
I knew it.
He did it again.
He was always like that.
He never wanted to admit that I existed.
We were born in the same place at the same time,
but he always treated me like a ghost.
Jun Ki. You're playing games with me, aren't you?
How could you say such a thing?
Who am I?
Do I really not exist?
My parents only accepted Jun Ki as their son. I was always alone.
I lived my whole life hating him.
I'm Lee Jun Gu.
I'm telling you. Lee Jun Gu really exists.
Are you telling me you're really Jun Ki's twin brother?
Yes.
Jun Gu. You'll be all right.
You must've been through a lot.
I didn't know about this.
No. It's all right. I'm used to this happening.
- Since you're here, have a seat. - No. That's all right.
I'm so heartbroken.
I don't think I'll be able to stay any longer.
Then I'll be going now.
Wait right there.
What's wrong?
- Where's Jun Ki? - What do you mean?
As you know, he's dead.
I mean, where's his graveyard?
- He was cremated. - Then where's the charnel house?
We meant to place him in one, but we just scattered his ashes.
Then there must've been an exact place you scattered his ashes.
Please tell me.
Better yet, can you take me there?
I'm a bit busy today. I should go.
- Jun Gu. - Yes?
I'm going abroad tomorrow because I have a game to play.
Let me say farewell to my friend before I leave.
Is that such a hard thing to ask for?
Drive safely.
Jun Gu.
How much longer do we have to go?
Do you hear me?
We're almost there.
This is it. This is the spot.
Here? Here?
Yes. Yes. This is the place.
Then this is where Jun Ki is?
Jun Ki.
Jun Ki. It's me. I came to see you.
How could you?
Jun Ki.
I can't believe this.
Are you... Are you...
crying?
To tell you the truth, Jun Ki and I were really close.
We were as close as real brothers.
Even when he stole my girlfriend,
I was angry at him at first,
but I managed to forgive him in no time.
Who would have known he would die so suddenly?
If he were alive, I would give him a warm hug.
It breaks my heart that I'll never be able to do that.
Jun Ki.
Forgive me.
Forgive me, Jun Ki.
I hope you rest in peace up there.
When I meet you in paradise,
please be my friend again.
Jun Ki. Jun Ki. Jun Ki.
Soo Bong. Soo Bong.
Why talk casually to me all of a sudden?
It's me. It's me.
I'm your friend, Jun Ki.
What are you talking about?
You said you're his twin brother.
You know I don't have a twin.
I'm an only child. I'm a four-generation only child.
I lied out of fear that you'd beat me to death.
It's me. It's me, Jun Ki. It's me,
Lee Jun Ki.
Here. Come here.
What are you waiting for?
You said you wanted to give me a warm hug.
Actually, I'm Jun Gu.
You scum.
Wait. I'm Jun Ki's...
You jerk!
Soo Bong! Soo Bong!
Please!
It's not easy to get your money back in cases like this.
It's nearly impossible.
(Information Division)
Du Shik, what should I do?
What should I do now?
I have no money left.
The model industry treats me like a useless being.
You can start again now.
Start what?
There's nothing I can do. I didn't even graduate from college.
Never mind. What would I even talk to you about?
You're just a weird guy who writes weird stories.
- What about it? - Are you happy with your life?
Aren't you embarrassed?
Why would I care about others?
To others, my work may seem useless.
But I'm happy doing what I like best.
Soo Ah, everyone has different standards of happiness.
So even now,
you can find something to do for the rest of your life...
that makes you happy.
It's too late to start over.
I'm already 29 years old.
That's not too late.
Do you know the average life span nowadays?
It's 80 years old.
If you think of your life as a baseball game,
you're only in the third inning.
Are you going to quit the game because you're losing then?
You don't know if you might get a double or a triple after that.
It might even be a home run.
No one can know until the end.
Don't you think so?
- Du Shik. - Yes?
How many innings are there in a baseball game?
Why is it so quiet here? Where is everyone?
(Dong Gu)
Hello?
Yoon Ah, where are you?
I just came to the house after the class finished.
Really?
I'm cleaning the third floor right now. Can you help me out?
Sure. I'll be there right away.
Dong Gu.
Yoon Ah.
I made a mistake yesterday.
I want to ask you out properly.
I like you, Yoon Ah. I really like you.
- I... - Dong Gu, why are you doing this?
I told you that I didn't want to.
What?
Is there something you don't like?
I've been decorating this by myself for hours.
I'll go downstairs.
Yoon Ah.
Yoon Ah!
Yoon Ah! Just wait a moment. Yoon Ah!
Why are you doing this?
Was it not enough?
Right. The ring!
When I earn more money, I'll...
Whatever you do, my answer will be the same.
I don't intend to go out with you.
Why?
Do you hate me that much?
You can go on a date with me...
and dump me if you don't like me then.
I don't have time to go on dates.
I'm busy as it is with my own life.
So don't do this, all right?
Then I'll wait.
I'll wait until you have time.
Don't wait.
I want to wait. I want to!
Can't I even do that?
Am I someone...
you don't even want to think about to you?
Am I?
All right.
I understand.
I'll stop.
I'll stop...
liking you.
What are you talking about?
You like her?
Why do you like her?
What is this about?
Soo Bong, why are you out here?
- Let's go. - What are you doing?
I heard everything.
I heard you were scammed. That's why you're living here.
Soo Bong, I...
Be quiet. Go to our parent's house.
Stay there, and keep quiet until you get married.
- Come here. - No. I don't want to.
Then are you going to stay here at Dong Gu's house?
Soo Bong, I want to start over.
Start what over?
You've been playing all your life, confident that you'd become a model.
You can't start over now.
And do you realize how old you are?
What about my age?
I'm only 29 years old.
- What? - Soo Bong.
Do you know the average life span?
It's 80 years old.
If you compare your life to baseball...
I mean, if you compare your life to the UFC main event,
I'm only in the 2nd round out of all 5 rounds.
Will you throw away your towel and give up...
just because you're losing on the second round?
You don't know if there might be an arm bar, a rear naked choke,
or a reversal high kick later on...
until you've finished.
Don't you agree?
I still have three rounds left.
I still have a lot of time left.
So I want to start over again.
Can't you trust me for once?
Do you mean it?
If you throw away your towel again,
you're going to experience my high kick, okay?
All right.
Thank you, Soo Bong.
Come here.
Yoon Ah, why didn't you go home?
I wanted more practice.
Is something wrong? Why the sad face?
Is it because of him?
I know you don't want to talk about it, but I don't feel good.
He seems like a good guy.
Why did you refuse?
I know that he's a good man.
I know better than anyone...
that he's a good man.
But Hyun Joon,
I don't want to trust anyone else again.
I...
don't want to be hurt again.
Whatever you do, my answer will be the same.
I don't intend to go out with you.
Don't wait.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
I'm happy I'm not dead.
So are you friends again with Soo Bong?
Of course.
We'll be friends even after death.
Here's your meal.
It's kimchi stew! It looks delicious.
This is great.
Dong Gu, let's eat.
It's fine. I don't feel like it.
Du Shik, can you look after Sol today?
I need to practice at Hyun Jun's workroom.
Sure. Don't worry.
Then see you later.
Yoon Ah has been going to Hyun Joon's studio...
a lot recently.
Could she be interested in him?
No way.
Dong Gu, don't worry about it.
I don't.
I'm not interested in Yoon Ah anymore, so just know that.
- That's good. - See you.
Where are you going?
Like I said, I'm helping out Director Kim from today.
- You said that? When? - I said it! I did!
I said it many times! You never listen to me!
Will you please listen to me?
Why does he always take it out on me?
There's no reason to be upset.
- Eat up. - What are you talking about?
Just eat. You look awful after getting beaten up.
(I Really Like You)
Gosh, I'm tired.
Where were you this morning?
I just got off work.
I had to attend previews and interviews,
write up reviews, and run errands all day yesterday.
I'm so tired after running around all night.
Are you celebrating getting beaten up?
"Just finished acting practice."
"Drinking coffee."
"Caffeine keeps me alive."
What are you doing?
I've created a social media profile.
Do you want to take a look?
I'll give you the honor.
What is it?
Gosh, that's so cringe worthy.
Why did you decide to do it?
Social media helps you communicate with your fans.
Don't be absurd.
You don't even have any followers. How are you going to communicate?
- You communicate with yourself? - Here.
I only just started.
I'll be getting so many followers soon.
My goodness.
Chewbacca, pretend you're my fan, and take a picture with me.
Forget it. I don't want to.
Come on. Let's do this.
All right.
Hey, smile.
1, 2, 3.
Stop it. Stop bothering me.
Chewbacca! Hey!
Why is she so cold to me these days?
She's never liked you.
That's right.
I have a shooting.
- Is it that children's drama again? - Yes.
I'll be shooting a battle scene against Aqua Man.
How should I shoot the octopus ink gun?
Like this...
- Oh, my. - Gosh.
See you.
- Gosh, you're gross. - He's crazy.
Have fun.
Why was I blushing?
I must be out of my mind.
I'm crazy.
Stop beating so fast.
Are you okay?
Aqua Man seemed to beat you up so badly.
I'm all right.
How long will we have to do this?
Are you okay?
We're in a better situation than him at least.
We should be grateful that we're not playing Cutlassfish Man.
Right.
- Did you go to the audition? - What audition?
Director Kim Jin Ho is starting a new drama.
Director Kim Jin Ho?
The one who directed "Son's Revenge",
which received a rating over 40 percent?
The one who turns every drama into a success?
Yes. I went to the audition yesterday.
- Really? - Yes.
I missed it.
Could there be a way to audition now?
Hey!
Why would he have the volume up so high?
Jun Ki.
It's been a while.
What brings you here?
I heard you were assisting Director Kim in his new drama.
Can I audition?
- What did you say? - Gosh.
- Why did you have to yell? - What?
I can't hear you.
Speak louder.
Why are you yelling at me?
I'm sorry. While shooting a bombing scene,
I injured my ears.
Really?
- Will you be all right? - Yes.
I'll be okay after treatment.
Right.
What were you saying?
Can I audition for...
Director Kim's new drama?
The audition is already over.
I know. Could you talk to the director...
so that he'll give me a chance to audition?
He's probably too busy.
He's speaking too loudly again.
Seo Jin.
Jun Ki.
- Do you have an interview here? - Yes.
You sure look like a reporter now.
What are you doing?
What's with her?
Does she hate me that much?
Please let me audition.
- Okay. I'll talk to the director. - Are you sure?
- In return, do me a favor. - Tell me what it is.
I'll do anything for you.
I haven't taken a shower in three days. I smell so bad.
- Do you have any ideas... - Hyun Joon...
who should play the Saudi spy who works for the Korean government?
It's hard to find a good Arab actor...
who can speak Korean.
Gosh, that's a problem. It's an important role.
What is that brat doing?
Dong Gu, do you have any ideas?
Hyun Joon!
Gosh.
Hyun Joon? What do you mean?
Sorry?
Oh, you mean Shin Hyun Joon.
Are you saying he should dress like an Arab...
and play the role?
Wouldn't it look unnatural if he plays an Arab?
It'd be funny.
It's a shift in viewpoint.
- Try contacting him. - Okay.
- Dong Gu. - Yes?
I love your ideas. You're good at this. Well done.
Thank you.
Good for you. I thought of Shin Hyun Joon too.
- Sorry? - But you were faster than me.
Sorry.
Whatever.
I wanted to treat you to something nicer than tteokbokki.
What are you talking about? This is nice too.
It tastes better because it's your treat.
You're letting me use your studio...
and teaching me baking skills.
I really wanted to treat you to something nice.
Tteokbokki is enough for me.
Are you sure it's enough?
It tasted really nice.
- Gosh, my back. - My goodness.
Are you okay?
- Try to get up. - I'm sorry.
Hey!
- Try to get up. - Okay.
Be careful.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
I've running around all day.
I need some sleep.
I need sleep.
(Jun Ki)
- What is it? - Seo Jin.
Do you have some time?
- Why? - Guess what?
I'll treat you to some nice food.
Come here.
Where are you? Okay.
Gosh, why does he want me to come all the way there?
Gosh, I really don't want to do this.
I'm doing you a favor.
This is so annoying.
I'm here.
Hi.
Why did you want me to come here?
I was so tired after working all night.
The thing is, I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Well...
Over here.
Who is he?
He is a producer I know.
Let me introduce you to each other.
This is my friend's sister, Kang Seo Jin.
This is Kim Jae Woo, a producer at JBC.
Hello.
Hello!
My name is Kim Jae Woo!
Nice to meet you!
Gosh.
Why is he yelling?
He injured his ears while shooting.
He'll recover soon. Don't worry.
Jae Woo!
Your voice is too loud!
Please control it!
I'm sorry. I apologize.
Why is he here?
He said that he liked you.
He wanted me to set him up with you on a blind date.
A... A blind date?
Jun Ki, can we talk in private?
What are you doing?
How could you do this without telling me?
- I'm leaving. - Hey.
You can't just leave.
To be honest, there's an audition I want to try.
He's the assistant director.
He said that...
if I introduced you to him, he'd give me a chance to audition.
Don't you feel bad for me...
who always has a hard time?
Seo Jin, please let me ask you for a favor.
Just this once.
Fine. However,
I'm leaving after a meal.
Thank you so much, Seo Jin.
Please take good care of him.
You can do it.
He's such a jerk.
Seo Jin. What would you like to eat?
Let's just eat...
gorgonzola pizza and carbonara spaghetti.
Pardon?
I can't hear you. Can you speak...
more loudly?
Let's get gorgonzola pizza and carbonara spaghetti.
Gorgonzola pizza and carbonara spaghetti?
What would you like to drink?
Grapefruit-ade, please.
Grapefruit-ade?
Excuse me. I'd like to order.
We heard you.
The chef is already making your order.
Thank you.
This is embarrassing.
I'm going to the restroom.
- Pardon? - I'm going to the restroom!
I see. Go ahead.
Release it.
I'm home.
Hello.
How was it? Did you enjoy working on a movie?
It's just hectic.
What is it?
What's this smell?
These are socks.
The director asked me to wash them because he has no time.
Gosh.
Why are you taking care of Sol? Where's Yoon Ah?
She isn't back yet since this morning.
What? Not yet?
It's so late.
Why? Are you worried?
You said that you don't care about her anymore.
I'm not worried at all.
It's because I'm hungry.
It's Yoon Ah.
Hello, Yoon Ah.
Is that so? I see.
Okay, I got it.
Was it Yoon Ah? What did she say?
She said that she'll be late.
She's at Song Hyun Joon's house.
He got hurt, and his child is sick,
so she has to nurse him.
Does that mean...
that they're alone in the house?
At this late hour?
What if something happens between them?
- You must be worried, Dong Gu. - Stop it.
What are you talking about? I'm not worried at all.
I should get some sleep.
Hello? Director?
Your socks?
Okay, I'll be right there.
What's wrong with him?
What is it?
My director is on location scouting.
He says that he has to wear certain socks for it.
He wants me to bring them.
Gosh, it's so late.
I'll be back.
Socks for location scouting?
- Do they exist? - I don't know.
Do they help with location scouting?
Why isn't she answering?
Why isn't she answering her phone?
Goodness.
Why are the lights off?
Why is no one here?
What's going on?
Where's Hyun Joon?
Yoon Ah. Yoon Ah?
Why are the lights off? Why is no one here?
What's going on?
Where's Hyun Joon?
- Yoon Ah. Yoon Ah? - Excuse me.
The class is over. What's going on?
Can you give me Song Hyun Joon's home address?
- Why? - Pardon?
It's because...
I have a package delivery.
Mr. Song Hyun Joon has a delivery.
- Let me see it. - Okay.
His name was written somewhere.
Wait, sir. His name was definitely here.
There's a name of the sender.
Here it is.
Here's his name.
Song Hyun Joon.
It's a package delivery,
but why isn't his address written on it?
There are many who write the name but not the address.
So please tell me Song Hyun Joon's address.
I can't give you his personal information.
Just leave it to me.
I'll give it to him tomorrow.
No.
It's an urgent delivery.
I have to give it to him right away.
I think it's food.
It's already rotting.
Smell it. It smells rotten.
I think it's very expensive.
I don't know.
Do whatever you want.
Whether it gets rotten or not,
you're responsible for it.
Please wait.
Yes?
Who is it?
- Yoon Ah. - Dong Gu.
Why are you at my director's house?
Your director's house? It's Hyun Joon's place.
That's impossible.
My director asked me to bring him something,
so I'm on an errand.
Did he give me the wrong address?
What happened?
Who is it?
- It's... - Goodness!
Hello.
We met briefly a while ago.
Right. Hello.
Do you live here?
It's not polite if I just leave.
You'd feel better if I come in and have some tea.
Don't you have to run an errand?
Right.
Yes, Director.
What?
You don't need socks for location scouting?
I see. Okay.
He's so fickle.
He said that I don't need to come anymore.
In that case, I should have some tea.
Yes, please come in.
Hello, Du Shik. What?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Okay.
Dong Gu, Sol can't stop crying.
I should get going.
Can you stay here for a while?
Pardon?
Me?
His son is sick, and as you can see, Hyun Joon isn't well.
Please take care of them.
Wait, Yoon Ah. Yoon Ah?
What do you mean?
Why is Dong Gu at his house?
His director's house must be in the same building.
Dong Gu thought that it was his director's house.
We bumped into each other when he rang the bell by mistake.
Really?
That's such an unlikely coincidence.
It must be very awkward...
when two strangers are together.
Let them be.
Nothing won't happen.
You don't get any comments on your social network.
Why do you keep looking at it?
What? I do get comments.
My fans write comments.
Fine, take a look.
Gosh.
"Cheer up, Jun Ki." "Your acting is the best."
What? It's true.
What kind of nickname is "junki love"?
Gosh.
It's true that the world is a big place,
and it's full of crazy people.
- Gosh. - What? You're jealous.
Give it to me. I don't want to talk to someone without fans.
"You're at the destination".
Gosh, what was that?
Who turned on the navigation so loudly?
Seo Jin, I had so much fun today.
Goodbye.
Thank you for giving me a lift.
- Take care. - Isn't that Seo Jin?
- Thank you. - Why is she screaming?
It's... Never mind.
Hello, Seo Jin.
Hey. Seo Jin. Hey.
Seo Jin, what's wrong?
Did anything happen?
Can't you see? My eardrums nearly burst because of him.
Just wait patiently.
He's being treated.
- He'll be better when it's over. - It's fine.
Now that you introduced me, are you satisfied?
Wait. Seo Jin.
I have a few days until the audition.
Can't you see him until then?
No.
All right.
Okay.
The audition is hopeless now.
If the drama succeeds,
I'll be regretting this moment for the rest of my life.
I think I'm destined to be without fame forever.
All right. All right.
But only until the audition.
Seo Jin, thank you. Thank you.
Let go.
Take a rest now. Rest.
Jerk.
Gosh, it's so awkward.
Do I have to stay the night with him?
It's fine.
I have you guys.
Hey. Dong Gu.
Dong Gu.
What is it? Why is he calling for me?
- What is it? - I'm sorry,
but can you come inside and help me?
What is it?
What are you doing? Gosh!
Why are you naked? Why!
Well, you see...
I got myself to the toilet,
but I can't stand up by myself.
And?
Why did you call for me? Why?
Can you...
help me up?
What? Help you up?
Do I need to help you in that state?
I can't stand up by myself.
All right.
Hold out your hand. Just your hand.
- I did. - Slowly.
Your hand. The other one too.
Make sure I don't touch it.
- I don't want to touch. - All right.
Let me go.
Gosh.
- Thank you so much. - It's nothing.
Wait. Can you...
What is it? What?
I'm sorry again,
but can you help me pull up my pants and underwear?
I can't bend my back.
All right.
Gosh.
Gosh, stand still.
- I'm sorry. - Gosh.
I'm sorry.
Oh gosh. I saw it. I saw it.
Try to cover it up with something!
Why do you have to do this to me?
What's wrong? Gosh! I saw it again!
Why did you fall down? Gosh!
Gosh, why are you doing that?
Is Dong Gu all right?
I should call him.
I'm back.
Hello, Dong Gu.
- How is his son? Is he all right? - Yes.
What a relief.
It must have been awkward with Hyun Joon.
Did anything happen?
What?
No, nothing happened.
Yoon Ah, I'm mentally tired right now.
I need to get some sleep.
What's wrong with him?
Did they fight?
It can't be. This can't be!
This couldn't have happened!
What's wrong with him?
Gosh, it's too salty.
Why can't you even cook noodles right?
- Then don't eat it. - It's delicious.
- Thank you. - Be quiet and just eat.
We've arrived at the destination.
What's this again?
Seo Jin must be here.
You might really hurt your ears if you stay with him.
Chewbacca. What's that flower?
Hey. Hey! Hey!
- Go talk to her. - All right.
Hey, Chewbacca!
What is that? What is it?
Did he give it to you?
It must be working out all right.
He asked me out.
- Really? - What do you want me to do?
Should I go out with him?
That's your choice to make.
- If you don't like him... - Jun Ki.
- Can I ask you something? - What?
Am I...
not a woman to you?
What are you talking about?
To me, you're a man.
What should I do?
Of course, I'm a man. I'm not a woman.
That's not what I'm saying.
I think...
I like you.
What?
(Thank you, Tae In Ho, Shin Seung Hwan, and Seol Jung Hwan.)
(Welcome to Waikiki)
Gosh, why do I have to feel sorry?
Is there something wrong with Seo Jin?
She hasn't been looking well these past few days.
- Should I look at it? - What is this?
Kang Seo Jin, what is this?
- Why did you do it? - Why do you think?
I'm going on a date with Seo Jin today.
What? You won't be seeing her today.
Seo Jin, we need to talk.
- I want to learn fashion design. - I'll help you.
Who's the prince that experienced a tragic death?
Yoo Ah In!
Should we start with English first?
- Hi, Johnny. - Jane.
- My mystic. - Mistake.
It's only because it's been a while. Don't worry.
Why do you care so much about Hyun Joon?
He's always near Yoon Ah. I don't like that.
Hyun Joon, you're really good with marbles.
Hello. Teach me how to play with marbles.
I need to learn.
I really want to be good at it. Please.
Song Hyun Joon, you should have a marble match with me.