It was you, wasn't it?
You did it, didn't you?
That's right. I stopped the news from being released.
Don't you know that the anchor has editorial rights?
What?
How can you still call yourself a journalist?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Stop acting so innocent.
You...
You'll...
end up getting hurt.
What? You jerk.
Cut.
That was great. Let's move on to the next scene.
Are you all right?
I don't quite know how to control myself yet.
It's all right.
That can always happen while acting.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you for understanding.
Jun Ki. Here's you cell phone.
It's been ringing nonstop for a while. Answer it.
I see. Thank you.
Hello? Yes. This is Lee Jun Ki speaking.
Excuse me?
Yes. Yes. I understand.
What was that about?
Well, you see,
I was just offered to appear in a commercial.
On top of that, it's a coffee commercial.
What?
Gosh. Even I haven't been in a coffee commercial yet.
Congratulations, Jun Ki.
That's awesome.
Thank you.
(The Morning Dew in Columbia)
Don't you know that the anchor has editorial rights?
What?
How can you still call yourself a journalist?
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
Stop acting so innocent.
You'll end up getting hurt.
You jerk.
Stop!
My goodness. See that look on my face.
Don't I look really charismatic?
You jerk.
Wasn't that amazing? Wasn't I great?
We get it now. Now, can we watch something else?
I'm sick and tired of watching that.
You're sick and tired of it?
- You jerk. - Gosh.
You're making a fuss over a supporting role.
I'm sure you'll get worse when you play a leading role.
What? You jerk.
By the way, why do they want you to be in their commercial?
I thought only top stars shoot coffee commercials.
Do they want to go bankrupt?
Gosh.
What? You jerk.
Stop it now, okay?
I'm going to the meeting.
Hold on. Can I use your car today?
Do you mean Rebecca?
Why? For what reason?
Without a car, it's too inconvenient to pick up clothes.
And taxis are expensive.
So I want to practice driving.
Is your car in a good condition?
Of course.
Rebecca is so sturdy.
But don't try to open the right window.
Why?
It's a sad story.
Please be easy on Rebecca.
- Okay. - You better use another car.
Don't worry.
But isn't it expensive to hire an instructor?
It's no problem. Du Shik will help me.
What? Me?
When? Where? What? How? Why?
Just follow me, Director Bong.
Hold on. I'm not even wearing socks. Just look at this.
Don't worry. You'll be sitting in the car anyway.
- See you later. - Hey.
- Hey. - Du Shik, it's dangerous.
- Dong Gu. - See you.
- Be careful. - Okay.
- Hey. - Rebecca is pretty rough.
I'll get going then.
I'm heading out too. Wait for me.
Okay.
Seo Jin, stop.
Didn't I tell you to keep a 5m distance from him?
You can leave five minutes after Jun Ki.
What?
When are you going to stop doing this?
Well, that would be when I don't have to suspect you two anymore.
Sit down, please.
- Gosh. - What?
Then I'll get going now.
Okay. Go ahead.
Gosh. You're bossing me around.
This is so annoying.
What? Do you have...
something else to do?
- No. - You have nothing to do anyway.
Can you drive?
Of course. I got my license eight years ago.
I haven't driven since then though.
What? Never?
It'll be fine.
I'll get the hang of it soon.
All right. Let's go.
This is annoying.
Du Shik, which pedal is for the brakes?
Is it the left pedal or right pedal?
What?
You want to drive a car without even knowing that?
It's been a while, so I'm a bit confused.
This doesn't feel right.
What is this?
It won't open.
You have to open that door from the outside.
Nothing in this car works.
Hold on.
What are you doing?
My gosh. Seriously.
Director Bong, what are you doing? Let's go.
All right. Just a second.
All right. Here we go.
Gosh. What are you doing, you idiot?
What? "Idiot"? Are you serious?
I take it back.
Here we go then.
(Can't tell the brake from the accelerator)
(Beginner driver, future murderer)
Hey, slow down.
You jerk!
Gosh, stop it.
Seo Jin, it's me.
Jun Ki?
What was that? You scared me.
Are you okay?
Are you sure you're not being followed?
I'm talking about Dong Gu.
What are you talking about?
Dong Gu has other things to do.
Didn't you see his eyes?
He looked like the Grim Reaper.
We better be careful.
My goodness.
Are we shooting a spy movie or what?
There's nothing wrong with being careful.
Then should we grab some coffee?
Don't you have a meeting this morning?
But I have time for a cup of coffee with you.
Don't worry.
I hope you'll get the commercial contract.
Don't worry. It's almost decided.
Really?
Have you told your father yet? He'd be so happy.
Yes. He feels proud of me.
He complimented me for the first time...
in the 31 years of my life.
Oh, I'm so proud of my boyfriend.
Darn it. I lost her.
Did she figure out I was following her?
Seo Jin. Jun Ki.
I'll catch you guys some day.
When I do,
you will no longer be alive.
There are not many cars...
or people on this road. It's perfect for practice.
But driving isn't that difficult.
Oh, I forgot the most important thing.
Hey, are you crazy?
Why would you take your hands off the wheel?
You got it. What's the problem?
You should put on sunglasses when you drive.
What are you talking about?
Put your hands back on the wheel.
This is not a self-driving car, you psycho.
- What? - I take it back. Hold the wheel.
Give me a second. Let me look in the mirror.
I can't believe you.
Gosh.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Is it funny?
Dong Gu, what are you doing?
Why are you scooping out the bread?
Oh, this?
I need to check if an air rifle fits inside this bread.
An air rifle inside the bread?
Our main character is a spy.
And they want to put a rifle inside the bread.
- Why? - I don't know.
They say it was my idea, but I don't remember anything.
Anyway, they want me to put an air rifle inside this bread.
I don't know what I'm doing.
- Where are you going? - I'm going to the studio.
Again?
Don't you think you're going there too often?
There's a lot to do around here.
I'm done with everything.
Are you sure?
I looked around yesterday,
and there were many things to repair.
Like what? Where?
Well,
the dormitory room on the second floor...
Do you mean the slightly loose doorknob?
I bought a new one and replaced it this morning.
Really?
The single room on the second floor...
The light that flickers every 4.2 seconds?
I went up there by a ladder...
and fixed all short circuits yesterday.
Oh, right. On the third floor...
Do you mean the third stair that was a bit unstable?
I bought a welding machine and fixed it this morning.
You can go then.
Okay. See you, Sol.
Please take care of Sol.
Bye.
Okay. Bye.
What was that?
Sol.
Your mom can even weld now.
She's like an engineer.
I don't want her to spend too much time with Hyun Joon.
Gosh, whatever.
Why are they putting an air rifle in the bread?
What kind of movie is this?
I'm sorry, Jun Ki.
The advertiser suddenly recommended Jae Hyun.
I didn't want to do it,
but my agency pressured me.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
Still,
I don't want to look like I'm taking your contract away.
This is not right.
By the way, do you know why they recommended me?
Well,
your smile is most important in this advertisement.
Some people were not completely satisfied...
with Jun Ki's smile.
But...
what kind of smile do they want?
A smile as fresh as...
morning dew.
"A smile as fresh as morning dew"?
Let's eat first.
Sure.
- Jae Hyun. - Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Wait. Why is he suddenly smiling?
You fell pretty hard.
It hurts a bit. But I'm...
really okay.
Wait. He's smiling again.
Is he showing off his smile?
Now, I feel...
a lot better now.
He is.
What if I lose my contract to him?
Then should we go eat now?
Sure.
My phone is ringing. Just a second.
Hello.
What? Really?
How...
Okay.
What's the matter?
A friend of mine collapsed.
He's getting surgery right now.
He's like a brother to me.
His name is Kang Dong Gu.
You must be so worried.
It's okay.
I'm all right.
Okay. I'm sure everything will be all right.
- Stay strong, Jun Ki. - Okay.
I should stay positive in difficult situations.
I'm okay.
I see.
Then what shall we eat for lunch today?
Tofu with kimchi or sandwich.
"Tofu with kimchi or sandwich"?
- How about you, Jun Ki? - I think...
tofu with kimchi...
or sandwich would be good,
but sushi is also good.
Hey.
Until when will you do that?
Why are you fixing your makeup while driving?
Can't you see the tan line from the sunglasses?
Be quiet, and grab the steering wheel.
Fine, I will. Goodness.
You're being annoying.
Hey, go slowly.
You're going too fast. Step on the brakes.
- What's this? - What?
Is this the brake pedal?
- Let me see. - Here you go.
- This is the brake pedal. - What?
Did the brake pedal just break now?
That's amazing.
It's not the time to be impressed.
Goodness, what's wrong with this?
- How did the brakes... - What do I do?
What do I do now, Du Shik?
Take your foot off the accelerator.
- Then the car will slow down. - Okay.
I took off my foot, but it's not slowing down.
What should I do, Du Shik?
My goodness, we might get in a car accident.
The hand brakes. The hand brakes!
What's going on?
What kind of car is this?
Du Shik, what should we do?
We have no choice. Let's report it.
Let's call 911.
- Call 911. - Where's my cell phone?
Where is it? Wait.
Darn it.
I left my cell phone on top of the car.
Soo Ah, give me your phone.
- Give me your cell phone. - My cell phone?
Where's my cell phone?
Gosh, I left it at home.
Seriously.
Then we have no choice.
What are you doing?
Jun Ki told us not to open that window.
It has a sad legend.
What else can I do? My cell phone is on top.
What is this? Why doesn't this window open?
Goodness. Jun Ki, that jerk.
This is such a mess.
I think I might reach it.
Hey, why are you raising the window?
I didn't.
It hurts. Lower the window.
- Okay. - My arm might get cut off.
- It's cold outside. - What?
- It doesn't work either. - What?
What kind of car is this?
Hey, Soo Ah.
What should we do? There's a big street.
A big street?
Turn left. Go to the construction site.
- Go to the construction site. - Okay.
Hey, go slowly.
Go in straight.
- How? - Go toward the side.
Why did you crash into that? What's happening now.
What should I do now, Du Shik?
Turn the car over there.
Keep turning.
What? Keep turning?
What else can we do? We might get into an accident if we go out.
Why did you suggest practicing your driving skills?
I didn't know this would happen.
(Room D)
Jun Ki, try some of this.
Oh, thank you.
It's nice to see you like that.
Are you quite close?
Of course. We're as close as brothers.
But sir,
is the concept for the commercial finished?
Of course.
The most important thing about this commercial...
is your smile as I mentioned before.
Next, is your facial expression.
Your facial expression must be as rich as...
a rainbow.
A facial expression...
- as rich as a rainbow? - That's right.
- Let's eat up. - Sure.
Gosh, it's so sour.
It's sour.
- Is the kimchi that sour? - Yes.
- It's like chewing on sour lemon. - Lemon?
- It's sour. - I should drink some water.
Gosh, it's so cold.
- It's really cold. - Here he goes again.
Fine. Bring it on.
The chili looks delicious.
It feels like my mouth is burning.
It's spicy.
I want dongchimi.
It's sweet and sour.
It's so sour, yet sweet.
It's flavorful.
It's sweet and sour.
Until when do we have to do this?
I don't know either.
You should keep driving until the car runs out of gas.
There's no one passing by.
Why do I feel so gassy?
Did I eat too much pizza earlier?
I'm about to fart. What should I do?
You startled me.
Why did you honk all of a sudden?
What? There was a cat.
A cat? I don't see any cats.
What's this smell?
Is there a sewer nearby?
Soo Ah.
Did you fart?
Is that why you honked?
No way.
I honked because there was a cat.
Stop kidding.
It isn't just the noise.
What will you do about the smell?
Fine, I farted.
But you seriously have no manners.
You should pretend not to know when a lady farts.
Did you have to say it?
They say that those who fart get angry. It's exactly right.
Forget it. That's why you've never dated until now.
What? Why do you make fun of my weakness?
Forget it. I won't talk to you anymore.
You startled me. What?
- Did you fart again? - No, I honked because of a cat.
Gosh, it smells.
What did you eat?
I honked because of a cat.
Stop farting.
I'm not honking because I farted.
Anyway, sir,
is there any other important factor...
other than rich facial expressions?
Another factor?
Your voice is important too.
How shall I put it?
It's a sweet voice like coffee powder...
melting in hot water.
Something like the voice of Gong Yoo or Sung Si Kyung...
from "Goblin".
Gong Yoo or Sung Si Kyung?
You're out of soup, Director.
- Excuse me, ma'am. - Yes?
Yes?
It tastes delicious and seasoned right.
As we enjoyed the soup,
we order one more bean paste soup.
- Pardon? - Also,
the texture is good.
It's simmered the right amount.
As we enjoyed rice,
we order one more bowl of rice.
Okay, another doenjang soup and rice at table three.
Why am I getting a call?
Pardon me for being on the phone.
Hello?
What?
Right now? I can't right now.
It can't be helped.
It would be nice
While holding your hand tightly
I wish I could walk on this street
Jun Ki, why are you singing all of a sudden?
Do you remember my friend, Kang Dong Gu?
He's in surgery right now.
He wanted to hear me sing.
Then you should sing.
Thank you for understanding. I'll finish it.
It would be nice
While holding your hand tightly
I wish I could walk on this street
You are the only one for me
I'm tired.
How long have we been driving?
Is it because of the pizza that I had?
I'm getting a stomachache.
I'm about to lose it.
My stomach hurts.
My endless farting doesn't seem normal.
Hey, aren't you being too harsh?
What did I do?
It's because there was a cat.
Stop talking about cats.
You aren't the only one with a stomachache.
I have a stomachache too.
If I relax just a little bit,
I'm in the verge of causing a disaster.
But I'm controlling myself because I still have a sense of decency.
Never mind. I refuse to speak to you any longer.
Don't you dare speak to me.
Why don't you just do it? Just go ahead, and do it.
What are you looking at? I can't concentrate.
Well, you looked so happy.
You really look happy when you bake bread.
- Do I? - Yes.
Hyun Joon. Was becoming a patisseur your childhood dream?
Yes. Ever since I was a child,
I loved bread.
So I spent too much money on bread.
I thought it wasn't right.
I figured I should start baking bread myself.
It all started from there, and here I am today.
Stop joking around.
Yoon Ah. What about you?
Did you dream of becoming a patisseur as well?
No. I had another dream.
I've given up that dream now though.
Is that right? What was it?
A rapper.
"A rapper"?
I honestly think my rap has a competitive edge,
but apparently, people don't get my swag.
You wanted to be a rapper?
I wonder how that would be.
Really? Then would you like to hear me rap?
Sure. It would be an honor.
Then I'll do an impromptu rap about you.
Yeah
Get it This is a song about
the boy that loved bread
Hyun Joon
Hyun Joon likes bread, right? It's delicious, right?
Baguette, croissant Sausage rolls, vegetable rolls
Red bean buns, cream buns
Bread, bread
Chew them well Yummy, yummy
(Garam red bean steamed bun)
Why is it taking them so long just to decide their model?
I have no intention of appearing in a commercial.
They're only wasting my time.
From the way I see it, the director...
really seemed to like you.
Jun Ki. Make sure you treat me to a meal if you get this job.
All right.
(Dad)
Yes, Dad. What is it?
The commercial?
It hasn't been decided yet.
I'm waiting for the result.
There's no need to worry, CEO Park.
We decided to cast Jae Hyun just now.
One moment, Dad.
I assure you.
How could I possibly turn down your favor, CEO Park?
I convinced the director to cast Jae Hyun, so don't worry.
In return, you have to give me that bag you promised.
I'll send you a text message with the exact name of the model. Okay.
Yes, Dad.
If you don't mind, can I call you back later?
All right.
Gosh. My stomach aches.
I can't even breathe now.
What if I really end up...
dumping my load in front of Soo Ah? I can't let that happen. My gosh.
Gosh. This is killing me.
I really think I've reached my limit.
Du Shik's with me. This is driving me crazy.
All right. I have no choice.
I'll have to jump out.
Du Shik.
If you don't mind, could you take over the steering wheel?
What? All right.
Soo Ah. Are you crazy? What are you doing?
Don't stop me. I think I'll die. My stomach hurts so bad.
So are you really jumping out?
You'll die if you jump out.
I don't care.
Whether I die by jumping out...
or die of shame after dumping my load in front of you,
either way, I'll end up dying.
No. It'd be much better dying from jumping out of this car.
What are you saying? Get a hold of yourself.
Don't stop me. Don't try to stop me.
It stopped,
right?
It stopped. We'll live.
- We survived, Soo Ah. - Du Shik.
Get off me.
- Tissue. - What? Yes, tissue.
I found some. I found some.
I found some. I found some tissue.
Du Shik. Give me a sheet.
What? There's only one sheet?
Du Shik.
No. I can't give this up.
This...
is my last bastion of my human rights.
Forgive me, Soo Ah.
I knew it.
Even I wouldn't be able to give it away myself.
I understand.
You don't need to feel guilty.
I'll try to get through this somehow.
I'll just have to find some wastepaper somewhere.
Soo Ah.
- Du Shik. - Take it before I change my mind.
Hurry up.
What about you?
It's already too late for me.
So hurry up, and go.
And go somewhere far from here.
Go as far as you can.
Du Shik. I'm sorry,
but I have a favor to ask.
Soo Ah.
I can't believe you.
You shouldn't be asking me to do this.
How could she ask me to do this?
Du Shik. It's time.
Does Yoon Ah know what time it is? Why isn't she home yet?
What on earth is she doing with Hyun Joon every day?
- Yoon Ah. You're home. - I'm home.
Dong Gu. How are you?
I'm not doing well.
Yoon Ah. Why are you home so late?
Do you know how much we have to do because you were gone?
I'm sorry. I didn't realize it had gotten so late.
Never mind. Go change your clothes,
and clean up the kitchen first.
All right.
Hyun Joon, I'll see you in class then.
Yoon Ah. Take this.
I almost forgot.
Thank you for the gift.
Don't mention it. After all, I was able to hear your amazing rap.
I thought I should give you something in return.
Thank you. I'll make good use of this mini oven.
I'll see you in class then.
- Then I'll get going now. - Wait. Wait right there.
Hyun Joon. You and I should talk.
What would you like to talk about?
If Yoon Ah comes home late,
it greatly affects our business.
So could you please have her come home early from now on?
She's my employee.
You have no sense of business ethics.
Are you that anxious?
What?
That's how it looks to me.
I'm clearly at a disadvantage,
but seeing you being that anxious...
doesn't feel all that bad.
You should get some rest.
Wait a minute. What is that supposed to mean?
We're not finished here. Where are you going?
What? Do I feel anxious?
Why would I be anxious?
I don't feel anxious at all.
What kind of joke was that?
Jun Ki, you're home.
What happened to that commercial?
Of course, like always,
I failed the audition.
Why? You said it was almost confirmed.
It just turned out that way.
What is that supposed to mean? There's got to be a reason.
You see...
What? How could they do such a thing?
Seriously. Those jerks.
What can I do?
I should accept the fact since I don't have connections or money.
Cheer up, Jun Ki.
I'm sure another good opportunity will come your way.
I'm all right.
I'll be all right about myself,
but I'm worried about disappointing my father.
He was so excited.
Have you been practicing driving until now?
But what happened to you?
Isn't that Soo Ah's dress?
Why are you wearing it?
That's right.
Where did your pants go?
What did you do outside?
Don't ask us anything.
Don't ask us...
anything at all.
Soo Ah.
I'll return this dress...
after washing it tomorrow.
No. Keep it.
I couldn't wear it again.
You can keep it.
I'm going to bed now.
Jun Ki.
Why don't you just scrap Rebecca?
What are you talking about?
Why would I?
Don't ask me why.
Just do it.
It's for your own sake.
Hey.
What are you talking about while dressed like a shaman?
Cheer up.
You'll get another commercial contract soon.
That's right.
Try this bread.
You didn't have any breakfast.
I'm okay. I don't have much of an appetite.
Wait. Isn't that the commercial you were going to shoot?
That's right. Colombia Espresso.
- Right? - I don't care.
I don't want to see it.
I need some rest.
- Wait. What's that? - It's morning in Colombia.
Coffee beans wake up with a smile...
as fresh as morning dew.
Emma roasts freshly-picked coffee beans every morning.
It brings out flavors...
as rich as the colors of the rainbow.
Coffee powder melts with a sound...
as soft as spring sunshine.
Enjoy a cup of coffee every morning.
Colombia Espresso.
What's that? It's so tacky.
- What was that? - Exactly.
It's so embarrassing.
It's a good thing that you didn't do it.
What's that?
He played such dirty tricks...
- to shoot that commercial? - Exactly.
It's so humiliating.
Why? It's the handsomest coffee bean I've ever seen.
He has a smile as fresh as morning dew,
facial expressions as rich as the colors of the rainbow,
and a voice as soft as morning sunshine.
You're finally laughing.
- Are you happy? - Yes, I am.
My appetite is suddenly back.
It tastes great.
It melts in your mouth.
My goodness.
Here. Eat a lot.
It just melts in your mouth.
Hey, what are you doing?
It's the 49th day since Olivia died.
Poor Olivia.
I hope her suffering has stopped.
Dong Gu.
You know you're as crazy as I am, right?
How can you say that?
You're the one who killed Olivia.
I'll buy you a better one when I get paid.
When?
When will you get paid?
I want to shoot movies, and I don't even have a camera.
If I had even a cheap camera, I'll be able to forget about Olivia.
It's not like this service will bring her back.
That's not why I'm doing it.
Jun Ki, I came up with something amazing.
- It's incredible. - Something amazing?
- What is it? - Do you want to see? Come.
- What is it? - Be quiet!
I'm holding a memorial service.
(Lee Jun Ki)
(Bong Du Shik)
Ready.
Go!
Go, go, go!
Go! Okay!
3.8 seconds.
Incredible. It's a new record.
Move. Let me try. It's my turn.
Here we go.
Ready.
- Go! - Here I go.
Go, go, go!
What are you doing right now?
Is it skeleton this time?
It's not exactly skeleton. It's something similar.
- Du Shik came up with... - Cut it out!
Don't you realize how childish this is?
- How old are you? - 31.
You're not a kid. What are you doing now?
I'm sorry.
Jun Ki, you didn't forget we're meeting my friend today, did you?
- Is it today? - You forgot?
Hurry up, and get ready.
Okay.
(No Matter How Much I Think about It)
What do you think?
I've been here recently,
and I thought the food tasted pretty good.
I love it.
- Thank you for bringing us here. - Don't mention it.
Seo Jin has been bragging so much about her boyfriend.
You're just as handsome as I imagined.
Thank you.
I get that a lot.
You're funny too.
Hey, you're lucky.
I guess so.
Right. Ji Young's boyfriend is a potter.
"A potter"?
So you're an artist.
Please come by studio sometime.
- Let me show you around. - Sure.
That'd be great.
I heard you're an actor.
You're appearing in "Newsroom" these days, right?
Yes.
What other shows have you been in?
Well, do you recognize this one?
- Octopus ink... - Octopus ink...
- gun! - gun!
Oh, that's a children's show.
You were so funny in that one.
No, I wasn't.
I'm not that funny.
You got me wrong.
That's hilarious.
Do you want to see another one?
That's so funny.
Seo Jin, why are you being like that?
Did I do something wrong?
Do you have to ask?
What did I do?
What's the matter with you?
Why would you do such silly things in front of my friend?
It was a bit awkward, so I wanted to brighten up the mood.
Why do you have to do that?
Are you a clown?
Why are you never serious?
Can't you act like a grown-up?
I'm sorry.
I'll be careful from now on.
That's not enough.
Just stop it altogether.
Stop it altogether?
Well, I'm not sure...
I'll do it just at home. How about that?
Fine. I'll stop.
I'll stop being silly. Are you happy now?
Are you sure?
Keep your promise.
I will.
That's my boy.
It fits.
Gosh, it really fits.
What is this?
Why are you coming in together?
We met in front of the house.
That's right.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Jun Ki!
What took you so long? I've been waiting for you.
Let's play another game.
Another game?
That sounds like fun.
My throat hurts.
Du Shik, I'm sorry,
but I don't think I can do it anymore.
What? Why?
Well, I'm not going to do things like that anymore.
You can do it by yourself.
Jun Ki. Jun Ki.
What's wrong? Jun Ki.
Why?
Yoon Ah, you're still here.
Yes. I just wanted to finish these.
Really? By the way,
I wanted to give you something.
Here.
What's this?
This is the money you earned from selling your muffins.
It's not much though.
What are you doing? Take it.
I'm not sure if I can take this.
You earned it. It's yours.
Go on.
Gosh, my hands are falling off.
Look, the envelop is falling.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- Hey. - Let's just do one game.
I'm not going to.
Are you really going to act like this?
Why are you doing this to me all of a sudden?
I don't want to play games like that.
Gosh, you've changed.
- I'm home. - Hello.
What are those?
I got my first payment for my muffins,
so I bought a few things for you.
What do you think? Do you like them?
Of course. I like it.
I'm going to wear this every day!
I really wanted to buy an elephant hat.
Thanks, Yoon Ah.
Yes.
I was looking for a mirror like this.
How did you know?
I really like this too.
But what is this?
What do I use it for? Blushers?
It's a shaving brush that is used for shaving.
Shaving brush?
It's made from badger's fur.
I heard it works really well.
Really?
It makes me so happy to be able to shave...
with badger fur.
I knew you'd like it.
In fact, I'm really good at choosing presents.
By the way, is Dong Gu in his room?
I have something for him too.
What do you think? Do you like it?
What?
Of course. I really like chickens.
That's why I don't even eat chickens often.
I knew you'd like it.
Dong Gu, are you free tomorrow?
Me? Why do you ask?
I have so much to thank you for,
so I wanted to buy you a meal.
A meal?
No, you don't need to.
When, where, and at what time do you want to meet?
Gosh, it's so embarrassing.
I look like an elementary school student.
But I had to wear this since it was a gift from Yoon Ah.
- Dong Gu. - Yoon Ah.
Sorry for being late.
You wore it today.
Yes, I liked it so much that I had to wear it.
Then what should we eat?
Wait.
It's strange. Why isn't he here yet?
What? Who's coming?
Yoon Ah.
Hyun Joon.
Why are you...
Why are you here?
I was on my way to meet Dong Gu...
when Hyun Joon called me to have lunch with me.
So I thought it'd be a nice idea...
to have lunch together. Would that be okay?
- Sure. - Well, sure.
Where did you get that shirt?
I liked it so much that I gave it to him as a gift too.
But I didn't know you'd wear it on the same day.
You must have really liked it.
Of course.
I like it so much.
Let's go eat.
- Okay. - Sure.
Why did you wear that?
What are you doing?
We should have a talk.
Let me go.
Gosh, why did you have to hold me like that?
People are watching.
Why do you sit next to Yoon Ah?
I just sat there.
One of us has to sit there.
Why does it have to be you?
What do you want me to do?
Hyun Joon, we're enemies,
but let's play fair like men.
"Play fair"?
I'm buying today, so eat up.
- Thanks. - Thanks.
Someone's calling me.
Sorry, but I'll go outside and get this.
- What? - What?
This must look weird.
Gosh.
Can't you sit away from me?
It's cramped here.
Do your best.
When I created this, I was inspired by...
- the famous potter, Peter Voulkos. - Really?
I wanted to make a Korean version of his abstract pottery.
I see.
- Do you want to see that one too? - Sure.
Seo Jin.
I don't know, I can't know
Doesn't this remind you of Uhm Jeong Hwa?
- Put them down. - Yes, ma'am.
I told you to stop joking around.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing? Why are you doing this alone?
It's nothing.
It's lonely to play alone.
I want to play.
Maybe I could play with you.
Really?
What do you think? I'm great, right? Shall I do it again?
No, it's fine. Let's stop here.
It's not fun playing with you.
What? Why not?
You don't have the fun in you...
that Jun Ki has.
What? "Fun"?
Why do you need fun when you are doing this weird game?
What? "Weird game"?
Is that what you think?
What?
Forget it.
That's why you are impossible.
What? Seriously.
I was playing with him only because he was bored.
Did you like the food?
Yes, it was very delicious.
It'd been better without someone.
It was delicious.
I feel the same way.
There's a bike.
That looks fun.
Do you want to ride a bike, Yoon Ah?
Watching other people riding bikes makes me want to ride one too.
- Then... - Let's go biking then.
I'll rent them.
Here you go, Hyun Joon.
- Let's go, Yoon Ah. - Okay.
Why am I riding a one-person bike?
That was the only one left. What else could I do?
Are you saying that you'll ride the two-person bike with Yoon Ah?
- That's right. - You said that...
we should play fair like men.
What do you want to do then?
Was this necessary?
You're the one who suggested a fair play.
Forget it.
Just step on the pedals.
This is embarrassing.
What are you doing?
Why are you putting your head behind my back?
- Let's just go. - People will misunderstand.
You're a strange man.
- Goodness. - Just go.
Thank you for inviting us today.
It was so much fun.
I'll invite you to the next exhibition, so please come.
Of course I'll come.
Just give us a call.
How is working as a reporter?
It's busy.
I had no idea that being a reporter was so hard.
- Is it that hard? - Yes.
By the way, how long have you two dated?
Goodness.
- What's wrong? - My tooth.
What's wrong with your tooth?
Did your tooth fall out?
It's not a tooth
It's a pine nut, a pine nut
What?
- You startled me. - You're so funny, Jun Ki.
Isn't it funny?
It's not a tooth, it's a pine nut.
Pine nut.
What's wrong?
Why are you laughing?
It's nothing.
I feel loved.
I'm jealous, but I'm also loved.
Gosh, it's refreshing.
Isn't it great...
to ride bikes and drink beer once in a while?
Right.
But it would've been better without someone.
Let's ride bikes and drink beer together...
more often.
Okay.
Let it be just the two of us.
I'm sorry, but I'll go use the restroom.
Go ahead.
Thank you for coming tonight.
Does everyone know...
that today is our one-year anniversary of the store opening?
- Yes. - Yes.
As I promised,
we'll start a couple event...
with amazing prizes on the line.
It's so loud.
What kind of event is this at a bar?
I know. I just wanted to drink a beer in peace.
The winner of today's...
couple event...
receives a new DSLR camera.
The prize is a camera?
Those who would like to participate, please come out.
I must participate.
Why isn't Yoon Ah back yet?
Are you going to participate with Yoon Ah as a couple?
Yes, I really need a camera.
But that's cheating.
How dare you participate in a couple event with Yoon Ah?
But this doesn't mean much.
It's because of the camera.
Please understand me. Okay?
We'll wait 30 more seconds before accepting the last participants.
Gosh, Yoon Ah isn't back yet. What should I do?
She won't come back.
Wait.
What?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Hyun Joon, can you participate in the couple event with me?
What?
Are you insane? That's nonsense.
Come on, Hyun Joon.
We're rivals,
but you can still participate in a couple event with me.
That makes no sense.
I really need a camera.
I really need that camera, Hyun Joon.
Okay. 10.
Nine.
- It's still too... - Eight.
Fine.
- Seven. - If we ride bikes again,
- Six. - I'll let you ride...
the two-person bike with Yoon Ah.
- Really? Can I sit next to her too? - Five.
- What? - Four.
- Aren't you being too greedy? - Forget it then.
Three.
Fine, but it's canceled unless we win.
- Two. - I'm in.
One.
- We're in! - We're in!
The team that lasts longer...
will win the latest DSLR camera.
Hold on.
- Hyun Joon, are you okay? - Yes.
I'm okay.
I'll hold it even if I die.
Keep going, Dong Gu.
Okay.
I'll hold it even if my legs break.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
- Let me pet your face. - Thank you.
- Let's win. - Come on.
- We can do it. - We can do it.
Where is everyone?
I'm hungry.
Shall we make some ramyeon?
I don't have an appetite.
I'll go and rest.
Oh, okay.
Jun Ki.
Let's do it.
(Bong Du Shik)
3.8 seconds.
Incredible. It's a new record.
Five Sec.
- Five Sec, Five Sec - Five Sec, Five Sec
Shall I feed you, or will you take it?
- Please kiss me. - My goodness.
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
What are we doing? When can we stop?
It's okay. Don't cry.
Why are you crying? Let's think positively.
This is amazing.
My goodness.
What's wrong with him?
Well, Dong Gu is completely worn out.
"Worn out"?
What did he do?
It just happened.
Yoon Ah,
I'll help Dong Gu to his bed, okay?
Sure, I'll get some water.
All right. Gosh.
Why is he so heavy?
Matilda.
If you're Matilda, I'm Leon.
What are you doing? Leave.
You can't do that.
I carried you up here and helped you earn a camera.
The least you can do is thank me.
Why should I thank you?
It was my first date with Yoon Ah,
but you ruined everything.
It's the same for me too.
You're unbelievable. Seriously.
Tell me, Yoon Ah.
Tell me.
What is happening here?
They look like newlyweds.
When did they get so close?
My gosh.
Where's Dong Gu? Isn't he awake yet?
No, Dong Gu and Hyun Joon are still asleep together.
They might even become best friends.
I mean, that's impossible.
Why not? What are you talking about?
What? It's nothing.
Jun Ki, you should eat. Take a seat.
Sure.
Du Shik.
What's wrong with your face? Are you sick?
You don't look so good.
I agree. Is something wrong?
It's nothing. I'm fine.
Jun Ki, what's wrong?
Wake up!
We took a test and found out...
that his liver somatic index and blood pressure are high.
All test results are not good.
But the strange part is that we can't find what caused this.
What? What do you mean you can't find what caused this?
A person, who was perfectly healthy yesterday, can't get bad this fast.
The only reason for this can be extreme stress.
Has he been...
- in tremendous shock lately? - Well,
there's one thing I can think of.
What is it?
He really like to joke around,
but I told him not to.
He became really quiet from that moment...
and lost all his energy.
That's where he got the shock. I'm sure of it.
What?
How can someone get sick from not being able to joke around?
It's not usual,
but that would be the only reason.
Maybe to him, joking around...
could have been everything to his life.
Everything to his life?
Joking around?
Hello.
What did he say? Am I really sick?
Yes, you might die.
What?
I can't be cured?
Won't surgeries work?
Well,
you'll get better if you joke around again.
What?
What are you talking about?
You're sick because I told you not to joke around.
So you can joke around as much as you want.
Really? Can I?
If not, you might die. What else could I do?
So do as you want.
Thank you!
Thank you so much!
But there's one thing...
I've really wanted to try. Can I?
Go ahead. Go.
Yes!
Seo Jin, look!
It looks like I'm flying, right?
Open up your wings
Seo Jin, try it on the other side.
Look at me.
Try this.
You haven't eaten all day.
It's fine. I don't feel like eating.
What's wrong with you? Is something wrong?
I don't know.
I feel weak.
I don't feel like eating either.
Du Shik!
Jun Ki!
Du Shik, I'm sorry for what I did.
You must have been angry at me.
What is this? Are you back now?
- Are you back to the Jun Ki I knew? - What?
Are you sure?
Yes!
Du Shik, let's play the games we haven't been able to play...
these past few days.
Let's go!
By the way,
I upgraded our cart.
Do you want to try?
Let's go!
Upgrade!
- If it's with you... - If it's with you...
Right, I've been meaning to give you this.
(Lee Jun Ki)
(Bong Du Shik)
(Lee Jun Ki, Bong Du Shik)
Let's go.
Ready.
Go!
Did you see how they all fell down?
It's called Cart Strike.
You get the highest point with this.
If you succeed twice, it's a double strike.
If you succeed three times, it's a triple strike.
It's so organized. It's amazing.
- I want to try. - Come here.
- Here. - Thanks.
I'll prepare the pins.
Go get ready.
Thank you.
Soo Ah, why are men like this?
They don't understand why we're so crazy about shopping.
We should just give up.
Let's go.
Cart Strike!
- No matter how much I think - No matter how much I think
(Welcome to Waikiki)
I was going to do it by myself. Why did you offer to shave?
I didn't do that on purpose.
Are you done talking, jerk?
How dare you?
Let's break up. Let's break up then.
Sure, let's do that.
- Dong Gu, we were joking. - "Joking"?
- Come on in. - It's well decorated.
What is this smell?
Is that his shoes?
Is this smell coming from his shoes?
Must they film here?
2, 3.
I told you...
that I didn't want to owe you anything.
Yoon Ah, are you free this weekend?
I want to tell you something.
- What? Hyun Joon. - Why are you here?
- Can you lend me some money? - What is this about?
Yoon Ah got in an accident.
I'll get the money right away. Follow me.