What is this?
Then say, "I like you."
Dong Gu. I like you.
- Trying to be cute. - I really like you.
Be brave.
I really like you.
What is this?
I like you.
I really like you, Dong Gu.
Would you be willing to start a relationship with me?
Yoon Ah.
Really? She asked you out?
Gosh, you succeeded at last!
I'm so jealous, Dong Gu.
Congratulations. That's good news.
- Congratulations, Dong Gu. - Thanks.
But this does feel a little weird.
I'm congratulating my ex-boyfriend for dating a new girl.
Am I supposed to do this?
You're so cool.
You're like a human dry ice.
I can see breath coming out of your mouth.
She's here. Dong Gu's girl is here.
Yoon Ah, give it to me.
You're up early.
- Did you sleep well? - Yes.
What are you doing today? Do you go to baking class?
- Yes. - What are you doing afterwards?
- Are you going to the bakery? - Yes.
I see.
Sol must be awake.
What is wrong with you guys?
- Are you sure you two are dating? - Yes.
She asked me out yesterday, saying she wanted a serious relationship.
So she said that you two are dating?
We didn't need to say that out loud.
Of course.
If she didn't say it, you're not together yet.
- Am I wrong? - What?
Jun Ki is right. You're not together yet.
Really?
Yoon Ah and I are not together yet?
If you're not sure, why don't you go and ask her?
I can't ask her now.
What if it turns out later that you weren't dating?
Maybe you're right.
I should probably go and ask her.
He's really going to ask her.
Is he stupid?
Guys, everyone becomes stupid when they're in love.
But I think he really is stupid.
- Be quiet. - Why are you leaving me out?
Gosh.
Is it fun to pull his leg?
It's really fun.
I think so.
I agree.
- Stop it. - Aren't you going to laugh?
Yoon Ah, can I come in?
Yes.
Yoon Ah, can I ask you something?
Well...
Do you remember saying that you like me last night?
You sent me a video where you say you like me.
You said you wanted to go out with me.
We laughed together too.
Yes.
Let me ask you something.
Are we together?
Yes.
I knew it. We're together, right?
See? I was right.
Those brats.
- I'll leave you alone now. - Okay.
It's so funny.
Did you ask her?
What did she say?
She said we're together.
What did I say?
Really?
But her reaction was a bit off.
What are you talking about?
Think about it.
You have a crush on someone.
You ask that person out, and you're finally together.
How would you feel?
I'd be on cloud nine.
Right?
And you are right now.
Yes.
But Yoon Ah doesn't seem to be excited at all.
Don't you agree, Du Shik?
He's right.
She seems to be a bit depressed, almost in pain.
You think so?
It's been bothering me a bit too.
Could...
Yoon Ah be regretting?
Regret what?
Sometimes, you ask someone out...
but regret it the next morning.
Right, Du Shik?
Of course.
I have no such experience,
but that happens all the time in movies and novels.
That's not okay.
That's really not okay.
Then why don't you...
take her on a date?
Win some points before she changes her mind.
Otherwise, you might get dumped again.
That's not okay.
(For New Couples)
Yes.
Dong Gu and Yoon Ah are having a date.
Lunch?
Yes, I had lunch.
Did you enjoy your lunch, Bacca?
Gosh.
Has his tongue gotten shorter?
I miss you too.
See you later.
Hang up first.
You should hang up first, Bacca.
Gosh.
What are you doing?
You're being so childish.
Right, Du Shik?
I want to be childish too.
Jun Ki and Dong Gu are enjoying the spring,
but it's still winter for me. Right, Sol?
Go on a date.
You're sitting right next to another lonely person.
Who?
Sol?
This girl? Soo Ah?
Yes.
You're both lonely. Why don't you rely on each other?
Are you crazy?
How could you tell me to go out with this idiot?
Hey.
I don't want to go out with someone who...
doesn't know anything about math and Crown Prince Sado.
- Are you serious? - I take it back.
Anyway, I'll never go out with her.
- Don't say such a thing again. - Okay.
I hate the idea too.
You're being ridiculous.
Gosh, I hate how she looks from behind too.
Sol, I don't want you to grow up to be an ignorant person like her.
You should...
read newspapers and become smart.
Let's see if there's anything fun to read.
(Frustrated Breadwinners)
"Frustrated Breadwinners".
"Layoff"...
That sounds terrible, right?
Of course.
How will they face their wives and children?
This is why I'm not sure if I should get married.
Don't worry.
You won't be able to.
How can you say such a terrible thing?
What's that?
Culture centers these days have so many different classes.
"Develop Your Baby's Five Senses".
(Develop Your Baby's Five Senses)
Wait.
What's this sound?
Where is it coming from?
Is it the sound of your heart beating?
Jun Ki, I think,
I'm in love.
With whom?
This woman?
All you've seen is a picture of her. Don't be ridiculous.
I'm going to the culture center!
- What are you doing? Get up. - Me?
No. Bacca would get angry.
I'm not telling you to date her.
I'll date her. I just want you to come with me.
Let's go.
Let's go to the culture center!
Let me finally be childish!
Why is Yoon Ah so quiet?
She looks a bit down.
Does she really regret her decision to go out with me?
That would be a problem.
The weather is so nice.
Yoon Ah, what should we do?
Should we eat first?
Yes.
What should we eat?
Should we eat your favorite, sundae?
Yes.
Should we go eat now?
What is this?
Why does she only say yes?
She doesn't want to talk to me?
Gosh, I'm getting so worried.
I feel so uncomfortable.
What is this on our first date?
Gosh.
I should really change the mood.
Yoon Ah.
What should we do after eating?
As the weather is nice, why don't we go to an amusement park?
Okay.
Do you like to go on rides?
Yes.
- Honey. - Okay.
Does it taste good?
- Yoon Ah. - Yes?
Open your mouth. Let me feed you.
I'm okay.
I want to.
Open your mouth.
I'm really okay. I can eat by myself.
Come on. I really want to feed you.
No. I'm okay.
Don't be like that.
I'm really okay.
Yoon Ah, are you okay?
My eyes.
I think I have salt in my eyes.
I have to use the bathroom.
Yoon Ah, I'm sorry.
Yoon Ah.
My goodness.
Du Shik, don't you have a feeling that...
they're getting the wrong idea about us?
What do you mean?
You have something on your lips.
What are you doing?
They already have the wrong idea. Are you out of your mind?
Get away from me. Get away.
What?
Hello. Hello.
Hello.
Are you alone with your baby?
Yes.
I thought we were the only men here.
What a pleasant surprise.
The thing is, I run a business.
I'm usually too busy...
to spend any time with my baby.
So I set some time aside for this class.
- That's great. - I see.
Is the instructor married?
Well, I don't think she is.
I see.
That's great.
- Good afternoon. - Good afternoon.
We have some fathers here today.
Nice to see you all.
Are you angry?
Why are you all so quiet?
Please applaud them.
Today, we'll learn...
a massage that's good for pooping.
Please put the mats and oil baskets back to where you found them.
Get up.
Are you Sol's uncles?
How was the one-day trial?
If you're pleased,
- would you like to register today? - I'd like to refuse.
Please reconsider it.
Consistent massage helps with body development.
No thank you.
- Jun Ki. - Yes?
Come on. Let's go home.
Okay.
(Soorgio Armhany)
Where did you go?
We've witnessed a side effect of Korean ITC technology.
- You made us tired over nothing. - I'm sorry.
Are you digesting better after a massage?
Her pooping sound is louder than before.
You're right. I'll bring a diaper.
Let's change your diaper.
Is this the same diaper?
What?
- Du Shik. - Yes?
Did the instructor say that the massage creates a thing,
that wasn't there before?
- Why? Did Sol get something new? - Yes.
- What? - A penis.
What? This isn't Sol.
It isn't her.
I thought something was strange about him.
What do you mean that she isn't Sol?
Where did she go?
Where did Sol go?
Du Shik.
- We must have switched babies. - What?
Why didn't you check the baby?
You hurried me, so I didn't have time.
Be quiet. It's not time to fight.
Go and get Sol now.
Okay.
- Sol. - Sol.
Goodness.
I'm sorry, Yoon Ah.
Is your eye okay?
Yes.
- Can you get on the rides? - Yes.
What should I do?
She looks unhappier than before.
I have to change the mood.
I must make up for my mistake.
That's it.
It has the right amount of thrill and physical contact.
It's the best ride to lift up the mood and show my masculinity.
Yoon Ah, shall we go on the Viking ride?
Pardon? Okay.
Let's go.
Viking ride starts now.
The security bar is going down.
I haven't ridden it in a long time.
Yoon Ah, hold tightly.
Okay.
If it's too scary,
you can lean on me, okay?
Okay.
Let's go.
Let's go to the unknown world.
- Aren't you scared? - No.
Was the Viking ride always this scary?
What's going on?
Why is it going up so high?
It's too high.
It's too scary. Stop.
Stop, stop.
Stop!
Sir, please stop it.
Please let me off.
Sir, sir.
Let me get off.
Calm down, Dong Gu.
- Let me get off now. - It's okay. It'll stop soon.
The security bar is going up.
Dong Gu, it's okay now. Get up.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
It really stopped.
I almost died.
Yoon Ah, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Goodness.
What should I do?
Dong Gu.
It's hard enough to earn money.
Do I have to make side dishes...
and prepare for the ancestral ceremony?
What have I done?
- Hello? - Hello?
Are you Hee Dong's father?
I'm Sol's uncle. We met at the cultural center.
Yes, what's going on?
I think the babies were switched.
We have Hee Dong.
I think you have Sol.
What? That's nonsense.
What's wrong? What happened?
It's nothing.
Meet me at the 2nd floor restroom in 1 minute.
Why isn't he here yet?
Du Shik, I don't know about us.
How could a father not realize that his baby was switched?
Is he really a dad? He isn't qualified to be a dad.
- Hee Dong. - Hee Dong.
- Sir, where's Sol? - Yes?
Let me explain first.
What do you mean? Where is she?
I'm sorry, but may I ask you a favor?
What favor?
Actually, I'm unemployed.
I've been staying home for two years, since I got laid off.
With money that my wife earns,
I'm living a miserable life.
- So what? - My wife looks down on me...
for not being competent.
She'll divorce me if she finds out that our babies were switched.
What do you want us to do?
Can we switch the babies without letting my wife know?
What? Are you kidding me?
Be quiet and bring Sol to us now.
It was too much to ask. I understand.
I'll just let her divorce me.
Let's go.
Wait, I understand.
What should we do?
I have a good plan.
Look at cacao nibs over there.
I like cacao nibs.
Goodness.
It's "buy one, get one free".
The price is quite low.
Goodness, Sol.
These aren't cheap.
How long do we have to do this?
What else can we do if she divorces him?
I feel bad for him.
Why did you suggest going to the class in the first place?
You're the one who switched babies.
Are you blaming me now?
- Gosh. - Gosh.
Where is that man? What is he doing?
You startled me.
Sir, what are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid that my wife will find out.
- Can you sit down for a moment? - Huh?
- Can you keep on the lookout? - What?
Stop looking in this direction.
Until when will you do this?
I'm sorry. Consider it that you're saving me.
Please help me a little more.
I want to help you,
but your wife won't give us a chance.
Speaking of which,
I have a plan that will work.
What is it this time?
Here's the plan.
The only place where we can secretly exchange...
Hee Dong and Sol is at the cashier.
It's the place where she'll take her eyes off of the baby carriage.
Once everything is scanned, the cashier will say this.
The total is 158 dollars.
Would you like to pay in cash or credit card?
I'll pay with a credit card.
Then she'll take her hands off of the baby carriage...
and take out her wallet.
We have five seconds, until she takes out her card.
- Do you have a membership card? - Let me enter my number.
It takes five seconds to enter her number.
The cashier will swipe the card.
It takes five seconds for the receipt to be printed.
It's a total of 15 seconds.
These 15 seconds will be our last chance...
to swap Hee Dong and Sol.
The signal to make our move will be...
"Will you be paying with cash or with a credit card?"
That'll be the signal. Keep that in mind.
That'll be 158 dollars.
Will you be paying with cash or with a credit card?
- I'll pay with a credit card. - Yes, ma'am.
Sol. Be quiet.
Wait. What are you doing?
Well, you see...
Why are you carrying my baby?
Pardon?
Well, you see...
Mister.
Wait. Do you know this person, honey?
No. I've never seen this person before.
What? Hey, Mister.
What are you talking about?
Who are you?
Who are you? How dare you touch our Hee Dong?
Mister. What are you doing?
How dare you touch our Hee Dong?
My wife met a useless husband like me.
Hye Sook's working her socks off to make a living.
She hasn't even been able to travel abroad like others.
I've never bought her a nice piece of clothes.
Hye Sook's my kind-hearted wife...
and Hee Dong's the fruition of our love.
How dare you try to hurt them.
If you're going to hurt my family,
I'd rather have you kill me, you scum.
- What? - Why would I kill anyone?
You were the one that told us about the 15 seconds.
Shut your mouth. Shut your mouth, you scum.
Whatever your name is,
please just act like you don't know me.
I beg you.
Whatever your name is,
but you've gone too far.
Please help this useless breadwinner.
All right. You caught me.
I can't imagine a more amazing husband than you.
Ma'am.
You should be grateful that you have an amazing husband like him.
I'll be going then.
Leave.
Get lost and never come back again, you scums!
- Honey. - Yes?
I never knew that you thought of me that much.
Honey.
Thank you, whatever your name is.
Don't mention it.
The breadwinners of Korea, cheer up.
Yoon Ah. I'm sorry.
I felt so nauseous, and I couldn't help it.
You're not upset, are you?
No.
You're not angry, are you?
She's angry. She's angry.
She has that grim look on her face.
I smacked her eye with a sundae and threw up on her skirt.
Who wouldn't get upset?
I'm ruined. She's regretting it for sure.
Yoon Ah.
Aren't you thirsty? Do you want me to get some soda for you?
Yes.
Wait just a minute.
It's over. It's all over.
She has a grim look on her face and only says, "Yes."
I'm sure she's regretting that she agreed to start dating me.
I'm ruined.
(Seo Jin)
Yes, Seo Jin. We're on our way home.
Is Sol doing all right?
Of course.
Sol was fine all day.
How about you? Did you enjoy your date?
Actually, since I was with Dong Gu on my own,
I was so nervous that I didn't know what to say.
My mind was blank all day.
All I could say to him was, "Yes."
What if he's upset with me?
I'm worried to death.
Anyhow, I'm so flustered right now.
Let's talk when I get home.
Yes. All right.
Dong Gu.
So that's the reason.
I didn't know.
Pardon?
Dong Gu.
Are you crying?
You see, since you...
didn't talk so much and had a grim look on your face,
I was worried that you might be regretting to date me.
That was all I could think of all day. I was so worried.
I was worried we might break up.
Why would I break up with you?
Just standing next to you...
makes my heart flutter.
Really?
If that's how you felt, you should've just told me.
You had me worried to death.
Then you're not...
regretting that you agreed to start dating me, right?
- No. - Then that means...
- today's our first date, right? - Yes.
Then since we're officially a couple now,
can I hold your hand?
Yoon Ah. Then how about...
we go on a proper date again tomorrow?
All right.
Is that all you can say though?
Yes.
Never mind. All right.
Let's just go. Let's go.
Listen up. You know we're expecting a lot of guests today, right?
Every nook and cranny of this house needs to be clean. Do you get it?
- Yes, sir. - All right.
Good.
Yoon Ah. Give it to me.
I'll take care of it.
You don't have to.
Thank you, Dong Gu.
You don't have to thank me.
You go on in with Sol and get some rest.
I'm all right.
That's enough, Seo Jin. You should go and get some rest too.
You worked overtime last night. You shouldn't have to do this.
Thank you.
I can always rely on you.
I think that's enough.
How could a single like me bear to live here?
If you're jealous, you should start dating someone.
You're just upset because you're jealous.
Wait and see.
I'll make sure I meet a girl...
much better than Yoon Ah or Seo Jin.
Is that right?
But you see, Yoon Ah is...
pretty, nice, and genuine. She's like morning dew.
I wonder if a girl like her even exists.
I agree.
My Bacca is so cute and adorable.
Her beard is cooler than Park Chan Ho.
No such girl can possible exist.
That's enough.
What did you just do, you jerk?
Stop it. You guys are acting childish.
By the way, where's Soo Ah?
I don't know. I think she's in her room.
What?
What is she doing in her room when we're all out here cleaning?
What are you doing?
I wasn't doing anything.
You couldn't have been doing a cucumber pack, right?
I wasn't.
I sliced them up so we can make side dished with them.
Why were you putting them on your face then?
You mean these?
I was just salting them.
You see, my face is quite salty.
Are you kidding me?
Stop now and just come down to lend a hand for the cleanup.
I'm shooting today for my online shopping mall.
I need my skin care before the shooting.
That's your problem.
You're living in my house but never listen to me.
Living in your house?
I'm here as a guest.
Gosh, a guest?
What's wrong? Stop fighting.
Why do you always fight?
She's mean all the time.
What? Mean?
How dare you say that to your sister?
Kang Seo Jin, is that all you have to say?
Yes.
You need to act like an older person for me to treat you like one.
- How dare you? - Stop.
- What? - What?
Gosh, I thought I was going to die.
I don't even have the strength to stand up.
Well done guys.
Welcome.
Who are you?
I reserved a room today.
What?
What language is that?
Maybe she reserved a room.
- Are you Angela? - Yes, I'm Angela.
- Angela. - But...
what language was she speaking in?
She's from Ukraine.
Can't she speak English?
Can you speak English?
No, I can only speak Ukrainian.
What's she saying?
- I don't think she speaks English. - What?
That's a shame.
I'll show you to your room.
Follow me.
Wait.
She's so pretty.
I thought she was a doll.
Right, Du Shik?
What's this?
What's this sound?
Is this the sound of your heart beating again?
Jun Ki, I think...
I'm in love.
What? Again?
You fall in love with everyone.
It's real this time.
I've never felt such a strong pull.
Wake up, Du Shik.
She's out of your league.
Don't do something rash.
You'll only get hurt.
Hey, wake up. Hey.
He's out of his mind. Hey!
Angela.
(Can Love be Translated?)
Angela, do you want to drink this?
Drinking?
Thank you.
What is she saying?
Do you like the room? Do you need anything?
I'm sorry, but I don't speak English. I don't understand.
Gosh, I can't understand anything.
Let's use the translator.
Angela, I fell in love at first sight.
Angela, would you like to split the first snow in half?
What? What did you say?
What?
What's this? I don't think she got it.
There must have been a mistake.
(Korean to Ukrainian Translator)
Angela, do you happen to have...
a boyfriend?
Angela, does your friend have your ovum?
What? What do you mean?
I'm sorry, but I need to go out now.
- Angela. Angela? - Bye.
Angela.
Gosh, what's this?
The translator isn't working.
What should I do?
Clean them properly.
I will. I'm doing my best.
Why are you shouting at me?
It's my senior.
Yes, ma'am.
"Yes, ma'am."
It's me. How's your vacation?
Yes.
I'm resting well.
Really? That's good.
In that case, I'll send you some documents through your email.
Can you send me a summary of that by tomorrow at 8am?
It's my graduate school assignment.
- Do you understand? - Me?
Why? You don't want to do it?
No, I will.
All right.
Gosh.
What's wrong?
She's making me do her graduate school assignment.
What? Why is she doing that?
I don't know.
But I can't say no to my superior.
Gosh, she never lost against me.
Now she can't say anything to her superior.
Shut it.
Go finish the dishes.
Gosh, it's my precious day off.
Serves you right. Gosh.
- What are you doing? - I'm learning Ukrainian. Why?
I don't understand a thing.
- That won't solve anything. - Then what should I do?
This is the least I can do to talk to Angela.
Don't worry.
We found a way for you two to communicate.
Really? How?
- Come on. Come on. - Come on. Come on.
- Yes! - Yes, come on.
Who are these people?
Aren't they our guests?
Listen to me first.
The problem here is that you can't communicate with Angela.
Why? The only language Angela speaks is Ukrainian.
- Right. - That's true.
It's going to get complicated.
So concentrate and listen well.
All right.
First, Mark from Germany can speak Ukrainian.
Bruno from France can speak German.
Hanako from Japan can...
speak French, as well as Korean.
- Do you understand? - No, not at all.
So what does this have to do with Angela?
Gosh.
So if Angela talks to Mark...
in Ukrainian,
Mark will translate it to Bruno in German.
Bruno will translate it to Hanako in French.
Then Hanako will translate it into Korean for you.
Do you understand?
So you want me to talk to her through three translators?
That's right.
You'll understand her.
Why? You don't like it?
- Okay. - No.
Thanks, Jun Ki.
What are you doing? Go and ask her out.
Hey, follow me. Follow me!
- Follow me! - Go! Go!
- Go! Go! - Go! Go!
Jerk. He's so happy.
But will Angela accept him...
even if they understand each other?
No, of course not.
We're just helping him out.
He can at least try.
He's obviously going to be rejected miserably.
Shall we follow him and comfort him when that happens?
Shall we?
He's probably going to cry again. Shall we take some tissues?
- Should I get two boxes? - Shall we go now?
What are you doing? Ask her out.
All right.
I...
I fell in love at first sight.
Really? Since when?
What do you like about me?
Hey, Hanako.
He didn't mean you.
You need to deliver this to Angela.
Gosh, all right.
Angela, I fell in love at first sight.
(Ukrainian)
Really?
Hey, no, Angela.
Not him. Him.
He likes you.
Ask her what she thinks of me.
All right.
What do you think of me?
I like him. He looked nice when I first saw him yesterday.
It's good news. She likes you.
Really? Really?
Can you ask her if she wants to go out with me?
- All right. - Go on.
Sure.
She wants to.
- What? - Really?
Are you sure, Angela?
- Yes. - Thank you. Thank you.
Jun Ki, Dong Gu, thank you so much.
It's all thanks to you.
Thank you so much.
It's great.
I did nothing.
Gosh.
Why do I have to work overnight on my day off?
Gosh, if she wasn't my superior, I would...
No, I need to suppress this anger.
I might get in trouble at work.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
I should probably eat something.
Can I use your hairdryer?
My phone.
Gosh. What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I didn't bump into you on purpose.
You're so careless.
I said, I'm sorry.
Just take it out.
I can't see anything. Shine some light.
I am doing it right now.
Move it a bit to this side.
- Fine. - There it is.
I got it.
Wait. What is this?
What is this? What's going on?
Gosh.
Your brush is tangled in my hair.
What are you going to do now?
It's because you kept rubbing your head against mine.
Gosh. Stay still.
It's not working.
- It hurts. - It hurts.
It hurts.
I don't think I can do it.
I can't seem to untangle your hair.
Really?
It's driving me crazy. What should we do?
Could a hairdresser help?
- A hairdresser? - A hairdresser?
Cheers.
Here.
By the way,
Angela seems to have surprisingly low standards for men.
- Right? - Yes.
They look so weird together.
Exactly.
It's like, "Beauty and the Beast".
Or more like, "Beauty and the Dwarf".
Why? I think they look adorable together.
Are you jealous that...
Du Shik has a beautiful girlfriend?
No way.
I have a beautiful girlfriend like you.
Why would I be jealous?
I am. I am very jealous.
I'm so upset.
How could Du Shik date a girl like Angela?
No way. I'm not jealous either.
I have a cute girlfriend like Seo Jin.
It hurts.
I'm so jealous that it hurts.
It feels like I have a huge weight on my chest.
I can't contain my anger.
It's not going to work.
It's tangled so badly I can't do anything about it.
I'll have to cut your hair off.
What? You're going to cut our hair off?
No. It'd ruin my style.
Are you going to stay like this forever?
I'll have to cut off at least one person's hair...
to get the brush out.
We have no choice. Your hair will have to be cut off.
What? Hey.
I'm a model for my shopping mall.
I can't have my hair cut off.
Are you saying my hair should be cut off?
Then this will be all that's left of my bangs.
How will I go to work?
Whatever. I'll never have my hair cut off.
I'd rather die that have my hair cut off.
You're responsible for this. Your hair should be cut off.
Why am I responsible? Your hair should be cut off.
Gosh, I can't believe you.
What is it now?
It's work.
Hello.
I received your summary.
By the way, can you come to my place right now?
Sorry? Right now?
I'm in the middle of something right now.
No matter what you're doing, come here within 30 minutes.
Hello? Hello?
Gosh, she's driving me crazy.
- What is it? - I don't know.
She wants me to come to her place right now.
Tell the hairdresser to cut off your hair now.
Why? You're the one in a hurry.
I have no reason to hurry.
All right.
Are you sure?
Hey!
It hurts. Hold on!
Where are our board games?
Angela wants to play. Do you want to join?
I'm fine.
- I'm fine too. - All right.
Du Shik.
- Will you be all right? - What?
- What are you talking about? - I'm talking about Angela.
Do you really know her well?
- What is this all about? - I mean,
Angela is so beautiful.
I just can't imagine her not having a boyfriend.
Think about it.
She's so beautiful.
Would guys leave her alone?
He's right. It's impossible.
Are you saying she might be two-timing me?
Well, that's not exactly what I mean.
But when you're on a trip, it's easy to...
cheat on your boyfriend or girlfriend.
That's right.
Doesn't that happen all the time?
Should I ask her if she has a boyfriend?
Well... Maybe.
Well, I was just worried about Du Shik.
Same here. I don't want him to get hurt.
Angela, I'm sorry to ask you this,
but do you happen to have a boyfriend in Ukraine?
That's what I want to ask her.
Okay.
She doesn't. You're her first boyfriend.
She's both beautiful and innocent.
I really hate her.
- Really? I'm your first boyfriend? - Yes.
That's such a relief.
What?
She doesn't have another boyfriend,
and you're her first boyfriend?
Yes.
I'm her first love.
Really? That's great.
Yes.
That's awesome.
Du Shik, you're so lucky. Congratulations.
Thank you.
Du Shik.
Do you have to look at me like that?
It somehow bothers me.
Really? I'm sorry. I'll be careful.
Be quiet!
Can you be more careful when you walk?
Your footsteps are so loud.
- It gets on my nerves. - Really?
Sorry. I'll be careful.
We're here. Let's get off.
Hey. Get off from this side.
You can't open that door from inside.
Come here.
I can't believe you.
Be careful.
What are you doing right now?
Are you joking with me?
No way.
Something happened.
Cut it out. Here's an outfit I bought.
Exchange it for a bigger size at the department store.
- Sorry? - I have an important appointment...
later today.
But I had too much tripe and soju last night,
and the outfit doesn't fit me anymore.
I've already called the store, so you can just go and exchange it.
Okay.
What are you doing? Hurry up. You don't have much time.
What's wrong with her?
Why would she tell her to exchange her clothes?
Whatever. Come with me.
Hey. Tell me before you move. It hurts.
I'm Angela's first love. It's unbelievable.
Right?
Yes.
I'm so happy for you, Du Shik.
By the way,
will you be all right?
- What is it now? - You're an international couple.
It won't be easy to maintain the relationship.
He's right.
She'll get tired.
If someone comforts her, she might leave you for him.
That's the way it is.
Isn't that what always happens?
You think so?
I probably should ask her.
I can't believe that Angela is an exchange student.
If she decides to stay in Korea,
we might even get married.
Right.
- That sounds great. - I know.
It's unbelievable.
Du Shik.
Would your parents be okay?
- My parents? - Yes.
You'll be an international couple.
Due to Confucianism, Koreans are biased against international dating.
What about your parents?
Will they allow you dating Angela?
He's right.
Everyone I know is against it.
That's what most people think.
You're right. I haven't thought about it.
I've never seen my parents so happy.
I had no idea that they would already call her a daughter-in-law.
Right. That sounds nice.
- Congratulations. - Congratulations, Du Shik.
Thank you.
Can you do something about your gum when you laugh?
It's very disagreeable.
Really?
I'm sorry. I'll be careful.
By the way, Du Shik.
Do something about your nostrils when you laugh.
Your nostrils almost smirk at me. It's annoying.
Really? I'm sorry. I'll be careful.
I was supposed to drink beer with Angela.
I'm going upstairs.
What are those fingers?
- My stomach hurts. - My stomach hurts.
Here you go.
Why did you come so late?
You couldn't handle a simple task like this.
I'm sorry.
Forget it. Leave now.
Goodness.
Who does she think she is?
You did a chore for her, but she didn't even thank you.
It's okay. Let's go.
You always talk back to me,
but why are you so careful around her?
You're not like yourself.
What else can I do? She's a senior at work.
I punched her thousands of times in my head.
Really?
Would you punch her if it were possible?
Yes, so?
What are you thinking?
Don't do it. It'll cause trouble at work.
Don't worry. She'll never find out.
Where's a convenience store nearby?
What for?
There she is.
Honey, I'm leaving now.
Okay, see you soon.
What's this?
What? What's going on?
What's wrong with this?
That hurts.
Why can't I take my hand off?
Hey! Who did this?
Do you think it'll come off easily?
That's super glue.
Is it okay to do this?
Of course. An eye for a tooth.
You mean an eye for an eye, not an eye for a tooth.
You're so ignorant.
Does it matter now?
What matters now is how do we discipline her.
Let's go.
I'll get in trouble if I get caught.
You won't get caught.
Lower your head a little. She won't see you.
- Still... - I worked hard to make the glue.
I bought 20l of water to make it. Step on it.
I don't know anymore.
Let's go.
Lower your head a little. She won't see you.
- Still... - I worked hard to make the glue.
I bought 20l of water to make it. Step on it.
I don't know anymore.
Let's go.
Lower your head.
Hey, who are you?
Hey, you!
That serves her right.
- She should treat people well. - Right.
It serves her right.
It feels great.
Right? Doesn't it feel satisfying?
Yes, thank you.
If you're thankful, may I get a milk facial?
No, never.
Aren't you grateful that I took a revenge on her?
I'll pay you back for it.
I can't live being indebted.
How will you pay back for it?
Why do you have that look on your face?
Is something wrong?
I don't know.
I feel low on energy.
Right.
I feel depressed and have no appetite.
I feel like I'm sagging.
I wonder why.
- We're home. - We're home.
Hello.
Where have you been all day...
What's wrong with your hair, Seo Jin?
What? I don't have energy for this.
Listen.
Where have you been, darling?
Do you want something to eat?
Stop it.
What happened to your hair?
What happened to your bangs?
Something happened.
Anyway, I don't owe you anything now.
I got it.
You don't ever lose, do you?
- All right. - What's that?
It sounds like Du Shik.
Why is he so excited?
Du Shik and Angela decided to go out from today.
- Things are going well for them. - Really?
I'm happy for Du Shik.
I can't seem to digest well.
Gosh, my stomach.
My stomach hurts all of a sudden.
My stomach.
What's wrong with them?
Cheers. Let's drink.
Bottoms up.
I'm tired.
Let's stop drinking and go to sleep.
Let's drink a little more. Isn't it fun?
Darn it. You lied.
"Darn it'? "You lied"?
Where did you learn Korean, Hanako?
You only learned bad words.
I have to pee.
I'm going to the restroom.
Tell it to Angela.
Pee or poop?
Do I have to say it?
Then she'll know how long she has to wait.
Gosh, fine.
I'm going to pee, okay?
Okay.
He's going to poop.
(French to German)
(German to Ukrainian)
(Ukrainian)
Does he have to say that?
It's so hard to pee.
Angela, wait a little.
I'll be back.
Have fun and drink.
What's wrong, Angela?
Du Shik and I can't communicate.
It's uncomfortable.
Isn't it hard for you to translate?
No, I was happy to be with you.
As I talk to you, I find that you're a good person.
Really?
Actually, I like you too.
What if I end up marrying Angela?
Wait, we'll have an Ukrainian wedding...
and a Korean traditional wedding.
Do we have to get married twice?
What about the guests?
Do we have to rent a plane?
I don't know. What do I do?
My Angela.
Goodness.
What's wrong?
I might have insomnia.
I couldn't sleep at all last night.
I must be stressed out about shoots.
I have serious insomnia.
Is that so?
That sounds terrible.
That's strange. Where did she go?
What's wrong?
Are you looking for someone?
When I woke up in the morning, Angela was gone.
Her luggage is gone too.
Hanako, have you seen Angela?
Angela?
She left with her suitcase early in the morning.
What?
What do you mean that she left?
Angela and Marco were together...
until early morning.
- It felt strange between the two. - What?
Both of them disappeared in the morning.
What are you talking about?
Hey. Wait.
Then does this mean Angela and Marco...
had a secret affair and ran away?
- What? - Oh, dear.
They fell in love. They did, indeed.
They speak the same language and he's good-looking.
Anyone would fall in love in that situation.
This can't be true. This can't be true.
Angela. Angela.
Oh, dear.
I feel so bad for Du Shik.
I was hoping this relationship would work out this time.
Me too.
I prayed all night for him, so he could finally start dating...
for the first time in his life.
I feel so bad for Du Shik.
What's going on?
How could they fall asleep so quickly when they have insomnia?
They're even smiling in their sleep.
They must be dreaming a happy dream.
(Welcome to Waikiki)
A fan? Do I have a fan now?
He can't stop smiling around her.
I can't even remember when we last went on a date.
Do you want to go see a movie?
Really? You promised.
I wonder why I haven't heard from Jun Ki.
- Jun Ki. - What are you doing here?
I switched them all with photos of me.
Why can't you stop teasing Du Shik?
Nothing's more fun than teasing Du Shik.
Du Shik. Have you fallen for Ah Young?
If you like her, why don't you ask her out on a date?
I'm planning on asking Ah Young to go out with me.
How could you do this to me?
You two seem be like newlyweds.
Dong Gu. How far have you gone?
I assume you two have kissed, right?
Affection isn't the yardstick for love.
Erase that dirty idea from your head.
I want to kiss her. I want to kiss her. I want to kiss her.
Dong Gu. Dong Gu. Can't you hear me?
Actually, I have something I want to say to you.
- Excuse me? - Yoon Ah.
I'm asking you if I can kiss you now.