When did it start?
Does that mean you've been lying to me all along?
We weren't lying on purpose.
We just couldn't tell you the truth since we knew you'd be angry.
If you had known, you shouldn't have started in the first place.
Dong Gu, we really like each other.
- It's true. So... - Be quiet!
I won't accept it. That's final.
Why not?
What's your reason?
There are some things that can't be. Just stop here.
No.
Who are you to stop us?
I'm an adult now.
I'm not a young girl who needs your approval to date someone.
She's right, Dong Gu. I won't give her up.
So you two still want to date?
All right.
Seo Jin, you're not my sister from now on.
And Jun Ki, you don't exist to me.
Do you understand?
Why do you need to be so harsh on them?
- They like each other. - Are you on their side?
Then you don't mean anything to me too.
Why are you being so childish?
I'm childish. So what?
So whose side are you on? Are you on their side?
Yoon Ah, are you on their side too?
What? I...
You must be since you can't answer me right away.
All right. None of you exist to me from now on.
Don't talk to me or even act like you know me.
Do you understand?
(Their Wretched Love)
It's been so long since I watched this movie.
That scene is so romantic.
It is. When will I get to fall in such a romantic love?
What are you cleaning?
It's the shoes that Mal Geum sent me.
You're so in love.
- Do you like them that much? - Yes.
I like them so much that I can't even wear them.
Gosh.
Soon, you'll start breathing moths.
When did you two start going out together?
It's been a while.
I'm sorry we haven't been able to tell you guys.
It's okay. We all know what Dong Gu is like.
I would have kept it from him too. I understand you.
Thank you, Du Shik. You're the best.
Hi, Trash of Mullae-dong.
I said I can't play today.
Count me out today.
I'm sorry.
Trash of Mullae-dong?
He's a member of my gaming guild.
We're supposed to play together today.
He's been begging me to join all day.
What? They can't play without you?
Are you that important?
Hey, you have no idea.
Jun Ki might be a nobody in real life,
but in the gaming world, he is the king.
People are willing to pay a fortune for his character.
Really? Why don't you sell it then?
What are you talking about?
I wouldn't sell my character for a million dollars.
- What? - When I die,
people will have to put it in a USB stick and bury it with me.
- Of course. - My goodness.
I don't understand you.
Yoon Ah, how is Dong Gu?
He doesn't want to eat.
His blanket is pulled over his head, and he won't come out.
He's being ridiculous again.
I can't believe him.
Where are you going? What are you going to do?
Dong Gu, I need to talk to you.
Oh, my blanket just moved by itself.
Is it a ghost?
Are you serious?
Oh my. It moved again.
I can't believe it.
Are you really going to do this?
I have an idea too.
What are you going to do?
Listen.
Until you approve of...
our relationship,
I won't shave, okay?
What?
You don't like it, do you? It's driving you crazy, right?
Fine. Let's see who wins.
Hey, Seo Jin.
Hey.
How dare she threaten me, saying she won't shave?
Seo Jin.
What is this all about? Why would you stop shaving?
An eye for an eye.
I'll protest against Dong Gu.
I'm all for that, but why would you stop shaving?
Dong Gu hates it when I don't shave.
It is the strongest, visual weapon...
I have against him.
But you have to go to work.
I can take a vacation.
I'll make him give in.
You can count on me.
Seo Jin.
Why would she take a vacation to grow a mustache?
Why?
Am I the only one who thinks it's weird?
She's Seo Jin. Dong Gu's sister.
They're the same blood.
Why don't you just break up with her?
Be quiet!
Why?
How can they be so weird?
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
Philip? His name is Philip?
He's an expensive model.
Do we really need him?
Hey. He is...
known as Park Bo Gum of the shopping mall model world.
Everything he puts on gets sold out.
Park Bo Gum?
He can't be that handsome.
Philip, we're over here.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've been shooting from early morning. I apologize.
It's okay. We shouldn't have come so early.
Hi.
I'm the CEO of Soorgio Armhany, Min Soo Ah.
Try this coffee. It smells wonderful.
All right.
But I have bad rhinitis.
I can't smell well.
I see.
Rhinitis, you bad boy!
You're very funny.
By the way... Well...
You have chili powder stuck in your teeth.
What?
Look.
Did you have to say that to my face?
Did you really have to embarrass me like that?
- Well... - What?
- I just... - Cut it out.
I...
can't shoot today because I feel too offended.
Wait.
I'm sorry we offended you. My boss is a bit insensitive.
Apologize to him right now.
I'm sorry.
Please stop being angry. It'll never happen again.
I'll...
let it slide...
for Director Bong's sake.
Thank you.
Come on in. This is our guesthouse.
We'll shoot here.
I see.
It's very cute. I like the interior design.
I'm glad to hear that.
- Please go upstairs. - Okay.
What's this smell? Did you fart?
Hold on. Is something rotting here?
I don't know. Where is it coming from?
What?
I think it's coming from there.
Hold on. Aren't they Philip's shoes?
Are you saying this stink comes from his feet?
I think so.
He looks fine.
I can't believe his feet stink so badly.
Does he even know how bad his feet smell?
He said he can't smell well because of his rhinitis.
Rhinitis can't explain this. Does he have no nose at all?
Du Shik, do we really need to shoot with him?
Of course.
We're supposed to upload pictures of our new products today.
Anyway, pretend everything is okay in front of him, okay?
The smell is just too bad.
- I can't stand it. - Didn't you see?
He got so upset when you pointed out the chili powder in his teeth.
If you complain about his smelly feet, there will be no shooting.
Just put up with it, okay?
Okay.
2, 3.
Why would she grow a mustache?
Why is she so stubborn?
Are we having cheonggukjang for lunch?
I can't wait.
Dong Gu, are we having cheonggukjang for lunch?
I don't...
Dong Gu, can we talk?
Dong Gu. Gosh, that...
Wait. It's not cheonggukjang.
What is this smell?
Did you think you could talk to me that casually?
I won't talk to you until you two break up.
I'll prove...
my determination.
There's no toilet paper.
Jun Ki...
Right. I'm not talking to him.
That was a mistake.
I almost talked to him.
What should I do?
I have no socks or towels here.
Dong Gu, can we...
Where did your t-shirt go?
You were wearing one a moment ago.
What?
Dong Gu. Hey.
That's strange.
I'm sure he was wearing one.
Gosh, it smells so bad. Hey.
The whole house stinks now.
Stop it. What if he notices?
Here he comes. Smile.
I'm sorry you had to wait for so long.
Should we start?
Where should I be standing?
Well... Let me see.
Maybe over there.
- Over there? - Yes.
Let me see...
What about this?
Yes. That looks good.
Your jeans are not rolled up.
Are they supposed to be rolled up? How high?
Let us help you.
What are you doing? Go help him.
- Me? - Of course. You're the stylist.
Do we have to roll them up?
Can't you just shoot?
Those jeans need to be rolled up.
Go help him. We don't have time.
Fine.
- Thank you. - She'll help you.
Roll it up a little more. Do it on the other side.
Thank you.
That's good.
That pose looks good.
Don't move the feet.
I should move them to look active.
No, your feet are fine.
The rolled-up part is the key-point, right?
Don't move.
That looks great.
The foot isn't in the frame. Don't move it.
What are they doing upstairs? Why does it smell?
Blocking my nostrils doesn't help.
Sol, can you believe that Jun Ki and Seo Jin are dating?
This isn't right, is it?
What do you think?
You don't agree, right?
That's why I'm so angry.
I'm furious. Those punks.
What?
My goodness.
Wait.
Gosh.
Goodness, these balls...
I should go out.
What? What's going on?
- Goodness. - What's this smell?
What kind of smell is this?
Hey, what are you doing?
Are you stuck?
Do you need help?
You're so stubborn.
Then stay like this.
You startled me.
Seo... Seo Jin.
Dong Gu.
You still won't accept it?
Is that so?
You won't accept it, will you?
Fine, let's see who wins.
Let's go until the end.
Seo Jin, Seo Jin.
What's wrong with her?
Dong Gu, until when will you stay like this?
Are you that against the idea that we're dating?
Fine, do whatever you want.
I'll treat you like a stranger, okay?
Darn it.
Do whatever you want.
That won't make me accept it.
Why can't I get out?
Goodness, I have to go to the office.
This is embarrassing.
Hello, Director.
I'll be there after the meeting with the actors.
How can I meet the actors while looking like this?
Excuse me, sir.
What? Goodness.
Who... Who are you?
I know that we just met,
but could you cut this for me?
The screenplay was written with you in mind.
Is that so?
Then I have to accept the offer, director.
- Oh no. - It's okay.
Director, we have no choice but to cast Seo Jin Woo.
Including Gong Yoo, Hyun Bin, and Won Bin,
no actors will take it.
What are you talking about?
His acting isn't good.
He isn't very handsome. I heard he has a bad personality.
- Stop it. - What do you mean, no?
I heard that he's bossy when he isn't a star.
Goodness.
Mr. Seo Jin Woo.
Jin Woo, listen.
It's okay.
The bossy actor who isn't a star will leave now.
- Good luck. - Wait, Jin Woo.
- It's just a rumor. - Jin Woo, wait.
- It's only a rumor. - Let me explain.
Are you out of your mind?
- I'm sorry. I didn't know. - Be quiet.
- Bring Jin Woo back here. - Pardon?
Don't think about coming back without him.
Why don't you just quit? Just quit.
That looks good.
Great.
That's good. One more.
That's great. Shall we take a break?
Already? Okay.
- I'll take a break. - Enjoy.
Take a break downstairs.
Du Shik, I can't do it anymore. I'll suffocate.
You're not the only one. My nose is getting sore.
- Just endure it. - I can't take it anymore.
Shall we open the windows?
What if he finds out about it?
Just don't do anything.
Shall we make him wash his feet?
Wash his feet?
How?
I brought you a drink.
Thank you.
- My goodness. - Gosh, I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
Your socks are wet. It must feel sticky.
You should wash your feet.
I don't have much time until my next appointment.
Let's continue the shoot. Let's go.
Gosh, but still...
Your feet will be sticky.
It won't be comfortable.
Is that so?
All right.
I'll take off my socks.
We don't have much left.
Let's work hard until the end.
Let's put our energy together.
Yes, we can do it.
We can do it. We can...
Let's go.
Why did you do such an unnecessary thing?
- The smell is worse. - I didn't know this would happen.
I'm about to lose my...
Why was Seo Jin Woo there?
I can't believe it.
Why was he even there?
Listen.
- Jun Ki? - Let's play just one round.
I can't.
I have to go home. I have a shoot tomorrow.
As the leader, if you treat us like this, I'll be disappointed.
Excuse me.
Dong Gu.
Why are you here?
What? Do you know him?
Pardon?
I knew him before,
but I don't anymore.
What do you mean?
Anyway, I have nothing to say to you.
Don't even try, and leave.
Could I please talk to you?
10... How about 1 minute?
- I said no. - One minute.
- Let's go. - Okay.
Mr. Seo Jin Woo.
Let's go in, Jun Ki.
Can you read the screenplay just once?
Mr. Seo Jin Woo.
Goodness.
How does Jun Ki know him?
I didn't know you were here.
Hello, Hyun Joon.
Did you have fun at the orientation?
Yes.
By the way, why did you leave early?
There was a reason.
I'll get going now.
- Are you leaving already? - Yes.
Dong Gu hasn't eaten anything since then.
I should go and make something that he likes.
Are you that worried?
- Dong Gu isn't a child. - He's like one.
Yoon Ah, may I ask you something?
Yes, what is it?
You said that...
you didn't want to believe anyone anymore.
That you didn't want to get hurt again.
- Yes. - What if...
there's someone you can trust?
What if there's someone who will never hurt you?
What will you do then?
That'd be great,
but will that person appear?
Why do you ask?
It's nothing.
I'll get going.
I can still smell it.
His feet are like chemical weapons.
Keep it down. What if he hears you?
I can't stand it anymore.
Du Shik, let's just wrap it up now.
Wrap it up?
Soo Ah, how could you say that?
What did I say that was so wrong?
You wanted to do it properly this time.
You said it's your last hope.
But his feet smell unbearable.
Min Soo Ah!
Is this the best you can be?
There will be a lot of hardships when we do business.
If you don't think you'll be able to suffer smelly feet,
just give it up already.
Min Soo Ah, I'm so disappointed in you.
I really am.
Du Shik, I'm sorry.
I wasn't thinking.
- Don't get so angry. - No. You should stay here.
I'll finish the rest.
Sorry I was late.
What are you doing?
I saw this ball over there.
I was a basketball player for a while when I was little.
Really?
I was a shooter,
and I never missed.
Keeping the form is important when you shoot.
- Do you want to see? - Sure.
Did you see that?
Do you want to see it one more time?
Wait... Wait.
By the way,
where did you get those shoes?
These?
I found them there and tried them on.
But these...
are really soft.
Sargent jump.
Why is your expression like that?
You crazy dirt bag!
How dare you wear them with your rotten feet?
You smelly monster!
What's wrong? What do you mean, smelly monster?
- Me? - Then would it be me, you lunatic?
You brazen scum!
Hey!
Do you know how smelly your feet are?
Your feet are rotten!
The smell is worse than the sewer.
It's worse than stinky tofu!
How dare you wear the precious shoes...
that my first love gave me?
I'm going to chop that wretched feet off!
Take them off, you scum!
I'm going to poke your eyes, you scumbag.
Gosh,
you're killing me.
You haven't met Seo Jin yet?
What have you been doing?
I can solve this...
Director? Director?
Gosh, he's driving me crazy.
All right.
I will go in and continue. Bye.
Gosh.
Doesn't he have any plans?
Should I ask Jun Ki?
But I have been ignoring him.
What should I do?
What is it? Do you want to talk to me?
What are you doing?
Let me meet Seo Jin Woo.
What's this?
You said you won't talk to me.
You told me I didn't exist to you.
I only mentioned talking, not messaging.
Are you going to help me or not?
You're so stubborn.
All right. I will.
But in turn,
you need to acknowledge the fact...
that Seo Jin and I are dating.
What's wrong? Gosh.
Forget it. I'll curse you until the day I die.
Gosh, he must be crazy.
Hey! What are we going to do now?
Philip was hurt,
and he's never going to work with us again.
I'm sorry.
But he was wearing the shoes that Mal Geum had given to me...
without any socks on.
- He even jumped. - Be quiet.
You got angry at me for complaining,
and yet, you complained and cursed at him directly.
What? "It's worse than stinky tofu"?
"The smell is worse than the sewer"?
- I'm sorry. - Forget it.
Gosh.
We need to upload the pictures of the new products by today.
Where will we get a model at this late hour?
Du Shik can do it instead.
- What? - What?
Du Shik?
We don't want to ruin the shopping mall.
Why do you say that? He's handsome in my eyes.
Yoon Ah.
You have poor taste in men.
This can't do.
But you need to upload them by today.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
I still can't get the smell out.
Should I pour some bleach?
- Soo Ah. - Yes?
What do you think? I tried my best.
Shall we begin? Where should I stand?
That way, sir.
What? Why are you addressing me that way?
It's nothing. Go on.
Okay.
Should I stand still like this?
- Sure. I'll begin. - Okay.
- Director, I'm here. - Hey.
Why is Seo Jin Woo here?
He decided to be on our film just now.
What? Really?
Thank you. Thank you so much.
You should thank Jun Ki.
He followed me around all day and asked me to read this.
That's the only reason why.
- Jun Ki? - I think...
you must be important to him.
He even offered me the game character...
that he had refused so many times.
Thanks to him, I became the leader of the guild.
Hi.
I heard...
that you asked Seo Jin Woo to help me out.
Why did you do that?
I'm still not going to acknowledge you two.
That's not why I did that.
I was only trying to help because you were having trouble.
It's fine.
Gosh, it's so bothersome.
We need to talk.
Why?
- I thought we weren't talking. - Stop being so picky.
Jun Ki,
do you really want to date Seo Jin?
Dong Gu, I'm really sorry,
but I can't give up on her...
even if that means you'll never see me again.
Do you really need to do that?
My feelings for her are sincere.
I truly mean it.
Are you really not satisfied with me?
- It's not that. - What is it then?
My sister and my best friend are dating.
Why would I not like that?
But what if...
you two break up?
What would I do?
I won't be able to see you again.
You know that, right?
- Is that the reason? - Of course.
How can we know the future? Aren't you worried?
Don't worry.
I will never break up with her.
I won't ever make her cry either.
If anything, I'd be the one to cry.
So just have trust in me, you punk.
What did you just say?
What?
What? What's wrong?
How dare you call me a punk?
You should treat me as an elder.
What are you talking about?
Wait.
Does that mean...
you'll let us see each other?
I was going to,
but you have no respect for me. Forget about it.
Sir.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
What?
That's too much. Stop it.
- Your spit tastes great. - Hey.
Seo Jin! Seo Jin, wake up!
What's wrong?
Hey, why does your beard grow so quickly?
Did it grow that much? It's great.
Wait here. I'll show it to my brother.
Seo Jin.
You don't need to do this anymore.
- We got his approval. - What?
Really? He did?
Gosh, I'm so relieved.
Why is it so hard to date you?
Can we go on dates as much as we want now?
Can I tell people you're my boyfriend?
Of course. You can even say it on a news program.
- I'm so happy. - Hey, it hurts.
I'm sorry.
This won't do. I'll go shave first.
- Seo Jin. - Yes?
There's something I've always wanted to do for you.
What is it?
I love you.
They've been in the room for a while now.
What are they doing?
Let them be.
They seem so happy. You should've supported them from the beginning.
I know.
I was worried at first.
But I could see in Jun Ki's eyes that I could trust him.
He'd never...
make my sister cry.
I knew that.
You're good at nothing.
I said I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Is that all?
Why did you have to insist on shaving my face?
- What if it leaves a scar? - I didn't mean to hurt you.
Also, why is your facial hair so stiff?
They're like whale tendons.
What? Whale tendons?
Are you done, you jerk?
"Jerk"?
Did you just call me a jerk?
I can't believe how rude you are.
Yes, I'm rude.
Do you regret going out with a rude girl like me?
Yes, I do. What are you going to do?
I see. Then let's break up.
Fine. Let's break up.
Dong Gu. We're breaking up.
Oh, really?
Well...
Dong Gu, calm down. I was just joking.
- You were joking? - Yes.
- It was just a love quarrel. - She's right.
Love quarrel, my foot.
Come here. Both of you!
- Come here! - I'm scared!
Seo Jin, come here!
Hello. Yes.
Okay. Yes.
I'll get a scoop by all means. Yes, sir.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
What's wrong?
It's work.
My boss will fire me if I don't get a scoop.
I don't know what to do.
Have you heard anything at the broadcasting station?
Anything like dating rumors.
It's not exactly a dating rumor, but I've heard something.
What is it?
- You know Han Min Ju, right? - Yes.
She and Park Jin Cheol, the chairman of Songjin Group,
are rumored to have a child together.
- They had an affair? - Be quiet.
That old man and Han Min Ju?
Yes.
It's from a 100 percent reliable source.
Who told you this?
You've been to the broadcasting station, right?
There is a secret hallway only for VIPs.
Only top stars like Gong Yoo and Won Bin...
or senior executives can access it.
Did you hear it from a senior executive?
No. I heard it from a security guard.
We usually grab coffee together. Isn't it amazing?
"A security guard"?
Are you kidding me?
You don't seem to understand.
High-quality information tends to come from those sources.
Is that right?
Then where can I meet him?
You two are here together.
Dong Gu, what brings you here?
I need to ask Hyun Joon a favor.
A favor?
You made some large-sized bread for me the other day, right?
I need about 30 more of those.
- A bit bigger this time. - Sure.
Are you two going somewhere together?
Yes. Something great happened to Yoon Ah today.
We're going to have a drink together.
A drink?
A place wants to sell my muffins.
Really?
I'd love to celebrate together.
Shared joy is a double joy, right?
- Am I wrong? - But not today.
I have something to tell Yoon Ah.
Can't you say it if I'm there?
Is it something I shouldn't hear?
(A Simple Confession 2)
Congratulations, Yoon Ah.
Thank you.
Isn't this place too expensive?
It's a happy day. We need great food.
Don't worry. Please just enjoy.
Okay. Thank you.
Please excuse me.
Dong Gu, let me fill your glass.
No. I'm fine.
I'll order something else for myself.
That wine is really not for me.
Also,
I don't want to drink anything you pay for.
All right. Suit yourself.
Excuse me. I'd like to see the menu, please.
Let me see.
Do they have my favorite wine?
Wait.
The cheapest wine costs 12 dollars a glass?
- Are you ready to order? - What?
- I'll have a glass of this. - Okay.
By the way, could you take away 20 cents' worth of wine?
- Sorry? - I have a lot to do tonight.
I'm afraid I won't be able to finish everything if I drink a whole glass.
Please take away about 20 cents' worth of wine.
- It tastes so good. - Right.
You said you had something to tell me.
Yes.
I'll tell you some other time.
It's getting late. Should we go home now?
Sure.
You should never leave any food.
When you die, you have to eat all the food you've ever left.
How much do I need to pay?
I've paid for everything.
You can just go.
Thank you so much for the dinner.
Hold on. Can we talk?
Then I'll get some fresh air outside.
Okay.
Look. Didn't I tell you...
I'd never owe you anything?
It's for my wine. 11 dollars and 80 cents.
Please wait a moment.
Thank you so much for the dinner.
Bye.
Okay. See you in class.
Bye, Dong Gu.
Hold on.
Wait here a second.
Why?
Just wait here.
- Yoon Ah, let's go in. - Okay.
- Here. - What is this?
It's for the taxi.
I'm paying for myself...
and Yoon Ah. Check if it's the right amount.
Don't complain later.
Is this really necessary?
Didn't I tell you...
I'd never owe you anything?
Gosh, it's 10 cents up now.
Here. 10 cents.
- Give me three cents. - What?
Forget it. You can keep it.
Also, you seem to keep...
taking my employee out.
Please stop.
It's interfering with my business.
You're the one who interfered today.
What?
What do you mean by that?
Never mind. I'll get going.
What was he talking about?
I really don't like him.
Well...
You're Mr. Kim Yong Shik, right?
Yes. Who are you?
I'm...
reporter Kang Seo Jin from Joyoung Daily.
What's the matter?
You said Han Min Ju and Park Jin Cheol have a child together.
Is that right?
Who says so?
I've never said that.
I heard it from Lee Jun Ki, who is appearing in "Newsroom".
Gosh.
I asked him not to tell anyone. This is so much trouble.
I'll never reveal your identity. Please tell me the details.
Did you witness it?
No, I didn't witness it myself.
I heard it from someone totally reliable.
Who is that person?
You know Elegance Salon in Cheongdam-dong, right?
- Yes. - Han Min Ju goes there.
There's a director there. Her name is Won Kyung Hee.
Won Kyung Hee.
Then you heard the news from that director?
No. She has a favorite hair designer at the shop.
The designer's name is Lee Jung Min.
Then you heard it from Designer Lee Jung Min.
No.
There's an assistant that works for Designer Lee Jung Min.
She's in charge of hair washing. Her name's Kim In Hae.
I can't believe my brother-in-law.
I told him not to tell anyone.
I promise I'll protect you,
so don't worry. Please tell me the details.
Then...
you can't write that I told you this no matter what.
Don't you worry.
Did you see it in person?
I didn't see it myself,
but I heard it from someone that's 100 percent reliable.
Oh, I see.
You know Han Min Ju's agency,
YS Entertainment, right?
Then you heard it from an employee of YS Entertainment?
No. In the agency's cafeteria,
there's a chef by the name of Lee Choon Bok.
Then you heard it from Chef Lee Choon Bok.
No. He loves jjamppong, so he orders in every day...
from a place called Yung Ho Gak.
Their jjamppong soup is amazing.
- Excuse me. - Yes.
Please get back to the point.
Anyway, among the delivery guys,
there's a guy named Uhm Ji Yong.
People call him "Uhm G Dragon"
I heard it directly from him.
Where's Yung Ho Gak?
I'm glad my muffins are selling well.
I'm sure it was somewhere around here. Where was it exactly?
(Uhm G Dragon)
I told her not to tell anyone.
She sure is a blabbermouth.
I promise I'll protect you,
so don't worry. Please tell me what you know.
Did you see it in person?
I didn't see it in person,
but I heard it from someone that's 100 percent reliable.
Pardon?
You know the famous designer Andy Kim, right?
Of course I do.
Did you hear it from Mr. Andy Kim?
No.
In Designer Andy Kim's fashion show,
there's a top model that appears regularly. Her name's Han Hye Jin.
Then you heard it from that model Han Hye Jin?
No.
You should hear me out.
I apologize.
These days, Han Hye Jin...
gives lectures at a model academy.
I heard it from a student that audited her lectures.
She's a fan of G Dragon.
She's a member of the fan club in the Gangseo Area.
I'm the club president.
How could she dare lie to the president?
Where can I find that person?
I heard she was recently planning to go abroad,
but she was swindled by her boyfriend.
I heard she's living off her ex-boyfriend these days.
Pardon?
By any chance, can I get her name?
I can't believe this. It was you...
that said Han Min Ju gave birth to the child of Song Jin's chairman?
What?
I never said such a thing. Who told you that?
The delivery guy at the delicious restaurant, Yung Ho Gak,
who is well known as "Uhm G Dragon."
I heard everything from Mr. Uhm Ji Yong.
Gosh. I can't believe our president.
We've held all those fan meetings together. We're basically comrades.
How could he just betray me like this?
Come on. Be honest and tell me the details.
The fact that Han Min Ju gave birth to Song Jin's chairman's child...
Did you see it in person?
I didn't see it in person,
but I heard it from someone that's 100 percent reliable.
Then you heard it from someone else too?
How come no one's actually seen it? Everyone's just heard it.
Is this even true?
It's 100 percent true.
I heard it directly from a nurse that works at the hospital...
that Han Min Ju's baby was delivered in.
She delivered the baby herself.
Really?
She delivered Han Min Ju's baby herself?
That's what I just said.
This is amazing. This is a scoop.
Soo Ah. Thank you so much.
My leg. My leg is killing me.
You should drive safely. Look what you've done.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Doctor. Is he extremely injured?
He leg is broken severely.
- Excuse me? - It's a compound fracture.
He must go into surgery, and there will be aftereffects.
What did you just say?
This is driving me crazy.
Miss. What are you going to do about this?
How are you going to take care of this?
I have to go to work tomorrow.
I'm truly sorry.
I promise you I'll take care of everything.
It's going in. It fits in.
Perfect. It went in.
Gosh. It actually works.
This is amazing.
Yoon Ah. Welcome home.
What's that look on your face? Is something wrong?
What?
No, it's nothing.
I'm a bit tired. I'm going to go and get some rest.
What's wrong with her?
Are you Nurse Yoon Ji Woo?
Yes. And who might you be?
I called you earlier. I'm Kang Seo Jin from Joyoung Daily.
You know Min Soo Ah, right?
You must be talking about that girl I met while shopping at Dongdaemun.
- Pardon? - She seemed like a fun girl.
We got closer over some soju and pork back-bone stew.
Why do you ask?
From what I heard, she said...
you told her that you delivered Han Min Ju's baby.
- Is that true? - Excuse me?
Yes, I did.
Gosh. This is a major scoop.
I delivered Han Min Ju's baby...
in my dream.
- Your dream? - Yes.
There's a mother that looks like Han Min Ju in our hospital.
The mother's beautiful, but her husband looks so old.
He looks like he's in his 60s.
Surprisingly, that came out in my dream.
I'm going to kill Soo Ah.
I see. So it was a dream?
I was a bit drunk that day.
I must have heard wrong.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? Is that all you've got to say?
Do you know how much trouble I went through today?
A person can make a mistake when they're drunk.
You call that a mistake?
All because of you,
There's a rumor spreading that Han Min Ju had an affair...
with an old man and gave birth to his child.
- Really? - Yes?
I didn't know I was such an influential person.
I wasn't aware.
So are you happy? Are you proud?
No.
So this is how rumors spread.
I never imagined a person that spreads rumors like that...
would be someone this close to me.
How on earth am I supposed to face my editor.
You take the blame. It's all your fault.
What are you going to do about this?
Then do you want me to give you a huge scoop?
This is a fact 100 percent.
A huge scoop?
What is it?
Come close.
What? Kang Dong Won is an alien?
That's what I'm telling you.
Kang Dong Won's looks are unreal.
If he cocks up his ears and uses telepathy,
a spaceship comes down to earth.
Stop that nonsense.
Gosh. You drive me crazy.
Wait. Then I'll give you something else.
Park Bo Gum has wings on his back.
He's an angel. He's an angel.
I need some water.
This is Yoon Ah's cell phone. She must've left it behind.
Hello? This is Yoon Ah's cell phone.
I see. Yoon Ah apparently left her cell phone at home.
May I ask whose calling?
Excuse me? What was that?
Did you say 30,000 dollars?
You should know that I'm helping her out...
by not going to the police and coming to an agreement.
I can't work with my arm and leg like this.
You don't know how much damage this is causing me.
But 30,000 dollars is too much.
How do you expect her to come up with that kind of money?
If she won't agree, we can just go to the police.
I'll go ahead and press charges.
No. I'll give it to you.
I'll find a way to come up with the money.
Please give me some time.
Yoon Ah. Yoon Ah. Yoon Ah.
Yoon Ah. We need to talk.
Dong Gu. What is it?
I heard you had a car accident.
You should have told me about it.
I'm sorry. I didn't want to worry you.
What is it? What happened?
What? 30,000 dollars?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't tell you.
It's okay. Let's talk about that later.
Can everyone get some money?
I'll also ask around.
- Okay. - You can count on me.
I will.
We can do it.
Don't worry so much.
We'll find a solution, okay?
Hello, Sung Yong.
It's been a long time.
May I borrow some money?
You're getting married?
Hey Hyung Eun, it's Dong Gu.
Dong Woo, how are you?
May I borrow some money?
Director, could you help me out?
I'm sorry, Dong Gu.
I don't have spare money.
Hello.
I can't take out more loans than I already have.
Did you get any money?
Is that so?
Okay.
What brings you here?
It's because...
I have a favor to ask you.
A favor?
You're asking me a favor?
Hyun Joon.
Could you lend me 30,000 dollars?
30,000 dollars?
What's going on?
I need to know what it's for, so I can lend it to you.
If you don't tell me, I can't lend it to you.
Yoon Ah got into an accident.
Yoon Ah? What happened?
Did something happen to her?
Yoon Ah got into a car accident, and she needs settlement money.
I tried to find money, but...
Let's go. I'll get the money now.
What are you doing? Come with me.
I'm sorry.
Sir, I don't have money right now.
Can I pay you a little later?
I'll definitely get it for you.
Forget it. Just call the police.
I have nothing to say to you. Just call the police.
- Call the police. - Sir, listen.
Did they come already?
The police advanced so much.
- Are you Seo Tae Hoon? - That's me.
You're under arrest for threat...
and insurance fraud.
- Pardon me? - Arrest him.
Why? I'm a patient.
You got lucky.
You almost got duped.
He's one of the worst ones who stage car accidents.
The doctor works with him,
so they duped so many people.
Thank you.
I don't have to pay the settlement, right?
Right, don't worry about it.
Take them.
Walk properly.
Thank you so much.
Yoon Ah.
Dong Gu. Hyun Joon.
I heard that you were in an accident. What happened?
Well,
it's been settled.
I don't have to pay him anymore.
He stages auto accidents.
I was so worried. That jerk.
Really?
That's a relief. I was very worried.
I'm sorry.
You have to come to the police station.
Me? Why?
We need to investigate witnesses.
Yoon Ah, don't worry so much.
I'll call an attorney to go with you.
Don't be so scared.
Thank you, Hyun Joon.
Thank you so much.
What happened? Has it been resolved?
Yes, Hyun Joon introduced me to an attorney.
Everything got settled.
I'm sorry for making you worried.
It's okay. I'm glad to hear that it's been resolved.
I'm tired.
I'll get some rest.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Yoon Ah's problem was resolved, so what's wrong?
Did something happen?
It's just... I feel pathetic.
Pathetic? Why?
I tried to get money for Yoon Ah but couldn't find any.
However, Hyun Joon could solve it within one second.
He also knows an attorney.
That's because he's much older.
He's also a famous pastry chef.
Right?
It's normal, right?
Something so normal...
doesn't feel normal at all.
I'm glad that the problem got resolved.
It's all thanks to you. Thank you.
No, I didn't do anything.
What did you want to tell me?
Let's eat first.
- Do you want more wine? - Okay.
Goodness.
- Are you okay? - Yes, I'm okay.
I'll go use the restroom.
Okay.
How was the food?
Yes, it was delicious.
What did you want to tell me?
Yoon Ah, actually I...
Wait.
Where did it go?
Is something missing?
Yes, my hairpin is gone.
I definitely had it a minute ago.
Where did it go? What should I do?
Gosh, where did it go?
Where did it go?
You can buy another hairpin.
I'll buy you a pretty one.
No, Dong Gu bought it for me.
It's the first gift from Dong Gu.
Did I lose it in the restroom?
I'm going to the restroom.
Yoon Ah, don't look so sad.
I'm sorry.
I ruined your mood.
No, it's okay.
- Wait. - What is it?
Isn't this the hairpin that you lost?
Yes, this is it.
I'm so relieved.
You're finally smiling.
Are you happy that you found it?
Yes, I thought I lost it.
I was very worried.
Shall we go?
Yoon Ah.
I have something to tell you.
That's right.
What is it? Tell me.
This is what you said.
You don't want to trust anyone.
You don't want to get hurt.
Right, I did.
I don't want you to be scared of love...
because you fear getting hurt.
I don't want you to hesitate either.
- Pardon? - So...
don't let go of the person that you like.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about Dong Gu.
You...
have feelings for Dong Gu.
- Pardon? - But...
you're worried and afraid you might get hurt again. That's why...
your pushing him away.
Isn't that right?
But by pushing him away,
what if you lose the person you have feelings for?
Won't you get hurt that way as well?
Don't you think that'll hurt more?
Shall we go separate ways from here today?
All right. Drive safely.
Dong Gu refused...
to even borrow 10 cents for his taxi fee.
But he came to meet me when you got in that car accident.
He asked me to help you.
He would've chosen to die rather than asking for my help.
I think that proves how much he likes you.
Could I be overanalyzing?
I should really get going now.
I'll sell all of these for you.
I'll help you, all right?
Please buy these muffins. Please buy these.
They're delicious.
Do you even know how she's living these days?
Get out of my way. Yoon Ah. Yoon Ah.
You're not hurt, are you?
You're okay, right?
Do you think a person that went to date girls came to eat sundae?
I like you, Yoon Ah.
I like you a lot.
What are you doing here all alone?
I was just sitting here.
Are you coming back from somewhere?
I went out to meet Hyun Joon.
I see.
Hyun Joon seems like a better guy than I had thought.
He's competent and has a good personality.
Also, he's pretty good-looking...
and he treats you well.
Wait a minute.
Why are you saying that to me?
I'm just saying.
Dong Gu. Do you know you're a real fool?
You sure are oblivious.
What do you mean?
Never mind.
I'm tired. I'm going downstairs and get some rest.
Why is she getting mad at me?
What is this?
- You like him that much? - Yes.
Then say, "I like you."
Dong Gu. I like you.
- Try to be sweet. - I like you.
Act lovely.
I like you.
Try to be cute.
I really like you.
Be brave.
What is this?
I like you. I really like you, Dong Gu.
Would you...
be willing to start a relationship with me?
Yoon Ah.
(Welcome to Waikiki)