Du Shik, Du Shik!
- Du Shik, sweep! - Sweep!
- Sweep, sweep! - Sweep!
Dong Gu, hurry!
- Sweep, sweep! - Hurry!
Sweep!
Hurry, hurry!
Hurry!
What are you guys doing right now?
Is it curling now?
I told you to clean. What nonsense is this?
We were cleaning.
What's so wrong with having some fun while getting it done?
We didn't want to do it. It was Jun Ki's idea, I swear.
What? It was Jun Ki's idea?
Did you really have to tell on him?
That's so petty of you.
What? "Petty"?
Hey, Seo Jin.
Why are you taking Jun Ki's side?
I'm not taking anyone's side.
That's absurd.
- What's with you? - I'm petty?
I have to go to the script reading.
Hurry!
Du Shik, is there something going on between those two?
What are you talking about?
Are you saying they're together or something?
- That's impossible. - You're right.
Jun Ki could do much better.
Are you crazy? Do you have a death wish?
(Secretly, Greatly)
I'm so tired of cleaning.
I really should be working on my Web fiction.
Du Shik!
What's the fuss?
This time, I came upon something I can do really well.
Take a look.
"Soorgio Armhany"?
"Business plan"?
I want to start an online shopping mall.
Soorgio Armhany Mall.
Soo Ah Mall for short.
I've been thinking,
and I'm convinced fashion is my thing.
You want to start a business?
Do you have money for that?
Yes, I received an investment from Soo Bong.
He just got paid.
Wake up. Do you think it's easy to run a business?
Also, you can't do this alone.
I'm not alone. You're going to help me.
What? Me?
When? Where? What? Why?
Wouldn't a shopping mall director be better than a part-timer?
Director?
I'll be a director?
How much are you going to pay me?
- 3. - 30,000 dollars a year?
No. Three dollars an hour.
The minimum wage is 7 dollars and 50 cents by law.
And you're going to pay me three dollars an hour?
Fine. I'll do you a favor.
I'll pay you 3 dollars and 50 cents. Are you happy now?
Director Bong, come with me. We have so much to do.
No. I don't want to do this.
- I don't need an evil boss. - Come here.
Hey!
I've just finished my work here. I'll be at the studio soon.
See you in a bit, Hyun Joon.
I'm interested in her.
I like her.
Are you going to the studio again?
Yes. I have to practice something.
I see. Are you done cleaning?
It was a bit messy on the third floor.
The third floor? I vacuumed and mopped the floor.
All right. I saw some stains on the upper right side of the bowl...
in the bathroom on the second floor. Have you cleaned it?
Yes. I cleaned it from the upper right side...
to the lower left side with bleach.
Okay.
Well, the billiard table on the third floor, at the 4 o'clock...
You mean the dust in the pocket at the 4 o'clock position?
I've wiped it off.
I even waxed the cues and balls.
- You can go then. - Okay. See you.
She's become so meticulous. She's like a cleaning expert now.
I don't want her to get too close with him.
Gosh, it's bothering me.
We're almost home already.
Are you sad, Bacca?
Bacca?
It's your nickname.
It doesn't feel appropriate to call my girlfriend Chewbacca.
I was deciding between Chew and Bacca,
and Bacca sounded cuter to me.
Would you rather prefer to be called...
Wolfman of Huam-dong?
I don't really like any of those names,
but call me anything except Wolfman of Huam-dong.
Then I'll call you Bacca.
By the way,
how long are we going to keep our relationship a secret?
Why don't we just tell Dong Gu?
What? Don't you know what he's like?
He'll beat me to death if he finds out.
Let's keep it a secret for the time being, okay?
Okay.
Are we just going home like this?
What do you mean?
Are we supposed to tumble or crawl or something?
That's not what I mean.
What?
- You want a kiss? - Yes.
But...
- right here? - Yes.
Someone might see us.
No one is around. Come on.
All right.
You're so cheeky, Bacca.
Come here.
Gosh, what are they doing on the streets?
Wait. She looks familiar.
Seo Jin!
It's you, right?
What are you doing right now?
Is it Dong Gu?
Yes. What should we do?
Who are you? Stay right there.
- Okay? - My goodness.
Hey. Where are you going?
You're mistaken.
Cut it out. Let go of me.
What just happened?
What a persistent idiot.
Hold on.
That red coat looks familiar.
Wait. No way.
You...
- No. - You...
Seo Jin. Tell me the truth.
It was Jun Ki at the park, right?
No, it wasn't him.
Who are you trying to fool?
He was wearing Jun Ki's coat.
I knew it. You've been shaving your face...
so regularly these days.
It wasn't Jun Ki.
Then who is he? Tell me.
Well,
I got a new boyfriend.
What? Boyfriend?
Then why did he run away?
Well,
you were yelling at him. He must have been scared.
No. Something doesn't feel right.
Something is very wrong here.
Yes, Director.
I just got home.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
What? Why are you staring at me?
Tell me the truth.
You were kissing Seo Jin in the park, right?
What are you talking about?
I've been rehearsing all day.
Seo Jin was kissing someone?
Who's the guy?
- Stop acting. - What?
He was wearing the exact same coat as you.
Just because I'm wearing this coat, I'm Seo Jin's boyfriend?
Also, why would I go out with a bad-tempered girl...
with a mustache?
That's your reaction? Fine.
Bring the guy then.
Bring your boyfriend right here.
- What? - You can't, right?
It's because Jun Ki is your boyfriend. Am I wrong?
Gosh.
Seo Jin, bring him.
- What? - Bring him here...
so Dong Gu can see that nothing is going on between us.
Do it.
Well...
Okay. I will.
Really?
All right. Let's see.
Jun Ki. Jun Ki?
Here.
Are you okay?
Wait. You're bleeding.
I'm okay.
When the car hit me,
my organs must have been damaged.
But at least, Dong Gu didn't find out.
Do we really have to do this?
Can't we just be honest?
Who knows if he'll support us?
Hey.
I wouldn't let my sister date a guy like me.
You think Dong Gu might support us?
- Dream on. - Gosh.
Why did you say I should bring my boyfriend here?
Don't worry.
I'll ask for help from a friend, who is a good actor.
This might be a good thing.
After seeing that guy, Dong Gu will stop suspecting us.
Things will become easier for us.
Don't you think?
I agree, but...
Don't worry.
Just trust me.
- Okay? - Okay.
What are you doing?
You're so ugly.
How can you be so ugly?
Thinking of such an ugly face growing a mustache,
who would be in a relationship with you?
Your ugly face wakes me up.
Wait.
What's wrong?
I'm saying this just in case.
If there's anything between you and my sister,
once I find out,
you will no longer be alive.
Got that?
Don't worry. That won't happen.
Do you understand?
There's something suspicious about them...
including the fact that they kissed.
Well, I'll find out today.
If Seo Jin is dating Jun Ki, I will...
Dong Gu, I'm going to the studio.
Again?
We have a lot of work to do. Aren't you going there too often?
I finished everything.
I saw piles of laundry. Did you wash them?
I washed and hung them on the drying rack.
I saw spots on the left pillowcase on the second floor.
I washed all pillowcases.
I sanitized and changed them too.
- On the third-floor windows... - The curtains?
I washed and hung them on the drying rack too.
Really?
What about the one that's hanging on the third banister...
The flag?
I washed, ironed, and hung it back.
- Then you can go. - See you later.
She became meticulous.
She's too quick.
When did she do all that?
He bothers me.
Song Hyun Joon.
What on earth?
Why are you sleeping?
You startled me. What are you doing?
I went around Dongdaemun and couldn't get any sleep.
How dare you sleep during working hours?
Hey, I couldn't sleep at all while making the home page.
Forget it. Did we get any orders?
Only you and I know the home page address.
Who would visit and order?
What should we do?
Is there a way to advertise?
Broadcasting is the best for advertisement,
but it isn't easy.
Broadcasting?
Let me think.
Part Two of "Meet Seo Yu Ri at Noon" started.
During Part Two,
we have your favorite part where listeners sing.
Let's connect to the first participant.
Hello?
We got it.
- Hello? - It's nice to meet you.
Could you introduce yourself?
Hello, I'm the director of an online shopping mall...
called Soorgio Armhany.
I'm Bong Du Shik.
Hello, Director Bong.
You shouldn't say the name of your company on air.
Is that so? I'm sorry.
We'll ignore it since you made a mistake for the first time.
Director Bong, which song will you sing?
I'll sing "Confession" by Lim Jae Bum.
"Confession"? That's a difficult song.
Let's hear it.
What should I do?
What am I supposed to do?
I'm not good enough
However
I love her
Let me go quietly, Soo Ah
I don't know either, Soo Ah
Soorgio Armhany
Shopping Mall
Soo Ah
The call got cut off.
I apologize for not having a stable connection.
Let's connect to the next participant.
Hello?
It's nice to meet you. Could you introduce yourself?
I'm Min Soo Ah from Huam-dong.
Which song would you like to sing?
I'll sing "Crooked" by G-Dragon.
"Crooked" by G-Dragon.
Let's hear it right away.
Nothing ever lasts forever
In the end, you changed
- There's no reason - Soo Ah
- Nothing is sincere - Soo Ah
Shopping Mall Soorgio Armhany
- Shopping Mall Soorgio Armhany - Shopping Mall Soorgio Armhany
Shopping Mall...
Darn it.
She has no manners for her listeners.
Wouldn't you hang up if you were her?
What else could we do? This is all we could do.
But we were amazing, right?
Yes, you sang well.
It's delicious.
- Really? - It's really delicious.
I'm so glad.
Actually, I'm most confident with making muffins.
I even came up with a name...
for my future bakery after Sol.
Really? What's the name?
Sol, Sol, Green Sol's Muffin.
I see. The name is quite unique.
- Is this the recipe? - Yes.
I made the recipe myself.
Are you saying that he's your boyfriend?
- Yes. - Be quiet.
Are you really Seo Jin's boyfriend?
Hi, hi.
Yes, I enjoy wearing a red coat.
While we were kissing in the park...
You screamed like that,
so I was startled and ran away.
I'm Seo Jin's boyfriend, Kang Hong Seok.
Hong Seok is a musical actor, so he makes big gestures.
He's expressive.
He is.
How did you meet Seo Jin?
Hey.
What's wrong with the lights?
The first time we met was before a performance.
Seo Jin entered the stage to make a report.
Step by step,
she walked in while clacking her shoes.
Then my heart pounded all of a sudden.
It started to pound.
I started to hear music that sang of our fate.
At this moment
Everything of me
I'll risk my body and my soul
I'll throw everything
I'll dedicate my all to you
I've been looking desperately for you
My destiny, Kang Seo Jin
For you
By the way, where's the bathroom?
Pardon? The bathroom?
It's over there.
- Over there? - Yes.
Please excuse me.
Step by step.
What did I tell you?
There's nothing between me and Seo Jin.
It seems a little strange,
but it's better than dating you.
What did you say?
What's wrong with me?
Be glad that it isn't you.
If you were dating Seo Jin,
once I find out,
you will no longer be alive.
I told you that I understood.
Stop saying that. You're frightening me.
You sound like the grim reaper.
You want me to do this?
Is this necessary?
We have to advertise our shopping mall somehow.
Gosh. What's going on?
What's all this noise?
Dong Gu.
What's all this? Look at you two.
What are you guys doing?
Us? We're about to do a webcast.
We have to promote our online shopping site.
Is that right?
- But what's that on your face? - What?
Are you talking about this?
Last time when Seo Jin shaved her beard, it went viral.
I thought I'd try shaving on our webcast,
so I made it look like I have a beard.
I see.
Then what are those bones for? Are they dinosaur bones?
Can you believe this? She wants me...
to eat bones like Jun Ki did.
On top of that,
she gave me these hard cow legs.
Jun Ki ate pigs' feet bones.
You should eat something tougher to get more viewers.
Gosh. Just do it.
Viewers are logging on.
(BJ Soorgio and BJ Armhany's Shaving and Eating Show)
Now, let's get this started, Du Shik.
"Gangnam Parvenu", hello.
I'm the hottest BJ bursting onto the shaving webcast scene.
I'm BJ Soorgio.
Hello. I'm the handsome BJ in the bone-eating webcast scene.
I'm BJ Armhany.
Then we'll get started...
with our bone-eating and shaving webcast show.
First, I'll put on some shaving cream.
What do you think you're doing? Hurry up, and eat the bones.
Du Shik.
Jun Ki. Your first shooting is coming up. Is practice going well?
I don't know. I'm doing my best,
but honestly, I'm a bit worried and anxious.
Cheer up. I'm sure you'll do a great job.
I can always rely on you. You're the only one...
that truly worries about me, Bacca.
You're grateful, aren't you?
Then shouldn't I be getting a reward?
A reward? What kind of reward?
You know perfectly well what I'm talking about.
What?
- Again? - Yes.
What if Dong gu catches us again?
I doubt it.
We should still be careful.
Didn't you hear what Dong Gu said yesterday?
You will no longer be alive.
Just the thought of that...
sends chills up my spine.
Still. Please?
Gosh. How could I refuse?
You adorable little Bacca.
Get those cute lips ready.
Get ready. Here I go.
I'll show you how it should be done.
What's am seeing now?
Hey! Seo Jin!
Who is that? It's Dong Gu, isn't it?
Oh, dear. What should we do?
Seo Jin. Who is it? Who is he?
Who is he?
What? What was that?
What just happened?
Wait a minute.
Seo Jin. How could you?
It's not what you think.
Who are you trying to fool?
- That hurts. Wait. - Come with me. Follow me.
Seo Jin.
Hong Seok said he's at the theater.
Then who was that jerk earlier?
Hold on.
As I think of it, from the back, he looked just like Jun Ki.
What are you saying? It wasn't Jun Ki.
Then who was it?
Who on earth was that guy kissing you?
Well, you see,
- it was my boyfriend. - What? Your boyfriend?
What about Hong Seok?
Then do you mean you're two-timing?
What?
Yes.
I met him while I was out covering a case today.
I couldn't help myself.
You actually kissed someone that you just met today?
I can't control myself these days.
I'm a bit sexually frustrated.
Do you actually expect me to believe that?
Yes, Director.
Thank you for giving me a ride home.
Drive home safely. Goodbye.
Look at that.
The back of your head looks exactly like that jerk.
What on earth are you talking about?
Don't try to deny it.
It was you that was kissing Seo Jin in the park earlier, right?
What are you talking about?
I've been practicing my lines with the director until now.
Wait a minute. Seo Jin was kissing a guy again?
You've completely lost your mind. You just love kissing, don't you?
So you're telling me that jerk wasn't you?
Fine.
Then go bring your boyfriend over here.
- Bring him over. - This instant!
What? Right now?
Why are you surprised?
I'm not surprised at all.
Seo Jin. Just bring him over.
- What? - Bring him over.
You can bring him over.
I have your back. Go ahead, and bring him.
Prove that you and I are just close friends.
Prove that to Dong Gu.
Go right ahead. Please prove that to me.
Call him!
What are you doing! I need to see him today!
- Bring him over! - This instant!
All right.
Why are you dressed like that?
You see, I was in the middle of shooting a historical drama...
when I was casted at the last minute.
You were casted?
What I meant to say was...
I suddenly received a call...
from my girlfriend, Bang Seo Jin.
Did you say Bang Seo Jin?
Did I get her name wrong?
- Pardon? - To be honest,
we just decided to start dating today,
so I don't know her name quite well.
Of course. That's possible.
I learned my girlfriend's name three months after we started dating.
- Is that right? - Anyhow,
I can assure you that I'm Seo Jin's boyfriend.
If you don't mind, if you're done checking,
may I go now?
You see, I'm scheduled to be poisoned in 30 minutes.
I see. Then you should get going.
I'll be leaving now then.
Did you see that? I told you it wasn't me.
All right. That guy's also kind of strange,
but it's better than having Seo Jin date you.
As if two-timing weren't enough,
I think kissing on your first date is too much.
Seo Jin. Don't you think you're being a bit too easy?
I'm sorry, Dong Gu.
I never know I could be so easy.
- I'm sorry. - You're making me worry.
We still don't have a single visitor.
(Visitors: None)
We've already bought a bunch of clothes. I'm so worried.
Gosh, my molars.
It's all Soo Ah's fault.
Director Bong. Follow me.
Follow you where?
We can't just sit back and wait all day.
We should try whatever we can. Come with me.
- Where are we going this time? - Just come with me.
What on earth do you have planned this time, Soo Ah?
Hello, we're from an online shopping mall,
- Hello, please visit... - "Soorgio Armhany".
"Soorgio Armhany", our online shopping mall.
Please visit "Soorgio Armhany", our online shopping mall.
Please try searching our site online.
Soo Ah. We've done enough.
This won't help promote our website.
Who promotes shopping sites with leaflets these days anyway?
Then what should we do? We have no other choice.
We should at least do whatever we can.
If you want to leave, go alone.
I won't go back until I give out all of these today.
Hey. Wait.
Please visit "Soorgio Armhany", our online shopping mall.
Thank you in advance.
("Soorgio Armhany" Grand Opening Event)
I told you we should stop doing this.
Let's go now, okay?
Soo Ah.
Are you crying?
Du Shik.
What's wrong with me?
Why can't I ever do anything right?
I really worked hard on this.
I really wanted to do this right this time.
- Get up. - Don't mind me.
I'm going to stay here. You go ahead.
Just get up. I'm hungry.
How could you possibly be hungry at a time like this?
We should eat something if we're going to continue handing these out.
- What? - Also,
how can an employee leave first when the boss is still working?
So get up already.
Here. Drink this.
No thanks. I'm not hungry.
Don't be stubborn. Drink some. Go ahead.
Don't move! Don't move!
Everyone, get down on the floor!
If you all don't want to die, get down on the floor!
- Is that a gun in his hand? - What?
It's a gun. It's a gun.
What on earth is going on?
You two right there.
Get down on the floor. Get down now.
Yes, sir.
- Hyun Joon. - Hello. Welcome.
Hello. Why did you suddenly ask me to come here?
You see, I have something I'd like to show you.
(Sol, Sol, Green Sol's Muffin)
What's this?
I'm a businessman.
Your muffins seemed competitive,
so I launched them. What do you think?
Really?
I followed every letter of your recipe.
My shop will take care of the manufacturing and selling.
But the profits will be shared with you equally.
Do you have any objections?
No, I don't.
Thank you so much.
I appreciate it, Hyun Joon.
I look forward to working with you, Patissier Han.
Park Doo Cheol, it's still not too late.
Drop your weapons, and surrender!
Cut it out!
If you want to save the hostages, get lost!
How long will this go on?
Wait.
It must be being broadcast.
That's right.
There are so many cameras.
Hold on. Du Shik.
These things are usually broadcast live, right?
I guess so. What about it?
It's an opportunity to promote our shopping mall.
It must be being broadcast live all over the country now.
Are you saying you want to promote our shopping mall right now?
Are you crazy?
You stay here.
- Let me take care of it. - Don't do anything.
He might shoot you. Stay still.
Stop it.
Don't do anything.
- Look at that. - What is she doing?
Hey, what are you doing right now?
Well, sir,
can't I just stand here?
I'll still be your hostage...
regardless of whether I'm standing or lying down.
- She's lost her mind. - What?
Have you lost your mind?
Get down.
Get down right now.
I have my reasons.
I've already given up on my life.
Do you want to die with me?
You're not the only one who is going through a hard time.
What?
I don't know about your situation,
but I wouldn't think mine is any better.
I was conned...
and lost all my money.
On top of that,
I'm living off my ex-boyfriend, who I dumped.
Really?
What's worse, my ex-boyfriend likes someone else now.
He even asks me for dating advice.
It's so humiliating.
What a jerk.
My online shopping mall was my last hope,
but it's about to close down.
So please just let me stand here.
Will you, sir?
Why are you crying?
People are watching. Stop crying.
I can't believe these guys.
Gosh.
Soo Bong's lessons sure helped.
Bacca, what's wrong?
- What is it? - You really don't know?
You made me look easy.
I couldn't help it because of Dong Gu.
How long do we have to do this?
- Forever? - You know what Dong Gu is like.
He'll kill me if he finds out.
Why are you such a coward?
- Are you that scared of my brother? - Yes.
I really am.
I don't want to die yet.
Forget it. It's over.
Let's just break up.
Wait. What are you talking about?
What's the matter?
Hey. Seo Jin.
Stop it. Let go of me.
- I can't. I won't. - Let go.
Seo Jin.
Is it Dong Gu again?
Gosh. Again?
Let's just tell him the truth.
I can't. He'll kill me.
Are you serious?
Stay right there.
- Okay? - I'm sorry, Seo Jin.
Come here.
What was that? Is he a human being or a cheetah?
Seo Jin. Who is that guy?
Whatever!
- Gosh. - What?
How dare she yell at me?
Hey! Seo Jin!
A woman suppressed the gunman with nothing but her bare hands.
Let's hear from her.
Hello.
I run an online shopping mall called "Soorgio Armhany",
Soo Ah Mall for short. My name is Min Soo Ah.
It must not have been easy to suppress the gunman.
Of course not.
But Soorgio Armhany's company mission...
is the realization of a just society.
What?
With highest-quality products, reasonable prices,
and fast delivery service, Soorgio Armhany will always...
be there for you...
who wish for a just society.
Our address is...
Tell me the truth.
Who were you hugging?
I don't know.
If you don't know him, why were you hugging him?
He was passing by, and I thought he looked nice.
You know I'm easy!
Why are you so angry?
I was just worried if you were dating Jun Ki.
Do you hate him that much?
What? Hey.
Why would I hate Jun Ki?
I like him.
He is a bit immature, but he's kind-hearted.
He's thoughtful too.
But...
I still don't want my sister to date him. That's all.
Really?
I'm asking you this out of curiosity.
What would you do if I really was dating Jun Ki?
Would you hit him or something?
Are you crazy? I couldn't hit him.
- But if you really were together, - Yes?
you'll have to pay the price.
Me? What do you mean?
I know this small temple...
deep in the mountains of Gangwon Province.
It's very beautiful and clean there.
You can't find a living soul around there.
And?
If I had to see you go out with Jun Ki,
I'd rather shave off all your hair...
and turn you into a Buddhist nun.
A nun?
The world and I are one
In addition, you won't be allowed to use a razor.
You know I'm not joking, right?
Yes, I do. I know that very well.
Hey, Dong Gu.
What happened? Why did he drink so much?
Hey.
I have something to confess to you.
You want to confess something? What is it?
What is it?
I'll be a man and tell you everything.
Me and...
Seo Jin...
Seo Jin, what are you doing?
He was so noisy.
He should just go to bed. I can't stand him anymore.
There's nothing I like about him.
Why does she hate Jun Ki so much?
I mean...
I really didn't have to suspect them.
Jun Ki, are you okay? Hey.
Bacca, did something happen last night while I was drunk?
I remember coming home,
but I blacked out after that.
Well...
You fell down.
Really?
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I'll tell Dong Gu about us today...
- even if he might beat me to death. - What?
No. Don't tell him.
- Why not? - I've thought about it,
and I decided that we should probably keep it a secret.
So let's just keep it from him from now on, okay?
All right.
Then I'm leaving for a shoot now.
Already? Isn't it in the afternoon?
- Why are you leaving so early? - I should go early and rehearse.
I'm shooting with Min Ki Young today.
Really? You must be so nervous.
My heart is about to burst.
Then should I give you some energy?
Give me some energy? How?
What do you think? Do you feel more energy now?
Yes. I have so much energy now.
It's out of control. What should I do?
What are you doing?
What if Dong Gu sees us?
I don't care.
(Expenditure for "Codename Dubai")
We have another order.
You seem to be getting some orders now.
It's probably because of the advertisement.
It's all thanks to me. You know that, right?
By the way, where's Yoon Ah?
She went to the bakery.
What? At this early hour?
I heard Hyun Joon let her sell...
her muffins at his bakery.
He's even sharing profits with her.
Really?
Du Shik, what are you reading?
- Is it fun? - It is.
What is it about?
This is about a man...
who pretends to be terminally ill to stay next to the woman he loves.
His love is so sad.
What? He pretends to be ill...
to stay next to his love?
He's lying.
That's not sad. That's cowardly.
- What do you mean? - It's true.
It's just like someone who lets Yoon Ah sell muffins at his place.
How can a man do that? He's such a coward.
Don't you think so?
Scum.
(Expenditure for "Codename Dubai")
(A Real Man)
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Jun Ki, you know him, right? You should introduce yourself.
Sure. Hello, sir.
It's an honor to meet you like this.
I'm Lee Jun Ki, acting as Song Jun Seok.
Are you the one acting as Song Jun Seok?
- Pardon? - Are you Song Jun Seok?
Yes, sir.
You look really kind.
Let's make this work.
Jun Ki, why are you laughing?
His pronunciation is a little...
He recently had a tongue surgery,
so he can't pronounce certain sounds.
He'll get better soon. Don't worry.
Really?
Get ready. Cue.
Sir, I can't follow your order.
I have to get this news out.
What?
Even if I lose my position as an anchor...
Even if I die, I'll announce this report.
Do you understand?
How could you do this to me, Song Jun Seok?
Don't you know what I've done for you, Song Jun Seok?
Cut.
Jun Ki, why are you curling your lips like that?
I... I'm sorry.
My lips are dry.
I'm sorry, sir.
It's fine. It's just because you're nervous.
Let's continue.
We'll start from your line, sir.
All right.
Cue!
I've been so good to you, Jun Seok!
- Why do you keep laughing? - Sorry?
Why do you keep laughing?
Do you think my acting is funny?
No, it's not like that.
Stop it. Director Kim,
let's continue later.
I'm sorry.
Why do you keep laughing?
His pronunciations make me laugh.
But still, you shouldn't laugh when he's acting.
Be careful, all right?
I'm sorry.
Sir.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Gosh.
Why do I keep laughing?
Song Jun Seok.
I must be crazy.
Now, we're nearly done.
- What happened to the hunting? - I'm looking into it.
He gave a spot to Yoon Ah?
He's going to keep her by his side by using bread?
- That scum. - Next,
when Shin Hyun Joon slips into the party room at the Dubai hotel,
where do you think he should hide his air rifle?
- I've been thinking. - All right.
There are musicians at the parties, right?
What if he hides it in an instrument case?
They already used that in "Mission Impossible".
Don't you have any fresh ideas?
Hey, he's doing that again.
He must have an idea.
Dong Gu, can you think of anything?
Bread!
Bread? What about it?
What?
A bread that we can eat?
So you want to hide the air rifle in a bread?
- That's a new idea. - Gosh.
How can you hide a big rifle in a bread?
We can make a long bread.
There will be food at parties.
It'd be natural.
Dong Gu, you got this one again.
I think you're ready to be a director now.
- It's great. You did so well. - Thank you.
You're ahead of me again.
I thought of bread too.
- Go easy on me. - What?
I'm sorry.
What brings you here, Dong Gu?
You're here to see Yoon Ah.
No. I only came here...
to look for movie props.
But where's Yoon Ah?
She's in the workroom. Do you want me to call her?
No thanks.
I heard...
you got her a spot to sell her muffins.
Yes, right here.
(Sol, Sol, Green Sol's Muffin)
So this was it.
I didn't think of you like this, but you're cheaper than I thought.
What do you mean?
You want to gain her affection...
by getting her a spot.
How can a man be so cheap...
to take advantage by using bread like that?
- What? - Enough about that.
Do you have any bread that might fit an air rifle?
Why put an air rifle in a bread?
It's something we need for our film.
I don't think you'd understand.
In that case, can you make bread...
that can fit an air rifle?
Just plain ones.
Sure. It won't be so difficult.
Then make 20 of them...
big enough to fit air rifles, okay?
All right.
What are you doing here, Dong Gu?
I'm here to look for props to use in my film.
- I'm going now. - Bye.
Gosh, Hyun Joon.
Be a man, all right? Be a man.
How can a man be so cowardly?
I can't live like that.
How cheap of him.
My legs!
Dong Gu!
- Dong Gu, are you all right? - Just calm down.
- Just stay calm. - What should we do?
Don't touch my legs!
Just stay calm, okay?
Are you all right?
Please call an ambulance.
- Hello, Jun Ki. - Hello.
Why do you look so sad?
Did something happen?
I nearly got fired.
What? Why?
Min Ki Young hurt his tongue,
so he can't pronounce certain sounds.
Okay.
And he can't pronounce the name of my role.
So?
Whenever he pronounces my name,
he sounds so funny.
So I was told off for laughing during the shooting.
What? Song Jun Seok?
Yes.
And he says my name...
with such a stern expression.
I couldn't hold back my laughter.
I understand. I always laugh at the same thing too.
I need to shoot with him again tomorrow.
What should I do?
Dong Gu.
What happened? Why are you in a wheelchair?
Dong Gu got hurt.
What happened?
It's nothing. Don't make a big fuss.
Yoon Ah, can you take me to my room?
Sure.
It's a big problem.
Both your legs were hurt.
He can't even move.
I know.
We can help today,
but tomorrow, we all need to go outside for work.
Don't worry. I'll stay next to him.
Then what about your classes and the bakery?
I can skip class for a few days.
And I'll ask Hyun Joon about the bakery.
Dong Gu, tell me if you need anything.
- Okay? - Okay.
I'll get some rest for now, Yoon Ah.
Let's go.
It means that she won't see him.
I'm glad that I got injured.
I got injured perfectly.
I slept so well.
Shall I go to the bathroom?
It doesn't hurt.
I'm really fine.
I'm so relieved.
Are you awake, Dong Gu?
Are your legs okay?
They're fine after getting some sleep.
I'm happy to hear that.
Dong Gu, then I'll go to the bakery.
I'm worried about work.
What? Then is she going to that guy's bakery again?
Gosh, that's not good.
My legs.
Dong Gu.
What's wrong, Dong Gu?
I thought I was fine, but I was wrong.
Gosh, I feel pain.
They hurt more than yesterday. What should I do?
I can't do anything alone.
Really?
- What's wrong all of a sudden? - I'm sorry, Yoon Ah.
You have to go to the bakery.
No, don't worry.
- I'll lay you down. - Okay.
Hello, sir.
I'm sorry about yesterday.
Please forgive me.
Right.
Don't do it again, okay?
I won't, sir.
- Have you eaten? - No, not yet.
If not, do you want some sandwich?
Thank you.
Have some apple juice too.
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing.
Thank you.
Goodness.
"Sandwich" and "apple juice".
That's hilarious.
It's funny whenever he talks.
What if I burst out laughing when he calls me again?
No, it won't be many times.
I should keep from laughing by pinching my thigh.
Gosh, it's a waste of a sandwich.
Hey, Jun Ki.
The writer changed the script.
There aren't many changes, so memorize them quickly.
Okay.
Oh, that's right.
(Song Jun Seok, Song Jun Seok...)
"Song Jun Seok".
Let's start the shoot.
Get ready. Cue.
Sir, I can't follow your order.
- I have to get this news out. - What?
Even if I lose my position as an anchor...
Even if I die, I'll announce this report.
Do you understand?
Song Jun Seok, Song Jun Seok, Song Jun Seok!
How could you do this to me, Song Jun Seok?
Don't you know what I've done for you, Song Jun Seok?
Song Jun Seok, Song Jun Seok!
- That's... - Again?
What's wrong with you?
I'm... I'm sorry, sir.
- Is my acting funny? - No.
I'm your senior. How dare you laugh at me?
Director Kim, I can't shoot today.
- Sir... - Sir? Sir?
Are you insane?
Why do you keep laughing?
- I'm sorry. - Be quiet.
If he quits, it's over for you too.
Got that?
Sir?
My goodness.
Why do I keep laughing? Why?
Pretending to be sick isn't easy.
Gosh, I feel so stiff.
It's fine as long as Yoon Ah doesn't go near Hyun Joon.
My legs.
Take your medicine.
Okay.
- Do they still hurt a lot? - Yes.
They're getting worse.
I wonder if I'll be able to walk again.
This is terrible.
- Take your medicine first. - Okay.
Can you get up?
I'll do my best.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Shouldn't you wash, Dong Gu?
Of course I want to wash.
Don't worry.
Come on, you should wash up.
Let's go. I'll help you.
You don't have to do it.
Move slowly.
Gosh, I really mean it.
Here you go.
- Thank you, Yoon Ah. - Don't mention it.
But how will you wash your hair?
It's okay. I'll wash it when I get better.
You should still wash your hair.
Then I'll wash it for you.
What? Would you really do that for me?
No, it's okay.
Shall I lie down? What should I do?
I'm sorry about my legs.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay.
Right there. That's right.
Are you home, Yoon Ah?
That sounds like Hyun Joon.
What brings you here?
I was worried about Dong Gu.
It was going well, but why is he here?
How are your legs, Dong Gu?
They're okay.
They got worse than yesterday.
He can't move on his own.
Really?
That's terrible.
- What are you looking at? - Hello, Seo Jin.
What? Really?
Okay, I got it.
Is something wrong?
Seo Jin left an important document. She wants me to bring it to work,
but I can't just leave you here. What should I do?
That brat.
You should go. I'll stay with him.
Can you?
- Then I'll be right back. - Okay.
Hey, Yoon Ah.
You can't just leave.
I'll rinse it.
What? Are you crazy?
Why would you rinse my hair?
You still have foam in it. You can't stay like this.
I'm fine.
Just stay still. I'll rinse it for you.
I'm fine. What are you doing? Don't touch my hair.
Stay still.
Gosh.
I think you should rinse it again.
It's okay. It's rinsed.
There's more foam left. I'll bring some water.
I said that I'm okay.
You still have some foam left.
No, I'm done rinsing.
- You still have foam left. - Come on.
- I said I'm fine. - Oh, no.
Darn it.
I said that I'm okay.
What have you done?
I'm sorry.
You're all wet.
You should get changed.
Where is your room? I'll get you changed.
What? You can't change my clothes.
Who do you think you are?
- Shall I let you go? - Yes.
- Okay. - What are you doing?
I'll help you get changed now.
I'm fine. I'm completely okay.
Just stay still.
Where shall I start? Let me change your pants.
What's wrong with you? Hey.
Let me do it. It's because I'm sorry.
I'll change them myself.
I'll change them.
How?
You can't move because your legs hurt.
Were you faking it?
What did you say? "Faking it"?
Who do you think I am?
So stay still.
- Hey! - Come on.
You're all wet.
I think we should change your underwear too.
Gosh, you can't do this to me.
Just stay still. Why are you...
It's done now.
Dong Gu, where are your panties?
Hey!
You can't leave me naked like this.
Hello, Bacca
Jun Ki, is it going well?
No.
I laughed again when he was acting, so I was told off again.
If I laugh one more time, I might really get fired. What should I do?
That's a big problem.
In that case, think of something else whenever you want to laugh.
Think of something sad.
I've tried everything.
I've even pinched my thighs and bit on my tongue.
But when he says, "Song Jun Seok",
everything doesn't work.
Nothing works.
Really? What should we do?
Then what do you think about trying this?
What?
Sir.
I was sorry about what happened before.
It will never happen again.
It's fine.
If you laugh one more time,
I won't let you get away with it. Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Let's begin shooting.
Get ready. Cue.
Sir, I can't follow your orders.
I have to get this news out.
What?
Even if I lose my position as an anchor...
Even if I die, I'll announce this report.
- Do you understand? - Song Jun Seok.
Song Jun Seok, Song Jun Seok, Song Jun Seok!
How could you do this to me, Song Jun Seok?
This is driving me crazy.
It will be the end for me if I laugh this time.
What should I do?
Wait, should I really try what Seo Jin suggested?
Whenever you feel like laughing,
think about something that scares you the most.
Think of something that gives you goosebumps.
All right. I have nothing to lose.
Let's try that.
Don't you know what I've done for you, Song Jun Seok?
You will no longer be alive.
Song Jun Seok!
You will no longer be alive. You will no longer be alive.
You will no longer be alive.
You won't be able to work here anymore.
Do you understand, Jun Seok?
Do as you want.
But sir,
is it the media's job to cover up issues?
Is it our job to distort facts and incite people?
The media cannot distort facts or omit them.
That...
is the obligation and duty as a reporter.
Do you understand?
Cut! Okay.
That was great, Jun Ki.
Thank you.
- Thank you, sir. - Well done.
You did so well. Why did you do that earlier?
You're good at acting.
Thank you, sir. Thank you.
I did it. I did it!
This is so embarrassing.
Why did he have to see that?
Why does something like this...
always happen with him? Why?
I'm sorry I was late.
I took the wrong bus.
It's fine.
What's wrong with Dong Gu?
Did anything happen?
Well...
No, nothing happened.
That's a relief.
You must be tired, Hyun Joon.
It's fine.
I'll get going now.
- Then I'll see you outside. - Okay.
Wait.
I'll see him out. You should stay here.
He nursed me today. I should see him out.
Don't touch me.
Wait.
We need to talk.
What happened today never happened.
I saw your... You know.
We'll both get hurt, okay?
All right. Nothing happened.
Are you satisfied?
Well, yes.
But did you really come here because you were worried about me?
Yes.
I want you to get better soon.
- Really? - Yes.
That way, I'll get to see Yoon Ah more often.
So you came here because of Yoon Ah, not me.
A man shouldn't act like that.
Pretending to be ill is not manly either.
What... What did you say?
"Pretending to be ill"? What are you talking about?
Are you saying I'm pretending to be ill?
Never mind then.
I hope you get better. Bye.
I...
I won't get better. Why should I get better?
Gosh, look at him. He didn't even listen.
I think he figured it out already.
What? Then did he do that on purpose?
Gosh, that scum. Seriously.
My gosh!
Yoon Ah! Yoon Ah!
Yoon Ah! Let me take a look. Are you hurt? Are you all right?
- I'm fine. - Gosh, that... Gosh.
- Your legs... - What?
Gosh, my legs.
Gosh.
You said you couldn't move, but you can even run.
I thought you were Usain Bolt.
Were you pretending to be ill?
I wasn't.
I...
I must have had superhuman powers for a quick moment.
Stop it.
Stop pretending, and stand up.
I'm not.
I'm Kang Dong Gu, the manliest man among men.
Really? Then use that power...
to come back home by yourself.
Yoon Ah.
Yoon Ah, let's go together.
I'm really hurt. Gosh, this is just a misunderstanding.
Yoon Ah, you should at least help me back up the wheelchair.
Yoon Ah. Yoon Ah.
I'm really in pain.
It's really cold down here.
(Welcome to Waikiki)
Dong Gu, do you have time tomorrow?
When, where, and what time do you want to meet?
What? I see you're wearing that shirt.
- Yoon Ah. - Gosh.
What are you doing here?
Why do you sit next to Yoon Ah?
That's the prize?
Can you please participate in a couple event with me?
Then I'll be off to the CF meeting.
Your smile is most important in this advertisement.
- Are you all right? - I'm fine.
- What's wrong? - I'm fine.
Next, your expressions.
It looks delicious.
Gosh, it's so good.
The game is on.
- Can I borrow your car? - Can you drive?
Of course.
- Du Shik, what are the brakes? - What?
Slow down. You're going too fast.
Step on the brakes. The brakes.
- What is this? - Is this the brake pedal?
Pull the side brakes. What's wrong with this car?
Du Shik, what should we do?