I was...
a little moved by you today.
Don't even talk about it.
It was a really important interview for you today, wasn't it?
So, please get into the company.
Okay?
You know what?
When I saw you today,
my heart fluttered.
Why do you think so?
I must be crazy.
Let me see.
Let go. What are you doing?
Let me take a look.
I don't understand.
Why did I think that you looked handsome?
Gosh.
Dong Gu, what are you doing here?
I couldn't fall asleep.
Why do you look so down?
You asked me...
if I was ready to deal with Yoon Ah's issues.
But I can't seem to answer that question.
I'm not sure if I'm ready.
Of course. It can't be easy.
Do you want to drink?
I was going to drink my problems away.
Sounds good.
Let's do that.
Let's go.
Take off your shoes.
Don't do this.
We're almost there.
Gosh.
Hey, get up.
- We're almost there. - Let go of me.
I want to drink more.
- Come here. - I'm going to.
Don't go there. Come with me.
I want to drink more.
I want to drink more!
Gosh.
My goodness.
Are you okay?
What is this?
This is Dong Gu's camera.
Seo Jin, what should I do?
I broke Dong Gu's camera.
What should I do?
No.
Don't throw up here.
Go to the bathroom.
(My Love, Olivia)
Gosh, I'm feeling terrible.
My stomach aches.
Why did you drink so much?
Don't talk to me. I'm tired.
Soo Ah.
You drink too much.
Hello. Yes, detective.
Have you found that con man?
Not yet?
All right.
Gosh, he keeps telling me to wait.
They still haven't found that con man called Yoon Seok?
No.
Where could he be hiding?
Once he's caught, I'll...
Don't worry. He'll be caught soon.
Du Shik, are you all right?
Since Mal Geum left.
I'm all right.
It's a good opportunity for her.
I'm happy for her.
Also, I have to start writing Web fictions again.
I don't even have the time to think about her.
Web fictions? I thought you were finished.
But my fans have been begging me to write...
"President Is Bruce Lee Season 2".
Season 2?
Wasn't the story about the US president defeating aliens?
I wanted to take a little break,
but as a writer, I couldn't turn away from my fans' request.
I have to go to work now.
Season 2?
Open your mouth.
There you go.
You all seemed to drink last night, so I made dried pollack soup.
Really?
Gosh, that was nice.
Dong Gu, try the soup.
Okay. Thank you.
Here.
Are Seo Jin and Jun Ki still sleeping?
They seemed to drink a lot last night.
They fight all the time, but they seem to be inseparable.
Perhaps, they'll grow on each other.
What? Going out?
What awful idea is that?
Seo Jin is my precious sister.
She deserves much more than that good-for-nothing.
- What's so wrong about Jun Ki? - What?
I'm not saying he is a bad person.
But I know every single thing about him.
He is not good enough for my sister.
Don't say such an absurd thing again, okay?
Gosh.
My head aches.
What's going on? Why did you drink together last night?
Where and when did you finish?
Whatever.
Seo Jin, what time did we get home last night?
I blacked out. I don't remember everything.
I blacked out too. I remember only some parts.
You blacked out?
We started drinking soju around 7pm.
After that, we ordered some beer.
And then, we had noodles with sea snails.
We were going to finish with fish cake soup and makgeolli.
But the owner of the place...
gave us some tofu kimchi for free, so we ordered some more soju.
We started drinking soju and...
What? What did we do?
Hold on.
I want to drink more.
What is it? What's going on?
Did something happen between you two?
No, nothing happened.
What could have happened?
I'll go take a shower.
I want to get some more sleep.
Gosh, it wasn't a dream.
It really happened.
Dong Gu will go crazy when he finds out.
I must have been crazy.
Why?
Why did I kiss him?
Seo Jin.
Do you remember what happened last night?
Do you remember it too?
Of course, I do.
I can't believe it.
What should we do now?
Jun Ki, can we...
- just forget about it? - Forget?
How could we forget about it? It already happened.
Why can't we? It'll stay between only you and me.
- What if Dong Gu finds out? - What? Dong Gu?
How could he find out? He didn't see it.
Hey, there is no secret in this world.
What are you talking about?
No one saw it. If we stay quiet, no one will find out.
You think so?
Yes. So...
let's take it to our grave, okay?
Fine.
It really doesn't feel right.
Gosh, I must have been crazy.
Why did I kiss him?
I blame the alcohol.
Gosh.
Why did I break Dong Gu's camera?
I blame the alcohol. It's the alcohol's fault.
The president died while fighting with aliens in Season 1.
Should I revive him?
A zombie.
That's right. He becomes a zombie...
and stands up to the aliens again.
"President Is Bruce Lee".
"President Is a Zombie".
What a fantastic title.
I'm looking for a ramyeon brand.
Which one?
- That's the name. - What did you...
Oh, you mean that Thai ramyeon. It's sold out.
I see.
Gosh, I was craving it.
Soo Ah is already seeing another guy?
- What does he do? - He runs a Thai restaurant.
Hold on.
Thai...
He looked like Soo Ah's ex-boyfriend.
I'll kill him!
Did someone just pass by?
I think so.
"I'll kill him"?
Dong Gu, I'm sorry, but I have a class to go to.
Can you watch Sol?
Sure.
Thank you.
Sol, your mom has to leave.
- See you later. - Okay.
See you.
I should check the bookings.
Who knocked these over?
Gosh.
My goodness.
Hold on. Why is my camera on the floor?
What happened?
What is this?
What happened to my camera?
Who broke it?
You did it, didn't you?
No.
- It feels so refreshing. - Seo Jin!
Is it you?
You did this, didn't you?
What do you mean?
I haven't seen your camera.
What? It must be Du Shik.
Hello? Bong Du Shik.
Did you break my camera?
You didn't? Hang up.
Who did this to my camera?
When I catch him, I'll break his back in half.
My poor camera.
Who did this?
It doesn't work.
Why did I kiss Jun Ki?
Am I insane?
It's true that Jun Ki looked charming at the interview.
Still...
Why? Why?
My goodness.
- Seo Jin. - You startled me.
You should knock.
I'm sorry.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Seo Jin, let's tell Dong Gu...
about what happened last night.
What?
Why do you keep wanting to tell Dong Gu?
Didn't you see Dong Gu?
If Dong Gu finds out later, he'll be furious.
I'm so nervous.
How would Dong Gu find out?
Seo Jin, nothing stays as a secret in this world.
If he finds out that we didn't tell him,
he might seriously kill us.
Don't you know Dong Gu?
Let's confess to him.
Let's say that we confess.
Do you think...
Dong Gu would be understanding?
Once he finds out, you and I are done for.
What?
Why did we do that?
Just delete it from your memory.
No one will ever find out if we keep quiet.
Okay.
Why does he want to tell Dong Gu about our kiss?
Is he insane?
Will he not find out if we don't say anything?
Seo Jin is terrible.
How can she stay quiet after breaking her brother's camera?
I'm afraid to meet a woman like her.
Detective, will we catch him now that he's caught on...
surveillance camera?
I have to wait again?
Until when...
Hello? Sir?
Why does the police always tell me to wait?
I can't take it anymore.
What are you doing?
I'm going to be on the lookout by myself.
What? Can't I do that?
You can,
but won't he run away if you stay here like this?
Would he?
What should I do?
Gosh, the design looks so cheap.
What kind of uniform is this?
What do you expect from a part-time job uniform?
Until when will you be here?
Until I catch that jerk.
Why? Can't I?
You can.
I'll organize the stocks, so stay at the counter.
Okay.
Hello.
Give me a coke.
Also bring me a chocolate bar.
Pardon me? Why would I do that?
Do what the customer says. You talk too much.
What did you say?
Why are you ordering me around?
Did I upset you?
You're only a part-timer. How dare you be so rude?
What?
What did you just say?
Hey, stop it.
I'm sorry. I'll bring them right now.
That's better.
- Here you go, sir. - Okay.
Here you go.
Hey, don't throw it on the floor.
The trash can is over there.
Your pay includes cleaning.
Don't you know that?
What did you say?
Are you kidding me?
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry. It's her first day today.
Goodness.
I'll let it go for your sake.
Do your job properly.
Why you...
Thank you, sir.
What's wrong with you?
What did I do? He's the one who was wrong.
He's always like that. He owns a barbecue restaurant nearby.
It's better to avoid him.
Gosh, you're such a pushover.
Goodness.
Yoon Ah.
Hello.
Wait.
Why do you sound so down? Did something happen?
While everyone is doing so well,
I seem to be behind in class.
Don't worry so much.
You'll catch up if you practice.
I have nowhere else to practice but here.
Yoon Ah, do you have time today?
- Come in. - Okay.
Why are we at a bakery?
Hello, sir.
Is this your bakery?
Yes. Follow me, Yoon Ah.
Okay.
What is this place?
It's my workroom.
I create recipes.
I take naps without telling my employees.
I see.
Yoon Ah.
Can you make the donut that you made in class?
I'll help you.
Really?
(11,350 dollars)
Why is this camera so expensive?
I don't even have money for myself. Goodness.
Dong Gu, did you go somewhere?
I went to repair the camera.
They said that it's too broken to be repaired.
My poor Olivia.
Olivia?
Who's Olivia?
It's her name.
I cared about her more than my real sister.
I bought it after working at construction sites for a year.
I wiped and took care of her every day.
I was very fond of her.
Dong Gu.
Are you crying?
It's just that...
I feel sad and empty as if my sister died.
Olivia.
Why haven't they sent me the interview result?
Sol, did I not get the job again?
That can't be, right?
Seo Jin.
You startled me. What is it?
I think I have to tell the truth to Dong Gu.
What do you mean?
Dong Gu is crying right now.
Why is he crying?
What does his crying have to do with us?
Seo Jin.
Do you have conscience at all?
What do you mean?
What does conscience have to do with this?
Don't you feel guilty?
Don't you feel sorry to Dong Gu?
Why should I be sorry to Dong Gu?
How could you do this?
I can't even look at Dong Gu.
Jun Ki, what happened was...
a mistake that we made after drinking.
It's nothing to be guilty about.
You're unbelievable.
Don't you feel embarrassed in front of Sol?
I had no idea that you were so shameless.
Shameless?
Jun Ki, I think you're too upset right now.
Get some sleep.
You'll feel better after some sleep.
Okay?
Get some sleep.
It'll be okay, right?
Why are you laughing?
I'm laughing because I can't believe it.
The US president becomes a zombie...
and does martial arts? It makes no sense.
The US president is reborn as Bruce Lee.
It appears in Season One in detail.
Does it make sense?
Even I can write that.
Hey.
Until when will you stay here?
Until I catch that jerk.
I'm getting off work soon,
so get changed soon.
(Fat Barbecue Restaurant Owner)
- Yes, sir. - It's me.
Pour water in five cup noodles and bring them to the restaurant.
Pardon?
I'm just about to get off work.
Then you can drop them off on your way out.
- Hurry up. - Hello?
Hello? Sir. Sir. Sir?
Why? What is it this time?
He thinks I'm at his beck and call.
Sir. I've brought the five noodles you asked for.
Hey. What took you so long?
You should be quicker.
How much is it?
That'll be 4 dollars and 50 cents.
Here.
- Goodbye, sir. - Okay.
Soo Ah. Let's go.
Du Shik.
While we're here, why don't we eat some meat?
It's on me.
Why eat meat all of a sudden? Let's just go.
Hey. Wait. Hey.
Come here.
Why? Do you guys want some meat?
Bring two servings of pork and one bottle of soda now.
I want the meat cooked.
I don't feel like grilling it myself.
- What did you say? - Why? You don't want to?
If your customer asks for something, just do it.
You little brat, how dare you talk down to me?
Why? Does it upset you?
Aren't customers allowed to talk down to the employees?
What?
Hey. Why did you throw it away here?
The price of the meat includes cleaning service fees, right?
That's exactly what you said earlier.
You little brat. You must've lost your mind.
What did you say?
Brat?
Did you just call your dear customer a brat?
My goodness. The owner here treats his customers like trash.
What are you doing? What? What's wrong?
What did you just do?
Did you just hit me?
A frail girl like me?
I didn't hit you. I just grabbed your shoulder real gently.
What's wrong?
- Gosh. - Look at this.
Look at how my arm's dangling.
My shoulder must be broken.
- All of a sudden? - Du Shik. Report him to the police.
- The police? - I'm in so much pain.
Why are you doing this? Please stop.
Oh, dear.
Hey, hey. Oh, dear.
Mommy.
What's keeping you? Hurry up.
It hurts again. I don't think I can handle it.
Du Shik. Hurry up and call the police.
I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry?"
That's it?
Please forgive me.
You should say it to him too.
What are you doing? Hurry up and say it.
Please forgive me.
Please forgive me for my actions.
That's all right.
- Hey, mister. - Yes?
He may seem like a fool,
but his mother ate seaweed soup after giving birth to him...
and celebrated. Do you know that?
So you have no right to talk down to him.
He's not your slave that you can look down on and boss around.
If I catch you treating him that way again,
I don't know what I might do to you.
- Do you understand me? - Yes.
By the way, how's your shoulder?
- I feel fine now. - Pardon?
You can give my medical expenses to your staff as a bonus.
Du Shik. Let's go.
All right.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye. - What are you doing? Let's go.
Soo Ah. Gosh.
You were amazing.
I feel like I got something off my chest thanks to you.
So if you see someone take advantage...
or give weaker people a hard time, don't let them get away with it.
If you do, they'll think it's okay to treat others like that.
You'll only become a pushover.
All right. I won't.
Why is my bag so heavy?
Hey. Carry my bag.
- What? - What are you doing?
Carry my bag for me.
It's heavy. Hurry and take it.
Oh, dear. It hurts. It hurts. It hurts so bad.
Putting on a complete act has gotten me hungry.
Hey. Go buy me some tteokbokki.
- What? - What are you doing?
I told you I'm hungry.
I'm hungry. I'm so hungry.
Okay, okay. All right.
I'll get you tteokbokki.
Wait a minute.
Soo Ah. Aren't you taking advantage of me right now?
How could there be such a thing between friends?
I'm asking you a favor. It's a favor.
What are you waiting for? Go and buy some.
Move.
- Move it. - All right.
It tastes...
great.
- Really? - Yes. It's really delicious.
You see? I said you could do it with a little practice.
Thank you.
I owe it all to you, Hyung Joon.
Yoon Ah. Why do you want to become a pastry chef?
Well...
This is a little embarrassing,
but I'm a bit sloppy,
and I always make careless mistakes.
But for the first time, I was praised.
People said the bread I baked was good.
I thought this might be the only thing I could be good at.
I'm going to work hard and make sure I succeed.
I'm going to open a large bakery like yours.
I want to let Sol...
do whatever she wants.
I see.
Yoon Ah. From now on, when you get the time,
come here to practice.
I'll tell my staff that you'll be coming.
Really?
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
What's that sound?
What on earth is this?
It's me. It's Olivia.
Olivia?
Olivia is...
You're Dong Gu's camera?
You don't know how much my owner cared for me.
You ruined everything.
This is all your fault.
It's all your fault.
I'm sorry.
- I didn't do it on purpose. - I don't want to hear it.
How long did you think you'd be able to hide the truth?
I was going to tell him,
- but Seo Jin... - Don't make excuses.
You didn't end up telling him either.
I can't forgive you.
I won't forgive you.
Blood, blood, blood.
This isn't right. I was wrong.
This isn't right.
Seo Jin. Seo Jin, wake up.
Seo Jin, wake up. Seo Jin.
Why? What is it now?
Olivia.
She was in my room.
Who's Olivia?
She was shedding tears of blood. Dong Gu's...
What on earth are you talking about?
I can't go on living like this.
I think we'll have to tell Dong Gu the truth.
Jun Ki. Wait. Why are you doing this?
Why do you keep insisting on telling that to Dong Gu?
That way, I think I can move on.
Olivia. Olivia.
Jun Ki. Jun Ki.
Gosh. What's wrong with him?
I can't imagine how painful it must've been.
Dong Gu. There's something I need to confess to you.
What is it?
To tell you the truth, Seo Jin and I...
- Well, you see... - Wait a minute. Wait.
What's wrong with you? Are you crazy?
Are you really going to act like this?
How much longer are you going to hide this from him?
Don't you feel bad for him? How much longer are you going to lie to him?
If you keep acting this way,
she'll eventually come to you.
Olivia.
- Olivia will... - What are you talking about?
What on earth you talking about?
What is it?
Seo Jin. You tell him.
This is your last chance to repent.
Gosh. You're driving me crazy.
Why on earth do we have to tell him? Why does he have to know?
Seo Jin. Are you really going to continue acting this way?
All right. I'll tell him. Are you satisfied?
This is driving me insane.
What are you two doing?
I don't understand why I have to tell my brother this.
Go ahead and say it.
- Dong Gu. Actually... - Yes?
Yesterday, after having some drinks...
We drank a bit.
Go on.
Jun Ki and I...
What is it? Why is it taking you so long?
We kissed.
Yes. She and I kissed yesterday.
What?
What are you talking about?
Why would I do that with you?
Weren't you talking about the kiss?
What are you talking about?
I was talking about how we broke Dong Gu's camera yesterday.
What?
Wait a moment.
So to sum it up,
you drank together yesterday...
and broke my camera.
No! No!
Before that,
you drank together...
and kissed.
Kiss? You two?
Is it true? Is it?
Dong Gu, it...
It was a mistake.
A mistake?
Dong Gu,
calm down.
Calm down?
How can I calm myself down right now?
Come here.
Come here!
What are you doing?
What are you doing inside the room?
Open the door!
Open it!
- Kang Seo Jin, open the door! - Dong Gu!
- Please calm down. - Open the door!
- Dong Gu, calm down. - Open it!
Think rationally.
Open it!
I...
What happened? Why did it get so quiet?
Is he gone?
- Oh, my. - Gosh, I thought I was dead.
Chewbacca,
did we really kiss?
Did we really do it?
Yes.
Why did you tell him that?
You told me to tell him.
You said that it was the last chance and that I should tell the truth.
I thought you were talking about the camera.
Gosh!
Wait a moment.
- Seo Jin. - Yes?
Did you make me drink alcohol on purpose?
What? Are you out of your mind?
- Why would I do that? - You!
Come here! Come over here!
Come here!
Hey!
- Dong Gu. - Shut it!
How dare you?
Kiss?
My head hurts.
Dong Gu, it was a mistake.
I must have gone crazy because of the drinks.
Even if I don't have a boyfriend,
he's not my type.
What?
I don't like you either with your outbursts and beard.
- What? Do you want to die? - Gosh.
Shut it!
You shouldn't be within 5m from each other now on.
Don't even look at each other,
talk to each other, or think about each other. Okay?
All right.
Okay.
What are you doing? Move!
Move away from each other now!
- Now! - Move!
Quickly! Move!
I'm stressed out as it is. They're making it worse.
Dong Gu, give that to me.
It's fine. I'll do it.
Just give it to me.
I'll do it.
Don't mind me. Just take care of your business.
- All right. - All right.
Dong Gu.
Are you angry at me?
You won't even talk to me nowadays.
What? I did talk to you.
It's nothing like that.
That's good.
I'll go downstairs and prepare dinner.
- Sure. You do that. - Okay.
What are you doing there?
Nothing.
What is that?
This?
It helps calm down my swollen eyes. It's a must-have for models.
My eyes swelled up after staying at the store the past few days.
Really?
Why are you sighing so much?
What's wrong?
Is it because of Yoon Ah?
I...
wanted to stop, but I can't stop liking her.
Soo Ah,
I like her more and more.
Why do you like her so much?
I don't know.
I don't know what I like about her, nor why I like her.
("A Simple Confession")
I don't know what to do.
I can't come up with answers.
I only have part time jobs on babies' first birthday parties.
I can't even take care of her.
("Three Idiots", "If Only")
Can I really become a movie director?
It might just end as a dream.
Dong Gu.
Long time no see.
- I haven't seen you in a while. - Hello, Director.
What do you do these days?
Not much. How about you?
I'm filming a movie.
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
I'm recruiting staff members.
Do you want to work for my team?
Me?
- I'll think about it. - All right.
- Bye. - Bye.
Gosh, we are in deficit again.
We might even lose our house now.
I know. It's a problem.
I'm here.
- Hello. - Hello.
How did the filming go?
It was good.
Why are you sighing?
Did something go wrong?
I met...
a director I used to work with on my way home.
- And? - He asked me...
if I wanted to work for his team.
So? Are you going to do it?
I told him that I'd think about it.
What is there to think about?
You're not going to earn much. You won't get to sleep at night,
nor be able to come home. You'll suffer.
What about the store then?
We might not be able to pay for the rent soon.
You can't do it.
I didn't say I'd do it. I only said I'll think about it.
I wasn't serious.
Hello?
Yes, it's Kang Seo Jin.
What?
All right. Thank you.
What? What was it about?
Did something happen again?
No, it was the newspaper company that I interviewed for.
I passed the final screening.
They told me to start working tomorrow.
- Really? - Yes.
I'm not in a dream, right?
Why did you pinch me?
It's not a dream. Did I really get in?
- Oh, my. - Oh my goodness.
- Gosh. - Good job. I'm proud of you.
What's this about?
Seo Jin got the job.
She'll start working tomorrow.
Really?
Congratulations, Chewbacca! Congratulations!
Don't come near her. I told you to keep the distance.
All right. Shut it.
Congratulations, Chewbacca. You'll buy us something, right?
Of course.
- Yes! - Congratulations.
You'll be a probationary employee for three weeks.
The entertainment department is shorthanded,
so you'll be working there.
Here is...
your seat right here. Good luck.
Thank you.
No, I need to say hello first.
Hello, I'm Kang Seo Jin. I'm new here!
I'll do my best!
Everyone must be busy.
Who are you?
I'm Kang Seo Jin, the new trainee.
- You're the new trainee? - Yes.
Nice to meet you.
But what are you doing? Why aren't you working?
Sorry?
I'm not sure what I'm supposed to do.
Give me any task, and I'll do my best.
Have you heard of "Mask Singer"?
There's one singer whose identity has been unknown for seven weeks.
Everyone is trying so hard to find out.
- I see. - You find it out.
Sorry?
Find out who Blushing Webfoot Octopus is.
How could I...
You said you'd do your best whatever task is given to you.
So find it out.
Also, don't forget to take a picture of their face.
It's important.
- Understood? - Yes.
How will I find it out?
My goodness.
Is it here?
All right.
Excuse me, is this where they film "Mask Singer"?
Yes. Who are you?
I'm a reporter.
I'm here for a news story. Please let me in.
Hold on. Where are you going?
It's not open to the public.
I'm a reporter. A reporter.
You can't enter.
I'm not even letting the president in. Please go back.
What?
Do you not respect the public's right to know?
If you don't let me in, I don't know what I might do.
Did you just laugh?
Let go of me. Let go.
Respect the public's right to know.
Just go back, okay?
Gosh, I can't believe him.
Hey!
What should I do?
How can you do this to me?
What is this?
- You look great. - That voice sounds familiar.
It suits you perfectly.
Gosh. I can't wear a costume like this.
What's going on?
You said it was a drama.
It is.
- A children's drama. - What?
Fine, let's say so.
But you said I'd play opposite the lead character.
You will.
The lead character is Aqua Man.
As the evil octopus, you'll be defeated by him.
It means you'll play opposite the lead character.
You deceived me.
- Excuse me. - What?
I knew it. It was you.
What's with that costume?
- Are you a webfoot octopus? - I'm an octopus.
A webfoot octopus has smaller suckers.
- What are you doing here? - Me?
I'm here for a news article.
You already get to write an article?
That's impressive, Chewbacca.
Stop calling me that.
By the way, do you know who Blushing Webfoot Octopus...
on "Mask Singer" is?
- Blushing Webfoot Octopus? - Yes.
How would I know?
Why are you asking?
I was ordered to find out.
It won't be easy.
They maintain tight security.
- Not even producers can find out. - Really?
I even have to take a picture of the person. I'm in trouble.
I don't care about Blushing Webfoot Octopus.
What are you going to do now?
What do you think?
You're all dressed now. Let's start shooting.
Follow me.
- Where are you going? - Hurry.
Wait!
He is never of help.
Why did I kiss him?
I blame the alcohol.
By the way, how will I find out who Blushing Webfoot Octopus is?
The shooting is done.
You're back. Have a seat.
Do you have something to tell me?
Someone requested us to edit a video of his child growing up.
Do you want to work on it?
Me?
Can I do everything the way I want?
Yes. All the materials...
have been uploaded. Feel free to download and use them.
I trust you'll do a good job.
It'll be like a beautiful movie.
You'll be surprised.
I haven't worked on a storyboard in a long time.
It reminds me of the old days when I used to make short films.
This is exciting.
I think I need to shoot some more.
What should I do?
You must be tired.
It's for you.
Thank you.
Let me go in now.
No.
Please sir.
Here. Are you happy now?
Thank you.
I'm going in.
No.
Please sir.
Sir.
Please.
Let me go in just once.
I really have to find out.
I'm begging you.
If you show up here again, I'll call the police.
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
What should I do?
Where am I? Where am I?
Here I am.
It's not working.
I can't shoot like this.
I know what I should do.
Are you happy?
You look so happy.
I'm sorry you had to come.
He was crying too much, so I couldn't shoot.
Don't worry. You're shooting something?
What are you shooting?
I need some clips for the baby's growth footage.
Speaking of which,
can you help me out?
Me?
What can I do?
Well...
Am I supposed to stay like this?
Yes. Stay still like that.
Do I have to wear this costume?
Yes, it'll make it easier to remove you from the video.
Please hang in there.
It won't take long. Ready.
Action.
- Good. - Good boy.
- You're doing great. - We're almost done.
Cut!
Good job!
Yoon Ah, you did a great job.
Are we done?
It's a bit out of focus.
Ready, action.
All right. Yoon Ah.
Higher.
- Like this? - Yes.
Look at me. Nice facial expression.
You're doing great. Look at me. Cut!
Cut!
Good job.
Yoon Ah, you did an amazing job.
Let's try one more time.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
How long do I have to play these roles?
An octopus ink gun?
What a pretentious name.
I couldn't pee well because of these tentacles.
- Go, Korea! - Go, Korea!
- We meet again. - I know.
What a coincidence.
Your costume...
I've been cast for the children's drama, "Super Aqua Man".
I'm Blue Crab Man.
- Really? - Yes.
I'll be on that show too.
I'm Octopus Man.
Now that we met,
why don't we have some octopus and soju together tonight?
- Sounds good. - Good.
Let's go.
After you.
What is this on my first day?
I thought everything would work out once I got a job.
Hey, trainee.
What are you doing here?
Ma'am.
Have you found out who Blushing Webfoot Octopus is?
Not yet.
Their security is too tight.
Are you asking me to cut you some slack?
No.
- That's Seo Jin. - Hey.
Are you sure you can work as a reporter?
Even if their security is tight,
you're supposed to find it out by all means.
How did you even get into the company?
- I'm sorry. - Cut it out.
You're not allowed to come back to the office until you find out.
If you fail to find out,
just quit. Do you understand?
Yes.
I can't believe that woman.
Do you know that girl?
- Blue Crab Man. - Yes?
Please do me a favor.
Blue Crab Man, are you ready?
Okay.
Hey!
- What do you know about crabs? - What is it now?
Hey, who are you?
I'm...
- Okay. - Protecting peace, I'm righteous...
Blue Crab Man.
How dare he...
Try to catch me.
- Hey, you. - Gosh.
Octopus Man, it's time.
Let me go.
Take my octopus ink.
Go ahead, Octopus Man.
- Take care of the rest. - Hurry.
(King of Kings)
Let's see.
"Scallop"?
What, "spoon worm"?
"Sea squirt" and "spoon worm"?
(Is It Sea Squirt)
Is it some seafood special?
Where's Webfoot Octopus?
Webfoot Octopus.
"Blushing Webfoot Octopus"? I found it.
There he is.
You startled me.
Who are you?
Hello.
Are you Blushing Webfoot Octopus?
You've been winning for seven weeks.
Yes, but who are you?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm the villain who fights against Aqua Man.
I'm Octopus Man, Lee Jun Ki.
What is your name?
Pardon? Why do you ask?
I'm Octopus, you're Webfoot Octopus.
We should be acquainted since we're both octopus.
I can't tell you. It's a secret.
Come on, we're the same type.
I told you my name.
Isn't it polite to tell me yours?
I can't tell you.
Hey.
How could you?
I wasn't going to do this, but I can't help it.
Come here.
No.
What are you doing?
Gosh.
My leg.
You're a murderer.
Who are you? Security?
Why aren't they coming? Goodness.
What are you?
Nice, Blue Crab Man.
Gosh, come here.
Hold him down.
Octopus Man, it's time.
Take it off.
What are you doing?
You're embarrassing yourself by crying in front of people.
Just leave. I'm not in the mood for jokes.
I wanted to tell you who the Mask Singer is.
I'll leave then.
Wait, really?
How did you find out?
It's thanks to Blue Crab Man's sacrifice.
- What? - You told me to leave.
- See you. - Jun Ki.
You can't just leave.
You're so mean.
What's this?
Blushing Webfoot Octopus is Kang Kyun Sung.
I attach a photo of him.
- Come here. - Hey.
Were you Blushing Webfoot Octopus?
I'm your fan.
Jun Ki.
Hey.
Don't be so sad.
Don't let your senior get you down.
You're good at being bold.
Seo Jin.
You can do it.
You can do it!
I'm busy.
I'm leaving.
- I'm home. - Hello.
Hello, Sol.
Why are you coming home together?
Yoon Ah helped me with my shoot today.
Du Shik, I'll take Sol. I'll take care of her.
Okay, let's go to your mom.
Sol, did you have fun?
Have you been well?
Yoon Ah, thank you for your hard work today.
Don't mention it.
Aren't you hungry? I'll prepare dinner.
I'm okay.
I have to edit, so I won't have time to eat.
- Dong Gu. - Did you sleep well?
What's going on?
Did you work all night?
I couldn't sleep because I wanted to finish it.
I worked all night and finished editing.
- Really? - Yes.
Okay, it's done.
I'm going to the studio.
Hello.
What are you doing?
I told you to quit...
if you don't find out who the Mask Singer is.
- Here you go. - Let's see what you took.
You didn't take a photo of a real webfoot octopus, right?
Let's see.
What?
Did you really take it? How?
Octopus told me.
- What Octopus? - Usually...
he's quite silly.
Sometimes he's amazing.
My goodness.
Soo Ah.
Until when will you wait at the convenience store?
Until I catch that jerk.
What? My nose bled today because of you.
Is this how you treat me when I got rid of that bossy man?
You're not loyal at all.
You're worse than him. You're the queen of bosses.
- What did you say? - I take it back.
I'm home.
Hello, Dong Gu. What happened?
It was a complete failure.
He said that it was terrible and called me insane.
What do you mean? Did something happen?
I made a video of the baby growing up,
but my boss hated it.
How did you make it?
Will you be the judge?
(Birth of Hyun Ah)
Dong Gu, what are those?
They're sperm.
What?
Why would there be sperm in the video?
The introduction...
shows the birth of life.
Sperms swim and meet an egg.
Then a baby is born.
Isn't it realistic and original?
It's original indeed,
but I wonder if this is necessary.
Really?
The next scene is amazing. Take a look.
(Hyun Ah is born.)
Gosh.
What's that?
Why did a baby pop out of that?
Don't you know "The Matrix"?
The baby grew in her mom's belly for 10 months.
Then she cries.
It's a dynamic scene of a baby being born.
Isn't it too bizarre?
Don't you get immersed in it as the baby appears like this?
Isn't it just like a movie?
Next scene is like...
the jump scene from "Whispering Corridors".
The baby jumps from here and there.
I think that's enough.
I'm tired. I'm going to sleep.
Thanks for "The Matrix".
What's wrong?
Dong Gu, do you have to become a movie director?
What do you mean?
I'm worried about your movies...
being shown to the world.
Hey, it isn't over yet.
Watch the rest.
I liked your video. It's like a movie.
I mean it.
It's fine.
Cheer up, Dong Gu.
I want to, but I can't.
I'm just worried that I'll just end up filming...
birthday footage for the rest of my life.
I'm worried that I'll never make it to the movies.
Then you can start now.
Start in the movie industry.
You said you got an offer.
- That's... - I've never seen you that happy.
I thought you were someone...
who frowned, got irritated and angry every day.
But when I saw you filming yesterday,
I realized that you could smile so brightly like that.
I realized that you must really...
love your job.
Did I do that?
So, Dong Gu,
don't be afraid. Start over.
That's not as easy as it sounds.
Gosh.
I didn't take you for a coward.
- What? - If you can't do what you like...
because you're worried of this and that,
would your life be happy?
Won't you regret it later?
What's wrong with failing and stumbling?
You can start over,
right?
Oh, my.
I must have sounded too nosy.
I'm sorry.
Dong Gu, I'm done with housekeeping.
I'll go and practice baking.
Sure.
Cheer up, Dong Gu!
Cheer up! Yes!
Sir.
Hello, Dong Gu.
Why are you here?
I want to work for the directing team...
that you talked about.
I'll do my best.
Hey, Dong Gu.
Soo Ah, where have you been?
I came out for fresh air after staying at the convenience store.
Why are you so happy?
Did something good happen?
I'm going to start working for the movie industry.
I'm going to try no matter what.
Really? Congratulations.
And I found out why I like Yoon Ah.
Really? What is it?
I just like her without reason.
I just like her.
What does that even mean?
How about her situation and Sol?
I'm not sure about that,
but there's one thing I'm sure about.
If I lose Yoon Ah while considering all conditions,
I will never be happy.
I will regret for the rest of my life.
That's why I want to ask her out.
Really? When?
Now.
Take care.
I'm sorry. You don't need to get me home every day like this.
It's fine. It's on my way home.
It's cold. You should go.
See you on the next class.
My phone...
I must have left it in his car.
Dong Gu.
Yoon Ah, I want to tell you something.
What? What is it?
I like you.
I really like you, Yoon Ah.
(Thank you to special guest, Kang Kyun Sung.)
(Welcome to Waikiki)