What are you looking at for so long?
Seo Jin. You should take a look at this too.
What do you think of this place?
"Guesthouse Boulanger"?
What's this about all of a sudden?
Well, it's almost spring.
I think we should make some changes to our interior.
So I'm doing some research on places we can use as reference.
Isn't this place nice?
The interior design is nice, and I like the vibe.
The owner even serves homemade bread.
- Really? - Yes.
Even the service is great.
Dong Gu. I need to go somewhere. I'll be back soon.
Right now? Where are you going this late at night?
There's just something I need to do.
- All right. See you later. - Okay.
Yes, Jun Ki. I'm here.
Where are you?
Seo Jin. It's me.
Why did you do that? You startled me.
Come in. Come in.
Come over here. Come here.
By the way,
are you sure you're not being followed? Where is Dong Gu?
He's at home.
You're overreacting.
I'm not.
Dong Gu has been watching us even more closely lately.
We can't go on dates freely,
and I can't tell anyone I have a boyfriend.
What is this?
We have no choice.
But I have no shooting this weekend.
Should we go on a date?
Really? You have no shooting?
I'm finally free this weekend too.
Why don't we go on a trip?
- A trip? - Yes.
We could go on an overnight trip somewhere nearby.
Isn't it too early for us to go on an overnight trip?
What are you thinking about?
We're going to sleep in separate rooms. Are you crazy?
Okay.
All right. Let's do it.
Let's go on a trip.
Let's do it. Let's go.
Hide!
Darn it. I lost her again.
She disappeared somewhere around here.
Something definitely is going on.
Kang Seo Jin and Lee Jun Ki.
I'll catch you guys by all means.
(Hide-and-Seek)
Hurry up. Clean every corner.
We don't even have many guests these days.
Why do we have to clean so often?
- Gosh. - Exactly.
The weather is getting warm. I'd love to go somewhere...
and get some good rest.
Don't be absurd.
We don't have money for that.
Go back to cleaning.
Hi, Hyun Joon.
I haven't been able to ask them yet.
But I don't think I can go.
I'm sorry. Bye.
What is it? Where were you going?
Well...
My baking class is going on a trip.
But I have to take care of Sol and work at the guesthouse,
so I told him I can't go.
Why? Just go.
Go with the rest of your class.
You can go. We'll take care of Sol.
When is the trip?
This Saturday. It's an overnight trip.
What? An overnight trip?
She'll be with Hyun Joon...
over the night?
She shouldn't. That's not okay.
Wait!
Too bad.
The trip just overlaps...
with our workshop.
Are we having a workshop?
Yes.
We've been so busy doing the laundry, dishes,
and cleaning.
So I was planning an overnight workshop.
Since when? You said we didn't have money.
What?
I was acting. I wanted to surprise you guys.
It's a surprise.
Anyway, Yoon Ah,
I'm afraid you won't be able to go on that trip.
Don't worry. It's no problem.
Okay. Do you all have time this weekend?
Hold on.
This weekend?
I can't.
Why? Do you have plans?
Well...
I'll spend the night covering a news story.
I see.
I can't either.
I'll be shooting all night this weekend.
What? You both will be...
working all night this weekend?
- It's true. - It's true.
I see.
What exactly is this news story you have to cover?
What? Well...
It's about a funeral.
What? A funeral?
The weekend is still a few days away.
How do you know when that person will die?
- It doesn't make sense. - What?
Well...
He is in a critical condition right now.
- Poor man. - It's very likely that...
he'll die this weekend. My boss wants me to stand by.
- Is that right? - Yes.
Can I call your boss and ask?
What?
There he goes again.
Fine. Do it.
- Call him right now. - Don't, don't!
Are you sure?
I'm calling him now.
Push the button right now.
Ask him.
I'm pushing it.
I'm pushing the call button right now.
Okay. That's enough.
Fine. I trust you.
But the rest of you have to go, okay?
- Okay. - Du Shik and I need to take...
some pictures for our shopping mall this weekend.
You can do that during the workshop.
Anyway, we're leaving this Saturday morning.
It's decided. End of discussion.
- Okay. - Go back to cleaning now.
Let's clean!
Hurry up!
Come downstairs.
Dong Gu, we haven't been on a trip in so long.
I was so excited I couldn't sleep well last night.
Are you that happy?
Yes. Yoon Ah, where is Sol?
She's sleeping.
I want her to sleep some more before we leave.
That's a good idea.
Hey. Are you moving abroad?
What's all that?
What do you think? It's the clothes I need for the photoshoot.
All of it?
Are you sure you need so many clothes?
Whose fault is it?
Who is forcing me to go on this trip?
You should, of course, bring them all.
Pack some more. Pack everything.
Are you leaving? Have a good time.
- Are you going to work? - Yes.
Why are you wearing a backpack to work?
Well...
I'll be working all night, so there was a lot to pack.
I wish you could come with us.
I know.
I'd love to come with you,
but I really need to work.
Seo Jin.
If you hang out with Jun Ki while I'm away,
what will happen?
"You will no longer be alive."
Is that what you were going to say?
Fine. I'll keep a 500m distance...
from Jun Ki at all times. Are you happy now?
Great. You can go now.
Sol must be up. I'll bring her.
Okay. Bring her.
(Hyun Joon)
Why is he calling her now?
Hello. It's me, Dong Gu.
Yoon Ah can't talk right now.
What's the matter?
I heard you're having a workshop today.
I just wanted to wish Yoon Ah a good time.
Don't worry.
Yoon Ah will have a great time with us.
You have a good time on your trip too.
We have to leave now.
I hung up while he was talking.
Jun Ki, I'm here.
What? Where?
3 o'clock?
Where are you?
Gosh.
- You startled me. - Get in before anyone sees us.
Oh, right. Remove the cover first. Hurry.
My goodness.
Are we on a date or a mission?
I can't really tell.
Give me your bag.
Is this really necessary?
There's nothing wrong with being careful.
What's this smell?
Something smells weird in here.
I don't know. It smelled like this since Du Shik and Soo Ah...
practiced driving with this car.
Anyway, our first trip starts now.
Seo Jin, are you okay?
I'm all right.
When you get some money, change your car first.
Why? Rebecca is still going strong.
Look. Rebecca, you're still okay, right?
See? She is okay. She's upset.
Let's go. Our trip starts now.
What is it?
- Are you sure everything is okay? - Rebecca!
The weather is lovely. And the view is so nice.
I'm so happy to be with you.
Even the evil Dong Gu is away. It couldn't be better than this.
I know.
It must be that place.
- We're here. - We are.
Let me park the car.
This is nice.
Let's go.
This place looks amazing.
It's called "Boulanger"? Even the name is pretty.
How did you find this place?
Dong Gu found it while searching for places...
with nice interior designs.
It looked so pretty, so I wanted to come.
With you.
Look at you, Bacca.
You wanted to come here with me?
Stop it.
- Should we go in? - Sure.
Princess, get on my back.
- Okay. - Let's go.
I can't live without Bacca
- Are you happy? - Of course.
Director Bong, are you okay?
I'm not sure.
I'm so nauseous.
The ride wasn't that long.
Stop nagging, and tap my back.
You're a nuisance.
Hey, be gentle.
- I might throw up my organs. - Fine.
What? "Guesthouse Boulanger"?
Are we staying at a guesthouse?
Yes, so what?
Why would we stay at a guesthouse when we work at one?
A resort would have been nice.
Do you know how much a resort costs?
The interior design is pretty,
so I wanted to take a look.
What do you think, Yoon Ah?
It's beautiful.
Let's go up.
Du Shik, let's go.
Come on.
What are you doing? Once you're done, get my luggage.
I'm really nauseous right now. You carry it.
I'm the boss. Do I have to do that?
Stop complaining, and bring it.
She's such an evil boss.
Let's see.
I need to look pretty for Jun Ki.
Shall I put on some makeup to look sexy?
Soo Ah, this is the women's room.
- You're right. - What?
That voice sounds familiar.
Isn't this great, Sol?
Darn it.
The room is well-decorated.
It is. It's nice and cozy.
There's someone else in here.
Is she sleeping?
- Let's unpack first. - Shall we?
This is great.
- How did they get here? - This is good.
What happened?
Goodness.
I'm tired from a long drive.
It's my first trip with Bacca.
I'm going to have fun.
Du Shik, it's over here.
Really?
Gosh, I'm so nauseous.
What?
The voice sounds unpleasant.
Do you need help?
Why did she pack so much?
The room is big and clean.
- Don't you think? - I don't know.
I feel sick, so don't make me talk.
There's someone else here.
Is he sleeping?
How did they get here?
Why?
Let's unpack later.
Let's take a look around.
I want to rest.
Come on, we came all the way here.
Let's go.
- I feel nauseous. - Let's go.
- No. - Come on.
What? Why are they here?
Are they having their workshop here?
This is unbelievable.
Wait, what about Seo Jin?
Yoon Ah, Soo Ah.
Unpack later, and come out.
Okay, we're coming.
- Shall we go, Yoon Ah? - Shall we?
Sol, let's take a look.
- Let's go with Mom. - Let's go.
Did they come here for their workshop?
I can't believe this.
Gosh, I should go see Jun Ki.
There's a swimming pool. Did you bring your swimsuits?
Gosh, it's amazing here.
- Isn't it amazing? - Yes.
- Hello. - Here are some towels.
- Thank you. - Let me know if you need anything.
Okay, thank you.
The guesthouse is beautiful.
Thank you.
Do you manage this big guesthouse alone?
I didn't see any staff.
It's expensive to hire people, so I run it with my wife.
Actually, we also run a guesthouse in Seoul.
Is that so?
Are you staying at a guesthouse when you run a guesthouse?
Pardon? Yes.
Then why did you make a reservation at the last minute?
Thankfully, the rooms were still available...
Aren't you busy?
- You should go and work. - Okay.
Call me if you need anything.
He's a talkative one, indeed.
Anyway, you worked hard to clean...
and do laundry.
You also worked hard to serve the guests.
Forget about the guesthouse,
and let's have fun, okay?
What shall we do?
I'm sorry, but I'll rest because I feel nauseous.
I'm about to faint.
Okay then.
Let's go back in.
I'll walk you.
Jun Ki? Jun Ki?
Gosh, where did he go?
Du Shik, are you sleeping?
Gosh, what is this?
Come on.
Lie down.
- Thank you. - Get some sleep.
I'll wake you up when we eat.
I'll join you in a little while.
Don't worry about me, and have fun.
Okay.
Call me if you need anything.
- Okay. - Okay.
Goodness.
He's sleeping for a long time.
Seo Jin? Seo Jin?
Where did she go?
Let's eat, Sol.
- It's time to eat. - What?
Mom will feed you. Good girl.
Were you hungry? I'll feed you.
Hold on a bit. Let's see.
What?
Where did it go?
Why? Did something disappear?
My camera disappeared.
I definitely put it here.
What if you put it somewhere else?
No, I definitely left it here.
Where did it go?
Excuse me? I'm sorry to bother you.
Have you seen a camera here?
When we were gone,
did someone else come by?
Go.
She's being suspicious.
Excuse me, shouldn't you respond when someone asks you a question?
How dare you?
What? Jun Ki.
Dong Gu. Why are you here?
What? Soo Ah.
You're here too.
What brings you here?
We came for the workshop. Why are you here?
- Didn't you have a shoot? - What?
Well...
I have an outdoor shoot nearby today and tomorrow.
The waiting time was so long.
I got a room, and I was sleeping.
Why are you sleeping in the women's room?
What? Is this the women's room?
I came where the host told me to.
Gosh, what was he thinking?
I should file a complaint.
He must've gotten it confused because he runs it alone.
- There's your camera. - Where?
I found it.
You didn't even look properly.
Thank you.
I can't believe that you're here.
Let's go.
I didn't imagine I'd see you here.
- What a coincidence. - I know.
It's such a terrible coincidence.
If Seo Jin didn't have work, all of us would be here.
That's unfortunate.
Right, you're right.
It can't be helped. Isn't the view beautiful?
How could there be a guesthouse at a place like this?
What? Why is there a rope?
I didn't see it before.
Is this a bell?
Sir!
Are you okay?
I'm so sorry.
I was cleaning. Why did you pull the rope?
- He's such a troublemaker. - Gosh, I'm so sorry.
- Shall I take you to the hospital? - It's okay.
A group of guests is coming soon. What should I do?
I have to clean and get groceries.
I'm sorry.
Let me ask you for a favor.
What favor?
Nice going.
You told us to forget the guesthouse and have fun.
What's this?
What else could I do? He got injured because of me.
It's fine for us,
but you dragged Yoon Ah from her baking class orientation.
Good job, Dong Gu.
I'm sorry, Yoon Ah.
It's okay. It's nice to fold towels where the air is fresh.
It's easier to fold them.
We only have to do this until he returns from the hospital.
- Hang in there. - Okay.
It's the owner.
Hello?
Pardon?
All right.
I see.
What is it? What did he say?
Well, he says he's going to take longer than expected.
He asked us to take good care of the arriving guests,
and he wants us to do the grocery shopping.
I can't believe this. This is so annoying.
I'm sorry. I'll go do the grocery shopping.
Could you guys just take care of the cleaning here?
Will you be all right on your own?
You'll probably have a lot to buy.
Then you two go together. We'll take care of Sol.
Right, Jun Ki?
Yes, all right.
Then I'll leave Sol with you guys.
Mommy will be back soon, all right?
- Let's go, Dong Gu. - All right. Let's go.
- See you later. - All right.
I'm sorry.
Why do you seem so agitated?
Why do you keep groaning? Is something wrong?
What? No, nothing's wrong.
Jun Ki. Help me.
I'm locked in the boys' room.
Why is she in the boys' room?
Since I'm done mopping the floor here...
I'll go change the bed sheets in the males' rooms.
All right.
Jun Ki.
- Du Shik. - What? Why are you here?
Didn't you say you had a shoot today?
Well, you see,
the set is close by,
so I booked a room here.
Really?
I can't believe this. What a coincidence.
You're right.
I'm so surprised that I think I'm going to cry.
Why are you staying in bed when you came all the way here?
Let's go outside, Du Shik.
I don't feel like it. I was carsick.
I feel nauseous and dizzy.
Then that gives you more reason to get some fresh air.
Why don't you and I go for a walk?
I'm tired. I don't feel like it.
Then get some sleep.
- I'm not sleepy. - Just close your eyes then.
I don't want to. I have a game to play.
Why are you just staying in this room?
Because I want to. Why are you getting angry?
What?
That's because I'm worried about you.
I'm worried about you.
Since when did you start worrying about me so much?
Never mind. I need to play this game, so don't talk to me.
Gosh. You're no help.
Jun Ki. What's keeping you? We have a guest.
- Hurry and come out. - All right. I'll be right there.
Anyway, don't you dare move.
Stay here just a while.
I'll find a way to get you out of here.
You trust me, right? Wait just a while.
I'll be right back, all right?
What's wrong with him?
Why is he trying to get me out of here when I said I'm dizzy?
What do we have to buy?
They said a group of guests want to have a BBQ party for dinner.
- Shall we buy the vegetables first? - All right.
There's a vegetable shop right over there.
- Hello. - Hello. What can I get you?
Please give us some lettuce and perilla leaves.
Just enough for about 10 people please.
All right.
You must be newlyweds.
You two make such a nice couple.
- Pardon? - Pardon?
It's so nice to see your husband doing grocery shopping with you.
My husband and I used to do that too.
You two look so nice together. I'll throw in some more for free.
No. You see...
Thank you very much. We appreciate it.
My husband here loves lettuce.
Honey, we're in luck, don't you agree?
- What? - My goodness.
Your wife is so sweet. You must be so happy.
- Have a happy marriage. - Thank you.
Honey, let's go.
- What? - Let's go.
What do you think you're doing? Did you call me "honey"?
She insisted on giving us more. Why would we tell her the truth?
We can eat the lettuce we got for free, right?
I don't think that was right of us.
It's not right to lie, Yoon Ah.
Honey.
Pork belly is your favorite food,
but I'm so poor I can only buy you 1,200 grams of it.
You can eat 1,200 grams of pork belly in no time.
It won't be enough. What shall I do?
Honey.
You love apples more than anything in the world.
This is all I can afford because I'm poor.
What shall I do?
This is so upsetting.
What are you doing? You told me I shouldn't lie.
We got some free meat and fruits. That's good, isn't it?
What else did you say we have to buy?
Yoon Ah. Come with me for a second.
- What is it? - Just go that way.
Where are we going?
Why are we here?
Let's see. This is pretty.
Come over here.
Dong Gu.
It's just that...
your bangs seemed to keep falling and covering your eyes.
If you end up falling down, that'll only cause me trouble.
That's why I'm buying this for you, so there's no need to feel awkward.
This doesn't mean anything. I assure you.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Let's get going then.
Yoon Ah.
Let's go.
- Yoon Ah. You like sundae, right? - Yes.
- Shall we go eat some sundae? - Shall we?
- We'd like two servings of sundae. - All right.
Why? Do you want to drink rice wine too?
What? No, it's not that.
It's just that those men are drinking rice wine with such relish.
Then you should have some.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Please give us a bottle of rice wine.
- You didn't have to. - It's all right.
This is delicious.
Gosh. Is it that good? Do you want another glass?
I might get drunk if I drink more.
We're here to relax. Who cares if you get a bit drunk?
Go ahead and have another glass.
Shall I then?
I shouldn't have given her that second glass of rice wine.
Gosh. My eyes are burning.
Why are we lighting charcoal when we should be having fun?
The more I think about it, it makes me so annoyed.
Why on earth did you guys have to come here?
Why are you yelling at me? Dong Gu chose the location.
- It's not ready yet? - It'll be ready soon.
There. It's done.
You can grill the pork here.
All right. Thank you.
That looks good.
Would you like to join us? We bought plenty of meat.
Really?
That's right.
Du Shik didn't have anything to eat all day. He must be hungry.
I should go ask him if he wants to eat some.
I'll go. I'll go. You wait here.
- Thank you. - Don't mention it.
Sol. Do you see this? It's meat.
Du Shik. They invited us to eat meat.
Let's go out together.
I don't want to. I feel nauseous. I don't feel like it.
I can't stand the smell of them cooking the meat.
How can I eat it?
Who knows? If you eat it, you might not feel nauseous anymore.
No. I told you I feel nauseous.
If you're so nauseous, how come you can't let go of your phone all day?
At least get some sleep, will you?
I told you I'm not sleepy. Why do you keep yelling at me?
You jerk.
Hang in there.
You have to be strong, all right?
I'll make sure I find a way to get you out of this room,
all right?
I'm not going out. I don't want to go out.
What the matter with him?
Why is he telling me to stay strong?
This is amazing.
Why are you alone? Doesn't Du Shik want to eat?
No. He said he doesn't want to.
Really? He really must be sick.
You should eat some then.
No. I'm not hungry.
Jun Ki. I want to eat pork belly. I'm famished.
How can she crave pork belly in this situation?
I can't believe her.
Give that to me.
What are you doing? Why would you take that?
You said Du Shik didn't want it.
Well...
I saw a starving cat over there.
I feel so sorry.
- Can I give this to the cat? - Sure.
Thank you.
Kitty, kitty
I used to call you
Why are you here again?
I said I didn't want any pork belly.
I'm not here to see you. Mind your own business.
- Then why are you here? - It's none of your business.
Focus on your game.
Why do you keep yelling at me?
What's that cup?
This?
It's coffee.
Now that I've seen you lying here, I'm leaving.
- Hold on. - What?
Where did the coffee go?
What?
Well...
Ta-da.
It's magic.
It completely disappeared.
Where could it be?
Amazing. That's awesome.
How did you do it?
Do it again.
Show me.
What are you talking about? Get lost.
It was in his hand.
Where's the lettuce?
Gosh.
Don't be like that. Show me again.
I just think it's so interesting.
Are you sure?
Is that what you want?
Yes. I want to see it again.
Show me.
Give me a second.
What? Aren't you going to show me the magic?
Where are you going?
Ta-da.
Amazing. That's incredible.
Where did it go? Show me one more time.
What are you talking about? Get lost.
Where did it go?
Where's the garlic and ssamjang?
Don't be like that. Show me one more time.
Are you serious?
Are you kidding me?
Must you really take everything...
to feel satisfied?
What are you talking about?
I'm just so curious.
Show me one last time.
All right. If you say so.
Ta-da.
It amazes me every time.
Where did it go?
That was the last time.
I'm telling you.
I can't do it anymore.
Don't ask me for anything more.
All right.
But that was incredible.
When did you learn that trick?
Whatever. Get lost!
Get lost! Why do you have to yell?
Yoon Ah, you're getting drunk. Stop drinking.
I'm not drunk at all.
I'm perfectly fine.
All right. But stop drinking.
We still need to pick up some more stuff.
Okay.
By the way,
do you like to play hide-and-seek?
Hide-and-seek?
I love it so much.
Do you want to play hide-and-seek with me?
What are you talking about?
We're not done yet. Get up.
- How much is it? - 14 dollars, please.
Here.
- Bye. - Bye.
Yoon Ah, let's go.
Wait.
Yoon Ah.
Where did she go?
My goodness.
Yoon Ah.
Where is she?
- Hey. - Yes?
Over there.
What are you doing here?
You found me.
You finally found me.
I'm it now.
Go hide.
What are you talking about?
Pull yourself together.
She was fine earlier. What happened to her?
Well... She drank some rice wine. She's a bit drunk.
Oh, right. I need some green onions.
Okay.
Here.
Wait.
Yoon Ah. Where did she go?
She's driving me crazy.
What are you doing here?
You found me again.
I'm it now.
Go hide.
My goodness.
Why are you so obsessed with hide-and-seek?
You don't want to hide?
Okay.
I'll hide again.
Where are you going?
Let go of me.
- I have to hide. - What should I do with you?
Dong Gu, let go of me.
I have to hide.
Be quiet!
What a weird drunken habit.
Follow me.
Gosh.
My goodness.
Let me hide.
Yoon Ah. Snap out of it!
Gosh, you found me again.
Fine. You can hide now.
I'm it.
My goodness.
Go hide.
All right.
I'll be it this time too.
You go hide, okay?
There is a place I'll never be able to find.
Where is it?
It's over there. Follow me.
Come.
If I hide here, you won't be able to find it?
I won't.
Okay.
Be quiet.
Hide now.
Dong Gu, I'm hiding.
Try to find me.
Okay.
You're hiding so well.
I have no idea where you are.
What should I do?
What am I doing now?
Gosh, you found me again.
Dong Gu, you should go hide. I'll be it.
Stop it.
Pull yourself together.
Are you angry at me?
I'm not.
No, you are angry at me.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Dong Gu.
You don't have to be.
Get some sleep on the way.
Please.
- Dong Gu. - What is it now?
I'm giving you a hard time, right?
I know that.
But...
I'm scared.
I'm scared...
that you'll get hurt again.
I'm really scared.
So don't hate me, all right?
Please don't.
Du Shik, how are you? Are you feeling better?
Yes, I'm feeling better.
Really? That's good.
Should we go out for some fresh air?
I will after I finish this. This is the last round.
What? What is this sound?
Was it someone snoring?
That person was sleeping even before we got here.
How long has it been?
What's that?
Why does a man have such long hair?
I know, right?
- Wait. - What?
Is he wearing clothes with floral patterns?
Floral patterns?
He is.
And I think it's a dress.
Are you sure it's a man?
What... What are you talking about? Of course it's a man.
A lot of men have long hair nowadays.
And don't you know unisex?
No one really draws a line between women's clothes and men's clothes.
See? My shirt has a floral pattern too.
- Hey, that hurts. - What are you doing?
But it's still strange.
And how can a man have a better body line than me?
- What? - I think so too.
- Maybe it's a woman. - What?
Soo Ah, go check.
- Shall I? - Yes.
Why do you need to check?
We don't need to interrupt a sleeping person.
That's not polite. Don't do it.
Move over. I'll just get a peek.
- Gosh. - Move.
Oh, my.
Gosh.
It's a man. He has a beard.
- A beard? - Really? I thought it was a woman.
- Wait. - What?
Seo Jin is a woman, but she has a beard too.
- Seo Jin? - Hey.
No woman on earth would have a beard like her.
That makes sense.
Well, now that you're feeling better,
we should go outside for the shoot when Dong Gu arrives.
All right.
Yoon Ah.
Yoon Ah. We're here.
My goodness.
Dong Gu.
What happened?
What do you think?
You got drunk and tried to play hide and seek.
Do you know how much trouble it was...
for trying to find you in the marketplace?
Gosh, did I really do that?
I'm sorry.
I have a habit of playing hide and seek when I'm drunk.
I didn't do anything else other than that, right?
- No. - That's a relief.
I'm sorry, Dong Gu.
It's fine. Take some rest.
I'm fine.
We have a lot to do. I need to go outside.
Gosh.
Where are the others? It's almost time. Seriously.
Hello?
The guests must be here.
Hello.
Hyun Joon.
Yoon Ah, what are you doing here?
Was this where you were going for the workshop?
Yes. How did you come here?
This is the guesthouse that my friend owns.
This is so cool.
I see. What a coincidence.
Let's move the luggage to the lobby first.
All right.
What's happening outside? It's so loud.
The guests must have arrived.
- Let's go, Du Shik. - Okay.
Seo Jin, wake up. Seo Jin.
What?
Wake up.
How can you sleep right now?
What's this? What happened?
I don't know, but we don't have time.
Let's hurry and go outside before the others come back.
All right.
Why is he there?
Gosh, it's driving me crazy.
Seo Jin, I don't think we can go out this way. What should we do?
Really? What should we do then?
All right. Let's go through the window.
Open it.
What's wrong with this?
- It must be broken. - What?
Gosh, that's a problem.
We can't get caught by Dong Gu.
What should we do?
Right.
What is it? Do you have any ideas?
- Seo Jin. - Yes?
Go inside that bag.
What? Go inside the bag?
Are you crazy?
What do you want me to do?
Du Shik is in front of the door, and the window is broken.
Do you want to go inside the sheets again?
What will you do if you get caught?
Do we really need to do this?
There's no other way.
All right. All right.
All right. Go inside.
Seriously.
Seo Jin, get in here.
- Gosh. - Hurry.
All right.
I'll get you out quickly.
Just wait a moment.
Oh, my. Seo Jin.
Seo Jin, I'm sorry.
Let's go.
- Jun Ki. - Gosh!
You made me jump. Why were you so surprised?
Where are you going with my luggage?
Well, I'm...
Are you helping me with my bag to the shooting?
- Thanks. - Wait...
Why is it so heavy?
Hey, wait...
Darn it.
Why is it so heavy?
- Why is it... - Keep pulling.
Why do you keep following us?
- That's true. - What?
I just wanted to help you two.
Isn't your luggage heavy, Soo Ah?
Shall I carry it for you?
I'd be grateful.
Okay.
Let's go.
- Hurry up. - Okay.
Anyway, I'm so happy to see you.
I was sad that you couldn't come.
I can't believe that we met here.
I know. I had no idea that the guesthouse was run...
by Hyun Joon's friend.
What should we do now?
It's too early to eat.
Shall we play a game?
That's a great idea.
- What shall we play? - Let's play 007.
- Electricity game. - Let's play What If.
Come on. The perfect game for situations like this...
is foot volleyball.
Foot volleyball?
We have women.
We can't play foot volleyball.
Both men and women can play sports.
What you say will cause misunderstanding.
It's because everyone is tired.
I don't think playing ball is a good idea.
Why don't we play an indoor game?
How about Express with Your Body?
Foot volleyball is perfect for orientation.
Don't you agree, Yoon Ah?
I still have a headache, so foot volleyball won't be easy.
I think Express with Your Body sounds good.
Play with us, Dong Gu.
Okay, why not?
I'm terrible at this.
We lived under the same roof for a long time.
I don't know about Hyun Joon,
but I can guess everything that you express.
(Egg)
The answer is fart.
The answer is constipation.
You can't take a dump.
- Egg? - That's correct.
(Shrimp)
I know the answer! Is it a zombie?
A zombie with a broken back!
Shrimp.
That's correct.
What's that? What is it?
"The Unbearable Lightness of Being".
"Even if the world goes to pieces, I would still plant my apple tree."
That's correct.
You're so good, Hyun Joon.
How did you guess that?
How is that possible?
That's impossible.
Here we go. That looks good.
One more.
That looked fake. Try something else.
That's good.
- Seo Jin, Seo Jin. - Jun Ki.
- Stop. - One more.
- Are you okay? - How long do I have to stay here?
My legs hurt, and it's suffocating.
I'm sorry. Hang in there.
I'll do something, okay?
Whom are you talking to, Jun Ki?
What? I...
I'm talking to the rock.
It must be frustrating to be stuck.
You're such a hard rock.
What are you talking about?
Let me get my outfit.
- I need it for my next shoot. - You can't.
You startled me. What do you mean that I can't?
No, you can't take this suitcase.
What? It's my suitcase.
- Get out of my way. - No way.
I can't give you this suitcase.
Are you out of your mind?
What's wrong with you? Give me my suitcase.
No, no!
What's wrong with him?
Du Shik, stop Jun Ki now.
Jun Ki. Hey, Jun Ki!
What's wrong with him?
Goodness.
Where did he go?
Why did he take my suitcase?
I know. Has he lost his mind?
I don't think he's here.
- Let's go over there. - Okay.
Wait.
It's over now.
Where did she go?
What happened?
Did I...
Darn it.
Seo Jin. Seo Jin.
Seo Jin! Wait for me!
(Shrimp)
("The Unbearable Lightness of Being")
"The Unbearable Lightness of Being".
Aren't you hungry after the game?
Shall we eat something?
Really?
Everyone should rest.
Men are supposed to cook when we're on a trip.
I'll cook.
Wait.
Then do it with the real man, Kang Dong Gu.
- Do you know how to cook? - Of course.
I've been a guesthouse CEO for many years.
Most chefs can't cook as well as I do.
Is that so?
Then let's cook together.
That sounds good. Let's go.
I'll show you a real man's taste.
What are you making?
I'll grill some meat and make kimchi stew.
Kimchi stew?
I was going to make that as well.
That's what I do best.
How will you make it?
I'll add some pork neck and kimchi.
Don't I just boil that?
The best kimchi stew is made...
with mackerel pike.
Isn't the easiest pork kimchi stew?
You don't know, do you?
Shall we place a bet on which is better?
That sounds good.
Let's start.
Why did you make two pots of kimchi stew?
Here's why.
Hyun Joon and I like different types of kimchi stew.
Try them.
Let us know which one tastes better.
We placed a bet.
Really?
Then shall we try some?
It's greasy.
This one is perfect.
You're right. I prefer the kimchi stew with pork.
How about you, Yoon Ah?
It's delicious.
How about that one?
It's delicious,
but it's a little greasy.
I don't really like fish.
Yes.
Why? Did Dong Gu make the one with mackerel pike?
Who wins isn't important.
Everyone should enjoy it together.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I need to get some fresh air.
The weather is nice.
The air is great too,
but Song Hyun Joon isn't.
Song Hyun Joon, Song Hyun Joon, Song Hyun Joon, you scum.
He's ruining everything. Everything.
I don't think anyone is going to eat this. Should I throw it away?
Just leave it. I'll eat it.
- You don't like fish. - What?
But it looks delicious.
All right.
I knew he was out of his mind,
but I really don't understand.
Why would he run away with my bag?
He must be crazy.
Just leave him be. Don't try to understand his mind.
Just leave him be.
Gosh, we couldn't do anything because of him.
- Jun Ki. - Jun Ki.
Give that bag to me.
What? What's wrong with you?
Just give it to me. Give it to me.
Did it do something wrong to you? What's wrong with you?
Give it to me!
- No! - Give it to me!
It's my bag. Leave it be.
- Give it to me. - What's wrong with you?
Give it to me.
My new clothes! What are you going to do about it?
Seo Jin. Seo Jin!
What are you talking about?
Gosh, Seo Jin!
Seo Jin!
- Seo Jin! - What is he doing?
No! No! No! Seo Jin!
Seo Jin!
Wait, what is he talking about? Seo Jin?
I don't know. He must be crazy.
Seo Jin!
No, Seo Jin. Seo Jin.
Why are you looking for Seo Jin?
- Jun Ki. - Seo Jin.
- Come here. - Come here.
- Push. - Seo Jin.
Seo Jin. Seo Jin.
What's that?
Are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Seo Jin?
Why was she in the suitcase? What happened?
No way. Could it be...
magic?
That's so cool. You could do magic like this?
What? What do you mean, magic?
Jun Ki, what happened? Why is she here?
- I... - What are you doing there?
- What's up? - Dong Gu.
Seo Jin, why are you...
You told me you were covering a funeral.
Dong Gu, I...
Wait.
What is this bad feeling I'm getting?
I feel like I'm about to find out something horrible.
What is this bad feeling?
I... Well... I...
Jun Ki, let's just stop here.
Let's tell him the truth.
The truth?
What are you talking about?
Well, I... The thing is...
Are you going to keep hiding? All right. Let's end all this.
You jerk.
What's this?
What are you doing?
Why are you holding hands?
Dong Gu, I like Seo Jin.
What?
What are you talking about?
I, Lee Jun Ki,
like your sister, Kang Seo Jin.
No, I love her.
What? Love?
So that means,
you two are in love?
- Are you serious? - Yes, I love her.
So...
you can choose to either kill me or keep me alive.
Kill you or keep you alive?
All right.
- Then die! - Stop, Dong Gu!
How can you do this to me?
You didn't tell me anything! My sister?
You scum!
When did this start? When!
- Stop. - Tell me!
(Welcome to Waikiki)
You've been lying to me all along.
- You're not my sister anymore. - Dong Gu, I need to talk to you.
And you mean nothing to me.
Don't talk to me or even pretend to know me.
I'm not going to shave my beard until you let me go out with Jun Ki.
What?
He's the Park Bo Gum of the modeling industry.
I'm Min Soo Ah.
That's too bad.
- What is this? - What is this smell?
It smells so bad.
- I'm sorry. - I don't feel like shooting today.
You should just stay here. You scum!
That's good news. Let's have a celebratory drink.
I should celebrate with you.
Hyun Joon, weren't you going to tell me something?
In fact, I...
Hyun Joon is a better person than I originally thought.
You're really stupid, do you know that?
Yoon Ah.