Well done guys. See you tomorrow.
- Thank you. - Sung Bin!
- Can you look over here? - Sung Bin!
Excuse me.
Yes?
Can you...
take a picture of me and Sung Bin?
Sure.
I'm ready.
1, 2, 3.
Thanks.
Jun Ki. let's go watch a movie this weekend.
The movie you wanted to watch was released.
And it's been a while since we've gone out on a date.
Okay.
What's wrong? Are you all right?
It's just that...
I thought people would recognize me...
and that I'd have fans after the drama aired.
But nothing's different.
You'll have fans soon.
Will that day really come?
We're home!
- Have you been grocery shopping? - Yes.
You two look like newlyweds.
Gosh, we don't. That's too much.
I know. You shouldn't say that.
Gosh, you two look so happy.
Wait, is Dong Gu Sol's dad now?
Sol's father.
No, I can't be her dad.
- You went too far. - He did.
Jun Ki, don't say that.
Gosh. I'm so envious.
- What's that by the way? - Right.
This was delivered to Jun Ki, but it doesn't say who it's from.
Really?
I wonder who sent this.
What... What's this?
(I love you, Jun Ki.)
What is it? Oh gosh!
What's that? Is that blood?
(I love you.)
Gosh, it seems like it.
- Hello? - Jun Ki.
Did you receive the presents I sent you?
"Presents"?
Do you mean...
Who are you?
It's me, Jin Joo.
Don't you know who I am?
"Jin Joo"?
I've never heard of your name before.
What?
How can you... How can you not know me?
I always think about you and watch you all the time.
You can't do this to me!
- What's this? - What was it about? Who is it?
I think it's the person who sent me these.
- What? - What?
She knows your number too?
- Maybe she's your stalker. - Stalker?
You know, fans who are too obsessive.
Does that mean I have a fan?
This is not the time to be happy.
Jun Ki, before anything happens, we should report to the police.
We can't report to them about a petty thing like this. Don't.
Let's see.
She's my fan. She loves me.
- It's fine. - Hello? Is this the police station?
(Stalker)
Drive properly.
- You're really bad. - Gosh.
Fire in the hole.
- Be quick. - Gosh.
- Let's go! - Gosh.
Hey, you can't do this to me.
How can you throw a banana at a beginner?
I'm sorry.
I'm going! I did it!
I won!
You tricked me into talking to outrun me.
Hey, losers should keep quiet.
You lost. Cook some ramen.
You're such a cheap, stingy, mean cheater.
- Do you want to die? - Do you want eggs or not?
No, I'll just do as I do.
- Tell me if you want some, Seo Jin. - Sure.
Make some delicious ramen.
How can you make fun of him all the time?
I don't know, but it's really fun.
Hello?
All right. Sure.
What is it about?
Jun Ki's stalker was caught.
We tracked the caller's number and caught her at an Internet cafe.
I'm sorry, Jun Ki.
I just like you so much.
You're so handsome.
I had no bad intentions.
I mean it.
What do you want? Do you want her to be punished?
Gosh.
I'm letting it slide because you promised...
you'd never do it again, okay?
Okay.
Do you like me that much?
Yes, I really like you.
I became your fan the moment I saw you.
The gangster's minion in "Cold-blooded".
The radioactive mutant in "The City of Supermen".
The kidnapper in "My Mom".
The driver in "Gayageum in My Heart"﻿.
And Octopus Man in "Super Aqua Man".
I've seen all your works.
Really? All of them?
Of course.
I even have DVDs...
for every work you were in.
Even I don't.
You're amazing.
Your name is Jin Ju, right?
Jin Ju, when you want to see me, you can call me...
and come over.
My address is...
Huam-ro 31-gil, Yongsan-gu, Seoul.
Waikiki Guesthouse.
The room next to the bathroom on the first floor.
How do you know that?
That's not...
important, is it?
What?
All right.
Are you hungry? Do you want some tteokbokki?
Sure.
Let's go.
I'm so happy.
Okay. Good job, Ah Young.
You must be busy with your work. Thank you for helping out.
Don't worry. I could use a little, extra cash.
Can I use the bathroom?
Sure. Give that to me.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Wait. What's this sound?
Du Shik, is it the sound of your heart beating?
What?
No, that's not true.
Yes, it is. Do you have a crush on Ah Young?
Ask her out if you want.
No. That's absurd.
My goodness.
Ah Young, Du Shik wants to take you to a movie.
- Hey, what are you doing? - What?
You do?
Sounds good. What should we watch?
Well...
Anything you want.
When should we go?
Mom. I'm here...
Gosh. Who are you?
Jin... Jin Ju.
What are you doing here?
You said I could come over anytime.
You looked so cute when you were sleeping,
so I've been watching you.
Since when?
Since around midnight.
Midnight?
I... I see.
I had no idea.
What's that?
What is this?
I hate to see you...
with someone else in pictures,
so I put pictures of me next to you.
Why?
Do you not like it?
I... I do. I like it.
It looks good.
That's a relief.
What's the noise?
Gosh. Who are you?
Why do you need to know that?
Don't you see I'm talking to Jun Ki?
What?
Jun Ki, have breakfast with me.
I've prepared some food for you.
You've prepared breakfast for me?
Okay. I'll be right there.
Hurry up.
Okay.
What's going?
- Who is that creepy girl? - What do you...
Right? I was so scared...
that I pretended to be asleep. Who is she?
She's my fan.
The one who sent me the pictures yesterday.
She's that stalker?
She's not a stalker. She's a fan.
She likes me so much.
I'll go have breakfast with my fan.
- She's a stalker. - She's just a fan.
- She's... - Don't eat anything!
I'm scared of what will happen to him.
- Du Shik. - Oh, hi.
Ah Young, you look beautiful today.
Really?
I dressed up for you. Do you like it?
Yes. You look very pretty.
Thank you.
You look good too.
You seem to love sweatpants.
Yes. They're so comfortable.
I see.
You already bought popcorn and drinks?
That's so sweet.
Thank you. Should we go in?
The movie was great, right?
Should we go eat now?
Forget it. I'm just going to go home.
What? Why?
You really don't know?
I'm so disappointed in you.
What? Why?
What's wrong? Ah Young!
Sol, do you want to learn some words?
The first word you should learn is,
"Dad".
Okay?
Say, "Dad".
Sol, you need to focus when you're studying.
Try. "Dad".
"Dad".
Please say it just once.
What's wrong?
You were so excited about your date. What happened?
Well...
What?
She was suddenly angry after the movie and left?
Yes.
Think carefully. You must have done something wrong.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I got there 30 minutes before,
booked tickets for the movie she wanted to watch,
and even bought popcorn and drinks beforehand.
The movie was fun too.
But she suddenly got angry and left.
What could it be?
Did the popcorn taste bad?
No. She finished everything.
Really? Then what is it?
Is it because you bought regular coke instead of diet coke?
No. She even drank mine too.
Really?
Could it be that she just didn't like your face?
- What? - When I stare at your face,
I get annoyed.
- That doesn't make sense. - It does.
What did I do wrong?
Du Shik, let's play another game.
Why do you look so down? Did something happen?
Well...
Gosh. It's no wonder Ah Young got angry.
Why?
What did I do wrong?
You really don't know?
You're not together yet,
but this was your first date. How could you wear sweatpants?
Sweatpants? What's wrong with them?
Hey, Ah Young must have...
dressed up for the date.
But you just threw on a pair of sweatpants?
Of course, she got angry.
I picked out the prettiest pair of sweatpants that I have.
Look at this.
- It's a frog. - Gosh.
- Why would she be angry? - Exactly. It looks good.
- It's super cute. - Right?
Gosh. You really don't understand girls.
Anyway, Ah Young is a sensitive type.
Be more careful.
Okay, I will.
- Sung Bin! - Sung Bin!
- Please look over here! - Sung Bin!
Jun Ki!
(Milky-faced Lee Jun Ki)
Milky-faced Lee Jun Ki!
I love you, Jun Ki!
Jun Ki, you did a great job today.
Here's a drink for you.
This is a vitamin that will give you energy.
And a candy...
to maintain your blood sugar level.
Here.
Is this really for me?
You didn't have to.
Thank you.
Director, this is my fan.
You're a celebrity now.
Sung Bin.
This is my fan.
Sir, this is my fan.
Why did you want to see me?
Ah Young.
- I'm sorry about yesterday. - Sorry about what?
Yesterday, I was careless and wore sweatpants to the movies.
I'm sorry.
You know, after all.
I'm sorry for being thoughtless.
How about I buy you something delicious?
Do you want to go to a nearby cake place?
The cake is so delicious.
I was stressed out today, so I was craving sweets.
Why? Did something happen?
Something annoying happened at work today.
My senior kept making me do his work...
while he was procrastinating.
Really?
I was also annoyed by online-shopping customers.
They wanted a refund for the clothes that they tore.
- I couldn't believe it. - How could they do that?
It must have been hard.
It's okay. It always happens.
You finished your coffee. I'll get a refill.
It's okay. I'm leaving.
What?
What's wrong? Did I do something wrong?
Do you really not know?
- You're terrible. - What?
Wait, what did I do wrong? Ah Young.
What's wrong this time?
Gosh, no wonder she got upset.
Really?
What did I do wrong?
Ah Young said that something annoyed her at work.
Why did you talk about your problem?
What's wrong with that? Is that upsetting?
Why?
Ah Young wanted you to listen and side with her.
She wanted you to empathize with her.
You should have sided with her or consoled her.
Why didn't you listen to her?
Instead, you talked about yourself. Of course, it's upsetting.
Really?
I see.
- Good job. - Thank you.
Thank you. Goodbye.
My goodness. They will be here today.
It's Jin Ju.
She must be here to see me.
Does she like me that much?
(You're mine, ASTAR.)
- Jin Ju. - Jun Ki.
Why did you come again?
Let's go. I'll buy you some coffee...
What's all this?
This?
It's an ASTAR fan club t-shirt.
This is A-Bulb for cheering.
I'm a fan of ASTAR.
"ASTAR".
Were you also a fan of other celebrities?
Among the actors, it's you. Among the singers,
it's ASTAR.
Is that so?
Aren't you going to watch my drama with me today?
I know. After ASTAR's performance,
- I'll be right there. - It's ASTAR!
There we go. It's done.
This should be enough.
The drama will be aired soon. Where's Jin Ju?
What are all these? They look delicious.
- Hey. - That hurt.
How dare you touch it?
I'll eat these with Jin Ju while watching the drama.
Did you prepare snacks for that stalker?
She's not a stalker. She's my fan.
Why isn't she here yet?
Jun Ki.
(Sponsored by Caffe Bono)
(Do Min Ho Pizza)
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
What happened?
The drama is over. Why isn't she here yet?
She isn't picking up either.
Did something happen?
The phone is turned off.
- Please leave a message... - What?
I could call her just now. Why is her phone off?
Is she...
avoiding my calls?
No, that can't be.
It can't be.
No way.
Jun Ki, what brings you here?
We were supposed to watch my drama yesterday.
But you didn't come, and I couldn't contact you.
I was wondering if something was wrong.
How did you know where I lived?
What?
That's not what's important.
Why didn't you come yesterday?
ASTAR's performance finished late.
I see.
Did you watch my drama yesterday?
No, I was too tired.
I fell asleep.
I see.
That could happen.
I downloaded the drama. Do you want to watch it with me?
Sure.
I'll come to your house later.
Will you? Okay. I'll wait for you at home.
Okay.
Ah Young, I'm sorry about yesterday.
Sorry about what?
You said that something annoyed you at work.
I didn't listen to you and only talked about myself.
You know, after all. Do you know how disappointed I was yesterday?
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
I'll be careful from now on.
Okay.
You aren't upset anymore, right?
What shall we do? What do you want to do?
Forget it. I'm leaving.
You're terrible.
Why?
Did I do something wrong again?
Don't you know?
How could you come without thinking what to do?
- Isn't it polite to make plans? - What?
I'm sorry. I was thoughtless.
Since the weather is nice,
shall we walk in the park?
Cherry blossoms have bloomed.
Forget it. I'm leaving.
You're so terrible.
Why? Why?
What did I do wrong?
Can't you see that I'm wearing heels?
Are you suggesting that we go to a park?
Do you want my feet to hurt?
Right. I'm sorry.
I was thoughtless.
Shall we go get some coffee?
Why not?
Okay, let's go.
(Twinkle, twinkle ASTAR)
Jin Ju, where are you?
Why aren't you coming?
We were going to watch my drama together.
It's him again.
Why does he keep doing this?
Where are you? Are you on your way?
Jin Ju, why aren't you answering?
Why aren't you responding after reading?
He's so persistent.
(Jun Ki)
I don't care anymore.
Why aren't you picking up?
Jun Ki, how did you get here?
That's not what's important.
What are you doing here?
Are you here to see ASTAR again?
Is this why you broke your promise?
What? No.
I forgot.
I was about to go.
Really?
It's true, right?
Then shall we go?
I got a present for you.
- Ta-da. - What is it?
This is...
Jun Ki's shirt.
This is a cheering stick for Jun Ki.
Why? Do you not like it?
I do. I really like it.
My goodness.
Great.
Jun Ki's stick.
Gosh.
Do you call yourself a journalist?
There's me. Look.
Jin Ju.
What are you doing?
Pardon? What's wrong?
Why aren't you waving my stick?
You were waving at ASTAR.
I was about to wave it.
What? Are you yawning?
Are you sleepy already?
You were cheering for ASTAR until late at night.
I didn't yawn.
I was impressed by your acting.
That's it, right?
Look, I'm on again.
Come on. What are you doing back there?
- Du Shik. - Go easy on me.
There's no going easy.
Okay, I shoot.
I got first place, didn't I?
I got first place.
I'm leaving.
You're so terrible.
I get it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I made a mistake again.
I'm sorry.
To make it up to you, I'll cook you noodles.
Let's go.
- All right. - Let's go.
Soo Ah. When did you get here?
What? Just now.
- What's that? - What?
It's just a game.
It was just released. I thought I'd play it with you.
Let's play it some other time. I have to eat noodles with Ah Young.
- Sure. All right. - Let's go.
Enjoy.
I can always play by myself.
It's more fun when there are 2 players than 1.
Soo Ah. Soo Ah. Soo Ah.
- Soo Ah. - Yes?
Du Shik. Let's play this game together.
Wait. Wait a minute.
Let's play another time.
I have something I need to ask you.
Me? What is it?
You see,
I want to ask Ah Young to be my girlfriend.
How should I do it?
What? You're going to confess?
I think I'll mess up again if I do this on my own,
so I wanted to ask you.
How do girls want guys to confess?
- How would I know? - Wait. I need your help.
Give me some advice. Please, Soo Ah?
I don't know.
Actually, there is one way.
What shall we have for lunch today?
How about spaghetti or maybe Chinese food for a change?
Ah Young.
Du Shik. What brings you here?
Why are you dressed like that?
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
What do you think you're doing?
Ah Young.
Will you be my girlfriend?
Du Shik. What are you doing?
What's the matter?
Is it because you're so moved?
Then is today the first day...
Ah Young. Ah Young. What's the matter?
Did I do something wrong again?
Where are you? Why haven't I heard from you?
You've gone to see ASTAR again, haven't you?
What's wrong with this guy?
He's a complete stalker.
Jun... Jun Ki.
I see you've come home, my dear Jin Ju.
- How did you get in here? - What?
That's not what's important.
It's not, is it?
You haven't been answering my calls these days.
I came over because I was worried,
but I see...
you're doing well.
I've been busy these days.
Is that right? Then I guess you weren't able to see my drama.
Shall we...
watch the relays of the episodes?
- Right now? - Why?
(Don't take your eyes off me.)
Do you not want to?
Excuse me?
How am I a stalker?
I didn't stalk her.
Jin Ju's my first fan,
so I did it because I was so happy.
I had no bad intentions.
Jin Ju.
You know how I feel, right?
So...
- would you like him punished? - Yes.
Yes, she wants... What?
Jin Ju.
Gosh. You had nothing better to do than...
stalk your stalker? Then you got a restraining order?
I didn't stalk her.
It was affection toward my fan.
My goodness.
You made such a big deal out of it.
You ended up losing your only fan.
- Gosh. - My goodness.
He's upset. I'm sure of it.
He sure has a bad temper.
Where were you two while being dressed like that?
Soo Ah!
How do you plan on explaining this?
What's wrong? What is it this time?
What? You confessed to her in public while tap dancing?
On top of that, you did it in front of her colleagues?
Are you crazy?
Don't you know girls hate when guys confess in public?
Really?
Soo Ah.
You told me it would work.
You said girls love it when guys do that!
That's strange.
I love it when guys confess in public.
I guess other girls don't like it.
I didn't know. I'm sorry.
Is that all you have to say?
What are you going to do about this?
You take care of this. Take care of this!
I said I'm sorry.
I'm tired. I'm going to get some rest.
Where do you think you're going? Where are you going?
Come back here this instant! Hey!
- Yoon Ah. - Oh my goodness!
- Go away. Go away. - Gosh.
Oh, dear. Dong Gu. Are you all right?
I'm sorry. It's just that I was so startled.
No, it's my fault. I shouldn't have startled you.
I'm late, aren't I?
The meeting ran late.
It's all right. I just got here after getting out of class.
Shall we go?
The weather's still quite chilly.
Aren't your hands cold?
What? No, I'm all right.
I don't think so. They look awfully cold.
Would you like me to warm them up for you?
I'm the type that has really warm hands.
You know I'm not doing this just to hold your hand, right?
All right.
Ah Young. Ah Young. Listen to me.
About that tap dance... Ah Young. Wait.
Gosh.
Soo Ah!
This is all your fault. Do you know that?
I said I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I wonder why Ah Young doesn't like tap dancing. I love it.
What? Who cares if you like it?
Hey. Come back here. Hey!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Why is it so hard to see you these days?
I'm sorry.
I've been busy shooting scenes.
I know. I know, but...
do you know how long it's been since we've gone on a date?
I'm sorry.
Then shall we go out to see a movie right now?
No. You'll pass out while watching a movie.
Let's go some other time.
I'm really sorry.
Then since my shoot ends early tomorrow,
shall we see a movie and come home together?
I'll make time for you no matter what.
Really? You mean it? You promised.
- I promise. - You promised.
I'm tired. I'm so exhausted.
How could the shooting last all night every single day?
This is killing me.
It must be tough.
But I'm lucky to be able to pursue my acting career.
It's physically tough, but I'm truly happy these days.
Hello, losers.
What's gotten into this sorehead?
Are you manic today?
Where were you?
I'm on my way back from a romantic date with Yoon Ah.
I see you can't stop smiling because you're so happy.
Have you made any moves yet?
I'm assuming you two have kissed, right?
What? Kiss?
We already kissed at the wedding, remember?
Do you call that a kiss? That was a peck.
Don't you know the difference between a kiss and a peck?
From the way I see it, you two haven't kissed yet, right?
- Did you hold hands? - Of course!
We hold hands every day. We hold them really hard!
Good for you.
That's great.
You should hold her hand forever.
Well, you can't measure love...
with physical affection, you pervert.
Sure, sure.
You should hold your hands and be in love forever then.
Wait.
Does that mean you've kissed Seo Jin?
Do you think you're a shrimp or something? Get up!
Did you kiss my sister or not?
Get up! Get up!
You're awake.
- Did you sleep well? - Yes.
What are you doing?
It's spring now, so I'm seasoning vegetables for some side dishes.
It looks delicious.
Yoon Ah, you have something on your lips.
It must have gotten there when I was tasting it.
Gosh, I'll take it off for you.
It's soft.
It's too soft.
It feels soft on my fingers.
It will be softer when my lips touch it.
Dong Gu, what's wrong?
I want to kiss her.
Dong Gu, are you all right?
What? I... Yes.
I was distracted for a moment.
I'm going to the office.
Sure.
Now, we have Shin Hyun Joon,
and it's possible to hide the air rifle in the bread.
The protagonist has to meet with the Arabian spy,
Shin Hyun Joon.
Would there be a unique way for them to check their identities?
They could send signals by touching their glasses.
That's too boring.
Don't you have any new ideas?
He's doing that again.
He must have an idea.
What would it be this time?
- Kiss! - Kiss?
Make them kiss to send signals?
That's new.
Director!
This is too much.
What do you mean?
It's new, sexy, and great.
Sir, I can't do this anymore.
- What's wrong? - I'm going to quit.
I... Sir.
Sir.
It must be hard for you to have shootings every day.
I'm fine.
I'm just happy to get the chance to act.
Do you have a management team?
- No, not yet. - Really?
So do you manage your schedules and your styling all by yourself?
Yes.
You should have a management team...
so you can focus on acting.
Right. Then should I try telling my boss about you?
What? Do you mean...
YS?
It's a huge company. I can't be a part of that.
I'll try to arrange a meeting for you.
You should talk to my boss.
Really?
Thank you. Thank you!
- I must get going. I'm busy. - Thank you.
Thank you.
YS. Gosh.
Jun Ki, you're here.
The writer sent me the revised script.
- The revised script? - Yes, an important scene was added.
- Look at scene 38 first. - Scene 38?
Jun Seok. He finds his position to be similar...
to that of Elizabeth inside the show window.
He cries while staring at Elizabeth.
Elizabeth?
But who is Elizabeth?
A turtle?
That's Elizabeth.
What? The turtle is called Elizabeth?
Yes, you'll be getting a turtle from this episode.
What? Why so suddenly?
The writer wanted to show...
the hard situation Song Jun Seok is in...
by comparing it to the hard shell of the turtle.
He heals his wounds by taking care of the turtle...
and shares his feelings with it.
Share his feelings?
With Elizabeth... With a turtle?
We don't have much time. Let's go.
Elizabeth... A turtle...
Song Jun Seok has enemies everywhere.
While going back home, he sees Elizabeth,
locked in the water tank and surrounded by walls.
Then he cries without realizing it.
Do you understand?
Yes. I'll try.
Okay. Then we'll start filming.
We're going now.
Okay, get ready. Cue.
Cut. Jun Ki, what are you doing?
You're supposed to cry.
Well, I...
I can't concentrate on my acting when I see the turtle.
Then what are you going to do? This is an important scene.
Listen. Stare into Elizabeth's eyes...
and connect with it.
But the turtle's eyes are so small.
Just... Just try.
- We'll try again. - Sure.
Okay, get ready. Cue.
Cut! Again!
Cut.
Cut. Gosh.
Connect! Connect!
All right. Connect. Connect.
Cut. Cut.
- Cut! - What?
- What's wrong with you today? - Right.
Is Shin Hyun Joon really going to be in your movie as an Arabian?
I want to kiss her.
Dong Gu.
Dong Gu, can't you hear me?
What?
No, I was listening.
Right. Yoon Ah,
I wanted to talk to you about something.
Really? What is it?
It's very important. It's not something I should be saying here.
Do you want to talk over there?
All right.
Let's go.
What do you want to tell me?
Well, I'm having a hard time with the movie...
and the low earnings from the house.
So I need something...
to keep me going in life.
Really?
Cheer up, Dong Gu.
But...
hearing those words...
won't really cheer me up.
Really? Then what should I do?
- Can you... - Sorry?
- Can you...just once? - What?
Can you just kiss me once?
What? Kiss?
So was all of this about kissing?
No,
it isn't because I want to kiss you.
I just really need something to cheer me up.
All right.
Really?
Yes.
What should I do?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I'm...
very ticklish.
You must have a sensitive neck.
Let me try again.
Are you ticklish on your sides too?
Okay.
Let me try again.
It tickles so much.
What should I do? It tickles.
Ah Young is ignoring my calls and messages too now.
What should I do?
Give up now.
No. I can't give up.
I think we're meant to be together.
You say that about a different girl every day.
Ah Young.
I'm back.
You're home early.
Do you want to go see a movie?
I dressed up for our date. What do you think?
Bacca, I'm sorry,
but I don't think I can go see a movie today either.
What? Why?
Well...
So...
you have to find a way to connect with this turtle?
Yes.
How are you supposed to do that?
I don't know either.
Anyway,
the director wants me to eat and sleep with this turtle.
We have to stay together at all times.
What?
Seo Jin, can we go see a movie some other time?
You've been saying that so many times.
How can you do this to me?
I'm sorry.
We'll go see a movie tomorrow instead, okay?
I'll treat you to some nice food too.
Let's go to the restaurant you've been talking about.
Are you sure?
Keep your promise this time.
Okay.
By the way, how should I connect with this turtle?
Elizabeth,
look me in the eye.
Let's open up and communicate.
Are you serious?
Elizabeth, where do you come from?
Do you have any friends? What about siblings?
What's your motto? What's your favorite book?
Gosh. Of course, it doesn't understand.
What was I expecting?
This is driving me crazy.
You're back.
Why do you look so troubled?
It's nothing.
What's that turtle?
What? Well...
I don't want to talk about it.
Jun Ki.
I have a question.
The main character in the movie I'm preparing has a girlfriend.
- And? - And...
this main character has to kiss his girlfriend.
However, she's so ticklish.
It's impossible to kiss her.
- So? - What should he do...
to kiss his girlfriend?
So...
you can't kiss Yoon Ah because she's too ticklish?
Yes.
I can't even touch her.
No!
I'm talking about the movie!
Who are you trying to fool?
What should I do?
Do you have any ideas?
It's no problem.
If she's ticklish,
don't use your hands.
Kiss her without using my hands? How?
Put your hands behind your back.
Hands behind my back?
Come on. That would look weird.
You think so?
Why don't you hold her by the hair? She can't be ticklish on her hair.
Hold her by the hair?
That would look even worse.
It's not romantic at all.
But you can at least kiss her.
Just forget it!
I'd rather not kiss her.
It's not like I'm obsessed with kissing.
I can't believe you.
What about now? It doesn't tickle, does it?
Are you saying...
you're going to kiss me like this?
We have no choice.
You're too ticklish.
Also, like I said,
it's not that I want to kiss you.
I just need some energy.
Fine, I get it.
What's wrong? I didn't even touch you.
That's not it.
Your breath tickles too much.
"My breath"?
Don't you think you're too sensitive?
I'm sorry. I tried to ignore it,
but I just can't.
All right. I'll hold my breath.
Let's try again, okay?
I can't do this.
What should I do? It tickles so much.
I'm sorry.
It just tickles so much.
Elizabeth, does it taste good?
Tell me what you think. Come on.
Are you serious?
I took a bath with you, let you sleep on my arm, and fed you.
Isn't it time you started to listen to me?
- Jun Ki. - Yes?
That's enough.
You're starting to look like a crazy person.
- What? - He is crazy.
Leave him alone.
How dare you?
It's not like I want to do this myself.
Do you know what kind of scene I'll be shooting with her?
What is it?
You know the movie, "Days of Being Wild", right?
Do you remember the scene where Leslie Cheung dances?
I have to do that with Elizabeth while looking into its eyes.
- What? - You have to dance with a turtle?
Yes.
The writer drew 10 stars to say the scene is super important.
I feel so sorry for you.
You never run out of problems. Seriously.
- Jun Ki. - Yes?
Don't forget about our date tonight.
Keep your promise this time, okay?
Don't worry.
I've even booked a restaurant.
Really?
We haven't been on a date in such a long time.
Gosh, we're eating here.
(Culture Department)
I'm so excited about our date tonight.
Should I have put on something prettier?
I better finish this up soon.
Seo Jin.
Go through these papers and make a summary...
by tonight.
Sorry? All of these?
Yes.
What? You don't want to?
Well, that's not what I mean.
No matter what happens, it has to be done by tonight, okay?
My gosh, this is driving me crazy.
I can't finish this today.
I'm going on a date with Jun Ki.
This is driving me crazy. Seriously.
Gosh.
What should I do? I better hurry.
Have you been able to connect with Elizabeth?
Sorry?
Well, I've tried my best.
All right.
Song Jun Seok loses his anchor position.
To deal with the pain,
he does a mambo dance with Elizabeth.
- Okay. - However,
how well you dance isn't important.
The viewers should be able to see the connection between you two.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Elizabeth, let's do this. Please.
Okay. Then let's start right away.
Let's start!
Relax your face.
Ready.
Cue!
Cut!
What are you doing?
Elizabeth is running away.
I'm sorry.
Try to connect with her.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Let me try again.
Elizabeth, what's with you?
Do me a favor, will you?
Let's start from where you begin to dance together.
Okay.
Do a good job, Elizabeth.
Ready. Action.
Cut.
Elizabeth is running away.
- I'll try one more time. - Connect enough before starting.
Okay.
Ready. Action.
Cut.
Cut!
("Newsroom" Episode 3)
Elizabeth.
Will you shoot this scene all day?
We've had over 10,000 cuts.
I'm sorry, Director.
I gave you a day. Why can't you communicate?
Also...
What will you do?
Elizabeth went under her shell.
- What will you do? - Pardon?
What can I do when she hid herself?
You're the closest to her.
Comfort her and make her come out.
Pardon me?
How can I do that?
I don't know anymore.
Let's take a break until she comes out.
I can't believe that I'm having this problem.
I'm sorry.
This is driving me crazy.
Elizabeth, please come out.
I have a date with Seo Jin today.
Elizabeth. Elizabeth?
What's wrong with her?
Come out, please?
Okay. I'm finished.
Here you go. I'm done.
- Did you finish all? It was a lot. - Yes.
Did you really do it thoroughly?
I did. I didn't eat lunch or take bathroom breaks.
I worked very hard to finish it.
- Good job. You may go. - Okay.
See you tomorrow.
Gosh, I'm tired.
Why is she always out to get me?
I'm happy thinking about going on a date...
with Jun Ki.
Why hasn't he called yet?
Will you keep acting like this, Elizabeth?
Come out.
Elizabeth.
Hello, Seo Jin.
Where are you? I'm here.
Well,
I'm still on set.
What? Why are you still there?
I only have one scene left,
but the shoot is getting postponed because of Elizabeth.
Could you wait a little?
I'll finish as quickly as possible.
Okay.
- Come soon. - I will.
I'm sorry.
Did you hear that, Elizabeth?
Seo Jin is already waiting.
Please help me.
Come on, Elizabeth.
If you keep doing this, I have another plan.
Turtle, turtle.
Show me your head.
If you don't come out,
I'll grill and eat you.
My goodness.
When will I get to leave?
Elizabeth, you're finally out.
Did it work?
Thank you for coming out, Elizabeth.
Goodness.
What is it?
Did you understand what I said?
What?
Did we communicate...
successfully?
Elizabeth.
It really works.
Gosh, Elizabeth.
Thank you.
Ready. Action.
Cut. Okay, that was great.
I could totally see you communicate with Elizabeth.
Good job, Jun Ki. That was impressive.
Thank you, thank you.
I won't forget this, Elizabeth.
Thank you.
Right. I'll be leaving, Director.
Okay, go.
Thank you, everyone.
Why are you giggling about?
I just came back from seeing Ah Young.
I don't think she's upset anymore.
- Really? - Yes.
I'm calling to ask her out on a date.
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
Please leave a message...
Why isn't she picking up?
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Extra fees will be charged after the connection.
Why is her phone off?
I could call her just now.
She's obviously avoiding your call.
Please leave a message after the beep.
- Why? - Don't you get it?
She's still upset.
No way.
I asked her if she was upset.
She said, "No, I'm not upset."
I asked her if she was okay.
She said, "Yes, I'm fine now."
You're so silly.
- She doesn't mean that she's okay. - What do you mean?
When she says that she's not upset,
it means that she's furious.
When she says that she's fine,
it means that she's not okay and that she's hurt.
- That's what it means. - What?
When she says that she's not upset, it means that she is.
When she says that she's okay, it means that she's not?
- Yes. - Why would you say the opposite?
You have no idea how women feel.
- Is she being sarcastic? - Yoon Ah.
Where's Yoon Ah?
- I think she's on the third floor. - Really?
What's wrong with him?
Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah.
I finally found it.
What did you find?
The way we can kiss.
Are you talking about kiss again?
I told you.
It's not because I want to kiss you.
I just need some energy.
Okay, so what's the solution?
What do you think?
You wouldn't be tickled by my breath, right?
Is this really necessary?
As I told you,
it's not because I want to kiss you.
I feel down, so I need energy.
Forget it.
This is our first kiss. Where's the ambiance?
Aren't you being harsh?
I'm sorry.
I couldn't find any other solution.
Was I being too childish?
I'm sorry, Yoon Ah.
Why are you so silly?
Pardon? Silly?
You don't get ticklish, do you?
- I don't. - Then everything is fine.
We could just do this.
From now on, if you want to kiss, tell me.
I'll kiss you.
What?
All right.
Then I'll be going downstairs now.
One more time. One more time. One more time.
I'm late. I should hurry.
I'm sure Seo Jin's really upset. I better take a taxi.
Jun Ki. You've finished your scenes, right?
Yes, just now.
Is something wrong?
Remember I mentioned before that...
I'd introduce you to my CEO sometime?
He's in the area taking care of some business,
and he said he wants to meet you.
Right now?
I told him good things about you,
so if you leave a good impression, you'll be able to sign a contract.
Really?
Why? What's the matter?
You see, I'm supposed to meet my girlfriend right now.
What?
Have you lost your mind?
Opportunities like this don't come along every day.
That I know, of course,
but you see, my girlfriends been waiting for me for hours.
I'm really sorry,
but could I possibly meet with him another day?
Is a date with a girl more important than your acting career?
If you miss this opportunity, do you actually think you'll ever...
be able to sign a contract with a major agency like ours?
You say you want to become an actor, but you don't seem desperate.
It's up to you. Do whatever you want.
(Jun Ki)
Jun Ki. Are you done?
Yes. I just finished.
Seo Jin, I'm really sorry,
but I don't think I'll be able to make it today.
What? Why not?
You see, there's an agency I really want to sign with.
The CEO said he wants to meet with me right now.
What?
So?
I'm really, really sorry,
but do you mind if we have a meal together another day?
I'm truly sorry, but...
it's just that this is a really important opportunity for me.
Can you be understanding just this one time?
All right.
Really? Really?
You're not upset, are you?
No, I'm not upset.
You're not lying, are you? Are you really okay?
I'm fine. Really.
Thank you Seo Jin. I appreciate it.
Then I'll see you at home later.
I'm all right.
Really.
I'm really all right.
(Welcome to Waikiki)