(Ms. Han Yoon Ah, Congratulations. You've passed the exam.)
(See the details on the website.)
Yoon Ah.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Hey.
Have you been well?
What brings you here?
I wanted to ask you for forgiveness.
I know that I can't be forgiven no matter what.
It's unnecessary, so just leave.
- Yoon Ah. - It's unnecessary. Just leave.
Yoon Ah, what's wrong?
Who is he?
Who is he? What's wrong?
I didn't know.
I really didn't know.
I'm sorry, Yoon Ah.
I'm really sorry.
You don't need to be sorry.
Sol is my daughter.
She has nothing to do with you.
I'll be responsible.
I'll be responsible for everything.
Responsible?
What will you be responsible of?
Where were you when I was suffering?
How could you say that now?
You weren't next to me when it was difficult every day.
You never called me.
There's someone who held my hand during those times.
And now,
I love him.
- Yoon Ah. - Stop it.
I decided to give birth to Sol.
You have nothing to do with my daughter.
We broke up.
Let's pretend that we don't know each other.
Goodbye.
Yoon Ah.
Yoon Ah!
Let's go, Dong Gu.
Seo Jin.
What did you mean?
Some time to think?
Let's reconsider...
our relationship.
Reconsider what?
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Is it because I couldn't keep my promise today?
Is it because of the scandal?
What is it? Tell me so I can understand.
Everything is difficult.
I can't see you often because you're busy.
We can't freely go on dates.
Everything is hard including having to hide that you're my boyfriend.
Okay.
Then I'll tell the truth to the reporters.
I'll fix everything. It'll be all right.
Don't do that.
Your career is finally going well after years of effort.
I don't want to interfere.
You don't want this or that.
- What do you want me to do? - I don't know either.
However, it's difficult.
I'm disappointed.
I feel pathetic.
I thought I was a strong person.
I guess I'm not.
Jun Ki.
I don't want to look at your face right now.
Can you leave?
- Seo Jin. - Leave.
Leave now!
Wait, Seo Jin.
Seo Jin.
(Because It Hurts)
The president became a zombie.
He pulled energy from his lower abdomen...
and focused it on his fingers.
Finally,
the president's super-ultra-energized...
finger jam exploded.
The alien gripped its torn eye...
and struggled.
Do I like a person like him?
Why?
I'm the legendary beauty queen of Huam-dong.
He wears sweatshirts and writes stories online.
That Bong Du Shik?
No, no way.
Of course not.
Why are you looking at me?
Why? Do I look handsome the more you look at me?
I was kidding.
What's with the serious look?
You can't kid about certain things. What kind of joke is that?
Was it such a terrible joke?
Forget it. Don't talk to me anymore, you pig.
You're calling me a pig again. Have you seen such a lean pig?
Did I gain weight?
You're home. How was your date?
What's going on?
- Did you argue? - I'll get some rest.
Okay.
What's wrong with her? Did something happen?
What?
Sol's dad came to see her?
Why all of a sudden?
I don't know. I can't ask her.
What's going on?
You're leaving in a week.
You must be bothered.
Soo Ah, the standard of happiness differs for everyone.
You still have time.
Find work that will make you happy...
all your life.
I just gave it a try.
What? They look cute.
Unconventional style is popular these days.
Do you want to try it on?
Gosh, why do I keep thinking about Du Shik?
This is driving me crazy.
The doctor told me not to drink so much.
Whatever.
I don't like Du Shik, do I?
(Min Bong Soo Du Ah Shik)
Eight.
20 percent?
I don't like him that much.
That's a relief.
Wait. Does 20 percent still mean that I like him?
Gosh, it became more complicated.
Wait.
(Bong Min Du Soo Shik Ah)
64 percent?
That means Du Shik likes me more.
Are you happy? Yes, I am.
Are you happy that this is correct?
You're crazy, Soo Ah.
You've lost your mind.
Why doesn't she come when it's time to eat?
She makes me come up to wake her up.
Is this a pigsty or what?
She even drank?
Soo Ah. Hey.
Hey, wake up.
Why are you sleeping here?
What?
What? What's the matter?
Why are you so startled?
Hey, why did you drink so much?
It's none of your business, you pig.
Hey. Why do you keep calling me a pig? It's childish.
Yes, I am childish. Do you have a problem?
Forget it.
Can't you clean up a bit?
It's so messy.
Whatever. I have an upset stomach. Stop nagging.
Gosh, my stomach.
What's all this?
Hold on.
(Bong Min Du Soo Shik Ah)
- Du Shik! - Gosh.
Why are you yelling?
Give that to me. It's mine, you thief.
I'm a thief now?
That was close.
It's not here.
Where is it?
Why is it not here?
Dong Gu, did you sleep well?
Yes.
It's grilled mackerel, your favorite.
- Doesn't it look tasty? - Yes.
Thank you.
Du Shik, why aren't you eating?
I heard so many insults this morning that I'm not even hungry.
Why? Did something happen?
The thing is, Soo Ah...
Soo Ah, what are you doing?
It's none of your business. Keep eating, you pig.
- See? She insulted me again. - Excuse me.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I have something to tell you.
What's with you?
I have nothing more to say to you.
What's going on? What's wrong, Yoon Ah?
Who is he?
Come with me.
Hey.
Who is he?
Is he...
What's with you?
I said we should be strangers.
There's nothing you can change now.
I'm not asking you to take me back.
I know I don't have the right to.
But...
even so,
I'm still Sol's dad.
I feel ashamed to say this, but I want to make it up to Sol...
and be forgiven by you.
- Can't I do that? - No.
You can't.
Let me tell you one more time.
Sol is my daughter.
She has nothing to do with you.
So never show up again.
Why is Sol's dad here?
I don't know. I wonder if Yoon Ah is okay.
Sorry for the trouble.
Daddy.
Sorry again for the trouble.
Bye.
Did Sol...
just call him Daddy?
- Did she? - Yes.
She never said it no matter how much Dong Gu tried.
That's so interesting.
They say blood is thicker than water.
That's probably right. Don't you think?
Hey.
- I need some rest. - Okay.
Hey, how could you be so insensitive?
What did I do?
- What are you doing? - I'm playing with Sol.
I'm sorry.
For what?
He'll never come back again.
So don't worry.
Okay?
I'm not worried at all.
Why would I be?
Don't worry.
That's a relief.
I heard you've been waiting since the morning.
What's the matter?
Well...
Sir, I'd like to deny the rumor about Cindy and me.
What? What are you talking about?
I'm in love with someone else.
I don't think this is fair...
for her.
Jun Ki, you're so romantic.
- Don't be such a romantic. - Sorry?
Do you think you're in the position to be romantic?
Director, what I'm saying is...
Cut it out.
A ton of actors disappear after one work every year.
Do you think you're an exception?
I'll work hard.
- I'll work... - If hard work can make you a star,
everyone would be one.
Do you know why people fail?
They lack luck and opportunities.
You're given the opportunity of a lifetime right now,
and you want to throw it away?
Fine. Deny it in front of the reporters if you want.
But as soon as you do that,
your contract will be canceled.
Well...
You need to stay somewhere else.
What? I need to move?
There must be a ton of reporters in front of your place right now.
This rumor should go on for at least a week.
Jun Ki, you can stay here for the time being.
The shooting will be postponed for a few days, so don't worry.
(Jun Ki)
(Decline)
I was going over the scenario yesterday,
and I didn't really like the ending.
Could we add some kind of a twist?
- Twist? - I don't need your opinion.
I want to hear Dong Gu's.
Look at him. He's coming up with something again.
Be quiet, everyone.
Dong Gu, what is it? Are you getting any ideas?
(Daddy)
Daddy! Daddy!
"Daddy"?
So he managed to assassinate the man,
but the man turned out to be his dad?
That sounds interesting.
The main character is Korean.
- How can his dad be Arab? - Why not?
He was adopted as a baby,
and he got lost while playing outside.
And he happened to get on a ship to Korea. Right?
What? That's a bit...
Be quiet.
Dong Gu, you did it again.
I'll retire after this movie. You can be the director.
- I give up. - Sorry?
If you guys need any help, ask Dong Gu.
He has as much authority as I do from now on.
Director Kang, I trust you.
Sorry? Okay.
I'm a director.
We need some additional tickets to Dubai. Is that possible?
What? Okay. Please call me back.
Okay.
Gosh, I'm so busy.
That's Sol's favorite.
Come on.
I don't have much time.
There you go!
One more time.
Come out!
Do you see this?
I'm not going home until I catch you!
Sol, I'm home!
You're home.
Yes.
I came by to pick up something.
- What's all this? - This?
Well, you see, Sol's father's secretary came by and left all this.
- Dong Gu. You're home. - Hi.
- Dong Gu. About all this... - Sorry, I need to get something.
I'm in a hurry.
What's she doing?
Is she Gollum or what?
Hey. What are you doing? Are you a miner?
Are you going to work in a coal mine?
What are you looking for?
I told you it's none of your business, you baboon.
Baboon?
Have you lost your mind?
I couldn't possibly curse in front of Sol.
Sol. What's this?
What is this paper you have?
There seems to be something written here.
Don't.
- Give it to me. - Why? What is it?
Just give it to me. It's none of your business.
That just makes me more curious.
- Give it to me. Let me see it. - No. Don't read it.
Hey. Give it to me.
- That hurts. - Let me see it.
Darn it.
Hey, hey. Wait.
Soo Ah. What do you think you're doing? What are you doing?
Hey.
Are you eating paper? Seriously?
Look.
I ate it all up. So what?
She's a complete maniac.
She's crazy.
That was really close.
But why was that in Sol's hands?
How did that happen?
It doesn't matter as long as I didn't get caught.
My stomach.
I don't feel well again.
Doctor. What's wrong with her?
I think she has stomach cramps.
- What did you eat? - Sorry?
Well, I had a few drinks yesterday.
What else?
Nothing in particular.
What are you talking about? You ate paper earlier.
Paper? What type of paper?
- A sketchbook sheet. - What?
Why did you eat that?
- Was it an appetizer? - No. You've got it wrong.
Stop asking me questions, and do something about this.
All right. All right.
We'll do a blood test and an endoscopy.
All right.
What's wrong with you these days?
I can't understand you.
Inside of me
There's so much of me
Doctor. What's there inside me?
You have a small cyst...
- and a mild stomach ulcer. - Is that so?
Inside of me
There are so many cysts
It's nothing serious,
so stop singing and give me that now. Please?
There you go.
Finally. Hurry up, and take him to the recovery room.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Inside of me
Bring in the next patient.
- Let me put a mouth piece on you. - All right.
Bite it.
I'll put in the anesthetic now.
Wait. This won't hurt, will it?
This is my first time undergoing an endoscopy.
Don't worry.
Once the anesthetic is in, you'll fall asleep. You won't feel a thing.
Here.
Actually, anesthetics don't work quite well for me.
It works perfectly fine.
All right.
Let's begin.
Here we go.
Let go of this. You have to let go of this.
Nothing lasts forever
You eventually changed
For no reason
What? Why aren't you singing along?
Again.
For no reason
None
You have no sincerity
Okay. You did a great job.
I've never seen a patient act like this from the beginning.
Why are all my patients like this today?
Please let go of this.
I have to complete your checkup.
No. I'm not going to give it to you.
If you bring Du Shik, I'll give it to you.
Du Shik?
Du Shik as in when you count numbers?
No.
I'm talking about Du Shik.
My friend, Du Shik, who's really cute and cool.
If you don't bring Du Shik over to me,
I'll refuse to open my mouth.
Is there a Bong Du Shik here by any chance?
Sorry? That's me.
Are you Mr. Bong Du Shik?
Yes. That's me. What is it?
This patient says she has something to say to you.
She insisted she wouldn't cooperate unless we brought you here.
Excuse me?
- I apologize. - This happens all the time.
Ms. Min Soo Ah.
Mr. Bong Du Shik is here.
Go ahead, and tell him.
You're right.
My friend, Du Shik, is here.
What's wrong with you? Stop this.
I have something I want to say to you.
What is it? Hurry up, and say it.
Du Shik.
You see,
I think...
I like you.
What?
Min Soo Ah...
likes Bong Du Shik...
a lot.
What?
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I've never seen someone confess their feelings here.
Love confession during an endoscopy. That's a first.
I'm so tired.
- Are you feeling better? - Yes.
Is the checkup over?
Am I in a serious condition?
No. Other than a slight infection in your stomach, you're fine.
That's good to hear.
Why are you laughing?
Did I fart during the checkup by any chance?
No. It's not that.
You told your friend that you liked him.
What? I confessed?
To whom?
- I think his last name was Bong. - Bong?
- Was it Bong Du Shik? - Yes. That was his name.
Then you mean to tell me that I confessed to Bong Du Shik?
How did that happen?
You refused to cooperate...
unless we brought your friend to you.
What?
I can't believe this.
I must be crazy. I'm crazy.
This is so embarrassing.
How will I possibly face him?
Hello?
Yes. This is he.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry I called you so suddenly.
It's fine. But why did you want to talk to me?
I wanted to thank you...
for taking care of Yoon Ah and Sol.
It's not something you should thank me for.
I really wanted to tell you how thankful I am.
And...
this...
is for you.
What? "For me"?
Do you want me to take this money and get lost?
Is that it?
You've been watching too many dramas.
This is so lame, and nobody does this in dramas anymore.
- I... - Are you that rich?
Let's see how much you brought.
Gosh. What?
(To Dong Gu...)
What's this?
It's a letter.
I couldn't express my gratitude in words.
I see.
I thought...
I'll read the letter at home.
And I want to ask you a favor.
I want...
to take care of Yoon Ah and Sol.
What?
I still love Yoon Ah.
"Love"?
Then you shouldn't have left in the first place.
You...
don't know what Yoon Ah's life has been like.
How dare you say you want to take care of her now?
I know that I've been a coward.
I know that I can never be forgiven.
That's why I want to pay my debt...
to Yoon Ah and Sol even though I know it's too late.
Can you help me, Dong Gu?
You really have watched too many dramas.
Did you think that I would say,
"I see. Sol would prefer her rich father..."
"rather than a useless person like me."
"It's sad, but I'll let them go"?
Listen to me carefully.
I'll protect...
Yoon Ah and Sol no matter what. So...
Don't ever contact them again.
I'm not going to give up.
Never.
Min Soo Ah...
likes Bong Du Shik...
a lot.
That doesn't make sense.
Soo Ah likes me?
Oh, my.
Hello.
Du Shik, let's grab a drink.
"A drink"?
- Why do you want to drink suddenly? - Just because.
I suddenly feel like having a drink.
Really? All right.
I feel like it too.
Hello, Jun Ki.
What? What do you mean?
Hello. Come in.
What is this place? Why are you here?
It just happened.
Why did you bring so many things?
These are drinks.
He wanted to drink.
Really? That's great.
I really wanted to drink too.
You too?
Then should we drink until the end today?
Should we?
It's been a while. Let's go!
Let's drink until we lost ourselves.
Let's go!
Let's drink until we go crazy.
You should do it too.
No, that's so childish.
Let's go!
Let's drink!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
What's wrong with you two?
Is something wrong?
It's been a while since just us girl have gotten together.
Do you want to have a drink?
Should we?
I'd love to, but I don't feel so good.
I'll take care of Sol. You two should drink.
Really?
Yoon Ah, let's go!
Let's drink!
Okay. Let's go!
- Let's go, Sol! - Let's go!
What?
Seo Jin broke up with you?
She says it's difficult to go out with me.
I see why Seo Jin said that,
and that's why I wanted to make things right.
But I hesitated.
At first, I was thankful for how far I've gotten.
But I keep getting greedy.
- So are you breaking up with her? - What?
When that happens,
you will...
no longer be alive.
No!
I won't break up with her.
Don't worry.
Of course.
If not,
you and Seo Jin...
- will no longer... - Will no longer...
- be alive. - be alive.
Here.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
It's been a while since we got together.
I know. There aren't any guests,
and Sol is asleep.
It's good.
We'll go bankrupt if we stay like this.
But it's nice and fun to be here...
by ourselves.
- But Seo Jin, - Yes?
did something happen between you and Jun Ki?
Did you fight?
It's been a little difficult recently.
- What is? - Everything.
I don't think he likes me...
as much as I like him.
I feel like I was in love with him by myself.
Why? To me, it seems like Jun Ki likes you more.
Yes.
Well,
but why don't I know?
I don't know. I really don't know.
Drink up.
Why are you sighing?
Just.
I'm a little nervous.
Why?
Are you nervous now that Sol's dad has appeared?
Are you afraid that Yoon Ah will go to him?
- Gosh. - Hey.
It's not like that.
But he's Sol's real dad.
And he's capable.
And he leaves Korea in a few days.
So I'm a little anxious.
Gosh, you don't need to feel anxious.
A few days ago,
Sol called him "dad".
I felt as if my heart...
had dropped.
So I keep feeling anxious.
I feel bad that I have to leave them for a month for the movie.
You should propose to her then.
"Propose"?
I'm not capable enough for that.
Yoon Ah.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Have you ever regretted going out...
with my brother?
No.
I've never regretted.
Really?
No. Dong Gu...
isn't talented, he is small-minded,
and he gets angry easily.
So he seems like a child,
but he loves me more than anyone else in the world.
I can see that from his eyes.
I can see how he cares for me...
and loves me.
That's enough for me.
Gosh, that's making me cringe. I feel like I'm getting sick again.
Are you saying that you can tell by looking in his eyes?
Yes.
I still don't understand.
Love is so difficult.
Love is always difficult.
I want to give up everything these days.
Why?
Do you have a crush on someone?
- Who is it? - Really?
No, don't worry about it.
By the way,
do you like playing hide-and-seek?
- Hide-and-seek? - Yes.
I love hide-and-seek very much.
Do you want to play it?
Since Soo Ah didn't drink,
you be "it".
I'm hiding.
What?
What's wrong with Yoon Ah?
Do we have to play hide-and-seek?
Hey, Seo Jin.
Where are you going?
You're "it".
I should go and hide.
Hey, wait.
Look for us after a count of 10, okay?
Goodness.
Soo Ah.
I'm hiding.
I'm definitely not hiding in the laundry room.
Never come here.
What's wrong with everyone?
Do I really have to look for them?
This is insane.
Both you and me,
life is so difficult.
Don't you think?
I know.
Why are you laughing?
It's funny.
Both of you seem superficial.
When did you become so superficial?
That's silly and cowardly.
- Why? - Isn't it?
Hey.
Since when did we care about competence?
You're worried that he's rich and competent.
What does competence have to do with love?
You're the same, Jun Ki.
You're not Kim Soo Hyun or Gong Yoo.
You have nothing to lose, but you're such a coward.
You refused help so that you can succeed on your own,
but it was a complete lie.
Gosh, am I wrong?
Is it normal to live like this?
It makes me a little sad.
I didn't think that we'd change.
We can be...
a little nerdy.
I still thought our lives were amazing.
Right.
Since when did I become such a coward?
Being a coward isn't as bad.
I'm the least accomplished person in the world.
That's right.
I almost forgot.
Shall I tell you shocking news?
Apparently, Soo Ah...
Soo Ah likes me.
What?
Soo Ah likes you?
Aren't you surprised?
I was really surprised too.
Come on, that can't be right.
He's right. That's impossible.
Wait.
Why is it Impossible?
Soo Ah is a great person.
Gosh.
She's cool and pretty.
- Right? - Goodness.
She's innocent too.
You're dating Dong Gu's little sister.
Hey, you punk.
That's still wrong.
You punk, that's wrong.
That's wrong, you punk.
You jerk.
- That's not what I mean. - Come here.
- Is it a mustache? - It's a lucky charm.
Even if I'm not with you, take a look at it.
Think that I'm always beside you, okay?
You know that I'm your number one fan, right?
Don't forget that I'm always cheering for you.
You can do it, Jun Ki.
To you,
aren't I a woman?
To me, you're a man.
I think I like you.
Let's start our relationship as a man and a woman.
Jun Ki.
Let's go for it.
Your career is finally going well after years of effort.
I don't want to interfere.
Where are you going?
I'm going to see my fan.
What do you mean?
What about your meeting with the president?
It doesn't matter. He can cancel the contract if he wants.
What's wrong all of a sudden?
I'll live like I did before.
Without plans or being matured.
I won't be a coward.
Jun Ki, Jun Ki.
Gosh, that startled me. What was that noise?
What's this smell?
Who farted? Who?
What? No one is here.
Did I fart?
It stinks.
I played hide-and-seek all night.
My whole body hurts.
My head hurts.
Gosh, my head hurts so much.
My stomach hurts too.
What?
Why is she sleeping here?
It's awkward.
I should just go to sleep in my room.
That must hurt a lot.
She must be sleeping deeply.
Where is it?
Right, there it is.
I hope that she moves a little more.
Gosh, that hurt.
Are you okay, Soo Ah?
Yes, I'm fine.
When did you get here?
I just got here.
I see.
I was sleeping so deeply.
I had no idea that you were here.
I thought so.
Aren't you picking up the phone?
I should. I will.
Hello? Yes.
What? Now?
Okay, I'll be there.
Soo Ah.
Could you help me?
Soo Ah, what brings you here?
Me?
I was driving, and I saw you.
If you're going to an interview, let me give you a ride.
I'm okay. I can take the subway.
Just get in. Hurry.
- I'm really okay. - Get in.
Du Shik, you're here too.
Yes. Seo Jin, take this.
- I don't want it. - I want it.
Seo Jin, please take it.
The door on this side doesn't open, and the window is broken.
Just take it.
The window opens a little bit.
Yes. It tastes very good.
Gosh.
Give it to me.
- What are you doing? - Close the widow.
I'm stuck again.
I knew it.
- Success. - Okay.
What are you talking about? Success?
What are you waiting for? Let's go.
Okay.
What are you doing now? Where are we going?
Jun Ki asked us to kidnap you.
So stay quiet.
What? I can't believe him.
- I'm getting out. - Hey, stay still.
- Stop the car! - Hey!
Leave Soo Ah alone.
- It's dangerous. - Du Shik, do something!
It hurts!
- Fix the window! - Stay still!
Hey.
What are you doing?
Yoon Ah.
What are you doing here?
I want to return some things.
- Yoon Ah, that's... - I know how you feel.
I also know...
you're sincerely sorry.
But no matter what you do,
I won't change my mind.
I really love Dong Gu.
I'd been suffering a lot,
but he helped me move on.
I don't even blame you anymore. I mean it.
Since Sol and I...
met Dong Gu...
I mean, since we met the family,
we've been really happy.
So...
let's just keep the good memories.
If you keep doing this,
even our good memories will be ruined too.
Wouldn't that be too sad?
I'll get going now.
Call me whenever you miss Sol.
Make sure we've packed everything.
I want everything ready when we're in Dubai, okay?
- Okay. - Okay.
Dong Gu, I'd like to see our schedule.
- Okay. - Bring it to me.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
What kind of parent leaves this tiny baby alone?
Sorry for the trouble. We'll get going.
Candy never cries even when she is lonely or sad
Neither does Dong Gu
- What's this? - Let's celebrate Sol's 100th day.
Thank you, everyone.
I like you.
I really like you, Yoon Ah.
I really like you, Dong Gu.
Why would I break up with you?
My heart races...
whenever I'm with you.
Director, there's something I want to tell you.
(Lee Jun Ki's Emergency Press Conference)
Gosh, what is this? Why isn't he here yet?
Seriously. What's going on?
What is this place?
Who are these people?
- He's here. - He's here.
He's here.
Hello. I'm actor Lee Jun Ki.
Thank you all...
for coming on such short notice.
I'd like to tell you all the truth...
about the romance rumor between Cindy and myself.
(Breaking news)
- Cindy and I... - What's this?
"Cindy is getting married."
"She was pregnant for three months"?
Cindy is getting married to actor Lee Min Seok.
She's pregnant.
Gosh, I knew it.
Why would she go out with a new actor like Jun Ki?
Let's go.
- Wait. - Gosh.
Cindy and I...
Are you going to take them all?
Excuse me!
Wait! Where are you going?
I...
Everyone's left.
What's this? Where is everyone going?
Cindy has announced her wedding plans.
Why would they want to stay here?
You were being so pretentious. This is embarrassing.
I know. You said we had to get Seo Jin here by all means.
Is this what you wanted to show her?
It's so embarrassing.
What are you all doing right now?
- I'm leaving. - Wait.
Seo Jin. Don't leave like this.
Let go of me.
I was going to tell all the reporters...
that you're my girlfriend...
and that nothing is going on between Cindy and me.
Are you stupid? Did I ask you to do that?
It's not what you want? Then what do you want?
You're so stupid.
- Forget it. I'm leaving. - Seo Jin.
I'm sorry.
I've been a coward.
But I've realized...
what's the most important to me.
It's you.
Are you sure?
Seo Jin.
I love you.
I really do.
I can finally see it a little.
- What do you mean? - People say...
you can see it in their eyes...
about how much someone cares about you.
And...
I'm starting to see it a little.
Really?
But just a little?
That's not possible.
Take a close look.
I'm sure you'll see a lot. Take a look.
That's gross. Stop it.
Just look. Look how much I care about you.
Look.
Are you joking around again?
They look great together.
Yes, indeed.
Why do they fight so often if they like each other so much?
Then shall we really go to the restaurant today?
All right.
Let's go. I'm buying.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Soo Ah, aren't you hungry?
I am. A little.
Really? In that case, do you want to go somewhere nice...
and eat?
Just the two of us?
Why?
Is there a reason why friends can't have a meal together?
Right.
But which restaurant do you mean by somewhere nice?
Well, let's go outside and find one.
Let's go.
Why isn't anyone home? It's strange.
Hello, this is Waikiki Guesthouse.
Yes.
What? Dong Gu?
Yes, all right. Okay.
(Dong Gu)
Dong Gu, what's this?
What are you doing?
Yoon Ah.
Yoon Ah,
would you marry me?
I'll make you and Sol happy forever.
Marry me, Yoon Ah.
I don't want to.
What?
Why?
Was I being too rude? Then I'll do it again.
Yoon Ah,
would you marry me, please?
No.
Why?
I'll tell you afterwards.
Dong Gu, what happened to your job?
The director just called.
I decided not to go to Dubai.
I couldn't leave without...
you and Sol.
Why not?
Is it because of her dad?
No, it's not that.
Gosh, you require so much effort.
What?
Kang Dong Gu.
Are you really that anxious?
Why are you so anxious?
I'm not. Why are you?
Gosh, you are a coward.
I'm not.
Did you think...
I'd be moved if you do this?
You're going to give up the job that you wanted to do all your life?
For me?
Can't you trust me?
I...
It's not like that.
Dong Gu.
Don't worry.
Just go.
I'll always be here.
I'll be...
next to you forever.
Forever?
I'm going.
- Bye. - Bye.
Bye.
Don't you fight and talk about breaking up when I'm not here.
All right.
You should take care of my sister.
You know what happens if you don't, right?
I know. I know.
"You will no longer be alive."
I'd treat her like a princess...
if that means I don't have to listen to you say that.
Okay. That's good.
Soo Ah, good luck with your business.
And stop scolding Du Shik, okay?
I never did.
I don't do that nowadays.
- Why not? - What?
Why aren't you scolding him? I'm really curious.
What?
Be quiet. Go. Go to Dubai.
Du Shik, you too. Quit dating.
Get some scenarios done, okay?
I don't date.
I didn't.
Anyway, finish the writing before I come back.
I'll check regularly.
All right. Stop preaching.
Yoon Ah, I'm going now.
All right. Take care, Dong Gu.
All right.
Don't forget to eat and sleep well even when I'm not here.
Make sure you digest everything and go to bathrooms regularly.
And don't even look at other men.
Gosh, okay. Okay.
Stop talking, and go.
All right. But I need to say goodbye to Sol.
Sol.
Don't forget my face.
Don't be sick. Be healthy.
I'll be back soon, okay?
- I'm really going now. - Okay.
Sol, bye.
Dad.
What?
Sol.
What did you just say?
Dad.
Did you hear that? Did you?
Did you hear her calling me "dad"?
- Yes. - We did. Are you happy now?
Of course.
Sol, can you say that one more time?
Say "dad". "Dad".
Gosh, why are you hiding? You're not easy, are you?
- One more time. Just one more time. - Gosh.
Stop it, Dong Gu. You'll be late.
I don't want to leave now that Sol is calling me dad.
Yoon Ah, should I just stay?
You're starting again. Go.
All right.
I'm really going.
- Okay. - Okay.
Sol.
Dad's leaving now.
- Bye. - Bye.
- Bye. - Take care.
(2 months later)
Who are you?
I know you're there.
Do you want to come out, or should I go to you?
Come out now, you scum.
I'm surprised you found me.
You're quick-witted, probably because you're the president.
Shut it!
Set our people free, you alien.
I'm surprised to see a president who worries about his people.
However, it's too late.
We've taken over your people and land already.
Don't you dare harm my people.
If you do,
this finger jab will teach you a lesson.
That's absurd.
Cut. That's no good.
("President is Bruce Lee")
You fool.
Why did you have to cough at that moment?
It's suffocating. Why are you making me do this anyway?
I'm the writer.
We have a low budget. I have no choice.
Can't a writer do this much for his own movie?
Dong Gu. I made time to play this main role for you.
What am I doing here?
I'm the famous Song Jun Seok of "Newsroom".
How much longer are you going to mention that?
You did that one drama and been bumming around since.
What did you just say?
Didn't I tell you I'm selecting my next piece very carefully?
I'm doing this without a guarantee fee. You should be grateful.
If we shoot this, will this movie actually be released?
Why are there more actors than staff members?
A great movie doesn't depend on the number of staff members.
At least we have a great director.
- Whom are you trying to kid? - I agree. I can't believe you.
You're more unbelievable!
How could you write such a terrible scenario?
- What do you mean? - What kind of director are you?
- I'm a writer. I wrote this. - You two are no different.
- All you did was bum around. - Be quiet!
You asked me to write an article. But are you fighting again?
Shall I write an article about you three fighting?
You fools.
This movie is bound to fail.
Let's just stop here.
What are you talking about? This movie's going to be a big hit.
He's right. We're going to go to the Cannes Film Festival.
And I'm going to win the Best Actor Award.
Dong Gu.
It's our food.
I've brought your meals. You should eat first.
Welcome, Yoon Ah.
I see my dear, little Sol's here as well.
- Is the shoot going well? - Of course.
I can just feel that this will be a big hit.
Let's eat lunch and continue shooting.
- Our food's here. - Let's eat.
Excuse me. What do you think you're doing?
You said you scouted the location.
You didn't pay the fee again, did you?
Have we been shooting here without a permit?
We have a low budget.
- What will we do? - What else?
- Run! - My goodness.
Darn it.
- Run. - All right.
- Hurry. Run. - Stop right there.
(We'd like to thank the viewers for watching Welcome to Waikiki.)
(Special thanks to guest stars Jung Kyu Soo and Kim Jin Woo.)
(Welcome to Waikiki)