To me, you're a man. What should I do?
- Of course, I'm a man. - That's not what I'm saying.
I think I like you.
- What? - I like you.
Why are you doing this? Come here.
Are you ill? You seem fine.
Is this a prank?
Did you set this up with the others?
- You're really good at acting. - I really like you.
What?
Do you mean it?
You like me?
You?
I'll ask you this again.
Am I...
not a woman to you?
Why are you doing this?
You can't be a woman to me. You're like my little sister.
I saw you since you were little.
We even share razors.
Don't do this. Don't.
All right.
I get what you're saying. Get out.
Why are you being so scary?
- Get out. - What?
- Get out! - Hey. Seo Jin.
- Seo Jin. - I told you to get out.
Seo Jin. Seo Jin, open the door.
We should talk. Seo Jin!
What is this?
Why are you knocking on my sister's door?
I told you not to go anywhere near my sister!
- It's not like that. - Come here! Come here!
- Dong Gu, it's not like that. - What?
Gosh, I don't need to feel bad.
He always causes trouble...
and earns his living by playing as extras.
(I'm a Woman Too)
Do I know Goni?
(Kim Hye Soo)
- He's the best gambler I've seen. - "Do I know Goni?"
"He's the best gambler I've seen."
Gosh, I want to be like Kim Hye Soo.
I want to have a cool life like her.
I agree. She's so cool.
- I'm home. - Hello.
Du Shik, why were you so late? I've been waiting for you.
Me? Why?
- Do you have something to tell me? - Yes.
You told me...
to find something that will make me happy for the rest of my life.
That's why I've been thinking, as I'm pretty...
and good at singing and dancing... You knew that, right?
I didn't.
So what do you want to do?
- I want to become an idol. - What? An idol?
You want to become an idol at the age of 29?
You're old enough to have a baby of your own.
- You must be crazy. - Gosh.
Maybe that's too much.
What should I do?
Isn't there anything you've always wanted to do,
maybe as a child?
There's one.
I've always wanted to learn fashion design at college.
But I can't take the entrance test at this age.
Why not? Haven't you read the news?
There are so many elders...
nearing the age of 70 who attend college after taking the test.
- Do you think I can do that? - Of course.
I'll help you with your studies.
- You? - "You?"
He used to be called a genius.
He's a writer who is good at everything else except for writing.
- Be quiet. - Yes, Writer Bong.
But you need to promise me to do your very best.
I will. Thank you, Du Shik.
I'm home.
Hello, Seo Jin. Did you eat?
I'm not hungry. I'll go rest in my room.
Is there something wrong with Seo Jin?
She hasn't been looking well these past few days.
- Why did we come to a bookstore? - Well,
to prepare for the entrance test, you need to buy a book.
I need to know your level first,
so I'll take a simple test.
Well, let's start with history.
Who was the crown prince that was the second son of King Yeongjo...
and the father of King Jeongjo,
who ruled in Yeongjo's place, but was ordered to a tragic death?
- I know that one. - Really?
- I even saw the movie. - Yes.
- Give me a hint. - Hint? Hint. All right.
- A wooden rice chest. - A wooden rice chest?
I know it!
- Yoo Ah In. - Yoo...
It's the crown prince.
Yes, it's Yoo Ah In.
No, which crown prince is it?
- The crown prince. - I told you it's Yoo Ah In.
In the movie, he says,
"I'm dumbfounded."
That was in the movie, "Veteran".
And the name of the crown prince is Sado.
Crown Prince Sado?
So that's why the movie is called "Sado".
- Yes. - Gosh, they did mention Sado,
but I thought it meant something else.
It's fine. You can study again.
Don't feel too bad.
Thanks.
It's nice to hear positive encouragements from you.
It's nice to be positive at all times.
So don't you worry. Cheer up!
All right. I'll cheer up.
I haven't been home for a few days, nor have I had a chance to wash.
By the way,
I don't even remember the last time I saw Yoon Ah.
Gosh.
Kang Dong Gu.
Do you have the papers ready regarding the venues?
Yes, here you are.
Oh, my. You found a lot.
You must have worked overnight. Well done.
But I think you'll have to work tonight again. I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Then you should go visit a sauna or something for a short time.
I'll give you an hour.
An hour?
Soo Ah, try reading this.
Can you do it?
Gosh, of course I can.
What do you take me for?
- Let me start. - Okay.
"Hi, Johnny."
- "Do you..." - It's not Johnny. It's "Jane".
Okay. Let me try again.
"Hi, Jane."
"Do you want some pine..."
"Pine..."
Pineapple.
That's right. Pineapple.
I mixed them up. My misty.
Not "misty".
Mistake.
What?
I was talking about the drama. You don't know "Misty"?
Kim Nam Joo's in it.
It's my fabric drama.
Not "fabric".
Favorite.
I see.
Sorry. English is definitely not my forte.
I'm sure it's just because it's been a long time. Don't worry.
Thank you, Du Shik. Let me try again.
Yoon Ah! Yoon Ah!
What's going on?
Dong Gu, it's been a while.
Are you finished today?
Cut it out. Where is Yoon Ah?
She should be somewhere in this house. Why?
What? I need to ask her something.
Gosh. I don't have much time. Is she on the third floor?
What is it? Gosh.
Hello, Director.
I'm at the sauna.
I'm putting on my underwear now.
My right foot is going in right now.
I'll be right there.
Gosh.
What's with him?
Was someone here?
I think I heard Dong Gu's voice.
He was here, but he left right away.
He said he wanted to ask you something.
Me?
What could it be?
This is not even my first audition. Why am I so nervous?
I really want the role this time.
My fans' support might be able to...
cheer me up.
There are no comments.
Is junki_love_ busy?
- Please come in. - Okay.
Don't be nervous.
Good luck. You can do this, right? Yes.
Okay.
Is the media supposed to cover up problems?
Are they supposed to distort the truth and manipulate the public?
The media should never...
distort or cover up the truth.
News programs should fear those without power...
and be feared by those with power.
That is...
a journalist's obligation and fate.
Do you understand?
That's all.
Thank you.
Well...
Thank you for giving me a chance to audition.
Hold on.
Do you like bean sprout soup?
Sorry?
I do.
Why don't we discuss your role over some bean sprout soup?
Pardon?
- What do you mean? - I liked your acting.
I was looking for a new face.
Are you sure?
(Newsroom)
What are you doing?
What? What's the matter?
Well... The thing is...
Congratulations!
- Congratulations, Jun Ki. - Congratulations, Jun Ki.
Thank you.
- Thank you so much. - Jun Ki, it's Dong Gu.
Dong Gu?
- Hi, Dong Gu. - Congratulations!
Good luck with your drama! You can do this!
Okay. Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Okay.
Get up. Come on.
- Lee Jun Ki - Lee Jun Ki
Thank you.
It's the director.
Hello, Director.
I'm in front of announcer Park Chang Ho's house.
Thank you for arranging this interview.
Okay.
I'll collect as much information as possible. Bye.
I'm nervous.
I can't believe I'll be interviewing Announcer Park Chang Ho.
(Park Chang Ho)
Your place is big.
Ma'am, please take this.
Thank you.
- Oh, my. - What does he want for lunch?
He'll skip lunch because of the interview.
It must have been hard.
Take some vitamins,
and lie down.
Thank you, ma'am.
- Oh, my. - Are you okay?
You can go in.
- Okay. - By the way,
if he wants to see me,
please tell him I'm not home.
Tell him I went out.
I'd appreciate it if you could do that.
All right.
She's not here?
Excuse me.
Hello, sir.
I'm here to interview you. I'm Lee Jun Ki, an actor.
You're here. Give me a second.
Welcome. Nice to meet you.
Hello.
It's an honor to meet you.
I hope I'm not interrupting anything.
Not at all. You're shooting a drama about announcers.
I'm more than willing to help.
- Please have a seat. - Okay.
Were you writing something?
I'm preparing an autobiography.
I was organizing my manuscripts.
It'll be about 20 volumes.
20 volumes?
You've been an announcer for such a long time.
I'm sure you have a lot to write about.
I've been trying to boil it down, but it's still a lot.
Should we get started?
(Interview Questions for Announcer Park Chang Ho)
I'd like to know what made you want to become an announcer.
What made me want to become an announcer?
I think it was 1987.
- Okay. - It was snowing.
It was probably December 12 or sometime around then.
Anyway, my family lived in a wooden house,
which was rare at that time.
It was built in a combination of Japanese and American styles.
I see.
The house had two rooms.
One room belonged to my mom, dad, me, my little brother,
and our two dogs, Bok Sil and Teun Sil.
The other room belonged to...
my three older sisters.
My family has had a tremendous impact on me.
Let me talk about my eldest sister first.
She was 170cm tall, which was pretty tall back then.
She weighed 48kg. She was quite thin.
Hold on. Why is he telling me all this?
Something's strange.
She's studying hard.
Soo Ah.
Drink this.
Can I check how far you've done?
What? You don't have to.
Come on. Are you worried you got some questions wrong?
Don't worry. Let me see.
It's okay.
It's really okay.
All the pages are empty.
What have you been doing all this time?
"Gangnam Station Exit 4"?
I suddenly remembered the old days.
I used to do this a lot on my textbooks.
I was going to study after this, I swear.
It's okay. I used to do this a lot too.
Finish it.
Thank you. I'll be quick.
My eldest sister loved mung bean pancakes...
and kimchi pancakes.
She met a man who was doing research...
for a flour company.
They got married in the fall of 1973.
They have a son and two daughters.
They're living happily in Pennsylvania...
in a red-roofed house three blocks away...
from the post office.
I see.
Now,
let's move onto my second eldest sister.
She is...
162cm tall and weighs 50kg.
She has an oval-shaped face.
She loved poetry when she was young.
Her hobby was knitting, and...
Jun Ki.
Yes? What?
I'm sorry, sir.
Due to acting practice, I couldn't sleep much last night.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
It could happen.
Sleep is resting in an unconscious state.
It's a natural behavior.
Sleep. What is sleep?
To understand sleep,
it's necessary to look at Freud's theories of psychoanalysis.
In order to understand them,
one must know about Freud.
Freud's name is Sigmund Freud.
He was born in Pribor, Czech Republic in 1856, between...
Jacob Freud and his 2nd wife Amalia, who was 20 years younger than him.
The makeup of his family was very unique.
Seven of his siblings...
His family was quite poor.
When Freud was nine, he received the best...
He was dedicated to school... He was 17 years old.
It was built in...
It showed how academically talented Freud was.
Yoon Ah.
Dong Gu, what brings you here?
I had an errand to run in the neighborhood.
I happened to see you.
- Did you just finish class? - Yes.
What's wrong with your face?
Your eyes are so red.
- Did you not sleep well? - That's not it.
My eyes get red easily.
I'm okay.
I heard that you were looking for me yesterday.
I heard you wanted to ask me something.
Oh, right.
When will THAAD issues be resolved?
Pardon?
You rejected me five seconds after I confessed to you,
but we're still both Koreans.
We can discuss international relations issues.
That's true,
but I'm not familiar with those issues...
Are you hungry?
What you craved was just sundae?
Yes, it's my favorite food.
Dong Gu, are you really okay?
You look very tired.
No, I am not.
People often tell me that I look tired.
How about you?
Is the class fun?
Yes, it's so much fun.
I also like my classmates.
We learned how to bake a cake today.
Dong Gu?
- Yes, what is it? - Did you just fall asleep?
No, I was thinking.
"Should I dip sundae in salt..."
"or pickled shrimp?"
Here's your sundae.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
It looks so delicious.
Let's see.
Try some.
- Dong Gu? - Yes?
What is it?
I wasn't sleeping. I was praying.
You don't usually pray.
I do before eating snack food...
especially sundae.
I was hungry.
It's so delicious.
Isn't it, Dong Gu?
As such, Society of Jesus is based on Catholicism at risk.
Goodness, I digressed from the topic of sleep.
There's more to say, but I'll skip it.
Let's go back to the main topic.
She loved me, and her hobby was knitting.
I'll finish the story of my second eldest sister.
My second eldest sister...
Jun Ki?
- Jun Ki. - Yes.
I was listening about Freud's psychoanalysis.
I talked about it 20 hours ago.
- You must be very tired. - 20 hours?
I'm sorry, sir.
What would you like for lunch, sir?
Just choose among meat, fish, salad, and porridge.
Just choose.
I studied everything about food in the encyclopedia.
Just choose one, please?
Please I beg you.
Okay.
- Jun Ki, what would you like? - Pardon?
I...
I'll eat meat.
Meat?
Which meat?
Pork? Beef? Mutton? Chicken?
I'd like pork.
Pork? That's a good choice.
Shall we go then?
Wait.
A certain body type is necessary to eat pork.
What's your body type?
According to Heo Jun's "Mirror of Eastern Medicine",
eating food according to one's body type is very important.
We must learn about Heo Jun who wrote "Mirror of Eastern Medicine".
Heo Jun was a court physician during the Joseon Dynasty.
He was the 20th generation of the Yangcheon Heo clan.
He learned how to read and write at an early age.
He was talented in various academic fields.
He was especially interested in Eastern philosophy...
such as Confucianism, Taoism, and Buddhism.
Based on these teachings,
he wrote a book called "Mirror of Eastern Medicine".
Heo Jun...
- I can't believe it. - Soo Ah.
Are you still eating?
Yes, why?
I thought you'd come back after eating, but it's been two hours.
Soo Ah, it's time to study.
No one should bother anyone who's eating.
Aren't you being too harsh?
I can't study if I'm hungry.
Really?
I'm sorry. I wasn't thoughtful enough.
Keep eating. Be comfortable.
I'm back.
What? Where have you been?
- Park Chang Ho's interview. - What?
Didn't you go there yesterday? Did you just finish?
What kind of interview is two days long?
Exactly.
I've never seen anyone as talkative as he was.
He lectured me on the history of prehistoric times for lunch.
- Hello, everyone. - Yoon Ah.
- Have you had dinner? - Yes.
I bumped into Dong Gu, so we ate together.
Sol must be awake.
She ate with Dong Gu?
He went to Sokcho for a few days for location scouting.
Really? Then why is he back?
Hello? Yes, Director.
Why are you so late?
- Where are you? - I'm at the sauna.
I'm wearing my underwear.
My right leg is going in.
I'll leave as soon as I put on my pants.
I'll keep my shirt off. I love you.
He'll scold me a lot when I get there.
It's fine as long as I saw Yoon Ah.
- Soo Ah. - May I come in?
Of course.
Look who's here.
- Do you have something to say? - No.
What did you eat with Dong Gu?
- We ate sundae. - I see.
Did Dong Gu go back to Sokcho?
Sokcho?
Did he go to Sokcho?
You didn't know? He went to Sokcho for his movie.
I wondered why he came back.
It was to see you.
Pardon? What do you mean?
Do you think he came all the way back to Seoul for sundae?
Dong Gu is immature,
and he has no talent.
His future isn't clear.
Still, he's a good person.
He's nice and has a lot of affection.
He's also warm.
I'm just saying.
Have a good night.
By the way, do you like the coat that I gave you?
Yes, it's pretty and warm.
Thank you.
You should thank Dong Gu.
He bought that coat for you.
What?
You didn't know, did you?
I thought you already knew.
Don't tell Dong Gu that I told you.
Okay?
Why doesn't junki_love_ post comments these days?
I wonder if something's wrong.
Shall I send a message?
She might be surprised to hear from me.
(Sending message to junki_love_)
"Hello."
"This is Lee Jun Ki."
"Are you all right?"
Add a question mark. Done.
(Hello, this is Lee Jun Ki. Are you all right?)
What was that?
Where did that sound come from?
Gosh. Seo Jin is so clumsy. She forgot to take her cell phone again.
I'm sure she'll make a fuss, wondering where she left it.
She sure is clumsy.
What is this?
(Hello, this is Lee Jun Ki. Are you all right?)
Junki_love_?
What's going on?
What is it?
Why are you coming in without my permission?
Seo Jin.
How do you explain this?
Were you the one who wrote the comments all along?
- Why did you do it? - Why do you think I did it?
I'm a bit busy right now. If you don't mind, please leave.
Soo Ah. How much longer are you going to watch television?
You watched this drama earlier.
Gosh. You sure are acting strict.
All right. I'll turn it off.
- What do you want me to do? - What?
Shall we study math?
Math?
That's my weakest subject.
That's all right. We'll start with the basics, so don't worry.
Then why don't we try solving this problem?
Here.
Hey. Are you kidding me?
I may not know the basics, but do you think I wouldn't know this?
- The answer's 40, right? - What?
Soo Ah. How could the answer be 40?
If you add 8 to 12, that's 20.
Then you multiply that by 2, so it's 40, right?
Soo Ah. You see,
if you have to multiply or divide,
you have to do it before adding or subtracting.
So you multiply 8 and 2 first,
and afterwards, you add 12.
What? Why do you have to multiply first?
There are priorities in the four fundamental arithmetic operations.
Even if it comes after, you must multiply or divide first.
Who says so?
Well, I don't know who made that rule.
What? Then are you...
trying to teach me when you don't even know who made that rule?
Why do I have to learn something you don't even know?
I can't believe this.
Who is he trying to teach when he doesn't even know anything?
He acted like he knew everything. Whom is he trying to kid?
If I have to calculate it first, it should be in the front.
Why make up a problem like that?
Are you trying to irritate me or what?
Do I have to question your character?
Hey, do you know that...
I'm actually having doubts about fundamental rules of math?
Did you ask if I know Du Shik?
He was the most positive man I knew.
Are you wondering what happened to that Du Shik who was so positive?
Hey, you bonehead.
How dare you doubt math when you have no idea at all?
Quit studying if you're going to behave like this.
If you're not smart enough, you should at least be diligent.
Is this the time to be watching dramas?
Can you even understand the lines in the drama?
You bonehead. Hey, hey, hey.
Did you bring up character? Who are you to bring that up?
I thought I'd help you out because I felt sorry for you.
You fool. You bonehead. Did you really graduate school?
Gosh. You're a complete bonehead. My goodness. You complete fool.
Jun Ki. Then I'll see you on the day of the shooting.
I'll see you then, sir.
Thank you!
Seo Jin.
Were you the one who wrote the comments all along?
- Why did you do it? - Why do you think I did it?
(junki_love_'s account)
I'm so crazy about "Octopus Man" these days.
I know you'll become a big star one day.
You may not have any lines, but you're still charming.
You may only appear briefly, but you have a strong presence.
Your performance is the best.
I have faith in you. Keep up the good work.
- Jun Ki. - You startled me.
Congratulations on getting the part.
I'm really happy for you.
I owe it all to you. Thank you.
What did you say?
I just thanked you.
No, I should be thanking you.
After all, you introduced me to Seo Jin.
As a matter of fact,
I'm going on a date with her today.
What? A date?
Yes. I expressed my feelings to her a few days ago.
She said she wants to meet me today.
This means she has feelings for me too, right?
Thank you so much, Jun Ki.
I'll ask you one more time.
Do you not consider me a woman?
I see you as a man.
What should I do?
- Surprise. - You look great.
Cheer up.
Congratulations, Chewbacca. Treat us to a meal on your payday.
You may slack off at times, but you do know how to act.
I like you.
- Jae Woo - What is it?
You won't be able to meet Seo Jin today.
- What? Why not? - I think I'll regret this.
Regret what? What are you talking about?
If I lose Seo Jin now,
I think I'll regret it for the rest of my life.
What?
If you didn't hear me, never mind.
What is it? Why are you here?
Seo Jin. We need to talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
I'll try.
What is that supposed to mean?
I'll try to look at you...
as a woman from now on.
So...
let's start dating...
as man and woman.
Jun Ki.
We need to keep this a secret from Dong Gu.
- All right. - If he finds out we're dating,
he'll beat me to death. Do you understand me?
All right. I get it.
Let go of me. People are looking at us.
No. I'm not letting go of you.
I'll never let go of you.
Hello.
- Welcome. - Welcome.
- Seo Jin. Show them to their rooms. - All right.
- Hello. - Welcome.
Jun Ki.
Please follow me.
- Come in. Come in. - Please follow me.
I didn't know what to do. There's been a problem at my place.
I owe you all.
We should be thanking you. After all, you've brought us guests.
I heard you'll be staying here as well.
That's right. You see, I have to show them around.
- Then follow me. - Okay.
Why? What is it?
Jun Ki. You remember we have a date later, right?
Yes, of course.
Then we're going on our first date today.
I'm looking forward to it.
What... What are you doing? Someone might see us.
Why do you care? No one's here anyway.
Really?
I'm home.
You... You're home.
Did you come straight home from Sokcho?
Gosh, I'm so tired.
Why are you two together?
I warned you.
I told you not to go anywhere near my sister.
- Where's my stick? - It's... It's not like that.
I met her by accident while going to the dining room to drink water.
That's right.
Really?
What are you doing there?
I... I'm... I'm just cleaning.
There is so much hair on the floor.
Gosh.
- Really? - So much hair.
What... What is that? Is that for me?
This? This is the famous semi-dried squid from Sokcho.
They're the same species as you.
These are squids, and so are you. Squid!
- What did you just say? - Your friend.
What is that sound?
Yoon Ah's teacher, Hyun Joon,
brought his friend.
He's going to stay here for a few days.
Song Hyun Joon is staying here?
Gosh!
What are you doing?
Oh, my. Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
It's so beautifully decorated and nice.
I'm happy you like it.
Oh, my! Who is this?
Dong Gu, when did you come home?
Just now.
We get to meet again.
I heard you're going to stay here for a few days.
Yes, I'll stay here for a few days.
But there are so many other guesthouses.
Why did you come here?
It's nice to go somewhere with people I know.
Yoon Ah is here too.
Oh, I see.
Dong Gu, what's that?
This?
This is semi-dried squid I bought in Sokcho.
They're the same species as Hyun Joon.
Well,
do you want one?
This is a welcome gift...
to celebrate on your stay here.
Sure.
(Life-and-Death Situation)
Jun Ki, I'm going home now.
Get dressed and come outside. I miss you!
Gosh, I can't get used to this.
Gosh.
I didn't know I would go out with Seo Jin.
Right.
She was such a small child with a beard.
I didn't know I'd ever go on dates with her.
This is unbelievable. Unbelievable.
No. No.
But we started dating.
Let's give this a try.
Let's give this a try. Let's go!
Follow me.
They were like family to me when I studied in New York.
We'd go on trips during our vacations.
Really? It must have been fun.
Why doesn't this open?
Dong Gu, will you open this for me?
All right.
Can't you open it?
It doesn't open. It must be broken.
- I'll try. - It doesn't work.
This lid is stuck...
- Oh, my. - Hyun Joon, you're really strong.
It was easy to open.
Hyun Joon, should we grab a drink?
Okay. Sure.
Yoon Ah, we're going to grab a drink. Do you want to join us?
You shouldn't say that to someone who is breastfeeding.
Dong Gu, Sol started eating powdered milk recently.
Really?
But it's too late to drink.
It's only 9pm.
Yoon Ah, Sol is asleep, so you should go and play.
I'll clean this up.
- Would that be okay? - Yes.
It's just for one day.
I want to drink too.
I feel like having a drink.
You must be good at drinking.
I'm not a bad drinker.
- How about you? - I'm not a bad drinker myself.
Do you want to join us?
Let's go.
(Announcer Park Chang Ho)
Why is he calling me?
Hello. How have you been?
Are you doing well, Jun Ki?
I have so many things I want to tell you.
I was wondering why you didn't come.
What?
I'm a little busy nowadays.
I see.
But why does your voice seem so far away?
My phone is a little old.
Really?
But it's so nice to have a phone at all.
Jun Ki,
- do you know how phones were made? - What?
To know about the history of phones, you need to know about telephones.
A telephone was first invented in Havana, Cuba in 1949...
by an Italian named Antonio Meucci.
We normally think that...
The first model...1873... Alexander Graham...
Alexander...British Royal...
In London...Graham...
He started...fixed the exteriors...
Gramophone...so as to help...
In that case, how did smart phones first come to be?
The first smart phone that was developed in 1992...
- by IBM called Simon... - Jun Ki, I'm here.
- To find out about Simon, - What are you doing?
- you need to know about IBM. - Just wait a moment.
- IBM... - Sir.
I'm so thankful for the explanation,
but I need to go in for a shoot. Yes.
I'll call you later.
Sure. Bye.
Gosh, my ear hurts.
Who was it?
It was Announcer Park Chang Ho.
The talkative one?
I haven't seen him for a while, so he's torturing me with calls.
I might need to block his number.
I'm sorry. Let's go.
The film will begin soon.
Jun Ki, let's have popcorn. Yes?
- What's wrong? - It's nothing.
Let's have popcorn.
Otherwise, you go native.
That's right.
Why are there so many kissing scenes in the movie?
Gosh, I'm already feeling awkward as it is.
Why? Don't you like it?
No, it's nothing.
Gosh, it's so awkward.
It's driving me crazy.
No.
You shouldn't think like this.
She's not that hairy kid from the past.
She's an adult now. An adult.
What is this? Why is her hand so small?
Was it always this small?
Oh, my.
What's wrong?
What are you staring at?
Why?
Do I have a beard again?
No, it's not that.
I get it. Am I too pretty?
Do you want to stare at me even though I'm next to you?
Gosh, you like me so much.
I'm so sad it's over.
Jun Ki, I had so much fun today.
Yes.
Sleep tight...
and dream about me.
Oh gosh. I still can't get used to this.
What... What's this?
- Gosh. - Stop it.
Get a hold of yourself.
Why did you drink so much?
Let me go.
I'm going to drink more.
What's this? What's wrong with him?
He had a bet with Hyun Joon, and he got drunk.
I'm sorry. He kept saying he was all right.
Mr. Kang, wake up.
Hey!
What are you doing?
You promised to call me Dong Gu.
Call me Dong Gu. Dong Gu.
All right, Dong Gu.
Wake up.
All right. I will.
No!
You promised to make me sausage bread. Don't forget!
I love sausage buns.
Okay, I'll put two sausages.
Two?
Two sausages?
How much did he drink?
Sorry. I'll take him inside.
- Sausages... - Pull yourself together. Let's go.
- Take him away. - Hey! Du Shik!
Gosh, it smells like vitamins.
How many vitamin pills did he take?
Gosh, it smells like red ginseng.
Seriously, what did he eat?
Gosh, what's the noise? My head aches.
I feel terrible.
Are you waking up now?
That brat.
Gosh, I feel nauseous.
Why are you wiping the floor?
What is this?
Where are my clothes?
Who took them off?
We did. Do you have a problem?
- Why? - Hey.
You wet yourself last night.
What? Me?
It doesn't end there.
You said Hyun Joon and you were brothers now.
You hugged and kissed him.
It was disgusting.
"Brothers"?
That jerk? Me?
Hyun Joon.
Hey.
I kissed you.
I was already worried...
when you were drinking too much to beat Hyun Joon.
Why do you care so much about him?
What do you think?
Yoon Ah is getting close to him,
so you feel jealous of him, right?
He's not over Yoon Ah yet.
That's not true.
I'm not interested in her anymore.
Really?
Then I guess...
I can tell Yoon Ah that you wet yourself.
Okay. Yoon Ah!
Jun Ki! Stop it.
Stop it.
Stop it right now.
Why? You're not interested in Yoon Ah anyway.
Fine. I still like her. What's wrong with that?
No matter how hard I try,
I keep thinking about her and missing her.
So that's why you care so much about Hyun Joon.
That jerk has been...
hovering around Yoon Ah. It's bothering me.
Why would that bother you?
Nothing seemed to be going on between those two.
You think so?
Something doesn't feel right.
Something smells fishy.
The smell is from your blankets.
Wash your blankets right now. They stink!
Fine.
What is this?
Du Shik.
Don't tell Yoon Ah I wet my bed.
All right.
By the way,
did I really say...
Hyun Joon and I were brothers?
Yes.
You acted like you found your missing brother.
You should quit drinking.
Gosh, I must have been crazy.
You're up.
Are you feeling all right?
Yes, I'm okay.
How are you going to face Yoon Ah now?
Why?
Did I do something?
You lifted up Yoon Ah with your hands and feet last night.
What are you talking about?
We're in Hawaii now.
Dong Gu, that's enough.
Let's fly to Paris.
We're experiencing turbulence.
But Dong Gu is strong.
Here we go!
After Yoon Ah said she's never been abroad,
you lifted her up while saying you'd fly her.
What? I did that?
Yoon Ah won't have to travel abroad anymore.
You're pathetic.
Dong Gu.
- You're up. - Yes.
Dong Gu, are you feeling all right?
Yes, I am,
Mr. Song.
What's with you?
We're brothers now, remember?
Are we?
I don't remember a thing.
I'm sorry, Mr. Song.
Don't worry, Mr. Kang.
Yoon Ah, we'll go upstairs.
Okay.
Go upstairs, Mr. Song.
Yoon Ah, I'm sorry about yesterday.
I was too drunk.
No problem. I enjoyed the flight.
Gosh. I'm crazy.
Hyun Joon, show me how to do it.
Okay. Just watch, and learn.
Hyun Joon, you're so good at this game.
That's not how you do it.
What? What do you mean?
When you play gonggi, it's important how you pick up the stones.
You should pick them up lightly.
If you do it so roughly, you'll make mistakes.
Are you good at gonggi too?
Of course.
I'm the gonggi champion of Huam-dong.
Do you want to see?
All right. Give them to me.
Like this. Lightly.
Like this.
You're very good.
It's nothing.
Hyun Joon, your skills didn't look bad either.
Why don't we compete?
Just for fun.
Well, why not?
But it'd be boring if there's no reward.
The loser takes 10 hits to his forehead.
Deal?
Sure. How many points?
- 50? - That's too little.
I say 100 points.
Like a man.
Let's decide who will attack first.
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
My goodness. It's paper.
I'll start first.
That's 100 points.
I win, Dong Gu.
Hyun Joon, you're amazing.
Too bad I have a hangover.
You're lucky.
You think so?
Let's just say so.
"Let's just say so?"
Are you saying I would have lost even if I didn't have a hangover?
That's not what I meant.
Then why don't we play another round?
100 points again.
The loser takes 20 hits to his forehead this time.
Sure.
Hold on. Gosh.
Hello, sir.
Right now?
Okay. I'll be right there.
I have some work to do right now.
Let's play another round when I'm back.
Hold on, Dong Gu.
I think you forgot something.
What? What do you mean?
Who would have imagined Shin Hyun Joon would say yes...
to the Saudi spy role?
Exactly.
He seemed excited.
He probably thought it sounded fun.
He wouldn't have expected an Arab role.
It's all thanks to Dong Gu.
We're done casting Shin Hyun Joon...
and the location scouting.
We only need props now.
What kind of gun should the main character carry around?
What about a Beretta or a Smith and Wesson?
That sounds boring.
I want something new.
Dong Gu.
Do you have any ideas?
Gonggi!
Gosh. Gonggi?
- What do you mean? - What?
An air gun?
That's interesting.
- Dong Gu. - Yes?
You're full of ideas.
You've done enough today. You can go home.
What? Okay.
- Who are you? - Hello.
I'm Kang Dong Gu.
I graduated from Hankook University, class of 2009.
You and I were in the same film club, Ready, Go,
back then.
Oh, you're Dong Gu.
What brings you here?
How long has it been?
I haven't seen you since graduation.
What's the matter?
I have a favor to ask.
A favor? What is it?
Do you remember...
the university festival?
The university festival?
We had a movie screening.
Was it a movie by Jean-Luc Godard?
That's not what I'm talking about.
Well, we had a bar too.
Not that either.
Then what is it?
The gonggi competition.
- What? - You represented our club...
and became the champion.
You finished 100 points...
within a record-breaking time.
I did. I remember now.
But what about it?
Please teach me gonggi.
What? Are you saying...
you came here to learn gonggi after eight years?
Yes, I have a situation.
I must learn gonggi. I really want to play it well.
I beg you, please?
Please.
What's wrong with you?
Did you bring the stones?
The weight should be adjusted.
There's too much iron inside.
A weight of 3.2g for each stone is enough for me,
but the right weight depends on the person.
You must find the right weight for you.
I see.
It is best to throw the stones near eye level.
If you throw them higher than your head, it's called Mount Baekdu.
It's considered as cheating in gonggi.
"Mount Baekdu"?
Let's start from level one.
For level one, the stones must be spread out...
as much as possible.
- Spread out? - Spread out like this.
- Okay? - Okay.
Level two is separating into pairs.
Lift the middle finger slightly so the opponent doesn't notice.
Do it instantly. It's not breaking the rules.
It's a technique.
Level three.
Put one stone under the thumb.
Drop it later.
The time difference is miniscule.
Play safely from level three.
- Okay? - Play safely from level three.
It's cold.
Why isn't she out yet?
What is this?
Hello, this is Park Chang Ho.
Goodness.
He sends me messages after I blocked his calls.
Even his messages are long.
What's this? Is it some kind of thesis?
Goodness.
I should block his messages too.
I'm sorry for being late, Jun Ki.
It's okay.
What shall we do today?
Let's do what you want to do.
Then let's go to a karaoke room.
- Karaoke? - Why? You don't want to?
Of course I do. Let's go.
Karaoke.
I'm so excited.
I always wanted to sing this song when I had a boyfriend.
Can I start?
Sure, go ahead.
Let's see.
4777.
I can't get used to this. Seriously.
I waited for today
I waited for this night to come
The night I spend alone with you
I've been waiting for it
Don't turn...
What are you doing? I was enjoying it.
You're too young to sing such an erotic song.
- What do you mean? - Be quiet!
Sing songs like this, you little girl.
156.
"Pororo"?
It's "Pororo".
I love playing the most
Gather around, my friends
Why aren't you singing? Sing!
Little Penguin Pororo
Sing with excitement!
We're already home.
That's sad.
If we got married, we wouldn't have to part.
What? "Married"?
Jun Ki, if we get married, where shall we go for honeymoon?
What? Honeymoon?
I want to go to the Maldives.
- And... - Stop it.
Watch what you say, little girl.
No, this is wrong.
Seo Jin.
I have something to tell you.
I tried hard,
but I can only see you as a little girl.
No matter how much I try, I can't see you as a woman.
So...
let's end it, please?
I'm sorry, Seo Jin.
Wait.
Don't do this, Seo Jin.
Please understand me.
Can't you see me as a woman even now?
I do.
I see you as a woman.
No, your answer sounds weak.
You still don't see me as a woman.
What?
Get out of my way!
Did Dong Gu not see us?
I don't think so.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know. He seems possessed.
I'm glad that he didn't see us.
I'm back!
Hello, Dong Gu. Have you had dinner?
I'm not hungry. Anyway,
let's play one more round as promised.
Gonggi.
Pardon?
The person who scores 100 first wins.
The penalty is 20 hits on the head.
Do you agree?
Yes, it sounds good.
Then let's decide the rules.
Mount Baekdu is not allowed.
(Throwing stones higher than one's head.)
You're out if the stones go above your head. You know, right?
Yes, I understand.
Bamboo Basket must be banned too.
When you catch the stones,
(Catching stones with one's palm facing up.)
you're out if you catch them like this.
Of course.
And...
Arirang counts.
Of course. Arirang must count.
(Attempting two catches during the final stage of the game.)
Let's start.
Let's decide the order.
Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
I won.
Then I'll start.
(Mount Baekdu)
You're out.
Mount Baekdu.
Beans.
Knock.
(Dong Gu: 41, Hyun Joon: 49)
That's it. Yes.
(Dong Gu: 52, Hyun Joon: 56)
The score...
is 96 to 83.
If I lose this time,
Hyun Joon will win.
I'm in trouble.
What should I do?
What do I need to do?
Lastly,
I'll teach you a special skill to use...
in times of need.
A special skill?
Let's say it's your turn,
but if the turn goes over to the opponent,
you'll probably lose.
You threw the stones...
and managed to put four stones on the back of your hand.
In that moment,
what choice will you make?
Well,
I'll catch four stones safely,
and start from the start again...
No, no, no!
If you make that choice,
the game is already over.
You can't be sure you'll be able...
to go over the whole round without making a mistake.
Then what should I do?
You need to make a winning bet...
with a skill called "Arirang",
"Arirang"?
It refers to an advanced skill...
in which you need to catch the stone...
from below and from above.
You can have five times the score of the normal throws.
It's a special skill.
- Five times? - In times of need,
don't forget the Arirang skill.
All right. There's no other choice for me.
I need to make a winning bet.
This doesn't feel good.
I don't feel good.
But don't worry.
I have...
the Arirang skill.
Oh, my.
I did it. I did the Arirang skill!
Did you see that? Did you?
You can have five times the score for an Arirang skill.
I'll get 20 points.
That means I won.
Dong Gu,
I lost.
My back hurts from playing gonggi.
I need to use the bathroom.
Excuse me, Hyun Joon.
You must have forgotten something.
Kang Dong Gu.
Gosh.
Thank you so much for the past few days.
I'll get going now.
Take care.
Wait.
- Let me ask you something. - Ask away.
I heard you lent Yoon Ah your workroom...
so that she can practice baking.
What does that mean?
What? What do you mean?
It's a little weird.
There must be many students in your class.
Why would you give such benefits to Yoon Ah alone?
I feel like she's like-minded, as we raise kids by ourselves.
Really?
- I thought... - That was the reason at first.
But now, I'm a little into her.
What?
I'm interested in her.
I mean,
I like her.
(Welcome to Waikiki)
They shouldn't stay close.
What's wrong? Why the wheelchair?
It's going to be a problem. You can't move.
Don't worry. I'll stay next to him.
Yoon Ah, are you home?
Why are you here, Hyun Joon?
I want to start an internet shopping mall.
Not everyone can do business.
Is there a way to advertise?
Why can't I do anything right?
I really tried my best.
Sir, it's Du Shik.
Giorgio Armani
Shopping mall
What are you doing?
Jun Ki started it first.
You didn't need to tell him off.
Jun Ki, if there's something going on between you and my sister,
you're going to die.
Do we really need to go this far?
Can't we just tell them?
I have a boyfriend.
What? A boyfriend?