Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah!
You can't come in. It's dangerous.
I know someone in there. Move.
- I said it's dangerous.
- I don't care. Just move!
Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah!
Dong Gu!
What are you doing here?
Is something wrong?
Dong... Dong Gu, what are you doing?
Are you hurt at all?
You're okay, right?
Yes.
But, could you please let go, Dong Gu?
Dong Gu, did you come here
because you were worried about me?
What?
I was just worried about
the neighborhood people.
You were here too, Yoon Ah.
Why did you hug me like that?
Well...
I have a habit of hugging people
when I'm worried about them.
Oh, President of the Women's Group!
Are you all right? Nothing happened?
President Kang, what's with you?
Mister, are you okay?
Mister Policeman, I was obstructing
your work, so I'm sorry.
Mister Fireman, oh my!
You are working so hard
putting out the fire.
Goodness, your heart was
beating hard because of heart problems.
- Soul mate?
- Give it a rest.
I'm worried about myself as it is.
What's wrong with you, Su Ah?
I broke a dish earlier and got hurt.
You really should be careful.
Where's Dong Gu?
I guess something happened because
he ran out like a crazy person.
Oh yeah. There was a fire at
the neighborhood grocery store.
- Huh?
- What?
- Our neighborhood?
- Yes.
Yoon Ah went to the grocery store.
I wonder if she's okay.
Yoon Ah? Yoon Ah went there?
Hey, hey. Call her now. Hurry.
We're home.
Are you okay, Yoon Ah?
I heard there was a fire.
I'm okay.
I stopped to buy chicken
on my way to the grocery store.
That's when the fire started.
Really? What a relief.
I heard you ran out
like a crazy person,  Dong Gu.
Were you going to Yoon Ah?
No.
I saw our neighbors on the news
and I was worried.
I'm good friends with the President of
the Women's Group, best friends.
- Since when?
- Huh?
It's been a long time, a long time now.
I thought something happened to my
best friend and I was so scared.
You're so crazy. I'm crazy.
I must really like her.
You're crazy, crazy, crazy.
Why did you go there?
Dong Gu, come out and have some chicken.
No, thanks.
I'm in no mood for chicken.
Come on. Don't be like that
and come have some.
I said I don't want any.
What's wrong with you?
We'll leave some for you,
so have it later.
You're crazy, so crazy.
You're totally insane.
Why did she grab my arm?
[Cute Girl]
What am I going to do?
I was going to eat that.
Give it back. Stop that.
- What about Dong Gu?
- He doesn't want to eat.
Is something wrong with him?
He has the blanket over his head
and won't move.
What? The blanket over his head?
Oh, he's mad again.
He does that for days whenever he's
mad about something, so don't worry.
Sol must be awake.
You should eat without me.
What the heck, Su Ah?
You just had a chicken leg
and you're eating another one?
I don't like dry meat.
So, you're going to eat
two legs by yourself?
Don't you have a conscience?
You're being too harsh
over one chicken leg.
Forget it. I won't eat it.
- Don't eat it!
- I'll eat it.
- What was that?
- Oh... oh!
Look at her taking
that chicken leg with her.
She is on a different level
of being shameless.
Seo Jin, I have credit card debt to pay.
Lend me money if you can.
What money? I have none at all.
Having no money
is nothing to show off about.
Gosh, what have you been
watching all this time?
Isn't this one of those eating shows?
Why would you watch these things?
- It's fun.
- How is it fun?
I don't understand people who do these.
Why would you film yourself
eating food and show others?
They are so pathetic.
Pathetic?
Joon Ki, do you know how much
these broadcast jockeys earn?
Popular BJs earn
100 million won in a year.
100 million won?
100 million won just for eating?
Yes, 100 million won.
100 million won, 100 million won.
Where did Doo Shik put it?
You're home?
Doo Shik, where's your laptop?
Why do you look like that?
These guys were hitting on Mal Geum.
Huh?
So, don't tell me you got into a fight.
An innocent guy like you?
I got so angry
when I saw Mal Geum crying.
I don't know why I did it.
Why else would you?
It's because you like Mal Geum.
- You think so?
- Of course.
What kind of a guy would get
beaten up for a girl unless he likes her?
Don't be like that anymore
and confess your feelings to her.
Confess? Forget it.
It's too early for that.
Hey, haven't you heard the saying
that love is about timing?
Love can go wrong because of
one minute or even one second.
While you sit around contemplating
what will you do if another guy
takes Mal Geum away from you?
What? That can't happen.
Joon Ki, how can I do this confession?
What do you mean how?
A man has to be
straightforward and driven, you know?
Straightforward and driven?
Yeah, but how?
Man, you're an amateur.
Look.
Long ago, there was a person
named Lee Joon Ki.
Suppose he sees a woman he likes.
This is his style.
He would walk forward.
Walk straight forward to her.
He has to walk to meet her.
How? He walks and stands before her.
How? In a bold way.
Grab her arm.
Push her. Push her to the wall.
Oh. Ouch.
Then confess your feelings.
How? Like this.
Because the days are good
and the days are bad...
I'm sorry. I love you.
Do I like you?
What are you guys doing?
Are you two dating?
No, what do you mean, dating?
Stop making absurd claims.
Continue what you were doing.
Whether you date or get married.
My gosh.
What does he mean by that? Hey.
What are you talking about?
Just walk. Keep walking.
When will those two ever grow up?
I'm already in
an anxious state, as it is.
Dong Gu, you're awake?
Why are you so surprised?
When did I get surprised? Geez.
Aren't you hungry?
I'll warm up the chicken for you,
so wait a little bit.
I like that lady?
Why?
Does she do her job well?
Is she pretty or cute...
She's cute.
Was she always this cute?
What are you staring at?
What do you mean, I'm staring?
You're one funny lady.
Why do you keep snapping at me?
Are you angry at me about something?
No.
Then why are you acting like that?
Is it possibly...
about the stain on your camera bag?
How do you know about that, Yoon Ah?
Was it you who did that?
I spilled some sauce while cooking.
Forget it. It's not about that.
Then is it about the broken lens cap?
How do you know about that?
Was that you too?
I was cleaning up the sauce
and I stepped on the cap.
I'm sorry, Dong Gu.
Please don't be mad, okay?
Please, please?
Stop being angry. I'm sorry, Dong Gu.
- I'm sorry.
- I said I'm not angry. Stop it!
Dong Gu!
Oh no. He must be really mad.
She's cute.
So cute.
I nearly forgave her for no reason.
How could someone be so cute
while saying sorry?
You startled me.
Dong Gu, what are you doing here?
It's nothing.
Maybe I should clean.
What's with him?
Why is his face so red?
Joon Ki, I need to borrow your razor.
Gosh.
Is that the only thing you ever
need to borrow from me?
Mine is broken.
It's over there.
What are you doing now?
I'm going to do an eating show too.
I have to pay my card bills.
So, you're going to make money
by doing an eating show?
You think anyone can do them?
Don't worry about it.
When it comes to eating,
I'm confident I can do well.
How come no one's coming in?
I'm going nuts.
Oh, there's someone here.
There's someone here now!
[BJ Joon's Chicken Eating Show]
Hello, Gangnam Nouveau Riche.
I am the pretty boy BJ of eating shows.
I am BJ Joon.
Forget all that. Hurry up and eat.
Ah, okay.
Nouveau Riche, you are very impatient.
How dare he talk informally to me?
Yes, Nouveau Riche.
Then, I will start eating my chicken!
It smells so good.
Yummy. It is crispy.
Gosh, you make it look so yucky.
Honestly, this is my first time
doing an eating broadcast.
Then, I'll try eating in
a really delicious way this time.
Oh!
Oh no.
Oh, delicious!
Dong Gu, how did work go?
Dong Gu, Dong Gu!
What's with him?
I think the person Dong Gu
is mad at must be me.
- What?
- I spilled sauce on his camera bag.
- I broke his lens cap too.
- What?
You should've been more careful.
The thing he cherishes the most
is his camera.
Really? What do I do?
Is there a way to get him to forgive me?
Let me think.
Oh, there is one way.
- What is it?
- Acting cute.
My brother may look very cold,
but he's weak to people acting cute.
Acting cute?
Gosh, I can't even look at her face.
But the more I look at her,
the cuter she is.
Dong Gu.
Dong Gu, Yoon Ah was wrong.
Please forgive me, would you?
What is this?
Why is he being like that?
Why else? It's because
you're not cute at all.
He usually gets over most things.
You really have no talent at acting cute.
Really?
I was trying my best.
Was it not cute at all?
So cute, so cute, so cute.
Even with a lisp, she's so cute.
I thought my heart would stop
when she shook her shoulders like that.
You startled me.
What are you doing here?
Huh? It's just...
What? Do you have something to say to me?
No, I don't.
Why has he been acting like that
since yesterday?
Are you feeling okay?
Oh, look at your lips.
They're all cut up.
Seriously, those jerks.
It's okay. I'm fine so don't worry.
Looks like we're starting
the shoot tomorrow.
You'll be busy from now on.
I guess so.
Maybe I worked out too much this morning.
Worked out? What kind?
It's called Krav Maga.
It's so much fun that
I can't tell time is passing by.
Krav... oh really?
I'm going insane.
I have to confess my feelings,
but I have no courage.
Okay, a man needs
to be straightforward and driven.
Be a man. Do it.
Mal Geum!
Yeah?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you all right, Doo Shik?
Yeah, I'm all right.
What was that just now?
How did you do that?
That's Krav Maga.
Martial arts for real-life fighting.
Won Bin used it in the film
"The Man From Nowhere."
Krav Maga isn't like Pilates?
It's martial arts?
Yes, so don't grab my arm suddenly.
I will react naturally.
Oh, okay. I won't.
Hello?
Yes, Chairman.
Yes, I'll be there soon. Yes.
I have a fan meeting today,
so I think I have to go.
- What can I do?
- Fan meeting?
You even have fan meetings?
Can I go there too?
Huh? I don't know about that...
I have something I have to tell you.
Cherry, Cherry, Cherry!
We're here. This is the place.
Oh, okay. Have a good fan meeting.
I'll be at a nearby cafe.
Oh, Writer Bong?
Oh, Chairman. Hello.
What brings you here, Writer Bong?
Ah, you came to see Cherry's fan meeting.
- No, that's not it--
- I'm glad you came.
Come on. I'll get you the best seat.
No, that's not it at all.
Yes, we will now begin
Cherry's fan meeting.
Please give a warm round
of applause for Cherry!
Cherry, Cherry, Cherry!
Here you go. Can you see the bone?
See. What do you think?
One, two, three. Clear.
Next...
before I eat the next plate of chicken
anyone who wishes to send me
stars can do so now.
Time for stars... now.
Okay, then let's move on.
I will start eating
my second plate of chicken.
Wait. Why are you throwing that away?
Ah...
Do you mean this?
These are the bones remaining from
the first plate of chicken I had.
Eat the bones too.
I'll give you 100 stars if you do.
100 stars if I eat the bones?
Hey, I'm broadcasting.
Why are you thinking about it?
- You're really going to eat them?
- Of course!
100 stars is 10,000 won.
Still, how can a person
eat chicken bones?
I have to pay off my credit card.
In order to not have credit issues,
I would eat feathers too, not just bones.
You could die.
Let go.
Nouveau Riche, you waited a long time.
This hairy person kept bugging me.
So, BJ Joon...
will begin eating the bones.
Oh, the smell of
the calcium and magnesium.
I'm getting healthier.
This is good. Okay, now.
Wow. This guy really
ate the chicken bone.
How can he eat chicken bones?
Isn't he embarrassed as an adult?
Hey, we'd better study hard
so we don't end up like that.
Here. Ah, ah...
I swallowed it. I ate it.
Nouveau Riche, I want my stars.
Okay, you got it.
100 stars!
Thank you, Nouveau Riche.
Sir! Nouveau Riche, sir. Thank you!
Thank you! 100.
He'll cause trouble doing that.
What are you doing here, Yoon Ah?
Oh, I was...
What? Dong Gu's still angry?
Did you do what I taught you?
No, I haven't sent it yet.
Why? It'll fix it.
I've never seen that
not work on anyone before.
Really?
- Okay, then I'll send it.
- Okay.
I couldn't even eat because of Yoon Ah.
What is this?
Geez.
Oh, it's Yoon Ah.
What is this?
Do you want forgiveness that much?
Yes.
Say, "Forgive me."
Dong Gu, please forgive me.
Be cute.
Please forgive me.
Be lovely.
Be charming,
Please forgive me.
Be tough.
What? Is he mad? What does that mean?
What is this in
the middle of my broadcast?
Are you eating ramen?
Did you make it for yourself?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Those are my pills.
They're for my bad heart!
- Hey!
- What's going on?
I think Dong Gu's still mad.
Let's give up.
You are no good at acting cute.
You are terrible at it.
Am I that bad at it?
Cute, cute. She's so cute.
Is she a person or a doll?
Good thing I had
these pills for my heart.
I nearly died from a heart attack.
Kang Dong Gu.
Why have you been
acting weird since yesterday?
Say it if you have something to say.
I have nothing to say.
Why is he acting like that?
Wait.
Is it possible...
that he still likes me?
The highlight of today's fan meeting,
the free prize, will start.
First, I'd like to show you
what we have for you.
Today's prize is from Cherry's debut film
"Bikini Investigators 3."
It is the very bikini that Cherry wore.
Please calm down everyone.
Please hold on to the numbered ticket
you all received when you came in.
Cherry will now select a number.
- Pick me!
- Me, me!
- Number 9!
- 89!
The lucky person who will
receive Cherry's bikini is...
number 38!
Is number 38 here?
- What is it?
- He's not here.
Is number 38 not here?
- Not here!
- Do it again.
Do it again!
Again, again, again, again!
Oh, number 38!
Number 38 is here. Here he is!
Oh, there he is.
- Please come on up.
- Number 38!
- Three-eight, three-eight, three-eight!
- Congrats.
Please give him a round of applause.
[Congratulations on winning the bikini.]
Hello, everyone.
Why don't we start BJ Joon's program
of eating all kinds of bones?
I've prepared all kinds
of different bones.
Let's go in order.
First, the chicken bone.
Then we have the pork backbone.
The back rib bone.
Rockfish bones.
Hairtail fish bones.
That's what I have prepared.
Today's highlight...
Pork feet bones.
That is the highlight today.
First, this is known
to be chewy and sharp.
I will start with
the rockfish bones first.
Let's start!
He is insane.
That guy...
Dong Gu, Dong Gu!
Give it to me. I'll do it.
I'll do it. Why don't you go inside?
I can do it.
Dong Gu, are you still
very angry with me?
I said I'm not angry at you.
Why do you keep asking that?
Then why are you acting this way?
Tell me, okay?
See. You can't tell me.
You are mad at me about the camera.
Fine, I am mad at you about the camera.
I'm not angry anymore though,
so don't worry about it.
- Okay?
- Really?
What a relief.
I was so worried about that for days.
Dong Gu, I won't ever
make a mistake ever again.
- Geez.
- I'm sorry, Dong Gu.
I have a cold.
It's fine. I'm okay.
Why do you always wear such thin coats?
That's why you get colds.
This is my warmest coat.
It's actually pretty warm.
Oh yeah. I left the stove on.
I'm going to head in first.
Oh, geez.
Nouveau Riche, thanks for the stars.
Venus, thank you for the stars.
All of this just for the rockfish bones.
BJ Joon doesn't know what to say.
Thank you very much.
Now with the strength of these stars...
the strongest of the bones.
I will try eating the pork feet bones.
Joon is fine. I am fine.
Okay, I will eat it now.
Oh, my stomach.
Joon will go on. Joon is fine!
What am I going to do? Ow!
Why did I have to win that?
I can't even throw it away.
Sorry. You waited too long, right?
No, it's okay.
It's cold, right? Drink this.
Thank you.
It was a little embarrassing
today, wasn't it?
Sorry, that's how my life is.
Don't talk like that.
Honestly, I didn't intend
to work in this business.
I did TV dramas
and other films, at first.
Things weren't working out
and I needed the money.
I decided to try it just once
and I ended up here.
What's wrong with erotic films?
Still, this wasn't my dream.
I want to be in dramas
and films like before.
But my image is set in stone now,
so I don't get other offers.
You can quit now if you want.
No, I can't do anything
because of contract issues.
I really don't know
what to do anymore either.
Sorry, I don't know why I cry
so much lately like a fool.
Oh yeah.
Didn't you say you had
something to tell me?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'll tell you next time.
Drink that.
I bought this,
but how do I give this to her?
Here, I bought this.
No, no, no!
I found it somewhere.
No, that's too obvious.
What was I planning when I bought this?
What if she figures out that I
like her once I give it to her?
We're here.
Be careful.
What's wrong, Joon Ki? What happened?
Well, Joon Ki was sick.
We went to the ER.
The ER? What was wrong with him?
Don't tell her.
Well... he ate the bones of a rockfish.
What? Rockfish bones?
Don't tell me you ate bones again.
No...
I'll go on up first
and clean up the room.
Why did I even buy this?
You dummy.
Oh!
- You were home, Dong Gu?
- What?
- Yes, I was.
- Oh.
What are you hiding there?
Ah, it's just...
Yoon Ah, here.
Gosh, you're heavy.
- What are you doing?
- Why are you all in here?
What's that?
Did you get that for Yoon Ah?
Uh, no.
I was asking her to give it to Su Ah,
but I'll give it to her myself... Su Ah.
What is it?
A coat? What's with the coat, suddenly?
Because it was pretty.
Guys, I'm sick right now.
Can you put me in bed
before discussing the coat?
Sorry. Come on, Joon Ki.
Gosh, why are you so heavy?
I didn't even turn off
the broadcast before leaving.
Hold on.
Let me take a look.
Seriously.
- He's back.
- He must've gone to the hospital.
- There's the mustache girl.
- What is all of this?
Why are you so shocked?
Hey, look at this. Look, look!
What is it?
Why are there so many people?
What? 23,400 stars?
Each star is worth 100 won.
You have more than two million won.
I didn't even have 200 when I left.
What happened?
- Seo Jin.
- Hm?
- Isn't this you?
- What?
Why am I there?
Where is that razor?
Here it is.
Is that woman shaving?
Is that mustache for real?
Today's broadcast is legendary.
This is very clever.
Started out as eating
and now it's a shaving show?
What is this?
So, my shaving was aired live?
Thank you, Chewbacca.
I can solve my credit card issues,
thanks to you.
Is that the issue here, you idiot?
The whole country saw me shaving my face.
Hey, what are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Who told you to shave here?
Oh, looks like someone's
coming into the room.
I bought this,
but how do I give this to her?
Here, I bought this.
No, no, no!
I found it somewhere.
No, that's too obvious.
What if she figures out that
I like her once I give it to her?
Huh?
What? What is it?
Give that to me.
Wait. What were you saying there?
"Figures out you like her"?
Well, uh...
Dong Gu, it can't be...
It's not like that.
You don't like Su Ah again, do you?
Huh?
No, it's not like that.
What do you mean?
The evidence is right there.
No, it's not that.
Dong Gu, let's talk for a bit.
Huh?
Sure.
Gosh, that fool.
You know that we're over.
Huh?
I know. I know very well.
- But...
- Then why do this if you know?
Dong Gu, is it that hard to forget me?
No, I can forget you.
I'll forget you.
I'll forget you right this moment.
I can forget you, Su Ah.
I can erase you, Su Ah.
So, don't worry about it. Bye now.
Dong Gu, what am I to do with you?
It is pretty, though.
What good is it if you like me?
You don't know my size.
Dong Gu, what am I to do with you?
Su Ah, what am I to do with you?
What am I to do?
Su Ah, is this why you moved in here?
You wanted to date my brother again?
No, I have a conscience, after all.
I can't bear to see
you two date ever again.
Do whatever you have to
in order to cut him off.
You got it?
Okay.
Su Ah.
Why did you want to meet me outside?
Well, I thought about it long and hard.
I don't think I can accept your feelings.
That again?
I'm fine so don't worry about me.
How can I not worry?
You shouldn't have gotten caught, then.
So, I prepared something for you.
Prepared something? What?
I'm setting you up on a date.
What? A date?
So, you're setting me up
with someone now?
She's here. Ye Rin, over here.
Oh, hello. She's really here.
This is a junior of mine, Lee Ye Rin.
This is my friend, Kang Dong Gu.
Hello, I've heard a lot
about you from Su Ah.
Hello, I wonder what you heard about me.
Dong Gu, do well.
- With what?
- I'm going to leave now.
Su Ah, where are you going?
Su Ah.
She's just leaving.
Yes, uh...
[For the Sake of Love]
I'm home.
- You're home?
- Oh?
Why are you home so early?
What about Ye Rin?
Oh, we just ended
the date a little early.
So, did the date go well?
- Did you ask her for a second date?
- What?
No.
Why? I saw her picture
and she's just your type.
Well, her looks are my type.
How should I put it?
I like girls who are intelligent.
Ye Rin is very intelligent.
She graduated with
a business degree from Seoul University
and studied abroad at Harvard.
Her IQ is high too,
so she's a Mensa member.
Yeah? It's good to
be pretty and intelligent.
I don't like it when girls
don't have a sense of humor.
Ye Rin is a comedian.
She became a comedian at JBC
in 2017 and she's hilarious.
Really?
Oh, but how should I put it?
I don't get that feeling of,
"She's the one."
Be quiet! This is because
of Su Ah, isn't it?
You still have feelings for her.
No, I told you it's not like that.
Then why didn't you ask her out again?
Why not?
- Well...
- Dong Gu.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you making things so hard for me?
I told you it's not like that.
Fine, I'll do it! I'll ask her out again.
Do it right now while we're watching.
What?
Gosh, fine. I'll do it.
I can do it, okay?
I'm doing it.
I asked her to help clean.
What is Su Ah doing?
Why aren't you coming down, Su Ah?
I was going to throw out
some clothes I don't wear.
You've made more of a mess.
Oh, this is the coat Dong Gu bought you.
Yeah, but it's too small.
I can't throw it out though.
You want to wear it?
Really?
All right. Let me try.
I'll wear it.
What? It's too small for me too.
Do you want to try it on?
Me? No, thanks.
Don't be like that
and try it on. Just once.
Here.
Oh, look at that. Fits you perfectly.
Yeah. Do you want to wear it, Yoon Ah?
How can I do that when
Dong Gu bought it for you?
It's okay.
You think so? Oh, whatever.
Why do you have so many clothes
when you have nothing else?
Oh, isn't that Mouramouge?
It is. It's Mouramouge.
Mouramouge? What's that?
You don't know it?
It's a designer label.
This 2017 Fall/Winter
vintage collection was worn by
Song Hye Gyo, Jeon Ji Hyun,
Kim Tae Hee, and so on.
All celebrities wore this collection
and it was a big hit.
Why don't you wear this?
I just don't really wear it.
Do you want it?
Really? Thank you, Su Ah.
Thank you so much.
Su Ah, don't clean today and just rest.
I'll do all of it.
I love you, Su Ah.
I'm taking all of it.
Okay.
So nice.
Why are you doing this, Director?
What?
Why would you put in scenes that aren't
in the script without talking to me?
Hey, turn on the lights.
Is this your first time filming?
Why are you being
so sensitive over nothing?
I can't do this film
if you're going to work like this.
Are you refusing to film?
- Then pay for breach of contract.
- What?
If you don't have the money for that,
stop talking and just work.
What will it be? Will you do it or not?
- I'm going to get some air.
- Seriously.
Get up.
- Doo Shik.
- Get up now.
What is it?
Where are we going?
Doo Shik, what are you doing?
You said you don't want to do this work.
Then don't do it.
Don't force yourself to do it.
Live your life doing what you want.
How can I do that?
I have the contract with the agency.
I'll take care of it,
so just go home for now.
I'll resolve everything and call you.
Doo Shik!
Writer Bong, what did you just say?
What? Cherry can't shoot the film?
That's right.
So, don't look for Cherry...
I mean, don't contact Mal Geum anymore.
Who decided that?
Then will you pay for the breach of
contract in the movie appearance?
As well as her breach of contract
with our management company?
Yes, I will pay you.
How much is it?
It's 40 million won,
40 million, 40 million.
What do I do? I'm crazy. I'm insane.
Ta-da.
Joon Ki, how do I look?
Wow, you look a bum
dressed in warm clothes.
Are you giving up on a job
and doing that now?
A bum? This is all designer.
Mouramouge F/W 2017 vintage collection.
What? Mour... what?
Forget it. You don't know fashion.
Never mind. I'm going to the library.
Dress warm.
- You're home?
- Yes.
What are those warm looking bum clothes?
Why do you have an onion bag?
It's not an onion bag!
- This is the Mouramouge 2017--
- Mour... what?
Never mind.
I can't talk to you two.
You don't know anything about fashion.
What is that thing then?
Where did she find those bum clothes?
All we need is a trash can
and she'd look just right.
Yeah. Oh, Joon Ki.
That bum isn't important.
I'm in big trouble.
Trouble? What trouble?
What? You have to pay
for Mal Geum's breach of contract?
Yeah, I just felt so bad for Mal Geum.
Even if you feel bad for her,
why would you do that?
I didn't know it would be that much.
What should I do?
Should I try to get a loan?
You think anyone can get a loan?
An unemployed guy
like you can't get a loan.
Then what do I do?
I'm going crazy.
There is an option.
Hm, there's a way? What is it?
The race has started.
You must place your bets...
It's the same here as always.
What? Isn't this place
for cycling or something?
Isn't this illegal?
Not at all.
They have a permit and everything.
Also, this is the only place
you can get big money quickly.
But what guarantee do we have
that we will win?
There is a way.
Have you heard of the cycling god?
Cycling god?
He can guess who will win,
so they call him cycling god.
Where is he today?
Over there.
That is the cycling god.
You just need to choose who he does.
Then you will win.
That's what they say.
Whoever that man is,
how will we know who he picked?
There is a way. Follow me.
- Huh?
- Follow me.
- What are we doing?
- Just stand there.
Stand where?
Get lost!
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm sorry. My friend is drunk.
Why would you show up after drinking?
Here you go.
So sorry.
Why did you suddenly push me?
I saw it. I saw who
the cycling god picked.
Really? Who?
Take this and make your bet.
- I have to go to the bathroom?
- Why?
I haven't been well
since I ate the rockfish bones.
I'll be right back. Bet everything, okay.
Hurry back.
Dong Gu, are you going on your date?
Yes.
Have a nice time.
Buy Ye Rin lots of yummy food.
Su Ah, can't I just not go on the date?
Why? Is it because of me again?
It's not that.
I don't have money
because we don't have guests.
Dates cost quite a lot.
Isn't it kind of hard to be
dating in this situation?
- I think--
- Dong Gu, I'm here.
Ye Rin! What are you doing here?
It costs a lot of money
to go out on dates.
I thought we should cook at home
and have a date like that.
I'll quickly cook something good.
Where is the kitchen?
Oh no. You shouldn't.
Over here. Follow me.
You see?
She's such a thoughtful person.
So, don't worry about money
and date comfortably, okay?
Okay.
How can she be so thoughtful?
She is so deep.
What took you so long?
The race started.
Sorry. I'm just not feeling very well.
You made your bet, right?
Here. How do we look at this?
You just go from top to bottom.
Huh? Hey, man!
I told you to pick one and nine.
Why did you pick one and six?
- What? You wrote here six and one.
- Huh?
You turned it upside down!
You're supposed to
read it like this, you idiot!
You should've said so in words.
We're ruined because of you.
Gosh, I'm going to lose it.
Then what do I do now?
This can't happen.
This is the final lap.
They are going faster now.
Final lap.
There is a pursuit for first
in the final moments.
Six is moving up.
One and six, one and six.
It's number six!
Awesome!
Yeah!
What happened?
Hey, the riders you picked won.
- We won!
- Really?
- Then we won?
- Yes.
Wow.
Wow, how much is this?
I think I can cover
what I need with this.
Should we go, then?
Wait, Doo Shik.
Doesn't it feel wrong to leave like this?
You earned that by
betting only 48,000 won.
You already made this much.
If you had bet all of this,
how much would it be?
It would be a huge amount.
Why do you ask?
Why do you think?
If we win one more time,
Mal Geum's money is no problem.
And our long-time wish...
We could even make a movie.
Doo Shik, let's do it! Let's go for it!
Our movie?
Ye Rin, you're a really good cook.
Right, Dong Gu?
I guess so.
Would you like some kimbap?
I'll feed it to you.
- Ah...
- No, it's okay. I'll eat it.
I want to feed you.
"Ah."
I said it's okay.
I'm sorry. I just wanted to feed you.
Come see me for a moment.
Why? We're in the middle of eating.
Why?
Kang Dong Gu, what's the matter with you?
What did I do?
Why won't you say "ah" when Ye Rin
wants to feed you kimbap?
Why won't you say "ah"?
I just want to eat it myself.
Don't lie. You're doing that
because of me.
You're thinking about me
and that's why you won't say "ah."
No, that's not what it is.
Then why won't you say "ah"?
Why won't you say "ah"
when she's giving you good food?
Okay. I'll say "ah."
I'll say "ah," okay?
Ah...
How is it? Is it good?
Yes, it's very good.
One more since you like it.
I just ate one though.
Ah...
Oh my goodness.
No one can take their eyes off me.
Everyone has such great taste.
It is Mouramouge, after all.
Mouramouge.
Oh, spicy rice cakes.
Looks good.
Mister, one serving of spicy rice cakes.
You do have money, right?
Yes, why do you ask?
You have to pay before eating here.
Ah, I see.
- Ma'am, please give me some onions.
- Which ones?
- These here.
- Okay.
Oh no. I'm out of bags.
Oh, there's an onion bag here.
I'll put it in here.
- Okay.
- This is great.
My bag.
Where did it go?
Where is it?
- How is this one?
- Ma'am, what are you doing?
- What?
- Well.
Why are you putting onions in my bag?
This is your bag?
I thought it was an onion bag.
It's not for onions!
This is Mouramouge Fall/Winter
2017 vintage collection.
Forget it. Just move.
Wait a minute.
It smells like onions.
I'm sorry.
This is my bag.
I really didn't know.
Yes, Hae Won.
What? You want to set me up?
Why would I do that
when I'm still looking for a job?
What? He looks like Daniel Kang?
Gosh. Where are you?
Hae Won, I'm here.
Oh, Seo Jin... you're here?
Sorry, I'm a little late.
Seo Jin, what's that smell?
It smells like onions.
Sorry, I had an
absurd thing happen to me.
I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I'm Kang Seo Jin.
Was the food to your liking, Dong Gu?
Yes, it was very good.
Would you like some gum?
Ah.
Oh, I'll just take it.
Ah...
What? Are you in pain?
I've been stressed out
and now my neck hurts.
A foot massage is the best for stress.
Would you like a foot massage?
- What?
- Give me your feet.
Oh no!
A foot massage? It's fine.
Sorry, I just wanted help
relieve your stress.
It's okay. No need for a foot massage.
Dong Gu, come see me for a moment.
Why?
Why are you being this way?
What did I do now?
Why won't you do the foot massage?
Ye Rin wants to do it,
so why won't you let her?
What? I met her yesterday.
Why would I get a foot massage from her?
Look at you again.
Did you think I wouldn't know?
You're not getting it because
you're thinking about me.
No.
It's really not because of you.
Then why won't you get the foot massage?
Even a minute of it would relieve stress,
so why won't you get the foot massage?
- Why?
- Okay, I'll get it!
I can get the foot massage!
Hm, where did this guy go?
Did he go to the restroom?
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Did the man sitting here go somewhere?
He just paid and left.
He left?
Where did he go
in the middle of a date?
Yeah, Hae Won.
Dae Young left without a word
while I was in the restroom.
What's with him?
Why would you come out dressed
like that when I'm setting you up?
And what's with that onion bag?
It's not an onion bag.
It's called a net bag.
Also, this is all Mouramouge.
The designer of designers.
Ah...
So, Dae Young left because
of the way I was dressed?
What do you mean that's not true?
Okay, I'm going to go.
How ridiculous.
These ignorant people
who know nothing about fashion.
He doesn't even resemble
one pore of Daniel Kang's.
The star of tonight is me. It's me.
It's me. It's me.
Waiting for you...
How can I not even win once?
Does this make sense?
How can we be wrong every time?
I don't know. I don't know.
I lost the money I won because of you.
I said we should just go.
What is this?
Doo Shik. I'm sorry, Doo Shik.
Hey, Doo Shik.
I'm sorry. Hey, Doo Shik!
I'm sorry, okay?
Doo Shik, I said I'm sorry.
Forget it. What do I do now?
We don't even have bus money.
How do we get home?
I'm going crazy too.
We can't walk all the way home.
You even lost your bus money.
Hello.
Greed will lead you nowhere.
Take this.
However, don't ever come back here again.
Can you promise that?
Of course, we won't come back.
Thank you. Thank you.
All right. I'll be going.
They won't ever be able to quit.
Thank you.
What a relief.
We can go home thanks
to the cycling god, right?
The bus is here, Joon Ki. The bus!
Wait, Doo Shik.
- What now?
- Isn't it wrong to leave now?
Let's play one more round.
Huh? With what money?
What? You mean with this?
What are you going to tell Mal Geum?
What will you do with Mal Geum,
who's trusting in you?
If we have one big win
you can help her
and we can make our film.
If things go well...
you could even marry Mal Geum.
Doo Shik, let's go!
Let's go for it!
Marriage?
Yeah!
Seriously!
I'm the crazy one for believing you.
I'm crazy. I'm a crazy punk.
I had a really good feeling this time.
Shut up and just walk.
It's so cold.
It'll take forever to walk home.
Doo Shik.
Look, it's 500 won.
What about the 500 won?
What about it?
You want to bet on races with that?
Are you crazy?
If we win big just once,
we can pay for Mal Geum and our film.
You can marry Mal Geum for sure
and your children...
will grow up with
silver spoons in their mouths.
Doo Shik, let's go. Let's go for it!
Silver spoons?
Yeah!
I'm the crazy one for going with you.
I must be insane.
Idiot, idiot.
I really thought it would
work out this time.
Oh, Doo Shik.
Look, it's a beer bottle.
What about the beer bottle?
What do you want with that?
Hey, this is 130 won per bottle.
If we can gather a few more,
we can get some money.
Then we can hit it big with a bet.
Then Mal Geum's money, our film,
your marriage, your kids...
What do you think, Doo Shik?
Doo Shik, let's go for it!
You crazy...
How can we do that with
an empty bottle, you crazy idiot?
We can pick up a few more.
Be ambitious, Doo Shik.
Let's go!
Stop the nonsense and let's go home!
Follow me, you crazy idiot.
- Hey, hey.
- Come on.
We have an event today for White Day.
Come look at the prizes.
First place is a
return flight to Jeju Island.
Come and try it out.
Excuse me.
Yes?
May I try too?
Ah, yes. Of course.
Oh, oh! I won the fourth place prize.
So, what did I win?
- Here you go.
- Wow. So cool.
Awesome.
Thank you.
Thank you!
This candy is really good.
We could've played one more game
if we'd sold the bottles.
I saw five beer bottles on the way here.
What kind of a man has no ambition?
Shut up. Shut up, man. I said shut up!
Oh, hey. Hey, hey.
She looks very familiar.
What do you mean?
Who is that? Isn't that Seo Jin?
I think you're right.
You're right.
Hey, Seo Jin.
Get up, Kang Seo Jin.
What is it?
You don't know anything about fashion.
Oh, the alcohol.
Where did she drink so much
this early in the day?
Look at her.
She even has a can.
- Doo Shik.
- What now?
Look at this. It's money.
What? Why does she have
money in this can?
We can play one more round
before they close if we go now.
- What do you think?
- What?
You want to bet again with this?
Are you truly insane?
If the gods have a conscience,
they have to let us win.
Doo Shik.
Let's go! Let's go for it!
Shut up! Stop saying crazy crap.
Yeah, let's give up.
Then you can't repay
Mal Geum's debts or get married.
You can live your life having a crush
on her and then die a sad death.
Give up.
That can't happen.
Doo Shik, let's try just one more time.
Doo Shik, let's go!
Let's go for it!
Okay, I can't die after
just having a crush on her.
Let's go! Let's go for it!
Let's go, Doo Shik!
I'll get going then, Dong Gu.
Get home safely, Ye Rin.
Dong Gu, I like you a lot.
Do you want to officially date me?
What?
The thing is, Ye Rin...
I want you to listen to me
without misunderstanding.
Ye Rin, you're pretty, intelligent,
and have a good sense of humor.
You're thoughtful, a good cook,
and you give good foot massages.
You're a perfect person
who even cleans well.
But, I wonder if I'm lacking for you.
- Also--
- Wait.
I'm getting rejected, right?
- It's not that.
- Why?
Is there someone you like?
What?
Well, uh...
I guess I was right.
What do you mean by that?
Do you mean me and Su Ah?
Su Ah is just a friend.
She's totally a friend.
I wasn't talking about Su Ah.
I was talking about Yoon Ah.
What?
Seeing how surprised you are,
I must be right.
How did you...
I'm very quick to pick up on things,
so don't lie about it.
I'm sorry, Ye Rin.
Could you keep it a secret?
Okay. I'll get going, then.
Thank you, Ye Rin. Goodbye.
Okay.
Bye.
However, even Ye Rin who
appeared to be perfect had a fault.
What?
Dong Gu likes Yoon Ah?
Yes, he does.
I asked him out and he rejected me.
That's when I just knew.
So, I asked him and he admitted it.
Dong Gu admitted it?
Okay, I understand. Bye.
Dong Gu really likes Yoon Ah?
Wait a minute.
What if she figures out that I
like her once I give it to her?
I was asking her to give it to Su Ah,
but I'll give it to her myself... Su Ah.
What? It fits you perfectly.
Didn't Yoon Ah say she was
going to the grocery store?
Where are you going?
Gosh, maybe I should clean.
Dong Gu, you... you...
- You!
- What?
What is it?
Is that why you ran to the store when
there was a fire and bought that coat?
So, the person you like isn't me,
but Yoon Ah?
What?
What? What are you talking about?
Don't try to get out of it.
Ye Rin told me.
What? She said she'd keep it a secret.
She already told you?
Dong Gu, did Ye Rin get home okay?
What?
Huh?
Wow, how absurd.
Wow, this is big news.
Wow!
Su Ah, what is it? Is something going on?
Dong Gu doesn't like me.
He actually likes--
Hey, hey, hey!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
Yoon Ah, you should have this.
Su Ah and I are just friends.
Yes, Dong Gu must have some other love.
Sol, don't cry.
What's wrong lately?
Would you like some help?
That's amazing. You really saved me.
We have a new instructor.
I'd like to introduce him to you.
You don't know Son Hyun Joon?
He's a star patisseur.
She's the first love
you mentioned before?
The pictures remind me of the past.
We were always together.
When did you start liking me?
Why are you asking that?
- Am I your first love?
- What?
What kind of unemployed person
naps on schedule like that?
What a nice life.
Do you want to die?
Stop it, would you?
They'll end up liking each other
at some point.
What? Liking each other?
Even if we were the only ones
on a deserted island
I wouldn't get involved with him.