Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
What was that?
Ew, I need water.
Oh, water.
What was that?
Hello.
Yes, that's me.
Pardon me?
Oh... yes.
I'm sorry.
If you could give us a little more time,
we'll pay that within the week.
What?
Then how are we supposed to
run our business?
Hello? Hello?
Why are you noisy?
What is it?
They're shutting off our water.
Our water bills haven't been paid.
What?
When?
Right now.
Hey, you think this is funny?
Is this funny?
I told you I don't like jokes like this.
Hey, are you really
going to be like this?
Hey, Kang Dong Gu.
Turn on the water now
unless you want to get into trouble.
- Joon Ki, Joon Ki.
- Huh?
This way, this way.
Oh. Kang Dong Gu.
Stop joking around and turn it on.
What joke are you talking about?
The water's shut off because
we haven't paid our bills.
What? The water's shut off?
Ow! Ow!
Gosh! Ouch!
Come on, now.
I told you to pay the utilities on time.
Don't you think I wanted to?
I had no money,
so what could I do?
How much could that be anyway?
- 420,000 won.
- 420,000 won?
- Yes.
- That is a lot.
Still, how could you not even
have 400,000 won?
This is all your fault, Joon Ki.
The guest house is a "blue ocean"?
If we just open it,
the Chinese tourists will pour in?
We can earn a ton of money
and film a movie?
How was I supposed to know that
this THAAD issue would arise?
How could I predict
the relations of the eastern--
Shut up!
Do you know how many loans we have?
We're on the verge of being ruined.
Now, we don't even have water,
so how can we do business?
Hey, don't worry about it.
Don't you think three guys
can't come up with 400,000 won?
Yeah, things can't
get worse than they are now.
- Let's be optimistic, Dong Gu.
- What?
Be optimistic?
Oh, you're right. I was wrong.
I almost made a big mistake.
We have no guests in sight.
Our loans are growing with interest
and we have no water now.
I was just too darn pessimistic.
I deserve to die for my wrongdoing.
Should I get on my knees?
That's not what I meant, Dong Gu.
Then what!
Hey, why are you getting mad at him?
It's all right. It's all right.
Yeah, I'm the crazy punk.
I'm the crazy one for trusting you two
and starting a business.
I am crazy. I really am.
What? Optimistic?
Why, you...
Nothing ever works out.
That guy has rage issues
if you think about it.
It's all right. Calm down.
Are you crying?
Why are you crying?
We should be optimistic.
What?
Things can't get worse than this,
so be optimistic?
If things get worse than this,
then it will be hell.
What is that?
What's that sound?
Why is there a baby...
Joon Ki! Doo Shik!
What is it? What?
- What, what?
- What is it?
- What?
- Why?
- Go, go.
- What is it about?
- Just go. Hurry.
- What is it?
It's a baby doll.
- It's moving.
- Huh?
It moved.
It looked me in the eye.
It moved. It moved.
[New World]
Why in the world is it here?
Why, why, why?
Could be a guest's baby?
We haven't had a guest in ages.
That's why we were drinking
all day yesterday.
Someone could've come
while we were drunk.
You think so?
I blacked out so
I don't remember anything.
Joon Ki, you don't know?
You didn't drink.
You know I slept because
I'm going to a shoot today.
Why don't we look
through the bag for now?
There could be contact information.
Should we do that?
There's nothing here.
Then what's going on?
Since the bag is here,
maybe the guest just left for a moment.
Does that make sense to you?
What kind of parent leaves
a tiny baby like this alone?
Hey, the baby's crying. It's crying.
Do something about it. Do something.
- What?
- Just do something.
Well...
Baby, are you hungry?
Or did you pee or poo?
- What is this?
- What? Is something there?
Hold on.
Oh my...
- What is that?
- The baby pooped.
Okay, then...
I'm going to open it up.
What? What is it?
Is it all over the place?
No, it's just that...
there's nothing there on the baby.
- She's a girl.
- What about it?
Even if she's a baby...
is it okay for me to change
a girl's diaper like this?
Our Dong Gu has such great manners.
He's a gentlemen.
What do you mean?
Don't be ridiculous and
just change the diaper, you punk!
I'll change it, okay?
Sorry, okay?
Wet wipes, Wet wipes!
Hurry it up! Hurry!
- Give me a wet wipe too.
- Okay.
More wipes, more.
- More, more, more!
- Okay.
Oh! Give me the diaper.
- Diaper, diaper!
- Diaper!
Okay, okay. I'm done.
Good job.
Well, now.
It was no big deal.
Wet wipe.
Wet wipes!
Hey, kid.
I fed you formula
and changed your diaper.
So, why do you keep crying?
Should we just report it to the police?
What if the guest just
stepped out for a bit?
Yeah, let's just wait for a day.
The kid will be tired
at a police station.
So noisy.
No guests and no water.
Now, there's a baby too.
I'm just dying here.
Gosh, my back hurts.
Oh, my back.
Oh, what's this?
She stopped crying, right?
Hey, that's amazing.
Woo!
Wow, I think I can live now.
- What?
- Gosh.
Why are you crying again?
What were you just doing? Do it again.
Get up, get up. Hurry.
I just stood up and bent my back.
Hey, you stand there just like that.
Just like this?
Then what can we do?
Otherwise, she'll cry.
But how can I keep doing this?
Then let's switch places.
I'm so tired.
Oh my. Look at the time.
I have to go film that movie,
so I have to go.
You said it was later tonight.
Hey, I'm filming with the great
Park Sung Woong today.
I should go practice my scenes
with him, right?
Thanks, then. Bye.
Wait. How early are you going?
Doo Shik.
I have to go to my part-time job.
Thanks, Dong Gu.
- What job?
- The convenience store. Bye.
- Hey, hey.
- Work hard.
How can you just leave?
Bong Doo Shik!
I'm going crazy here. I'm going crazy.
Hello? What's up, Su Ah?
Talk about something important?
Now?
Okay. Let's go.
All right.
Looks good. Okay.
Look up.
Last one.
Good work, Su Ah.
Thank you.
[Yoohan Bank: As of February 5th]
[you have outstanding loans
of 12,316,340 won.]
Su Ah, I'm here.
Oh, you're here?
What's this?
So, I woke up this morning
and she was in my room.
A guest must have...
I don't know. I don't know.
- It's a long story.
- Stay strong.
Thanks.
Su Ah, you're what keeps me alive.
What did you want to talk about?
Oh, let's break up.
What?
Break... break up?
What do you mean?
Hm... how should I put it?
Let's just break up.
Why? What's the reason?
Three days and nights isn't enough
time to tell you why.
Let's just break up.
So, just tell me.
I'll listen for three days and nights,
or even a year.
Really? Okay, then.
First, you're too immature.
Second, you don't have enough talent.
Third, I don't see a future with you.
4th... 5th... 6th...
7th... 87th...
89th, your hairstyle really sucks.
90th, the sounds you make while
eating are really annoying.
- 91st...
- Stop, that's enough!
I got it, so stop.
Gosh, wow.
How could you stand it
if you hated me so much?
- Did you even love me?
- Love?
I did.
But you can't only
look at love forever.
You seem really materialistic.
It's not that I'm materialistic.
You're just immature.
Anyway, it's been fun.
I'll return this to you.
Fine. Let's break up.
I don't need that ring,
so do what you want with it.
Thanks so much for
dating a loser like me.
Please eat well and live well.
Let's shoot that scene one more time.
Okay!
- Do a good job today.
- Hey.
Joon Ki, you're here.
Hey, I had to beg the director
for this favor, so do a good job.
All right.
I get paid for the role as soon as
I finish filming, right?
Yes, I said you would.
You haven't met
Park Sung Woong yet, have you?
- No.
- Let's go. I'll introduce you.
Okay.
Senior, this is Lee Joon Ki,
the person you will be acting with today.
[Heartless Man]
Hello, Senior.
It's a true honor to act with my hero.
Pardon?
Excuse me?
What?
Sen... Senior!
Why... Why is being like that?
Did I do something wrong?
Why are you so dense?
He complimented the glint in your eyes,
but you said nothing.
- When?
- He did this to you.
That's what that meant?
He could say it in words.
Why did he do that?
He never speaks much.
He really hates it when people don't
understand his words, so be careful.
- Got it?
- Yes.
See you later.
He doesn't speak,
but hates it if you don't understand.
Then what am I supposed to do?
Ah... is that what charisma is?
That was charisma... charisma.
Ready!
Action!
Cut! What is it, Senior?
Me... me?
What?
Huh... I...
Senior, where are you going?
Senior!
Director Jo, who brought that kid?
I'm sorry, Director.
Gosh.
Hey, get it together.
What did I do?
Senior Sung Woong told you to
take a step back, so why didn't you?
He told me step back?
- When?
- He kept doing this.
He did this and told you three times.
You said that meant
he likes the glint in my eyes.
That depends on the situation.
How could you be so dense?
Senior Sung Woong!
Why can't he just say it in words?
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh.
Why can't they pay me in advance?
What am I supposed to tell Dong Gu?
I'm going crazy.
How can this be...
How am I supposed to know?
Joon Ki. Joon Ki!
You're just getting back?
Yeah, you getting off from
the convenience store?
Yes, do you want one too?
It's only three days past expiry.
Forget it.
You can eat up
and live until you get old.
Why are you in such a bad mood?
Did something happen?
Oh yeah. You were
filming with Park Sung Woong.
How is he? Full of charisma?
He does have charisma.
- He's a little strange though.
- How?
He doesn't talk.
But he hates it
if you don't understand him.
He doesn't talk but hates it
if you don't understand him?
- Does that make sense?
- That's what I'm saying.
Look, suppose I'm Park Sung Woong
and you're me.
We were filming and he does this.
Like this... what does it mean?
- To go one step back.
- How did you know?
It seems obvious to me.
All right, fine.
We met for the first time.
I told him it was an honor to meet him.
Then he went like this.
What does that mean?
- He likes the glint in your eyes.
- Everyone knows?
Only I don't know?
You ought to know depending on
the situation. You're so dense.
- What?
- How will you be an actor?
How is this...
This darn finger.
We're home.
What about the baby's mom?
Are you sick?
Then what's with you?
Is something wrong?
Is not talking a trend or what?
Just talk, you punk!
Su Ah and I broke up.
Huh? Why? For what reason?
Reason? I stopped listening
after about the 90th one.
She would've stayed up
all night if I'd let her.
Why? What's wrong with you?
Hey, it's so obvious.
Su Ah is getting older too and
her family is probably talking marriage.
Just look at him.
Does he have a good job,
money, or a bright future?
On top of that,
this guest house will fall into ruin.
I would break up with him too.
Dating is a luxury
for poor people like us.
Were you depressed like this
because a girl dumped you?
You didn't latch on to her
like a loser, did you?
Why would I do that?
I said I don't need you either.
Then I took my couple ring off
and threw it on the floor.
Why you throw that away?
That's gold and
gold is expensive these days.
Yeah, we could pay
our water bill with that.
You are so thoughtless!
- Should we look for it?
- Are you crazy?
Why would you look for it?
A man has his pride.
So, you stay here and guard your pride.
- We'll go get it. Let's go!
- Be quiet!
Did you get any money?
I have tuna kimbap.
You can have it all to yourself.
I never expected anything
from you two anyway.
Hey, I'll get paid tomorrow
once I finish shooting.
What do we do with her?
We can't wait forever.
I don't know anymore.
Let's call the police. I'm so tired.
Let's wait a little longer, Dong Gu.
Yeah, just wait until tomorrow.
I feel bad for her.
If you feel so bad for her,
then you two watch her.
I've been bouncing all day,
my back hurts so much.
Take turns. Undo this now.
- Move up there a bit.
- Okay.
Go, go.
I said undo this.
Where are you going? Get over here!
Get over here!
Open the door.
You locked it?
I'm going to break it down.
I can really break it.
I'm angry. I'm getting the hammer.
I'm going to get it.
Get over here!
Hey, open it! Hey!
Gosh.
Get over here. Get over here.
I'm going get sick
because of this little thing.
These jerks.
They're gone already?
They've become really diligent.
It's not like them at all.
My goodness.
Hello. Yes, speaking.
What? The electricity?
This week?
Our water's off and if you turn the
electricity off, how can we run our--
Hello? Hello, hello?
They hung up. You hung up again?
What am I supposed to do?
Save me, would you?
Come on. What's with you?
How embarrassing.
A man has to have his pride.
Oh, Dong Gu.
What brings you by?
Su Ah's not here yet.
Oh, then can I wait inside?
- Sure, you can do that.
- Thank you.
Oh, by the way...
did the studio get cleaned yesterday?
No, it didn't. Why?
It's nothing.
What are you doing here?
Oh, you're here?
Oh, that... I'm just, uh...
You acted like
you'd never see me again.
What brings you by?
Oh, the thing is...
I had something to ask you.
- What is it?
- It was, uh...
When do you think the THAAD
issue will be resolved?
You came to ask me about that?
Yes.
We may be broken up,
but we are both Korean people.
We can still discuss
foreign affair issues.
Don't you think so? Right?
We can meet and discuss these things.
Wait.
Yes, what? What?
Shouldn't resolving the problem
to the north be priority?
I'm thinking a two track solution with
six-party talks being held by the UN.
Great. That's a good solution.
Do you really think that
would be best though?
Then what do you think?
How would I know?
The politicians should know. Bye.
What was that?
Kang Dong Gu is always so forgetful.
Dong Gu! Kang Dong Gu.
[Gold Store]
Hello.
Hello. You buy gold rings, right?
Yes, I do.
What do you want to sell?
This here.
Not all of this. This thing here.
How much can I get?
It's 18 karat gold.
Is that what you came looking for?
Su Ah.
You should've told me.
I would've looked with you.
Well, the thing is...
our water bill payments are overdue
and even our electricity, too.
Really? Then...
add this to it too.
Ah...
You left your phone.
Su Ah. Su Ah! Su Ah...
Senior Sung Woong,
you're so funny.
How could something like that happen?
That is so shocking.
Hello, Senior.
I'm so sorry that I couldn't
understand you yesterday.
Please forgive me.
Thank you for forgiving me.
Hey, you understood this time.
You're finally getting used to it.
Really? I really got it right?
Yes, he went like this and
he tapped your shoulder too.
Make sure not to offend him anymore
and do a good job.
All right.
So, it is working out.
Oh my. I'm so sorry.
Cut. Okay!
Good job, everyone!
Senior, great working with you.
Thank you for the compliment, Senior.
I'll work hard.
What? Really?
Yes, Senior.
Everyone! Senior Sung Woong will
treat everyone to Hanwoo beef today!
Park Sung Woong, Park Sung Woong,
Park Sung Woong, Park Sung Woong!
Senior, why don't you say a few words?
Thank you for the food!
Cheers!
My stomach is dancing
after feeding it good beef.
Senior, I enjoyed the food.
What is it?
Pardon?
What?
What is it?
I'm home.
Did something happen?
What's with the mood here?
Joon Ki may not be able work in
the film industry anymore.
Why?
Park Sung Woong told him
to take a rice off his face.
He gave him a kiss on the cheek.
Why did he do that?
I saw the look in his eyes.
It was easy to make the mistake.
I thought he wanted the kiss
for the beef he bought.
What's with you, then?
He went to look for the couple ring
and got caught selling it by Su Ah.
What?
She was looking at me just like that.
With eyes full of scorn.
Gosh.
Still, we can pay the water bill now.
I didn't sell it.
I may be at my lowest,
but I couldn't sell the couple ring.
Then what do we do?
How can we take guests with no water?
I know.
We really are a sad lot.
How could three guys not come up
with a mere 400,000 won?
Why don't we stop now...
and give up?
Give up? On what?
Let's close the guest house.
What do you mean?
We said we'd make money to make a film.
We're supposed to go to Cannes.
Dream on, man.
How can we make a film?
We'd be lucky not to starve to death.
Yeah, I don't think this is right.
Both this guest house and the film,
let's just give up.
We're just giving up in our life.
What kind of life is this?
What do we do with her though?
What else? We should
take her to the police.
Even her parents gave up,
so what can we do?
Still, it is the last time.
Shouldn't we feed her one last time?
The formula ran out.
Was this what she used to eat?
Why is this so expensive?
Do you have money?
Take your cash out.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
That's ours.
We only put it down for a moment.
There's no such thing.
It belongs to whoever gets it first.
Hey now. I said it's ours.
What are you doing? Let go.
- Oh.
- Hey.
What is this? What's going on?
These people are insisting that
this formula is theirs.
We were going to buy it
and put it down for a second.
Oh, why are you arguing over nothing?
Why don't you young men
just give up on it?
What?
Give up?
Why?
Why should we give up?
Well, that's because--
We worked hard too,
so what can we do if things didn't work?
We worked ourselves to death.
The world isn't helping us,
so what can we do?
The painting, wallpaper, and interior
were all done by us through hard work.
It was our last hope.
What are you talking about right now?
We can give up on everything,
but I can't give on this formula!
All right? Give it!
Me too!
Did you see that
woman's expression back there?
It was white and pale.
I know.
Who did she think she was messing with?
It's the perfect weather
to drink formula milk.
It's nice and warm.
What are you two doing?
Filming a movie?
What? It's fun.
This punk always ruins the mood.
I know.
Hey, you saw how we protected
your food, right?
You can't forget that.
Yeah, you'll get in trouble by me
if you do, okay?
Yeah, kid.
Oh, look at that.
- Oh my god.
- So cute.
Yeah, yeah. Cute baby.
Thank you. Thank you.
You're on a tour?
Yeah, we're traveling together.
Where are you going now?
Actually, we're just kind of
looking for a place to sleep.
- Sleep? Sleep, sleep?
- Are they sleepy?
We have a guest house.
Oh, really?
Do you happen to have empty rooms?
Yeah. Room, room, room.
We have many rooms... many rooms.
- So, you want rooms?
- Yeah, sure.
Tonight?
Tonight. Let's go!
Let's go! We have guests.
Okay, okay. Follow me.
They're here!
Guests?
Guests.
- Guests!
- Guests.
What's going on here?
This isn't a dream, right?
Yeah, I don't think we've had this many
guests since our opening.
I think the baby is a blessing.
We paid off the water
and electricity bill with this.
We can pay off the loans and
make a film if this keeps up.
Are you happy?
I thought you wanted to give up.
Well, that was...
I'm saying I want to
give up on giving up.
Just move.
That guy.
Is that right?
Do you feel good, princess?
You like your big brother that much?
Must you talk like that?
Oh, Dong Gu.
Is it bothering you that much?
Aw, aw.
- Give it a rest.
- You brat.
Is our Dong Gu mad?
Oh, how scary. So scary.
That devil.
I told you to stop. Stop!
Why are you screaming? She's crying.
Wait. Maybe she's hungry.
- Where's the formula?
- I put it in the kitchen.
Princess, just wait a little bit.
I'll get your food ready.
Oh dear.
- Come here.
- Hey, hey.
Do you think her parents
really threw her away?
How could they do that to that cute baby?
I'm sure they had their reasons.
What if no one ever comes?
Then we can just raise her.
Didn't you see how guests came
because of her?
I'm a little scared that
her mom will show up.
Still, how can we raise her?
I don't know.
Let's think about that later.
It's time for our blessing to eat.
Our little princess,
it's time to eat yummy food.
Where is she?
Hey, hey! Our blessing, our blessing!
Hey, stop! Hey, hey!
Hey! Someone get that person!
Hey!
Hey! Stop right there!
Hey! Get over here!
Get over here! Stop!
Go that way.
I'm fine. Get him.
Get up. Get up.
Sorry about that. I'm sorry.
Gosh, you sure run well.
You're dead today.
Let me see you. Hey!
Oh...
Are you hurt at all?
My name is Lee Joon Ki.
And your name is?
[Birth of a Family]
Sol, I'm sorry.
Your mom is so sorry.
Mom is so sorry.
I won't ever do it again.
I'm sorry.
Sol, I'm really sorry. I'm sorry.
Her name is Sol?
Gosh, you shouldn't have left her
if you were going to cry so much.
That was a harsh thing to say.
Must've been hard.
Do you need a shoulder?
Do you want to do that in this situation?
What did I do?
Stop it.
Why did you leave your baby here?
Yes, why?
Where is the baby's father?
Yes, her father.
- Then where's your home?
- Yes, your home.
Stop crying and say something.
Then we can take you home or something.
There must be a reason she can't say.
Stop pushing.
I'm sorry, and I'll get going now.
Now? Do you have a place to go?
You don't even have a place to go.
Where will you go with the baby?
Even if you leave,
you should stay the night.
Stay the night? What do you mean?
There are no rooms.
There's Seo Jin's room.
She'll probably spend the night
at the library.
No, I don't want to burden you.
You're not a burden.
It's okay to stay the night.
Also, don't pay any attention to him.
He got dumped by his girlfriend,
so he's just bitter and twisted.
Who got dumped?
It was a mutual break up.
I have no feelings for Su Ah anymore.
Why are you bringing that up now?
If it's not true, then fine.
Why is he getting mad?
- Hey!
- Stop it.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Let's go. It's all right.
Slowly and carefully.
Sleepy, sleepy, sleepy.
I need to sleep.
Sleep.
What is this? Who are you?
Are you a burglar?
No, it's not like that...
Oh my goodness. What is that?
What's going on here!
- What the heck!
- What!
Why did you scream?
Burglar, baby, burglar...
Burglar, baby...
Gosh, I thought it was something.
This girl always makes a scene.
Yoon Ah, are you okay?
You must be shocked.
What? You know her?
Yes, this is Yoon Ah.
She came here.
Chewbacca, you look good.
You're a woman now.
What?
Get out. Get out now!
I see. Then why didn't you call me?
We're not the kind of siblings to
call each other about such things.
- I suppose.
- Sorry, this is my fault.
No, I'm sorry for my mistake.
Anyway, it's late,
so sleep for one night with Yoon Ah.
- Together?
- Then should I sleep with her?
Dong Gu. Don't you know
I can't sleep with others?
I said no but
these two insisted she stay.
There are other rooms.
There are no empty rooms
because we have guests.
- How did you fill all the rooms?
- It's a long story.
That's how it is
so just endure it for one night.
How can I sleep in the same bed
with a person I just met?
You're making such a fuss.
Then sleep on the floor.
You woke us all up from our sleep.
You clean this up.
Let's all go to bed.
Let go of this.
Go to bed.
Oh my gosh.
You must've been uncomfortable.
Why didn't you wake me?
You were sleeping so well.
Sorry, I have very bad sleeping habits.
Did I do anything strange in my sleep?
No, nothing besides farting a few times.
It didn't smell much either.
Here you go.
Breakfast.
Goodness.
Hey, the bread is bleeding.
Cover your mouth when you yawn.
We have guests.
I couldn't sleep
because it was uncomfortable.
What was uncomfortable?
Could it be comfortable sleeping
with a person I just met?
If I managed to fall asleep,
the baby would cry.
Or the baby's mom would snore.
And that woman has a skill for
making people uncomfortable.
On top of that... What?
I owe you a lot for yesterday.
I'll get going now.
You have nowhere to go.
You can stay a few more days.
- What are you saying?
- She has nowhere to go.
You are so inhumane.
No, I don't want to
burden you any longer.
Then have breakfast before going.
It's okay. I'm not hungry at all--
Sit down. I'll prepare it for you.
It's like thunder.
Take your time eating
and have some milk too.
Doo Shik is looking after Sol,
so don't worry.
I'll get more.
What do I do?
What is it? Why is she crying?
I don't know.
She just started to cry.
I can't get her to stop.
Look at the time already.
Oh, thank you.
Sol, you were hungry, right?
I'm so sorry.
I'll give you your food.
Two more pieces of toast...
Oh, that shocked me.
What did I see?
- Did you see?
- No.
I told you that she makes people
feel uncomfortable.
What's wrong? How strange.
What? What's the problem?
She's not sucking out the milk.
Then should we make formula milk?
No, Sol has a weak immune system.
I have to give her breast milk
until she's one.
Do I have to pump my breast?
Pump... pump it?
I don't have the breast pump.
This is a problem.
What is a breast pump?
Do you know?
- How would I know?
- Ask her.
Excuse me.
What is a breast pump?
A breast pump is...
a machine that gets breast milk out.
When a baby can't get breast milk out,
you pump out breast milk for them.
Where... where do they sell that?
They would sell that in a
baby product store.
But, it's a bit expensive
and I don't have money.
All right. I'll buy it. I'll buy it.
Please just stay put.
- I'll go.
- I'm coming too.
I have a part-time job,
so I need to go.
Wait, guys!
Guys, take me with you too.
We have guests so you can't go.
You stay here.
Yes, stay here.
- Sorry.
- Why?
She makes me uncomfortable.
Take me with you.
Take care of things here, Chewbacca.
Joon Ki, Joon Ki!
They say when you become a mom,
you only see your baby.
She just bares her breast
in front of all those men.
It was so shocking.
I know, right?
They have all sorts of things here.
What does a breast pump look like?
They sell clothes too.
It's just wide open here.
How could you wear this?
Hello, there.
The product you are looking at now
is a nursing outfit.
What is a nursing outfit?
There are times when you go out with
a cute baby and she cries out of hunger.
When there are many people,
it can feel like too much to nurse.
Do not worry.
You can pull this zipper up
and take your breast out.
You can breastfeed your baby without
worrying about the looks of others.
In other words,
it's like a pocket for your breast.
A pocket...
A pocket for your breast?
Looks like there are
lots of interesting things.
What is this?
Hello, there.
The product you are looking at
is a nursing pad.
What is a nursing pad?
When your baby is hungry and
sucking on the mother's breast
then what would happen next?
The baby takes its mouth
off the mother's breast.
What do you think happens?
Without a place to go,
breast milk sprays out like a fountain.
That's when you would stick on
this nursing pad.
Phew. You can feel at ease.
It is a breast milk preserver,
to put it in other words.
Oh!
Is there something
you're looking for in particular?
I'm here for a breast pump.
It's awkward.
So awkward I feel like dying.
I have to say something... say something.
Oh my. Your baby has
such defined eyebrows.
Look at those chubby cheeks.
He's like a general, a little prince.
It's a girl.
I see.
No wonder she had a boyish charm.
You know it's a trend
to have a girl crush look.
Her dad must adore her
since she's a girl.
We broke up.
I see.
It's not a bad thing for a woman
to raise a child alone lately.
Who needs a dad?
Grandma and Grandpa
can love her twice as much.
They passed away.
Both of them.
When I was two...
in a fire.
Dong Gu, hurry up.
Hurry, hurry, hurry!
There are manual breast pumps.
There are automatic breast pumps too.
With this manual breast pump,
put his funnel shape against the breast.
Stick it there and pull this here.
That is the system
to pump the breast milk.
With the automatic breast pump,
you merely press this button.
It will pump 40 to 50 times
in one minute.
Just give us anything.
Stop explaining.
I'm begging you, please.
My trauma level is at terminator levels.
Right?
Yeah.
Should I take something to
help with my nerves?
Okay.
Hey, there's Su Ah.
Dong Gu, there's Su Ah...
Dong Gu. Kang Dong Gu.
What are you doing there?
Huh? Oh, there's
a foundation column here.
Oh, it's strong.
Of course, it's strong.
Would it be weak then?
Are you by chance...
Hey, Su Ah!
What are you doing?
Don't do that. Don't!
- Don't do that.
- Hey, man.
Get on your knees and beg
if you can't forget her.
Why? What did I do wrong
that I should beg?
Getting caught selling your couple ring
wasn't so great.
Well, that...
I told you not to bring that.
I told you not to.
It's obvious you still have feelings.
I do not. I do not!
Okay, keep that pride of yours.
Live your whole life with regrets.
Su Ah went that way.
I'm going that way. Bye.
- You stay.
- Wait up.
Just go then.
I don't know then.
It's not like pride will keep me full.
I'll just get on my knees.
Better than regretting it
for the rest of my life.
Hey, there. Su--
Su Ah!
Yoon Seok.
Why were you so late?
I'm sorry. I'll buy you
delicious pasta to make up for it.
Let's go.
- What's wrong with him?
- What is it?
He suddenly fainted. Hold on.
Excuse me. Are you okay?
Are you sick?
- Yeah.
- Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Let me see your face. Excuse me.
Hold on a little longer.
Oh! Joon Ki, Joon Ki!
What took you so long?
What's with you?
I can't breathe!
It was so awkward.
I thought I was going to a mental
hospital because of this breast pump.
Why? Did something happen?
I don't know. Don't ask.
I don't want to think about it.
- That's what I'm saying.
- Be quiet. Go inside.
Go on in.
Yoon Ah, here's the pump.
Thank you. Sorry to be a nuisance.
Don't say such a thing.
Sol must be hungry.
You should feed her.
Sol, you must be very hungry.
Let's feed you.
So, this is what it looks like.
Why is she doing that?
I told you she makes people
really uncomfortable.
What's wrong with this?
What now? What... what is it?
The breast milk still isn't coming out.
I think the milk ducts are clogged.
That's a problem.
What? Yoo Sun? Is that a person?
("Yoo Sun" sounds like "milk duct")
There's a duct in the breast where
the milk comes from and it's clogged.
What do you need to do for that?
It opens up with a massage.
It costs a lot to get a massage.
Okay, I'll get a loan to get one for you.
Please sit still!
What? 100,000 won for one?
It really is expensive.
- Can you come now?
- What?
That won't do.
- All right.
- They can't come?
They're fully booked and
can't come until next week.
What do we do?
There's nothing we can do.
What is it?
My breasts are swollen
so they're in pain.
That's a big problem.
What? Why are you looking at me?
- You try it.
- What?
- What do you mean?
- Massage.
Try massaging.
Is it a big deal?
You just squeeze and it's a massage.
Are you crazy telling me to
massage a stranger's breasts?
Should I do it then?
Of course, I want to do it.
I would love to give it a try.
- Should I close my eyes and try?
- Are you crazy?
So, you should try.
Don't you feel bad
for Yoon Ah, who's in pain?
Ah, it hurts.
I do feel bad for her, but still...
How can I massage someone's breasts?
No, I'm really okay.
Oh, that hurts.
I'm going crazy here.
I'm going crazy.
Excuse me. Are you okay?
I'm really going crazy.
Go! Just go, man.
Yoon Seok, let's go now.
How can we leave a sick person here?
Just leave me.
Leave me and just go!
Over here.
Did you call it in?
He suddenly fainted
and can't seem to get up.
I think he hurt his face.
Really?
Sir, can you hear me?
Try getting up.
Gosh, this won't do.
We'll have to force him up.
All right. One, two!
Sir, don't fight it.
One, two!
Is something wrong?
I think he needs to go to a big hospital.
Hold on.
Okay, I'll get up.
Are you awake now?
I'll be totally embarrassed
if I get caught here.
Gosh, who cares?
Sir?
Are you okay?
Oh no. He must have hurt his head.
I will get started now.
I'm so tired.
When can I stop working part-time jobs?
I'm probably the only CEO who works
part-time to keep his business afloat.
What's this?
How is it going?
How did it go?
Did you succeed?
Can't you tell by seeing?
I thought the milk gland exploded.
What a relief.
You worked hard.
I'm proud of you. I'm so proud.
Be quiet. Where's the breast pump?
Bring it now.
The pump is in the living room.
Is Yoon Ah older than you?
You look much older than her.
What?
I haven't had a workout lately,
so I'm feeling antsy.
I'm just joking.
Joke, yeah right.
Joke, joke, joke.
It was a joke.
I told you it was a joke.
Ah, this feels great.
Let go.
Hey! What are you doing,
you crazy punk!
- What did I do?
- What, what?
Why, why, why, why?
Do you know what this is
to put on your body?
Why are you hitting me?
Isn't it a massage machine?
Massage machine?
You punk, it's a pump for breast milk...
What? It feels great. Try it.
Try it? You little punk!
Do you know how much this is?
You punk!
You just need to do well.
Oh, why do you look like that?
Did something happen?
Don't ask me anything.
Not a thing.
Why is it so quiet here?
- Where are the guests?
- Hm?
They're having a party on the roof.
I made pork belly for them
and they loved it.
Yeah? Good job.
Ah, did that woman and the baby leave?
Huh? Yeah, she left. She did.
Yeah, that's good.
Doesn't the house feel empty
without any noise though?
I wonder if Yoon Ah is okay with
nowhere to go?
- I'm worried.
- So worried.
Right, Dong Gu?
Yeah, she could've stayed here.
You're really worried too, right?
What is this?
Why are you all acting suspicious?
You're all hiding something, right?
No, we're not!
What would we hide?
- Yeah, no way.
- No.
What is that? Isn't that a crying baby?
What? I didn't hear anything.
- I didn't hear anything.
- Me neither.
Hey, Seo Jin.
I think my milk glands are clogged again.
Why... why is she here?
You said she left. You said so.
Who? Her?
That's not Yoon Ah.
That's someone else.
Yes, Yoo Sun. I'll be right there!
Oh, really? I see.
You think I'm a fool.
What's with you?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Don't you have pity for Yoon Ah?
We may not have money,
but we have humanity.
- I don't.
- Hey!
Hey, stop that.
Let go of me. Let go!
Dong Gu, let's just let her stay here.
Yoon Ah, go inside. Get inside!
Get inside. Go in.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
She will cause a big problem.
I know it.
Oh, what do I do? Oh no!
What do I do?
I don't like her. I just don't.
I really don't like her.
Buy me this.
- Who?
- My girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
A Korean X-Man.
It'll be a hit, 100 percent.
If you ruin the makeup,
I'll get rid of the role.
Take this!
Joon Ki.
Life is so hard. It really is.
- Chewbacca?
- Seo Jin?
Yoon Ah.
If I don't shave for half a day,
I get all this hair.
Chewbacca, we're dying out here.
Did you make the stew
with this mushroom?
We're all sick because of it!
I'm sorry.
I can't let this go.
She has to pack up and go.
What are you doing?
Su Ah.