Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
We are the world.
To all of those who are here
with us at our Waikiki guest house
I truly want to thank you.
I sincerely hope you have a
great vacation while you are here.
Next.
- Ladies and gentlemen.
- Gentlemen.
Thank you.
Woo!
That... that's it?
I said a long thing.
I compressed mine.
Just get the point across.
Never mind.
What can I expect from you?
Now, let's have some fun tonight.
Cheers!
What's wrong with him?
He got dumped recently.
Don't worry about him.
We'll have fun together.
- Cheers!
What's wrong with her?
She also got dumped a few days ago.
It was a very sad situation
that happened in a miserable way.
Don't worry about those two.
Once again, let's...
- Cheers!
It's okay. I'm going up to rest.
Why? Things were just getting good.
Where are you all going?
- Wait.
- Guests!
- Stop, stop.
- Hey, hey.
Mayday, mayday! Emergency.
Hey, hey!
Gosh.
Hey, stop blowing your nose.
You'll blow out
your bone marrow at this rate.
How long are you
going to keep this up?
Can't you see the guests
are uncomfortable?
I'm sorry, Joon Ki.
I keep thinking about Tae Hyun.
I can't stop the tears.
- What's she saying?
- What did she say?
Don't cry.
Seo Jin!
- That scared me.
- Is he Jean Valjean or something?
Senior, what are you doing here?
I wanted to see you.
I wanted to see you so badly.
Weren't you disappointed by me?
Why would I be?
Because of your mustache?
Who cares about that, you dummy!
Are you stupid?
Even if bananas grew out of your head...
Even if kelp and seaweed
grew out of your armpits...
He must be crazy.
I don't care at all, Seo Jin.
Senior.
Do you want to officially start dating?
Senior Tae Hyun!
Whether it's kelp or seaweed,
I don't care.
They think they're in a film
or something, don't they?
It's a lowly third-rate
cult film, at that.
Don't you agree, Dong Gu?
I'm so envious.
[Beautiful Farewell]
- Come on. Come on.
- This one.
That's right. We got it!
Senior, here's a coffee.
Thank you.
Senior, your nose is bleeding.
It's okay.
I tend to get nosebleeds often.
These paintings are really nice.
We're already here.
- It's late. Go on in.
- Okay.
Oh yeah.
- Here.
- What is it?
Open it once you're inside.
I'll really get going now.
- Get home safely.
- Okay.
I've loved you since I was...
You love me.
I'm home.
You're home?
Did your date go well?
Chewbacca, why is your face so red?
Just like a person
who kissed someone.
No, I didn't. What kiss?
What do you mean? You totally did.
What is that?
This? It's a gift from Senior Tae Hyun.
A gift? Let me see. Give it to me.
No, why would you look at it?
Because I'm like a big brother.
Give it to me.
Why else would I look?
Oh, it looks nice.
What is it? What, what?
He bought you a razor?
Why would he...
Senior shouldn't have.
I've never seen such a thing
in all my life.
You're probably
the only woman in the world
who's received
a razor from her boyfriend.
Be quiet.
Don't you agree, Dong Gu? Huh?
What now? What?
Now that I think about it...
I don't think I ever
bought Su Ah a proper gift.
It's kimbap!
Don't touch it.
It's for Senior Tae Hyun.
How cheap and petty of you.
- I won't eat it!
- Don't eat it.
You never even
made us a ramen in your life.
You are so devoted to your boyfriend!
Seriously, so petty.
Don't you agree, Dong Gu?
Again? What now?
I don't think I've ever made
Su Ah kimbap before.
How many guys
in this country do you think
have made kimbap for their girlfriends?
Don't you agree, Doo Shik?
Isn't it only right to ask
someone who's had a girlfriend?
- Sorry, man.
- You're bad.
Seo Jin, why are you standing there?
It's nothing.
Senior, you have a nosebleed.
I have a lot of stress due to my job.
I'm getting nosebleeds more often.
I see.
I'm almost done my article,
so wait just a bit.
Yeah, take your time.
I have to study too.
This is...
I'm done.
What is this anyway?
Oh, this? It's kimbap.
You made that for me?
Yes, why don't you try some?
It should be good.
- Wow.
- Here.
Seo Jin, you have to eat kimbap
with your hands to optimize the taste.
Looks good.
Yum, it's just so good.
You try one. Ah...
No, I will eat it on my own.
Come on, Seo Jin.
I want to feed it to you.
Try it. Hurry. Ah...
That's right. Go on.
- Ah...
- There you go.
You're eating well.
So cute.
Oh! What's that?
There was nothing there.
What was it?
I must have seen wrong.
Oh, you're so cute!
Cutie, playful thing.
Seo Jin, only feeding you one
means I don't have affection for you.
- Ah...
- No, no.
It's okay.
Can't we watch something else now?
Just leave it.
It feels new every time I watch it.
Hm? There are no more tissues.
Don't touch the remote control.
Gosh!
I'm home.
Oh, Chewbacca. You're home?
How did your date go?
Yeah, well...
What's with your facial expression?
Did you two already fight?
No, it's not that.
Senior Tae Hyun has a strange habit.
What habit?
He picks his nose a lot.
People can pick their nose sometimes.
Sounds like nothing to me.
I'm telling you it's not nothing.
He doesn't wash his hand
after picking his nose and eats kimbap.
- Then he feeds me and pinches my cheek.
- Hey, Chewbacca.
You're being so selfish.
Why am I?
That Tae Hyun guy is overlooking your
mustache and you can't overlook that?
Is that the same thing?
Mine is physical and his is a habit.
Whatever! Talk to him
if it bothers you that much.
Can I do that?
What if he gets mad?
He was understanding about your
mustache, so this is nothing.
My seat.
What now? What, what, what?
There's no toilet paper in the bathroom.
Oh, my head. My head hurts.
Dong Gu, I made some porridge.
Try having some.
I have no appetite.
How long are you going to keep this up?
You haven't slept
or eaten in days. You'll die!
Just leave me to die.
I don't even want to live.
Crazy punk. What a crazy punk.
Have you nothing better to do than waste
your life on a mere girl like Su Ah?
What?
"Mere girl like Su Ah"?
Joon Ki, are you done?
What did I say wrong?
She may seem like nothing much to you.
She was true love to me.
I won't forget my memories
with Su Ah until I die!
It is a wound that will never heal!
Do you know that?
How dare he get mad at me? Hey, you!
What are you doing here alone?
Nothing, really.
It's very hard, isn't it?
A sudden breakup is so hard
that you feel like dying.
I've been through it,
so I know it very well.
Still, Dong Gu,
though it feels so painful right now
you will eventually forget
once time passes.
- So--
- No.
It's not like that for me.
10 years... no, even 100 years
could pass and I wouldn't forget Su Ah.
Why?
There was so much I couldn't do for her.
I regret it so much.
Do you know what I regret the most?
I couldn't even give her
a beautiful farewell.
If I could meet her one last time...
If I could give her a farewell
that I wouldn't regret...
I'd want to give her
one that's beautiful.
What brings you here?
I came because I had a favor to ask.
What favor?
Please meet Dong Gu just once.
Why would I?
Dong Gu is going through
a very tough time.
He can't sleep or eat
and all he does is cry.
What does that have to do with me?
I heard you dated for four years.
Then you shouldn't
just end things like this.
So, if you could meet Dong Gu
just one last time--
I told you I don't want to,
so please go.
I need to work.
Please don't do that.
Think of it as saving a person just once.
Please, Su Ah.
Su Ah, Su Ah, Su Ah!
Please don't do that
and just meet him once.
I said no, so just leave.
Su Ah! Don't be like that
and see him just once.
Please, Su Ah!
Su Ah!
Why are you staring?
Is there something on my face?
No. It's nothing.
I'm almost done,
so wait just a bit.
All right.
[Nose, nose, nose, nose...]
Senior.
You startled me. What is it?
I'm very sorry.
But could you please
stop picking your nose?
Ah, sorry, I didn't realize.
Could you also please stop rolling it
into a ball and flicking it?
All right. I'm sorry.
I was conflicted
about saying this to you.
- I have to say it today.
- Okay.
Did you know you have
a severe nose-picking habit?
Really? I do?
Yes. Also, you said you
tend to get nosebleeds a lot.
That's not it.
It's because you pick your nose a lot.
I must have picked up
the habit unconsciously.
I'm really sorry.
It's okay. You can fix habits.
You're not feeling bad, are you?
No, you told me for my sake.
Why would I feel bad?
I'm so relieved.
Then let's go have a beer somewhere.
Let's go, Senior.
Okay. Sure.
Dong Gu, over here.
What? Why did you call me out here?
There's a part-time employee
I used to work with at the store.
She kept asking me
to set her up with someone.
- And?
- What else? I'm telling you to meet her.
They say you need to meet someone
to get over your ex.
- So...
- Are you crazy?
- What is it?
- Do you take me that lightly?
When I think about Su Ah,
I still feel a tense pain right here.
I'm not ready to send Su Ah off yet
and I don't want to, okay?
- Seriously.
- How can you just leave?
- You're crazy.
- Just say hello.
There she is. Over here, Mi Na.
Mi Na, this is the friend
I told you about, Kang Dong Gu.
Hello, my name is Lee Mi Na.
Hello.
I'm saying hello because of you.
Don't do this again, okay?
Yeah. Okay.
I heard a lot about you from Doo Shik.
Really?
Ah, I see.
Should we go have coffee then?
Why don't we go drinking instead?
- Should we do that?
- But, Mi Na...
I am afraid that
Dong Gu has to go home.
He actually broke up
with his girlfriend a few days ago.
He doesn't feel like being set up.
Oh, I see.
It's okay. There's nothing we can do.
Dong Gu, I'm sorry
I didn't know how you felt.
Go on in now. Go and rest.
Get plenty of rest, okay?
Yes, I will.
It was still nice to meet you.
I'll see you next time.
Doo Shik, you have to
treat me to grilled clams, okay?
Okay.
What have you been doing lately?
You haven't called.
Hey, Kang Dong Gu.
Why are you looking?
You're not regretting it, are you?
You've only just broken up with Su Ah.
Pull yourself together, Kang Dong Gu.
Yum, this is good.
What appetizer should we order?
Sesame leaf... sesame leaf pasta?
Senior! You're doing it again.
- Sorry.
- This really won't do.
We need to take special measures.
Special measures?
Seo Jin, do we
really need to go this far?
We have no choice
in order to fix your habit.
Why? You don't want to?
No, I'll do it.
Senior, cheers.
Hold on.
Cheers.
Mi Na, eat up.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Hey, Dong Gu.
You guys were here?
Mi Na wanted to eat grilled clams.
What brings you here?
I wanted to gather my thoughts,
so I thought I'd have some soju.
- Alone?
- Yes.
- Alone at a grilled clam place?
- Yes. Why?
I come alone two to three times a week.
Is that weird?
Would you like to join us, then?
- Should I?
- No, Mi Na.
Dong Gu wants to
gather his thoughts on his own.
He's not in a good place lately.
Dong Gu, don't worry about us
and eat lots.
- Eat up.
- Yeah, okay.
What would you like?
One soju and an order of grilled clams.
By yourself? It'll be a lot.
I eat like that two
to three times a week.
Give it to me.
Why is there so darn much?
I keep eating,
but there's still so much.
I'll pour it for you.
- Cheers.
Mi Na, isn't that person really dense?
How could a person be so dense like that?
Who was it?
His name is Lee Joon Ki.
We live together.
He must be naturally that way.
How could he not get it?
- Doo Shik, have a drink.
- Okay.
That was really good.
Should we get going now?
Shall we?
You're going too?
Yes, I was just about to leave.
You have lots of clams left.
Oh, this? I'm going to
take them to go for Sol.
You're giving clams to a baby
who just passed 100 days old?
You can blend them
and give them to her.
Ma'am, I'll take this to go.
Senior, there you go again!
You do it whenever I'm not around.
Seo Jin, this is going too far though.
How is it going too far?
I'm going to hit you whenever
you pick your nose, just so you know.
All right. Let's just stop.
How can I stop?
You must not take me seriously to
go right back to picking your nose.
Why won't you listen
even after I tell you?
I said please just stop.
Why are you getting angry?
Is picking one's nose some deadly crime?
I'm doing this all for your sake.
You get frequent nosebleeds
and it's bad for hygiene.
Honestly... it's unpleasant to look at.
"Unpleasant to look at."
Then what about your mustache?
Why would you bring that up?
I understood your mustache.
Why can't you understand me?
How are the two alike?
Mine is physical and yours is a habit.
I have a physical issue
where I get lots of snot.
What did you say?
Honestly, what's more strange between
your mustache and my nose-picking?
Are you curious? Should I ask people?
Excuse me!
Right now, this woman grows a mustache.
What's more strange between a
mustache and picking one's nose?
Senior, why are you doing this?
It's embarrassing.
Embarrassing? You're embarrassed of me?
I'm embarrassed of you too.
Do you know why?
When I have dates with you
from morning to evening
your mustache starts to grow.
I can start to see it.
Then when I kiss you...
it feels so rough.
On the days that I kiss you,
I go home and apply ointment.
Having to do that...
I endured all of that.
So, why are you making me feel
so wretched over picking my nose?
If it bothered you so much,
why didn't you mention it?
How did you bear it?
So narrow-minded.
What? Narrow-minded?
Are you finished?
Yes, I called you narrow-minded.
What kind of a guy is so narrow-minded?
Yes, I'm narrow-minded.
What about it, hairy woman?
Hairy woman?
- You snot!
- Snot?
Yes, you snot!
Don't even call me snot.
You're Huam-dong's hairy woman.
Huam-dong's hairy woman?
- You're Wangsimni's snot!
- Wangsim...
What do you take Wangsimni for?
I won't accept this. Let's break up.
Yes, let's break up.
Don't contact me again, you snot.
Don't contact me.
You're Huam-dong's hairy woman.
Can't hear you. Snot, snot, snot.
Hairy woman, hairy woman...
Please, can you be quiet?
Oh, you scared me.
You're still here?
Please just come see Dong Gu
one last time.
Why are you doing this?
- Did Dong Gu put you up to this?
- No.
Then why are you the one doing this?
Being unable to have a proper
goodbye with a person you love
is something I know a lot about.
So, please meet with him one last time.
I'm asking you this favor.
No, thank you.
I don't want to see his face again.
Just give up and leave.
Gosh.
You're being too harsh.
Su Ah.
If you keep this up,
I won't stand for it.
What?
What are you going to do then?
Gosh.
Hey! My bag.
What kind of person does that?
Hey, you!
Thanks for the meal today, Doo Shik.
It was nothing.
Don't forget the date I'm
setting up for you on Friday.
What? A date?
He's already introducing her
to someone else?
I don't even have her number yet.
That disloyal punk.
Wait. Why do you need her number?
Do you really have an interest in her?
Get it together.
Get it together, Kang Dong Gu!
- Ouch.
- Oh, that startled me.
What? You haven't left yet?
What's the matter?
I have something stuck in my teeth.
Do you have a business card, Mi Na?
Why do you need a business card?
Business cards are the best to
get at food stuck between teeth.
I get so annoyed with food
in my teeth that I throw a fit.
I didn't know that.
Mi Na, do you have a business card?
Hey, I have one.
[Pig's Mom]
Here it is.
This is a card you cherish
that you got from Pig's Mom.
- How can I use that?
- Maybe you're right.
Hold on. I have another one.
Do you have one, Mi Na?
A business card. One moment.
I'm not sure...
Oh, I have one that
I used from my old job.
Yes, this is it.
This kind of corner is best.
This is my favorite kind of corner.
This angle is just perfect.
This can be really hard to find.
Oh, what a relief.
You should get going then.
What's with him?
That was natural.
That was brilliant. Very good.
Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah! Please stop.
Only if you say you'll meet Dong Gu.
Give it back while I'm still being nice.
I won't give it to you until you
say you'll meet with Dong Gu.
Seriously, why are you being like this?
You can't be like this
with someone you once loved.
Don't be this way and see him just once.
All right. All right!
Really?
- Where is Dong Gu?
- Probably the guest house.
Let's go.
It's Kang Dong Gu
who you were set up with today.
Just calling to see if you got home okay.
It was nice meeting you today.
Su Ah.
You went out on a date today, Dong Gu?
How is it that Su Ah is here?
You said you wanted nothing more
than to see her just once.
Yes, that's true...
Su Ah, what happened here is...
Dong Gu, should we go talk?
Huh?
Okay... yes.
Su Ah, it's a misunderstanding.
It really is.
I had no intention of being set up,
but Doo Shik suddenly called me out.
I must've gone crazy for a moment.
I'm really sorry, Su Ah.
Dong Gu.
You don't need to be sorry to me.
I have no right
to hear those words from you.
Thank you so much for liking me
for the past four years.
I was happy.
- But--
- Stop.
What... what are you going to say?
Get angry instead.
If you do this, I can't even beg.
It really feels over.
Su Ah, I'll be better.
I'll be 100, no, 1,000 times
better than that guy.
- So, Su Ah--
- Dong Gu.
You were very good to me
all those years.
It's not your fault
that this happened to us.
It's all my fault.
I changed.
But, you know what?
I'm so happy with Yoon Seok.
So, you should forget about me.
I want you to be happy too.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Dong Gu.
I'm really sorry, Dong Gu.
Thank you for liking me all those years.
I'll get going now.
"You all live for tomorrow."
"Those who live for tomorrow will die
at the hands of he who lives for today."
"I only live for today."
"Just how screwed up that is..."
"I will show you."
- Leave your profile there.
- Yes, Sir.
What you saw just now was
rookie actor, Lee Joon Ki.
Please remember me.
Good luck with your project.
[Are You Still Dreaming?]
Bye. See you again.
Bye.
I'm home.
Where did you go dressed up so early?
I thought of it as morning exercise
and distributed my profile everywhere.
What good is it
to give your profile to everyone?
You never have any lines
and always stand in the background.
- It's a waste of paper.
- What did you say?
Is that anything to say to someone
who just worked all morning?
Gosh, that's why you got called
"hairy woman" by your first love.
Hey, I told you not to say that.
Don't say it. Just don't say it!
Stop fighting. We have guests.
- Kang Seo Jin!
- Let me go.
What's with the camera?
Why do you need that?
I have a shoot tomorrow.
A shoot? Since when?
Oh, I agreed to
help Tae Shik with his work.
Why the sudden part-time job?
I want to make money.
Money? Is something wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
Oh... Su Ah and I broke up for good.
It seems like she met a good person,
so I want to send her off.
What does breaking up with Su Ah
have to do with making money?
Now that I broke up with Su Ah,
I realized I only have films left.
I want to focus this year
and go all-in on films.
Hey, I want to have enough production
money within a year for our film.
Joon Ki, keep practicing your acting.
You need to hurry up
and finish that script.
Kang Dong Gu with the strong will.
I see the old you!
Are you going to write
what you talked about back then?
You mean that story about the
US president and Bruce Lee?
Gosh. How long will his resolve last?
Why are you sighing?
Yoon Ah, what is it?
Is something wrong?
Seo Jin, do you have a dream too?
Yes, I have a dream. To be a reporter.
I dreamed of becoming one
since I was little.
But I've failed the interview
so many times that I can't remember.
Why do you ask?
Because I envy it.
Everyone has a dream.
Dong Gu, Joon Ki, Doo Shik, and you.
You sure envy strange things.
Don't you have a dream?
I did, but how can I have a dream
in my situation?
What does that have to do
with your dream?
My situation isn't so good.
I have Sol too.
Yoon Ah, do you know who
Joanne Rowling is?
She was a divorcee with a child.
All she had for income was
a weekly 15,000 won.
She was lacking formula for the baby,
so she mixed in water.
She overcame that and
do you know which book she wrote?
It was "Harry Potter." "Harry Potter."
Saying her life was hard,
she had no time
or her family didn't have money?
Those are all just excuses.
So, tell me what your dream is.
I'll help you if it's too hard,
so just tell me.
Rapper.
Rap... rapper?
A rapper like Dok2 or BewhY?
Why? Is it weird?
It's not that it's weird,
just unexpected.
Do you know how to rap?
A little bit. Should I try it?
Okay. Sure.
Yeah. Get it.
The world is spread out before me.
It's an illusion.
Delicious table of food.
The best is the on the prime minister's.
Or maybe it's the president's table?
Perhaps not?
You loser. Unwanted wild man.
Misery. Yeah.
- How was it?
- Oh, it had character.
If you practice a bit more,
I think it'll be better.
Really? Then you think I can go for it?
Of course, why can't you?
It is your dream.
Thank you, Seo Jin.
I would've kept it buried in my heart
forever if not for you.
- Thank you, Seo Jin.
- No need to thank me.
Keep at it.
No, you can't die.
Private.
There's a radio.
Mayday, mayday. Emergency!
Gosh, are they even coming?
Private, you have to hold on. Private!
Private? Private!
Those jerks.
Let's meet in the afterlife.
That is all.
By the way...
did you come here knowing
what our film was about?
Yes, Director.
Marine, like the marine troops, right?
No, it's about a swimmer.
Marine Boy, Park Tae Hwan.
Swimming, the Olympics, and youth.
I'm sorry, Director.
I've been going to so many auditions.
I will do it again.
No, you don't need to. You can go.
What?
Director, please give me another chance.
I'm a great swimmer.
The role doesn't matter
and I don't need to be paid.
Please just give me anything, Director.
Please!
Then take off your clothes.
Excuse me?
Why do you suddenly need that?
It's about swimmers.
You need to have a good body in
order to get a minor role or something.
Yes, I'll get undressed.
Oh, wait. Is that all body hair?
Yes, it is.
- Are your legs like that too?
- Ah, yes.
I have a lot of male hormones in my body.
- You fail.
- What?
Zip up and go.
But... but why?
Have you seen a swimmer as hairy as you?
Swimmers try to minimize air resistance
so they get shave
their armpits and heads.
They even get rid of hair there.
Don't you know?
I will get rid of it.
Except for the hair on my head,
I'll get rid of everything else.
Do not worry, Director!
Marine... ouch.
So, this is where they do it.
Gosh, do I really have to do this?
I'm going crazy.
What is this?
Why is this all torn apart?
Oh my.
Hello!
Yes, who are you?
I'm the waxer who will be waxing you.
You will be doing it for me?
Don't be shy about it.
Many other men get it done too.
Really?
Well, let's not waste time
and do it, then.
Then get started and lie down.
Should we put this away?
Keep it. You will need it.
Please remove your gown, then.
I'll get started.
Bear with me even if it hurts.
I'm removing the sheet.
Ouch. Ow! What was that?
So that's why I need this.
[President is Bruce Lee]
Are you trying to create fake views?
Do you have to do that?
Everyone else does it too.
Why aren't there views?
It's driving me nuts.
- Seo Jin.
- Hm?
Lend me your ID.
- Why?
- To put up comments.
No thanks.
Seo Jin, I made a song.
- Would you like to hear it?
- What?
You already wrote something?
A song? What kind of song?
Yoon Ah says her dream
is to become a rapper.
Rap... rapper?
So, you know how to rap?
Yes, I wrote something
with Seo Jin in mind.
Would you listen?
Yes, sure.
I had no clue you had this kind of skill.
- Give me a beat.
- Sure.
Yeah. Get it.
Your eyes are the eyes of hawks.
You're like a hawk with your career.
Hungry? How many amps?
Try and fool my eyes.
I can see into your heart.
Try and hide away.
You're dead if I find you.
I'll beat you up if I catch you.
Don't make a move if you're scared.
Yeah. Woo, woo!
What did you think?
Oh, yeah. It's good.
There a uniqueness to it
and a grotesque charm, too.
Really? I have one more song.
Do you want to hear it?
No. Oh, it's not that.
I just have to shower now,
so I'll listen later.
Later...
Seo Jin, I'll get started.
Get it.
My name is Han Yoon Ah.
In English, Yoon Ah Han.
Your name is Kang Seo Jin.
Backwards, it is Jin Seo Kang.
Geez.
That was shocking.
Isn't it too much to become
a rapper with those skills?
What are you doing? Get out.
Sorry. Why didn't say you were here?
How can I when I was showering?
Wait a minute.
Joon Ki! What is that?
What happened there?
It's nothing. It's nothing.
What do you mean?
- I said it's nothing.
- Move.
Where did it all go?
It's because of the temperature.
- Stop turning me around.
- Where did it all go?
A Brazilian wax? Why would you do that?
The director told me to,
so what could I do?
I wouldn't get the role otherwise.
You're really doing
all sorts of crazy things.
- What's the role.
- Swimmer Eight.
Seeing that you have no name,
you probably have no lines.
Swimmer Eight is pretty great too.
There's even a Swimmer 28.
What do you know?
Oh, really?
Wow, there are 28 swimmers?
Shut up!
Oh, it's Ji Soo.
Hello. Yes, Ji Soo.
Yes, it's Joon Ki.
Tomorrow? I'm not doing much. Why?
Oh, with your mother!
Yes, yes. Of course. Okay.
Yes, see you tomorrow. Okay.
You already have a new girlfriend?
How many days will it last this time?
I'm very serious this time.
Can't you tell when I'm having
a meal with her mother?
- Oh.
- Really?
You must really be serious.
I really am.
It feels different than
all the other girls I've dated.
Dong Gu, did you feel like this
when you dated Su Ah too?
Yeah, well...
- Joon Ki.
- What?
I was just asking in passing.
- Sorry.
- No need to be sorry.
- Hope it works out.
- Thank you.
Gosh, seriously.
You are so unaware of the situation.
Why would you bring up Su Ah?
I didn't do it on purpose.
Also, he said it was okay.
Why are you throwing a fit?
He doesn't look okay.
He's fine. Just look after yourself.
Thank you. Thank you.
What are you doing here?
Just sitting here.
You were thinking about Su Ah,
weren't you?
It's hard, isn't it?
You don't have to say anything.
I know how hard it is.
I also know that words
can't console you right now.
So, I prepared something for you.
What is it? What?
Yeah. Get it.
Wounds of a breakup,
bear into your heart, tears fall.
Don't cry even when
you're lonely and sad.
Are you Candy? No, you're Dong Gu.
What are you doing?
What's with the sudden rap?
Look into my eyes.
Lesson, you can forget Su Ah.
You can erase Su Ah.
So scary. Stop it.
Why are you suddenly rapping?
Are you crazy?
Now, run. Run toward your dream.
You're just going to go. Where?
I said stop. Why are you rapping?
You're a really strange lady.
Why are you rapping?
I know where.
I told you to stop.
Why are you doing this?
Yeah!
Where's Joon Ki?
He got dressed up and left this
morning to meet his girlfriend's mom.
Oh yeah.
You're going to work too, right?
Yeah, I'm shooting a baby's birthday.
Are you going to the library?
Yeah, I have a study group.
You, me, here, this, noise, we, know.
Why is that lady suddenly doing that?
Yoon Ah's dream happens to be
becoming a rapper.
Rapper? With those skills?
I was the one who told her to go for it.
I'm going nuts.
It was you who got her started.
Even if it is her dream,
that's not right.
Stop it before it's too late.
Who knows what trouble she'll cause.
She's so serious about it.
I can't say anything.
You figure that out. I'm going.
- Take a bagel.
- I'm fine.
You, me, here, this,
noise, we, know. Woo!
Oh, oh...
My Ji Soo was showing off
about her boyfriend so much.
I was curious about who he is.
You're handsome just like she said,
and very polite.
You're too kind, Mother.
Oh my, my. You're humble too.
Thank you, Mother.
One moment.
No problem at all.
Hello? Oh, really?
Okay, I'll be there soon.
Oh, what am I to do?
I have an urgent matter.
I think I have to go.
- I'm sorry.
- I understand, Mother.
Travel safely, Mother.
- I'll see you again.
- Okay.
I am Lee Joon Ki!
I must've been nervous.
My legs were really tense.
How was I?
I think my mom really liked you.
Really?
Oh, good job, Lee Joon Ki.
- Why isn't she coming?
- Is someone else coming?
My younger sister finished work early,
so she said she'd come.
I'd better get prepared then.
- Sorry, Ji Soo.
- It's okay.
Joon Ki, say hello.
This is my younger sister, Ji Min.
My name is Lee Joon Ki.
Hello.
I'm the waxer who will
be waxing you today.
Why?
What is it?
Do you two know one another?
Well, actually...
What is it? Why can't you two speak?
You two didn't date in the past
or something, did you?
- No, no, no.
- Oh no.
Oh no. Not at all.
Then what is it? What is it, Ji Min?
You tell me.
Actually, your boyfriend
came to our store as a customer.
Joon Ki did?
Joon Ki, you got a waxing?
Well, it was... it was for a role.
- Work, work!
- Oh, is that all?
As long as it wasn't you who did it.
What?
Don't tell me.
You did his waxing yourself?
Say no.
There were no male employees at the time.
Ji Soo, don't think much of it.
It's just work.
- Work.
Work, work, work.
Ji Soo, Ji Soo.
Wait. Ji Soo, Ji Soo!
Wait, wait!
Ji Soo, I'm sorry.
I never dreamed that
she was your little sister.
I had to do it for this film.
I haven't even held your hand yet.
- My sister has seen everything.
- Everything?
Well, that's just...
It was all just for work, okay?
Okay, but I don't feel good about it.
I'm going to go home today.
Ji Soo, wait. Ji Soo...
Ji Soo!
I'm going crazy here.
Why did she have to be
Ji Soo's younger sister? Why?
My gosh!
- Are preparations going well?
- Yes.
You haven't shot anything in a while.
Have you lost your touch?
It's me. Kang Dong Gu.
You know I'm skilled.
You should be making films.
Why are you doing this?
Have you given up on films too?
No, I'm going back soon.
I just need some money to do so.
Yeah, don't give up like me.
Go all the way.
- All right?
- Okay. Thanks.
Min Seo, stop crying.
It's almost time for the party.
Excuse me.
Are you just going to take pictures
when the baby's crying?
Pardon? What about his crying?
Other people make the baby laugh
when he cries.
- Make him laugh!
- What?
You want me to make him laugh?
I'm not a comedian.
Oh, I'm so sorry. So sorry.
It's his first day on the job.
I'm sorry.
One moment.
Hey, what are you doing?
What do you expect me to do
about a crying baby?
You have to be better at making
kids laugh than shooting the camera.
Watch me.
Hey, Min Seo. Look at Uncle here.
The baby is so cute.
Did you see that?
That's how you do it.
You try it.
You want me to do that?
Hey, you think making money's easy?
You can quit if you don't want to do it.
Oh no. I'll do it.
Do it properly.
Do a good job.
Seo Jin, can you lend me your laptop?
What for?
I need to register
for something on the internet.
Register for what?
Oh, I'm going to go on
"Show Me the Money."
What? "Show Me the Money"?
I want to have my skills
evaluated by the pros.
Yoon Ah, isn't that a rash decision?
I know that my rap skills
aren't at a pro level yet.
However, I think I can overcome it.
The thing is, Yoon Ah...
I didn't say anything to keep
your feelings from being hurt.
You really suck.
What do you mean?
It's total chaos, to put it simply.
Is my rap that bad?
Honestly, most people can rap
about as well as you.
I can do it too. You want to see?
Insomnia, lethargy,
the form of a zombie playing.
Pour some water on it and
the heavy armor of reality comes off.
Like flickers of fire that fall on feet,
it is beautiful.
You see? You can see I'm better, right?
I see...
That's how it was.
Why didn't you say anything?
Yoon Ah, I'm sorry.
- I was worried you'd get hurt.
- It's fine.
I'm okay.
Don't worry about it.
Was I too harsh?
I shouldn't have gotten her excited.
This is driving me crazy.
Whatever, whatever.
Gosh, the noodles are soggy.
- I'm so hungry.
- You're home?
What's with you? Did something happen?
Don't ask.
- Did you just make this?
- Yes.
Give me one bite.
No, make your own if you want one.
Didn't you eat with your
girlfriend's mom?
Something happened and I couldn't eat.
Just give me a bite.
No way. Make your own.
So petty. Give me one bite.
You're going to grab it?
Why are you so strong?
Do you lift weights?
It's mine. I made it.
Gosh. Forget it!
What a waste to spill it all.
Ow, ow, ow!
Seo Jin, you!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Doctor, my life as a man is over.
Doctor, Doctor! What do I do?
Lee Joon Ki is over!
Kang Seo Jin!
Seriously, Kang Seo Jin!
Doctor, what are you doing?
Do something for him.
I'm sorry. Page the doctor once more.
She's coming down now.
What is it?
Why are you paging someone
just out of surgery?
The intern doctor was too embarrassed
to see the patient.
Hey, you still call yourself a doctor?
You'd better see me later.
What kind of patient is it?
Oh, Joon Ki?
Who is it?
It's me, Ji Soo's mom.
Oh, Mom.
Please do something... oh my!
Mother.
Mother, why are you here?
I'm a doctor here.
What happened to you?
He spilled hot ramen.
Oh no.
Let me take a look.
Wait. Mother.
No, no. I'm fine now.
I really am okay.
I will head back home now.
You're not okay.
Where will you go in this state?
No, I really am okay, Mother.
Joon Ki, I am a doctor
before I'm Ji Soo's mom.
- Nurse Kim, hold the patient down.
- Yes.
Why are you holding me down? Where?
Ow! Why, why, why?
- Just stay still.
- No, no!
Mother, Mother, Mother!
No, no, no!
- I'll take a look.
- No!
No! Don't do it! Stop!
Wait. What is this?
Sorry.
No wonder.
A burn this bad usually wouldn't
occur from spilled ramen.
That was why.
Yes.
Treatment went well.
You can go home.
Thank you, Mother.
Joon Ki.
Oh... Ji Soo.
Oh, uh... you're here?
I have to go now. Goodbye.
I'll be outside too.
Ji... Ji Soo.
Joon Ki, why are you doing this to me?
You got a waxing from my sister
and now my mom...
Were you going to expose yourself
to my whole family?
How can I look at
my sister and mom again?
- Ji Soo, it's not like that.
- Forget it.
I don't want to hear it.
Let's break up.
What? Break up?
- What do you mean?
- I'm sorry.
I don't think I can bear it.
Be well, Joon Ki.
Wait, Ji...
Ji Soo, Ji Soo.
Ji Soo, Ji Soo!
Breathe.
Ji Soo! Listen to me.
Ji Soo! Ji Soo!
Three bears lived in a house.
Daddy bear, mommy bear, and baby bear.
What are you doing?
He's crying even more.
Is there anything else?
Something else? I'll try again.
Our baby, Min Seo.
Thank you so much
for coming into our lives.
Happy birthday.
We love you forever.
So, you did that
until your head was bleeding?
Ow.
It was the only way to make him laugh.
What could I do?
It's really hard to make a living.
It's really hard.
Ji Soo. Please listen to me, Ji Soo.
Don't hang up. Don't hang up, Ji Soo.
I didn't do it on purpose.
Just listen to me, Ji Soo. Ji Soo!
She really wants to break up?
Yes.
Why did you bother waxing?
A minor actor like me
has to do what I'm told.
What can I do?
You'll meet someone good.
Stay strong.
Breaking up with Ji Soo is one thing.
I wonder if I'll end up
playing minor roles forever.
I feel weak thinking about it.
Why would you say something like that?
The actor Hwang Jung Min was an
unknown actor for 10 years.
Kwak Do Won was unknown for 20 years.
So, you're saying I should be
unknown for 20 years?
I'm saying if you work hard,
you can be like them too.
You are a pretty decent actor, after all.
I can act pretty well.
People do know that.
Yeah.
Let's keep our hopes up.
Then we'll have a day when the sun
shines bright for us too.
Yes, of course.
In order to stay strong,
let's eat first.
I'm so hungry.
What's with you?
When aren't you hungry?
Tell me. Tell me now.
Oh, muffins!
You can just have these for dinner.
I don't feel like grocery shopping,
so I just made these.
Yoon Ah, are you still angry?
No, I'm not angry.
I'm in a great mood. I feel like flying.
Okay, so you're not angry.
You're not angry.
Oh, you made these?
Why? Can you bake as well as I can?
Ah, everyone in the world
can bake as well as I can.
No, it's really delicious.
Guys, try it. Try it.
Shall we?
Wow.
It's really good.
Yoon Ah, you made these yourself?
These are better than
muffins from the bakery.
- Oh, yeah.
- Really?
They are.
Yoon Ah, why don't you become
patisseur instead a rapper?
A patisseur?
To tell you the truth,
becoming a patisseur is my second dream.
Really? Then become a patisseur.
Should I?
But, I still like
rapping a little more...
- Yoon Ah.
- All right.
I was joking.
- Is it really good?
- Yeah.
- Patisseur, patisseur.
- It's very good.
- Really?
- You have a specialty, Yoon Ah.
Is it good?
Good, good. Very real.
Oh, yeah. I like it. Very good.
See, you got a clean wax.
You look so real and good.
Thank you. I will do my best.
What's that? You did your armpits too?
Good job.
It worked.
What a shock.
Hey, did you really?
- You even shaved you head?
- Yes, Director.
I don't need hair if you want to
make the film look real.
Very good. It's great.
This is how an actor should be!
Director, Soo Hyun is here.
- Oh yeah?
- Yes.
It's cold, so cold.
Let's film it quickly.
Soo Hyun, you didn't get a waxing?
You know I get cold easily.
I'd get cold without
body hair and get sick.
Still, this is about a swimmer.
You just don't look real.
Hey, I'm playing the role of a swimmer.
I'm not an actual swimmer.
If you insist upon it,
cast someone else.
No, no, no.
What's so important about accuracy?
Let's just go with it.
Why do these people look so smooth?
I stick out too much.
I'll get insulted for it later.
I can't film like this.
Oh, you're right.
What should we do?
We'll start the cheering scene.
Lots of emotion!
Make it real, okay?
Yes!
Ready... action!
Woo! You can do it!
Go get it! Good luck!
Korea!
Korea...
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
Big news. Big news.
I have been cast in something.
Guess who's in it?
It's Kim Hee Ja!
I hate kids who act up because they
have someone backing them.
This is just a rehearsal.
What? Rehearsal?
I told her not to go too far.
How can you do that
at someone's birthday event?
What if they see you?
Hey, there.
I'm going crazy.
I passed. I passed.
The interview is a bit unique.
Do you have boyfriends?
I like glamorous style.
If you like drinking so much,
drink with your little sister.
Are you crazy?
Let go of me while I'm still using words.
Yoon Ah got chosen
as soon as she arrived.
What happened with Sol's dad?
What an incredibly dramatic life.
Should we find Sol's dad?
I'm here to see Han Yoon Ah.
What are you doing here?