Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
The products we are
selling today live on TV
are very trendy pants
in the country these days.
Auto hip-up, set of three pants.
Take a look.
Isn't the design so stylish?
Let's take a look at the back.
What do you think?
Your hips just seem to
lift up to the sky, don't they?
That is the strength of
this auto hip-up design.
There's the fabric too.
Ow!
It's the very best quality.
You can exercise or walk in them
and they will be comfortable.
You don't believe me?
Then we'll test it for you.
Take a look.
Even though they stretch like this,
it isn't uncomfortable at all.
You still don't believe me?
One, two, three.
Oh no!
Um...
Geez.
Uh, today's product comes in
blue, black, and sky blue.
It's a set of three.
[Good Work Today]
God and Buddha.
Please let me get
an interview at one place.
I'll go to church and temple.
Help me, merciful Buddha.
Amen.
Seo Jin, what are you doing?
Praying. I just applied for jobs.
I applied to 25 places.
I hope things work out for you.
Oh, it's that actor.
He's really good at acting.
What was his name again?
Lee...
Who? Mister Duk Hwa?
Mister Duk Hwa?
Do you actually know him?
That's Joon Ki's father.
What? Joon Ki's father?
That's really amazing.
I'm going to ask Joon Ki
for his father's autograph.
No, you can't.
Joon Ki doesn't like
to talk about his father.
- Why?
- The thing is...
- Mister Duk Hwa--
- I understand. Yes.
What is this? What's this mood here?
Is this because of me?
You were insulting me again,
weren't you?
What did you say,
you hairy woman?
It wasn't like that.
Tell me now if you
don't want to get into trouble.
Big news, big news!
Why are you making such a fuss?
- You're a total star. Look.
- Huh?
What is it?
"Who is the man on
the home shopping channel?"
Who am I?
What is that?
What are all of those?
Awesome.
What the heck are those?
What's that?
What is that! What?
Your face is all over the internet.
You even have a nickname.
Guess what it is.
Pink Boy. Hey, Pink Boy.
What boy?
- I should make one too.
- Close it.
They sure did great job Photoshopping.
Yes, hello.
Yes, yes... stop it.
Yes, that's me. Excuse me?
Yes, okay. Yes.
What was that call about?
It's a film production company.
They want to cast me.
They were impressed by me.
What? By you?
Where did they see you?
- Home shopping.
- Home shopping?
Don't tell me it was
the Pink Boy. No way.
Stop calling me that.
[My Mom]
Here.
It's the script and shooting schedule.
You're casting me without an audition?
Does it seem like I'm a fraud?
No, that's not what I meant.
What kind of role is it?
The film is about a mom
whose daughter is kidnapped.
She gets revenge on the kidnappers.
You'll be one of the kidnappers.
Then will I have lines,
by any chance?
Not many, but you have some.
You have a scene with the main character.
Who is playing the main character?
The main character?
Kim Hee Ja.
Kim Hee Ja!
Kim Hee Ja from "Desert"?
The nation's greatest actor, Kim Hee Ja?
Yes, that's right.
So you have to practice hard
on your acting, okay?
Yes, I'll work very hard.
Thank you!
How is it? Is it good?
Uh, yes.
It is good.
But when will we eat rice, Yoon Ah?
We've only been eating bread
for days, so I feel a little--
Just eat.
What if she suddenly gets mad again?
All right. I'll eat.
There's plenty. Take your time eating.
You guys! You guys!
Big news, big news, big news!
I got a role in a movie!
Guess who's starring in it.
The nation's greatest actor.
It's Kim Hee Ja, Kim Hee Ja!
Kim Hee Ja, for real?
What's your role this time?
I get murdered by Kim Hee Ja.
I knew it. It's another minor role.
I have lines this time though.
Regardless, that's good news.
Shouldn't we have a party to celebrate?
We should have a nice stew and rice.
Sorry, but I need to go over the script
and I don't have time.
Let's party next time.
- Kim Hee Ja!
- Joon Ki, I want rice.
He's so excited, isn't he?
Doo Shik, you dropped it.
Have a new one.
Thank you.
Hello!
You scared me.
I died because of you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you practice a lot?
I didn't sleep for a week
and I practiced a lot.
Wow.
Where is Senior Kim Hee Ja anyway?
She'll be here soon.
There she is.
Senior Kim Hee Ja.
Senior, hello.
Why is she like that?
She's immersed into her role.
The sadness of a mother
whose daughter has been kidnapped.
So, she doesn't eat, sleep, or
go home during the whole shoot.
She says it breaks
the emotion of her character.
Anyway, it's amazing.
Hit him and strangle him.
Wow.
She truly does seem like
one of our nation's greatest.
This is the scene when the mom has
found one of the co-conspirators.
We'll show the anger of the mother
when she finally confronts him.
Also, the terror you feel
when you see her.
The angry mom will fight
with the kidnapper.
She is so overcome with anger
that she ends up murdering him.
Understand?
Okay. We'll rehearse it first.
Yes, Director.
Rehearsal, cue!
Who is it?
I said who is it? Who is it that...
How did you find me?
Where's my daughter?
Where's my daughter, Soo Jin?
Tell me, you bastard!
Oh, this is just a rehearsal.
What? Rehearsal?
Tell me! Where is Soo Jin?
Tell me!
Wait... hold on.
My daughter!
Hee Ja, stop! That's enough!
Joon Ki, wake up!
Wake up, wake up!
Are you okay?
A white tunnel and a black shadow.
Gosh, I thought something happened.
Sorry, Director.
I was so in character.
Are you all right, Joon Ki?
Here.
Oh, I'm all right.
Director, I'm going to go calm myself.
My heart is racing.
Seriously, I told her to take it easy.
What if someone has to
go to the hospital again?
The hospital?
The person who had the role before you
ended up in the hospital.
He was beaten by Hee Ja
and was there for four weeks.
- What?
- So, be smart about how you get hit.
Got it?
Yes... okay.
Joon Ki, are you ready?
Yes, yes... yes.
Ready, action!
Wait.
How did you find me?
Where's my daughter?
Where is Soo Jin? Where?
Tell me!
Blood.
Wait, wait! That's metal... metal.
Where is she?
Cut.
Stop, stop, stop.
No, no, no.
- No, no!
- That's enough. Stop.
Wow.
Dong Gu, you filmed this?
Yes.
Wow, they made it so pretty.
Oh, look at the cute baby.
How cute.
Cute, yeah right.
After I started this job,
I believed in good and evil.
People are definitely born evil.
Hey, is that something
you should say about a baby?
You just haven't seen
kids crying their heads off.
When the baby starts crying,
the mom tells me to make him laugh.
I'm not a comedian.
How can I do that?
It's not so hard at all.
Then is it easy?
It is easy. Want to see?
Ah buru, buru, buru, buru, hwon!
(Gibberish)
Hwon.
What? She laughed right away.
What... what did you just say?
- Ah bu, what?
- Ah burubu hwon?
Ah burubu...
- Pong?
- Pong, pong.
Not, pong. It's hwon.
- Phong?
- No.
Do, re, mi, fa, so...
Use the "so" tone to say,
hwon, hwon.
Ah, hwon?
What else? Do you have more?
Something else? Hm.
Take Sol for me.
- Come on, Sol.
- Here you go.
Oh, Mommy's gone.
Where did Mommy go?
Here she is!
Awesome, awesome.
Wow, awesome.
"Where did Mommy go?
Here she is."
You have to raise your tone
for this a little more.
- At a C tone.
- C tone.
- Here she is.
- That's it.
- Here she is. C tone.
I'm home.
You're home...
Why do you look like that?
It's from the shoot.
I got injured.
What kind of shoot was it
that you got this injured?
Senior Kim Hee Ja really gets
immersed into her roles.
Even if she gets immersed into her roles,
she can't beat people like this.
She could end up killing a person.
It's all right.
It was during acting.
I'm fine. I'm...
Joon Ki, Joon Ki?
Is he asleep right now?
Is he breathing?
Goodness,
what a tumultuous life he lives.
He really does.
A white tunnel and a black shadow.
Is he talking in his sleep?
What's he saying?
- Are you okay?
- No, don't!
Save me. Please save me.
We'll continue shooting
yesterday's scene today.
After killing the kidnapper,
the mom is sobbing like crazy.
Joon Ki, you're dead,
so you cannot move. You got it?
- Yes.
- Shall we start then?
Ready, action!
Where's my daughter?
Where's my Soo Jin?
Where's my daughter, Soo Jin?
Tell me.
- Tell me!
- I can't.
Where is she, huh?
Where is my daughter?
You bastard.
Where is she? Tell me.
Where is she?
Cut! Okay, that was good.
Oh my.
Hee Ja, that was great acting.
I got goosebumps everywhere
while watching you.
Joon Ki, you were good too.
I was nervous we'd have to cut.
Wow, you were able to
hold on through that.
Thank you.
I'll be going to the bathroom now.
What do you think about him?
Better than expected, right?
I suppose so.
He's a good actor and
I like a junior who can act.
Where did you find someone like that?
Oh, him?
The thing is...
Oh, I thought I was going to die.
Why did it have to go in my mouth?
Joon Ki, he said you did well!
The world is finally recognizing
my acting talent.
Hello.
Thank you.
Why is he acting up today?
He hasn't been well since morning.
Ma'am, I'll take some pictures of
Jang Goon before we start.
Jang Goon isn't feeling so well now.
What can we do about that?
About that, Mister...
You want me to make him laugh?
How did you know?
When people look at me like that,
they all say the same thing.
I'll give it a try.
Do, re, mi, fa, so...
Ah buru, buru, buru, hwon.
What are you doing?
He's crying even more.
It's okay. I have one more.
Jang Goon, Uncle is gone.
Where did Uncle go?
Here he is!
What are you doing?
He's going to throw a fit.
Jang Goon, it's okay. It's all right.
That's weird.
It worked well for Yoon Ah.
What should I do?
Ah buru, buru, buru, buru, hwon.
Where did Auntie go?
Here I am.
Oh my.
He's laughing just fine.
You told me to come out
right away for this?
That's strange.
He cried when I did it.
You're very good with babies.
I feel at ease now.
- Ouch. My stomach hurts.
- It hurts again?
This won't do.
Let's go to the hospital.
What about Jang Goon?
Your mother will be here soon.
I'll watch the baby.
You should go.
Could you do that for me?
I'm sorry, but can you get him
changed into these clothes too?
Sure.
Don't worry. I'll watch over him.
Thank you for your help.
Go on.
What a strange kid.
I did the same thing.
What's the difference?
Babies apparently know the
difference between good and bad people.
So, are you saying I'm a bad person?
Not necessarily.
I'll be in the restroom,
so keep an eye on him.
Oh, this is so pretty.
I wonder how much all of this costs.
Oh yeah.
I have to change his clothes.
Here we go.
Oh my gosh. It's so cute.
It would look so cute
on my Sol too. Right, Sol?
Look, look.
What did I say about liking the work?
Director, thanks for everything.
Yes, good job. Good job.
Okay, we finished the shoot well.
Let's all go out for pork belly and soju!
Sounds good!
Come with us.
Will you be going too, Senior?
Why I am your senior?
I'm tired, so I'll head in first.
What's wrong?
- Did I offend her somehow?
- No.
Hee Ja, Hee Ja!
How can you leave like this?
I'm not in the mood to go out.
Because of what I said earlier?
I really hate kids who act up
because they have people who back them.
You know very well, Hee Ja.
Duk Hwa helped me a lot
through my hard times.
He asked me to cast his son.
How could I say no?
What are you talking about?
Joon Ki, it's not that.
What did you just say?
My daughter, look over here.
Oh, don't you look so pretty.
Look this way.
That's right. Look over here.
- What are you doing?
- You scared me!
Why are you so startled?
Why are you taking photos
of a stranger's baby?
I thought it was Sol from afar.
It's Sol.
What's going on here, Yoon Ah?
- Well, actually--
- Wait.
What if the parents come?
I'm sorry. Actually, I just--
It doesn't matter.
Just change her clothes.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
Jang Goon!
Come here.
Oh, my Jang Goon.
My baby, Jang Goon.
It's been a long time.
Your grandma has been living in the US.
I haven't seen you since you were born.
We finally meet again.
- Oh my.
- He is so handsome.
Why has he lost so much weight though?
He had chubby cheeks in the pictures,
but he's lost the weight.
I doubt that.
And you are?
Oh, I'm here to photograph
and film the event.
- Oh.
- Grandma, you must be tired.
- We'll hold on to him.
- I'm just fine.
It's been ages since
I've held my Jang Goon.
In our Gyeongju Lee clan
he is the only son
out of eight generations.
Just to have a son...
his parents had to go to fertility
clinics and go through so much.
I have to interview you, Grandma.
You need to say something
to your grandson.
- Give Jang Goon to us.
- All right.
I'll hold him and do it.
It looks nicer to hold him
during the interview.
Oh, you can't do that.
How crazy is this?
Oh, did you poop, Jang Goon?
Wait just a moment.
Grandma will change
your diaper, Jang Goon.
No, no. We'll do that.
Babies these days have
very toxic poo smells.
- I'll do it.
- Oh no.
I'm going to change it.
Let me take a look at
my baby's little penis.
- Penis?
- You're going to look at his penis?
Oh my. Let's see my Jang Goon's pee pee.
Let's see here.
Get that off.
What do you think you're doing?
Even if he is a baby,
shouldn't you protect his privacy?
Privacy for a baby? Nonsense.
Oh? What's with you?
Grandma, he may be young,
but please respect Jang Goon's rights.
This is a violation of rights.
Violation of rights? What in the world...
Why, you little punk.
Are you playing around here or what?
It's because I have a trauma.
My grandma always said,
"Let's eat that penis."
To this day,
I still can't eat peppers.
What kind of nonsense is that?
- You can't.
- Hey.
Move your hand.
You're not going to move it?
Move it. Move, move!
No! No, I can't.
Look at this punk.
Hey!
You little rascal.
No. You can't, Grandma.
You should've moved when I told you to.
No. You have to stop, Grandma!
All right. Let me take a look...
What...
What is this?
My Jang Goon...
His pe...pe... penis.
Oh no! Grandma.
- What do we do?
- Sol!
What brings you by
without even a call?
Why did you do it?
Why did you do it again?
What are you talking about
out of the blue?
I heard everything from Director Kim.
I told you not to do that anymore.
I'm trying my best on my own.
- Why do you keep doing it?
- Then...
you should do well on your own.
Yeah, I enjoyed watching you
on home shopping a few days ago.
Gosh, it was so embarrassing.
Yes, I asked for a favor.
I don't like to see
my only child suffering.
What's so wrong about that?
I can't be proud about it.
Why not?
Because I'm your son.
I'm the son of the person I respect most,
actor Lee Duk Hwa.
So, I need to do this more honorably.
I want to succeed on my own
without your help.
That way, I can feel
truly proud around you.
So, just trust me, Father.
Watch over me.
That's all I want from you.
I understand what you mean...
All right, fine.
Go on home shopping.
Or play minor roles forever.
Do whatever you want.
Gosh, kid.
Also, you...
What's with the pink underwear? Pink?
You're a man.
It's sexy.
My goodness.
All right. Let's go inside.
Come in and have dinner before going.
No, Father.
I have to do something, so I have to go.
Hey, kid. Hey!
All right.
I sure did raise him well.
I'm sorry for everything.
Joon Ki, it's not like you knew.
Whether I knew or not,
it's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for the meal.
I'll get going, Sir.
Joon Ki, Joon Ki!
Gosh, that kid.
Yes, Tae Shik.
How about the grandma?
Really? That's a relief.
I'm sorry about today.
I'll take responsibility for all of it.
I'm really sorry. Yeah.
What happened? Was it resolved?
Yeah, somewhat.
What were you thinking when you did that?
I'm sorry.
Sorry or not, how could you do that
at someone's 100 day baby event?
I did it because I was sorry.
I was sorry to Sol.
My Sol was born to
a mom who is so lacking.
She never got to celebrate her birth.
She never got pretty clothes
or nice toys.
So, I just wanted a picture
of a 100 day celebration.
I'm very sorry.
The product we have for you today
is a bright, bright smile corrector.
Wear it only three minutes per day.
And it will give you
a naturally beautiful smile.
How does it feel to wear it?
It feels like my smile
is coming into place.
You feel your smile
coming into place naturally?
Could you tell us in detail how
your smile is coming into place?
- In detail?
- Yes, in detail.
Very detailed.
How can I put it?
Usually, my lips turn down.
Wearing this makes my mouth turn up.
So, my smile feels more natural.
What the heck is this?
It was hard enough as it is.
Why do they make me talk?
Gosh, my mouth hurts.
Wait, is this going to be captured too?
Is this all over the internet?
Darn it!
Who is it now?
Hello?
Yes, this is Lee Joon Ki.
What?
A meeting?
Excuse me.
- Leave it here.
- Okay.
No, it's not that.
My name is Lee Joon Ki
and I received a call.
Ah, welcome.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes, you too.
Why did you ask to see me, Director?
Oh, I'm starting a morning drama soon.
Someone recommended you to me.
Recommended me?
Who?
Who recommended me?
I did.
Oh, she's here.
Senior!
- Hello.
- Nice to see you.
Hello, Senior.
But, why would you recommend me?
Director Choi was looking for a new
actor who is handsome and can act.
Your looks aren't that great,
but you can act.
That's why I recommended you.
- Why? You don't like it?
- Not at all.
Thank you, Senior!
Use your skills to get the role.
- Work hard.
- Okay.
Hee Ja, take a look at
this script for my drama.
Thank you, Senior!
I'll call you.
Yoon Ah... come out for a bit.
Why? What is it?
- Ta-da!
- Ta-da.
Ta-da.
[Happy 100 Days, Sol!]
[Sol, congrats on 100 days!]
What is this?
What else? Come over here.
This is Sol's 100 day party.
We didn't do much,
but we made it ourselves.
Please understand
even if you don't love everything.
That's not it.
Everything's so pretty.
Thank you, everyone.
It was nothing.
You should thank Dong Gu, not us.
It was all his idea.
No need to mention that.
Really? Thank you, Dong Gu.
I was just worried
that you'd cause trouble again.
And stop crying over nothing, would you?
Crying like that is a bad habit.
I'm sorry.
It's just so pretty.
But there's no cake.
It would've been perfect with cake.
The cake has arrived!
Of course, we prepared cake.
Did you think we'd have
a party without cake?
- Thank you.
- There she goes again. Look, look...
Seo Jin, light the candles
before it's a sea of tears.
Okay.
You bought champagne too?
Oh, you have great sense.
Hey, this is to congratulate myself.
For what?
I got cast in a morning drama.
It's a regular character, at that!
Wow.
Regular? Really?
This time I'm the driver
for the main character.
I knew it.
You're a minor role again.
Okay, let's talk later.
Take the picture for now.
Let's go. Let's go.
Yoon Ah, over here.
Everyone, get together.
Let's take a picture, Sol.
Okay, get into your places.
Dong Gu, hurry it up.
- Smile, would you?
- Okay.
This will go off in 10 seconds,
so get ready and pose.
Did you light it? Kimchi!
All right, now.
Kimchi!
Wait.
Now that I think about it,
there's no 100 day ring.
It really would've been perfect
if we had a ring for Sol.
- Yoon Ah.
- Seo Jin, go buy a ring.
Why did you bother buying these?
Get rid of these.
Get rid of the table.
- Get rid of it all.
- Okay, okay.
- Buy the ring.
- No, no.
Okay, let's get started.
I'll make a left turn.
Oh, I'll make a right turn.
Yes, I'll reverse.
There's this version.
I'll make a left turn.
Oh, I'll make a right turn.
Yes, I'll reverse.
There's this version too.
Which one is better?
Be brutally honest.
What's different?
They seem the same.
What?
The first driver was one that
worked diligently no matter what.
He was someone who wanted to
make something of himself.
The second one was tired and annoyed,
but going along with his boss.
He was a driver who was
just doing his job carelessly.
Ah, was that it?
You want to be a director.
Yet, you can't tell the difference.
What will you do?
Sorry.
Gosh, this is my first regular drama.
This is a big issue.
I know.
Should I find a driver
and ask about the job?
You only have three lines.
Why bother doing that?
You're going overboard.
Just let him do what he wants.
Do you know anything about acting?
Oh, what's that, Yoon Ah?
Someone threw out a perfectly
fine toaster oven on the street.
I brought it here.
Toaster oven? Why do you need that?
You said that I could probably
sell the bread I make.
So, I want to try selling it.
Sales? Then what about
working at the guest house?
I'll do my work here
and do it on my time off.
Do what you want, then.
But it can't get in the way of
your work, okay?
Don't worry. It won't.
Goodness.
Oh no!
Sorry.
[That Man, That Woman's Story]
[Daeyoung Daily: You have a new message]
- Dae... Dae... Dae...
- Open it.
Geez.
- Joon Ki.
- Yeah?
I'm just too nervous.
Can you look for me?
Okay.
What happened?
Oh, what are you going to do?
Seo Jin.
The interview...
They want you to come.
You passed!
Really? Is it for real?
Yes, take a look.
[Congratulations on passing...]
It says I passed!
You still have to do the interview.
Don't get so emotional yet.
I don't care.
I just really want to work here.
Congratulations.
You can work there then.
Stop crying. You look ugly.
I smell something burning.
I think it's from the kitchen.
What is this?
What is this? What's all this smoke?
What's this smoke?
- What is this?
- There's smoke!
Oh no! My bread in the oven's burning.
- Then turn it off now!
- What?
What's wrong with this?
I can't turn it off.
This thing.
You can just unplug it.
You could've caused a big problem.
I think the timer broke.
Why would they throw out a broken thing?
They threw it out because it is broken.
- Ah...
- What do you mean "ah"?
You almost started a fire!
Why do you like these things?
Seo Jin got an interview.
Let's go have a celebratory drink.
Seo Jin, let's go.
That's enough now.
- Seo Jin got an interview.
- Let's go.
Yoon Ah, we should go too.
No, I'm going to clean up here first.
Oh, really?
Then clean up and come up.
Okay, then I'll get started.
Spin it, man. Hurry up and spin it!
Whoa!
Joon Ki, Joon Ki!
It's me. Okay, okay.
Ask me anything.
I'll answer whatever you ask.
Who wants to go first?
- Me.
- Oh! Me, me, me, me!
- I want ask.
- Go ahead.
When, who,
and how was your first kiss?
Was my first kiss in grade nine?
No, it was in grade two.
It was on the playground
with an older neighbor of mine.
I was coming down the elephant slide.
It was so hot.
Wow, Shi Yeon's lips were so hot.
- Enough, enough.
- All right.
I don't want to hear anymore.
What happened next? What next?
You asked me first. Be quiet.
It was Shi Yeon.
I cut some fruit. Have some.
Did you clean the kitchen?
Yes, I did.
All the smoke is gone,
as well as the smell?
Stop harassing her.
Yoon Ah, sit down.
- It's okay.
- Sit down. We're playing the truth game.
Play with us.
You can't refuse us.
Then should I?
Okay, I'm going to spin it again.
Go, go, go, go!
Yeah, Yoon Ah got chosen
as soon as she joined us.
What should we ask Yoon Ah?
Me, me, me, me, me!
- I want to do it.
- Is she a vending machine?
I have a question
I really want to ask Yoon Ah.
Really? What is it?
Well, it's actually...
What happened with Sol's dad?
Why would you ask something like that
and make her uncomfortable?
Why not? You're all curious.
You're all just unable to ask, right?
It's okay. It's not a secret or anything.
Where should I start?
To be honest...
That's what happened.
So, your parents died in a fire
when you were two years old.
And you stayed with relatives.
Those relatives just took the insurance
money and left you in an orphanage?
Then you were abused by the
director of the orphanage.
You ran away, worked part-time,
and met Sol's dad?
You broke up because Sol's dad's
family didn't approve of you.
You then found out you were
pregnant after you broke up?
Hold on.
Then Sol's dad knew you were pregnant
and turned his back on you?
No, he doesn't know that Sol exists.
Why not?
Huh?
Well...
Sol must be awake.
I'm going downstairs.
I feel so bad for Yoon Ah.
It must've been so hard for her
all this time.
You! Be good to Yoon Ah
and stop lecturing her.
When did I do that?
You were about to eat her alive
about the fire thing just now.
I was just... cautioning her.
You're cautioned.
We're going to drink to ourselves.
Cheers!
Guys! Ta-da.
How do I look?
Wow. Awesome!
It totally doesn't suit you.
It's hard for that outfit
not to suit you.
I'm stupid for asking you guys.
We're just joking.
Why are you dressed up?
I have my interview today.
I'm getting nervous seeing you
acting up like this.
Don't you two worry.
Now, should I get started on my makeup?
Oh no!
What do I do? What do I do?
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
It's almost time for my interview.
What is this?
Don't cause such a scene.
Change into something else.
I can't because this jacket
and blouse are a set.
Other blouses don't match.
Wash it and dry it quickly.
You still have time.
I'd better do that.
What are you doing, Yoon Ah?
You said you're selling
muffins today, right?
- Yes.
- Should we help you?
No, I'm almost done.
I'm all done.
Oh, Sol must be awake.
Watching the baby,
doing housework, and selling muffins.
Yoon Ah is working too hard.
You're right.
Hey, is there any way
that we can help Yoon Ah?
I wish we could,
but there's nothing we can do.
We can't make her a husband.
That's not a bad idea.
Should we try looking for Sol's dad?
We don't know who he is, so how can we?
That's true. How would we find him?
Isn't this Yoon Ah's phone?
I think so.
We can look for his number.
How can we know who he is
out of all these numbers?
We can just look.
- What is this?
- What?
Her contact list is only us,
a Chinese food place, and Kim Joon Sung.
Kim Joon Sung must be Sol's dad.
Does that make sense?
Then is the
Great Wall of China Sol's dad?
No, I'm saying how do we know
this is Sol's dad?
That's true.
I can call him.
- Call him.
- You're crazy.
What will you do once you call?
Let go. I'm just going to try.
You're causing trouble again. Geez.
Hello.
Hello, is this
Kim Joon Sung's cell phone?
- Yes, it is.
- Stop it.
Do you know someone named Han Yoon Ah?
I dated her for a bit.
Who is this?
He says he dated her.
He dated her. It's him. It's him.
Oh, this is a delivery company.
Han Yoon Ah sent you a package.
What is your home address?
It rained and the address got erased.
I can't see a thing.
It's so sunny out.
Yes, yes. One moment.
35 Dongsangri.
Yes, I'll send the package.
It's him. It's Sol's dad.
We have his address.
Should we look for him?
This doesn't seem right.
You stay out of it.
I'll go alone. You have no loyalty.
All right, I'll go. I'll go with you.
Where are you two going now?
- You don't need to know!
- What?
- Loyalty!
- What's with them?
What kind of trouble are they up to now?
- Are you going out?
- To sell my muffins.
You're really doing that?
Sales are not for everyone.
I still want to try.
Wait, wait.
You want me to carry that?
No, I can do it alone. I'll be going.
I think it'll be hard alone.
Goodness, why do that with a baby in tow?
Whatever, don't worry about it.
Buy some muffins!
They're handmade muffins!
Muffins...
Buy some muffins!
They're handmade muffins.
Hello. These are handmade muffins.
Welcome.
Dong Gu? What are you doing here?
I saw you while passing by.
How are sales going?
I can see by your face
that it's not going well.
What is this?
Baby is suffering
and the mom is suffering too.
Not just anyone can do sales.
Also, any bakery you go to sells muffins.
Who would buy them off the streets?
You have no competitive edge.
Also, these signs are so hectic.
"Mix-in Muffin"... the names are so bad.
Why did you name them this way?
I told you...
Oh, Yoon Ah.
Are you... are you crying?
I'm already upset
that no one is buying them.
I'm so sad now with you
saying these things to me.
Well, still now.
Why would a grown adult cry?
I'm sorry.
Gosh, now.
People are staring. Stop crying.
Gosh.
I'll just... I'll sell them for you.
I'll help you, okay?
- Really?
- Yes, so stop crying.
Okay? Stop.
I'll stop.
I think this is the place.
Joon Ki, I don't think this is right.
Let's turn back now, huh?
You can go back.
You have no loyalty.
You really won't do.
The boss.
Be careful, be careful.
- There's the boss.
- Wait.
Geez.
Excuse me.
- Yes.
- Is this Kim Joon Sung's house?
- Yes, why?
- Ah...
We needed to speak to Kim Joon Sung.
Gosh, how annoying.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Someone's here to see you.
- Me?
- Yes.
Who are you?
- Kim Joon Sung.
- Yes.
Hello, I'm Lee Joon Ki.
We have something we have to tell you.
Oh, really?
- What...
- By any chance, long ago--
Honey!
How long will the construction take?
There's not much time.
It's a problem.
It'll be done before our wedding.
Don't worry.
Who are these people?
They said they had
something to speak to me about.
What is this about?
Ah, yes. It's just...
I came for part-time work.
- Part-time work?
I wasn't looking for part-time workers.
Oh, President Choi sent you.
I was yelling about the lack of
manpower yesterday.
He finally sent people.
Yes, that's right.
President Choi sent us.
You should've looked for me
if you came for part-time work.
Why would you go looking for him?
Follow me.
Ah, yes.
Why would you suddenly
bring up part-time work?
How can I bring up Yoon Ah
when his fiancée is there?
That's why I said we shouldn't come.
Let's just go.
That's a good idea. Let's go.
Where are you going?
Actually, that's not what happened.
We have a lot of work today.
What happened here is--
So, the thing is--
I--
This punk.
- Follow me.
- Doo Shik.
Mister, you have it wrong.
Mister, Mister!
- Sorry, it's my first day.
What are we doing?
How long do we have to stay?
What am I supposed to do?
He won't even listen to me.
Gosh.
You want to go?
- It won't work.
- Never mind.
Just go.
Get up.
Why isn't this drying?
What if I'm late for the interview?
Excuse me.
Is anybody here?
What now?
Is no one home?
I'm going crazy here.
What do you want?
I'm sorry, can I get an extra towel?
I'm so darn busy.
Where did everyone go anyway?
Oh no! I'm running late.
Hey, I'm busy right now.
Towels are over there.
Go find it yourself.
All righty.
Also, look after the guest house
while I'm gone, okay?
- Say what?
- Do you understand?
Yeah. I got it.
Buy some bread.
It's very good.
What are you doing?
You have to be louder.
I am trying.
Buy some bread.
It's good... it's good.
They are handmade muffins.
Yoon Ah, let's stop and go home.
I don't think anyone's buying.
No, I have to throw these all out
if I can't sell them.
You sure are stubborn.
Why do you choose to
live such a difficult life?
What do you mean by that?
I mean with Sol.
Haven't you ever thought of
telling Sol's father?
No, I've never considered that.
Isn't it hard to raise her alone?
Of course, it is.
But I don't want to hold him back
using Sol as the excuse.
Sol is my daughter
who has nothing to do with him.
So, I'm going to raise her
the best I can on my own.
That's why I started selling bread too.
Do you want to go back if you're tired?
I'm going to stay a little longer.
Go on home.
No, forget that.
I spent the day here anyway.
What's the point now?
Buy some bread. Buy some bread.
It's very good.
Buy some bread. It's delicious.
Please buy some bread.
Buy some bread.
I've tried it.
It's good. Why won't you buy it?
It's very good. Buy some bread.
What are you doing here?
What? We're selling bread.
You have a permit, right?
Of course, Dong Gu permitted it.
I permitted it. What's the problem?
[Daeyoung Daily: Closed for interviews]
Don't we have unique interviews?
Don't be nervous.
We can have a meal and drink together.
We can relax and talk.
Take your jackets off and relax.
Okay.
What happened? My blouse?
Where did my blouse go?
I must be crazy.
What should I do?
What are you doing, Kang Seo Jin?
Take your jacket off and relax.
No, thank you. I'm a little cold.
Oh, really?
Do as you please, then.
The meat is here.
I'm so sorry.
Give that to me.
I'll launder it for you.
No, I'll do it.
No, I'll do it. Give it to me.
I said... I'll do it.
I'm okay, so please just go, okay?
Hey,  hey.
Come on over.
Good job today and get home safe.
- Come back tomorrow.
- Okay.
Oh, hey. How much is this?
He may look that way,
but he pays well.
Are you happy?
You must be glad to be paid well.
Hurry up. I'm so tired.
- Don't do that.
- Okay, okay.
Hey, I think the fiancée went home.
- Should we tell him about Yoon Ah?
- Are you insane?
That Kim Joon Sung guy
is getting married soon.
What would happen if he knew
that Yoon Ah had his baby?
- Then his marriage would be called off!
- Right...
- What did you say?
- Huh?
Yoon Ah... had my baby?
Is that true?
Do you have boyfriends?
What?
No, I don't.
I don't have one yet either.
Really?
Yoon Soo Mi, you look like you'd be
popular with men, so that's unexpected.
Men like glamorous types
like you, Yoon Soo Mi.
Pardon me?
Why are you surprised?
Ah, is this sexual harassment.
So sorry. I'm just kidding.
These days, women are so scary.
You can't say anything. Goodness.
I'll be in the bathroom for a moment.
What kind of person is that, seriously?
I would just like to...
No.
Hold yourself back, Seo Jin.
You have to get a job this time.
Yoon Soo Mi, should we go to a nice place
and have a drink after the interview?
Ah, I have plans though.
What plans?
Are they more important
than passing this interview?
I guess you don't care about
failing this interview stage.
Well...
Let's just have one drink.
It doesn't mean anything.
You're just like my little sister.
Yoon Soo Mi,
don't you want to get hired?
She said she doesn't want to.
What did you just say?
You say she's like your little sister?
If you want to drink so badly,
go with your real little sister.
What?
Hey, are you crazy?
Let go... while I'm still using words.
What? What will you do then?
What? Are you going to hit me?
Then hit me.
Here, here. Hit me once.
What? You can't do it?
Hey, bluff when
the situation is suitable.
How dare a girl like you act up to me--
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
Report me if you want.
I'll sue you for sexual harassment.
Let's go.
We don't need interviews like this.
- Let me go.
- What?
What's wrong with you?
Are you going to be
held responsible if I fail too?
Why would you do something useless
and damage my chance?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you injured at all?
Are you all right? I'm sorry.
I'll do it for you.
Oh no.
Joon Ki.
Do you think we did something
we shouldn't have?
What do you mean by "we"?
Hey, you're the one who told him.
What? You're a petty bastard.
Are you putting the blame all on me?
What did I do? What?
You told him with your mouth.
It was you, you, you.
You must be crazy.
You're trash... trash!
Trash? Did you call me trash?
I call trash what it is.
What else would I call you?
Again? You fight every chance you get.
What's with you two?
Wash your face. Wash up.
You're here?
Why are you coming in together?
We met out front.
Yoon Ah, how did sales go?
- Well, actually...
- We were selling bread.
We got all the bread
seized by the regulators.
"Illegal street stall."
She even got fined
for selling food products.
Really?
It was my fault for not looking into it.
- You're hungry, right?
- Yes.
Sol's asleep, so I'll put her in bed
and get dinner started.
All right.
- How can you call me trash?
- How can you put it all on me?
- You wanted to go.
- But, you told him.
Anyone here?
Yes, come on in.
That voice.
I'm here to see Han Yoon Ah.
Oh, Yoon Ah?
Who are you?
Joon Sung?
Yoon Ah.
How did you know to come here?
We need to talk.
- Oh no.
- What's going on?
- Who is that?
- Oh, that.
Sol's dad.
What? Sol's dad?
How did he know to come here?
The thing is... we went looking for him.
- To tell him about Sol.
- What?
Why would you do that?
Are you two crazy?
Are you crazy?
I didn't do a thing and he told him.
What are you going to do now?
Are you really going to
betray me, you trash?
Trash?
I told you not to make that sound.
That's not important right now.
Hurry, hurry. Let's follow her.
Why are we following?
It's their own family issue.
- Why are we going?
- Just go.
What's going on? Why are you here?
Han Yoon Ah,
are you trying to ruin my life?
What? What do you mean?
Listen carefully.
I'm getting married soon.
So, here. Take this.
Take this and
don't contact me again, got it?
What is that?
What is this?
Is it not enough?
You wanted to use a baby to get money.
It's not enough?
You should be thankful to get this.
Honestly, how would I even know
who that baby's dad is?
What is that jerk saying?
Hey, Dong Gu. Dong Gu!
You could be playing me for money.
Isn't that right?
You suddenly show up and
I don't know what you're talking about--
- Oh!
- Ouch!
You jerk.
How can you even say that?
Do you even know how she's been living?
- That guy and his anger.
- Get money from you?
- Dong Gu, what are you doing?
- Let go.
A guy like this has
no right to be Sol's dad.
- A guy like this should just--
- Wait!
Sol's dad? What are you talking about?
He's not Sol's dad.
What? He's not Sol's dad?
Then, who is he?
Just a guy I was set up with long ago.
Then why was his phone number
saved in your phone?
I wanted to know not to answer it.
He would always drink,
call, and come looking for me.
Then why are you here?
The day we met,
I drank and blacked out.
I wondered if
something happened that day.
Oh... how embarrassing.
I'm the crazy person
for believing these two.
Seriously.
Hey.
Where do you think you're going
after punching me?
What?
You know what?
I had an interview today.
I don't I passed though.
I...
used a pork rib to slap
the interviewer across the face.
Just like this.
He was a really bad person.
But you know what?
I was told that I was wrong.
That I made a mistake.
I really thought...
that I did the right thing.
I don't know.
I just don't.
I really don't know.
I only talked about my problems.
You look like you have problems too.
Tell me. I'll listen to them.
By the way, Mister...
are you not wearing pants?
Mister?
You have to wear pants
when you go to an interview.
You're in trouble if you don't.
Stop looking forward and look at me.
Look at my blouse... my blouse.
Ow, my eye.
He has a good punch.
How embarrassing.
Gosh, I was crazy.
Those guys are so unhelpful to my life.
Geez.
Here.
- Does it hurt a lot?
- Yes.
So, why did you do that?
He was talking in such a rude manner.
Oh my.
So, you were thinking of my feelings?
Thinking... thinking of you, no.
It's not like that.
Never mind, then.
Whatever the case,
thank you, Dong Gu.
What for?
For letting me stay here.
I was very lonely before coming here.
I don't really think
those thoughts anymore.
I have people who worry about me now.
I never had a family,
so I don't really know very well.
I think to myself,
this must be what family is like.
Then just do your work properly.
There's your lecturing again.
Hey, your bruise won't go away
if you do it like that.
- Give it to me. I'll help.
- Forget it.
Give it to me. I'll do it for you.
I said forget it.
Just trust me.
- Gosh, I said no.
- Oh!
What do we do?
Seriously, I said I got it!
What kind of woman
can't do anything right?
Well... I didn't do it purpose!
Look at you.
You're yelling back now.
My gosh.
I was a little nice to you.
This won't do.
It was partially your fault too, Dong Gu.
You always just pick on me.
You think I don't have a temper?
Oh, how scary.
What did I do wrong?
Let's see that temper of yours.
What will you do?
- What will you do? Huh?
- Oh?
Oh! I'll get really mad.
- Get mad, then.
- I was holding myself back.
What will you do if you don't hold back?
You've seen me mad, right?
You'll be truly shocked.
You're the one who
will be shocked, Yoon Ah.
Why are you so strong?
Why is your head like a rock, Yoon Ah?
I'm really going to get mad!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
You scared me!
I'm going to give up on a job.
What Seo Jin needs now
is sincere consolation.
If you can get through this harsh wind,
you'll bloom into a beautiful flower.
Why are you at a police station?
Kang Seo Jin,
you didn't do anything wrong.
So, stay strong!
Joon Ki, I think I'm in love.
She totally seems interested in me.
What are you doing?
I was watching a movie.
- Let's watch together.
- No!
Why did this get sent to her?
You crazy punk!
Do you have a girlfriend?
What do you think of me?
She seems to have met another guy.
I'll find him no matter what
and kill him.
The flu?
It's all for the sake of your mom.
Because I'm worried about your mom.
Yoon Ah, did you know you're
sort of the nuisance type?
I'd like to ask Yoon Ah out on a date.
Isn't that Yoon Ah? Who is that?
Do you want to lose the business
or get married?
What? A wedding?