Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
Maybe I should start cleaning.
Dong Gu, you... you...
Is that why you ran to the store when
there was a fire... and that coat too...
So, the person you like
isn't me, but Yoon Ah?
What?
What are you talking about?
Don't try to get out of it.
Ye Rin told me.
What? She said she'd keep it a secret.
She already told you?
Dong Gu, did Ye Rin get home okay?
What?
Wow, how absurd.
Wow, this is big news.
Wow!
Su Ah, what is it? Is something going on?
Dong Gu doesn't like me.
He actually likes...
Hey, hey, hey! Get over here!
What is it?
What's with them?
I can't breathe.
Sorry, sorry.
Do you really like Yoon Ah?
Why did you act like you liked me?
I was worried that
Yoon Ah might find out.
What?
So, you used me because you
didn't want Yoon Ah to find out?
It just worked out that way.
I'm sorry.
Could you keep it
a secret for now, Su Ah?
- Why?
- Well...
I'm still very taken aback by it.
So, keep it a secret for now.
Su Ah, I'm asking you for a favor.
Please, please, please.
All right. Just stop it.
- Really?
- I said yes, so get out.
- Get going.
- Okay, I'm going.
But, Su Ah... could you give
this coat to Yoon Ah?
- I bought it for Yoon Ah.
- What?
Yoon Ah is a bit weak,
so she gets colds easily.
- And her coat is so thin.
- Okay, I'll give it to her. I will.
Thank you, Su Ah.
You're the best.
What is with him?
My pride hurts for some reason.
This is ridiculous. My gosh.
[A Secret That Cannot Be Spoken]
Who knew I'd choose to come here again?
Yes, Chairman.
Writer Bong, when are you going to
pay for Mal Geum's contract?
I'm sorry. Please wait a bit.
I'll get it somehow.
Please don't say anything to Mal Geum.
I'm asking you, please--
Hello? Chairman, Chairman?
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh.
Hey, you'll spend more on these
bandages than what you'll earn.
It will take you forever
to earn the money.
Then what do I do?
I have to do something.
Does Mal Geum know you're doing this?
She doesn't, right?
Just tell Mal Geum how you feel.
I'll tell her after I pay
for her breach of contract.
- Gosh.
- Hey, Doo Shik.
Someone's here for you.
Me? Who?
Mal Geum.
Is she that first love you told us about?
Huh? Yeah.
Where is the milk? Oh, milk.
Hey, hey... my milk!
Mal Geum likes lattes.
My goodness.
You were dying just a moment ago.
Now, you're full of life.
Love is a shocking thing.
Of course, the power of love
can really shock you.
Right, Dong Gu?
Hm? I don't know.
- Yoon Ah, you should take this.
- What?
Why would I?
You should just wear it.
It is much too small for me.
Still, it was a gift to you
from Dong Gu, so how can I?
It's fine. Dong Gu doesn't mind at all.
- Right, Dong Gu?
- Huh?
Oh, yeah. Of course, I don't mind.
Don't worry about it and wear it.
Su Ah and I are just friends.
That's right. We're friends.
Dong Gu must have
a love somewhere else.
What?
Anyway, you should wear this Yoon Ah.
Hand it over nicely.
Why are you throwing it?
I wanted to.
But Sol cries when I get within
one meter of her, so what can I do?
Does that make sense?
Want to see?
Why are you making him cry?
- Oh?
- What's with that?
Awesome!
This little thing can already
differentiate between good and bad.
What a genius. You're evil.
Genius and evil.
Joon Ki, what did you say?
You want to die?
I momentarily lost my mind.
Seeing these pictures
reminds me of the past.
We were always
hanging out together, right?
- When did you start liking me anyway?
- What?
Why kind of question is that,
all of a sudden?
What is this then? What is it?
Oh, this...
You liked me, right? Since when?
Was I your first love?
No, no! This isn't...
Doo Shik, I brought you bandages...
Oh, you have a guest.
- Who is it?
- Oh, my friend.
Friend? Oh, that first love
you told us about?
Hey! What are you talking about?
It's not her.
- Get out, get out.
- Okay, I'll leave.
I even bought you these
and you're getting mad at me.
Leave.
- Have a nice time.
- Hey!
Why do you need those bandages?
Are you injured?
Oh, it's nothing.
I was working construction...
- Construction?
- Huh?
A friend of mine said they're lacking
manpower so I'm helping out.
Is it because of me, by chance?
Is it my contract?
No, I took care of that already.
- Did you really?
- I did.
So, don't worry about anything and
just focus on your drama auditions.
Now, I have a cold and can't even work.
When will I ever repay that money?
Oh, I'm dying here.
[New Drug Testing:
Two million won per week]
Two million won a week?
- Two million won?
I... I... I want to do it too.
It's a test for cold medicine,
so you need to have a cold.
A cold?
Then I'll just catch a cold.
How?
Let's go.
Joon Ki, do you really have to do this?
Of course! It's two million won per week.
Two million,
two million, two million won!
Pour it on me.
I don't know.
I'm just going to pour it on.
- It's cold.
- Are you okay?
It's cold. It's really cold.
Let's go for the cold!
Let's go. Let's go for the cold!
Yeah!
Sol, don't cry.
Let's go, my daughter.
Don't cry. Don't cry.
All right, there.
What's the matter? Don't cry.
- I got you.
- Don't cry. What's wrong?
Help me out, Sol.
Hold on a minute.
Excuse me. I'll try calming her down.
- What?
- Wait here.
Okay, then.
Mommy.
Isn't the sound amazing and fun?
So, stop crying and play
with this with your mom.
Wow, that's amazing.
Babies have good hearing,
so they like noises like this.
Thank you. You really saved me.
Oh no. It was nothing.
Thank you.
- Get home safely.
- Yes, thank you!
Dad, what are you staring at?
It just feels like I'm looking
at myself in the past.
Hoon, when you were young,
I was just like that.
I didn't know anything,
so everything was hectic for me.
I don't think that's it at all.
Dad, are you sure you didn't
fall for her at first sight?
Where are Joon Ki and Doo Shik?
Doo Shik is suffering from his cold.
Joon Ki is probably doing
something crazy somewhere.
Are you in a rush or something?
Why are you standing and eating?
I have to eat when I have time.
Why?
Because of this.
Sol doesn't seem to want to be
away from Yoon Ah lately.
So Yoon Ah can't sleep at all
and it's a big problem.
Oh, really?
Water.
What is with this fashion?
Where were you anyway?
- I went for a walk.
- A walk?
In this cold and in those clothes?
Yes, I need to catch a cold.
You need to catch a cold?
What do you mean by that?
Tell us so we understand.
I need a part-time job
in a human testing lab.
So, I need a cold.
Isn't there a good way to catch a cold?
- He's crazy.
- I'm so sick.
Oh, this is good.
Ugh.
What the heck?
Why are you eating my candy?
Why else? I need to catch your cold.
So dirty. That won't
help you catch his cold.
You're right.
It's not enough. Eat it again.
Gosh.
I need a foolproof way to catch a cold.
Oh, this would work.
What, Joon Ki?
What's that dirty look in your eyes?
I thought of a foolproof way
to catch a cold.
Doo Shik.
Let's kiss just once.
What? K... kiss?
Are you crazy?
Don't come near me.
I've never done it before.
Get away from me.
It's okay, it's okay.
It'll be over soon.
Get away from me.
I've never kissed anyone.
Doo Shik, it'll be over soon.
What are they doing?
Sol, where is your mom anyway?
What is this?
What is this all about?
Dong Gu, Yoon Ah... wake up.
- Why sleep here instead of your rooms?
- Huh?
I put Sol to sleep and fell asleep
while studying for the academy.
Oh.
Dong Gu, why are you
sleeping here next to Yoon Ah?
Huh? Oh, that...
Ow, my back.
I drank so much yesterday that
I didn't even know I slept here.
Oh, my head hurts.
Don't drink so much.
Don't you feel bad at all?
You must all be hungry.
I'll prepare breakfast.
I'll help you, Yoon Ah.
- You can watch Sol, Dong Gu.
- Okay.
Good morning, Sol.
Sol, did you sleep well?
Um, excuse me. Hot water, please?
Yes, one moment.
Yoon Ah, what are you doing?
What do you mean?
What do I do?
So hot!
- Ouch.
- Are you okay?
Are you okay, Yoon Ah?
I'm okay.
Sorry, I can't seem to
concentrate right now.
This won't do.
Yoon Ah, you're on break from now on.
So, don't do anything here
and go do whatever you'd like.
What? I'm really okay.
Hey, now. Do as you're told.
You're not going to listen?
It's not that--
What are you doing?
Hurry up and get going.
Yeah, go and get some rest.
- Still...
- Get going.
Go on. Say, "Bye, Mom."
All right. You're all done.
Press down on it until it stops bleeding.
And take this medication at 9:00.
Yes.
Hey, hey. This is the best part-time job.
I could do it forever.
They take some blood, give us medicine,
and we get two million won a week.
It's like free money, right?
Yeah.
[Mal Geum]
Isn't that Mal Geum?
Why aren't you picking up?
Just because I don't want her to worry.
Why would she worry when you have
the best part-time job?
Sol, your mom is on a break today.
Let's have fun playing together.
What a hardworking guy we have here.
You're even watching her kid for her.
When you were dating me,
you only cared about yourself.
You've changed a lot.
What do you mean?
What is it, Sol?
Do you want to eat it too, Sol?
No, you can't eat this.
Oh no. You can't eat this.
Sol, I gave you abalone porridge too.
So, you sit here for a bit, okay?
You like that? Me too.
Where did I put that file
for the baby's birthday party?
It's time for your medication.
Again? We're taking it quite often.
Oh, what's wrong with my voice?
- You're right. It's weird.
- Oh.
What's wrong with my voice?
Is it because our colds are severe?
Ah, ah, ah.
- Ah, ah.
- Ah. Hey.
Isn't my voice kind of sexy?
Doo Shik.
Should we play?
Oh, stop. Don't do this.
It's sexy. Very sexy.
Please stop that.
Excuse me. Just take your medicine.
Let's do so.
I don't want medicine.
Should I feed you
or do you want to come here?
Joon Ki, kiss me.
Oh my god.
Oh my god!
Oh, I'm tired.
How long do I have to live doing
these baby birthday party gigs?
I miss the film industry. I really do.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm drinking coffee and editing
the videos for the baby birthday party.
Yeah? What about Sol?
Sol? She's right here.
Where did Sol go? Where is Sol?
Oh, Sol!
Hey, why would Sol be there?
Where is Sol?
Can't you see I'm looking? Where is she?
- Sol, Sol!
- Sol!
Sol wouldn't be in here.
Sol! Hey.
Sol, where are you? Sol.
Sol, where are you?
Sol.
Sol, where did you go?
Here you are. No, you aren't.
Sol!
Where could she have possibly gone?
What are you going to do now, huh?
What if something's happened to Sol?
I'm going crazy too!
How are we going to find her?
This was your amazing method
of finding Sol?
Sol will cry if she goes
within one meter of her.
Looking for her like this will be faster
than if we just look alone.
Hey, are you looking for a water source?
Am I a radar?
Aren't you asking too much of me lately?
What can we do? We have to find her.
Stretch out your arms. Good.
Let's go.
This way.
Oh, what was that?
Isn't that Sol crying?
Look, there's nothing here.
What do you mean?
I know I heard something.
Is it the bed?
Does that make sense?
How could she get into the bed?
There you are!
- Oh my.
- What?
How did she get up there alone?
Does that make sense?
Does that make any sense at all?
Why is that important?
We found her, didn't we?
Sol, how did you get up there?
I was so worried about you.
I'm relieved nothing happened to her.
Wait. Why are her cheeks so red?
Hold on, Sol.
Oh! She has a fever.
What?
She really does.
Why does she suddenly have a fever?
Sol.
Lee Joon Ki and Bong Doo Shik, wake up.
We need to draw blood.
Again?
Ah... ah, ah, ah.
What? What's wrong with my voice?
What's with your voice, Joon Ki?
What's wrong with my voice? Ah, ah...
Why are their voices like that?
What? Mine is like that too.
Oh! Mine too.
What's going on here? This is a problem.
Doctor!
What's going on here?
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
What's wrong my voice?
This is seriously insane.
- Ah, ah, ah.
- Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Testing... ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
It won't stop.
Ma'am, one order of the blood sausage.
- One moment, please.
- Sure.
Oh, hello.
Oh, you're the person
who helped me with Sol.
- It's you, right?
- Yes.
We meet again.
Where is that cute baby?
You're alone today.
Ah, her dad must be
watching her today, right?
No, Sol doesn't have a dad.
I'm raising her by myself.
Oh, I see.
I left my son, Hoon, with a babysitter
and I was having a day out too.
So, you're on a date with your wife?
No, I separated from
my wife six years ago.
I realized that we don't even know
each other's names yet.
I'm Song Hyun Joon.
I'm Han Yoon Ah.
It was nice seeing you again, Yoon Ah.
Yes, it was nice to see you.
You have something...
right here.
What? Oh, when did Sol do that?
Oh, that little baby did it.
Gosh, my Hoon vomited so much too.
I didn't have any decent clothes.
One moment.
Yes, Seo Jin. What is it?
What?
Sol?
Yes, okay. I'll be right there. Okay.
What is it? Is something wrong?
Sol is sick. I'd better get going now.
Yes.
Sol... Sol!
What's wrong my Sol?
They say it's intestinal inflammation.
Intestinal inflammation?
Why would she have that?
She was fine this morning.
It seems she ate something
she shouldn't have.
I didn't feed her anything.
You know I can't get
within one meter of her.
It can't be that.
Well, I did feed her something.
What did you feed her?
A little bit of bread from a corn dog.
Bread from a corn dog?
I really wasn't going to give it to her,
but Sol looked so desperate to eat it.
But it is organic bread.
There wasn't anything else?
A little bit of ham and abalone...
What? Ham and abalone?
It was abalone porridge... porridge.
Are you insane, Dong Gu?
How can you feed ham and abalone
to a baby who's still breastfeeding?
How can you be so thoughtless?
Sorry, I thought she could eat it.
I'm really sorry, Yoon Ah.
No, it's my fault for
not telling you earlier.
Sol, I'm sorry for leaving you.
I shouldn't have left.
I'm sorry.
Ah, ah.
Gosh, what is this?
What kind of side effect is this?
What if our voices never come back?
I know.
Those jerks.
What kind of medicine is that?
Let's hurry home for now.
Taxi!
Taxi, taxi.
Mister, can you take us to Huam-dong?
Huam-dong.
The Waikiki Guest House.
What's wrong?
Oh, it must be because of our voices.
Mister, we're not playing a joke.
We were subjects in a research lab.
This is the side effect of a medication.
We're not kidding. It's the truth.
What is it?
What is it, Mister?
It's true. It's a side effect.
We're not playing a joke on you.
Yeah right, you punks.
You're doing this because of me.
You're making fun of me!
You're dead. You're both dead today!
What are you doing?
Oh, you're here?
You should go in if you want.
I do want to, but...
I can't face Yoon Ah and Sol
because I feel so bad.
I don't know why I was so stupid.
Dong Gu, may I ask you one question?
What is it?
About you liking Yoon Ah...
Did you think about her situation
and Sol when you started it?
What do you mean by that?
Yoon Ah has Sol and everything.
You have the confidence
to handle all of that, right?
Don't tell me you never thought about it.
I may be overstepping.
If you don't think you can handle it,
don't even start anything.
Yoon Ah's already someone
who's been hurt a lot.
I thought you guys would be gone
a few days, so why are you back?
Is the job done?
So, did you make some money?
How much did you get paid?
So frustrating. What are you saying?
That hurts. Why are you hitting me?
What's with your voice, Joon Ki?
Well, it's an adverse side effect
from the medicine.
This is all your fault!
Where did you find
a crappy job like that?
Who told you to come?
Why did you come and throw a fit?
What? You did nothing right,
so why get mad?
What did I do wrong? What?
My voice is like this because of you.
What the heck is this?
Of all the things they do...
It's your fault!
[Mal Geum]
It's Mal Geum.
I can't get the phone with this voice.
What do I do?
Seo Jin, you pick up.
Gosh. Give it to me.
Yes, hello.
Yes, this is Doo Shik's phone,
but he's in the bathroom right now.
If you give me a message,
I'll relay it to him.
Uh, okay.
Yes.
- What did she say?
- Mal Geum has something to say.
She wants to meet you outside the house.
Huh? Something to say?
What could it be?
Maybe she's going to tell you
she has feelings for you.
Feelings? Oh, I doubt that.
Oh, you'd like that.
You're hoping for that.
Don't pretend to be innocent.
Stop that. Stop that.
I don't know what she'll say.
Sorry for calling you out so suddenly.
I had something I wanted to tell you.
Well...
I...
I agreed to work with
the agency's chairman again.
What?
What are you talking about?
Doo Shik, what's wrong with your voice?
Ah, ah. It's nothing.
I have a bit of a cold.
Ah, ah.
What do you mean
you're working with him again?
So, you're making erotic films again?
No.
He has a drama he's working on
with a Chinese production company.
He says I can be in it.
So, I'm going to China.
- When?
- Tomorrow.
I'm going in a rush
because of the filming schedule.
That quickly?
Mal Geum, did you happen to hear
something from the chairman?
Hear what?
Oh, that you were paying off the fee
for my breach of contract?
I already knew about that.
I knew you were working
those jobs because of me.
I pretended not to know.
I wanted to run away, no matter how.
Then are you working with him again
because of money?
Mal Geum, I'll get
the money somehow, so--
No, it's not just because of the money.
It's because I want to do it.
No matter how much I try here
I can't do anything
because of my history.
So, I want to start over in a place
where no one knows me.
Do you have to go?
Can't you not go?
It's a really good opportunity for me.
I don't want to lose
this opportunity, Doo Shik.
You'll be rooting for me, right?
Thanks. I really
wanted you to support me.
Oh yeah.
While I was packing,
I found pictures of us together.
So I brought them.
Doo Shik, I'm thankful
for everything you've done for me.
Very thankful.
I'll get going then.
Please be well.
Who is this that
you drew hearts like this?
My first love.
Is our Sol all better now?
Was your tummy hurting
because of that crazy uncle?
You're crazy.
How can you feed ham and abalone to
a baby who's still breastfeeding?
That's enough. He didn't know.
Don't worry too much, Dong Gu.
Sol is all better now.
Sol, come here.
Sol, you're all better now, right?
I may be overstepping.
If you don't think you can handle it,
don't even start anything.
Yoon Ah's already someone
who's been hurt a lot.
Can I handle it?
I couldn't even protect Sol.
Are you okay?
I can't even take care of myself.
What's with him?
He was in the wrong,
so why's he acting like a victim?
Wow, you have a great life.
You take naps even though
you should be looking for a job.
I was preparing for interviews all night,
so I took a short nap.
What about you?
You say you're an actor,
but you work weird part-time jobs.
What? Weird part-time jobs?
Hey, I sacrificed my body for
the development of new medicine.
Seo Jin, don't be like that.
Why don't you give up on a job
and go in for human testing?
You know, for women's hair removal.
Not many women have mustaches.
- It's all rough and prickly.
- Why you...
You want to die? Do you?
Chewbacca is killing someone.
Jedi, help me. Jedi!
Stop it, would you?
You two fight every time you meet.
Leave them be.
They'll end up liking each other
at some point.
What? Liking each other?
Why would you say such a horrific thing?
He is the man I have the
lowest opinion of in the world.
Even if we were the only ones
left on a deserted island
I wouldn't go near him.
I don't like you either.
If we were on a deserted island,
I'd rather live with a sea turtle.
I won't live with you.
A sea turtle doesn't have a mustache.
They're smooth.
I just got a call from that sea turtle.
It says it doesn't like
loser types like you.
- Loser?
- What?
- This is mine.
Gosh, why did you buy
the same phone as mine?
I bought it first.
I don't like anything about you.
What is that sound?
I will be waiting.
Though I have nothing great to offer you.
Shamelessly, I want you for myself.
Does he really want to sing
that song with that voice?
Be understanding.
Mal Geum is leaving Korea today.
Ah...
His side effect is lasting a long time.
Listen to that voice. Gosh.
You are...
Dong Gu, would you stop Doo Shik?
I want it so badly.
Please love me.
Please don't make me cry.
This one word,
more commonly spoken than breathing.
I cannot say it with confidence
and I am always hiding.
I am nothing but a coward.
What's wrong with him?
This house is never normal.
It never is.
Please love me.
Please don't make me cry.
This one word,
more commonly spoken than breathing.
- Doo Shik.
- Dong Gu.
I am a coward.
I'm a coward too.
[My Gangster Lover]
I'm Seoul District Prosecutor
Kang Ji Wan.
Do you want to come quietly
or should we fight?
It's your choice.
However, if we have to fight...
you'll have to put your life on the line.
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
What's your role this time?
A prosecutor, prosecutor.
A prosecutor who goes up
against gangsters, at that.
A prosecutor, with that face?
You're not some gangster or street thug?
The director has a bad eye for people.
Chewbacca, are you going to
talk to me that way?
I think I'll have some ramen.
You don't even support me.
Why isn't this turning on?
Joon Ki, come take a look.
You're only nice when you need me.
Just take a look.
It was working before.
It was fine before.
Why wouldn't it work? Move.
Why isn't it working?
Let me see here.
I turned it on. How weird.
Joon Ki!
Geez. What is this?
Hey, you.
How could you turn the switch on
when I had my face up near the range?
Sorry, I didn't think it would
turn on so suddenly.
Of course, fire lights up suddenly!
I'm seriously going crazy here.
I have a scene to film.
How am I supposed to go like this?
What's been with you all day, Dong Gu?
Is something wrong?
Leave him alone.
This isn't the first time
he's tried to look cool.
Go away, you and you fake cool act.
Stop that. I'm not in a good mood.
What's that? Joon Ki, your eyebrow.
Did you wax it?
Your eyebrow's gone.
Don't laugh, you punk. Don't laugh!
This is all your sister's fault.
Don't laugh!
What's that?
- It's a model set.
- A model set?
Oh, your voice is back.
It came back this morning.
Why do you have that model set?
I just felt a little down.
What's going on with your eyebrow?
Don't laugh, don't laugh!
You seemed practically dead
just a moment ago.
So, why did you buy that model set
when you're down?
Oh, I thought I could organize my
thoughts if I completed this.
Yeah, then let me join you, Doo Shik.
I have a lot to think about too.
Sure, you can join me.
But, isn't that really funny?
I know.
Just shave the other one too.
Is he Harvey Dent or what?
Don't laugh!
Hey, have you ever done this before?
It's harder than it looks
and it's not for everyone.
What?
I can make this with my eyes shut
in half a day.
Really?
Once I open up a box
I don't eat or sleep until I complete it.
Is that okay with you?
If you're going to give up in the middle,
then just leave now.
I will never give up.
If you don't think you can do it,
don't hang around here and go.
Then, shall we get started?
Shall we?
Su Ah, what do you think of this?
You like an idiot
who drew on his eyebrows.
What? An idiot?
Geez.
Su Ah, how about this?
You like an idiot
who has tape on his face.
An idiot with tape?
I'm going crazy here.
That girl Kang Seo Jin ruins everything.
[Mona Lisa Wigs]
Joon Ki.
Call them and ask
if they have eyebrow wigs.
Are you kidding right now?
You're pouring fuel on a burning house.
Forget it, then.
Here it is.
Kang Seo Jin, what are you
going to do about this?
How can I go on set like this?
I said I was sorry.
I'll be going to my interview then.
Hey, you ruined my filming today
and you can actually go interview?
Sorry. I said sorry. I'm sorry.
Bye.
- Seo Jin, wait.
- What?
Have a good interview.
I'm always rooting for you.
- Good luck.
- Oh, okay.
Thanks.
- Good luck to you too.
- High five.
Good luck!
You're next, so be prepared.
[Joyoung Daily: Interviews]
Lastly, why do you want to be
a reporter, Kang Seo Jin?
I believe a reporter
can change the world.
I hope to write articles to right
the injustices of the world.
I want to be the voice
for people who are weak.
I want to make the world
a little better to live in.
That is why I want to be a reporter.
I understand. Thank you.
We will contact you.
Thank you.
Ah, Kang Seo Jin.
Yes? What is it?
There's something stuck on your back.
What? Why is this here?
What's this? Balding.
"You are not the exception.
Prepare in advance."
Did you bring this for me,
by any chance?
No. Not at all. I really didn't.
All right. You may leave.
Why was this here?
Wait.
I'm always rooting for you.
Good luck.
Don't tell me that was when...
Lee Joon Ki, that crazy jerk.
Hey, are you joking with me?
What's with your face?
Where's your eyebrow?
- I'm sorry.
- Is sorry going to fix it?
How is this the face
of an elite prosecutor?
Could we get some special makeup?
Do you know how much makeup costs?
I'm going nuts. We have to film.
I'm having problems
because of something like this!
Wait, wait, wait.
Ah.
- We can do this.
- What?
I'm Seoul District Prosecutor
Kang Ji Wan.
Do you want to come quietly
or should we fight?
It's your choice.
However, if we have to fight,
you'll have to put your life on the line.
You stay put, you punk.
Prosecutor or whatever you are
if you take one more step, I'll just...
Cut, cut, cut!
Hey, what are you doing?
Is that the best you can do
with your acting?
You have the scariest looking face.
But you're going to say your lines
like that, seriously?
Sorry, my role was
suddenly changed, so...
I'll try again.
One more time.
This is all because Kang Seo Jin.
What is this?
Just wait until he comes home.
- Hey!
- Hey, Lee Joon Ki.
You did this, didn't you?
Do you know what happened to me
at the interview because of this?
Hey, I got cursed at on set
and lost my role because of you!
I said sorry for that.
Do you know how important
this interview was for me?
Are you going to take responsibility
if I don't pass? Are you?
What? Hey.
Then take responsibility for my eyebrow!
What? Seriously!
Seo Jin, what is it?
What text did you get?
[Joyoung Daily:
You did not pass our interview.]
Ow. Hey, hey!
What was that text?
Seo Jin didn't pass her interview.
- What?
- Really?
Why would you play
that kind of joke, Joon Ki?
What? Is it my fault?
I'm also a victim!
Goodness.
What do we do about Seo Jin?
She failed, so what can we do about it?
Are those two still doing that?
They haven't eaten all day.
Aren't they even hungry?
I'm hungry.
My back hurts too.
My eyes hurt like crazy.
It's so hard that
I can't gather my thoughts at all.
I can't think at all.
Isn't that kid having a hard time at all?
That scary punk.
It's so hard.
It's so hard that I can't
gather my feelings at all.
I think my body is paralyzed.
Why does he seem so fine?
That scary punk.
Doo Shik, how much have we made?
Are we almost done?
I don't know. Should we take a look?
Yes.
What? There's still this much left?
Darn it.
This is nuts.
When will we ever finish all of this?
I'm so tired I could die.
Doo Shik, I can continue, of course.
Look at this.
It's time for "Knowing Bros" to air.
I never miss "Knowing Bros"
because I'm a a big fan.
You want to watch together?
Say you'll watch it.
Please say you'll watch it.
Let's rest for an hour, at least.
Of course, I could do this all night too.
I am a "Knowing Bros" maniac,
just like you.
Let's go watch "Knowing Bros"
and come back to this.
I can live. I can live.
"Knowing Bros" or
"Bros Who Don't Know"
let's just rest for now.
Where are you going? You're already done?
Not yet.
Today happens to be the day
"Knowing Bros" airs.
I'm a maniac for that show.
Me too. I'm a big fan of that show.
- I was in Seo Jang Hoon's fan club too.
- Yeah.
- I really was.
- Oh yeah?
"Knowing Bros" was canceled today.
Oh, really?
"Knowing Bros" is canceled,
so we'd better get started.
Yes.
"Knowing Bros" is canceled.
We should start building it again.
Where are Dong Gu and Doo Shik?
I don't know.
They were building that model
and didn't come into the room all night.
They're still at it?
They're more persistent than I thought.
They must have a lot on their minds.
I pity those two.
Where's Seo Jin?
She doesn't want to eat.
She's been crying all day
under the blanket.
I'm worried about her.
Go apologize first, Joon Ki.
Why should I?
Hey, I'm the victim here.
Don't you see my eyebrow?
Still, you went too far.
Just let it go this time, Joon Ki.
Yeah, Seo Jin is crying.
Fine! She is so petty.
Chewbacca, aren't you going to eat?
I don't want to talk, so leave.
I'm sorry, okay?
I didn't think you'd go all the way to
the interview with that on your back.
So don't be mad anymore, okay?
Whatever. Just leave.
I'm apologizing to you first like this.
Can't you accept?
Truthfully, it's not all my fault that
you didn't pass the interview.
I know that.
I know very well that
it wasn't because of you.
Then why are you being like this?
It's not the first time
you didn't pass an interview.
This... was my last interview.
What do you mean by that? Your last one?
I was going to give up on being
a reporter if I didn't pass this time.
I made the decision
to look for other jobs.
Now that I got rejected,
I'm just so upset.
So, don't worry about me and just leave.
Let me be alone and go.
Hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Sleep in your room if you're tired.
Why are you sleeping here?
Sleeping? Who?
Me? I wasn't.
I was just blinking very slowly.
Ah... you were sleeping, Doo Shik.
I didn't sleep.
I was thinking.
About how to build
this model in a cool way.
Honestly, I was sleeping.
I was sleeping sweetly.
I was about to fall into REM sleep,
but I woke up.
I want to sleep comfortably in my bed.
But this guy will look down on me
if I suggest sleeping.
I'm going crazy.
I want to sleep.
My eyes are starting to close.
Should I just go and sleep?
Then this guy will
look down on me and tease me.
What do I do?
Oh... oh dear.
What do we do?
What? What is it?
Look at this.
My fingers are glued together
because of the glue.
Look. Oh no.
My fingers are glued together too.
What about it?
You need your index finger and thumb
the most when you build these models.
But they're stuck together.
We can't build it even if we want to.
Yes, it's really too bad.
What can we do
with our fingers like this?
I really wanted to complete it.
I'm really upset
but this must be the end of the road.
Do you really want to
complete it that much?
Of course.
Why would you even ask?
Don't worry. I have acetone.
You can use acetone
to make the glue come off.
I'll do it for you.
No, acetone won't work.
I doubt that.
It's very strong glue.
How could acetone work?
It would probably take a very long time.
It won't come off so easily.
- Doo Shik.
- Me too?
See? It works fast.
Now you can work on it all you want.
Acetone.
You just stay put.
Prosecutor or whatever you are,
if you take one more step...
I'll just...
Seriously, that girl.
I can't act because
this eyebrow is bothering me.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
Is this Kang Seo Jin's phone?
What? Kang Seo Jin?
Oh, we switched phones again.
What is this about?
This is Joyoung Daily
where she's supposed to
come for her second interview.
What? She got a text yesterday
that she didn't pass the first one.
Kang Seo Jin passed the first interview.
I guess they sent the wrong text.
What did you say?
How can you say that now?
Never mind.
What time is the interview?
What? 2:00 pm?
What? Is there another
"Huam-dong's Hairy"?
Hello.
Yeah. It's me, Seo Jin.
What? It's you, Joon Ki?
What is it?
The thing is...
I accidentally left
with your phone again.
Again?
So, you saved my number as
"Huam-dong's Hairy"?
That's not the important part.
Seo Jin, you passed the first interview.
What? What are you talking about?
Joyoung Daily just called your phone.
They want you to come in again.
Is that true?
So you need to go to the seminar room
at Joyoung Daily, 10th floor by 2:00.
2:00 pm?
- What do I do?
- What?
You can get ready quickly,
take a taxi, and get there.
I came out to get some air and
I'm on a bus to see the ocean.
I've already come a long way.
Even if I go quickly,
I'll be too late.
Then you're going to give up?
You said this was your last interview.
But, the time...
I'll do what I can. Just get here.
Hang up.
Mister!
Please stop.
We're going get started soon.
Please stand by!
Yes!
Excuse me. Where are you going?
We have a new instructor today,
so I'd like to introduce him.
Please come in.
Hyun Joon?
Yoon Ah, what are you doing here?
Excuse me. We need to
introduce you to the class first.
Yes, I'm sorry.
- I'll talk to you later, Yoon Ah.
- Okay.
Hello, everyone.
I'll be teaching your class
starting today.
My name is Song Hyun Joon.
It's nice to meet you all.
I can't believe it.
- So awesome.
- Why?
Is he that famous?
He's a star patisseur and
one of the famous few in our country.
Really?
- Good job.
- Thank you.
- Excuse me.
- Oh my gosh.
How much time
until the interviews are over?
- They're over.
- They're over?
Could you wait a little longer?
That will be difficult because
the managers have a schedule too.
What happens if you don't make it
to the interview today?
I suppose you would fail this round.
Fail...
How can you do that?
It was your error that caused it!
I don't know what you're referring to.
What do I do?
[Interview Location]
This is crazy, crazy, crazy.
Hey, where are you going?
Good work, everyone.
You can't go in there!
What is this?
Don't move.
What do you think you're doing?
Who is this person?
All of you stay put.
Prosecutor or whatever you are...
No, wait...
Interviewers or whatever you are,
you're dead if you take one more step.
Who are you and
what do you think you're doing?
Shut up!
Stay calm if you don't want to get hurt.
- Got it?
- This guy just won't do.
What?
So, what are you going to do?
What are you going to do?
That was unexpected.
Why is he... What? Why?
- Hey.
- Yes?
Why don't we go talk?
Come here.
Why are you doing this?
Please don't do this.
Let's talk briefly.
Don't do this. Please don't do this.
Get over here.
Please save me. Save me.
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me, excuse me.
I'm here for an interview.
My name is Kang Seo Jin.
Please wait. Some weird man
is inside causing a commotion.
Let me go. It hurts.
Sir, please!
Oh gosh.
Oh my.
Sorry about that.
What kind of person does that?
Do you know him, by chance?
What?
- No.
- You said you're Kang Seo Jin?
- Yes.
- You're a bit late.
I'm sorry.
Director, we have one more interviewee.
What should we do?
We should see her. Come in.
Thank you.
This is it.
I can't bear it any longer.
But I can't say I give up first.
What do I do now?
Where did it go?
What? What? What?
I made a radar. It disappeared.
I can't do it any longer, then.
What? You can't do it without that radar?
Of course, an aircraft carrier
without a radar
is like a guest house without guests.
I really wanted to complete it.
Now there is no meaning
behind building it.
Maybe you're sitting on it.
No, I'm not.
You never know. Stand up.
Okay.
I can stand up.
What? It's not there.
I told you it's not there.
I really wanted to complete it.
I'll be going now then.
Does it make sense for
the radar to disappear, Doo Shik?
Gosh, how shocking.
It's seriously so upsetting.
I'm so upset.
How could we lose the radar?
Seriously, I don't think
I'll even be able to sleep.
I'm so concerned
that I don't think I can do it.
Why?
I'm worried about Dong Gu.
I'm okay because
I've been trained for this.
One can get quite traumatized if they
lose a radar while building these models.
It can get quite bad.
- Really?
- Oh yes.
You don't know...
how that feels.
It can be so terrible.
Dong Gu, are you okay?
You're very shocked, right? Dong Gu.
You're upset about the radar, right?
What are you doing?
Does it taste good alone?
I told you to rest at home
after the interview.
Why did you come here?
Just because.
Here. Give me some too.
Did your interview go well?
You didn't make a mistake?
Yes, I did well.
But what did you about
your filming schedule today?
Huh?
Oh... I just quit.
Yeah.
Was that because of me?
No, it wasn't. Not at all.
My image is very intelligent and smart.
The elite prosecutor was perfect for me.
The gangster role didn't suit me at all.
Anyway...
thanks so much for today.
No need to be cheesy
and thank me.
Never mind that. Let's just drink.
Why are you drinking
alcohol like it's water?
Today, you made feel a tiny bit
touched by what you did.
Touched? No need for that.
Like you said,
it was a very important interview.
It was an important interview.
You said it was your last interview.
So...
you should pass and get the job.
All right, girl?
Okay, I will.
If I get the job
I will get you an eyebrow tattoo.
A really pretty one.
Thank you.
But, I don't want a tattoo.
How about you give me those
right here as a gift?
Hey, you.
Why, you...
It's a joke. It's just a joke.
You know when I saw you earlier?
My heart was racing, you know.
Why do you think it did that?
Am I crazy?
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey, just let me look at you.
- What?
- You punk.
I don't understand it.
What is attractive about this guy?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
What did we do last night?
Alcohol is my enemy.
Alcohol, Alcohol.
Joon Ki, you dared to do that
to my sister? Get over here!
I'm the rookie employee,
Kang Seo Jin.
Find out who the masked singer winning
for seven weeks is.
I'm a reporter.
Are you getting in the way of
what the people deserve to know?
Did you find out who?
How can you be a reporter then?
Give up on this job.
You're the Red-faced Octopus, right?
He definitely looked like
Su Ah's ex-boyfriend.
Did you catch him?
- What are you doing?
- I'm going sit here myself.
Get me a cola.
- Yes, President.
- Don't you get angry?
What took you so long?
Doo Shik, let's eat some meat.
I'm treating.
This is my personal workspace.
You can practice here. I'll help you.
Dong Gu, are you mad at me
about something?
Are you crying?
Dong Gu, you're more of
a coward than I thought.
So what if you fail or fall once?
That's why I'm going to
tell her how I feel.
Yoon Ah, I have something to tell you.