Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
The Japanese put six bullets in my body.
This is from an assassination attempt
in 1929 in Gyeongseong.
There are two holes.
This was in 1922 in Shanghai.
This one was in 1927 Khabarovsk.
Then in 1932,
this was during the the explosion.
By my heart right here,
that was in 1933.
They say I turned on three comrades.
None of you know the truth!
You do not know what I was feeling
when I let them go.
They were walking toward their deaths.
Judge!
Thanks for the audition.
Leave your profile there.
Yes, sir. I am rookie actor,
Lee Joon Ki.
Please give me a chance.
Director, we don't have much time left.
Where will we find an actor so quickly?
You're right.
Hold on.
Hey, you.
- Come here.
- Me?
Okay.
Why are you doing that?
What's your height and weight?
I'm 180 centimeters and 71 kilograms.
180 centimeters and 71 kilograms?
Do you want to be in our film?
We have a role.
Really?
Whichever role you give me,
I'll work very hard!
Okay.
The thing is,
it's for a bed scene...
You'd be a stand-in.
It's not even just a bed scene.
But, a stand-in for the bed scene?
I don't know about that.
- It's a bit difficult, right?
- Yes, it is.
You happen to have
a similar physique to our main actor.
I was just asking.
Okay. You should get going.
Thank you.
Gosh.
We have everything set up.
Soo Jung thinks we're shooting that day.
Wait, did you say Soo Jung?
The epitome of innocence and glamor,
actress Shin Soo Jung?
- Yes.
- Then, she'd be who I film with?
- Shin Soo Jung?
- Yes.
The main female actor for our film
is Shin Soo Jung.
I will do the bed scene.
I will do it no matter what!
Okay, sounds good!
None of you know the truth!
Wow.
[Jealousy Is My Strength]
Make sure to get it everywhere.
Don't miss a spot.
All right.
Also, focus on my back.
- The back is important.
- I heard you.
You have to keep your promise though.
- Shin Soo Jung's autograph.
- Okay.
Make sure to spread it out everywhere
to every crevice.
Hold still, would you?
I'm home.
My back.
What is this offensive image here?
Joon Ki got cast in a film,
so he's taking care of his skin.
What is the role that he has to
take care of his back?
He's a stand-in for a bed scene.
What? A stand-in for a bed scene?
Gosh, you're doing all kinds of crap now.
Let go! Hey! What do you mean?
Do you know who I'm filming
the bed scene with?
It's Shin Soo Jung, Shin Soo Jung!
Even if I weren't a stand-in, but crew,
I'd have to say thank you.
That's how it is.
Of course.
It's not just anyone.
It's Shin Soo Jung.
Goodness.
What's with men?
Oh, I'm going to get going then.
- Okay.
- Where are you going?
Oh, it's your first day at
the baking academy, right?
- Yes.
- Have a nice day.
Don't get sleepy in class,
and listen to your instructor.
- Okay.
- Did you forget anything?
Of course, not.
I have my wallet and phone.
Do you know how to get there?
Of course, the way there is...
- Well...
- Here.
This is the bus number and your stop.
I wrote the directions to the school,
so follow this.
Thank you, Dong Gu.
I'll be going, then.
- Have a good day.
- I will.
- Be careful of cars.
- Okay!
Hey, what was that?
What is this sweet mood
like that of a newlywed couple
saying bye in the morning?
Yeah, you even drew her
a map with directions.
Something smells very suspicious.
What? What's so suspicious?
I did it in case she created
a hassle by getting lost.
Stop sniffing me.
Why are you getting mad over a joke?
That angry boy.
What's with him?
Yeah, it's more suspicious of him
to act that way.
What's so suspicious?
Are they suggesting I like Yoon Ah?
It's just sympathy. That's all.
It's just helping a disadvantaged person.
Yes, of course.
The problem is that I'm too kind.
Oh, you're so nice.
First, make sure to get this down.
Kneading the dough with hot water...
Thank you.
I'll have skin like a baby if I use this.
Great.
Dong Gu, can you put lots of this
on my butt when we get home?
You're insane. No way.
Why are you asking me? Are you crazy?
You're really going all out, seriously.
No need to get testy.
Isn't that Yoon Ah?
Thanks for the ride home.
Get home safely.
Bye.
- Yoon Ah.
- Why are you out here?
Were you waiting for me?
Why would we wait?
We were buying diapers for Sol.
Who's that?
Oh, I met him in class.
He drove me on his way home.
Wow, you're already so popular, Yoon Ah.
Popular, yeah right.
Why would you get in a car with
someone you don't know well?
She said they met in class.
Also, what's it to you
whose car she gets into or not?
That's because she's being a nuisance.
I told you not to be a burden to
others and be indebted to them.
That it becomes a habit?
Yeah, I'll be careful.
If you know, then good!
Why is he getting mad? Huh?
What is it? You don't like it?
I think it would be better if there
were a more provocative scene.
I'm not too sure what you mean.
Here.
Take a look at this.
"Free Wife 2017."
"I want to play aggressively tonight."
That's right.
Then I'll take a look for now.
Don't work out too much before the shoot.
You have to maintain your body, okay?
Yes, Director.
The main male lead will be here soon.
Let's try to match the hair,
skin tone, and other details.
Don't worry too much.
You two are nearly the same.
Oh, you're here.
- Yes, Director.
- Say hello.
This is your stand-in for
the bed scene, Lee Joon Ki.
Hello, my name is Lee Joon Ki.
I'm Kim Woo Sung.
Let's work well together.
I'm a fan.
Oh, what happened?
Why did you lose so much weight
in just a few weeks?
I was sick and suddenly lost weight.
- I couldn't gain even though I ate.
- Oh no.
Really? How much did you lose?
I weighed 71 kilograms.
I weighed myself this morning
and I weighed 60 kilograms.
What? How much do you weigh again?
71 kilograms.
I think we may need a new stand-in.
What? This can't happen.
Director, I will lose the weight.
You're going to lose 10 kilograms?
I will do whatever it takes
and lose the weight.
You agreed to lose
10 kilograms in one week?
Why do you have to lose weight
like that just for a bed scene?
Do you really not know?
Shin Soo Jung.
I don't think I need to explain further.
You would walk on fire just to film
a bed scene with Shin Soo Jung.
Not only would I walk on fire,
I'd even jump off a cliff for it.
Yoon Ah, are you home?
I'm not expecting anyone.
- Wow.
- It smells good.
What is all of this, Sang Yeon?
I happened to bake some doughnuts.
I baked too many.
I wanted you to try some.
Oh, I see. Thank you so much.
Yoon Ah, who is he?
You're the person
who drove Yoon Ah, right?
You attend the same academy?
That's right.
Hello, I'm Lee Sang Yeon.
- Yes, I saw you.
- Hello.
You must be Sol.
So cute. Peekaboo.
You drove Yoon Ah home
and you've brought doughnuts.
Are you interested in Yoon Ah?
Green light?
Yes, I...
am interested in Yoon Ah.
Me feelings are just one-sided,
so please don't feel burdened by them.
Ah, okay.
Sorry, but could I use the bathroom?
Yes, it's just over there.
Yes. One moment, please.
He proposed with doughnuts.
What's this?
That guy is interested in you.
What are you talking about?
It's not like that.
He just said so himself.
You should give it a go.
He seems like a good guy.
Hey, what do you know about him
to say he's a good guy?
He has a weird look in his eyes,
in my opinion.
Yoon Ah, be careful of him.
- What?
- Hey, man.
Who are you to tell her
to be careful or not?
I'm just saying it out of concern.
I'm worried.
If she dates a weird guy
Yoon Ah may have
difficulties in her life.
Shut up! You're not making sense.
This looks good. Eat a doughnut.
Forget it. I don't want it.
- I said I didn't want it!
- How dare you get mad at me?
What a waste of the doughnut.
Why didn't you just take the doughnut?
[Han Yoon Ah]
What are you doing here?
Why are you brushing your teeth
with that toothbrush?
Ah... my mouth felt a little dirty.
Then why don't you ask for a toothbrush?
Why are you using Yoon Ah's toothbrush?
Pardon?
Oh, was this Yoon Ah's?
I really didn't know.
How could you not know?
Her name is written right there.
Ah... the names are written there.
Oh, geez.
I really didn't know. Bye, now.
It's written right there.
What's with that guy?
I had a great time today.
I'll get going.
Yoon Ah, see you in class.
Yes, get home safely.
- Goodbye.
- Come again.
Bye.
He's a cool guy.
Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah.
Come over here.
Sit down, sit down.
Yoon Ah, he is a really great guy.
Yeah, he has good manners
and he looks like a nice person.
Nice person? Yeah, right.
Something's off about him.
What is?
I went up to the bathroom earlier.
He was brushing his teeth
with Yoon Ah's toothbrush.
What? My toothbrush?
His mouth must've felt dirty.
Hey, does it make sense to use
another person's toothbrush?
Why not? I sometimes use yours.
What? Why?
Your toothbrush is soft.
Mine is so hard.
- It hurts and I bleed.
- That's so dirty!
Anyway, I got a bad feeling.
He's very weird.
You're the weird one.
What? Are you jealous
because he's friendly with Yoon Ah?
Yeah, you gave her directions
this morning.
Do you like Yoon Ah, by chance?
What? Me?
Like Yoon Ah?
Just forget it. I shouldn't bring it up.
Gosh, is worrying about a person
considered liking her?
I just have a kind heart.
Why are you all doing that?
He's been acting strange since morning...
What is it? What is it?
I talked so much today
that I'm dying of hunger.
You think starving will help you
lose 10 kilograms in a week?
I don't know what else to do
in order to lose weight.
Ask Seo Jin for help.
She diets 365 days a year.
Really?
Seo Jin, help me with my diet.
- For free?
- Geez.
You capitalistic girl.
Fine, I'll buy you
the newest model razor that's out.
It even pulls the roots out.
Okay, but you have to do
everything I tell you to.
Right, I'm supposed to watch this.
There's going to be a ruckus
if I get caught watching this.
Why are you so startled?
I'm not.
Why don't you knock before coming in?
Why would I knock
before coming into my own room?
What? Were you secretly watching porn?
No, what porn? What are you saying?
I suppose you don't watch that stuff.
You're such an innocent guy.
- Hey.
- Huh?
What? What is it?
Isn't that Sang Yeon guy kind of weird?
He has eyes that are kind of perverted.
I don't know. I didn't notice.
Really? That's strange.
Hey, is this lock broken?
Yeah, it's been broken
for a long time. Why?
No reason.
You were in here?
Gosh, I told you to knock.
Sorry, I didn't know anyone was in here.
What are you doing in here
with your laptop?
Huh? Oh, I'm writing my script.
- I write well in the bathroom.
- Really?
Then go on and write.
I'm just going to wash my hands.
Okay.
- Hey.
- Huh?
What? What is it?
Now that I think about it,
that guy didn't even use toothpaste.
Does it make sense to brush your
teeth without toothpaste?
I suppose you could.
Really?
You can?
Hey, is this lock broken too?
Yes, this one's been
broken for a long time too.
And the second floor guest rooms?
Those are broken too.
None of the locks work in our house.
Then fix them. Just fix them!
Why don't you fix them if you know?
Why? Gosh!
Am I the only owner?
That punk.
No toothpaste?
Did I misunderstand it?
If I do this, will I lose weight?
Here. Wear all of this.
I have to film the bed scene.
Where do you think you're going?
Start your jumping jacks, now.
Shin Soo Jung! Bed scene!
You would walk on fire just to film
a bed scene with Shin Soo Jung.
Not only would I walk on fire,
I'd even jump off a cliff for it.
Get up now!
Shin Soo Jung. Bed scene.
Bed scene!
Shin Soo Jung!
I don't see Doo Shik around.
He went out to meet the director.
He seems busy with that script.
Joon Ki, are you all right?
Joon Ki.
A white tunnel... huh?
You startled me.
What is it? Are you okay?
I'm okay. I think I fainted for a moment.
Even if you have to lose weight,
you should eat something.
You could really die, Joon Ki.
It's okay, it's okay.
I can drink water... water.
No, water is banned starting today.
You're shooting the scene
the day after tomorrow.
You're going too far.
If you don't want to do the bed scene
with Shin Soo Jung...
then you can drink it.
I'm going to do it. I am.
Bed scene.
Yoon Ah, I'm here.
That sounds like Sang Yeon.
Why is that guy here again?
Sang Yeon, what brings you by again?
There's a great pizza place
in my neighborhood.
I bought some for us to eat together.
How unfortunate.
We just ate rice.
What do you mean?
There's always room for pizza.
Thank you.
You're such a pig.
Don't even dream about it.
You cruel girl.
You don't even have blood in your veins.
This pizza is really delicious.
Is it?
Sang Yeon, you should eat it too.
No, thank you. I had some already.
Yoon Ah, you should eat lots.
Yes, thank you.
Excuse me.
- What?
- What were you just doing?
- What did I do?
- What's wrong, Dong Gu?
That guy was sniffing Yoon Ah's hair.
Me? I wasn't doing that.
I was smelling the pizza.
I saw it very clearly.
Are you going to keep lying?
Oh, I'm sure you saw wrong.
Why would Sang Yeon smell my hair?
That's what I'm wondering!
What's wrong with smelling hair?
I often smell your hair.
My hair? Why, why, why?
There's a yummy smell
coming from your hair.
- Black bean noodles are tasty.
- What are you doing?
Stop that, stop that!
I really saw him smelling Yoon Ah's hair.
- Why are you being so rude?
- I really saw it.
I really saw it. I did!
I'm going crazy here.
Seriously, now.
Sang Yeon, I'm sorry.
I'll apologize on his behalf.
No, it's my fault for
causing the misunderstanding.
Wow.
I'll take a look around
the guest house while you all eat.
Sure.
Yoon Ah...
You have something on your lip.
Oh, thank you.
It was just a birthmark.
Should I head this way?
Yes, you can look around.
Why are you taking that?
Why is he taking that?
Dong Gu, what's with you?
He took that tissue with him!
Dong Gu, calm down.
Wow! I'm truly going insane.
He put the tissue in here...
Joon Ki, you have no right to eat!
What about the bed scene? Bed scene!
Shut up!
Yoon Ah's scent.
I think that Sang Yeon
really likes you, Yoon Ah.
How do you feel about him?
I told you it's not like that.
Don't be like that and date him.
He's good looking, gentle,
and I heard he has a nice car.
That means he's successful too--
Stop that. What's with you?
Oh, I thought you should eat more pizza.
You like pizza.
What is he doing
that he's not coming back?
Jesus. Wow.
Yoon Ah.
Ah... be brave.
Yoon Ah. Yoon Ah.
- What are you doing here?
- What?
Well, actually...
Why are you wearing Yoon Ah's clothes?
What's going on here?
Oh my. Sang Yeon!
Why are you in my clothes...
Wait... this is all
a misunderstanding, Yoon Ah.
Misunderstanding?
You were caught red-handed.
Sang Yeon, what's going on here?
Well, I...
Well, to tell you the truth...
I wanted to know what your size was.
I wanted to buy you a coat as a gift.
Your coat looked so worn down.
Wait. What did you say?
You could ask her yourself
if you need to know her size.
Also, the sizes are on the clothing tag.
Why would you try it on?
If I asked her myself,
then Yoon Ah would know.
Her pride might be hurt,
so I couldn't ask her.
And the coat is so old that
the size was erased from the tag.
That's why I tried it on.
Are you satisfied?
Oh, that's what it was.
We didn't even know.
Hey, you believe him?
Even so, why would a guy
try on a woman's clothes?
Why not?
I put on Seo Jin's clothes sometimes.
Why would you? Why?
I wear them down to get back at her.
That's why I wear them.
What? Are you crazy?
I am sorry though.
I think I made you
uncomfortable again, Dong Gu.
I only had good intentions.
I will get going now.
Oh! He smelled it!
- Sang Yeon, Sang Yeon!
- Did you see?
Dong Gu, what is the matter with you?
I'm telling you I saw it!
Thank you for the ride.
Writer Bong, did you finish
watching that movie I gave you?
Oh, you mean "Free Wife"?
Yes, a bit.
She was a very free wife.
Not a bad movie, right? Here.
Try this one.
This one is a masterpiece
of erotic films.
Ah, okay.
- Drive home safely.
- All right.
Why does he keep giving me these?
I have nowhere to watch.
What is it this time?
"Sweet Whip:
I can't forget the taste."
It's even more erotic this time.
I'm scared someone will see.
Sang Yeon,
you can't just leave like this.
I'll apologize on his behalf.
No, Yoon Ah. I don't think I should stay
while being suspected of these things.
What are you doing, Dong Gu?
Apologize to him.
Why should I?
What did I do wrong?
He's leaving because of you.
Are you going to be this way?
Wait, wait!
What is this?
Aren't these women's panties?
No, these...
are my panties.
What? You claim these are yours?
These hot, red panties with lace?
Yes, I like this kind of design.
It gives my heart peace.
You are shameless, so shameless.
Even if they are yours, why would
anyone carry around women's panties?
Why not?
When I'm in a bad mood--
Shut up! Get away from me!
Oh, hey!
Tell us the truth.
Are these really yours?
I told you they are.
I have many of them at my home.
Would you like to come with me to see?
Hold on.
Those look like my panties.
I'm right. These are mine!
They're yours? Really?
What did you say? Jesus, that can't be.
Those hot, red, sexy lace panties
do not belong to Yoon Ah?
You must be crazy.
Damn it!
Why are you disappointed?
I thought they were yours!
You punk. Get over here!
Are you a total pervert?
A pervert? Aren't you being too severe?
I am so offended that
I must leave this place.
How could they not be Yoon Ah's?
- Oh no.
- Where do you think you're going?
Ouch!
What is this?
"I can't forget the taste."
"Sweet Whip"?
This guy really is a pervert.
What do you mean by pervert?
Also, that's not mine.
If it's not yours, whose is it?
Huh, huh, huh?
It really isn't mine. Believe me!
Why, you scoundrel...
This won't do, Dong Gu. Call the cops.
Yeah, call the cops.
The cops? Hold on!
Okay, I'll be honest.
I stole these panties.
I'll admit to that.
However, that CD is not mine.
You have to believe me.
If it's not yours,
then whose is it?
Speak up.
I saw it fall from your hand.
What? You're saying
it belongs to Doo Shik?
Do you know how innocent this guy is?
He's like a clean, white paper
that hasn't even held a girl's hand yet.
Why won't you believe me?
I saw it fall out of your...
Shut your mouth, you punk!
Do I look like I'd watch this crap?
What do you take me for?
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
I said shut up!
You're dead, you pervert. Follow me.
- It wasn't me.
- Be quiet!
- Dong Gu!
- Get him!
This scene would work best
if you did it yourself.
I told you already.
I promised my parents that
I would never film a bed scene!
I was just making a suggestion.
Hello, I'm here.
Wow! He really lost a lot of weight.
How much did you lose?
- 10 kilograms.
- What?
10 kilograms.
Ah... 10 kilograms.
Wow, you must've
suffered a lot. Good job.
No, it was nothing.
Oh, Soo Jung.
Be careful.
Joon Ki, it's okay. You're almost there.
Joon Ki, you can do it.
Hello.
I'm Lee Joon Ki who will be
doing this scene with you.
It's an honor to meet you.
Is that so?
- It's nice to meet you.
- It's nice to meet you too.
Director.
Who is this woman?
Oh, she's Soo Jung's stand-in
for the bed scene.
Stand-in?
Shin Soo Jung isn't doing it?
Did you think you were shooting
the bed scene with Shin Soo Jung?
Oh...
Shin Soo Jung!
Bed scene!
What's wrong, Joon Ki?
- Director.
- Huh?
Soo Jung just called.
She feels that using a stand-in
isn't right to the viewers.
She says she will
film the bed scene herself.
Really?
That's good news for me.
Looks like you will be doing
the bed scene with Soo Jung.
- Get ready.
- Yes, Director.
I'll get ready quickly.
- Wait, Director.
- Yeah?
What?
I will do that bed scene.
Why are you suddenly doing the bed scene?
I just suddenly changed my mind.
Why now of all times?
Director, can you take him away?
Hurry, hurry.
You're doing this to do a bed scene
with Shin Soo Jung, aren't you?
I know everything, you jerk!
I worked so hard for this!
What did I say?
I told you he was weird.
There was the underwear,
but he said that CD was yours too.
- Don't you agree?
- Huh?
Yeah. I know.
Anyway, sorry for doubting you.
We thought you were jealous
because you liked Yoon Ah.
Hey, does it make sense
for me to like Yoon Ah?
Also, jealousy?
Goodness, how absurd.
What was that?
Isn’t that Joon Ki?
Why isn't he at the film shoot?
I don't know.
Why is he acting crazy?
Joon Ki, Joon Ki!
What's going on with him?
Excuse me.
I go to the same academy as Yoon Ah.
Is Yoon Ah home?
Yes, why do you need to see her?
I wanted to ask her out on a date.
Ah...
a date.
But, did you know this about her?
What?
The truth about Yoon Ah is...
That bastard!
Soo Jung said she would do the shoot
and he steals it away from me?
I worked so hard to lose that weight.
Yoon Ah, you're home?
- Yeah.
- Why do you look that way?
There are some strange rumors
about me in my class.
People say that
I'm addicted to plastic surgery.
What? Addicted to plastic surgery?
Yes, and I heard people say I have
loans from loans sharks and debts.
There's even a rumor that I'm a man.
That I was in the marines.
And I can bite through steel
with my teeth.
What kind of crazy person
would start rumors like that?
I don't know.
People were asking me about it.
They actually believe it?
What? Why are you
looking at me like that?
Fine. I did it, okay?
It's all for your mom's sake.
I'm worried that she'll meet
some sort of pervert and suffer.
It's the truth.
Don't get the wrong idea.
There's no one this week too.
Why aren't there any guests lately?
Maybe because it's so cold.
What if our business goes into ruin?
Yeah, the landlady called
about the rent yesterday.
She even sent a certification
of our business contents.
It's okay, it's okay.
Hi.
Pres... President.
- What brings you by?
- What else?
I came for the unpaid rent.
The rent?
Business just hasn't
been very good lately.
So, you're saying you don't have it?
Get started.
- What?
- Start what?
- Who are you people?
- Why are you running around?
This is very familiar.
- What is this?
- A seizure, seizure...
- You can't do this.
- Is this a drama or something?
Is our business really over, Seo Jin?
Where's Dong Gu?
When is he coming, Seo Jin?
You can't take that, Mister.
[Marriage Is a Crazy Thing]
I'm home.
Why are you all just sitting there?
- President.
- Long time no see, President Kang.
- What's with the baby?
- Pardon?
Ah, uh...
She's Dong Gu's baby.
Dong Gu got in some trouble.
He did what?
- So, this is his baby?
- Yes.
He's already poor and now he has
a baby to take care of.
There are the baby diapers,
formula, and so many other costs.
We had actually saved up money
to pay you the rent owed.
We had to use all of it
because of the baby.
Oh my. I see.
What about the baby's mom?
The baby's mom?
Oh, the mom is...
She ran away.
She said she couldn't
live like this any longer.
What kind of a mother does that?
Yes, we can leave if you tell us to.
However, on these freezing streets
we will be fine,
but what about this baby?
This poor baby.
That isn't our problem.
I think we should forcefully evict.
Stop, Lawyer Kim.
I will wait exactly one month.
I'm only doing this for the baby,
so you have to pay me back.
Really? Thank you.
Thank you so much!
Forget it and just
take good care of the baby.
- Yes.
- Let's go, Lawyer Kim.
You poor baby.
So upsetting.
Goodbye.
- Bye.
- Have a nice day!
I thought we were getting kicked out.
Still, why make up that kind of lie?
What could I do?
Don't you see all those red stickers?
We'd be on streets if I hadn't lied.
What if we get caught later?
Why would we?
It's not like she's hanging around
the community center here.
What do we do now?
We managed to buy one month,
but what do we do next month?
We'll figure it out.
It's okay, it's okay.
Oh, Su Ah.
Oh, Doo Shik.
It's been a long time.
Have you been doing well?
Yes, pretty much. Is Dong Gu doing okay?
Huh? Yeah, pretty much.
Why are you at a real estate place?
I put my place up.
Yoon Seok is opening a few locations
in the US and wants me to come.
- How long are you staying?
- One or two years.
- I could end up staying there too.
- Oh?
I have a lot to prepare,
so I'll get going.
- Bye, then.
- Okay.
Bye.
Looks like she might end up
marrying that guy.
Yeah.
If Dong Gu finds out,
he'll be down for days.
We don't have to tell him.
Why bother telling him
when he's in a good place now?
Oh, isn't that the landlady’s car?
I think you're right.
Why is she headed toward our place?
I have a bad feeling.
I'm back.
- You're back?
- Yes.
- Did you get your wisdom teeth out?
But...
what is all of this?
It was just some business.
I'll tell you later.
- Does it hurt a lot?
- No.
If only it would stop bleeding.
That's how it usually is.
You'll have to suffer for a day.
Really?
I'd better change the cotton gauze.
Where did I put that again?
Here we are.
Hello, did you need a room?
I'm not a guest.
- Who are you?
- Pardon me?
I'm Han Yoon Ah.
What is it, Sol? Are you hungry?
Should Mommy feed you?
- Mom? You're the baby's mom?
- Yes.
- When did you return?
- What?
- I just got back from the hospital.
- Hospital?
Why were you at the hospital?
Ah, for the past few days--
Wait, wait!
You scared me.
Why are you suddenly screaming?
Sorry, President.
What brought you back here?
I felt so bad for the baby
that I bought some diapers.
Why is it so noisy? What's...
- President!
- President Kang.
When did you find the baby's mom?
Yes, what happened was...
- So--
- By the way...
why was she in the hospital?
The hospital? Oh, um...
So, she was passed out in the hospital.
We brought her home.
- That's what happened.
- She passed out?
What's wrong with you?
What? I just...
Oh! Blood.
Oh, not again.
Ew.
Seo Jin, hurry up.
- Take Yoon Ah to her room to rest.
- Yes, okay.
- Let's go.
- Hurry.
- Why?
- Just go on.
- Go on with her.
- You need to rest, Yoon Ah.
Get some rest.
Oh my.
How sick is she
that she's vomiting blood?
Yes, so it's...
No, there's no time for this.
Get her to the hospital.
- No, no!
- Why?
Well, we brought her home because
the hospital said they can't do anything.
What?
Then, it's untreatable?
Uh, yes.
Ter... terminal stage?
Yes, yes.
How could such a thing
happen to a young person?
President Kang, it must be so hard.
What?
- Oh, yes.
- Be good to your baby's mom.
Make sure she's happy until the end.
Have you two even had a wedding?
A wedding? Uh...
I suppose you two wouldn't have
had the time to have a wedding.
I feel so sorry for the baby's mom.
She'll never get to wear a wedding dress.
You should still stay strong,
President Kang.
Yes, thank you.
I'll get going.
Thank you for the diapers.
Goodbye, President.
Goodbye.
That was a close call.
Why did you have to lie?
We nearly got caught.
We got through it.
Nothing will happen.
- Don't worry.
- What if we get caught?
Take the diapers.
Look at you taking those. Gosh.
This is so crazy.
What do you think of this place?
What... what is this?
Oh, I want to hold a wedding
for the two of you.
- What?
A wedding?
Don't worry. I'll cover the costs.
Oh no. It's okay. It really is.
You don't know how women feel.
A woman who doesn't get to wear a
wedding dress will regret it forever.
No, I don't need to wear a wedding dress.
I want to do it for you. I want to.
Honestly, I've been busy
making a living for myself.
I never had a wedding with my husband.
So, I never got to wear a wedding dress.
Oh, I see.
So, I know just how you feel.
Don't feel burdened by it
and have the wedding.
No, it really is okay.
Are you going to continue
rejecting my kind offer?
Don't do it then.
Instead, leave the building right away.
What? How does that work?
Make a decision.
Lose the business or get married.
We'll do it.
We can do it.
You should have said so.
I think doing it
as soon as possible is best.
How is Sunday?
This coming Sunday?
She's not feeling well,
so it'd be best to do it quickly.
Ah, okay.
What?
She's planning a wedding for you?
That's what I said.
Why would you make up
that useless lie and create this mess?
I didn't know this would happen.
This isn't right at all.
This is marriage fraud.
I should go to her and tell the truth.
Hey, hey, hey!
- What?
- Are you crazy?
Don't you know her temper?
If she finds out that we lied,
she'll sue us on top of kicking us out.
What am I supposed to do, then?
Dong Gu, I'm sorry.
Can you just look the other way
and do the wedding?
- Joon Ki!
- You're crazy.
What can we do, then?
We can't be kicked out on the street
in this cold weather.
You and Yoon Ah...
just do it.
Stop it, stop it!
We really don't need a ring.
It's okay, President.
I want to get you rings.
Go on and pick one.
Oh, Dong Gu!
Oh, Sang Pil.
It's been a long time.
Have you been doing well?
Yes, I've been okay.
Who is that?
Oh, this...
Ah, your girlfriend?
Well, actually...
Bride and groom, how are these?
This is the most popular design.
Bride and groom?
What's this? You're getting married?
Oh, that...
Yes, I'm getting married.
Why didn't you contact me?
When is it?
Oh, that.
This Sunday.
Then you should have contacted me.
You really are something.
Don't worry, man.
As for all our classmates, seniors,
juniors, and professors
I'll bring them all,
even the club members.
Congratulations on
getting married, Dong Gu.
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
I'm so thankful, I could cry.
I'm going crazy.
Why did I have to see Sang Pil there?
Oh, Sang Pil.
Sergeant Kang?
Oh, Officer Kim.
.
How have you been?
Pretty good.
- It's been a long time.
- President Kang.
How's this?
You have to wear a tuxedo
for your wedding, right?
- Yes.
- A wedding?
Are you getting married?
Oh, the thing is...
Yes, I'm getting married.
Really? When?
- This Sunday.
- Sunday?
You should've told me earlier.
I feel a little hurt.
Don't feel hurt.
There is a reason for it.
A reason? What is it?
What? How did things end up like that?
Stay strong, Sergeant Kang.
Yeah, thanks.
You are doing a great thing.
This is a warm, touching story.
I don't know about that.
I only want these two to be happy.
Anyway, I will contact
our platoon and squadron.
Oh no. There's no need for that.
Hey now, we should be together
when things are tough.
Like being loyal in battle, right?
That's right!
All right. Thanks.
You are full of loyalty in battle.
This is really crazy.
Does marrying make sense?
You're laughing? You can actually laugh?
It's just kind of amazing.
What is?
I imagined these things
a lot when I was younger.
"Where will I get married
when I grow up?"
"What kind of wedding dress will I wear
and what kind of bouquet will I have?"
I gave up on all of that after I had Sol.
Somehow, I'm having a wedding.
Oh, I'm tired from going here
and there all day, aren't you?
I don't know.
I went around in such a daze
that I can't even feel fatigue.
I wish this was all a dream.
Yoon Ah, should we tell her the truth...
What's this?
You fell asleep in that time?
Geez, life is so
simple for you, isn't it?
Oh, gosh.
Gosh.
Pillow.
Geez.
This lady requires so much care.
We're home.
Here comes the new groom.
I was just joking. It was a joke.
You looked down,
so I was trying to make you feel better.
How can you joke?
Do you know what happened to me today?
Do you know what kind of
huge mess you've created?
Hold on, here. What is this?
Isn't this President Kim?
What is it?
There's an article about her.
What kind of article?
"President Kim of Huam-dong
is melting this cold winter."
"Couple Kang Dong Gu and Han Yoon Ah
who can't pay rent and run a guest house"
"will have their wedding
paid for by President Kim."
Who wrote this article?
Who would write such a thing?
Reporter Kim Tae Yong?
I became a reporter.
Officer Kim!
That crazy idiot.
Why would he write this?
Why doesn't he write something else?
Hello, this is Waikiki.
Yes, hello.
Hello, this is the singer, Wheesung.
What? Singer, Wheesung?
- Wheesung?
- Wrong number.
No, I really am Wheesung. I really am.
Oh, really?
- Hello, I'm Park Hyo Shin.
- What?
Let's have a song battle.
Good person.
Even if we part...
Don't prank call. Hang up.
I even thought of marrying you.
It really sounds like him.
What is this about?
You read the article?
What? You want to
sing a song at the wedding?
It's really Wheesung?
Wheesung, hold on.
I have another call.
Hello, this is Waikiki.
Designer Park Sool Nyeo?
- What?
You want to give them hanbok to wear?
This is becoming a big blockbuster.
We can't live in this country
if we get caught.
People will beat us to death.
Who? Chef Lee Yeon Bok?
[We will not be receiving gifts.]
Dong Gu! Congratulations!
Thank you. You really brought everyone.
- Yes.
- Looks good.
- Congrats.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Go on in.
- Congratulations!
Let's give him a salute.
To the new groom!
Unity!
Unity.
Sergeant Kang.
Officer Kim, I read your article.
Congratulations.
Hey, congrats!
Thank you.
- Congratulations.
- Congrats!
- You look good.
- So handsome.
- Congratulations.
- We'll be inside.
Thank you.
Uh... are you okay, Dong Gu?
Do I look okay to you?
My college classmates,
professors, army friends...
Even the chairman of the women's group.
I really am a married man now.
At least everyone is talking about
how pretty the bride is.
You haven't seen Yoon Ah
in her dress, have you?
Awesome. So pretty.
Really awesome!
What about it?
I should be happy about a pretty wife?
Wow, I'm so happy about my pretty wife.
Calm down.
Calm? Do you think I can be calm?
This is your fault.
You're not even a friend.
- You're an enemy.
- What are you all doing?
It's almost time to start the wedding.
Hurry on in.
- Yes, we'll be there.
- We should start soon.
I have to go in first.
- See you later, Dong Gu.
- Bye.
- Do a good job.
- Get ready.
Okay.
Starting now, we will start the union
of groom Kang Dong Gu
and the bride Han Yoon Ah.
Groom, please enter.
You should salute.
You look good!
You're doing well.
He wasn't so good in the army.
Isn't the groom strong?
Now, today's real star.
February's bride.
Please applaud for Han Yoon Ah.
Bride, please enter.
Salute to the bride!
Unity!
She's really pretty.
Dong Gu, Dong Gu...
Kang Dong Gu.
Love is delicious. Love is precious.
Split in half
and share it with each other.
Always keep it in your heart.
Spend every moment together.
Thank you. Thank you.
Wheesung.
I truly want to congratulate you
and pray that you'll be happy forever.
I usually cost more money.
I sang for free today.
In return...
I would like to request
a passionate kiss from the couple.
A passionate kiss, yes.
Don't try to back out now.
Kiss, kiss, kiss!
This is crazy.
Kiss, kiss, kiss, kiss!
Kiss, kiss, kiss!
Dong Gu, just do it.
- What?
- Let's just kiss.
How can we just kiss?
Enjoy your honeymoon.
Use this to buy your wife
whatever she wants.
Yes. Thank you.
You should get going.
Have a nice trip.
Yes, we'll get going.
Shall we get going, Yoon Ah...
I mean, Honey.
Let's do that, Honey.
Yes.
Dong Gu.
Dong Gu?
- Dong Gu.
- Huh?
Why? What?
- What have you been thinking about?
- What?
I wasn't thinking about anything.
How long do we have to wait here?
They said they'd call once she left,
so let's wait a little bit.
Oh, President Kang.
- Lawyer Kim.
- What are you doing here?
Oh, you're going on your honeymoon.
Yes, I am.
Oh, yeah. You're going
to Jeju Island, aren't you?
I'm going there on a business trip.
What time is your flight?
It's the 6:30 pm flight.
Mine is at 6:30 pm too.
We're on the same plane.
We're sitting next to each other.
That's amazing.
It's time to go. Let's go.
Dong Gu, what do we do?
I don't know. I'm going crazy.
Hurry up.
Their flight probably landed by now.
I hope they had a nice trip
and she wasn't sick.
What's this?
This slippery, bad feeling.
What kind of dog pooped here?
The house feels empty without  those two.
I know.
Dong Gu and Yoon Ah must be back.
Should we go pick them up?
Why bother?
It's not a real honeymoon.
Why should we pick them up?
How did they happen to meet
Lawyer Kim at the airport?
I know.
Do you think...
Dong Gu and Yoon Ah will
develop feelings for each other?
I doubt it.
It's just a relief that we didn't
get caught by President Kim.
I never dreamed that she would think
Dong Gu and Yoon Ah were married.
- What do you mean?
- Oh my gosh!
President Kim.
What are they if
they're not a married couple?
You didn't lie to me, did you?
That's not it, President Kim...
Tell me the truth now!
President Kim, President Kim.
I'm sorry, President Kim.
It wasn't on purpose and honestly--
Shut your mouth
and put your print on that.
What is this?
Payment contract regarding wedding costs.
If you can't repay it in one month
this is a polite warning that
something scary could happen.
By something scary,
what do you mean by that?
Multiply it by 100.
Think of the most terrible thing you can.
I would like to stick you all in jail.
I'm stopping at this
because I feel bad for the baby.
Put your fingerprint on it now.
Still, how can we pay
all of this back in one month?
Do you want to go to jail?
I just need to put my print here?
What will you do now?
There are no guests and you have a debt.
I don't know.
This is all because of that guy,
Lee Joon Ki.
I'm going home and I won't
let him get away with it.
That was so scary.
He could cause an accident.
Why is he going so fast?
Dong Gu?
Dong Gu.
Can you hear me?
Huh... what?
What? Did you say something?
No, I was just saying thank you.
You should look straight ahead
when you're walking.
You really need to be
taken care of all the time.
Come on.
You may as well close your eyes then.
Wait up, Dong Gu.
Su Ah.
Dong Gu.
You...
What are you doing here?
Is something wrong?
What do I do, Dong Gu?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
I can't burden Dong Gu anymore.
How long do I have to stay here?
- Did you pay extra for that?
- What?
Hey, stop right there!
What's wrong with helping out
an ex-girlfriend in trouble?
Here, Su Ah.
- Why are you giving this to me?
- It's pretty.
You're not over Su Ah, right?
Did you get the wrong idea?
Why would I get the wrong idea?
Take good care of Su Ah.
What's this album?
Why did you draw hearts?
- First love.
- How did you meet?
I'm an erotic script writer and
she's an erotic film actress.
Lee Joon Ki,
you brought this on yourself.
Please don't resent me.
Lee Joon Ki, your life's savior!
So, do you have any money?
I'm thinking of doing an eating show.
I need to use my card.
You think anyone can do those?
100 stars if I eat bones?
A complete medical exam?
Is it very bad?