Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
Seo Jin, you should get up now.
You haven't eaten in days.
Yeah, it's not the first
interview you've failed
so how long are you
going to keep this up?
I'm fine. Just leave.
Who told you to slap the interviewer
with the meat, girl?
She says he was sexually harassing her.
Still, does it make sense to slap him?
With meat, at that?
You and that temper of yours.
That's enough!
You scared me.
Why are you screaming?
Also, would you please shave, Seo Jin?
What if our guests see you?
Are you crying?
Do you know how much
I wanted to work there?
Ever since I decided to become a reporter
it was my goal to work there.
You can't even comfort me
and you're picking on me.
That's not what I meant.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry. You'll get a job next time.
Forget it. I have a bad temper.
I can't control my feelings.
Becoming a reporter and getting a job...
I'm going to give up on all of it.
What, give up?
Hey, Kang Seo Jin!
Does it make sense to give up
on your dream over this?
You're acting so pathetic.
The Kang family--
Yes, I'm pathetic!
That's why I'm giving up!
I didn't say much.
Seriously, man.
Read the mood in the room, would you?
- It's not the time for that.
- You have no sense.
Seo Jin, eat first and sleep.
I don't want to.
[You Are Not the Problem!]
How is Seo Jin doing? Did she eat?
No, she won't even leave her room
and she keeps crying.
Gosh, this is a big problem.
Isn't there a way
to make Seo Jin feel better?
Ah, Seo Jin likes to eat chicken feet.
Should we go eat chicken feet tonight?
Do you really think that would
make her feel better?
What Seo Jin needs right now is
sincere consoling, not chicken feet.
Consoling?
Saying things like,
"Pain is a part of youth."
Those things are so cheesy
that I can't say them.
Don't you agree, Yoon Ah?
Yoon Ah...
I wonder how much you need
to set up a store like this?
You would need a ton of money.
You want to open a bakery?
You sure have a big dream of
becoming a patisseur or whatever it is.
Did I say that?
I was just talking to myself.
Can't I even talk to myself?
I realized that you have no sense
when it comes to reading
the mood of a situation.
What did I do?
I only said one thing.
Gosh, why are you
getting irritated with me?
When did I? I have never gotten
irritated with anyone in my life.
You are right now.
When did I? When?
You are getting
irritated with me right now.
Don't you know the meaning of the word?
Hey, what are you doing here?
Are you having a couple's argument?
Don't be ridiculous.
What's with that car?
I'm starting my drama soon,
so I got myself a car.
It's not even a great role.
Why would you buy a car?
Be quiet and get in.
It's cold, so I'll drive you home.
My goodness.
Rebecca!
Welcome.
How old is this thing? Does it even work?
Of course.
Rebecca drives much better
than she looks.
All right, we'll get going then.
Oh, Rebecca...
What happened?
Did the engine just shut off?
It's okay, it's okay.
I can start the engine again.
- What's this?
- It's okay, it's okay.
I can sew the seat belt back on.
This car...
It's okay, it's okay.
What do you mean it's okay?
I want to get out.
What? This isn't opening.
It's not working.
It only opens from the outside.
What?
It's okay, it's okay.
I can get out and open it for you
from the outside.
- Open it right now.
- Hey, Rebecca!
What is this? Why is it falling off?
Leave Rebecca alone.
I can see its insides.
Rebecca is a transparent friend.
Was this car assembled properly?
It worked. Okay, we'll get going now.
Rebecca! My Rebecca!
- What's wrong, Dong Gu?
- I nearly died.
See if I ride in that Rebecca ever again.
What kind of a man is so full of fear?
It's okay, it's okay.
Stop that.
Doo Shik, give Sol to me.
Thanks for watching her.
Let's go to Mommy.
Sol, I missed you.
I missed you so much.
I missed you too, Sol.
What are you doing?
[President is Bruce Lee]
You're faking your views again.
Everyone else does it too.
Why are they so low lately?
It's driving me insane.
Because your writing is darn boring.
Why is it boring?
Doo Shik is a good writer.
Good writer?
You haven't read his latest
web novel, have you?
Listen up.
The president is kidnapped by aliens.
The president then shoots a powerful
wind from his hands and kills the aliens.
But guess who that president is.
The American president.
There's a detailed explanation
that the president
is a reincarnation of Bruce Lee.
You see that?
Does it make sense for Bruce Lee
to shoot strong winds?
Fine. Look down on me.
For that, I won't write a role for you
in my work when I do succeed.
Okay. Thank you.
Move!
- Doo Shik.
- He's angry again. Look at him.
Give it a rest, would you?
What is this book?
"Project to console youths."
"Falling is not failure.
Failure is the inability to get back up."
The words are nice.
It's so cheesy.
What kind of book title is so cheesy?
Do they think those words
make someone feel better?
I really wonder.
I'm so hungry.
I think I'll make some ramen.
- One for me too.
- Then I'll make two.
You scared me!
- Hey.
- Seo Jin.
Hey.
- Kang Seo Jin.
Hey, how long is she
going to keep that up?
I don't know.
I'm worried something will happen to her.
Yoon Ah.
Can you take Seo Jin out
and go get some air?
And console her or something?
What? Me?
Remember what you said earlier?
Seo Jin needs sincere consoling
or something like that.
I'm asking you for this favor, please?
- All right. I'll try.
- Okay.
Wait and see.
I'll succeed no matter what
and get revenge.
- Lee Joon Ki!
- Hey, you.
Didn't I tell you not to do
other things during work?
Sorry, sorry.
If you have nothing to do,
go put this in my house laundry.
Our house entry code is 48914, okay?
All right, just let go of me.
When are you hiring
the other part-time employee?
I already hired someone,
so stop whining.
Here she is.
Say hello.
She'll be starting today.
This is Kim Sun Woo.
She's my daughter.
- What?
- Why are you so shocked?
Hello.
So, don't be hard on her.
Teach her well. Got it?
Yes, Father-in-law.
What?
What? I didn't say anything.
That's strange.
Come on, Dad.
I have to work, so please go.
Go on.
It's hard working
because of my dad, isn't it?
He's a cold guy.
Not at all.
Speak casually to me, please.
I'm much younger than you.
Oh, should I?
What is it that you do, by the way?
I'm actually a writer,
though I'm still aspiring to be one.
Wow, that's amazing.
What do you write?
Scripts.
Oh.
It's my dream to write a pure love story
like Shunji Iwai's "Love Letter."
I love that movie.
Once you finish writing something,
you have to show me first.
- Okay.
- You promised me.
Okay, Wife.
- What?
- Huh?
No, I didn't say anything.
I didn't say a thing.
How many times have we seen this?
Gosh, that "doo, doo, doo."
Just seeing a goldfish
makes me grind my teeth.
Hey, UFC is on right now.
- Should we turn it on?
- Should we?
All right, all right. Watch it.
Just watch it forever.
Doo, doo, doo...
What is this sound?
Where's it coming from?
Hey, was that the sound of your heart?
Joon Ki, I think I'm in love.
Geez.
His sickness is back. It's back again.
- Who is it this time?
- Hm?
It's the convenience store
owner's daughter.
- She's so cute and pretty.
- Not interested!
Didn't I tell you before?
The cuter and prettier a girl is
the chance it works out with you
grows closer to zero.
So, dream on.
It's different this time.
She seems totally interested in me.
Hello? Yes.
A film production company?
Here you go.
I'm the owner and director of
Artist Tak Films, Tak Myung Hwan.
Ah, yes.
Your web novel made quite
the impression me, Writer Bong.
Oh, I see.
Was my web novel that good?
No, that web novel is trash.
Then, why...
However, in your web novel,
"President is Bruce Lee"
there is a bed scene
in book seven, page four.
I dare to say that you are
a genius in writing eroticism.
No, you're like a god.
I'll get to the point.
I would like to hire you for a script.
What? A script?
What kind?
Have you heard of the series,
"Goodbye, Sister-in-law"?
I've never heard of it.
What's it about?
It's an erotic film about forbidden love
between a brother and sister-in-law.
I need a script for
"Goodbye, Sister-In-Law 5"...
What do you take me for?
I don't write things like that.
Paul Verhoeven, Ang Lee, Stanley Kubrick.
- Do you know these three greats?
- Yes.
You must know their works
"Basic Instinct,"
"Lust Caution," and "Eyes Wide Shut."
I'm not trying to make
a mere erotic film with you.
Writer Bong, would you like to make
a great masterpiece with me?
Also, let's go to Cannes together.
What do you think?
Seo Jin, isn't it great being outside?
Doesn't it feel like the weight
on your heart is being lifted?
It's not great at all.
My heart just feels frozen.
Yoon Ah, I'm cold.
Let's go inside.
Wait, I brought you out because
I had something to say.
What is it?
Say it quickly. I'm really cold.
Seo Jin.
"Falling is not failure.
Failure is the inability to get back up."
What?
Do you see that boy?
I don't know how many times
he's fallen to get that kite to fly.
Still, he hasn't given up
and he gets back up.
He succeeded in
flying that kite in the end.
And?
Just like that boy,
get back up again even if you fall.
Someday, you'll be able to fly high
in the sky like that kite.
Wow, look at that kite up in the sky.
Why would I bother looking at it?
I'm freezing to death.
Seo Jin, are you going to be this way?
Fine, I'll look at it.
Why are you telling me to look at it?
Oh no! Seo Jin!
Oh, what do we do? Are you okay?
Seo Jin, are you all right?
Blood, blood.
Blood!
Seo Jin, I'm sorry.
Seo Jin, open the door.
Seo Jin!
I said it's fine! Just leave me alone!
Gosh, I told you to console her.
Why would you go look at kites
and create this situation?
I didn't think this would happen.
I'll try talking to her again.
Forget it. I'll take care of it.
What's so hard about consoling her?
How frustrating.
What is it?
What is it!
Dong Gu?
Why are you waking me up
when I'm sleeping?
We have somewhere to go together.
Where, at this hour?
You'll know once we get there.
Hurry up and get up.
I'm sleepy.
Where are we going now?
Why are we in the mountains
so early in the morning?
Well...
I had something I wanted
to tell you, Seo Jin.
Tell me?
What is it?
Seo Jin. "Falling is not failure."
"Failure is the inability
to get back up."
Seo Jin.
That sun always rises from the east
and sets in the west.
It doesn't stop there. It rotates again.
Then it rises again.
What about it?
So, if you don't stop here
and keep on going
you will shine bright one day
just like that sun.
You know what I'm trying to say, right?
Kiddo, should we go down then?
Seo Jin, want to make a bet
on who gets down first?
Hurry up.
Dong Gu, are you okay?
It hurts! Ow!
I hit it right on the rock,
the soft part of my bone.
Why did you insist on coming here?
Can you stand up?
Ow! I can't get up. I can't!
I hit the bone on the rock!
Ow, it hurts!
You said you have to get back up
even when you fall.
Sorry.
Still, don't forget what I said before.
- Falling is not failure.
- Shut up!
My gosh.
Seo Jin, I'm sorry.
Don't be mad.
I was wrong.
Gosh, after you said
all those thing to me.
It really did hurt.
The soft bone here
went right into the rock.
Be quiet!
You two don't do anything right.
I'll make Seo Jin feel better
for certain.
You two stay out of it.
Don't you know how she feels?
How hard is it to console her?
You two are such amateurs.
What is it now?
What now?
Get up. We have somewhere to go.
Where now?
Seriously, why are
you all doing this to me?
You'll know once we get there.
Hurry and get up.
I really don't want to.
I'm not going.
Hurry.
I don't want to. I'm not going!
I said no! I'm not going.
Oh, what a shock.
Gosh, who is it?
[Sun Woo: Doo Shik.]
It's Sun Woo.
Doo Shik, have you had lunch?
Yes, I had instant black bean...
Spaghetti.
Wow, that must've been so good.
I totally love spaghetti.
Then should we go eat spaghetti sometime?
Really? I would like that.
Oh! She's so cute.
Talk, talk. You have a message.
Oh, it's Director Tak.
Writer Bong,
I read the script you sent me.
But I'm just not feeling the bed scene.
Oh, really?
I've captured a few good bed scenes.
I'll send them to you.
Take a look at them and tell me
which ones you like the feel of.
Hold on. Where did I put them?
Oh, here they are.
- Oh, this one.
- Doo Shik.
Please recommend some movies for me.
The ones that you enjoy watching.
Send.
Ones with this feeling?
All right. That's finished then.
Why isn't Sun Woo replying?
Oh, how? How did this
get sent to Sun Woo?
Damn it!
She hasn't read it yet.
Don't read, don't read.
- Don't read.
- Doo Shik!
Sun Woo.
Hello, sir.
Where are you running off to
like a crazy man?
Is something wrong?
Not at all.
I'm just out for a jog.
Sun Woo, did you see my messages?
You sent me messages?
I didn't see them yet.
My dad suddenly wanted to go out to eat.
I forgot and left my phone.
Oh, is that right?
Why are you sending messages
to my daughter, huh?
It's only because I asked him to
recommend good movies to me.
Let's go eat, Dad.
- We'll get going.
- Okay.
Goodbye.
What a relief.
She hasn't seen them yet. Not yet.
Wait.
If they're going out to eat,
the house is empty.
This is the place.
You woke up a sleeping person
to go for a drive?
What? It's nice.
I do have something
to talk to you about too.
You too?
Why do so many people
want to talk to me lately?
What do you have to say?
Okay, Seo Jin.
"Falling is not failure."
"Failure is the inability
to get back up."
How did you know that?
Did you three plan this?
Why have you all been
saying this since yesterday?
Don't you get it yet?
Seo Jin.
Look at those reeds.
Just look at the field of reeds.
They sway when the wind blows,
but they will never fall.
So?
So, if you can beat out this wind
you can get back up like those reeds
and bloom into a beautiful flower.
Do you understand what I mean?
I do. I understand, so let's go home.
Good kid.
You feel stronger after
hearing my words, don't you?
I feel stronger, okay?
So, please go back home.
Kiddo. You're so cute.
All right. Let's go.
Okay, let's get going then.
We're going now.
What is this?
It's okay, it's okay.
How is it okay? It's stuck.
It will go. Here we go.
Good job, Lee Joon Ki.
What's going on here? What is this?
Hey... hey. What the heck.
Hey, hey. Seo Jin, wake up.
Take this thing off.
I can't drive because of it.
You're really going all out,
aren't you?
What's with this window?
It's broken.
Hurry and get it off.
I'll end up in an accident!
This is crazy.
Where did you buy this car?
Good job.
- What's going on?
- What?
Joon Ki, do something about it!
Hold on.
Ow! It's going up even more.
It won't work. It just won't.
Then stop the car and fix it!
- How can I stop the car here?
- Then you expect me to stay like this?
Just wait. I'll find an intersection
to stop at. Hold on.
My arm hurts.
How could you do this to me?
How could you?
I was always like this.
Didn't you know?
People end up with
other women in life sometimes.
You're overreacting over nothing.
How can you say that?
You jerk!
All right. Hit me once.
Hit me once and let's have
a cool, beautiful goodbye.
Hit me. I'm ready. Come on.
Stop crying now.
Let's have a beautiful goodbye.
Hit me!
Gosh, stairs.
Why do they live up so high?
I'm on the 6th floor.
Apartment 605.
Apartment 605. Apartment 605.
605!
Sun Woo's room, Sun Woo's room!
Bathroom!
No, this isn't it.
Here it is!
There it is.
What is this? I'm going nuts.
How could you leave your wallet
at home when we're going out to eat?
I know. I'm sorry.
I said I'm sorry.
Sun Woo.
Doo Shik said he sent me messages.
What is this?
Let me see.
What is this? That little punk...
He must be crazy!
I ought to just...
No, Dad. Doo Shik's not like that.
He's a very innocent, pure person.
Why do you keep taking his side?
You don't like him, do you?
No, I don't like him yet.
What do you mean no? You do.
Don't you have anyone better around?
Why would you like him?
Forget it. It's none of your business.
Give me my phone.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to confirm with him
that it was sent by mistake. Why?
Talk, talk. Pick up now.
Sir.
This is all a misunderstanding.
It's a misunderstanding.
Sun Woo, it's not what it looks like.
What happened was...
Why is this here?
You perverted creep!
No.
Look here, Kang Seo Jin.
Why did you slap someone
who was just standing there?
It's not that
she slapped him on the face.
Her arm was trapped in the window
and it was accidental.
Does that make sense?
Do you know how injured that man is?
It is true. This is insane.
Why did you have to slap him
and make him faint?
- Hey, hey!
- Are you okay, Seo Jin?
What's going on here?
What happened that
you're at a police station?
Joon Ki, what did you do to her?
I was just driving
and a newspaper suddenly...
- What?
- So...
Her arm got stuck in the window
and suddenly...
I'm not a pervert.
It's all a misunderstanding.
Doo Shik!
- Why are you here?
- Dong Gu!
Let me go.
Dong Gu!
Dong Gu.
What? What is it?
Tell them I'm not a pervert.
He isn't! He isn't. Who said that?
- What a mess this is.
- Who said that?
Hey, why did you go
into their house anyway?
I don't know.
Don't ask me anything.
It's a relief that you've only been
ordered to stay 100 meters away.
They'd put an
electronic monitoring device on you
if things didn't go your way.
Seo Jin, I'm sorry.
I didn't do it on purpose and
I was really just trying to console you--
Who asked you to do that?
I just asked you to leave me alone.
I already feel bad enough.
Why are you all doing this?
I didn't do anything.
Hey, hey. Seo Jin, Seo Jin.
I said I'm sorry.
What can I do to make you not angry?
I'll do anything you tell me to.
I'll die if you tell me to.
What is that? A strip show?
I'll even do that too.
Just say the word.
You can all do it too, right?
- I'll do it.
- Sure, I will.
- Then do it.
- Okay. What should I do?
- Strip show.
- What?
Now?
Here? In this weather?
What? You can't do it?
Then don't ever talk to me again.
Got it?
Seo... Seo... Seo Jin.
Hey, Seo Jin!
Strip show.
Kang Seo Jin!
What?
- What's this?
- Hey, Dong Gu.
Joon Ki, what are you doing?
What? You said to do a strip show.
What are you two doing? Come on.
What are you doing? Just do it.
I just got let go by the cops.
Do it, do it.
So cold, so cold. Kang Seo Jin!
You didn't do anything wrong.
Hey, what's wrong with hitting a guy
who sexually harassed you?
Isn't that right?
Yeah, guys like that deserve a beating.
Does it make sense to give up on
a dream because of a guy like that?
Soon, you'll get a job at a good place.
- Don't worry.
- That's right.
Oh yeah.
So stay strong, girl!
Yeah.
You've got this!
- You've got this!
Crazy.
Stop it, already.
People are watching.
What are you doing?
- You laughed!
- You laughed.
- She's not mad anymore.
- She laughed.
All right. I'm not mad anymore.
So put on your clothes.
- Hurry up.
- Get dressed.
What are you doing there?
- Oh no!
- Run!
I'm not a pervert!
Seriously, why is he doing that?
Oh, that pervert.
Sun Woo!
I'm sorry!
I...
have been ordered to stay
100 meters away from you!
I can't be close to you!
What's he saying?
Sun Woo!
I'm sorry!
I guess I am a man, after all!
To tell you the truth,
I'm writing a script for an erotic film!
I really am sorry...
Get moving quickly.
The group is checking in soon.
Okay.
Even if it's a group,
do we have to give up our rooms?
Where are we supposed to sleep?
Sleep wherever in the living room.
We haven't had a group booking
in a long time.
Yeah, let's think about
all the rent we owe and endure it.
The landlady called again earlier.
Really? Is she telling us
to move our business out again?
- Yes.
- That's a big problem.
We're so busy.
What's that guy been doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm regulating my condition.
- Mind control.
- Mind control, what a joke.
Leave him alone.
His first drama shoot is today.
He tries to copy everything
that the celebrities do.
Doesn't he, Yoon Ah?
- Yoon Ah?
- Huh?
- What?
- What's wrong with you?
Are you sick?
- I haven't felt well since this morning.
- Really?
Look at all this sweat.
What? You're boiling hot!
This is the seasonal flu.
What? The seasonal flu?
Yes, but you don't
need to worry that much.
Most people get better
after resting and taking medicine.
However, it's highly contagious,
so she should isolate herself.
It's very contagious? How contagious?
Extremely.
It can be easily transferred
through coughing.
[Complete Feeding]
Sorry, I know there's
a group booking coming in too.
No, it's just a relief you'll
get better with rest and medicine.
What do we do though?
We can't have our guests infected.
That's true.
We have to quarantine her,
but our rooms are taken up by guests.
There are no rooms left.
What do we do?
Should we get a motel room, then?
What? Hey, man.
How can you send
a woman alone to a motel?
You are so cold.
If you're so worried about her,
take off that mask.
I have my first shoot today.
You understand, don't you?
Of course.
Thank you.
A motel is not right.
Guests there could get infected too.
I suppose.
Then what should we do?
This really isn't right.
How can a sick person stay here?
Do you have another solution?
Should we cancel the group booking?
- Still, this is kind of--
- Hey.
No, I'll be all right.
There are the guests,
but I can't have Sol get sick.
There's an electric blanket.
There's a heater in there too,
so it won't be as cold.
Honestly, you hold some responsibility
for not taking care of yourself.
It may not be comfy, but endure it.
Hey, why would you say
such a nasty comment?
You cold punk.
Shut the door.
Wait. What about the bathroom?
Ah, I didn't think of that.
The bathroom...
Hey, this really isn't right.
Yeah, you punk.
This is a violation of human rights.
How can you tell an adult to
go about their business here?
Do you think I want to do this?
Where did you even get this?
I borrowed it from
Mi Dal Restaurant down there.
Her daughter, Mi Dal, used this.
Music comes out if you press this,
so it's less embarrassing.
As if it's less embarrassing!
You are the cruelest person.
That's enough, everyone.
I'm okay. Please watch Sol for me.
Don't worry about Sol, Yoon Ah.
All right, the guests
will be here soon. Let's go.
It's almost time.
Why aren't they coming?
They'll be here soon.
Do you really think Yoon Ah will be okay?
I worried with the weather being so cold.
Yeah, I know.
What did you say before?
She should endure it
since she's responsible
for not taking care of herself?
What did I do wrong?
- It's true that she didn't.
- Why, you...
Oh, here they come. They're here!
Over here!
Seo Jin, go on
and take them to their rooms.
Okay.
Aloha!
Hey. Good afternoon.
Wow, how long has it been
since we've had a group booking?
So, Dong Gu, you know
what I mentioned about...
- Hey.
- Huh?
You have a runny nose.
Runny nose?
Oh, why do I have a runny nose?
Get over here.
What is this? You have a fever too.
You don't have...
No way. I doubt it. It can't be.
- I said I don't.
- Get away from me!
Germs!
My goodness. Geez.
Dong Gu.
Why do you have that blanket?
He has the flu too.
Get in. Hurry up and get in.
I will go in. Stop poking me.
What's taking you so long to get in?
Did you get it from me,
by any chance?
Who else would I get it from then?
I was supposed to shoot
a baby's 100th day tomorrow.
This is crazy.
I will turn left.
I will turn right.
Right turn... right turn.
Why is my throat so tight?
I'm not sick too, am I?
This is my first day.
I have to do well and not make mistakes.
Gosh. Who did this?
My neck, my eyes!
Seriously!
Who did this?
Oh! My eyes and neck.
My Rebecca! No, my Rebecca!
Where are you looking when you drive?
Sorry, I'm a beginner driver.
Don't bring your car out
if you can't drive, then.
How unlucky of me.
I'm in a rush so give me
your contact information.
Yes, yes.
Hurry it up!
- Hurry and give me your business card!
- Yes, I'm sorry.
Gosh, the roads are scary.
You're a murderer in waiting.
What are you thinking?
Ouch, my eye.
Don't you cry, Rebecca. My Rebecca.
Oh, I'm in pain.
Hello, Director.
Oh, you're here?
Your eye...
and what's wrong with your neck?
I got in a little car accident
on my way here.
But it won't affect the shoot in any way.
Okay, that's a relief.
Did you practice a lot?
Of course, there is no need to worry.
This is why I like you, Joon Ki.
Director, Writer Kwon is here.
Writer Kwon?
- Joon Ki.
- Yes?
You haven't met Writer Kwon, right?
- No.
- Come. I'll introduce you.
- Introduce me?
- Yeah.
You are the driver.
Yes.
Writer Kwon!
Oh, you scared me.
You must be busy writing.
Why did you bother coming?
Oh, where did he go?
- Who?
- Let's just go.
Let's take a 10 minute break!
That driver is...
Dong Gu, I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
It's fine.
Yoon Ah.
Can I give you a piece of advice?
What is it?
Do you know that you're sort of
a nuisance type of character?
You don't do it on purpose.
You cause harm to others
and end up indebted to people.
It's really not a good thing.
It starts to become a habit.
I'm saying this out of concern for you,
so don't be offended by it.
Okay, I'll be careful from now on.
I hate to cause others harm
and be indebted more than anything.
I really don't understand it.
For goodness' sake.
I don't know how you can bear it.
Over here.
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
It's cold, isn't it?
- Sit, sit.
- Yes.
- I'm pushing the chair in.
- Thank you.
Here you go.
How are you feeling?
Oh, I'm feeling just fine.
I think I feel healthier
now that I've been in the accident.
My appetite is back.
That's a relief.
But why did you want to meet?
Ah, yes.
Honestly, I wondered if
I was too rude this morning.
I thought, perhaps, I hurt your feelings.
You don't know how much I worried.
Not at all.
Actually, I wasn't in
my right mind this morning.
I don't know if I should say this
to someone I just met.
It's my childhood friend...
He passed away this morning.
His name was Kang Dong Gu.
He was like a brother to me.
Oh, I see.
Now that I think about it,
he came to this restaurant regularly.
Dong Gu.
There. You can eat this one.
You really don't have to do that.
Just eat that one.
It's because I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Hold on. It's a little chilly, isn't it?
Excuse me, waitress.
Could you bring us a lap blanket?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Please eat.
I don't know if the food
was to your liking.
It was so delicious.
What a relief.
Then will you forget about
my mistake this morning?
Of course.
Then, please get home safely.
I'll get going now. Bye.
- Wait.
- What is it?
By any chance,
do you have a girlfriend?
What? A girlfriend?
I don't. Why do you ask?
What? So, you're dating that writer?
What was I supposed to do?
If I'd rejected her,
it'd be worse than when I yelled at her.
I'll just have to date her
while I do the drama.
You make your life so difficult.
You really do.
Wait. What time is it?
Food's here! Eat your food!
- Hey.
- I'm busy. I have to go.
That guy is just feeding us like animals.
You're just leaving the food?
This isn't a prison.
I'll go get it.
Forget it. I'll go get it.
So cold.
Let's see what it is.
Dong Gu!
- My back, my back.
- Are you okay?
- Dong Gu!
- My back.
Are you okay?
I'm okay... I'm oka--
Oh, that hurts.
I can't move.
Aren't you eating, Dong Gu?
I'm going to eat. My gosh.
Oh, my back. Seriously.
Yoon Ah, can you help me up?
Why?
I thought you couldn't
bear to be indebted to others.
You said that'd be a nuisance
and it gets to be a habit.
Never mind, then.
I was only asking to see.
I'll lie down and eat.
No need to say that
with big, round eyes.
Why isn't this working?
Should I feed you?
- No thanks.
- Forget it if you don't want me to.
If you insist on feeding me,
then you can do so.
Gosh.
Yoon Ah, like I told you earlier
I'm not the type of person
to be indebted to others.
Okay? So, don't get the wrong idea.
Water, water, water!
Here.
I nearly died.
I really don't rely on others like this.
All right. I got it, so just eat.
- "Ah."
- Yoon Ah!
One ham wrapped in dried seaweed.
Rice comes after.
Oh, I have to pee.
Did I drink too much water?
Ah, I'm going crazy here.
Oh my.
Dong Gu, are you all right?
Where are you trying to go right now?
I wanted to get some air.
You're not even feeling well.
Why would you go outside?
Lie down again.
I have to pee.
What did you say?
I said I have to pee.
- What?
- I said I have to pee...
We're here, so stop.
Right here.
Go down right where you're standing.
There you go.
Dong Gu, can you undo your zipper?
Of course, I can undo my zipper.
What do you take me for?
I told you I don't like
to be indebted to others.
You may go now.
She's going to hear everything.
This is driving me nuts.
Seriously, now.
Yes.
Yes, Hye Jin.
Yes, see you tonight.
Yes, yes.
Oh, that's hot.
It's not like you're kids
dating for the first time.
Why are you talking all night?
Writer Kwon refuses to hang up.
What could I do?
Do you know what she said
as she hung up?
She said she'd tell me the details
when we met up.
What kind of a writer
doesn't write the script?
What? Then you have
another date tonight?
Yes.
Why is living so hard? Why must I live--
It's the director.
Hello, Director. This is Lee Joon Ki.
Yes.
Now?
Why are you drinking so much
in the morning?
Did something happen?
I fought with my girlfriend
a while back, and...
she asked for a break
to think about things.
I think she met another guy in that time.
What?
That really is so harsh of her.
You had a girlfriend, Director?
- This is a secret.
- Okay.
- Keep it to yourself.
- Of course.
Writer Kwon.
That Writer Kwon?
The Writer Kwon who is writing our drama?
Anyway, wait and see.
Whoever he is,
I won't let him get away with it.
How?
I'll do whatever I need to
in order to find him.
I will... destroy him.
What?
The director and the writer were dating?
Yes.
What am I supposed to do now?
How could things
get so twisted like this?
Why does he live like that?
Gosh.
[Writer Kwon]
I told you from the beginning--
Hye Jin.
Yes. Of course.
I'm heading out now. Yes.
I have to go on a date with Writer Kwon.
What is he planning to do?
I really don't know.
By the way, I wonder how Dong Gu
and Yoon Ah are doing.
I wonder if Dong Gu
is picking on Yoon Ah again.
I hope not.
Blow hard, blow.
Harder than that. Harder.
Oh my. So, so dirty.
Yoon Ah.
I'll tell you one more time.
- I usually don't like to be--
- Don't say it!
Okay.
Why is there so much dirt on your face?
Now that I don't have Sol here,
I have a big baby.
We're here.
This is where I live.
Ah, I see.
It's late today. Go in and rest.
I don't want to say goodbye.
Do you want to come in for some coffee?
Coffee?
Oh no! What do you mean? It's fine.
You must be tired. Go on and rest.
I'm fine. Let's go in.
- Where?
- Come on.
Wait, wait.
Hello, there.
- This is my place.
- Yes.
I'm okay to walk.
Hey.
Then I'll just have one coffee
and get going.
All right.
Then sit here and wait
while I make coffee.
Okay.
Who is it?
Why is he here?
Hye Jin, open up.
Hye Jin, open the door.
Let's talk.
Joon Ki, there's something
I haven't told you yet.
There was a guy I was dating.
I'll explain everything
and end it cleanly.
- Don't misunderstand, okay.
- No!
Don't do that. Don't do anything.
Hye Jin, are you really
going to be this way?
I know you're inside!
I already know!
I saw you going in with that punk!
Don't worry. I won't let you get hurt.
I will get hurt.
Don't do anything. I'm begging you.
If you're going to be like this,
I'm just coming in, okay?
Don't open it. Don't open the door.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
Oh, you reek of alcohol.
You drank again?
Yeah, I did. So, what?
Where is he, anyway?
Where is he?
What's wrong with you?
What's it to you who I date or not?
Where did you hide him?
Let's see that great face of his.
Oh, he must be in here.
Damn it.
Get out here, you punk.
I'll break this door down
if you don't come out!
Huh? Where did he go?
Get out. Get out here, you punk.
Look at you. Oh, look at you.
- Stop right there!
- Director!
Oh, I finally caught you.
You dare to steal my girl?
Let me see what you look like.
- No.
- Hey.
Get rid of this. Get rid of it now!
Gosh!
Move this thing!
Huh? You...
You punk.
Hello, Director.
It's me, Lee Joon Ki.
What? So, you're dating Writer Kwon?
It's a misunderstanding.
I got into a car accident
with Writer Kwon.
She suddenly asked to date me,
so I was forced to date her.
So, Writer Kwon is not so great.
She really isn't my type.
Joon Ki!
Writer Kwon, I didn't mean that.
Please listen.
Director, it's not that.
What happened was...
Director, it was just that...
Oh, I mean, Director...
Writer Kwon. I mean, Writer Kwon.
I... I'm the director, you punk.
I'm the director.
I'm Lee Joon Ki.
You punk rascal!
Hey, man. Why do you live like this?
Do you think I knew this would happen?
You don't think I'll get fired
or anything, right?
No way.
That writer is a pro too.
It would be petty to get revenge.
I should be okay, right?
I really should be.
It's okay, it's okay.
Dong Gu, are you okay?
Oh, your fever is getting worse.
I'm fine.
I'm sure I'll be fine once I sleep.
What are you doing instead of sleeping?
I had some books to read.
Do you still want to be a patisseur
or whatever it is?
Yes, it is my dream.
Also, I won't give up, for Sol's sake.
You sure are stubborn.
Yoon Ah, I'm sorry,
but can you get me my phone?
Hello?
What?
I don't need it.
I'm already overflowing with loans.
Yoon Ah, hang it up.
Don't these people sleep?
Who is this person, Dong Gu?
Ah... my mom.
Wow, she's beautiful.
I don't think I've ever heard you
speak about your mother.
She passed away.
Oh, I see.
What kind of person was your mother?
My mom?
Well, she was stubborn and prickly,
and she nagged me all the time.
Like you, she never gave up on
something once she decided to do it.
I was hit by her a lot
when I was growing up.
She must have been a strong person.
Still, she had a soft heart.
She would nurse me all night
and give me medicine.
Don't you miss her?
Of course, I do.
I miss her so much,
but I can't see her.
Your cough is getting worse.
You'd better get to sleep, Dong Gu.
I think I should.
What's this?
How did this...
Then did Yoon Ah do this?
Oh, I must've fallen asleep.
Did Dong Gu's fever go down?
It did.
What a relief.
Dong Gu, are you sleeping?
Dong Gu.
Oh, I feel like I can live now.
I thought I was going to die.
What do I do?
It smells.
You missed Mommy,
didn't you, Sol?
Mommy missed you too, Sol.
I missed you so much.
You all suffered
taking care of Sol. I'm sorry.
It's okay. Don't worry.
It's starting.
Joon Ki's drama is starting.
Don't watch. I told you not to watch.
Why? It's your drama debut.
We have to watch.
- Where's the remote control?
- It's on.
We've arrived, Chairman.
It's on.
I won't let them get away with it.
They dare try to take my place?
I'll destroy everything here today.
- Driver Kim.
- Yes, Chairman.
Would you like this candy?
- That's sudden
- Yes, Chairman.
Don't eat it.
What? Why is he doing that
after eating the candy?
Driver Kim! Driver Kim!
Who knew he'd die
such a meaningless death?
I'm sorry, Driver Kim.
Still, the dead are dead,
so let's forget.
Find a new driver, Secretary Han.
- Yes, Chairman.
- What was that?
That's the end?
He eats candy and dies?
You're not on anymore?
No.
That writer really holds a grudge.
How could you kill someone off like that?
Where were you?
You missed the drama.
I saw it on my phone.
He dies eating the candy.
Joon Ki, what kind of candy was it?
Was it peppermint?
Is that important right now?
Yes, it was peppermint. It was!
Are you satisfied?
Really?
It's the peppermint candy's fault.
Why are you getting mad at me?
Yoon Ah, take this.
What is it?
You said you wanted
to become a patisseur.
You could read home-baking books
for 100 days but that wouldn't help.
You need a license from an academy.
I don't have money to go to one.
You don't have to pay.
There's a government program
that supports single moms.
- Really?
- Yes.
I looked in the area and there are
some good baking academies.
We should go tomorrow and apply
for the money and look into a school.
Thank you, Dong Gu.
There you go again.
Don't cry over every little thing!
Thank you, Dong Gu.
What's this?
Why is your face red, Dong Gu?
What?
What do you mean?
It's because I can't breathe.
Why... why are you suddenly hugging me?
You're a strange lady.
Oh, he's even stuttering.
What's going on?
You two lived together
on the roof for a few days.
Did you catch feelings or what?
What are you talking about?
It's not like that!
My goodness.
Strange.
Put on something else.
Why watch this when he died?
My gosh. What feelings?
Why did your face turn red then?
Do I really...
No, that makes no sense.
It can't be.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
I met him at the academy.
He drove me on his way home.
He's a really good catch.
He's good looking and gentle.
You should date him.
You don't know him,
so why say he's a good catch?
He has a weird look in his eyes to me.
Yoon Ah, be careful of him.
Dong Gu, do like Yoon Ah?
Want to be in our film?
Pure and glamorous actress,
Shin Shi Jung?
I will do the bed scene.
Lose 10 kilograms in a week?
Ask Seo Jin for help.
Go faster!
Bed scene!
No walking!
Hey!
Keep going. Bed scene!
You'll really die at this rate.
Hi, I'm here for the rent.
We'll be auctioning the items in order
to get the unpaid rent.
Do you want to lose the business
or get married?
A wedding?
Singer Wheesung?
He's going to sing a song at the wedding?
Kiss, kiss, kiss.
Dong Gu, what am I going to do?