Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
No, I'm all just fine.
Don't feel burdened by me.
I don't even have a boyfriend now.
But why aren't you
saying anything at all?
You're too perfect for me.
I know by the look in your eyes.
No woman approaches
a man first like I do.
I am just the same.
Just like this!
Oh, my butt.
Oh, who's this?
Did you sleep well, our little Sol?
- Did you sleep well too, Yoon Ah?
- Yes.
You got up early today.
Good morning, Yoon Ah.
Morning, did you sleep well--
You probably didn't know,
but he always does that.
What group was it again?
- Groo... something.
- Grooming group.
It's called a grooming group.
Men need to change these days.
Yoon Ah, I'm actually a film actor.
- Actor.
- Wow, a film actor?
That's amazing.
Actor, yeah right.
You never even have lines and
just stand in the background.
Gosh, Writer Bong has
such a pretty way with words.
Doo Shik, you're a writer?
Wow, what do you write?
I write novels and web novels.
My dream is to become a screenwriter.
You're writing a screenplay right now.
All you do is ghostwrite for students.
Last time, he got paid a bag of snacks.
He wrote a paper for
the neighbor primary school student.
He's not a writer.
He teaches people wrong things.
Are you done now?
Give it a rest now.
You two are just the same.
No one is better.
Hey, we're still better than you.
You said you'd become a film director.
You tried to bake a sweet potato
and burned the set down.
Why would you bring that up?
It wasn't a sweet potato.
It was a potato.
Whether it's a sweet potato or potato,
you started the fire.
How is it the same? How!
Sweet potato is two words
and potato is one!
How is that the same?
Why bring up word count
when I'm talking about fire?
Sweet potato and potato are different!
Why did you say crap to Joon Ki
and start this?
Why are you fighting?
Try to calm down.
Why did you have bring it all up?
- He started it.
- No, you did.
Shut up!
Men are so childish.
Try to understand, Yoon Ah.
Men in this house are so strange.
Ha! What? Strange?
If we're talking strange,
you're at the top of the list, Chewbacca.
Chewbacca? What is that?
You know that furry guy on Star Wars.
Hold on.
Here it is.
Chewbacca!
Ah, but what does this
have to do with Seo Jin?
This Chewbacca and Seo Jin
are connected--
I told you to stop, didn't I?
I told you to stop.
I won't do it. I won't.
Chewbacca!
- Chewbacca!
- You're dead.
Ouch, ouch.
He's older than us, after all.
Look at you!
You two siblings have bad tempers.
They are really odd people.
Did I make the right decision
staying here?
Are you hungry, Sol?
Should we eat?
Sol, let's have some food.
You were so hungry, weren't you?
Yummy food, yummy food.
That startled me.
- She's the strangest person.
- You're right.
Why does she do that?
[Anyone Can Become Wolverine]
So, should we
get started on cleaning now?
Yeah, Seo Jin said
she'd inspect everything.
Let's hurry before she says
something again.
But do all three of us
really need to clean?
That's why I'm bringing this up...
Want to make a bet?
A bet?
So, you're going to put on pants
without using hands?
Does that make sense?
- How can you do that without hands?
- I know, right?
If I fail to do so,
I'll clean on your behalf.
If I succeed,
I'm exempt from cleaning.
What do you think? Are you in?
- I'm in.
Let's go!
30 seconds.
He can't do it.
What is that?
- What?
- What's he doing?
- What's going on?
That actually works?
Oh, what is that?
What's going on here?
What are you doing?
I told you to clean.
What is this insane nonsense?
- I was going to clean.
- Me too.
Hey, hey! I succeeded.
I'm exempt, okay?
Exempt, yeah right.
- Follow me.
- I said I'm exempt.
I succeeded in exemption. Hey!
I'm so tired.
There's so much to clean because
we have an increase in guests.
You only cleaned a little
and you're complaining.
Get moving, already.
It's check-in time soon.
All right. Aren't you
going to the library today?
- You're going fool around if I go?
- No!
You're graduating soon.
How's your job search going?
I want to get a job.
I really, really want to find a job,
but it's not easy.
It's so hard to get a job these days.
Stay strong.
I do get strength from you, Doo Shik.
Oh, come on.
I keep thinking I'll become like you
if I don't get it together.
I even wake up in the middle
of the night. Thank you.
That girl.
What are you doing?
Are you going to do this all day?
Wash the bed sheets and
clean the rooftop too.
Also, put away the tree
in the lobby area.
Christmas passed ages ago--
I got it so stop nagging me.
I'm already feeling upset.
What are you upset about?
- Su Ah and I broke up.
- I know.
It wasn't enough
that you were an incompetent guy
but you sold your couple ring too.
Yet, you still can't get over her
and you're hanging around annoyingly.
- Who said that?
- Joon Ki.
That guy has such a big mouth.
Things are over once it ends.
Just get over it.
I dated Su Ah for four years.
How can she and I break up like that?
I won't accept it.
Then meet her and talk to her.
She won't meet with me.
She ignores my calls and texts.
She won't meet me
even if I go to see her.
Su Ah is very set on breaking up.
Isn't she being too harsh?
Hey, in your eyes...
is your brother untrustworthy
and someone with no future?
Huh?
- Look at the time.
- What?
It's time for me to
go to the library. Bye now.
That kid.
My only little sister
is looking down on me too.
Oh, I'm so tired.
I'm going to die from cleaning too much.
You all worked hard.
Would you like a drink or something?
- Yes.
- No, thank you.
Stop putting so much on.
Hey, you have to put a lot on the
T-zone because it comes off fast.
Also, I have a film shoot today.
That's why I'm doing this.
Which film is it this time?
You guys know the X-Men, right?
It's a Korean "X-Men."
It's a film about
the struggle of those mutants.
Who's starring in it?
Jo In Sung.
This was be a hit, 100 percent.
Besides that, I will become a star.
Besides that...
it's only a matter of time before
I won't have to see your faces.
This star better get going then.
Do a good job.
See you later.
Oh no. What do I do?
Yoon Ah, are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine.
You should've been more careful.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I haven't actually approved
you living here yet.
I'll see how you are at working.
If it doesn't work out,
then I'll ask you to leave.
Yes, don't worry. I'll work hard.
Just go. I'll clean up here.
I'm sorry.
Wait, give me the rubber gloves.
Oh, right.
Oh no. What did I do?
What do I do?
Oh my. I'm so sorry.
Hey, the bubbles!
Ew, what is this,
first thing in the morning?
- Gosh.
- I'm sorry.
Stop saying sorry and please just go.
I'm just so sorr...
I mean... I apologize.
Gosh, seriously.
I don't like her. I don't like her.
I really don't like her.
She can't focus because of her baby.
What can she do?
You're really irritated lately.
Is it because of Su Ah?
It's not like that.
What do you mean it's not?
It's written on your face.
I said it's not!
Just know that it's not!
Why won't you listen
when I tell you that it's not!
So annoying! You clean it.
So upsetting.
Why does he always get angry at me?
I can hear you!
Director.
Are you ready to shoot?
Yeah, almost.
Radiation mutant!
Where are you?
- Hello, Director.
- Hey.
Great makeup job. Looks good.
We're start once In Sung arrives.
- Stand by.
- Yes, Sir.
Where's the genetic mutant?
Genetic mutant!
Hello?
What? What did you say?
Ah, that's a big problem.
Okay. Gosh, I'm going insane.
What is it?
In Sung got into an accident on his way
and is in the hospital.
Then what do we do about filming today?
What can we do?
The star isn't here.
We have to shut it down.
Assistant Director, what should I do?
Take off the makeup for today.
What do you mean?
Why would you take it off?
The makeup fee is expensive.
Go home just like this and
come back tomorrow like this.
Got it?
Looking just like this?
If you ruin your makeup at all,
I'll get rid of your role.
It's up to you, okay?
Get rid of it?
We're shutting down for today.
Wait. Where is everyone going?
This is... what do I do?
Huh? Wait.
Hello, there.
- What is that?
- So scary.
- What in the world?
What is that?
You have to take a picture.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
Why are there so many people?
I can't ruin the costume.
Sorry.
You should be more careful.
I told her to clean the towels,
and yet they're still here.
That woman doesn't do anything right.
- Dong Gu.
- What?
Who are you?
What are you? What?
It's me.
Joon Ki? Why do you look like that?
The shoot got delayed because
the star got into an accident.
The director doesn't want
to pay for makeup again.
He has to stay like that
and go back tomorrow.
You sure live a hard life.
You really do.
I don't want to hear it.
I'm really embarrassed too.
Geez.
Gosh.
Doo Shik, put the phone against my ear.
Hello. Yes, I'm Lee Joon Ki.
What? The police station?
We caught a pick-pocket thief.
He had your wallet.
My wallet? Hold on a moment.
What?
Why, that jerk. My wallet!
Yes, I'll be right there.
- Hang it up.
- Wait.
You're going like that?
What can I do?
It had my ID, credit cards, money...
Ah, I have no money.
That little jerk. He's dead.
Nothing is normal here.
What is this?
Who left the fridge door open?
What if all the food goes bad?
This was that woman again,
wasn't it?
Yoon Ah! Yoon Ah!
Yes, did you call for me?
Did you do all of this?
I was cleaning the fridge
when Sol started to cry.
- I'll clean it soon.
- Forget it.
Take care of Sol first.
What is this?
The mushrooms are growing mushrooms.
Throw this out.
Yes, yes.
You finished eating, Sol?
Go to sleep now.
Do your work properly.
I'm sorry.
If you're so sorry,
don't do things to be sorry for.
What now? What's going on?
This is all your fault!
- You and Joon Ki.
- Gosh, every time...
You make me the bad guy.
Why is he taking it out on me?
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
No.
Yoon Ah, give Sol to me.
I'll watch Sol.
You can clean this up.
I just feel so bad about it.
It's okay.
I have nothing to do
before my part-time job.
Also, Sol likes me so much.
Isn't that right, Sol?
You like me enough to vomit?
All right?
Since I've suffered pain already,
why don't you let me off?
You want a beating?
You little punk!
Ah, excuse me.
How can I help you?
Who are you?
Who... who are you?
I... I got a phone call.
My name is Lee Joon Ki and
I was told my wallet is here.
Could you please put the gun down?
Ah, you're the victim I spoke to earlier.
- Ah, yes.
- You scared me.
Why is your face like that?
Ah, I'm an actor.
My film shoot got delayed suddenly.
You said my wallet is here?
My wallet... there it is.
Hold on.
We need to check your identity.
Lee Joon Ki.
Are you really Lee Joon Ki?
Yes, I am Lee Joon Ki. Take a look.
Well, it seems like you,
but not really.
Look, I am Lee Joon Ki.
We're the same.
I can't confirm because of the makeup.
Can't you do something?
No, I'll get fired if I damage this.
Ah, we can do fingerprints.
Give me your finger.
Fingerprints.
Can we remove this fur?
No way! I'll get fired if you do.
Then what do you expect me to do?
You can check my DNA.
You can take my blood.
You want me to check your DNA
just to check your identity?
Take your blood and hair to
the National Forensics Center?
Is that a bit much?
But it really is my wallet.
Please give it to me.
I can't give it to you
until I can confirm it's you.
How can a cop have such bad eyes?
Lee Joon Ki is Lee Joon Ki.
So, you couldn't get your wallet?
They couldn't confirm my identity.
What could I do?
He has no eye for things.
I don't know how he's a detective.
Are my looks something that can
be hidden by this makeup?
I'm home.
Chewbacca, you're back from the library?
I told you not to call me that. Oh my!
What is this thing?
Who else would do this in our house?
Joon Ki? Why do you look like this?
I don't know!
What kind of girl always hits first?
Sorry, I didn't know it was you.
I suppose you would've hit me with
the corner of the book if you knew.
Thanks for using the flat side.
- The food is ready.
- Eat up.
It's mushroom stew.
Looks good.
Doo Shik, give Sol to me and eat.
Yoon Ah, you're not eating?
I ate bread earlier, so I'm full.
Go to Mommy.
Geez.
Wow, this stew broth is great.
Right, Dong Gu?
Well, it's not bad.
That's a relief.
I was worried it wouldn't
suit your tastes.
- Joon Ki.
- Yes?
- You should eat too.
- Oh, okay.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
Are you an animal?
Yoon Ah, I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Must you insist on eating like that?
I told you I'll get fired if my
makeup gets damaged.
Have some stew too.
Oh, that's nice. It's good, Yoon Ah.
Eat up, everyone.
Hello.
Su Ah, can't you meet me just once?
Give just a minute of your time.
I'll explain everything.
It's not right to
break up like this. Hello?
She hung up. Call again.
Oh, my stomach.
Why do I suddenly feel this way?
Ow.
Oh... oh.
What is this?
What are you all doing here?
Don't talk to me, man.
Chewbacca, get out now.
I'm going to die out here.
I feel like I'm going to die too.
At least you can talk,
I feel like I'm...
Joon Ki, you have stomach pains too?
You too, Doo Shik?
Yes, ever since I had lunch,
I feel sick.
- Ah!
- This won't do.
Hey, hey!
Oh, what was it that we ate?
What did we eat for lunch?
Mushroom stew, kimchi, and...
Mushroom stew?
It can't be.
What's the matter?
That stew you made earlier...
you didn't use
these mushrooms, did you?
I did. Why do you ask?
What do you mean why?
I told you to throw them out
earlier today because they went bad!
What? I'm so sorry.
I must've missed that
because I was focused on Sol.
Do you think "sorry" will fix everything?
Everyone is sick right now...
Oh no! What should I do?
I'm so sorry. I really am.
Forget it.
I can't let this go.
Pack your bags and leave right now.
Dong... Dong Gu!
Until the day when
the East Sea's waters
and Mt. Baekdu are dry...
and worn away.
God protect and preserve us.
[Broken: Do Not Use]
Ouch!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Oh... Su Ah.
Wait, wait!
- Wait and talk to me.
- I have nothing to say.
Wait. I just need one minute.
You have just one minute.
What do you want to say?
Well...
Su Ah, I...
I'm sorry, but can I go somewhere briefly
and then talk to you?
- Forget it.
- Okay, I'll talk. Let's talk.
Why did this have to happen now?
- What?
- It's nothing.
I'll talk.
Su Ah, I was very wrong.
- I'm very sorry.
- What are you sorry about?
- Everything.
- Everything like what?
Tell me in detail.
In detail?
So...
Well, oh yeah, selling the couple ring.
What else?
Having no responsibility.
- What else?
- There's more.
Yes, um...
What else is there?
Did you just fart?
In this situation?
No, no.
It was this sound.
You're joking around even now.
Forget it.
Su Ah, that's not it!
You're not even coming after me?
I want to come after you.
Forget it. It's truly over now, okay?
Wait, Su Ah!
Su Ah, I'm so sorry.
Oh.
Mister... Mister, Mister.
Mister, Mister.
[Public Washrooms:
Selling All-In-One Toilets]
Take a look before deciding.
People really seem to like this one.
- Would you like to see it?
- Yes.
Why is it locked?
Is someone in there?
Someone's inside.
Uh, who's in there?
Do I have to tell you that?
What are you doing in there?
Just wait.
I'm almost done.
Done? With what?
You sure are frustrating.
I'm on a toilet pooping.
What else would I be doing?
You're doing what?
What are you doing? Get out!
- Get out now!
- What's with you?
- You're dead once I'm out.
- Get out!
What are you doing
in a place of business?
I'm sorry.
I thought it was a public toilet
and I was in such a rush.
Even if you were in a rush.
It's brand new and hasn't been sold.
How could you poo in there?
What are you going to do now?
It's so dirty.
Who can I sell it to now?
I'm sorry.
I'll take responsibility for it.
Dong Gu?
Yoon Ah? What are you doing here?
Everyone got sick because of me,
so I was buying medicine.
Dong Gu, did you really poo in there?
Oh, that...
Don't even ask.
He pooped so much.
Dong Gu.
That's not right.
Yeah, we have a bathroom at home.
Why did you buy that?
No, after our recent experience
I felt that we were lacking in bathrooms.
Then add another toilet in the bathroom.
Why buy that thing?
Oh no!
I'm sorry.
You should try to be careful.
That was the only award Dong Gu received.
I'm sorry.
It's fine, you didn't do it on purpose.
People can make mistakes, right?
Don't worry about it.
What's with you?
You were telling her to pack up and go.
That was just to shock her.
It was a way to cheer her on
to do better in the future.
Yoon Ah, let's forget everything
that's happened so far.
Let's try to get along.
- What?
- All right?
Ah, yes.
In return, you must take what
happened today to the grave.
Don't worry.
Thank you.
Welcome...
Hello.
Oh no.
Gosh.
It's okay. I'll get them, so get on.
I'm sorry.
Sorry about this.
What am I doing?
I'd better get famous soon
so I don't have do these shameful things.
Genetic mutant?
Oh, my stomach.
Seo Jin.
Yoon Ah.
[The Thing is, It's a Secret]
Why would you do that?
It looked fun when my dad and
brother shaved, so I copied them.
It started to grow back thicker.
What's the big deal?
You can just shave it every now and then.
It's not just now and then.
If I don't do it for half a day...
I start to get a shadow.
Gosh. Hey, you.
Why would you copy
shaving the face of all things?
I didn't know this would happen.
Is that why your nickname is Chewbacca?
Chewbacca isn't the only one.
Bigfoot, Zhang Fei,
Im Kkeokjeong, Jang Seung Eop.
- Anyone with lots of hair--
- Stop it!
Hey, it's okay.
Is growing facial hair a crime?
Don't worry about it.
Thanks, Doo Shik.
Hello. Yeah, Yoo Jin.
What? Senior Tae Hyun is coming?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Tae Hyun, the guy you've had
a crush on since your first year?
- It's not like that.
- Yeah right.
Life is good for a graduating student.
You even have time to date.
I'll take care of my life.
You take care of your own life, Joon Ki.
- Yes...
- I have to go.
- Look how excited she is.
- My gosh.
What good is that?
She hasn't even told him her feelings.
Seo Jin is a dating amateur
if you think about it.
I don't think a guy who's
always solo ought to say that.
Yoon Ah.
Oh, it's the angry guy.
The eggs and bread have run out.
What's going on?
Oh no. I forgot.
- Sorry.
- How can you forget that?
I told you to buy it beforehand for
the guest's breakfasts.
Sorry, I'll go buy it now.
Hurry.
She doesn't do anything right.
Stop berating her.
She's trying her best.
Trying her best? Yeah right.
She's going to cause big trouble.
I just know it for sure.
She'll get better with time.
Just trust her and wait.
Why did you come back?
I left the grocery cart here.
I'll get going.
You see. How can I trust her?
A person can forget.
- Why are you back again?
- I left my wallet.
I'll be back.
My goodness.
What is it this time? What?
Where is the grocery store?
How can you not know your way
when we've been here so many times?
Sorry, I'm very bad with directions.
I think I know for sure now.
You sound so sure that I feel
more worried now.
I'm tired of nagging you too.
You need to do things right
on your own, okay?
Okay?
What are you doing there?
The toys are on sale.
I've never been able to buy one for Sol.
Wow, it's even expensive on sale.
Let's just go.
Pick just one.
Really?
But, it has to be just one.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
Is she shameless or naive?
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Su Ah.
Who is it? Is he someone you know?
Oh, he's a friend.
Friend? Hey, Min Su Ah.
Who is this man? Who is this person?
Hello, I'm Lee Yoon Seok
and I'm dating Su Ah now.
Dating?
I own a Thai restaurant nearby.
If you come by sometime,
I'll treat you to a meal.
Dong Gu! Dong Gu, I picked one.
Buy me this.
Who's this?
Huh?
She's my girlfriend.
Girlfriend?
- You're already dating someone?
- You are, so can't I?
That's not a problem.
- What does she do?
- What?
A doctor, a doctor.
She's a neurosurgeon.
Maybe because she's a doctor,
she always chooses toys like these.
Dong Gu, what's going--
You silly girl who only cares about work.
What are you doing?
Su Ah, we did run into them.
Should we have tea with them?
No, I'm not that comfortable with them.
There's no need.
No need to be uncomfortable.
Why don't we have dinner
at my restaurant after work?
Doctor Han here is very busy with work.
I don't know if she'll have time.
We'll see if we have time and decide.
Let's go, Yoon Ah.
Please let us pass. Beep, beep.
Dong Gu, what just happened?
- Be quiet, be quiet.
- Okay.
Is that Su Ah? She's very pretty.
Please be quiet.
- Quiet, please.
- Okay.
Dong Gu, you are buying me
this toy, aren't you?
I will. I'll buy it all.
Please just be quiet.
What? Su Ah already has another guy?
What does he do?
I don't know.
He owns a Thai restaurant.
That guy invited me to his restaurant.
That arrogant punk.
Still, why would you lie
and say Yoon Ah was your girlfriend?
And you said she was a doctor?
I suddenly got angry seeing her
with another guy, so I couldn't think.
Gosh, Su Ah is completely
gone now. She's gone.
No, no.
This could be a chance,
your last chance.
A chance? What do you mean?
I guarantee you that
Su Ah will contact you soon.
I doubt it.
What? She really did.
See, what did I say?
How would you read this text?
"Nice seeing you."
"Your girlfriend is pretty."
No, that's wrong!
"Nice seeing you."
"Your girlfriend is pretty."
This is how it is.
Do, re, mi, fa, so...
So, it's that really irritated tone.
Oh, I doubt that.
You are all amateurs.
- Kang Dong Gu.
- Huh?
You're immature, with no ambition
and no future at all.
So you were dumped.
Yoon Ah here very good looking.
Plus, she's apparently
a successful doctor.
How would Su Ah feel?
- That girl stepped in crap.
- No, no!
Su Ah is really confused.
Her head is full of complex thoughts.
Why in the world? Why?
Why would a woman like that
be with Dong Gu?
Was Dong Gu really a decent catch?
Did Dong Gu have
something special I didn't see?
It's bothering her like crazy.
Huh, huh, huh?
That could be true. Then what?
If you use this chance wisely,
you could date Su Ah again.
- That's what.
- Really?
Joon Ki, then what should I do?
What else? That guy invited you
to the restaurant.
You have to go with Yoon Ah.
As a close couple.
Then what?
Then you show her
what a great guy you are.
Make Su Ah regret it so much.
- How?
- That depends on Yoon Ah...
Depends on Doctor Han.
What? What am I supposed to do?
Yoon Ah, please help me.
I'm asking you for this favor.
I do want to help you,
but I don't feel confident about it.
Are you going to be this way?
If you help me this time,
I'll forget everything that happened.
So, please help me. Please, please?
All right.
Thank you. Thank you, Yoon Ah.
What do I have to do now? Huh?
We have to start by making
Doctor Han beautiful.
Elegant and gorgeous.
Oh, my bag. Gosh.
Oh, what brings you to school, Senior?
I was just dropping by
the career center.
I thought of you guys,
so I came by.
When is Senior Tae Hyun coming?
So, you're here to see him.
No, I'm here to see you guys.
Forget it.
He called a little while ago.
Work's taking long,
so he's running late.
I have somewhere to be.
I'll get going.
Okay. I... I'm going to go soon too!
I really am going!
You look pretty decent dressed up.
You usually look like a bum.
It's only because I don't dress up.
I can be right up there with Gong Yoo.
Don't insult Gong Yoo.
You're not up there.
Can I trust you, Joon Ki?
Everything will work out
if you listen to me.
Nothing worked out from listening to you.
I don't know if this will work.
Just trust me. Trust me.
Everything about you is bad.
- Not trusting people is the worst.
- Be quiet.
Why isn't Yoon Ah coming out?
How do I look?
I haven't put makeup on in a long time,
so it felt awkward.
Weird, right?
No.
You look pretty, very pretty.
Right, Joon Ki?
Yes, you do.
You look like a completely
different person.
Right, Dong Gu?
Yeah.
It's not bad.
- It's almost time. Let's go.
- Okay.
Will it be okay to leave Sol behind?
Don't worry and go.
We'll take good care of Sol.
Okay, I'll be going then.
Make sure to succeed, Dong Gu.
Sol, wish your mom luck.
Good luck, Mom!
That is one strange "good luck."
What a good daughter you are.
Hold her, would you?
I need to go get some "good luck" too.
Why would you do that now? Joon Ki!
Why is it so empty here?
Seo Jin.
Kang Seo Jin.
Yes. What? What?
Oh, Senior Tae Hyun.
It's been a long time.
Yes, it's been a long time.
Work ended so late,
so I worried that no one would be here.
I'm so thankful that you waited for me.
I... I wasn't waiting for you.
I didn't even know you were coming.
Really, I didn't know.
Okay, okay.
No need to cause a fuss.
Oh yeah. We remodeled the media room.
Do you want to see it?
Wow, it's really clean now.
There used to spiderwebs and rats.
It was like a haunted house.
Oh!
This is still here?
What is it?
This... here.
Reporter Kang Seo Jin's first article.
How is your employment search going?
I'm just trying hard.
Come to my newspaper.
Working together would be fun.
I already applied actually.
I didn't get hired.
Hey, it's okay.
I failed twice before getting hired.
You'll get in next time.
Stay strong.
I'm hungry. Should we go eat?
Re... really?
We should go.
- What's wrong?
- Why isn't it opening?
What do we do?
Why isn't this opening?
Seo Jin, give me your phone.
I left it on the desk earlier.
I left my phone in my bag too.
What should we do?
We're in trouble now.
Yoon Ah, we'll go over it one more time.
- Your job?
- Korea's top neurosurgeon.
Your parents?
Dad's a hospital director
and mom's an artist.
The first place we met?
The third table from the entrance
of the hospital cafeteria.
- Okay, ready?
- Yes.
I'll do my best.
Okay, then let's go.
I didn't really think you'd come.
How unexpected.
Doctor Han finished work early,
so I dropped by.
I thought it was a great restaurant.
- It's quite simple.
- You think so?
I can guarantee good food though.
Let's order first. Here's the menu.
Ah, you can choose.
Over here.
Prepare these for us.
As for the dishes...
One each for those. Also...
- Those, as well.
- Yes, President.
The names of the food sound like
Muay Thai athlete names.
It's very aggressive.
What would you like for alcohol?
I don't need a drink.
I'm nursing right now.
What? Nursing?
No, it's not that.
Oh, not nursing...
she meant surgery.
Doctor Han has an important
surgery tomorrow morning.
Ah... surgery.
What kind of surgery?
What?
It's... it's uh...
the duodenum area?
What?
Neurosurgeons do surgery
on the duodenum too?
Well... well...
Doctor Han is a neurosurgeon.
She specializes in multiple areas.
Neurosurgery, general surgery,
and obstetrics.
She specializes in all of them.
Why would a woman like Yoon Ah
be with someone like you...
Other people may think
there's not much to Dong Gu.
They are wrong about him.
I could see it.
I could Dong Gu's great future.
Oh, come on now.
No, I'm sure of it.
Dong Gu, you will become
a great film director in the world.
I've never been wrong about anything.
You can trust me on that.
I can't stop her.
But, he still...
has not opened up his heart to me,
so I'm suffering.
I told you.
The wound on my heart has yet to heal.
It's all right.
I don't expect anything more
from you, Dong Gu.
I'm sorry.
What did I do to deserve you?
We're trapped in here.
I don't think we can leave until
the kids come tomorrow morning.
Still, because I'm here with you...
it's not so bad.
What do you mean?
Seo Jin.
I have something...
to tell you.
What is it?
Honestly, for a long time...
I...
What? What is it?
You have...
something under your nose.
What? Do I have
something under my nose?
Yes.
One moment.
Oh no. It's growing.
The hair is growing.
My razor is the bag.
What do I do?
What? Is something wrong?
It's nothing. I think it's some dust.
I see.
Anyway, what I wanted to say was...
Stay back. Stay back.
What's wrong with you?
I said to stay back, so stay back.
I have to get out of here.
If I get caught here,
it's over for me.
Excuse me! There's someone trapped here.
Please save me! Save me!
Seo Jin, what's the matter
all of the sudden?
Stay back. Just stay away.
Over here!
Over here! Can anyone hear?
Someone's trapped in here.
Kang Seo Jin, pull yourself together.
Please save me!
I hope the food suited your taste.
It was not bad.
It wasn't as good as the traditional
Thai food Doctor Han tried in Bangkok.
Is that right?
I feel a bit disappointed.
You should stay for one more drink.
I wish I could.
Doctor Han here has a surgery,
so she can't stay.
We will treat next time.
- Stay healthy.
- Okay.
Today was fun, Yoon Ah.
I had fun too. Let's go, Dong Gu.
Yes.
Yoon Ah, stick closer to me.
Like this?
Dong Gu, how was I today? Good?
Good. You're a good actress.
Your acting is great.
Thank you.
Why is my mom with your father?
It can't be...
- It can't be.
- No way.
It makes no sense.
Then you're saying
you are my father's daughter?
Daughter! Oh I'm sorry.
Oh my.
You're my half sister?
Sister, sister, sister....
That's nonsense, nonsense!
- What, what, what?
- Oh, oh!
Why do you think it's nonsense?
There's nothing in the world
that's nonsense.
It's merely...
evil ambition that people want to hide.
- So scary.
- What do you mean?
You cast aside
Yoo Geum Ran 30 years ago.
- He knows Yoo Geum Ran.
- What's going on?
How do you know her?
Because I am her daughter.
What? What did you say?
Then you're my daughter too?
- Daughter? Daughter, daughter!
- Awesome.
I made the decision long ago.
I would get my revenge on you.
What?
- You devil.
- Devil.
You are the devil!
Bravo.
Bravo, bravo.
I want to applaud that show for
keeping us guessing until the end.
I never imagined the father-in-law's
wife was his own daughter.
Me too.
How can I wait until tomorrow?
I'm dying of curiosity.
What are you doing?
You're back?
So, how'd it go?
There was a little danger
in the beginning.
Yoon Ah is better at acting
than I thought.
Yeah? That's amazing, Yoon Ah.
I just tried my best.
You really think it'll work out, Joon Ki?
Of course.
Su Ah is probably
100 times more confused.
"Why did I dump that great guy?
Did I do a useless thing?"
That's what she's thinking.
I really hope it works out like you say.
You must be tired
from watching Sol, right?
No, she only vomited five times
and pooped seven times.
And urinated about nine times.
Oh, something's coming again.
Give Sol to me now.
I'll watch her.
Oh, Sol.
Oh, my arms hurt. I need to eat.
Go on and eat.
- I'm going to play games.
- Go on.
Our Sol, did you tire out your uncles?
Sol, did you miss Mommy?
Mom missed you too, Sol.
Mom?
What do you mean?
Sol, did you miss Mommy?
Mom missed you too, Sol.
Mom?
What do you mean?
Su Ah, what are you doing here?
Yoon Ah left her bag behind.
Oh no. Did I do that?
Thank you.
What do you mean by "mom"?
You two have a baby? Since when?
It wasn't when
you were dating me, was it?
No, why would you say
such an awful thing?
- Then what?
- Oh.
That's just...
Yoon Ah likes babies,
so she always says "mom."
It's a habit, right?
Of course, why would
I have a baby at this age?
How cute.
Then who is that baby?
Hold on. That baby...
- Isn't she the one the guest left?
- Yeah.
Yes, that...
Well, we decided to raise her.
Why would you raise a stranger's baby?
Oh, uh... hm...
She's Joon Ki's.
What? She's Joon Ki's baby?
So, it was Joon Ki's girlfriend
who left her here?
You know he lives recklessly.
He deserves punishment.
Really, Joon Ki?
You know I live recklessly.
I suppose you would
do something like that.
Oh, thanks for the bag.
It's late, so get going.
I would feel hurt to just leave
when we're already here.
Show us the guest house
and let's have a beer too.
Sure, sure.
Yoon Ah, can you take them to
the third floor then?
I'll bring up the beer.
Yes, okay.
Then why don't you go to Daddy?
There he is.
Daddy, Daddy, Daddy.
Oh, so you're my daughter?
You're surprised?
This way.
Go on up and I'll bring the beer.
What are you doing? Are you crazy?
It was urgent and it just came out.
Whatever.
Whatever. Don't worry about
the guy who lives recklessly.
Go on up.
- Sorry, Joon Ki.
- Don't touch me.
Sorry.
Daughter?
What do I do?
It's getting thicker.
If I get caught with this mustache,
it's over forever.
I'm going insane.
So sleepy.
I'm so sleepy.
No.
I can't sleep. I can never sleep.
I must've dozed off.
What is this? What are you doing?
Seo Jin, it's nothing.
I just thought you'd get cold.
I told you to get away.
Senior! Senior!
Senior, please wake up.
Senior, I was wrong. I'm sorry.
Open your eyes.
Are you okay? Are you awake?
Oh, my head hurts.
My head hurts... ouch.
Hey, you... mustache...
I am really sorry!
I'm sorry.
The mood of the guest house is nice.
It's very cozy.
Doctor Han wants me to close it down
and focus on films.
I just can't do that.
I want to do it without her help.
I want to succeed on my own.
Ah, I see.
Sorry, Yoon Ah.
I'm being too selfish.
Not at all.
Emergency. Sol is crying in hunger.
Need your presence immediately.
Sorry, but I need to use the bathroom.
Here.
Should we toast to your dreams, Dong Gu?
Shall we?
We're all out of beer though.
I'll get more.
I need to use the bathroom too.
Yes.
Oh, is our Sol up?
Are you happy to see Mommy's nipple?
Oh, you're so happy.
Oh, my baby.
Food. Food.
There you go.
Joon Ki...
Yoon Ah!
What...
are you doing right now?
- Su Ah.
- Why are you...
Why are you breastfeeding Joon Ki's baby?
Oh no. I wasn't doing that.
Sol hasn't changed her diaper.
- Su Ah.
- Joon Ki.
Why is Yoon Ah breastfeeding your baby?
So, what happened is...
She needs nutrients from breast milk.
Breast milk is best for babies.
Getting breast milk
from Dong Gu's girlfriend?
Wait! She's not a birth mom,
so why would she have breast milk?
Right, she's not.
When Yoon Ah is in a good mood,
she can gather her strength and--
What nonsense!
Yoon Ah, you tell me.
What's going on?
Well, the thing is...
Honestly, Sol is my daughter.
What? Your daughter?
You said she was yours.
She was. No, she is.
I thought your ex-girlfriend
left her here.
Then how is she Yoon Ah's daughter?
Then is Yoon Ah your ex-girlfriend?
Does that make sense?
Why do you think it's nonsense?
There's nothing in the world
that's nonsense.
It's merely evil ambition
that people want to hide.
What are you saying?
Then Yoon Ah is your ex-girlfriend.
And this baby is yours and hers?
I wanted to keep it a secret
until the end.
Are you saying Dong Gu doesn't know?
I was going to tell the truth,
but struggled after breaking up with you.
I couldn't bear to tell him.
Yoon Ah, is this the truth?
Actually...
Shut up, you wench!
You have nothing you can say
for yourself.
This woman will stop at nothing
if she wants something.
You're the only person who can save
Dong Gu from that devil.
Please come back to Dong Gu.
Please.
- Hey.
- Huh?
- Did you plan this with Dong Gu?
- No.
You know what happens
if you lie, don't you?
Look at me and talk.
You two planned it, right?
I don't think so.
You little punk...
- Tell me properly!
- I will. I will.
- What is it?
- I can't tell you in little bits.
I have to tell you the whole story.
- Tell me.
- This story...
I still can't forget the night sky
from Doctor Han's home in Malibu.
It's as if gold dust
were thrown into the sky.
We should go on a couple's trip
when you have time.
I would like that.
Yes.
You're back?
Su Ah, I mentioned to Yoon Seok
he should make some time.
We are going to Doctor Han's home
in Malibu sometime.
You're okay with that, right?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is there something on my face?
No, on the back of your head.
I'll take it off for you.
Su Ah, Su Ah.
Su Ah, I was wrong.
I'm really sorry.
Let go before I hit you again.
Hold on, Su Ah.
Why do you think I went so far?
I really love you and
I don't want to break up.
Really, but what will you do?
Even the tiny sliver of goodwill I had
for you is completely gone.
I don't want to see your face again.
Don't ever show up in front of me again.
Su Ah, Su Ah.
Su Ah.
Dong Gu, stop drinking.
Stop drinking. You drank too much.
Leave me alone!
I'm going to drink and die.
Don't stop me!
Things never turn out well when
he listens to you, Joon Ki.
Do you think I knew
it'd get this twisted?
I'm going crazy.
The siblings are both
putting on a show tonight.
Shut up, girl!
Senior Tae Hyun.
Su Ah!
So tiresome. Gosh.
Senior Tae Hyun.
Su Ah!
Come on down.
So noisy!
Su Ah!
Stop drinking. Stop.
Su Ah! I'm going to drink!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
How long are you going to be this way?
You need another girl to forget her.
You'll meet another good person.
Stay strong.
Kim Hee Ja.
Korea's most talented actress,
Kim Hee Ja?
Director, please?
It's about swimmers.
Have you seen swimmers?
Hello, I'm here to give you a wax.
I think my life as a man is over.
Lee Joon Ki is over!
Seo Jin!
Do you want to date?
It's like they're filming a movie scene.
He picks his nose
whenever and wherever.
He doesn't wash his hands
and eats kimbap.
Then he pinches my cheek.
I was going crazy.
He's getting married soon.
What do you think he'll do if he
knows Yoon Ah had his baby?
What do you mean?
She had my baby?
Are you trying to destroy my life?
Be thankful I'm even giving you this.
Who knows if you're lying?
Wait!