Subtitles by DramaFever
[This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.]
Su Ah.
Dong Gu.
You...
What are you doing here?
Is something wrong?
What am I supposed to do, Dong Gu?
What are we going to do now?
If we can't pay President Kim back,
we'll get kicked out right away.
I know.
We have nowhere else to go.
I'm going insane here.
This is all your fault, seriously.
What are you going to do now, huh?
It's not like I knew this would happen.
Gosh, how am I supposed to get
that kind of money in one month?
I'm going nuts.
Joon Ki, it's not the time
for you to worry about money.
What do you mean?
Don't you know Dong Gu's coming soon?
A fake wedding, fake honeymoon,
and you put him into debt.
You don't expect to be safe, do you?
I pray for you to rest in peace.
I pray for you.
Doo Shik, give me Sol.
Why do you need Sol?
I need to be holding Sol to stop
Dong Gu from hitting me.
What are you talking about?
I'm home.
D... Dong Gu. Please stay calm.
Listen to what I have to say.
Don't say a word, not a single word.
What are you doing? Come on in.
What? Is someone here?
Huh?
Su Ah.
[The Time When We Loved That Girl]
Don't think about anything today
and just get some rest, okay?
Dong Gu, I don't think this is
the right thing to do.
I should have a conscience.
How can I burden you?
I'll just leave.
Hey, Min Su Ah.
You said you have nowhere to go.
Where are you going this late?
Go in the morning if you're going.
Don't make me worry.
Get some rest.
What?
The guy Su Ah was dating is a con artist?
He took her apartment deposit and
the money for her to study abroad?
Yes.
It seems that there are many others
besides Su Ah who got scammed.
She got targeted by a real professional.
I feel so sorry for Su Ah.
Why would you?
She got punished for
casting my brother aside and leaving.
Hey, why would you say that?
What? She ended up that way
because she left you for a rich guy.
How could she dare to follow you here?
She has no conscience.
She has nowhere to go.
She has her parents' home.
Su Ah's father is sick.
He'll pass out if he hears about this.
She was shaking and crying in the park.
Don't make her feel unwelcome
and be good to her.
Gosh, you feel
so sorry for her, don't you?
Why? Do you still have feelings for her
and want to make things work again?
What are you talking about?
It's not like that, you...
No need to get mad if it's not true.
Dong Gu, I'm sorry to ask.
I can't help but keep looking at
those oranges from Jeju Island.
You punk! You actually want to eat that?
What are you going to do about the money?
What are you going to do?
You take care of it,
no matter what.
Otherwise, I'll kick you right out.
I will. I will.
What's with your voice?
Do you know what I did for these oranges?
Just one, just one.
Dong Gu, did you sleep well?
No.
I couldn't sleep well at all
because of these red stickers.
Oh, I see.
Wait a little bit.
I'll prepare breakfast soon.
No, it's okay.
I'll just have milk.
- Here's a cup.
- Thank you.
Oh, that stings.
Maybe it's the cold wind,
but my lips are so dry.
Hey, what are you doing?
The milk is overflowing!
What am I doing? Gosh!
What were you thinking about anyway?
Nothing. It's nothing at all.
This is crazy.
Why do I keep thinking about that?
I just made some pies.
Do you want to try some?
That's what this nice aroma was.
Wow, that looks great!
- Looks good.
- Looks delicious.
Joon Ki, have you looked into
how to get money yet?
Wow, the pies turned out great.
The shape is so pretty and
Yoon Ah, you're pretty too.
That guy...
What are you doing with the food?
Yoon Ah, are those walnuts in there?
Yes, why?
Soap, soap, antibacterial rinse...
It's just food.
Why is he acting like that?
He's allergic to walnuts.
He gets hives, chills, and diarrhea
when he eats walnuts.
He suffers for about a week.
Oh, I see.
Yeah, right.
He's acting like that
because I brought up money.
Su Ah, did you sleep well?
What's with the luggage?
I think I should go.
Do you have a place to go?
Don't worry.
I can get rent money
if I sell all of these.
I put them up online
and I already have a buyer.
Really? You should eat before going.
No, it's okay.
I have a conscience, after all.
I can't ask any more of you.
I'll get going now.
Bye, Dong Gu.
Goodbye, everyone.
Okay, goodbye.
Wow, those are all designer bags.
Good thing you guys broke up.
If you had married her,
she'd have bled our household dry.
Give it a rest.
I think I bought her one of those bags.
Oh, you fool.
Gosh... it's almost time.
Why isn't she coming?
Are you "Bag Shuttle"?
Are you "Usain Bolt,"
who wanted to buy the bags?
- Yes. Hello.
- Hello.
Could I see the bags first?
Yes.
I cherished them like I would my life,
so I can guarantee their condition.
Wow! They really look new.
- May I try it on?
- Of course.
Wow.
Do you want to try this?
- It's so nice.
- Look at the color on this.
Oh, wow!
What should I do? I like them all.
I will buy all of them.
- How much do you want?
- Really?
Hold on.
It is...
Oh, my shoelace is undone.
Are you good at running, by any chance?
Excuse me? Not really.
Why do you ask?
I used to be an athlete representing
Seoul in short distance running.
Oh, is that so?
The start is the most
important thing in running.
Take a look.
First, you need to get into a position
where you can take off whenever.
Now, say "bang"... "bang."
Put three fingers up like this.
"Bang."
- Put it up.
- Up? Up?
- Up, up, up...
- Up... bang!
Wow, she is really fast.
She really must be an athlete.
Usain Bolt, where are you going?
Over here, over here.
What the heck? Hey, stop right there!
Thief!
Usain Bolt, you awful girl!
So cold.
It's so cold.
Why is he calling me out in the morning?
Is the director not here yet?
Sorry, are you okay?
Yes, I am.
Wait...
Are you Bong Doo Shik?
What? Yes, but who...
It's me, Mal Geum.
Don't you recognize me?
Mal Geum?
Mal Geum as in Yoojin Elementary School,
Class 6-3. Yoon Mal Geum?
How long has it been?
Yeah, I know.
You haven't changed at all.
You're still pretty.
Really? You've become handsome.
No, I really haven't.
Ah, we should have coffee. I'll buy it.
- Go sit down.
- Okay.
Writer Bong, you're here early.
- Yes, you're here?
- Yes.
What is this about?
We cast the female lead for our film
and I wanted to introduce you to her.
What? You already cast the female lead?
Yes, her name is Cherry and
she's a rising star in this industry.
You'll like her once you meet her.
Cherry?
Oh, she's here already.
Cherry.
- Hello, Director.
- Hi.
Say hello, Writer Bong.
That's the Cherry I was speaking about.
I'll get going now.
I'll see you next time.
- Goodbye, Director.
- Bye.
Goodbye.
The script was fun.
You always liked to write as a kid.
I guess you really became a writer.
Huh? Yeah.
You always were mature as a kid.
I guess you became an ero...
Never mind.
I'll get going then.
Which way are you going?
I'm going this way.
See you next time, Cherry...
I mean, Mal Geum.
Okay. Bye, then.
Bye.
Yeah, it's been a long time.
I just thought of you.
You know that it was me who saved you
when you fell in the water, right?
Yes, I saved your life. Lee Joon Ki.
So, I was wondering
if you had some money.
I was... hello?
Hello?
You disloyal punk. I saved your life.
I don't need you! Who needs you?
You're back?
What's with the album?
Yoon Mal Geum?
Who is she that you
drew hearts next to her name?
My first love.
First love?
Wow, she's pretty.
Why are you suddenly
looking at pictures of her?
I ran into her today.
You ran into her?
How did you meet her?
As a writer for an erotic film,
and she was the erotic film actress.
Is she still pretty?
What happened? What's she doing now?
She's the lead female
of my erotic film script.
Are you crying right now?
You must be really happy to see
your first love again.
- Joon Ki.
- Yeah?
Gosh, you must've been really happy.
You're such an innocent kid.
You liked it?
Ah, it's so cold.
I have no money or place to go.
My conscience won't allow me
to go back to Dong Gu again.
I'm going crazy.
That nasty girl, Usain Bolt.
Su Ah.
- What are you doing here?
- Huh?
I was just passing by.
Oh, this was your building.
I never even imagined it was.
How could you not know?
You were here every day
just a few months back.
Huh?
Well...
I have night blindness,
so I can't see anything at night.
Night blindness? You have that?
Huh? Uh...
I got it after we broke up.
I must've caught it from someone.
My goodness. Min Su Ah.
You have nowhere to go, right?
Isn't that why you're here?
No way.
I didn't like any of the places,
so I was taking my time looking.
All right, then sleep here tonight
and look around tomorrow.
No, I do have a conscience.
How could I burden you again?
You said you have night blindness.
You said you can't see a thing at night.
Since you are so worried like this,
I'll stay here for just one more night.
Su Ah, go up and rest.
Oh, I can't stand this night blindness.
I really can't.
Oh, night blindness!
Night blindness, yeah right.
She's walking around just fine.
She was going on about her conscience
and now she's back?
I don't think she found a place,
so I brought her in.
What a load of crap.
Hey, you still have feelings
for Su Ah, don't you?
No, I don't! I don't!
Why would you bring that up here?
Where would I bring it up then?
Should I say it in the kitchen,
bathroom, bedroom, or to Su Ah?
Whatever, be quiet!
Did you even get the money?
Oh, this is nice and sweet.
I knew it.
Don't eat a single thing
until you get the money.
Yoon Ah, don't give this guy
any food starting tomorrow.
What?
Fine! You're so cheap and petty
that I won't eat.
I'll get that money somehow
and throw it in your face.
Wait and see, you punk!
I'm so scared.
I'm sure you'll get that money.
So scary! I'm going to pee my pants!
Hello. Yes, Tae Shik.
What time is the baby's party
this weekend?
Oh, 2:00 pm.
Okay.
By the way...
uh, is there any way
that I can get paid in advance?
Yes.
If you could pay me two years
in advance, I'd be really thankful--
Hello?
Hello...
Yes, two years was asking for too much.
Geez... what the heck.
What's she doing there?
She doesn't even have a blanket.
What if she catches a cold?
Hold on.
Why am I worried about it?
Why do I keep worrying
about this lady? Why?
Gosh...
All right. Yeah.
It's only sympathy.
It's like helping those
who are less privileged.
I must be crazy. I really am.
Oh, the smell.
What did she eat?
Dong Gu.
Yeah, what? Why? What?
Why are you so startled?
It's nothing.
Are you leaving now?
I should go. I do have a conscience.
Do you have a place to go?
Yes, I called my friend
and she told me to come.
Dong Gu, I really won't ask for
your help and burden you anymore.
Be well.
Yeah. Goodbye.
Okay.
What's with this lady today?
Does she have bowel issues or what?
Oh, it smells. What did she eat?
Oh, my word...
Okay, bro.
Thanks for the intro. Yeah.
Do I really have to do this?
I'm going crazy here. Gosh.
I'm going crazy here.
Why does Mal Geum have to be
the lead in my film?
How am I supposed to look at her again?
Did Su Ah leave?
She should call or something.
Hey, you worry about Su Ah that much.
Yet, you don't worry about me,
who's suffering this much?
Not at all.
What's going on with the money?
Did you get it?
I'll get it. I said I'll get it!
You expect me to believe that?
I'd believe a dog's baby over your words.
Wh... what? A dog's baby?
Hey, do you know what I decided to do
just to get that money?
What did you decide?
You don't need to know.
What are you going to do
if I manage to get the money?
If you can get that money...
I'll call you Father from now on.
You have to crawl through my legs.
Race... you can back out
if you're scared.
Why would I be scared?
Just get the money.
I'll do whatever you say.
Kang Dong Gu.
You'd better keep your promise.
I will get that money,
no matter what.
I will do it.
Mal Geum, you came
to see the audition too?
Yes, the director wanted me to come.
We're choosing the male lead,
so of course the female lead should see.
Okay, let's get started.
Hello, I'm the terminator
of the erotic industry.
Deok Chul, Deok Chul.
I am Won Deok Chul!
Yeah!
Wow, you have a good body.
What do you think, Writer Bong?
Don't you think he'd suit Cherry well?
What?
Wait.
The guy who gets cast today
will do a bed scene with Mal Geum.
With my precious first love?
What do you think, Writer Bong?
What? Uh, yes...
Everything's good, but his legs are
slightly bowed in an O-shape.
Those can't convey
the message of my story properly.
Really? What is the message?
An upright and straight heart.
Our film has that kind of message?
Yes.
Hm, everything is good.
But his double eyelid is so deep
that it goes against my plans.
Next person.
Would you like some water?
Hm, everything is good.
His collarbones are too prominent
and they don't fit the character.
Writer Bong, you are
pickier than you look.
No one feels quite right for this role.
Hello.
I'm a rookie actor
in the erotic industry.
My name is Lee Joon Ki.
Joon Ki!
Doo Shik!
So, you were writing
an erotic script all this time?
You were the one who wrote
those beastly lines?
You said it was a melodrama
about the love of family.
- It is, though.
- How is it?
"Goodbye, Sister-in-law."
I guess you are right.
Why are you here, Joon Ki?
I...
need to make money.
Dong Gu is harassing me so much.
I have to make money somehow.
I'm going to throw it in Dong Gu's face.
Anyway, let's keep this a secret.
That's what I want too.
Let's take this secret to the grave.
All right, good work on the audition.
Let's hear your opinions.
In my opinion...
I think Lee Joon Ki is the best.
What do you think?
What? Joon Ki?
I think Lee Joon Ki is the best too.
His acting was the best too.
Also, there's something about his eyes.
He's a natural erotic film actor.
- Writer Bong.
- Yes? I think--
If you have no issues with it,
let's go with Lee Joon Ki.
We have to film soon.
Okay? Okay.
- Good.
- I... I...
What? Joon Ki is the male lead?
Then Joon Ki and Mal Geum
will do a bed scene?
No! That can't happen!
This can't be. It can't!
Joon Ki, Joon Ki!
What are you doing right now?
Can't you tell?
I'm working on my physique.
The director told me to.
He already contacted you?
Joon Ki, are you really doing that film?
I have to! I'll do it and get paid.
I'll make Dong Gu crawl between my legs.
Joon Ki, what if your parents
happen to see it later?
My parents? It's okay.
My parents like erotic films.
They're very open people.
Then, what if your future wife sees it?
My wife? It's okay.
I'll meet someone who likes erotic films.
Then, what if your future child sees it?
My child? It's okay.
I'll watch it with them.
Isn't it important
to educate them early on?
Also, is it a crime
to be in an erotic film?
This is art too... art.
That's true, but still...
You wait and see.
Since I'm doing it,
I'm going to do my absolute best.
I'll film a bed scene that remains
famous in the erotic film industry.
You can't... you can't.
Stop, stop! Stop working out!
Why?
Stop it. Stop it.
I've only been eating eggs for days.
Now, my breath smells like rotting eggs.
How long do I have to stay here?
[Dong Gu]
Young lady, how many days
have you been here?
- Have you paid for your stay?
- What?
Not yet.
I was going to pay when I left.
Then pay now for
the time you've stayed.
Do I look like I'd run off
without paying for staying here?
I'll pay right now.
Oh! My wallet.
Ma'am, my wallet was definitely here.
It really was.
Okay, I understand.
I suppose that can happen.
I'll be on the phone, okay?
Hello, is this the police?
Ma'am!
The customer you have dialed
cannot take your call...
Su Ah hasn't picked up her phone in days.
Do you think something happened to her?
Why do you keep worrying about her?
Tell me the truth, Dong Gu.
You're not over her, are you?
You still like her, don't you?
Hey, no, I don't. That's not true!
Why would you say that here?
Then where would I say it?
Should I say it on
the veranda or the balcony?
Just forget it, okay?
It's just not like that, all right?
Oh, it's already time to make dinner.
I'd better prepare dinner.
I told you it's not true.
Why are you worried about strange things?
Why are you getting mad at me?
Stop saying useless things.
Yoon Ah, do you need help with anything?
No, it's fine.
Yoon Ah...
you're not misunderstanding
anything, are you?
Misunderstanding?
About Su Ah, I mean.
People help the less privileged,
and even those in Africa.
One could help an ex-girlfriend
who's going through a hard time.
That's true.
So, I'm saying that doesn't mean
I have feelings for Su Ah.
Or that I want to date her again.
It's not like that at all.
Just in case you had the wrong idea.
Why would I get the wrong idea?
Take good care of Su Ah.
Ah... sure.
I will.
Dong Gu, I'm going to the store.
Do you want anything?
I don't want to eat anything.
No need to get annoyed over it.
I'll be back.
My gosh.
Looks like she doesn't care at all.
You think I care about you, huh?
I just didn't want you
to get the wrong idea.
I'm not worried about it either.
Hello.
What? The police station?
Dong Gu.
I'm sorry.
The policeman insisted
on calling my parents.
I had no choice.
Get up. Let's go.
Let go. I'm really not going to go.
You have nowhere to go.
What are you going to do?
Follow me.
Still, this isn't right.
It really isn't right.
Why isn't it right?
Think about what I did to you.
How can I ask this of you again?
You can ask favors of me.
You should've lived
well after you left. What is this?
So, stop making me worry and go inside.
Look, your hand is all frozen.
Follow me.
What's wrong with this bag?
Lee Joon Ki.
You brought this all upon yourself.
Why did you show up there?
Please do not begrudge me.
There you go.
That tastes good.
What is this? What?
What's wrong with my face?
What is this?
What is it, Joon Ki? Is something wrong?
Oh, my stomach... my stomach.
Oh... Doo Shik.
Oh, you have hives all over your face.
What will you do?
I know. We have the reading today.
The shoot is in a few days too.
What do I do?
How can you shoot in this condition?
Your hives take a while to go away
and your diarrhea is severe, too.
I think you have to give up this film.
Right, Joon Ki?
Doo Shik, can you talk to the director
and postpone the shoot?
Are you crazy?
Do you know what he hates
more than anything?
It's postponing the shoot.
Then what am I supposed to do?
What else can you do?
You have to give up on it.
I'll talk to the director and make sure
he doesn't pursue you legally.
Just let it go, okay?
Okay... Doo Shik, thank you.
No need to thank me.
Where's the hair dryer?
What's wrong with your face?
I woke up this morning and I had
hives all over my face and body.
Did you eat something weird?
Did you have walnuts?
No, I didn't even go near walnuts.
Then why are you like that?
Wait... Joon Ki.
You knew you couldn't get money,
so you ate walnuts to put on a show.
What? Hey, you punk.
How can you say that to a sick person?
You said you would get the money.
This is so like you, Joon Ki.
Seriously, you idiot.
You arrogant jerk! Hey, hey!
Doo Shik, this won't do.
I'm afraid I have to film this movie.
What? What are you saying, suddenly?
I can't have that guy
look down on me any longer.
Kang Dong Gu, I will destroy you.
Joon Ki... Joon Ki.
Gosh.
Joon Ki, don't do this and just give up.
No... I will never give up.
Didn't you hear what
Kang Dong Gu said to me?
Still, how can you shoot
a film in this state?
No, even if I die on set,
I will never give up.
I will never give up!
Seriously! Just don't do it!
Why the heck are you yelling?
Is there a reason
why I can't do your film?
The thing is...
it's my first love!
Do you love me?
Since when have I been your first love?
What are you talking about?
Mal Geum, Mal Geum, Mal Geum!
She's my first love.
Yes, Mal Geum was my nickname
before I was born. How did you know?
I'm talking about Cherry!
Cherry is Mal Geum, my first love!
Huh? Mal Geum...
The Mal Geum in your album?
- Mal Geum is Cherry?
- Yes.
Joon Ki, so please don't do it.
Please, please don't.
Oh, I see.
Why didn't you just
say so earlier, Doo Shik?
- But, I have to film this movie.
- Why?
I have to do it and have Kang Dong Gu
crawl between my legs!
Otherwise, I'll die of rage.
Joon Ki, okay.
Then you just need to get revenge
on Dong Gu, right?
- Yes.
- Then how about this?
What?
Joon Ki went to the army at that age?
Yes, they showed up this morning
and forcefully dragged him away.
It seems he pulled all sorts of
dirty tricks to avoid the army.
What do we do?
What can we do?
There's no actor, so we need to postpone.
Ah, this is driving me crazy.
Also, the payment for your script
has been deposited, Writer Bong.
- You can check.
- Yes, thank you.
Geez.
We even kissed in front of people
and she doesn't care?
Fine, I won't care anymore either.
Hey, Kang Dong Gu.
What's with that arrogant pose?
What are you doing?
Pay the landlord with that money.
Use the remaining money
to buy snacks, kid.
It's real money.
How did you get all this money, Joon Ki?
You don't need to know!
What do you mean, Joon Ki?
You need to call me "Father."
You really want me to do that?
You wouldn't go back
on your word, would you?
Not the great Kang Dong Gu.
That would be petty.
Oh, gosh.
- Give it back, then.
- Father.
Yes, Son.
There was one more thing
you had promised me.
You want me to do that now?
You wouldn't go back
on your word, would you?
Not the great Kang Dong Gu.
That would be petty.
I'll do it! I can do it.
I'll do it.
Okay, Son.
Your dad is here.
Come to your father.
You worked hard for the money, Father.
Yes, Son. Come to your father.
- Good for you.
- Thank you.
It's been hard
for your father to raise you.
It's not right, you disobedient child.
I am your father starting today.
Yeehaw!
This soybean paste stew is delicious.
Yoon Ah, it's really good.
- Really? Eat lots, everyone.
- Yes.
Dong Gu, don't you have your appetite
back with the seizure stickers gone?
Yes, I can finally sleep now that
we paid the landlady back.
Kids, you know who
to thank for all of this.
Stop showing off about it, Joon Ki.
What did you call me?
Stop showing off, Father.
All right, Son.
I'll control it.
Son? What's that about?
I don't know. It's just something.
- Good morning.
- You're awake?
Su Ah, what is that? Do you have a cold?
This? It help the cheeks from drooping.
All models need it.
Model, what a joke.
You've never even been on a runway.
- Hey.
- I thought her jaw came loose.
Oh, Seo Jin.
You say the cutest things.
Oh my. Do you still have a mustache?
You have to put on cream if you're
shaving or your skin gets damaged.
Be careful of that.
Oh, it smells like fermented soybeans.
What? You don't like this stew?
It's not that.
It's nice to have something light
like Eggs Benedict for breakfast.
What?
It's nothing.
I'll starve for the sake of my diet.
Enjoy your meal.
She is so simple-minded.
She seems happy.
Did she get scammed or is she camping?
I can't tell with her.
I really don't like her.
Dong Gu, when is she leaving?
Dream on.
Su Ah isn't staying here for free.
She's a long-term guest.
It's a 100 percent deferred payment
with no time limit on the payment.
Your great brother even wrote up
a contract with her yesterday.
What? Are you crazy?
Why are you telling everyone?
Su Ah said she'd pay me back.
You fool.
- How long will you be manipulated?
- Fool?
You'd better stop.
Su Ah may be immature,
but she has a kind heart.
She's kind? Her?
What's with you, Son?
Why do you keep taking Su Ah's side?
Your father won't have
a daughter-in-law like that, so dream on.
Daughter-in-law?
I told you it's not like that.
Yoon Ah, I told you before.
It's really not like that.
I have no feelings for Su Ah.
- What?
- What's with you, Son?
Why would you explain to Yoon Ah?
Are you interested in Yoon Ah?
Are you with both girls?
You can't have two households!
Interested in her?
Seriously! You're full of it.
- You scared me.
- I nearly broke the table.
- What?
- Stop it!
Hey, hey. Son, Son!
Look at his manners at the table
when his father is here.
I'm going crazy here.
Why do I keep caring
what that lady thinks?
I must be crazy. I'm crazy.
I'm seriously crazy.
Son, didn't your dad tell you that you'd
become a pig if you read in bed?
Give it a rest.
Please give it a rest, Father.
I'm going to run away from home
if you don't stop.
- How long are you keeping this up?
- I don't know.
Until I'm no longer angry.
That will be a long time from now.
What kind of a rude child looks down
when his dad is talking?
Doo Shik, you haven't forgotten
about meeting later, right?
See you later.
What is it? Who is it from
that you're so happy?
Huh? Oh, Mal Geum.
Mal Geum?
Ah, you mean Cherry?
Who is that?
- Who's Mal Geum and who's Cherry?
- Huh?
She's my classmate from primary school
and she lived in the US.
Her English name is Cherry
and Korean name is Mal Geum.
Oh, a girl?
Things must be going well.
You two are texting and all.
I don't know about going well.
We're just friends.
Hey, it goes from
friend, to girlfriend, to wife.
From wife, to your enemy,
to the courtroom and you get divorced.
So, make it work.
Honestly, I do think about
Mal Geum a lot.
I don't know if it's because I like her
or if it's because she's an old friend.
Why don't you know?
If you like someone,
your heart races like crazy.
You hands and feet tingle.
You come out of it as if
you were hit by a hammer.
I do like being with Mal Geum.
How should I put it?
I don't feel certain.
Certain... certain...
There is a way to know
in times like this.
Should I tell you?
What is it?
You know NASA, right?
The USA's space program.
This is a method developed by
Richard Friedman.
It took five years to calculate it
using a super computer.
Really? What is it?
- Are you curious?
- Yeah.
We're almost there. Okay.
We have the answer.
The chances that you like Mal Geum
are 80 percent... 80 percent.
It's correct.
You definitely like Mal Geum.
Are you kidding me?
How can this tell me
if I like her or not?
Hey, this is strangely quite accurate.
Now, should I check to see if your
love with her will work out or not?
Yes.
Look carefully.
I need a mechanical pencil.
Get it ready.
First, you draw a heart
with the mechanical pencil.
Then let the lead out.
Just let it out, very long.
Make it as long as possible
and then start coloring the heart.
Keep coloring it like this.
If you can color this heart
without the lead breaking on you
your love with her will come true--
Shut up!
I'm the crazy one for asking you.
- Oh?
- Gosh.
Hey, this is extremely accurate.
Hey, it's true! Let's color it.
I'm crazy for expecting anything.
Why doesn't he ever grow up?
[When A Man Loves]
[Kang Dong Gu, Han Yoon Ah]
What? 76 percent?
Then, I like Yoon Ah 76 percent?
Does that make sense?
No, that can't be.
[Park Myung Ja's Pork Stew Rice]
Park Myung Ja.
91 percent!
So, I like Park Myung Ja 91 percent,
though I've never seen her?
Does that make sense?
Sure, they have very good pork stew rice.
That doesn't mean
I like Park Myung Ja, right?
Whatever.
There's no way this is right.
I told you to come down...
- Su Ah, what are you doing?
- Hm?
Uh, well I was...
Hold on.
Were you planning to
wash your face with milk?
No, I wasn't going to do that.
Then why did you pour milk
into the wash basin?
Well...
I was going to drink it.
I really like milk a lot.
Is that right? Then drink it.
Hm? Right now?
You said you poured it to drink it.
What are you doing? Drink it.
I was going to drink it anyway.
You'd better not leave one drop.
I'll just kick you out of here.
Sorry, sorry!
Okay, I was going to
wash my face with it.
What? Who do you think you are to yell?
- What did I do?
- Why is it so loud?
What is it?
Look at this.
Su Ah was going to use
the breakfast milk to wash her face.
What? Why would you?
I have to take care of my skin.
All models do it.
Dong Gu, you can add
the cost of milk to my stay.
Satisfied?
What kind of person does that?
She has nothing and
she's washing her face with milk.
Isn't she even sorry to us?
She says all models do it.
Let's stop and just go.
Oh, that fool. I'm going crazy.
I'm certain that Dong Gu
still has feelings for her.
What if they start dating again?
Dong Gu suffered a lot
after breaking up with Su Ah.
It'll be good if things work out well.
What a waste.
We don't even have guests and
she washes her face with milk.
Stop it, would you?
How can I stop?
We have no milk,
so we have to eat it like this.
Then don't eat it!
Look at this.
Even Doo Shik is so upset
that he's sighing over it.
That's not it.
Doo Shik met his first love again.
He's confused about
whether he likes her or not.
What? Why would you be confused?
I don't know. I'm just confused.
Really?
When I like someone,
I can even recognize their footsteps.
You recognize their footsteps?
That's a load of crap.
You're interested in everything
about the person that you like.
Then you end up knowing the sound
of that person's footsteps too.
Ah...
Then you must've known that
Tae Hyun snot guy's footsteps too.
Could you recognize
the sound of him picking his nose?
Hey, I told you not to bring him up.
That hurts. Stop hitting me.
- I'm hitting you to hurt you!
- Don't use so much force.
You're so strong that I'm so miserable.
I'm telling you that I'm right.
This theory has been proven.
You think that makes sense?
I'm telling you I'm right.
Hey, how can you tell if you
like someone by footsteps?
- Does that make sense?
- What about you?
Does the name compatibility make sense?
Of course.
Name compatibility was developed by
NASA's Richard Friedman.
He used a super computer--
Ow...ow!
What is it? Are you sick?
It's my heart.
- My heart...
- What about your heart?
- My heart is racing so fast.
- What?
- Why?
- I don't know.
My heart started beating as soon as
I saw that woman who passed by.
I can't breathe.
My hands are tingling
like there's an electric current.
These are the early symptoms
of falling in love.
Love? You think that makes sense?
Why not?
Fine, then I'll confirm it.
How?
I'll find out her name
and check our compatibility.
I have my chance to prove
Richard Friedman's theory.
That woman...
It's her.
Why would he prove it? He's crazy.
Joon Ki, where are you going? Joon Ki!
Excuse me, wait!
Wait!
Excuse me! Wait, wait!
Gosh, she went up.
- I'm going crazy.
- What's with you, Joon Ki?
Pull yourself together.
Seo Jin, that woman
could be my soul mate.
She's just a woman
you bumped into on the street.
That's why I need to check.
I only need her name, just her name.
Seriously, what's wrong with him?
What's with this?
Who left the TV on?
- You scared me!
- Shh... quiet.
Seo Jin will get mad at me.
Seo Jin went out with Joon Ki.
Really? I hid for no reason, then.
You scared me there.
I wanted to watch TV
and I had to do a massage.
I was hiding from Seo Jin.
Ah, I see.
You did the right thing. You did.
Seo Jin must be coming. It's Seo Jin.
That's not Seo Jin. It's Yoon Ah.
I'm home.
- Hi.
- It really is.
How did you know
just by hearing her footsteps?
Huh? I don't know.
When I like someone,
I can even recognize their footsteps.
What? How do I know Yoon Ah's footsteps?
Does that mean I like her?
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's kind of rude.
Oh, it's nothing.
It can't be. I like her?
Does that make sense? That can't be.
Yes, this is because
I have very good hearing.
Yes, of course.
Oh, someone's coming again.
These footsteps belong to...
the deliveryman?
You have a delivery!
Okay, I was right! Deliveryman!
- Deliveryman!
- Here.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
What are you doing?
I just have good hearing.
I have really good hearing!
Thank you! Thank you, Mister Deliveryman!
Cheers.
Wow, you're good at drinking, Mal Geum.
No, I'm usually not much of a drinker.
Today, I feel like drinking.
Honestly, today's my birthday.
Huh? Birthday?
Why didn't you say anything?
I would've bought you
a present if I had known.
It's okay. It's enough of a present
for you to drink with me.
Shouldn't you have a party
with friends if it's your birthday?
Or have dinner with your parents?
Actually, I'm not so close with my
parents since I started working.
I haven't seen them in a long time.
Same for my friends, too.
Let's stop talking about
depressing topics and just drink.
Sure.
Give that to me.
Mal Geum, I'll be in
the restroom for a moment.
Go ahead.
- What's with the ramen?
- Hm?
I was a little hungry.
You work so hard on your skin,
but you're allowed to eat ramen?
Oh, that's good.
I'll be at the grocery store.
Yoon Ah, you said you had a lot to buy,
so I'll go with you.
Ah, okay.
Su Ah, do you want to come too?
No, cold air is bad for the skin.
I am a model, after all.
Then, we'll be back.
I'll clean up, here so go on.
Okay.
What happened?
Are you okay, Su Ah?
Yes, I'm okay.
What do you mean?
You're bleeding a lot.
Yoon Ah, where's our first aid kit?
It's in the living room. I'll get it.
No, I'll get it.
Yoon Ah, you should go to the store.
I'm sorry I can't go with you.
It's okay. You should treat
Su Ah right away.
Okay. See you later.
Su Ah, I'll get the
first aid kit. Wait here.
I just need the name... her name.
Gosh, seriously.
No, not here.
Let's stop now.
How can we find her in this big building?
Why? Are you afraid?
That Richard Friedman might be right?
Who the heck is this Richard Friedman?
Look forward to it.
You'll see how scientific
the name compatibility is.
I will prove it to you.
[Cardiologist]
Doctor Kim Hyo Jung.
Seo Jin, this is her, right?
How would I know?
I'm certain this is her.
As soon as I saw the picture,
my heart started racing again.
99... 99 percent.
You see? Do you still not get it?
Hyo Jung and I are soul mates.
How would you know through
this name compatibility test?
Kang Seo Jin.
Just acknowledge it already.
You're being disgraceful right now.
Richard Friedman's theory
has been proven.
I'd better go meet Hyo Jung.
- Really?
- Yes.
Hyo Jung.
Hyo Jung, Hyo Jung.
Do whatever you want.
I just don't know anymore.
Why am I so curious though?
Come on in.
Hyo Jung.
- Sit down.
- Yes.
What part of you is feeling unwell?
It's my heart.
It's beating so hard.
Since when?
After I saw a beautiful woman,
it started to beat very suddenly.
Then I confirmed our
name compatibility was 99 percent.
I felt like my heart would burst.
Any other symptoms?
I feel very dizzy in the head.
My hands and feet are tingly.
I feel like there's electricity
and I'm short of breath.
Really? Let me take a listen
with my stethoscope.
No, Hyo Jung. There's no need.
Oh, Hyo Jung. That's cold.
- Oh? Oh?
- Oh...
- Why is it like this?
- Why am I like this?
- The sound of your heart...
- Can you hear it?
Something's off about it.
The symptoms you told me about are
bothering me. You need to be examined.
Nurse Kim,
please prepare a complete exam.
- Wait.
- Let's go.
What's going on?
What's going on...
What on earth is going on?
Excuse me.
What's going on here?
Patient, we're starting now.
Please don't move.
Okay.
What's going on here?
What is this, suddenly?
Oh! I'm going in.
Doo Shik, what took you so long?
Is the restroom that far?
Ta-da.
What's with the cake?
It is your birthday.
You should have a cake.
Thank you, Doo Shik.
You don't need to thank me.
It's my friend's birthday,
so I should get the cake.
Here you go.
Excuse me.
Are you an actor, by any chance?
What?
Yes.
See, I told you so. I told you.
So, what have you been in?
Films, TV dramas?
Well...
Sorry, but we're talking right now.
Ah! I just remembered it!
"Bikini Investigation," that erotic film!
You were in that, right?
I knew I had seen you in something.
It was that.
You're all covered up right now.
Wow, your body is really...
the best!
It's an honor to meet you.
May I shake your hand?
You don't want to?
Is she playing hard to get?
Sorry, but we're--
Forget it. Forget it. Never mind!
She thinks she's a star.
She's nothing but an erotic film actress.
Yeah, I'm in erotic films. So what?
If I act in erotic films, do I have to
shake hands with rude people?
Oh, she has quite the temper.
That's how she could be so bold
in those films and...
What did you say?
What did you just say?
Mal Geum, Mal Geum.
Let it go. Let's just leave.
- Oh.
- They're leaving.
She's very daring and bold.
What a joke.
How is it now? Does it still hurt?
No, it's okay.
We have breaking news for you.
[Large Grocery Store Fire, Huam-Dong]
There was a fire.
Wait, isn't that this neighborhood?
Oh, it is.
Oh, looks like a big fire.
Didn't Yoon Ah say she was
going to the grocery store?
Oh, Joon Ki.
Sit, sit.
What did the doctor say?
What are your results?
The thing is...
I don't have a good heart.
What?
My heart beating fast, shortness of
breath, and tingly hands and feet...
that's all because of a heart problem.
- Is it very bad?
- No.
Thankfully, they found it early enough
that it'll be okay once I take medicine.
What a relief.
I thought you were really sick
and I was worried.
Hey, how do you think I felt?
I was so scared in there
that I nearly peed.
What did you say?
Love at first sight?
Soul mates?
I'm embarrassed already, so stop.
Also, it is sort like a soul mate.
If I hadn't met that doctor earlier,
I could've met an untimely death.
There couldn't be a more dramatic fate.
Yeah, I guess the heavens
intended for you two to meet.
This can't be, though.
Our names had a 99 percent compatibility.
You saw that.
Stop it with the name compatibility.
- Does that make sense?
- What about you?
You said you recognize the person's
footsteps if you like them.
I'm just saying that's how it is.
Honestly, forget about
the name compatibility and all that.
Isn't it always the same
when you like someone?
Oh my. People must be hurt too.
[Large Grocery Store Fire, Huam-Dong]
You think about that person all day long.
Dong Gu, where are you going?
You worry when you don't see them.
When you see that person going
through a hard time
it's harder for you to see it.
Hey!
You punk! Get over here.
How dare you say that?
Get over here. Get over here!
Even if you get hurt...
you can do anything for that person.
Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah!
You can't come in. It's dangerous.
I know someone in there.
- It's dangerous.
- I don't care. Move!
Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah, Yoon Ah!
Dong Gu!
What are you doing here?
Is something wrong?
Just the fact that
they exist in the world...
makes you feel so relieved and grateful.
Well, isn't that what love is?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Go Go Waikiki]
I like that lady?
I'm crazy. I'm crazy.
Are you mad at me about something?
Don't be mad at me, Dong Gu.
I'm sorry.
I really thought I was going to do it.
I know how you feel.
- I'm setting you up with someone.
- What?
This is the 2017
fall/winter vintage collection.
- You look like a bum.
- A bum?
Everyone is looking my way.
You do have money, right?
What are you doing?
What? You got set up on a date?
Oh, isn't that Seo Jin?
We will begin Cherry's fan meeting.
Cherry, Cherry, Cherry!
It was embarrassing, right?
I can't do this film in this way.
Don't contact Mal Geum.
Pay for the breach of contract then.
I think I caused a problem.
This is the only place you can get
big money like that in short time.
Did we win?
We hit it big!