ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Is that the ocean?
It sure is.
What else would it be? A river?
It's Haeundae.
What is "Haeundae"?
What? You've never heard of Haeundae?
Is this your first time in Busan?
What have you been doing?
You should've visited sooner.
That's Haeundae over there.
It's very nice.
The Gwangan Bridge, Jagalchi Fish Market…
There are so many awesome places.
EXHIBIT HALL 1, HALL 2B
Second floor. Section B is clear.
Section D is clear.
What's going on?
SISYPHUS
"Thank you for taking the time
to join us."
No.
"I'd like to thank everyone
for taking the time
to join us."
You startled me.
Seo-jin, I told you
not to do things like this outside.
We're not "outside" right now.
What are your plans after this?
Sorry.
I have dinner plans
with the chairman and the investors.
Then how about later at night?
At night?
-Stop it.
-Stop what?
How do I look?
Let's see.
Everything looks great,
except for one thing.
-What?
-What do you think?
Your tie is crooked.
-There you go.
-All good?
Seo-jin.
Tae-sul asked me
if we were seeing each other.
I was taken aback.
Me too. Is he really not coming today?
No.
You're doing all the hard work,
yet he's the CEO of the company.
What an easy life.
What can I do?
The company wouldn't exist without him.
It's okay, though.
-You're giving the keynote speech.
-That's right.
-We'll begin in three minutes.
-Okay.
Shall we?
Let's go.
We'll begin in three minutes.
Be on standby.
I'd like to thank everyone
for taking the time to join us.
I'm Edward Kim,
the vice president of Quantum & Time.
CEO Han Tae-sul, who was supposed to give
the keynote speech today,
is at home trying to recover
from the plane crash.
So I will deliver
the keynote speech instead.
Writer William Gibson once said,
"The future is already here.
It's just not evenly distributed yet."
Ladies and gentlemen.
Meet the new future
Quantum & Time
would like to present to you today.
Isn't that Han Tae-sul?
-Gosh, it's Han Tae-sul!
-It's Han Tae-sul!
It's Han Tae-sul!
Hello.
Please welcome
Han Tae-sul of Quantum & Time!
-Do you want to die?
-What?
-You've been receiving death threats.
-I know. I'm the one receiving them.
-Leave the stage at once.
-Seung-bok.
I'm not going to die today.
Testing. My voice sounds nice.
First off, I'd like to apologize.
I was a bit late
because I took the train here.
I'm still scared of flying.
"The future."
You see,
the future is indeed already here
right in front of us.
To be more precise, it's in my lab.
I'm not letting it get out just yet
because we're still in the process
of applying for patent rights.
What the heck?
Hey, pay your fare! You crazy woman.
Excuse me!
Wait!
-Identify yourself.
-Move.
Hey! Get her!
-Stop her!
-What I'd like to show you today is…
It's…
this.
I guess you're disappointed.
I can hear our stock price plummeting.
Weight, 2,73g. Density, 0,468g/cm.
Height and width, 18mm. It's a sugar cube.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the future of Quantum & Time.
I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
I'm not saying Quantum & Time will open
a sugar refinery out of the blue.
They say that
any extremely advanced technology
is indistinguishable from magic.
So keep your eyes wide open from now.
Don't even blink.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Let us reveal our magic.
For the first time
in the history of mankind,
we succeeded in teleporting
a polymer compound
via quantum teleportation.
I didn't have breakfast,
so I needed a little pick-me-up.
All right. So what does this mean?
-Gosh!
-What happened?
Tae-san?
What's wrong with him?
Get him off the stage now.
Hurry!
Tae-san.
Tae-san! It's you, right?
Han Tae-san!
-Tae-sul, come on.
-Tae-san.
-Have you lost your mind?
-Hold on.
-Wait, Tae-san!
-Get a grip. Cut it out!
I have to go. I must go now.
Han Tae-sul.
Han Tae-sul! Get down!
Do you want the company to go bust?
-Tae-san!
-Are you crazy?
Let go, you jerk!
Han Tae-sul! Get down!
GET DOWN
I said, get down!
Tae-sul!
-Hurry up and go.
-Tae-sul.
-Tae-sul!
-We must get out of here! Come on.
-Be quiet.
-Tae-sul!
Tae-sul.
Han Tae-sul.
Han Tae-sul, wake up. We need to go.
Tae-san!
-What's going on?
-Let's go! Hurry!
An emergency at PEXCO. Requesting backup.
Evacuate everyone and move in!
-What was that?
-This way.
Police! The police are here!
-Police! Over here!
-Hurry up!
Where are we going?
Who are you?
Shut up.
There's no point in running away.
You know how this is going to end.
Get lost.
Get up.
Police! Over here!
Drop your gun. Hands up!
All right, calm down.
Calm down and drop your gun.
Don't follow us.
The suspect is armed.
She's on the run with a hostage.
They're stuck
in the emergency exit of the east wing.
Requesting backup.
Go in carefully.
-Up there!
-Spread out and go after them!
Get up.
Hurry up.
This is nuts.
This is nuts! Insane!
Run.
I'm exhausted.
I'm dizzy.
I'm so dizzy right now.
What the heck?
-What is this?
-Hurry. If you get caught, you'll die.
No way. Who are you?
-Follow me.
-Okay.
Freeze!
It's over. Drop your gun and surrender.
They're right.
That's enough. Let's surrender.
-No!
-Hey!
Hey!
Hey, wake up.
Damn it. What do I do?
He's alive. Thank God.
He looks a little different
from the photo.
I thought I'd die.
You're bleeding. We must run.
The Control Bureau isn't the only one--
You almost had us killed! Who are you?
What are you after?
Money? A terror attack?
Who put you up to this? Who sent you?
I saved your life.
I shouldn't have come here.
You're…
You.
You're this one, right?
"This one"?
What's going on?
Goodness.
Mr. Han Tae-sul.
What an honor.
We spoke a few times on the phone.
It's me, Mr. Park.
That's right.
Youngsters these days
fire bullets whenever they want.
Mr. Han, why don't we talk it out?
Sounds good.
Let's go.
You said we'd talk it out, jerk!
A violent terror attack took place
in broad daylight.
Korea is no longer safe from such attacks.
Choi Ji-eun has the story.
CEO Han Tae-sul was attacked
yesterday at 4 p.m. in PEXCO, Busan,
as Quantum & Time
was holding a conference.
This shooting incident,
which happens rarely in Korea,
has left the nation, which was known
to be free from gun violence, in shock.
The victim, CEO Han Tae-sul,
is said to be in critical condition.
The suspect,
who's an anti-corporate activist,
was arrested at the scene
immediately after the shooting.
We kept the kidnapping top secret
as you requested.
But the reporters are snooping around,
so it's only a matter of time.
-Give them money, gift cards, and wine.
-Yes, sir.
Have you identified the suspect yet?
And the gun? Where is it from?
Won't the information
help us find Tae-sul right away?
We're looking into it,
but the fingerprints aren't registered.
Neither is the DNA.
Therefore,
first, we need to find out if anyone
could be holding a grudge against him.
X-74852 TOP SECRET
CASE FILE NO. 582502
Among the e-mails, death threats,
and malicious comments he received,
we picked out only the serious cases
and organized them alphabetically.
That's a lot.
How many hours has it been
since he got kidnapped?
About 12 hours?
Right?
It's been about 16 hours.
It's been 16 hours--
No, it's been 17 and a half hours.
Isn't that enough time for him
to be dismembered
and buried in multiple locations?
Look.
Are you looking for a teenage boy
who ran away from home?
He's the CEO
of Korea's most valuable company.
A business tycoon got shot and kidnapped,
and you ask me who could be holding
a grudge against him?
Are you kidding me?
Do you know how many companies
have gone bankrupt because of him?
Do you know how many people
we fired during our M&A?
Environmental groups, labor unions,
and lunatics.
He received death threats
from dozens of people daily.
How could you ask
such an obvious question?
Find him.
If you can't do it on your own,
get the military's help and find him!
DO NOT ENTER
INVESTIGATION IN PROGRESS
Why did he miss the target
from such a close distance?
Right?
What a headache. I have so much to do.
Hurry up and go.
How many fell?
Three or so. One is unconscious.
Clean up the mess.
-Don't forget the witnesses.
-Yes, sir.
Where did she and Han Tae-sul go?
I'm really sorry. It's all my fault.
I'll find the kidnapper
as soon as possible--
You don't need to apologize.
Why is it your fault?
I told the reporters to keep it a secret,
and I've already called
all the top police officials.
The company has decided
not to give in to the kidnapper's demands.
-Sir.
-The stock price fell again.
Last time, we kept quiet
because you said we should wait,
but the situation
has worsened significantly.
Let's vote him out.
But how, when Tae-sul is still missing?
This has to be done if he doesn't return.
What if he does?
Tae-sul is like a son to me.
I've known him since he was in university.
I feel bad for him too.
I want to do whatever it takes
to save him,
but as one of the executives…
We have 20,000 employees.
And what about our subcontractors?
If we include their families,
we're talking about 100,000 people.
Given the current situation,
it would be better for him to not return.
Sir, this company can't exist
without Tae-sul.
We have you, Eddy.
And you should see this
as an opportunity, not a crisis.
Talk about a live nationwide broadcast
in broad daylight.
Is this where he was last seen?
Yes, it looks like he's hiding
with the girl he fled with.
If we search the motels in this area,
we might…
What's the matter?
The brokers.
Welcome!
You brat, can't you say hello?
Hey, wake up.
Are you awake?
Where are we?
I don't know.
I should be asking you that question.
How annoying.
I told you to run. This is all your fault.
What did you say?
Why are you blaming this on me?
Who are you?
You're the girl in that photo, right?
What's your name?
Tell me your name at least.
Seo-hae.
Seo-hae? As in "West Sea"?
What do you want from me?
Forget it.
Do you see that steel ruler
under your feet?
Extend your leg. I think you can reach it.
You can reach it, right?
We'll pick it up
and use it to cut this rope.
After that… We'll think about that later.
We're screwed.
My plan got all ruined because of you.
-Come on!
-What?
I told you to hand it over.
Hey.
I don't understand
why you're so angry right now.
It's not like I asked you to save me.
I lost sight of my brother because of you.
Tell me everything while we're at it.
Who are you? Are you stalking me?
And what's with that wedding photo?
Did you photoshop it yourself?
Then what? Did we do it?
Did we have a one-night stand?
Are you crazy?
Hey!
You're the crazy one. Well done.
I guess we'll die here, then.
We've never met before. Okay?
Are you kidding me?
You'd better tell me the truth.
Who sent you?
Who are you?
Me? The person who saved your life.
Then save my life now.
What the heck is this?
If you want to live,
shut up and stay still.
Hey, if you want to live,
go pick up that ruler.
-Pick up the ruler now.
-Be quiet.
You be quiet.
What's going on here? You guys woke up.
Let's see.
Goodness, why bring this?
What is all this?
Why would they risk their lives
to bring this useless junk
all the way here?
Don't the brokers there tell them
they don't need these things here?
Goodness, Mr. Han.
Did you sleep well?
You look more handsome
with your eyes open.
I dressed your wound here.
I'll change the gauze for you later.
Cut it out. Don't be such a flirt.
What?
Do you have a death wish?
Hey!
Don't fight in front of the guests.
Mr. Han.
Come with me.
Let's go inside.
Close the door behind you.
You guys should eat something.
Come on in.
Where is this from?
Sit down, both of you.
You fools always forget
to bring the bottle opener.
It's been 72 hours since
Quantum & Time CEO Han Tae-sul got shot,
but the police haven't even been able
to identify the suspect yet.
Initially, the company stated
that CEO Han was doing fine,
-but he hasn't been seen in public,
-See? They're keeping it secret.
-raising speculation that he is in danger.
-The society should be transparent.
CEO Han's bodyguard, Yeo,
who got injured at the scene,
is unconscious and in critical condition
at the moment.
That was a good meal.
Seon-ho!
Make me a cup of coffee.
Coffee, anyone? No?
Get it right this time.
One cream, two sugars.
If you get it wrong again, I'll kill you.
Yes, sir.
That idiot is so dumb.
He gets it wrong every single time.
Wait and see.
He'll put in two creams and one sugar.
Anyway, did you guys get some rest?
Right.
Now that we've had some food,
let's get down to business.
I'm the owner of Asia Mart.
But this is only a small part
of my business.
Our main focus is…
We're like the unofficial embassy.
We look after people
who came here from the other side.
Mr. Han,
the reason I brought you here is--
Why are you trying to kill me?
Kill you?
No!
The folks from the Control Bureau
tried to kill you.
As you can see,
I brought you here safe and sound.
I even got your injuries treated.
If I wanted to kill you,
you'd already be dead.
The Control Bureau? What do they control?
Where's the key? Did you bring it?
What happened to my brother?
Why are you asking me?
That key is mine!
-No, it's mine.
-You little…
What is the Control Bureau?
And what kind of "embassy"?
What happened to my brother?
And the suitcase?
Tae-san fell from the sky.
What is going on?
Why?
-Do you want to know?
-Yes.
It'd be better for you to remain unaware.
Fine.
Then let me ask you one last thing.
Think carefully before you answer.
Okay, Mr. Han.
Let's say there's something
you regret doing in the past,
and you want to change it.
How much would you be willing
to pay for it?
Everything I've got.
"Everything"?
All of it?
I see.
I understand what you mean.
I'll just take this.
-Did you get it right this time?
-Yes.
All right.
See? He got it wrong again.
Even though I know
he'd get it wrong every single time,
I can't help it.
You see, the future is…
It's a mirror of the present
and can't be changed.
That's right.
If I tell you,
give me the key.
Okay.
All right.
Seeing is believing, so let me show you.
Guys.
Show Mr. Han what we exactly do.
Are you really taking them along?
You've never let me go with you.
It's nothing nice.
Fine, if that's what our boss wants.
-Is anyone coming?
-Let's see.
No.
Let me check another server.
That's the downloader.
What is she downloading?
Hold up your hands.
Put this on.
Your hands.
You put this on too.
-Why?
-Why ask?
Don't do it, then.
Why is he aiming the rifle at us?
Is he a robot?
Hey, what do you mean
by "from the other side"?
Where are you from?
That's not important.
Then what is?
The important thing is…
I spotted one.
The temp agencies.
I hate that place.
Why do they keep sending them there?
It's the best place to disguise yourself.
Let's go. Turn around.
Take this.
For motion sickness. Don't puke.
Hey, you.
You're from the other side, aren't you?
You should've reported your arrival
as soon as you got here
and handed over your belongings.
Why did you run away?
Didn't you get any instructions
on your way here?
Nope.
"Nope"?
Why are the youngsters these days so rude?
-What's your name?
-Seo-hae.
-And your last name?
-I don't have one.
What about your parents?
I don't have any.
Come on.
No one is born without their parents.
What a rude brat.
Fine. Who do you know here?
No one.
No one?
-Not even one?
-Nope.
Okay. Then why did you come here?
Sightseeing.
Sightseeing? That's nice.
Got a death wish?
You little…
By the way, if you took the downloader,
you--
You need to pay.
There's no such thing as a free ride.
If you don't pay…
Hold on.
Look at this.
What's all this?
What are these for?
Are you going to war or something?
Ridiculous. How cute.
What's this?
What is this? A diary or a planner?
Give it back, or I'll kill you.
Damn you.
"Dear Seo-hae,
Happy birthday. By the time--"
FOOD, CURRENCY EXCHANGE,
JOB PLACEMENT, INQUIRIES WELCOME
You little…
What's wrong with you?
Sit down. Back to your seat!
Hold on.
Hey, calm down.
That thing's huge.
If you fire it, everyone here will die!
Calm down, please.
This isn't the US.
Can we not resolve conflict without guns?
I'm so not used to this.
You let go of him first and sit down.
And you, put your gun down.
Enough already.
Good. We want peace.
We're good now. Peace.
Why on earth did you read her diary?
Hey, this is mine.
Guys, kill them.
Stop! Let's get this straight.
Why is it yours?
Because everything she brought is mine.
What a nasty jerk.
I'll buy that diary.
Are we good now? I'll buy it.
-For how much?
-How much is it?
It's expensive.
Come on. I'm rich. How much do you want?
A hundred million won?
Her diary costs 100 million won?
Where's my phone?
Hand it over.
Come on, Mr. Han.
If you turn on your phone,
it would be like announcing
you're held captive here.
Will you call your family,
ask them how they're doing,
call the cops and make a report?
Is that your plan?
No.
The GPS tracker on my phone
is always turned off
because my friend, Seung-bok,
always stalks me.
I'm serious.
It will only take ten seconds,
so turn it on and see.
Seung-bok?
Give me his phone.
If the GPS is on,
you're dead meat.
It's true.
Here.
See this bank account number?
Send 150 million won here.
Wait, you said 100 million.
There's a fee for using the account.
What's the matter?
Are you reluctant to send it
because it's too much?
"A fee for using the account"?
I've never heard of such a fee.
Fine, 150 million won.
Look, 150 million won.
We're good now, right?
Impressive.
This is why the ladies love you.
Just hand over the diary.
All right.
Goodness.
I never asked for your help.
You said you saved my life.
We're even now.
-Do you have the key?
-Why do you ask?
That scumbag will kill you
the moment you give him the key.
I know.
You guys are so chatty.
We're here.
-Two plasterers!
-Over here!
Come here! You too.
-Your ID and safety certificate.
-ID and certificate?
-Here you go.
-Get in the car! Your ID and certificate.
-I brought them with me.
-Just get in the car.
GWANGSEONG MANUFACTURING
SEONGMUN STAFFING SERVICES
Those illegal immigrants
should get deported!
-Hey, you.
-What did you just say?
Hey! Go back to your country,
you cockroaches!
-What?
-You rat!
What did you say?
-You punched me first!
-We can't get jobs because of you punks!
-Damn you.
-Hey!
-We're in this mess because of you!
-You jerk!
-What's your problem?
-You scumbag, let go!
The Control Bureau! They're here!
-My gosh!
-The Control Bureau is here.
They're here. Run!
-Let's go.
-Just run!
-Are they here?
-Go. Hurry!
-They're here!
-We're here for an inspection. Don't move.
Don't move!
Is this a crackdown or a ruse?
Back off.
Arrest all those illegal immigrants!
Those scumbags…
Why are you scanning us?
We're all Korean! Arrest them!
-Get them!
-Catch them!
You punk.
-Let me go!
-Come here.
Come here.
Let go of me!
Those jerks from the Control Bureau…
Look at them
trying to suppress and control
the small business owners
who work hard to make ends meet.
Then who's responsible
for this country's economy?
What a mess.
Hello, Bingbing.
The Control Bureau is here.
Can you take a look and locate them?
I got one, just now.
-I sent you the coordinates.
-All right.
Mr. Han, let's do some work.
Everyone.
It's now time for you to witness
the secret of this hidden world.
Let's go.
This is the spot.
What are we waiting for?
-A person.
-Who?
Do you contribute to the National Pension?
I paid 400,000 won this month.
They're thieves. Total swindlers.
We all know that
the pension money will run out by 2040,
but they keep collecting contributions.
Why do you think this is happening?
Weird, right?
But if you think about it,
even weirder things happen.
Have you ever experienced
anything like that?
Such as
seeing a photo of you
that you don't remember taking
or seeing a photo of something
that hasn't happened yet, for example.
When is this?
This is crazy.
The conference in two days.
Why? You've experienced it?
I guess you have!
That's it, Mr. Han!
You're smart, so think about it.
How can something like that happen?
Mr. Han, the important thing
isn't where they come from.
That's not important.
Then what is?
The important thing is…
What matters is
"when."
He's here.
Have you heard of this quote?
"The future is already here.
It's just not evenly distributed yet."
Cool, right?
Welcome to the future.
Welcome to
the future.
You want to know why they come here?
It's because of regret.
Even when they know
they can't change anything,
they think,
"Why didn't I do that back then?"
The thought torments them every night.
I know where your brother is.
-What?
-Han Tae-san.
Did you find him?
-They got away.
-Find them, then!
Keep tracking Han Tae-sul's phone.
And hijack every signal that it transmits.
It's good to see you again, Mr. Han.
Go! Hurry!
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs