ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Look what I've got!
"SPRING DAY"
BTS
Nice!
CHOOSE THREE FLAVORS
Thirty-eight centimeters…
ICE CREAM!
Did you find any batteries?
No, everything's taken already.
Same here. We should look somewhere else.
Okay.
I'll see you at Exit 2.
UPLOADERS
VISIT US FOR CONSULTATIONS
OPEN 24/7, ALL YEAR ROUND
CONSULTATIONS AVAILABLE (ADDITIONAL FEE)
SISYPHUS
Let's finish up quickly and go eat.
Hurry up.
What's your number?
Around 250,000.
We arrived pretty early.
Theirs are around 10,000.
Downloads are difficult,
so there's only a ten percent chance
of success.
And even if they come over,
half of them get caught
by the Control Bureau.
That means there's only
a five percent chance of surviving
and settling down in Korea.
But they still risk everything
to come over to this side.
Do you get it now?
Han Tae-san came here through that.
But on the way here,
something went wrong with the downloading.
Are you okay?
No.
It happens the first time.
Did he take the medicine?
-Tell him not to vomit in the van.
-Goodness.
All right. Stop it.
That's enough. Stop it.
I'm done talking, so give me the key.
Can I go there and watch them?
Them? What's there to see?
Fine. Have a look and give me the key.
Okay.
If Tae-sul does anything dumb,
just shoot him.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
-What?
-What is that?
-Atropine.
-Why are you using that?
They're taught to run
as soon as they arrive.
Why do they come only in their underwear?
They need to transfer the least amount
of information to prevent errors.
What's in that suitcase?
Stuff they want to bring.
Stuff that could be money.
You said they need
the least bit of information.
They can't come empty-handed.
They need money to survive.
Right. But…
What if someone's future self comes here?
Won't there be any issues
if it's the same identity and information?
Their bodies and memories get mixed.
And eventually, one side disappears.
Are they flirting or what?
But why are you taking all their stuff?
-Are you complaining?
-No, I'm not.
Do you have my phone?
-What?
-I'm just asking if you have it.
Yes. I have it. So what?
Nothing.
Hey, Hayby. Send my location to Seung-bok.
Location sent.
-We found him.
-Really?
Okay, got it.
Han Tae-sul's phone is on.
He's nearby!
You're not supposed to inject
atropine in the neck.
It's for the thighs.
Hey! Go get him!
Hey.
Hey!
You idiot. Catch him at least.
Hurry up and get him!
It's the Control Bureau!
Darn it.
Let's go.
Hurry up!
That jerk.
ASIA MART
I have to get out of here.
Han Tae-sul.
Help me.
I know where your brother is.
-What?
-Han Tae-san.
I'll tell you where Tae-san is.
Just help me.
Get up. Come on.
How could she just run away by herself?
Hey. You really know
where my brother is, right?
You'd better not be lying.
What?
Darn it!
It's good to see you again, Mr. Han.
You're right. We should become friends.
Go!
-Get them!
-Hey!
Hey, it's an electric car.
Wait.
Damn it, it's stuck.
Get in. Hurry.
Hold on. The registration certificate.
The registration certificate.
Okay, 39572.
It's 39572.
I need the ID and password.
But I don't have that,
so I'll install an app first,
enter the VIN,
and log in through the manufacturer's
website database.
-Excuse me.
-"Sign in." It's not working.
Hang on. We don't have time,
so I'll make a new app.
Open the Amacs text editor.
The Perl script.
-Mr. Han.
-What?
-The woman.
That little…
People are watching. Put it away.
Catch her.
Hey! Stop fighting and come over here!
Come on. Work!
Why isn't it working?
Come on. Work.
It's working! Okay!
Go! Hurry!
"Go"? You want us to go?
-Hurry up!
-Get them!
"Go"? Darn it!
Get them!
Goodness. We finally got you.
Yes. We couldn't catch Han Tae-sul,
but we caught the girl who kidnapped him.
Okay. We'll bring her there right now.
Hi.
Where did Han Tae-sul go?
I don't know.
Where did he go?
You're not going to talk?
Why did you approach him?
Tell me. Why did you approach him?
If you don't talk, I'll kill you.
I'm not going to die today.
That nonsense again?
All right. Let's see if that's true.
Didn't I tell you to hurry?
How could you just abandon me?
You ran away on your own too!
We're even now, then.
Come on.
I'm home.
Why haven't you eaten?
I'm already busy as it is.
All you have to do is press one button.
Why can't you do it yourself?
What does it say?
I can't read it.
Give me that.
Over 240? Before eating?
Mom, did you eat ramyeon again?
No, I didn't.
Mom.
The doctor told you to eat
only multigrain rice and vegetables
because of your complications.
But it tastes awful.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you want to become blind?
Eat up.
I'm going to die anyway.
Then just starve to death!
Where are you going? You just got here.
I'm on duty today.
Son!
I'll see you later.
Whatever.
Lieutenant,
can't you just get automatic tickets?
The thing is,
a mutual friend of mine
won the lottery by choosing
the same numbers on ten tickets.
That's impossible. Come on.
It's true.
Lots of people won that way recently.
HOME
-Aren't you going to answer it?
-She always says the same thing.
"I can't see well." Stuff like that.
How is she these days?
Same as usual. She doesn't watch her diet.
I hate her.
Still, don't treat her like that.
You should do better, Hyeon-gi.
You'll regret it later
when your mother is gone.
Just like I did.
Be good to her while you can.
I will.
A robbery at 201, District A.
Thank you. Bye.
We're heading there.*
-Why is in this neighborhood?
-My goodness.
-What should we do?
-The cops are here.
It's okay. They're here.
-Excuse us.
-It's the cops.
What happened, ma'am?
Some guy appeared just in his underwear!
He must be a pervert!
Could he be a flasher?
Which way did he go?
That way!
It's so scary.
Go.
-How can he do that?
-All right.
Please calm down.
When exactly did you see him?
I think it was about 30 minutes ago.
You said it was an hour ago.
-Oh, right.
-What did he do after that?
He just ran that way!
Did you find him?
No.
Oh, my gosh!
Excuse me, sir!
Water!
Get up.
Get up!
Water.
Sir, where did you get this?
You stole it, right?
Just come with me to the station.
Sir. You have the right to an attorney,
and the right to defend yourself.
-You may request a review--
-Water!
Water.
All right. Fine.
I got the suspect.
-Did he get him?
-He got him!
Good work. Let's wrap up and have dinner.
Just bring him out.
Lieutenant!
Hyeon-gi!
Hyeon-gi, what are you doing?
Everything is going to end now.
Help me.
Come on.
What's going on?
What?
We'll take care of this.
-Who are you?
-Please answer this call.
Hello?
Let him go!
All right.
I'll call you back when we're done.
-Hyeon-gi, come on out. Let's go.
-Officer Jung will come with us.
-What's this about?
-We need to do some further investigation.
-Cover his eyes.
-What?
Sir, a text came from Tae-sul
early this morning.
Hello.
This is our vice president, Eddy Kim.
Eddy, he's from
the National Intelligence Service.
-Please have a seat.
-Okay.
I'm sorry, but I'm not allowed
to reveal my exact position.
I heard Mr. Han
contacted you this morning.
-Yes.
-Did you report it to the police?
No, I can't trust them.
Good thinking.
And you spoke to him on the phone?
No, just a text. He sent his location.
If you didn't talk to him yourself,
how can you be sure
that it was him who sent it?
No one except Tae-sul
can turn on that phone.
Whether I talked to him
or got a text from him,
it doesn't change the fact
that he was there.
-We have to send someone--
-Mr. Kim.
I know you're feeling impatient right now.
I'm sure you're anxious.
Could you show me that text?
Of course. Just a minute.
MESSAGES
NO MESSAGES
Wait.
But I got a message. I definitely got--
When you're feeling anxious,
you may believe
you got a message when you didn't.
No, that's impossible.
Sir.
I will go now.
-Okay. I'm sorry for bothering you.
-It's fine.
-Wait--
-Eddy.
Keep tracking Han Tae-sul's phone.
And hijack every signal that it transmits.
All right.
The number you have called
is not available.
-Leave a message--
-Why isn't he picking up?
Darn it!
What's the date today?
-August 19.
-It's August 19, 2020.
Excuse me.
You said you know where my brother is.
Where should we go?
Imun-dong, Dongdaemun-gu, 192…
Just go to Sinimun Station, Exit 2.
Does that mean my brother's in Imun-dong?
No, I have to stop by somewhere first.
Come on!
What are you playing at?
I'm taking you with me because
you said you know where my brother is!
-Just go there first.
-Where is he?
I have to go there first!
You're driving me nuts.
Fine. I'll take you there.
You'd better tell me when we get there.
Hey, you.
Are you really from the future?
Yes.
Is that how you predicted
the shooting in Busan?
-Yes.
-And what's with the downloader?
I coded that in 2001.
There are uploaders in the future.
I don't know how it works,
but it's like a copy machine.
They copy stuff
and send it to the other side.
They go inside a huge machine.
It's a quantum teleporter.
It teleports objects
by controlling the time value.
That's what I demonstrated
at the conference.
But controlling the time of humans
or other objects
with a huge amount of information
is technically impossible.
I'm not sure,
but it was around 2021
when the uploaders appeared.
What the heck?
Why are they coming here?
The success rate
is only about five percent.
And what's with
that radiation detector or something?
Are they getting exposed
to radiation on the way?
Hey, stay away from me.
Stick to that side.
Then if my brother got into that accident
after arriving here on an uploader,
he really is alive right now.
-Yes.
-He won't die if he doesn't come back.
Then I should find him
and tell him to never come.
And what's with that wedding photo?
Are we going to get married?
How am I supposed to know?
It can't be true.
We could've just taken a photo.
I'm sorry, but you…
Darn it.
You're not my type.
-You're not my type either.
-I don't want to get married.
Fortunately, now that we know,
let's agree not to get married
in the future.
Why don't you want to get married?
Never mind.
Just be quiet and stick to that side.
-You're annoying.
-I'm way more annoyed than you.
Why are you here, then?
Is it like some crazy TV show?
Is there some secret behind your birth?
Am I your dad?
-Shut up.
-Okay. What a relief.
I was nervous for a second.
Over here.
What's this?
Goodness.
What's all this?
Mom!
I'm home.
You're here.
Who are they? Are they your colleagues?
What took you so long?
I'm sorry.
I'm a bit late.
HWA RAMYEON
What the heck is he doing?
Mom.
You said you wanted
some ramyeon last night, right?
I did.
Let's have some ramyeon.
You told me not to.
It's just a little. It's okay.
Eat up.
It won't taste good if it gets soggy.
You should give some to our guests.
It's okay. They already ate.
Hurry up before it gets soggy.
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
I had this every day when you were young
because we had no money.
I'm used to this taste now.
Mom.
I even added rice cakes, your favorite.
Here.
It's so good.
You want to know why they come here?
It's because of regret.
BOARD MEMBER: EDWARD KIM
AUGUST 15, 2020
THE VOTE HAS BEEN APPROVED,
CONFIRMING CEO HAN TAE-SUL'S DISMISSAL
They come here because of regret.
Even when they know they
can't change anything,
they think,
"Why didn't I do that back then?"
The thought torments them every night.
That's what regret is.
Mom. I'm sorry.
I was always harsh to you
and I didn't let you eat what you wanted.
I always came home late,
and I always left you at home alone.
I'm so sorry.
I know.
It's all right.
Mom.
I missed you so much.
I know.
Mom. Rest well.
I love you so much, Mom.
Mom.
So?
What about you? What did you regret?
Listen carefully.
You may already know,
but they're trying to kill you.
Like who? The Control Bureau?
Everyone. Especially Sigma.
"Sigma"?
Busan was only the beginning.
They'll keep chasing after you.
Why are they trying to kill me, though?
I'm not sure, but…
It's probably because
you invented the damned uploader.
-Me?
-I came to protect you.
And whatever happens,
I'm going to stop you
from inventing the uploader.
Why?
Tell me later.
Thank you.
The address.
You won't like what you'll see there.
Just give me the address.
Promise me one thing.
Don't go to the second floor.
The study.
And you. Don't go outside.
There's a sniper.
My first mission was to kill you.
Who were you working with?
The Control Bureau.
I'm really sorry.
I did things that
I shouldn't have done to you.
I'm sorry.
It was August 27.
There was some kind of party.
JONGNO-GU, SEOUL
I found them.
I see Han Tae-sul
and two illegal entrants.
That's the chairman's house.
What happened--
Wait.
-Hold fire!
-Hold!
Hold fire!
Capture them alive.
Hey! Over here!
It's over now! Surrender!
What are you doing?
I was thirsty.
Do you want some?
Is there no coke in the future?
The boiling point of this butane gas
is -1 degrees.
What are you on about?
If I do this,
it stays in this bottle as a liquid.
And…
Let's go!
Hey!
The Control Bureau…
Run. Take the car.
No matter what I do
from now on,
forgive me.
That's the only way you can win.
Sir!
Let's go.
What's going on? Report!
We lost communication.
Second unit, going in.
That one!
Hey! Seat belt!
They got away.
Find them, then!
SMART INTERSECTION DATA SYSTEM
CAMERA VIEW
Stop. Number two.
-Rewind that.
-Yes, sir.
Zoom in.
SCAN RESULT
FEMALE, GANG SEO-HAE, 250811
-What's the plate number?
-It's 5816.
SMART INTERSECTION DATA SYSTEM
DATA
VEHICLE TYPE: MATIZ
I found it.
Block the routes and get a drone there.
-It's a drone.
-What? A drone?
Here they go again.
But how did they know our location?
They know everything.
This happened in their past.
My smartphone.
My GPS was on!
-That was so close.
-Go faster!
Move aside!
Hey! Watch out!
-Can't you drive properly?
-Why don't you drive, then?
-I can't!
-Why? Can't you drive?
You can shoot guns
and you can climb down a building,
but you can't drive?
Are there no cars in the future?
Or are they all self-driving cars?
-Stop talking and just drive!
-Hey.
I don't know what your world is like,
but this is a civilized society.
We don't chase people in cars
or shoot guns!
I get it. Just drive properly.
What just happened?
-What is this?
-Who did this?
You're attracting everyone's attention.
Is this a game to you?
Clean up the scene!
Keep the internet and media quiet,
and send more drones!
What the heck? They're chasing us again!
One, two.
Three, four. There are four of them now.
Those jerks!
They're using my taxes on stuff like this?
We've blocked their escape route.
-Start cornering them.
-Yes, sir.
Where did they go?
Go faster! Hurry!
Shut up. I'm trying my best.
Hey, watch out!
Duck!
Okay!
Wait.
-What?
-Darn it!
Hold on tight!
We can't just keep running.
Get out and fight them, then!
Hey!
-Turn the car around.
-I can't!
-Turn it around.
-I can't turn it now!
Hang on. It's 50km/h now.
Ten meters. One, two…
Move!
Hey! Put your seat belt--
Good work.
Now, put your seat belt back on.
You too, for turning the car around.
It's nothing.
I'm sure there was one more.
Where did it go?
Get lost.
Did you block their escape route?
Yes, sir.
Yes, I understand.
But where did the orders come from?
How can you not know?
Why do we have to block
a road that's under construction?
Hello?
-Sir.
-Any news from Officer Jung?
-No, not yet.
-Where did he go?
-What did you find?
-It's a robbery and murder suspect.
We're doing all this for one robber?
Did he rob the Blue House or what?
It says it was just a normal house.
REQUEST TO BLOCK SUSPECT'S ESCAPE ROUTE
Hey, what is this?
This is Hyeon-gi's address.
What's going on?
-Stop that car.
-Contact the Center! Hurry!
-Hey, look ahead!
-Ahead?
Stop chasing us, you jerks.
Get lost, you assholes!
Stop the car!
-Plate number--
-Stop the car!
Plate 5816! Hey!
Hey! Contact the Traffic Center! Hurry!
Contact the Center. Page them.
Are they really going to keep chasing us?
What are you waiting for? Speed up.
-Go faster!
-This car can't go any faster!
-What's that over there?
-What?
-Over there.
-There?
What? Is the road cut off?
-Stop the car!
-Hey!
-How can I?
This is insane.
What happens if we get caught
by the Control Bureau?
Do you really want to know?
No, I was there for a short while.
It wasn't good.
They're all coming out. Let's go.
-What?
-Get out.
Those jerks.
Darn it.
What are you doing?
-Take that off.
-What?
Take it off. Leather absorbs water.
You might not be able to swim.
You want to jump?
Do you have any other ideas?
Mr. Han!
Come with us.
The wind is pretty chilly.
It'll just get tougher for you
if you keep stalling.
You're right.
It's so windy, I might fly away!
Hey, take off your bag.
What are you doing?
-What?
-If you just jump, you'll die.
-You need to think.
-Think about what?
The water won't be cold
this time of the year,
so you have to stretch out your legs
and fall vertically.
-How much do you weigh?
-Why do you ask?
-I need to calculate.
-No way.
-Okay, let's say you weigh about 55kg.
-It's 50kg.
What? 50kg? Why are you so skinny?
You need to eat more.
If you drop from this height,
you'll go six to seven meters underwater.
The current will be fast,
and you won't see anything.
You won't know which way is up.
So what I mean is,
don't let go of my hand.
They won't be able to run away,
so don't shoot. Capture them alive.
Run, on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Three!
Find them!
Dear Seo-hae,
Happy birthday.
By the time you read this, I'll be dead.
Don't be surprised.
What you're looking at is from yourself.
Listen carefully.
There is something we must do.
Take the uploader and go to the past.
Save Han Tae-sul.
If he lives, the war can be stopped.
Only you can do this.
Han Tae-sul.
Stay away from him at all costs.
You must not cross paths with him.
Don't even talk to him, okay?
A police officer of all people.
Even worse.
Where am I?
The Control Bureau.
It's sort of like the Immigration Office.
She broke into your house,
stole your gun and car, and ran away.
After contacting an illegal entrant,
Han Tae-sul evaded our pursuit
and ran into 250811 in Busan.
He ran away with her help.
You said you won't let me
make the uploader.
Does it have to do with it?
There will be a war.
Everyone will die.
All sorts of mysterious people
will continue to try to kill me.
You're in danger too. Right?
Then let's go our separate ways.
How can I go back?
You're the only person I know
whether from the past, present, or future.
-You can't do it on your own.
-No thanks.
I prefer working alone.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs