Sub by kisscambodia
♪How to separate♪
♪Our entangled fate♪
♪Love doesn’t need any logical thinking♪
♪Instead of right pace♪
♪Baby You’re my only remedy♪
♪I’m willing to be
treated by you all my life♪
♪On my heart you knock knock knock♪
♪There comes your exclusive summons♪
♪Your eyes are engraved on my mind♪
♪I want you to belong to me♪
♪A sure and happy future♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
My Little Happiness
Episode 22
Dabaihui Plaza
Wen Shaoqing
Are you busy now?
Yes.
Save it.
What’s there for you to be busy with?
Don’t you want to try the cakes I made?
Take it as an obligation
of being an uncle.
Save me from being boring.
Not available.
You sound cold.
What is it?
Anything that makes you unhappy?
Tell me.
I love gossip.
Nothing!
So cranky.
He’s been dumped?
How is those kids’
craftsmanship?
Without my supervision,
it must’ve retrogressed.
Boss.
What is it?
Are you off work?
Not yet.
Just right.
Tell me
the clinical symptoms of
acute epidural hematoma.
Usually accompanied by
temporal bone fracture,
disturbance of consciousness,
and increased intracranial pressure.
Boss, aren’t you on a break?
Why are you suddenly testing me?
Zhong Zhen,
what are you doing?
Hurry!
I’ve been on break for only a few days.
But you guys are slacking off, right?
I’m busy here.
Talk later.
I’ll hang up.
You must be lying.
I’ll teach you a lesson when I’m back.
Zhong Zhen
Now you’ve realized your mistake.
What is it?
Boss?
Why is that you?
It’s all because
you called me for nothing earlier.
I made the wrong call.
I’ll hang up.
Wait a sec.
Repeat what you just said to me.
Sorry, Boss.
It’s just we’re so occupied right now.
There was a chain collision
on the highway.
The injured have all been sent here.
I gotta go now.
I must find Dr. Chen immediately.
Okay.
Fine.
You have work to do.
So do I.
Sleeping so early?
Zhong Zhen.
Rong,
what’s Boss doing now?
You’re asking me?
Tell me, have you made mistakes
while your Boss is on a break?
How come? I don’t want to be killed.
I called you to warn you that
you’ve got to care more about
your strange boyfriend.
What’s wrong with him?
I think he acts a little strange.
You need to lead him to a brighter road.
Make it clear.
Rong,
according to my observation these days,
I think my poor and lonely Boss
is really becoming more and more
like a weirdo.
You have to save him!
Okay.
I get it.
I’ll hang up.
Hello, Mom?
Dear, your Dad Jiang
wants to meet Shaoqing.
I told you I’ve been busy.
I can’t go back.
Save it.
If you don’t come back,
he and I will go to you.
Okay!
I’ll go back in a few days.
Don’t play tricks.
Take Shaoqing with you.
Okay, okay.
I will take him with me.
I’ll hang up.
You are back.
Remember we agreed to go for an outing?
I’ve figured out the destination.
Domestic Departure Information
Cong Rong.
Is the destination your...?
Yeah.
Right guess.
My home.
Let me show you
our family photos.
This was taken when I was at college.
This one is my favorite.
Look, the three of us all have
the same expression.
This is a picture
of my parents on their trip.
Mom loves travelling.
So, Dad Jiang travels with her.
The two of you seem to get along well.
That’s right.
Dad Jiang treats me
just as his natural child.
Scolds me when I do wrong.
Praises me when I do right.
There’s no barrier between us.
Knowing that you were a naughty kid,
I didn’t expect that
you accepted him so smoothly.
Of course not.
I excluded him a lot at first.
Guess what I used to do to him?
I spat out watermelon seeds at him.
He was unwilling to be outdone.
So, he fought back in the same way.
But every time he would
win me by one more seed.
Later, melon vines grew out
in the flowerpot.
Your mom didn’t scold you?
She did.
I don’t know when exactly but gradually,
Dad Jiang and I were no longer
hostile to each other.
We became concerned about each other.
Are you happy?
Yes,
I am.
Dad Jiang takes infinite care of my mom.
They live very happily.
I told you,
it’s only a casual dinner.
If I knew you would buy so many gifts,
I should’ve told you about it
till we get to the door.
This is my first formal visit.
Of course I must prepare
as many gifts as possible.
What if my father-in-law
considered me inconsiderate
and didn’t want to marry you to me?
Father-in-law?
Don’t call him that when you meet.
So, your family live inside the school.
Dad Jiang is a professor of philosophy.
Of course we live inside the school.
We are already near your home.
We don’t need to hurry.
Show me around your Alma Mater.
I’m quite curious of
your school environment.
No. You’re curious of what happened here
when you and I
were separated, aren’t you?
Let’s go.
I’ll take you to a place.
Okay.
That is the administrative building.
Every time I went there,
the security
would give me a candy.
That building
is the gym.
It’s super huge.
There’s even a pool in it.
Are these the girls’ dormitories?
Yep.
Which room did you live in?
That one.
But my roommates and I were not close.
My home is in the school, you know.
I spent much time at home.
Is that it?
But I guess there must be other reasons.
It’s just I received more love letters.
And?
And... Sometimes, someone
gave me meals,
tea,
gifts.
And?
And...
Maybe someone liked to block my way.
I understand that.
I also had that kind of trouble.
Headache.
-Then how many love letters?
Not many.
So-so.
Did you take them?
What do you think?
Wait for me!
Wait for me.
Are you still in touch
with some of those people?
What about you?
I wasn’t even in touch with
any of them ever.
I didn’t even take
any of the letters ever.
Dad Jiang?
Dad Jiang is over there.
Dad Jiang,
what are you doing?
You are back.
This must be Shaoqing.
Really handsome.
Even handsomer
than the one on the photo.
Nice to meet you, Uncle.
You look even younger
than the one on the photo.
That’s sweet.
No wonder her mom
always speaks highly of you.
Cong Rong always tells me
how much she admires you.
I can even recite all your
heroic deeds backwards fluently.
Heroic deeds? No.
You’re flattering me.
When will you stop
flattering each other?
Dad Jiang,
you even ignored me
after you met him.
We often meet,
don’t we?
But this is my first time
to meet my son-in-law.
-We have a lot to talk.
-Yeah.
I agree with you, my father-in-law.
Dad Jiang.
What were you busy with?
When your mom and I married, I buried
two jars of Chinese liquor here.
Today, Shaoqing came.
I want to dig out one jar,
and drink with him at dinner.
But I couldn’t find it.
Buried under this tree or that tree?
Well, I... I’ll continue.
Wait for me.
Why did you bury the liquor
under a tree?
These are osmanthus trees.
So?
The liquor buried under
an osmanthus tree must be Nyu Er Hong.
In ancient China,
a father brew some Chinese liquor
when his daughter
was entering the marriageable age.
When his daughter was getting married,
he dug out the liquor underground
to treat the guests.
The taste was extraordinary.
Your father is digging it out,
which means his daughter
is going to get married.
Don’t gloat only because
he called you son-in-law.
I haven’t said yes.
You will soon.
I found it! I found it!
Great! I found it.
I found it. I found it.
No rush.
Take a look.
This liquor is amazing.
One jar of it will do for today.
The other jar of it
will be drunk at a more important event.
Let’s go.
Let’s go home for dinner.
Let’s have a good drink tonight.
Look at Shaoqing’s
cutting and slicing skill.
Impressive.
You’re flattering me.
Skill comes from practice.
I just use knives
more often than others.
I get too familiar with them.
That’s right.
He’s a professional butcher.
He’s only good at using knives.
How could you say that?
Impolite.
What did I tell you?
You can find no one
that has better
cutting and slicing skills than him.
I thought
you were the luckiest woman
for marrying me.
But check this.
Well,
our daughter
is even luckier than you.
Do you think we should be jealous
or relieved?
Relieved, of course.
However, I still think
my husband is the best man in the world.
Of course!
Be restrained, okay?
This sweet couple always
ignore my feelings.
I’m so miserable.
We’re setting a good example for you.
Come on, sit, sit.
I’ll do it.
Food coming.
Uncle, Aunt,
have a check.
Are you satisfied with
Cong Rong’s daily meal standard?
Can’t be more satisfied!
Right?
Come on.
Sit, sit.
Now I see,
these two kids are trying to
make us jealous, right?
Considering your performance today,
I’ll give you a score of 120!
Hurry, let’s eat.
I’m starving.
Okay, okay.
Let’s eat.
Wait!
Wait a sec.
Shaoqing.
Here.
From now on, this pair of chopsticks
belongs to you.
Let’s welcome our new family member.
Thanks, Uncle, Aunt.
What are you waiting for?
Come on, applaud!
Welcome, welcome!
All right.
Sit, sit.
Come on.
Guys, cheers.
Cheers.
Hey, you.
Cheers!
-Cheers.
Shaoqing, a good name,
more importantly, a good person.
He’s not only humble and gentle,
but also talented in cooking.
You’ve seen countless people,
but you’re wrong
about a person this time.
Why?
He’s not humble or gentle.
He’s tactful and sharp-tongued.
A man
needs not only wisdom
but also tactics
to protect the one he loves.
I think Shaoqing
can totally handle it.
Yes, that’s right.
I agree.
Your dad is the same kind.
Of course.
Thanks for your appreciation,
Uncle, Aunt.
Let’s have a toast.
A toast to you two.
Cheers.
Okay, okay.
We have confidence in you.
Come on.
Another drink.
Fill it up. Come on.
Dad,
don’t drink too much.
You still have work to do tomorrow.
That’s no big deal.
Are you...? Protecting me
or him?
A man
can’t drink too little.
What’s big deal of getting drunk?
The way a man drinks
reflects his character.
Right?
Shaoqing is a good man.
Huh?
Of course!
Look how happy your dad is.
Cheers.
A toast on his behalf!
That’s better.
Let me fill your cup up.
Your cup.
Let me fill it up.
Dad!
Mom!
What?
He’s fine.
He can still drink.
Be good.
Be good, dear.
Look how happy your dad is.
Right?
Shaoqing,
do you know why I brew the Nyu Er Hong?
I’m from Shaoxing,
that liquor’s hometown.
As the saying goes in Shaoxing,
“The liquor brewed by using
the water from the local lake
can even be smelled
by people from another town.”
When my younger sister was born,
my father brewed a few jars
of Nyu Er Hong.
I was too young
to understand my father.
Until later, Rong came into my life,
I understood him.
You know her life experience, right?
I know.
For these years,
we didn’t give birth to another child.
Because in our heart,
Rong is our only beloved daughter.
So,
I wouldn’t allow you to hurt her.
Actually, the bond between me and her
began much earlier
than Aunt and you know.
Holding her hand again
is really a blessing for me.
After so many years,
we met again.
I will never hurt her.
Being by her side
is happy, right?
Yeah.
It’s hard to describe,
but I feel each day
is given a different meaning.
Cong Rong is like...
A clock pendulum.
Every day, she takes me
with her, swinging.
Every second is different.
Uncle,
it feels amazing.
I know, I know.
I was young once.
I’ve been through this.
Couldn’t help loving.
Still the same now.
If I may,
I want to hold her hand forever,
never letting go.
Uncle.
I don’t know what could happen
in the future,
but please trust me,
Cong Rong is the first priority
of my life.
I hope you can feel at ease
letting her be with me.
I will protect her well.
You are her choice.
I respect her choice.
As parents, we don’t want much.
We only want you
to be happy.
I’ll take a walk,
and enjoy the breeze.
Careful.
Sure.
How could my dad
let you drink so much?
Are you clear-headed?
Yes!
Careful.
Lift your feet.
You drank too much.
I want to sleep there.
You passed the guest room.
Wait, this is my bedroom.
You’d better go sleep in the guest room.
My parents will come back soon.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Why are you laughing?
What are you afraid of?
Drunkenness is medically called
alcoholic intoxication,
which can cause
nervous system abnormalities
and blood circulation disturbance.
And loss of ability to commit crimes.
I’m really drunk.
That’s yellow rice wine.
It has a strong delayed effect.
I told you to drink less.
He was testing his son-in-law’s
drinking capacity.
I had to drink.
♪I’m with you♪
♪Standing under the tree♪
♪Making a promise of the future♪
♪Marching forward to happiness♪
♪Promise I’ll be by your side♪
♪I’m with you♪
♪Being with you♪
♪The light with you♪
♪Only if I’m with you♪
Let’s go check Shaoqing
to see if he’s recovered from the drink.
His drinking capacity is not bad.
It’s your fault.
Now we can’t explain it.
Calm down.
I need your collaboration.
Where are the kids?
I also wanna know.
You are back, Uncle, Aunt.
Well, Cong Rong felt uncomfortable.
So, I brought her here to take a rest.
Something must be wrong
with your liquor.
Let me see.
Nothing can be wrong with my liquor.
Shaoqing,
are you all right?
I also have a headache.
Why is it red here?
Are you allergic to the liquor?
Yes, yes, yes.
Yeah.
That... That sounds right.
Sounds right.
Yes, yes, yes.
She’s allergic.
I’ll get you some water then.
Something must be wrong
with your liquor!
Liquor?
Nothing can be wrong with my liquor.
Liquor...
Dad.
Don’t worry.
I’ll take a walk with him.
Yeah.
Liquor?
What’s this place?
Looks a little romantic.
Every school has this kind of place
for young lovers.
So, you came here before
with your adorers?
Impossible.
This is my first time to come here.
Really?
What a coincidence.
This is also my first time.
Do you know what I told your dad?
Huh?
Finally, I found you.
I don’t want to be separated
from you for a second.
Okay.
Go in.
It’s loading.
I couldn’t hit him.
Let me do it.
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪
You slept a long time.
We’ve landed.
What time is it?
Zhong Zhen
Zhong Zhen?
Rong,
are you with Boss?
Looking for him again.
What is it?
Speak.
Terrible news!
The family of the patient in Bed Three
has sued the hospital
and... Boss!
What?
Grandma
Seems I’m going to be scolded.
You’re here.
Why are you also here?
Your grandma misses me.
She called me back to have dinner.
They have known that I’ve been sued
and are going to interrogate me?
I’m afraid you have to
transcribe a book.
I’ve prepared it for you.
Compendium of Materia Medica.
After you’re done,
give them back to me within a month.
Good.
Speed up your speaking speed.
Use long sentences
instead of short ones.
Don’t act like a parent
in front of me.
Yes,
Father.
He’s educating his own son.
Why do you have to set foot in?
What?
I’m also a dad here.
I can’t educate my own son?
Daddy,
eat.
Come play chess with your younger son!
Let’s go!
Come on, let’s go.
You naughty kid.
Dad.
The director has told you?
Yes.
Did you get hurt?
Just a little.
I’m all right now.
What’s the punishment?
I’m suspended.
For how long?
It depends.
I heard this incident is huge.
Some reports are unfair.
Adjust your mentality well
and be cooperative with
the hospital’s investigation.
I don’t care about those reports.
There’s just a disorderly crowd.
They’re just venting their emotions.
Good to know you understand that.
Dad,
aren’t you going to blame me?
As a father,
I won’t encourage my son to fight.
As a senior,
I won’t encourage a junior
to fight, either.
But as a doctor,
I don’t think you made a big mistake.
However, you must remember
that you are from the Wen family.
Many people are observing.
I can’t be biased in your favor.
I was being impulsive.
I won’t make the same mistake again.
Have a good rest then.
Take it as an opportunity
to improve yourself.
Improve what?
Shaoqing has been good enough.
He doesn’t make me worried like you do.
Don’t give the kid too much pressure.
He’s still got dinner to have.
Mom,
I wasn’t scolding him.
I was just educating him.
Anyway, I’m so far away now.
I can’t do anything to him.
It’s good you know.
I’ll hang up.
Mom.
You...
Your dad is old.
Likes nagging.
Grandma,
let me give you a hand.
Take it.
What do you mean by this, Grandma?
I’m not short of money.
I know you’re not.
This is your... Travelling fund.
You rarely have a chance
to take a long rest.
Don’t just stay at home.
Go travelling the world.
Take your girlfriend with you.
She has to go to work.
Grandma,
I know you feel sorry for me.
It’s okay.
The suspension won’t be long.
Shaoqing,
as an old woman,
when I look back what I’ve been through,
I find most difficulties
no longer difficult.
Don’t be too hard on yourself.
Enjoy the pleasures life affords.
Also, enjoy the bitterness life affords.
Understand?
Understand.
These strawberries smell really good.
I grew them in our yard.
Just eat.
It’s dirty.
It’s sweet.
Do you like the dishes I cooked?
Of course!
I love the food you cook the most.
Good.
Come to eat more often then.
Sure.
Here’s some sesame paste.
It’s for my future granddaughter-in-law.
Thanks, Grandma.
I promise I will marry her.
I can’t let her taste your food
for nothing.
We’re both waiting for that.
Sure.
These are
a few dishes Chengcheng loves.
I won’t take them.
They would be a waste.
You...
Dad!
You brat.
Have you quarreled with Chengcheng?
Take them.
Use them as an apology.
That’s right.
Take them.
Hurry, take them.
You know nothing
but still want me to apologize.
It must be your fault.
That’s right.
Be good to her.
You’ve finally got a girl
that likes you.
Cherish her.
I know.
I’m leaving, Mom.
Just leave.
Grandpa, Grandma,
I’ll visit you another day.
Be safe on the way.
Bye, Mom.
You’re grow-up
but still make us worried.
You...
What?
You were dumped?
Why don’t you take them?
Sure.
No way.
I...!
Haven’t taught you a lesson lately.
Now you’re this bold?
Fine, fine.
Do you think I’m stupid?
Honestly speaking,
very stupid.
You wanna die?
Are you done?
Enough.
Is it good?
Yeah!
My grandma made it by herself.
It’s made of walnut,
Chinese date,
and...
And she said in particular that
it’s for her granddaughter-in-law.
I shouldn’t have been worried about you.
Seems you didn’t get scolded at home.
I thought your whole family
was so strict on you.
Grandparents spoil grandkids,
don’t you know?
Not to mention I’ve been
well-behaved since little.
My grandparents really spoil me.
Convey my thanks to Grandma.
I’ve got gourmet’s luck.
Eat more if you like it.
I think the color of your hair
is a bit of strange.
I dyed it specially, alright?
It cost much.
And you often lose your hair.
Every time after you left
my place,
your hair would be everywhere.
I once thought Rangyirang’s hair
turned dark.
You’re a dog!
Don’t move.
Done.
How about letting my law firm take up
your case?
Good.
Let me get this straight.
You and I are going to be
lawyer and party soon.
You must watch every manner of yours.
You can’t let me
violate my professional ethics.
That complicated?
What about after the case?
After?
Who knows?
What do you mean?
When you are my party,
I must treat you fairly.
But when you’re not,
I won’t have to do that anymore.
Is there really a law against
the romantic relationship
between a lawyer and a party?
Article 60 of Chapter VI of the Law
of the People’s Republic of China
on Lawyers stipulates that
any person who has
an improper relationship
with a party by providing legal services
shall be warned by
the judicial administrative department.
If the circumstances are serious,
he shall be suspended
from practicing for three months.
Really?
Yeah.
Miss Cong,
you made up that law, right?
You’re bullying an ignorant citizen.
Yes!
I’m bullying you ignorant of laws.
Chen Cu
Bro,
I just attended a meeting
with the leaderships.
Call me back when you have time.
Let me get you another bowl of it.
I still have some at my place.
Wait here.
Bro.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t expect you would be involved.
That’s my patient.
Don’t say that.
I didn’t do it for you.
Director Yan wants you to come
to the hospital when you have time.
He’ll tell you the details.
I get it.
Did...?
Did they mention the reinstatement
at the meeting?
No, they didn’t.
Let’s first settle the problems at hand.
Okay.
I get it.
What?
You can’t wait to eat?
Even for a minute?
I’ll coordinate the case
as soon as I get to the office.
Trust me.
I
will help you out.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Finally we hold hands♪
♪Intimacy is assurance
of your tenderness♪
♪The unforgettable smile♪
♪I want to remember it each second♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪