Sub by kisscambodia
♪How to separate♪
♪Our entangled fate♪
♪Love doesn’t need any logical thinking♪
♪Instead of right pace♪
♪Baby You’re my only remedy♪
♪I’m willing to be
treated by you all my life♪
♪On my heart you knock knock knock♪
♪There comes your exclusive summons♪
♪Your eyes are engraved on my mind♪
♪I want you to belong to me♪
♪A sure and happy future♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
My Little Happiness
Episode 21
Thanks, bro.
When will I attend your wedding, huh?
Happy wedding.
I’ll take my leave.
Catch you later.
Wen Rang!
You’re leaving so soon?
Won’t you join the following activities?
Not today.
Several major booksellers
are also present at the wedding.
There’s still time.
I can introduce you to them,
so that your poems can
be on the bookshelves
at major bookstores.
We can discuss that another day.
Wen Rang.
This is a rare opportunity.
If your poems are seen by more people,
so will be your literary talent.
Don’t you expect that to happen?
Thanks for your concern.
But I don’t expect that to happen.
Wen Rang.
Now you’re cold to me
because of her?
Jiang Yao.
You always think yourself in the right.
Take a picture of me.
My friends are gonna like it.
No problem. Go ahead.
I’ll take more pictures.
Pose over here.
I keep recording your everyday life
and posting the videos on WeSee.
Now you have
several hundred thousand followers.
Look, guys.
I specially cooked it for him.
Do you think after he tastes it,
he’ll ask me to be his girlfriend?
The world even seems smaller.
I didn’t know he could do rock climbing.
We both have 24 hours a day.
But the things he can do in 24 hours
are even more than
what I can do in 48 hours.
Really admire him.
How industrious he is!
Do you think if I go
help him with the cleaning,
he’ll ask me to be his girlfriend?
He’s cleaning the bookshelves.
Don’t walk away.
Look here.
Let me interview you.
How many times a day do you clean them?
Once is enough if you’re not here.
How many times is it if I’m here?
Four or five.
But why?
I never give you more trouble.
Don’t try to run!
Chickens.
Bear. Bear.
I wanna play with you.
Sure.
Do you want to see bubbles,
kids?
Yes!
Still so carefree.
Her sorrow never lasts
longer than a day.
That’s good.
I don’t need to be worried.
Be careful. Don’t burst them.
Mommy,
I wanna fly a kite.
It’s run out.
How about this?
Fly a kite in the park tomorrow, okay?
Okay.
Why did you stop?
The bubble water has run out.
I’ll go get some.
You guys go play over there, okay?
-Okay.
I’m running.
Hey, let go of the kite.
I’m doing it. I’m doing it.
Let go when the wind blows.
Three, two…
Inpatient Department
Here we are.
Thanks,
my private driver.
How are you feeling
about having your girlfriend
drive you to work?
Feeling great.
Hope we can do this every day.
Does it still hurt?
Having your tender care,
I recovered long ago.
Don’t push yourself too hard.
Those families of that patient
must still be at the hospital.
I worry they may give you a hard time.
Legal Assistant Cong Rong
If they badger with you,
let them come to me.
I get it.
I can feel your strong desire
to protect me.
All right.
I gotta go to work.
Careful on the road.
Please don’t stand here
and affect our work.
Is Wen Shaoqing a doctor
in your hospital?
It’s said that
he hit the patient’s family yesterday.
Is that true?
Do you support his deed?
We want to interview him.
Can you ask Wen Shaoqing to come here?
Can you ask him…?
-Boss, don’t go there.
-To tell us the details?
Why are there so many journalists?
Don’t bring it up.
It’s a total mess now.
That patient’s families
contacted several media.
They all want to interview you.
Look how eager they are.
You mustn’t give them the chance.
The problem must be solved.
I can’t escape all the time.
Forget about the things here for now.
Think about
how to deal with the Director.
Sorry.
We aren’t available for an interview
right now.
I told you, we aren’t available…
It’s you.
You must stop them, understand?
Tell them
that the hospital will give them
an explanation soon.
Director.
You know what?
I’ve been busy with nothing
but the calls.
How could you get involved in a fight?
If in any case you got your hand hurt
and couldn’t operate anymore,
your career and future
would both be ruined, right?
It’s never easy for a hospital
to train a good doctor.
If you are a responsible man,
the first thing you should do
is to protect yourself.
I just didn’t want to let those kids down.
Well,
this is my fault.
I hope you won’t punish them.
This is no big deal.
The hospital will
deal with them accordingly.
Then be simple
and tell me the punishment for me.
Go home and rest for a few days.
The hospital will deal with
the patient in Bed Three and the media.
Wait till this is over.
How many days exactly?
At least a month.
Boss,
what’s their decision?
Dr. Wen,
the patient in Bed 15 doesn’t feel good.
Please have a check.
I’m on suspension.
I can’t see a patient.
Chen Cu.
Please take over my job.
I should’ve been the one
to take the responsibility.
Don’t say that.
This is my fault.
The one deserving punishment is me.
I won’t be there with you
on the night shifts lately.
Don’t miss me too much.
Go.
The patient is waiting.
Okay.
Let’s go.
What?
Don’t give me those sad faces.
I’m just suspended, not fired.
I’ll be back.
All get back to your work.
Or the director will scold you again.
We were all involved.
Why did you take all the punishment?
You’re still young.
You’ll understand in the future.
By the way,
I’ve made a call to your teacher.
Write a self-criticism later.
The school won’t be hard on you.
One more thing.
I’m writing down
all the important matters
needing attention
of several patients.
Director,
don’t punish those interns, please.
With more and more doctors getting old,
we need more and more
young doctors to become pillars.
Matters needing attention of patients
Do as I have written down.
Don’t make any mistakes.
Why are you still standing there?
Get back to what you should do!
When in that white coat,
you’re entrusted with
the patient’s health and life.
Bear it in mind.
You may leave.
I also should…
Leave for home.
Boss,
we’ll wait for you to come back.
You came back early today.
Zhong Zhen told me that you’re…
On suspension.
You look like you’re going to a war.
Let’s take it as a vacation,
to which I’ve been looking forward.
Come on.
Let’s eat.
Are you sure?
Are you sure you’re not worried at all?
Why should I be worried?
My life has been so boring.
Most of my time has been taken up
by the patients and the hospital.
Only a little belongs to myself.
Now is good.
I finally have time to enjoy my life
and finish my list.
You have a list?
Of course I have things I wanna do.
Are they weird things like
carving patterns on chopsticks
or working on the best way
to kill a chicken
for the best taste, etc.?
Working on a recipe
is interesting indeed.
But I have a more important thing to do.
Being with you.
But now,
what you should do is to taste
the meal cooked by a weird chef.
This one.
Newly developed by me.
Delicious!
You too have a bite.
Chengcheng.
I didn’t expect it to be so popular.
You must be tired.
I’m fine.
Here are your wages.
These are your due.
Thanks a lot.
Sir.
Excuse me.
♪Trust me♪
♪The future will only become better♪
♪However long the road is♪
♪We’ll take it together♪
I thought if only I gave out light,
the lonely boat would come to me.
But the truth is some boat
already had its destination long ago.
Since I’m not your destination,
more stories of us
would only bring more regrets.
Goodbye.
I wish that in the future,
you will never write lonely verse again.
♪Me holding your hand♪
♪In the final rays of the sun♪
♪We are taking a slow stroll♪
♪A slow stroll♪
♪Breeze fiddles with your hair♪
♪A smile creeps across your face♪
♪We are leaning close to each other♪
He’s really handsome!
Wish you happiness!
Are they in love?
What happened afterwards? Any update?
No more updates. Quit following.
♪I’ll whisper♪
♪Your troubles will disappear♪
♪We gaze at each other♪
♪We enter each other’s heart♪
♪Our love will last forever♪
Thank you.
Cong Rong:
How have you been, Chengcheng?
I’ve been good.
I just finished the work at the hotel.
I’m on my way home. Focus on your job.
Don’t worry about me.
Cong Rong:
Do you have any plans for tomorrow?
I’ll go to the restaurant.
The remaining stuffs…
The remaining stuffs need to be cleared…
It’s okay.
As long as you’re back.
You won’t even ask
why I suddenly came back?
No need to ask.
I know you’ve been
suffering a lot outside.
Home is good, isn’t it?
I’m such a failure, don’t you think?
I just want to run my own small business
and earn my own bread.
Why does it have to be so hard?
You want to be
independent and self-reliant.
There’s nothing wrong about that.
Your mom and I support you.
But some things in life
just don’t suit you.
Don’t suit me?
Right.
He and I are not from the same world.
How can we suit each other?
Chengcheng,
what’re you talking about?
Did someone hurt you?
No.
It was my fault
to let you and Mom down.
In fact, sometimes it’s our fault.
From now on, as long as you’re happy,
you’ll have our full support.
There’s no big deal.
Let’s take our time.
Yeah.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Rangyirang,
your breakfast.
What a hearty breakfast!
Nutritionally speaking,
a healthy breakfast should have
four to five hundred calories.
There should be an appropriate
amount of carbohydrate,
protein, vitamin and mineral substance.
So that you can have enough energy
for the whole morning.
You got up early
only to make me breakfast?
That’s not the whole truth.
I also made you lunch, dinner
and night snack.
Don’t forget to take them.
Are you going to be a full-time chef?
You lawyers often skip meals
when being busy
and casually order takeout
which contains little nutrition.
Now is good.
I have plenty of time
to cook for you.
Lately, you’ve been busy with
that online loan case
and always work overtime.
You may get hungry at night,
so I’ve prepared more food for you.
You’re so good to me
that I don’t even know how to repay you.
You can marry me.
Time for work.
I gotta go.
Go on enjoying your retire life.
I’m leaving for work.
I’ll walk you out.
Stay at home and have a good rest.
No need to walk me out.
Then I won’t walk you downstairs.
I’m off.
You lied.
I pushed the button for you.
Don’t thank me.
A walk after eating helps digestion.
I’ll walk you to the bus station.
Let’s have an outing when I’m less busy.
Good.
Where do you want to go?
How about going to see animals?
Elephant.
Goat.
Swallow.
Look.
Looks like a swallow?
Yeah.
A rabbit?
A rabbit.
It doesn’t look like a rabbit.
A rabbit should look like this.
Huh?
Right?
Right indeed.
You should go back.
I’ve been too busy lately.
You should go to bed early.
Don’t wait for me.
How about walking me farther?
Sure.
Last time,
you were on purpose, right?
What last time?
I don’t remember a thing.
East
That’s it.
You should go back.
You agreed to walk me
only to the front of the building.
Then I’ll go back.
Remember to eat on time.
Eight. Still early.
Wen Rang.
I can see that
you’re going against yourself.
You have an interesting soul.
You have great talents as well.
What’s more, I think you are
a very, very good person.
Don’t deny yourself
because she doesn’t understand you.
Hello?
Hello.
Am I speaking to Mr. Wen Rang?
Yes,
you are.
What can I do for you?
The venue for your book sharing session
has been settled.
What book sharing session?
About the book A Castle in the Clouds.
Miss Jiang Yao told me to contact you.
So, when are you available this week?
Okay,
I’ll call you when I confirm.
Okay.
Rang Kai Bookstore
Cheers.
I didn’t expect the performance
to be so successful
and us to be so appreciated.
I’m so happy.
It’s because that our female vocal
looks beautiful
and sings well.
Isn’t because that our guitar player
is handsome and talented?
Eat.
I gotta say
time really flies.
It’s been two years.
Do you still remember how we met?
Of course I do.
I remember that you were
wearing similar clothes.
You were playing the guitar
near the school garden
with so many girls surrounding
and admiring you.
I remember you began to sing
while I was playing the guitar.
You were wearing a red dress
and being eye-catching in the crowd.
So, I was wondering
who
this proud girl was.
But she sang really well.
So, you lost your heart to me
at that moment?
Yes.
Fine.
To celebrate the second anniversary
of your losing your heart to me,
I have a gift for you.
Close your eyes.
Don’t peek.
I won’t.
Hurry.
Open your eyes.
Is it for me?
Open it.
Come on, open it.
This brand is expensive!
Where did you get the money?
Tell me, where did you get the money?
I worked part-time for months!
Wen Rang.
Do you like it or not?
I… I’m telling you.
It… It is not an ordinary guitar.
It is special.
Look.
Look here.
My surname’s initial is here.
This guitar represents me.
Having it by your side
roughly equals having me by your side.
Do you have to leave?
I can’t give up a bigger world
because of one person, right?
What bigger world?
We’ve been together for years.
You always tell me that
you like the way
I’m being stubborn
and retaining my dignity instead of
succumbing to a temptation.
I’ve been grateful to you.
Grateful to that girl
who worked hard for months
just to buy me a nice guitar.
Just tell yourself that girl is dead.
I was young and ignorant.
In my eyes, there was only the guitar,
the songs
and you.
Now I’ve changed.
I want more,
which you can’t give me.
Turn on the lights!
What’s going on?
Be careful.
Check the lights over there.
Why are you here?
Jiang Yao.
I’m here to return the guitar.
Don’t you remember the meaning of it?
Just because I remember it clearly,
I have to return it to you.
You don’t want to sell your books
by string-pulling.
That’s fine.
I’m holding this book fair for you,
to give your work a chance
to win others’ favor.
Are you still not satisfied?
Do you have to use this book fair as…?
Jiang Yao, you know
it’s not about the book fair.
It’s time for us to
end this and move on.
I was wishing you to come back
to me while hating you.
That’s a stupid thing I did
when I was young.
I had been doing that stupid thing
till I saw you again.
I regretted
and rued.
However, I eventually realized that
my emotions for you
were just my obsession.
Obsession with the past
is meaningless.
Isn’t our past your everything?
You once said
that you would always remember
that girl in a red dress
singing in the crowd.
You once said
that’s your fleeting glimpse
of an enchanting beauty.
You got excited
every time you talked about that.
You forgot all of that?
That’s all meaningless to you?
Jiang Yao!
You are no longer the girl
you used to be.
Even I, who always believe that
I would never be changed by this world,
have unknowingly
changed.
I’ve been asking myself
if I came back too late.
If I came back earlier,
we could’ve made it up,
we could’ve gone back…
I asked myself the similar question.
If we did it all over again,
would it be different?
Maybe yes.
But people are stubborn
when they are young.
No one would change for the other.
We have only one chance
to make a choice.
We both made the wrong choice.
Thank you.
Madam.
I want to buy that glass fish
I saw last time.
These are all I have.
Take your pick.
This one?
You sure?
Yeah.
I won’t make the wrong choice this time.
What?
Still reading the court records?
Yeah.
I’m learning about the trial procedures
of these two presiding judges.
I’ve got to be prepared.
Good.
As a trainee of Mr. Shangguan,
you have good thoughts.
She’s forced me to watch it
for three times.
Now you’ve watched the video
for so many times.
Have you learned anything particular?
In this contract dispute case,
maybe we shouldn’t
bring all the evidence
to the court.
According to the claim of the defendant,
the acceptance list
provided by the plaintiff
could be easily challenged.
I’m afraid it wouldn’t be wise
to provide such evidence.
The counterattack
is in favor of the plaintiff.
Mr. Shangguan also taught me that
we should arrange the evidence
according to its strength.
Is that right?
Am I wrong?
Good thinking.
Yeah.
Keeping trying.
I’ll go ask Mr. Shangguan to look over
the cross-examination views.
Okay.
She’s more mature.
Cross-Examination Views
Well written.
But a few problems still.
Come over here.
This sentence.
The relevance of Exhibit 5
needs to be enumerated in this way.
These sentences.
Here.
Revise them and it’ll be fine.
Okay.
I get it.
I’m going to revise them now.
One more thing.
The trial is due in a few weeks.
Rest well.
Stay in good state.
I will.
Thanks, Mr. Shangguan.
How are you doing there?
Need my help?
It’s fine.
Don’t worry about me.
There aren’t a lot of things.
It won’t take me long to pack them.
Go on with your work.
Cong Rong
By the way,
don’t tell or ask
Wen Shaoqing anything.
I can adjust myself well.
I’ll get better soon.
Way to go, Chengcheng.
When I’m free, let’s go shopping,
hang out and have fun.
A Castle in the Clouds
Even there was no Jiang Yao,
he and I still wouldn’t
be together, right?
A Castle in the Clouds
How did you get in here?
I won’t go home!
Let go of me!
Give me pepper powder.
Cumin
What’s wrong with you today?
Are you blind?
I gave you the wrong one?
What are you doing?
You got hurt.
I can’t succeed in anything in life.
I’d rather be a vegetable.
Nonsense!
Spit it out.
Burang Barbeque
For Rent
Why are you renting it out suddenly?
Your business is good, isn’t it?
This is just a small business.
Is it good?
Not even close.
It’s not like that.
You said that
the scale of the business
doesn’t matter,
nor the profit.
What matters is to find the true self.
I think I was being childish then.
People can’t live in
their own fantasy forever.
We should get out of our comfort zone.
Look at those friends of mine,
they all have made achievements
on their own.
While I…
I seem to have wasted
too much time here.
Why did you suddenly
change your thought?
Are you in trouble or something?
No.
I just… Walked on a wrong path
for some time.
Now I should get back to the right path.
I have a gift…
Oh, right.
Take this.
A Castle in the Clouds
It wasn’t until I sorted out
the restaurant that I realized
there was nothing worth staying for.
My boyfriend is here to pick me up.
I gotta go.
Bye.
Rang Kai Bookstore
Burang Barbeque
Don’t be sad, dear.
Your mom and I are with you.
Let’s go.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Finally we hold hands♪
♪Intimacy is assurance
of your tenderness♪
♪The unforgettable smile♪
♪I want to remember it each second♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪