♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaf clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage
and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 23=
Did you write everything down?
Yes.
And if construction continues at this pace,
we should be able to finish ahead of schedule.
From what I see,
it seems you've become pretty close
with the staff on site.
Because I come here often.
I've only come here a few times.
I always come here secretly.
And sometimes, I'd come
and stay for a while
at the weekend.
To do what?
Nothing.
Just watch things quietly.
Seeing something being built from nothing
is very fulfilling.
This emotional?
This is the first project
I've ever taken part in.
There were a few twists and turns along the way,
which I also treasure.
This is my first starting point.
During this project,
I learned a lot
and grew a lot.
You were the one
who gave me these opportunities.
You earned them yourself.
Even if
you were to work at other companies,
you would've achieved
the same results.
You won't even scold me now.
It depends.
If you make work-related mistakes,
I'll scold you of course.
Got it.
Let's go.
Not working overtime today?
No overtime today.
Now that we're off work,
you're not my boss,
but my boyfriend, right?
What?
I just want to know
how it works.
You're not going to discharge electricity
right away, are you?
Although the mechanical heart
doesn't operate through beating,
it has
a theoretical performance index.
If something causes
the heart rate to elevate,
it will work faster.
When heart rate goes up,
so does the theoretical index,
causing electric discharge.
This means that
whenever I come close to you,
your heart rate goes up,
which in turn, causes you to discharge electricity.
It depends.
When you came close just now,
I didn't discharge any electricity, right?
If something more
"stimulating" were to happen,
then I may
discharge a bit of electricity.
Will discharge cause any damage to it?
Right now, yes.
But, everything will be okay
in three months.
Oh, so endure it for three more months.
Don't let me "stimulate" you
in these three months.
But,
holding hands is fine.
I've held these hands
ten years ago.
You were so withdrawn earlier,
like a cold-blooded animal.
That must have been so hard for you.
If I hadn't met you,
I probably would have
ended my own life
after winning the Jin An Award.
No way!
Never say something
like that again.
That was my plan before I met you.
You shouldn't think that way
even if you didn't meet me.
People
run into accidents,
warmth,
and endless hope
when they don't have any plans.
Meeting you
gave me a new
goal in life.
What goal?
To be with you.
Boss,
could you say more
things like that in the future?
Why do things like that sound
so good coming from you?
You like hearing it?
Of course.
You don't think
it's too cheesy?
With a face like yours,
it works no matter how cheesy it is.
Then, what will be my reward?
Your reward will be
treating me to a feast.
Let's go.
♪Am I abnormal or are you shining♪
♪Woo~~♪
♪Falling in love is having you by my side♪
Here,
have this.
If you like it,
we can order more.
Boss,
you're suddenly so generous towards me,
I'm not used to it.
Was I really stingy before?
You were the boss before.
I was too embarrassed
to order more.
As long as you're happy,
there's no need to care about
other people's opinions.
My dad said
the same thing before.
Really?
When I was little,
my dad loved
celebrating my mom's birthday.
Every year, I looked forward to
my mom's birthday too.
Because the three of us
would go eat at a fancy restaurant,
where there'd be someone playing the piano.
Right then, I thought
people who can play the piano
are pretty
and elegant.
I even wanted to learn how to play.
And then?
Why didn't you learn to play?
And then, I thought about it.
My hands are
only meant for moving bricks.
[*"Moving bricks" is a Chinese slang for working.]
Your hands are also meant for holding mine.
Boss,
you're really getting the hang of it.
Have some of this.
Although you haven't
dated in ten years,
you really know
what to say.
I searched things up
on the internet recently.
Why didn't you ask
the King of flirts, Mr. Xu?
Is he trustworthy?
Him?
Fair enough.
Although this is
the first time I'm dating someone,
I think
you should let the person you like
feel that you like them.
Love should be expressed boldly.
After girls start a relationship,
shouldn't they be more reserved
or talk less?
Actually, I'm not talking that much now.
Fair.
Your starting point
is higher than others,
so when you talk less,
others can't really feel the difference.
You're talking a lot more than before.
Really?
I'm the same as I've always been.
When you get excited,
your body will discharge electricity.
But
when we hold hands or hug,
I can't feel anything.
Does this mean that sometimes
you don't like me that much?
Of course not.
It's because
you're insensitive.
I can feel that
you like me.
I find that you're really
getting bolder
and bolder now.
Humans should make bold attempts.
But
you have to keep your feelings
towards me under control.
Otherwise, discharging electricity too often
would be bad for your heart, right?
Excessive discharge
would cause discomfort
to the body.
In addition,
I have to charge my heart.
If my heart runs out of power,
a twenty-percent
back-up power
will be activated automatically.
Sort of like
when cellphones run out of battery.
Sounds pretty cool.
The little guy inside you,
is it the only
mechanical heart in the world?
There are others who use it,
but not many,
since it hasn't been perfected yet.
Unless
there are really no other options,
it wouldn't be used.
Also,
there are side effects.
Think about it.
Who can control
their emotions perfectly?
I'll be good from now on.
We'll do everything as you say.
I'll never make you angry.
I find having this little guy
is quite handy.
Careful not to get too excited.
It'll discharge.
Eat.
I've got it under control.
I've really got it under control.
We got back so soon.
I have to cherish the time I have right now.
When I pick you up tomorrow,
you'll be my boss again.
I never expected that office romance
would feel like this.
What did you think
it was going to feel like?
I've never fantasized about
an office romance before.
Then what did you fantasize about?
With a university upperclassman
who is really smart
and gets good grades.
Whatever I ask him,
he'll always have the answers.
Knows everything and does everything.
Gentlemanly
and wear a pair of glasses.
Do you know
what those upperclassmen know,
I know;
and what they don't, I know too.
I know.
Why are you two here?
I didn't see you when I went to
take out the garbage just now.
Look at me.
Getting old and blind.
Aunty.
It's late,
so Boss dropped me off.
Mr. Gu,
you're so nice to Xiao Ning.
You haven't eaten yet, right?
Come upstairs with us.
Aunty will make dumplings for you.
Aunty,
I've eaten already.
Girls should be more careful
when walking alone at night.
In the future, if Mr. Gu isn't busy,
it would be good if you could drop
Xiao Ning off more often.
Aunty,
I'll leave now then.
Speaking of which,
as an aunt,
I've been a little careless.
I should have exchanged
contact information with Mr. Gu earlier,
right?
Thinking about it,
her parents passed away years ago.
I'm her only legal guardian.
So,
as her guardian,
if something were to happen to her,
I should communicate
with her bosses.
Right.
Aunty...
Mr. Gu,
you don't mind, do you?
No, I don't.
Here, Aunty.
Thank you.
You got it?
Yes.
I got it.
Alright. If you have time,
make sure to come over for dinner.
It's a deal then.
Okay.
Aunty, I'm leaving then.
We won't see you off.
Bye now. Come on.
Bye.
Hurry up.
Go on.
Let's go, Xiao Ning.
Up you go.
Bye-bye.
You're still watching?
Aren't your eyes tired?
Aren't you ashamed?
You're bold enough to date
without telling me, huh?
No,
I just haven't gotten around to telling you yet.
You're really in a relationship?
Nice going, Xiao Ning.
Right?
That Gu...
Chuan.
Yes, Gu Chuan.
Gu Chuan is pretty exceptional,
really difficult to find.
So,
our Xiao Ning is pretty exceptional too.
Right?
Nice.
Speaking of which,
your age difference
is kind of...
You don't mind?
Of course, I don't mind.
Because I like him.
Alright, alright.
You like him that much?
Yes,
I like him a lot.
Hello?
Is this Mr. Gu?
Hello,
this is Xiao Ning's aunt.
Aunty.
Hi, Aunty.
What's wrong?
Are you busy?
Are you at work?
Am I bothering you?
No, I'm not busy right now. Please go on.
It's nothing really important.
I'm near your company,
how about I treat you to lunch?
Xiao Gu,
we've already met
many times,
but Aunty feels like
Aunty doesn't know you very well.
Aunty,
if you'd like to know anything,
just ask directly.
It's nothing, really.
Just chatting.
Don't take it to heart.
Which university did you go to?
UCL.
U what L?
It's a university in the UK.
I heard that
you graduated with double Masters?
Yes.
What do your parents do for a living?
Both my parents are university professors.
They used to work in research facilities.
But these years,
they've been living abroad,
so they're not around much.
Then you must own houses.
Where are they located?
One in the New District,
one in the CBD,
and
one in the resort area by the lake.
Aunty, Aunty.
I'm okay.
If this is the case,
then Aunty is
a little confused.
Look at you,
you check all the boxes
and you can be with any girl.
Why weren't you dating?
Aunty,
of course
I've dated before.
But I've been having some health issues
in recent years,
so I haven't been dating.
You have health issues?
What issues?
Are they treatable?
There's the possibility
that I’ll be cured.
In other words,
there's the possibility that you won't be cured?
Mr. Gu,
I just remembered that
I have to deal with something at home.
I have to go. I have to go now.
Sorry.
My bad.
Aunty.
Aunty, you haven't eaten anything.
Next time.
Zhao Yan.
Mr. Tang.
Getting off work?
How's Xiao Ning these days?
Pretty good. Things at her new job
are going well.
Okay.
Hey, godson.
What do you want from my girlfriend?
See you later.
Bye, Mr. Tang.
Take care.
What's with your attitude?
Why are you so hostile towards him?
You're afraid he'll take your dad's company?
I'm afraid he'll
take advantage of you
at work if he knows about us.
What do I have to do with you?
Again?
I have a heart condition.
Can't deal with you
doing this to me.
Go have your condition checked out.
You care about me so much?
Are you sick?
I am.
I'm sick with an illness
called "can't live without you".
That's easy to cure.
It can't be cured. It's terminal.
Hello?
Okay.
I'll be right there.
See you soon.
Who are you going to see?
A real estate agent. I'm looking for a place to live.
Looking for a place to live?
My lease is up.
Is finding a new place a problem?
I'll go with you.
What does this have to do with you?
I'm looking for a place too.
There's no need to pick another day.
Today is the day.
Hello. We're coming now.
My phone.
Xu Cheng Ran.
Look at the decoration of this apartment.
So refined.
It has a spacious living room,
two bedrooms,
open kitchen,
and a huge French window.
It's a great choice for couples like you two.
We are not a couple.
It'll just be me.
We're not a couple yet, but soon.
If you live here by yourself,
this apartment is a little big for you.
Do you also want to
see the apartment next door?
Okay.
I think this one really suits you.
Suits what?
I'll be living by myself.
Why do I need such a huge apartment?
You'll have friends to visit you.
Doesn't Jiang Xiao Ning
love to sleep over with you?
Also,
if your relatives come to visit,
it'd a waste of money to
ask them to stay at a hotel.
Right.
How dare you say
staying at a hotel is a waste of money.
He lives in a hotel every day.
Bro,
you live in a hotel every day?
Reduce the rent in half.
I'll pay for the other half.
Okay, no problem.
Miss Zhao, if you're
satisfied with this apartment.
I'll call the landlord to negotiate
the rent.
I guarantee it'll be cheaper than
the one you had rented before.
Really?
Really.
But I need to
tell you something.
Someone died
in this apartment.
That's why it's so cheap.
Otherwise, you'd never be able to
rent such a high-quality apartment
with this price.
I'm okay with it.
Not a problem.
There is another workaround.
If a male were to
live here,
everything would even be better.
Do you need any help?
Why are you looking at me?
Well.
I can live here to suppress the misfortune.
Do you know what I dislike the most about you?
What?
You have a glib tongue.
You sound like you don't care
about anything when you talk.
Okay.
You can treat me as air.
I won't talk.
Do you have time tomorrow?
I'm going to move tomorrow. Come if you want to.
I'll be there for sure. What time?
I thought you weren't talking to me?
How dare I.
Make a peace sign.
Be quick.
What happened?
There was a camera.
I want to poke your eyes out.
You're so annoying.
So cute.
Chuan, what do I need
to get a marriage certificate?
I think
I'll get married soon.
You know what?
Not only did she ask me out,
but she also asked me
to view the apartments with her today.
Such a private matter.
Sorry.
I can't come to
visit you often anymore.
I'll have my own place soon.
Don't need to live in a hotel anymore.
She's starting to need my company
and starting to need my protection.
Companionship is the longest confession of love.
Protection is the most silent companionship.
Chuan, do you get it?
I'm talking to you.
Why are you ignoring me?
What are you sending?
"I miss you a little."
Miss what?
You've made huge progress.
I thought not being in a relationship for ten years
would make you rusty.
Mind your own business.
Close the door
when you leave.
You can't match my progress
no matter how fast you go.
"I miss you a little."
I know what I should do.
I'm home.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Come here.
I have something to tell you.
Aunty, what's the matter?
You must break up with Gu Chuan now.
Why?
Stand up.
You guys don't match.
What was your parents'
biggest wish?
They hoped you would be happy.
Now that they're gone,
I'm responsible for taking care
of you.
Aunty.
Why do you always bring up my parents?
It's like I did
something heinous.
Didn't you like Gu Chuan?
Why did you suddenly change your mind?
Don't ask.
Anyway,
break up.
What happened?
Don't you know about
his physical condition?
Did you talk to him?
Of course, I needed to
check him for you.
It's good that I asked.
Otherwise, there will be huge issues.
Think about it.
He's in poor health when he's still young.
If he gets sick again
after you guys are together,
you'll be his personal nanny?
What else did he tell you?
Nothing else.
Don't ask again.
He really didn't tell
you anything special?
What special things could he tell me?
No.
Then listen to me.
Break up with him now.
I'll never break up with him.
I'll explain
things to you later.
I don't want any explanations.
Break up with him now.
I'm going to bed.
You should rest too.
I'll wait until you calm down.
Kid,
I haven't finished talking.
Don't you know manners?
(What do men think when they are in love?)
Hope you take the lead.
Sometimes, in a relationship,
the people who take the lead
feel they are putting more effort into it.
They'll also feel tired if they always take the lead.
(What are you doing?)
(I'm...)
(I'm studying.)
(Shouldn't he tell me)
(Aunty went to talk to him?)
(Okay, you keep studying.)
Fine, I won't bring it up if you don't mention it.
Jiang Xiao Ning, hold back.
Must hold back.
You can do it.
Hold back.
Let's see when you will contact me.
Why are you here?
I came here
to check if you're actually studying.
Of course.
You know I'm studying...
You woke up so early during the weekend?
I couldn't fall asleep.
If you can't fall asleep,
why don't we take a walk outside?
Great.
Somebody said he would come to help me.
I was helping you clean up
the apartment this whole time, right?
Look how clean
and how organized it is.
Why can't I get the door open?
Why did you take my key?
Whose things are these?
They're all mine.
Xu Cheng Ran, you are way out of line.
I'm not.
The master bedroom is yours.
The second bedroom belongs to me.
We can share the living room and the kitchen.
Well-planned.
Did you ask for my input?
Also,
you're rich.
Why bother to
share an apartment with me?
Yan Yan.
I think you shouldn't have
bias against me.
I'm actually a thrifty
and economical young man.
I don't like to
live a wasteful lifestyle.
Sharing an apartment saves us money.
We can also accompany each other.
The layout of this apartment
is very good.
With the living room in the middle
and bedrooms across from one another,
we won't bother each other.
Also,
I can stay here to suppress the misfortune.
You'll have a sense of safety.
I'll have a sense of happiness.
It's perfect.
Are you serious?
I'm sharing the apartment with you for sure.
Things have changed so much around here.
It feels different every time
I come back.
This town has become
a tourist attraction.
More people come to visit.
After the construction
of the old house is done,
I want to bring Grandma and Aunty here.
That way,
I can visit Grandma and Aunty
when I come
to pick you up.
You'll also get to eat
dumplings made by Aunty.
Didn't Aunty ask you anything?
You finally asked me.
What did you talk about?
Did you
tell her about
the mechanical heart?
I didn't.
I just told her
I have some health issues.
You don't really need to tell her.
How can I not?
You dislike cheating the most.
You can be more strategic.
Does Aunty have a strong attitude?
No.
Don't overthink it.
Aunty just cares about me too much.
It's also my first time
being in a relationship.
I can understand why she's worried.
Actually, her worries
make sense.
They don't.
I won't allow anyone to say anything bad about you.
Eyes on the road.
You're letting me move in
without a second thought?
No other requirements
or other schemes?
Why don't you eat a self-heating hot pot first?
You...
Stay if you want.
If you don't want to stay, get out right now.
♪You're the haze in my sky♪
♪A disaster for my clear blue sky♪
Tell me the truth.
Do you like me?
If I don't like you,
why would I let you move in?
How much do you like me?
A little bit
of a fleeting like.
A little bit is enough.
I'll keep working at it
until I reach where
Gu Chuan is at.
Oh right,
I have a secret
to share with you.
About Gu Chuan and Jiang Xiao Ning?
I know.
You know too?
Am I the last person to find out?
It's delicious.
This garden used to be pretty.
We planted all kinds of
flowers in the garden.
My dad also
built a swing for me.
I spent all my summer breaks here
when I was young.
Unfortunately,
everything got burned down.
I'll work hard to
save enough money
to rebuild this house.
I can help you out.
This way, you'll have
less pressure.
Of course, I hope
someone could help me.
It'll certainly
relieve some of my pressure.
But,
since I promised my dad,
I'll rely on my own efforts to
rebuild the house.
My dad's dream was
to design everything on his own.
To build
a house that
can bring all family members together.
Now that I've taken over
my dad's dream,
I'll do the same.
Although I don't know
when I'll have enough money,
I'll work harder and harder
and earn more and more money at your company
to rebuild the house.
I want to do something for you.
You've helped a lot.
I know you don't mind,
but I do.
When we eat out,
I can't afford to pay
even if we split the bill.
So,
I accept the fact that
you pay for my meals.
However, I still want to be your equal,
as equal as possible.
Because only when we're equal,
can I love you
with confidence.
Okay, show me around.
Sure.
Look at this door.
Be careful.
Spider webs everywhere.
I really didn't expect
the little girl back then
to become like this today.
Become what?
Become pretty.
What else?
Besides being pretty,
what other strengths do I have?
Maybe you're so pretty
that I end up ignoring your
other strengths.
You're indeed Mr. Xu's friend.
You must have
hidden it too well.
It seems that
I need to get to know you again.
No rush.
We have plenty of time.
These days,
I feel like
things are a little unreal.
Taking a walk
with the person I like.
Looking at the stars in the sky.
The weather is nice too.
Feels like I'm living in a dream.
Kongming Lanterns.
(Wish Lantern)
♪July, summer♪
♪A scalding wave of heat♪
♪Cicada chirping at the end of the street♪
♪Two sleeping cats♪
♪Coolness after the rain♪
♪Endless dreams ♪
♪Pink roses, Diana♪
♪Heart beating like green grass blades♪
♪Time passing by gently♪
♪Our eyes meet inadvertently♪
♪Do you feel it in your heart♪
♪Open the doors and windows of the new moon♪
♪Embrace the longing for pouring rain♪
♪You say hello as you smile♪
♪Clouds gather♪
♪Suddenly dark clouds spread over the sky♪
♪Just like gradually♪
♪Forget about your good deeds♪
♪Pink rose, Diana♪
"Gradually fading away"
♪Time flies away♪
I like you.
Me too.
♪The lover is no longer here♪
♪Close the door and window under a full moon♪
♪Move forward in a heavy rain♪
♪Summer is ending eh♪
I'm not scared of electricity.
Aunty, you're still up.
I saw your boss
dropping you off.
Aunty asked you to break up for your sake.
Why don't you
listen to me?
Aunty, I've grown up.
I know what is good
and what is bad.
You're independent, right?
You don't need Aunty anymore?
Aunty, you know
that's not what I mean.
I went to the old house today.
Gu Chuan brought me back.
I know
he is good to you.
If he is
healthy,
there is no way
Aunty will say no.
Do you know why
he has health issues?
I don't want to know.
It's because of me.
Don't talk nonsense.
How could it have anything to do with you?
Gu Chuan is the big brother
who got hurt saving me ten years ago.
Sorry I made you worry.
It's okay.
I'm just afraid you'll
have a hard time because of me.
Not at all.
I must let Aunty know how much
you deserve to be loved.
How lucky am I
to have met you.
Charging completed.
You have health issues?
What issues?
Are they treatable?
There's the possibility
that I’ll be cured.
In other words,
there's the possibility that you won't be cured?
(Dr. P mobile)
(Heart rate: You've received a message)
Your phone has been buzzing.
What's this?
This is an app I got
that can help locate my friend.
I'll call him.
Chuan, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm really okay.
Is that Gu Chuan?
Is everything okay?
He said he's fine.
Don't worry about him.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪