♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and let's count down
to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 24=
Mr. Gu, are you going out?
My parents are here.
I'm having a meal with them.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I always picked them up.
I'll go with you.
Consider it a welcome reception
for your parents.
It's fine.
Do you need anything?
Here. The new design is ready.
Leave it on the desk.
I'll check it when I get back.
Let's go.
(Chuan Design Studio)
Wang Kai.
What?
Send me Mr. Gu's parents'
hotel information.
Am I supposed to know?
Besides you, who else would know?
Hurry.
I bought them something. I need to send it over.
I'll send it to you later.
Send it now.
Meeting your parents so soon.
I don't think it's appropriate.
Not at all.
Don't put too much pressure on yourself.
Let's go
to the art gallery for inspection.
After that,
I'll take you out
to have dinner with my parents.
Sure. Whatever you say, Boss.
Who is it?
Uncle, long time no see.
It's you, Man Lin.
Come on in.
Uncle.
I've bought you some stuff.
What did you buy?
Why are you being such a stranger?
Consider it a token of apology.
I was supposed to pick you up
at the airport.
But I have been too busy recently.
Young people
should focus on their work.
You're here, Man Lin.
Aunty.
Why are you standing here? Come and take a seat.
All right.
Aunty.
I've bought you a gift.
It's right there.
I don't know if you'll like it.
You're being such a stranger.
Man Lin, how are you lately?
It's all good. Same old, same old.
Uncle and Aunty.
How long will you be staying this time?
Stay longer,
if you're not busy.
I was thinking to arrange
a stay at a nearby resort area
for you to relax a bit.
It's fine.
Uncle and I came back
just to visit Xiao Chuan.
Fang Yun.
What time
are we meeting Xiao Chuan?
Should we go now?
That reminded me.
Uncle, are you going out?
That's right.
Xiao Chuan has
made a reservation for us at a restaurant
to welcome us back.
Man Lin, do you have any plans later?
No.
That's perfect.
Come with us.
We can talk while we eat, right?
Sure, anything you say, Aunty.
Let's go.
Aunty, come on.
Aunty, have you been
to Europe before?
Have been to a few places.
-Son, here you are.
-Here you are, Xiao Chuan.
Xiao Chuan, Man Lin
brought a lot of gifts
to the hotel to visit us today.
Well, it just so happened
that we are having dinner with you.
So I asked her if she has any plans
and she said she is free.
So we asked her
to come along.
Here, take a seat.
Why are you still standing there?
Look at you.
Every time we come,
Man Lin will pick us up and drop us off.
You didn't even ask her to join us for dinner.
The more people having dinner
together, the merrier.
Don't just stand there. Take a seat.
We're waiting for you to have dinner together.
Aunty.
We were talking about Europe earlier.
There's a really nice place.
Where is it?
Norway.
My friends have been there before
and they said
the aurora is spectacular.
If there's a chance,
how about going there together?
Sure.
That's awesome.
Back then, when Xiao Chuan graduated,
we were planning to go.
It's a deal then. Let's go together.
Sure.
Waiter.
Aunty, do you need to refill some hot water?
I'll do it.
Are you alright?
Are your hands okay?
It's alright.
This isn't something
that you should be doing.
Get the waiter.
Man Lin, sit.
Boss, it's alright.
Be careful.
Waiter!
Aunty, are you full?
Yes, it's delicious.
That's great.
Come and find us when you have time.
Sure.
Uncle and Aunty,
let me drive you home.
Okay.
Mr. Gu,
I'll drive Uncle and Aunty home then.
Okay. Drive safe.
See you, Uncle and Aunty.
-All right. See you.
-See you.
Let's go.
I was the one who almost got scalded.
Why are you being so upset?
It's easy to get emotional.
Everything about you
affects my heart.
How can I not be mad?
I'm fine, aren't I?
The purpose of the dinner
was to tell my parents about us.
You should have given me a heads up.
At least, I can dress up.
It's not like they haven't seen you before.
My status is different now.
It should be more formal.
It's all good enough
when you're being yourself.
Well, there's still room
for improvement, right?
Su Man Lin was there just now.
It was hard for me to tell them
about us with an outsider around.
Next time,
I'll find a chance
to have a meal with my parents
and tell them about us.
Actually, I never understand
why people tend to avoid
office romance.
Well, it would be awkward if things didn't work out.
It's fine if they stay together.
But if not,
you'll have to meet often
because of work.
It's like a scar on your body breaks open
over and over again every day
and it will never heal.
Why think about
breaking up?
I'll never leave you.
All right then.
Tomorrow, I'll go to the office
and announce
our relationship to all.
No.
That would be awkward.
I also feel awkward
hiding around every day.
From tomorrow onwards,
I'm not going to hide anymore.
See you. Be safe.
Bye.
(Xiao Ning.)
(Why don't you wait for me anymore?)
(Yang Chun Alley)
(Design Director Chuan)
Come in.
What's up?
My university lecturer called me.
He is now the Associate Dean,
responsible for student affairs.
He wants me
to lead the graduates
to redesign the library
and gymnasium.
That's good news.
Do you want to take some time off?
I haven't decided yet.
Besides, I'm just helping out.
I don't want it to affect my work.
Although I'm doing it for free,
in exchange,
I requested
a spot
to undertake advanced studies.
Advanced studies?
You've always lauded Jiang Xiao Ning, right?
I think she has the potential.
But she must go through
systematic learning.
It's not sure
if she can earn her degree
in the exit examination.
If the result isn't satisfactory,
this will give her
the chance
to study for a few years
before returning to the company to work.
There's no need for that.
This is a rare opportunity.
You should know that
architecture majors rarely offer
a spot for advanced studies.
She will pass the exam.
I mean, just in case.
That won't happen.
I'll tutor her myself.
What?
You don't have faith in me?
Never mind.
Give me another one of this, too.
Drinking to heal your broken heart?
Says who?
It's written all over your face.
Are we that close?
You don't even know me.
There's no need to.
Are you saying
that
I'm easy to read?
It's because you're too stubborn.
You thought
you hid it well.
Anyone with a discerning eye
can see
your feelings for Gu Chuan.
But I think
he's not going to marry you.
What are you trying to say?
You can be
good working partners
and you can talk about everything.
But there are no sparks
between the two of you.
I've put so much effort into it.
And I'm worse
than Jiang Xiao Ning?
You should know
that love isn't an exchange.
You don't get
what you give.
You can talk the talk.
Aren't you a loser yourself?
I'm different from you.
There's no difference.
Jiang Xiao Ning and I
grew up together.
Although our relationship
did not evolve from friendship to love,
at least,
I didn't change anything for her.
And you?
You gave up your world
for Gu Chuan,
didn't you?
Well, at least, I tried.
Unlike you.
A coward.
It depends on what you measure it against.
Let me ask you.
Is Gu Chuan
your only measure of happiness?
It is to me.
Look.
This is the key difference
between us.
To me,
I'll not use anyone
to measure myself.
So every step that I take now
is to accomplish
my own goal.
I'm a winner.
And you?
To you, getting Gu Chuan
is your goal.
You're a loser.
Tang Xu, what are you looking so smug about?
Chill.
I just find it unfair for you.
You've been with him for so long
and you've loved him for years.
But you don't even get the chance
to confess your feelings.
You are so poor.
(You gave up your world)
(for Gu Chuan,)
(didn't you?)
(To you, getting Gu Chuan)
(is your goal.)
(You've been with him for so long)
(and you've loved him for years.)
(But you don't even get the chance)
(to confess your feelings.)
(You are so poor.)
Gu Chuan.
Gu Chuan, open up!
Gu Chuan!
Here.
Drink some water.
Right now,
I look like a joke, right?
Indeed, it's not the one that I'm familiar with.
I want to stop pretending
to be perfect and proud.
So you're going to
make yourself like this?
Perhaps, I've reached the limit.
If I don't say it out,
it might suffocate me.
Some things
are better left unsaid.
I like you.
Su Man Lin.
You're drunk.
Go home and get some rest.
When you wake up tomorrow,
you won't
do drunk talk again.
Gu Chuan.
All these years, can't you tell?
Can't you feel it
at all?
We are just
partners,
colleagues,
and friends.
Since I joined the company,
I have moved my seat
to the opposite side of your office.
That way,
I get to see you every day.
I'll observe
if you sleep
or eat well,
and if you're in good mood.
I hope
that whenever you need something,
I'll be able to show up
in front of you immediately.
I changed
your assistant over and over again
not because I'm petty
or jealous.
It's because I was worried
that they couldn't take good care of you.
We go to work together,
eat together,
and pick up your parents together.
My concerns for you
are far beyond the scope of my work.
Can't you feel it?
To me,
we're just
good partners
and good friends.
I don't want to be your friend.
Why can't we
take a step forward?
I think
I am different from others.
If I did something
that gave you the wrong idea,
I'll apologize
to you.
Since
I have said it out,
just be quick
and give me an answer.
There's no answer.
None of this
should happen.
But it already happened.
Are we going to pretend
that nothing has happened?
Go home and sleep.
When we wake up tomorrow,
I'll pretend
that none of this has happened.
Just tell me!
Do you like me or not?
No, I don't.
Why?
As a partner and a friend,
you're irreplaceable.
But if you want
something more,
that's impossible.
It's so cruel of you.
At times like this,
it's either being cruel or promiscuous.
I'd rather
if you can be promiscuous with me.
Why do you want
to turn yourself into this?
Su Man Lin.
Where did
your pride go?
All I want is you.
How is Jiang Xiao Ning
better than me?
Both of you
are two different people.
There's no way
to compare the two of you.
Why did you choose her and not me?
Stop asking
such lame questions.
What kind of spell
did she put you under?
In just a few short months,
she made you fall head over heels in love with her.
And me?
I've waited for a good six years
and this is what I got.
You're drunk.
Go home and sleep.
But she's not good enough for you.
She is a girl
who didn't even graduate from university.
Such an unprepossessing girl
with no family background
is not good enough for you!
Su Man Lin!
If you keep this going,
things are going to get really ugly.
What's said is said.
I can't take it back.
How about this?
You can go home
and take a few days off.
Think it through
and pull yourself together.
You can go now.
How did I lose to her?
There's no winning or losing.
You just picked the wrong guy.
Xiao Ning.
Give this to Sister Man Lin.
She's not here.
I think she went out.
I didn't see her since morning.
I have a lot of documents
for her to sign.
Wang Kai.
Where's Sister Man Lin?
I don't know.
I'm looking for her as well.
Is she on leave?
That's not possible.
She's an iron woman.
Besides being hospitalized,
I haven't seen her take time off
since she started working here.
What should I do about this?
Well, show it to Mr. Gu then.
All right then.
Did something
happen to Su Man Lin?
This is very unusual.
Give her a call
and ask her.
Look how concerned you are.
Cheng Dong.
Call her.
She's your colleague. Show some concern.
I didn't bring my phone.
Jia Jia.
Mr. Cheng wants you to take a look at this.
Give me a second.
Here.
This is for you.
Is this a gift?
It's from my mom.
From Aunty Fang?
Well, she felt sorry
about the dinner.
So she...
Is it okay for me to take it?
Besides,
I was the one who wasn't careful.
What should I give her in return?
No need for that.
Just keep it.
By the way,
why didn't Sister Man Lin come to work?
She has been working hard lately.
So I gave her
a long break
to get some rest.
Well, I'll get back to work.
Hi, Xiao Ning.
When do you have time
so we can meet and have a talk?
Aunty.
Sorry, I'm late.
It took me so long
to find this place.
It's all right.
This is where
your Uncle and I had our first date.
Look.
A lot has changed over the years.
Well, that makes sense.
We're old now.
Not at all.
You still look young.
Thank you.
Xiao Ning.
Actually,
when I first met you,
I've been very fond of you.
You have pure eyes
and a dazzling smile.
I can tell
that you're nice to Xiao Chuan.
So
if you two are together,
you have my blessing.
Thank you, Aunty.
Look at you.
You're not shy at all.
My boss said the same.
You're very outstanding.
But Xiao Chuan's case
is a different one.
I know.
Gu Chuan has told me all about it.
You knew?
From the looks of it,
Xiao Chuan thinks you're the one.
All right then.
I'll go ahead and say it.
Go ahead, Aunty.
Actually,
as you can see,
we're not close.
Since he had
the heart surgery,
he has started
to alienate himself from us.
Such estrangement
is fatal to family relationships.
Which is why
I really hope
that we can clear the air
if there is any misunderstanding.
That's because
we're getting older.
We won't be able
to travel back and forth as often.
Aunty.
Gu Chuan is just not good at expressing himself.
I believe
if you talk things out,
there's no misunderstanding
that cannot be resolved.
Today,
I have something important
to tell you.
Dad. Mom.
I was at fault
and I apologize to you.
I'm sorry.
Silly kid, we're family.
There's no need to apologize.
Back then, I kept alienating myself from you.
I thought
if I had been more annoying,
and when I was gone,
you wouldn't get so upset.
Nonsense.
No parents
will actually
hate their own children.
Even if you used worse ways
to hurt us
over and over again,
I know deep down
you felt worse than any of us.
Xiao Chuan.
Since your heart surgery,
your personality
has changed tremendously
and you once refused
to be taken care of
by me and your mom.
So I couldn't help thinking
that it would get harder
for us
to communicate with each other.
In the end,
I've started to even accept
the estrangement
from you.
But Xiao Chuan,
remember this.
Your mom and I
have never thought
about giving up on you.
It was too selfish of me.
Xiao Ning told me
that my action
was only to fulfill my goal
and I've neglected your feelings.
Now that I think of it,
how can I
deny the whole world
just because of a mechanical heart?
After all,
I have you.
You little brat.
Think about it.
If you got silly and left
back then,
where could you
find such a good girlfriend?
Not even in your next lifetime.
Meeting Xiao Ning
is my greatest blessing.
Xiao Ning, thank you.
Aunty.
I didn't do anything.
All I did was
blurting out a few words.
I hope you won't mind that I talked too much.
Why did the atmosphere
become so tensed
all of a sudden?
Son.
Drink with me.
Sure.
I'll drink with you today.
Boss.
You can't drink.
It's fine.
I drank the other time too, right?
An alcohol level of 3%.
I can take it.
Don't worry.
It has a low alcohol level.
Besides, it's a wooden table.
It's not conductive.
Even if it is,
the bill is on you, Dad.
Isn't it?
Yes, it's on me.
But the money is with your mom.
Knock it off.
Xiao Ning, drink up.
Here.
Here, son.
Here, Xiao Ning.
You're back.
It's been a long day.
Why are you working so late today?
I'm so exhausted.
Eat something first.
I have heated the food up three times.
What's wrong?
Not feeling well?
Perhaps, I caught a cold.
My head hurts.
Hold on. I'll make you some cold remedies.
Here, drink it.
I used warm water. It's not too hot.
Warm and thoughtful.
Eat up.
Try my cooking.
If it's not to your liking,
I'll order delivery for you.
Still feeling unwell?
I was just thinking
I'm quite blessed
to have someone waiting to have dinner
with me after coming home from work.
This is nothing.
There's more than this.
You seem pretty experienced.
Of course.
Yan Yan, that's not what I meant!
I've never cooked for other girls.
The food is cold. Reheat it.
(Cohabitation Agreement)
Whether you're in the right or wrong,
the man should take the initiative
to cheer the girl up.
Once serious consequences are caused,
the man will be held responsible.
Never walk away from a fight.
Even if you do, never step out of the community.
It's a must to bring your phone and never turn it off.
Do you have a problem with that?
Can I add another one?
What is it?
No kicking the other person out
or getting physical during a fight.
Anything else?
And...
Based on the principle of equality
and mutual assistance,
(Whether or not the objection is accepted,)
I strongly suggest that
(the woman reserves the final explanation right.)
this one should be removed.
Appeal dismissed.
You don't have to sign it if you don't want to.
I'll sign it.
You reserve the final explanation right.
So you agree to that one too?
Which one?
The fifth one.
Give up your status as a rich second generation
and be an ordinary person.
Is being rich a bad thing?
I don't want others
to think
that I covet your family property.
I don't want to be branded a money-grubber.
That way,
your dad will have nothing to worry about.
My dad will probably kill me.
Xu Cheng Ran.
Do you dare to give up
on your luxury cars, mansions,
and the fancy lifestyle
that you used to have?
Just live a simple life with me
in this small apartment.
I dare to.
Aunty.
My boss said you have airsickness.
This is the medication
in case
you don't feel well.
Xiao Ning, come and visit me.
I'll cook for you.
Thank you, Aunty.
Dad.
Cut down on drinking.
Xiao Ning and I will find more chances
to visit you two.
I know.
Not going to hug?
Be well, son.
You can go back.
Safe journey.
Bye, Uncle and Aunty.
Okay, you can go back.
I'm leaving.
Take care of yourself.
All right now. Just go back.
Thank you.
Boss,
you're welcome.
Yes, pack everything in.
Send them to Director Su's new office?
Yes.
Send it over there.
All right.
Why the sudden change
of seating position?
She had it changed before too, right?
You men are so slow-witted.
Su Man Lin
has never changed her seat in the last six years.
She has moved into her own cubicle now.
You're overthinking it.
She's a senior staff
and the vice president of the company.
Isn't it normal
to move into her own cubicle?
The point is
the one taking over her place
is Jiang Xiao Ning.
Xiao Ning is an assistant too.
Mr. Gu can see her
when he looks up.
It's more convenient to call her.
You're really hopeless.
How so?
Sister Man Lin, you're here.
Where's all my stuff?
It's moved into the cubicle.
I'm not moving.
I'll take the same position.
I'm sorry.
It's Mr. Gu's arrangement.
Since I joined the company,
I have moved my seat
to the opposite side of your office.
That way,
I get to see you every day.
To me,
we're just
good partners.
Where's the room?
The one on the left
at the end of the corridor.
Brother Kai.
I'm not going to
take Sister Man Lin's seat.
I'll just stay at my own place.
Well, Mr. Gu only told me
to arrange a room for Su Man Lin.
Whether or not you're going to take the seat,
it's all up to you.
Director Xu.
Take a look.
This new project
is going to start soon.
The initial plan
is to build
a large comprehensive community.
You are responsible
for this tender.
Thank you for your trust.
I've learned a lot
from you
and gained a lot of experience.
Don't worry.
I'll get it done.
That's great.
Do you think
you should give the project plan
directly to your brother?
I heard
that Gu Chuan from his company
is a sought-after designer.
Director Xu.
I know where you're coming from.
But our group
has our own long-standing partners.
If we were to change them,
wouldn't that
make their hearts sink?
What's more, this is a big project.
I don't think it's a good idea
to give up on bidding.
As for Gu Chuan,
he's a very capable guy.
Even if he bids openly,
he'll win for sure.
That way,
it won't give people something to talk about.
You seem to know Gu Chuan really well.
He just won an award
and has a good reputation
in the industry.
I've been keeping tabs on him.
Very well.
Director Xu...
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪