Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 18
Qibao Amber Pagoda.
Strength Boost.
It's a lot lighter.
Yeah.
Soul Skills are not allowed.
Why?
If we don't use Soul Skills,
what are we training for?
Train your body muscles.
What's the point of that?
How long can your
White Tiger Vajra Transformation
last?
About an hour.
Why can't it be longer?
If I go past my limits, my body will ache.
Correct.
When you use Soul Skills,
it creates a huge burden on your body.
Every muscle,
every bone,
is withstanding pressure.
If you train your body well,
your Soul Skills can last longer
and become more powerful.
Anyone else wants to say this is meaningless?
Come on.
If someone can't finish it,
everyone will be punished.
I won't be following you.
You can cheat during the training.
Just remember.
You can deceive me, but not yourself.
Without determination,
you won't last as a Soul Master.
Let's go.
Come on.
Wait for Rong Rong.
Hurry.
The pampered one
should just go home!
I'll help you later.
Come on.
Wait for me!
Rong Rong.
I'm the daughter of the Ning family.
I'll never admit defeat!
Good.
Gang.
Here.
I understand your intention.
But shouldn't it be done progressively?
Ask them to run such a long distance
in the beginning,
isn't it too difficult?
It's impossible for some of them to finish it.
You want to kick a few of them out?
No.
Unless they understand the meaning of teamwork.
True.
Brother Dai.
Why don't we wait for them?
No way.
The sign is right ahead.
We'll rest only when we reach it.
Look back.
Yeah, we really can't go on anymore.
The sign is totally out of sight.
Ou Si Ke and Ning Rong Rong
can't carry on.
How far have we gone?
Perhaps not even half of it.
Ou Si Ke.
Give your rocks to me first.
Brother Dai.
Rong Rong's basket is the least heavy.
You can take Rong Rong's one.
No need.
I can handle it.
I don't need your help.
We are a team now.
You heard what Master said too.
If any one of us can't finish it,
everyone will be punished together.
We carry it on first.
When we can't hold on anymore,
we'll return it to you.
I disagree.
Give me the heavier one. You take the lighter one.
Ou Si Ke.
Give me.
Brother Dai.
You're a little different today
from who you usually are.
What's the difference?
You're especially compliant
to Master's order today.
Also, you're not fierce to me today
as usual.
Am I usually fierce to you?
Tang San.
When we were in the Star Forest,
you surprised me.
Me?
You had great willpower.
You could even overcome a Soul Beast's nature.
It was impressive.
You flatter me.
I just wanted to protect my sister.
Actually, I want to be stronger.
I really want to.
I know.
As long as it makes me stronger,
I'm willing to try anything.
Even if that person has only Double Soul Rings
and his Soul Power is no match for me.
Brother Dai.
Actually, Master
is not who you think he is.
Tang San.
Give my rocks back to me.
I can carry them.
Hold on a little longer.
Let's discuss it when we see the sign.
It's right ahead.
Come on.
Come.
Have some water, Brother Dai.
Thank you.
Tang San, drink it.
Wu.
Why is this salt water?
This must be what Master prepared for us.
Drink more.
Don't drink too much.
After taking a rest,
let's make the trip back.
Give me my rocks.
Alright, here.
Brother Dai.
Give back my rocks to me too.
If you can't hold on later, give them to me again.
Slowly, slowly.
I don't think we can make it before lunchtime.
Luckily, we had enough breakfast.
Lunch?
It'll be a miracle if they can make it for dinner.
Do you think
I should go and check on them?
No way.
Two reasons.
First.
The tougher it gets,
the more we should stay away.
In the future,
they have to face
the hardest challenge on their own.
I can't help but feel that recently
we've switched our positions.
You doted on Tang San.
Now?
You're getting crueller.
My teaching is based on their aptitudes.
They can bear these things.
Sure, sure. You're right!
What's the second reason?
The second reason.
You don't have time to check on them.
Why?
You should be going out to earn money.
They are having meat every day.
We're spending money every day.
Who is Headmaster now?
You said
that I'm in charge of training.
Earn money!
Make sure you come back on time.
Later,
you still have to supervise their lessons.
You treat me like a dog!
Ma Hong Jun.
Give your rocks to me.
I can handle it.
Cut the cackle.
I don't want to miss dinner
because of you.
I can do it.
I'm fine.
Give some of yours to me.
No need.
Brother Dai.
Brother Dai, give me
Hong Jun's rock.
I can carry it.
No need.
Why is he so persistent today?
Let's go.
Master, we made it.
Rong Rong.
They didn't cheat or give up.
I'm surprised.
They will become the best team.
Tang San.
Who is it?
Hong Jun.
Why are you still awake?
I miss my dad.
It's so hard being a Soul Master.
Hong Jun.
Whatever we do,
we have to make an effort.
Never give up easily.
I won't give up.
Aren't both of you going to sleep?
Where's Brother Dai?
Brother Dai said he was going to try
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
He wanted to check if it could last longer.
Today is the first day of training.
Why is he in a hurry?
I think so.
He seemed really anxious today.
Brother San.
Are you hungry?
Now that you've said it,
I'm kind of hungry.
Ou Si Ke.
Give me two sausages.
I am not a cook.
I know.
I have the fire. I'll cook it.
You...
What are you doing here?
Brother Dai.
Honestly,
you are very important to me.
Had it not been for you,
I wouldn't have come to Shi Lan Ke.
I wouldn't have stayed here either.
What do you mean?
I came for you.
Spiritual attack?
You're too worn out.
There's no way you can resist my spiritual attack.
Tell me.
Tell me all your secrets.
Don't hide anything.
I'm sorry.
May I ask
what you want to do
to my cute brother?
When will he regain his awareness?
He is very strong spiritually.
He will wake up soon.
You're his fellow student?
Has he ever mentioned me?
Never.
Do you know who I am?
I don't.
Then why are you scared?
Let's play a game.
I'll close my eyes,
and try to catch you.
You're bleeding.
Is it a dark or light color?
Does it look pretty?
Your breathing seems to disappear.
The smell of your blood has changed.
But this is the blood of a weak person.
I'm familiar with it.
It belongs to my useless brother, right?
You have a Spirit Branch Martial Soul.
You can manipulate Soul Masters?
What is your Martial Soul?
A coward hiding behind him.
You are confident.
You think
that in front of my brother,
I won't be able to attack with my full strength?
He's useless even as a puppet.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave!
Too weak.
White Tiger Vajra Transformation!
Is this all you can do?
Triple Soul Rings.
Unfortunately,
it's still too weak.
I'm not a cook!
I make sausages for you?
Alright, enough. Enough!
How about an iron sausage?
Stop fighting!
I'll make an iron bar to beat you up!
Do you want to take a beating?
Enough! Stop!
How about
I find food for both of you?
Stop fighting, alright?
It's late at night and you want...
Just a kiwi...
I'll come back soon.
Don't fight.
Your acting was pretty good. Good job.
Here.
Have some water.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Where are you going?
I'm going to Tang San and let him comb my hair.
You must see him all the time?
Even your hair has to be combed by him.
He does it best.
I'm good at it too.
Come, sit here.
I'll comb your hair.
Wu.
I want to ask you something.
Alright.
Have you ever
kissed Tang San?
Don't move! I'm still doing your hair.
Why would I kiss Tang San?
What is your relationship with him?
He's my brother.
And then?
What?
My dad told me
that if any man wants to call me sister,
I should beat him up.
Why?
He said
that men would call themselves brothers,
but they would become beasts later.
Why would they turn into beasts?
I don't know either.
It should be mutual affection.
But what do the beast and affection
have to do with each other?
I asked my dad too.
He said
I would understand it in the future.
But,
how do I know if I feel affection?
Affection?
I think it's about
wanting to be with him all the time.
If you don't see him for a while,
you will start to miss him.
You're awake.
We trained so hard.
You should sleep more.
Where's Dai Mu Bai?
You see that?
She's already missing him.
Sister Qing, you feel affection for Brother Dai?
Nonsense, I don't.
You don't?
You looked for him the moment you woke up.
I'm just worried about him.
Why are you worrying?
You haven't seen him for a while,
and you're already worried?
It's you?
You're useless.
It took you a long time to wake
from being manipulated.
Looks like your departure from home
is a meaningless act.
Don't worry.
I'll bring you home once I kill her.
Coward.
The game is over.
Your death will be quick.
Don't worry.
It won't hurt.
Dai Mu Bai.
You must work with me.
Otherwise, we'll both die here.
Why would I kill my beloved brother?
I am the direct disciple
of the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
The chief of Martial Soul Hall is your master?
That's right.
That's great.
I'd really like to see
the blood of the disciple
of the Greatest Soul Master in Douluo Continent.
What color would it be?
Are you alright, Brother Dai?
Your Blue Silver Plant is interesting.
Both of you, run away. I'll stop him.
None of you can escape.
Can you use White Tiger Intense Light Wave again?
It's useless against him.
How can you know?
What did you do to me?
You protected me
even when you lost your awareness.
I'm truly grateful.
Thank you.
You're lying!
Use White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
We'll solve the problem once and for all.
Really?
I'm waiting.
It needs to be a delayed outburst.
Trust me!
I've scheduled their training
for the next few days.
But it still lacks actual combat experience.
Why don't we
let them go back to battle in the Soul Arena?
We can consider that,
but their opponents may not be strong enough.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave!
What's the point of letting it explode in the air?
It's a warning.
Headmaster, he wants to kill us.
Seven Soul Rings.
You're a Soul Saint?
Don't kill him, Headmaster.
He's my brother.
Why are you here in Tian Dou Empire?
Seems like you know who I am.
I don't care who you are.
You're not allowed to harm my students.
I can spare them,
but I have to bring my brother back.
No way.
What if he's willing to go back with me?
Tell him, Dai Mu Bai.
Are you coming back with me?
I'll go with you.
Brother Dai, you're willing to go with him?
If I go against him,
the school will get into serious trouble.
I'm asking you
if you're really willing to go with him!
So what if I'm unwilling to go?
You cannot even imagine
the force behind him.
Then we'll face it together.
Even though Shi Lan Ke is small,
we're not afraid of danger.
We will fight together on your side.
Fight together?
How many students do you have in your school?
Seven!
You only have seven students at school?
Dai Mu Bai.
It seems that after you left home,
you haven't improved enough
to be able to change your fate.
But right now,
I can still give you a chance.
I heard
that your records
in Suo Tuo Soul Arena are quite good.
I'll give you five days.
After five days,
we meet in the Soul Arena.
All seven of you against me.
If you can defeat me,
you don't have to go with me.
But if you lose,
Shi Lan Ke School
should cease to exist!
No way!
Sure.
Headmaster.
I trust all of you.
You will know
that number is meaningless!
No matter how many of you are there,
you're still just insects.
Tang San, Tang San.
You were fighting.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'll definitely tell you next time.
I heard Brother Dai was there too.
Where is he?
He's with Headmaster.
You just arrived. You're leaving?
Sister Qing was worried
about us walking at night.
So she accompanied us here.
But our dorms are close to each other.
Besides, Sister Wu, you're good at fighting.
Shouldn't she
worry about the one beaten up by you instead?
You said "us".
Is Rong Rong coming too?
Wu!
Why did both of you walk so fast,
and didn't wait for me?
Why did Sister Qing leave?
Take a seat.
Did I miss anything?
It's...
I'll tell you.
This is the situation now.
Brother Dai has an elder brother
called Dai Wei Shi.
One word to describe him.
It's "mad", you know?
He's basically the advanced version
of Brother Dai.
He challenged us
to a battle.
All seven of us against him alone.
He's that mad?
He's even madder than Brother Dai!
Exactly!
They're truly biological brothers.
How many Soul Rings does he have?
Brother Dai said
he has four.
Quadruple Soul Rings Soul Honour.
Sounds pretty strong.
But with the seven of us against him,
we should be able to win.
Brother Dai also said
Dai Wei Shi is extremely strong.
His strength cannot be compared
with normal Soul Honours.
Here. This is the medicine I made.
Drink it up.
Thank you.
Mu Bai.
You said Hu Lie Na had asked you out
and used a spiritual attack on you?
Yes.
When I regained my awareness,
my brother was already there.
Explain it to me.
I asked Brother Dai out
because I like him.
Do you need to use a spiritual attack
on him if you like him?
I didn't do it on purpose.
His brother suddenly appeared from the back,
and I thought it was an ambush,
so I retaliated.
It was an accidental hit on Brother Dai.
Then about my Soul Skill,
how do you explain that?
You even used your power to manipulate him?
If I were really that capable,
I would use it on his brother.
Wouldn't it be fine?
I'd make him return to where he came from.
Why would I manipulate Brother Dai?
Gang.
It's true that she doesn't have the capability.
She may have used a special tool.
Hand it to us.
What?
During the fight, you said
you were the direct disciple
of the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
With that identity,
it's normal that you have a tool like that.
I don't have such a tool.
You don't trust me?
You can search my body.
Brother Dai.
Are you mad at me?
I apologize.
I'm willing
to fight together with you five days later.
You're not a student of Shi Lan Ke.
Why do you have to fight?
I like you.
I'm willing to help you.
I came to Shi Lan Ke because of you.
This is a fight for Shi Lan Ke School.
The attached student doesn't need to go.
His brother is so strong.
I have Triple Soul Rings.
I can help.
No need.
You heard him.
I want to create
a team that can trust each other.
Unfortunately, you are not qualified.
Why?
Just because I like Dai Mu Bai,
but didn't express it?
Who you like is your own business.
But in Shi Lan Ke,
who do you trust? Who believes you?
If you are unwilling to trust in this team,
then the team does not need you, either.
Whatever.
I'm leaving.
Wait!
What do you want?
Dai Mu Bai, I have something to tell her.
You may leave.
Since our trip to the Star Forest,
a lot of things have happened,
and I haven't had time
to properly speak with you.
What do we have to talk about?
Was Su Yun Tao always around?
He was protecting you.
No such thing.
He's dead.
What?
In the Star Forest,
I saw someone kill him.
Nonsense!
Who killed him?
It was a shadow.
What kind of answer is that?
Even though I couldn't see the face,
I've been speculating for the past few days.
Why did the killer want to kill Su Yun Tao?
Do you have an answer?
In the Star Forest,
the killer was meeting up
with the Azure Bull Python.
The King of Star Forest?
Su Yun Tao was killed
probably because
their meeting was a secret.
But the problem is
that the shadow's face couldn't be seen.
How could Su Yun Tao reveal the secret?
You mean
that the killer is likely
to be someone he is familiar with?
That's right.
This is the only reason to kill Su Yun Tao.
Su Yun Tao has no family members.
He has been living in Martial Soul Hall.
If the killer is someone he's familiar with,
it might be someone from Martial Soul Hall.
These are just my speculations.
I told you
because you were fighting
alongside Tang San earlier.
Thank you.
It's nothing.
You can go.
You're using Hu Lie Na
to warn the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
Am I right?
Chief.
An officer from Martial Soul Hall told me
that you wanted to see me.
Su Yun Tao
was killed in the Star Forest.
Su Yun Tao is dead,
but she is still in Shi Lan Ke School.
Take care of her for me.
Make sure she doesn't cause trouble.
Me?
You'd better not cause trouble, either.
Chief.
You must have heard
of what happened last night.
We still have five days.
If we lose the battle,
Dai Mu Bai will be taken away.
If any one of you is unwilling to participate,
you can quit now.
After all, I accepted
the duel with Dai Wei Shi for you.
It's just a fight.
The seven of us will definitely win.
Master.
Are we starting our training now?
For the next few days,
you will be training separately.
Shouldn't we train together?
There are only five days left.
We don't have enough time
to develop your teamwork.
It's better to make each of you stronger.
Wu, Zhu Zhu Qing.
Follow Headmaster to the forest out of town.
He will train both of you.
The rest.
I have special training for you.
I know both of you have great speed.
Now,
I want to see how fast you can get.
As soon as you touch me,
you pass.
I'm not done yet.
I can't go beyond the range of the bell.
I am not allowed to ring the bell either.
What about us?
Both of you have no restrictions.
Are you done?
Done.
Don't forget your Martial Soul.
Gang.
You're saying
that the training is just a trap?
Not for them to increase their power.
That's right.
No one can really improve
in just five days.
Then why are you lying to them?
I'm not lying. I'm guiding.
How so?
They're still young.
Just having enthusiasm and passion
is not enough.
So this training
is to change their attitude.
First, use my way
to let them discover their own weaknesses.
When they want to make up
for their flaws themselves,
we can train them
according to their aptitudes
and teach them step by step
how to develop their skills.
Let me think about it.
So you're saying,
through our guidance,
they'll change from passively accepting
to actively discovering the truth.
Know one's strength and make up for one's weakness.
That's right.
This doesn't make sense.
Why don't you
just tell them their weaknesses?
Wouldn't it speed up
their understanding?
Sometimes, it's harder for people to accept
what others tell them.
If they can discover their weaknesses
during the training,
and learn to think,
that is the most valuable experience
a Soul Master can have.
Amazing, Gang.
You really deserve to be
Douluo Continent's number one
in Martial Soul theory.
To have a teacher like you
in Shi Lan Ke School.
Next semester,
I can increase the school fees!
Tuition has increased.
Headmaster, why are you smiling?
What's it about increasing school fees?
No, no, no. It's nothing.
What are you waiting for? Continue your training.
To reminder both of you.
Be aware
of your surroundings.
Come.
Dai Mu Bai, Tang San, Ma Hong Jun.
Tell me your Soul Skills one by one.
Triple Soul Rings.
White Tiger Protection Barrier.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
White Tiger Vajra Transformation.
Triple Soul Rings.
Intertwine.
Parasite.
Constraint of Spider Web.
I never thought of the names.
Basically,
one lets my fingers release fire.
Another
lets the flame grow stronger.
Then why don't we call them Phoenix Firing Line
and Fiery Phoenix?
Do you know how to use your Soul Skills?
Of course!
Have you ever tried
using White Tiger Protection Barrier
and White Tiger Vajra Transformation
at the same time?
Then simultaneously release
White Tiger Intense Light Wave.
Use three Soul Skills together?
Never thought about it?
Try it.
How is it?
It exhausts my strength quickly.
This is the most exhausting training method.
But it's also the most effective.
All three of you,
try to use your Soul Skills mixedly.
Direct all your attacks to this boulder.
Just like this? What's next?
Continue hitting it. Don't stop.
Before I return,
none of you can stop.
You two, follow me.
Brother Dai.
Let's do this.
Ou Si Ke.
I've heard that you don't want to be a Soul Master.
Yeah.
My dream is to spread arts.
I want to join a troupe.
I want to write my own plays and act them out.
Why do you not want to be a Soul Master?
My Martial Soul is too embarrassing.
Idiot, your Martial Soul is unique.
Others' Martial Souls are used for combat.
My Martial Soul only makes food with a bucket.
Why do you have to fight?
Isn't it good enough to stand behind others
and let them protect you?
But I'm a man.
This is my Martial Soul.
I'm actually like you.
When people attack,
I can only watch by their side.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪