♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad Episode 28
An Rou, is the carriage ready?
Mr. Hao has been waiting here for a long time.
Come on, I'd better go on my own.
You should stay here.
If his Highness really feels uncomfortable,
look for doctors as soon as possible.
Princess, don't you need me with you?
Since Mr. Hao is with me, nothing should be worried.
Stay here and look after his Highness.
You trust Mr. Hao a lot.
No kidding at this moment.
Yes.
Go.
Go!
Don't take away my little brother!
Ms. Wu!
- He's still alive!
- Ms. Wu!
Don't cremate him!
- Don't cremate him!
- Ms. Wu!
He's my younger brother!
Don't cremate him!
What are you doing? Let her go!
Save him!
They want to cremate my brother!
He'll die!
He has a plague.
My brother!
Ms. Wu!
Stop her!
My brother!
Don't cremate him!
He's really my younger brother!
Miss. Mister.
One by one, people die of the plague.
The corpses must be cremated.
It can't be delayed.
Princess.
Brother!
Ms. Wu!
I know.
Don't cremate him.
I know you can't believe it.
But your brother is seriously ill.
Don't chase him.
But now he's not painful anymore.
Last night,
I hummed a ditty
to put him to sleep.
Suddenly, he had a high fever
and black spots on his skin.
Then his body became cold.
Slowly.
I rubbed his hands, feet and face.
But he became totally cold.
I can do nothing.
He died.
Ms. Wu.
Your brother became bereaved after birth.
It's already hard for you to raise him up.
It's lucky that you're sister and brother.
Granny.
He's not had enough rice and steamed buns.
He came to this world
but left as if he had never existed, why?
When we arrive in Luoyang, I can give you anything you want.
I want you to give me a lot of rice.
I've never tasted rice.
I know your brother went to see your parents in the nether world.
Let him go.
I hope he won't be born into a family like ours in the next life.
He went to see our parents.
But I'm not happy at all.
I don't want him to see our parents.
I know.
Ms. Wu.
You can miss him.
You can feel sad.
But you should continue your life.
Lead a good life with the hope of your brother.
Sun.
A'Li, you had a nightmare.
You repeatedly called Sun.
Who is he?
Nothing.
You shouldn't shut yourself up in your room every day.
One will think too much if staying alone for a long time.
What you dream about at night reflects what you think about in day.
A' Bi.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I don't read many books.
Thanks to Ms. Quan, I have the very basic knowledge.
But when I was little, my mom always told me that
one can always lead a good life
if he combs his hair, brushes teeth, cleans his face with tissues
and has three full meals everyday.
I think Master is right.
You're so clever that you always think too much.
What you just said reflects real wisdom.
Yes.
Master always says my vague manner conceals a brilliant mind.
By the way, did you call a man A' Sun?
Or it's a monkey you raise?
It's Sun.
Sun?
So it's a bird you raise?
He's my former companion.
Since he's your companion, why doesn't he look for you?
I don't think so.
I did something that hurt him.
If he doesn't look for and hate me,
I'll feel a bit relieved.
Go!
Stop!
Any information of Changge?
Mr. Qin. I have the news.
We found a person similar to Young Master.
She went to Luoyang with a doctor and a young man in a donkey cart.
Who are the doctor and the man?
Is Changge safe with them?
Stop pretending to care about her.
We'll find Commander Li.
None of your business!
Xu Feng.
He's impetuous.
He never cares about what he says.
But he's always loyal to Young Master.
Don't think too much.
So we should speed up and arrive in Luoyang as soon as possible.
Since we're all for Young Master's good,
why do you always embarrass him?
During these days,
haven't you found that he really cares about Young Master?
Even if he really cares about Young Master,
I'll never forget the hatred in Shuozhou.
I know how you're feeling.
Since we are consistent in our goals, we should work together.
No need to quarrel with him without thinking twice.
Well.
Don't think too much.
Brother A'Zhun, water.
Have a rest.
Set out early tomorrow.
Hug me.
Come here.
Brother A'Zhun.
Throw me high.
One more time.
Stop!
Yuan is naive.
Are you naive, too?
Too dangerous!
What's your purpose?
You frighten her.
Yuan.
Don't play with him.
Play with me.
No.
Yuan.
You can play with any other person, except him.
He's not called Zhun.
He's Ashile Sun.
He put your parents...
Xu Feng.
A'Zhun, it's late at night.
Take Yuan to sleep.
Yuan, behave yourself.
Yuan.
Shall we play together elsewhere?
You have gone too far!
She scolded me!
What did I do?
Why don't you understand?
Do you want Yuan to be the second Young Master
who always lives in hatred?
You witnessed Young Master's pain and sorrow.
Don't you know the cost of hatred?
Did you see how happy she was just now?
Governor and his wife hoped that
their daughter could grow up lightheartedly
instead of suffering from hatred.
[Luoyang Office]
Princess.
The supplies of South Hill are ready.
What's the matter?
His Highness went out.
Did he go to South Hill?
Of course not.
He went to the street.
When will he grow up?
Well.
Seeing the miserable condition of the people, he may be touched.
Hope he won't make any trouble.
Princess, now you behave more and more like a sister.
Colored umbrella!
Look at these umbrellas!
Fresh cabbage!
Fan!
Look at the fans!
Little tiger!
Come and have a look!
All home-made!
Shengxin.
Since Madam selects you, you should behave yourself.
Good!
Great!
Come on!
Good!
Wrestle!
Move out of my way!
Great!
Wrestle!
Good! Wrestle!
Good!
Again!
Good. Go on!
Come on!
Go on!
Wrestle!
Go! Get him down!
Good!
Roll logs for us!
Money!
Don't grab!
Mine!
Don't squeeze! Don't grab!
- Don't squeeze!
- Mine!
Don't grab!
Move out of my way!
Don't squeeze!
Back off!
Mine!
Don't squeeze! Back off!
Beat!
Don't grab!
Don't squeeze!
Come on.
Don't grab!
Painful.
Don't move.
Let me apply the ointment to you.
Painful.
Still painful?
Thank you for saving me.
Tell me your name.
I'll give you money.
I'll repay you.
You're welcome.
Mister!
Here you are.
Back!
Mister, are you OK?
Come back!
Are you OK?
Back!
Give me a pie.
Here you are.
Brother A'Zhun.
Do you like this song?
Lazy bone!
Xu Feng is right.
You shouldn't get too close to me.
Why?
Yuan.
It's a wolf whistle.
It's our specialty.
I have nothing else to compensate you.
Blow it when in need.
I'll protect you on behalf of your parents.
In this way?
Very good.
[Sun]
What am I thinking about?
New trouble arose as soon as His Highness came here, why?
His Highness?
I'll finish.
More ointment.
Don't touch water.
Bear the pain.
A' Bi!
What happened?
His Highness secretly watched juggling and spread money
on the street instead of comforting the refugees after he came to Luoyang.
But the street was so crowded that many people were trampled on.
His Highness is here?
He never did anything right.
My apprentice.
Let me bandage it for you.
If you have spare time to care about the official affairs,
you'd better work with me in South Hill.
Let's go!
Your Highness.
Mr. Wei, finally you come!
People outside seem to be mad.
I want to return to Chang'an!
Get the carriage ready!
You're injured.
How did you protect him?
They're a bunch of thugs!
I spread money to them out of kindness.
But the outcome is terrible.
Some people were trampled to death.
Too terrible!
I want to go back to Chang'an!
What trouble did you make?
Sister.
I'm injured.
But why don't you care about me?
You show no kindness to me at all!
Let me see.
Chengqian!
Brother Shuyu.
Look around with me.
- Go.
- Princess.
It's my duty.
Keep an eye on His Highness lest he wants to go back to Chang'an.
Okay. Thank you.
Move out of my way!
- Commander!
- Go!
Be lenient on me!
Commander!
- Stand up!
- Commander!
Please be lenient on me!
Hurry up!
Commander.
It's these beggars who made troubles.
Commander, please be lenient on me!
We're not on purpose.
We've been hungry for days.
A rich man spread money in the street.
We just picked several more coppers.
We didn't expect things should go wrong.
Commander.
I know very well the people outside.
They're just too hungry.
Some people are kind on the surface, but vicious inside.
Some people look indifferent but are warmhearted, like you.
Take them back and let Magistrate deal with them.
Yes.
Go!
Commander!
Be lenient on me!
Commander, show mercy on me!
Hurry up!
Slow down.
Are you feeling better?
Bear the pain.
Why are there so many refugees?
They used to be ordinary people.
In the face of disaster and war, they became refugees.
As long as society is not stable, there will be more refugees.
Feel uncomfortable at the sight of that?
They are more fortunate than those who have no place to live
and no food to eat.
Some of those who have not escaped the disaster and war
are still wandering and struggling,
while some of them have been buried in the earth
and have no chance to live.
My friend.
Here you come.
Master.
Ms. Wu.
Master, who's this sister?
Is she new here to cultivate herself?
Ms. Wu.
She's A' Li.
She's been cultivating herself in the temple.
I'm busy today.
Can you take her to go outside tomorrow?
My apprentice.
Aren't you called Li Changge?
When did you change your name?
What I'm called doesn't matter.
Okay.
Change your name and restart your life.
[Luoyang]
Have you found her?
No.
I searched there but in vain.
Search in all directions!
Yes!
What happened?
Yuan is missing.
Yuan is missing!
You're the only one out there.
Didn't you see anyone running out?
Stop!
Xu Feng.
Listen.
If there's anything wrong with Yuan,
I'll get even with you for all the matters.
I'll kill you for Gongsun family.
First, find her.
Then it's up to you.
Where to go?
Yuan!
Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Let me take you out.
OK?
Come on.
Yuan.
Why are you here?
Tomorrow is mom's birthday.
I want to pick some flowers for her.
I saw flowers on the tree, but I couldn't reach them.
I didn't expect to fall into the pit.
What a good girl!
You are filial.
Gongsun's greatest wish is that you can be safe and happy.
It's a pity that he can help all people in his life
but can't protect his family.
Well, let's go back.
Nothing serious.
You can't do this again.
Painful?
I will immediately count the number of injured and the registered residence of each household.
Please come with me to comfort them and give them subsidies.
Mr. Wei, you can do it alone.
Or I wouldn't have brought you here.
How can you talk to Brother Shuyu like that?
It's all your fault.
You should comfort those people.
Sister.
My kindness is not rewarded.
I gave them money but was hurt.
I'm sad.
Leave me alone!
You're Crown Prince.
If you don't go, should I go?
So you said you would go.
I...
You're Princess of Tang.
You should do that.
Last time you comforted those refugees in person.
Sister.
I've already been injured.
Let me have a rest for a few days.
Let me see how long you can be so willful.
Sister.
Come on.
I'll go on your behalf.
But just this once.
Mr. Wei.
I dare not go into the street again.
Anywhere else can I go?
I heard that Ziwei Palace of Sui Dynasty is here.
Can you go with me?
Your Highness.
It was built by Emperor Yang. It's a sheer waste of energy and money.
I think you'd better go to visit common people.
Anyway, his Majesty appointed you...
Yes.
I think you're right.
You should watch Luoyang carefully, especially Ziwei Palace.
Emperor Yang was quite extravagant.
I have to see the palace
in detail as a reminder.
Get the carriage ready!
Wound healing unguent. Blood recovering pills.
Medicine is ready.
Princess, why not go with Mr. Hao?
[Anti-plague pills]
No need.
It's not the case in Chang'an.
There are many refugees.
They came from many different places.
Mr. Wei will take care of his Highness.
So he can't accompany you.
But I'm afraid if Mr. Hao isn't here, either.
I'm either in the mansion or in South Hill.
He'll find me for sure.
By the way,
it's impossible that he follows me all his life.
We should be able to protect ourselves.
Princess, you really change a lot.
It's better that Mr. Hao doesn't follow you.
Sometimes I'm scared at the sight of him.
Yes.
I was also afraid of him before.
Before?
Now you're not afraid of him?
Now...
Princess!
I finally find you!
Let me take you home.
Yesterday, Master asked me
to take you to South Hill today to look around.
Sister A' Li.
Do you have anything in mind?
You looked blue yesterday.
Why do you live in the temple?
Where's your family?
They all died.
Sister A' Li.
Here you are.
The candy was given from Master.
I haven't had it.
Here you are.
You want to give it to me?
Sister A' Li.
Don't be sad.
In fact, my family also died.
The people I met yesterday are not your family?
I used to live in Yunzhou.
When winter is approaching,
people from the grassland will come to loot.
Later, in the year of disaster,
no one could survive.
Our parents took us out.
They said we could survive in the south.
But later, my dad died of disease.
Then my mom also fell ill.
She said that ordinary people like us
can only depend on heaven for food;
if God wants to take back your life,
you can only accept such fate.
It shouldn't be the case.
But I can do nothing.
My parents died.
I took my little brother all the way to Liuyun Taoist Temple.
A few days ago, my brother died, too.
I miss him very much.
But I was told that people won't feel pain after death.
So he won't suffer anymore.
Is that true?
Sister A' Li.
Yes.
He won't suffer anymore.
Now he's with your parents.
But I'm still not happy at all.
Granny Chen told me that
my brother won't suffer in a family like ours.
But...
But I'm still sad.
Sister A' Li.
What sins have we done?
Why does God just refuse to treat us well?
You has done nothing wrong.
It's the fault of endless war.
I was born in a wealthy family.
We swam in luxury.
We went out by beautiful carriage.
We lived in a fantastic mansion.
But everyone wanted more.
I have thought that if I were born into a peasant family,
I would have been able to live in peace.
But I'm wrong.
I should understand earlier that
in troubled times,
if death can make my wish realized,
that will be much easier.
Here you are.
Have a taste.
Let's go.
A' Li.
Did Ms. Wu take you to see anything?
Taoist.
Could you teach me how to save these refugees?
Why do you have that thought?
I hope we can lead a peaceful life.
I go with the flow, like duckweed.
You can see heaven and earth, and all living creatures in the world.
It seems that your heart has been cured.
[Dapu Inn]
We're in Luoyang now.
Let's settle down here.
Mr. Qin.
Is Changge really in Luoyang?
If you don't believe my intelligence, you'd better find her alone.
Xu Feng.
Grandpa Qin.
What's wrong with Brother Azhun?
Nothing wrong with him.
He's afraid he won't find your Brother Li.
Thank you for your kindness.
Sister A' Li.
You're quite a fast learner.
You are more skillful in pounding herbs.
Come here, everyone!
Someone donates some medicine to us.
Princess.
Princess!
Princess, here you come!
Changge.
You don't hate me?
I was so stubborn that
I always refused you.
Leyan.
Can you forgive me?
I've never blamed you.
Thanks to God, we can meet again.
I really thought I'd never see you again.
The fate has brought us together again.
Don't cry.
How about you?
Are you Ookay?
Where did you go after we farewell in a hurry in Youzhou?
Did you go directly to Luoyang?
After leaving Youzhou, I went all the way north.
Then I met Taoist Sun.
It's a long story.
You must have suffered a lot.
You went through many difficulties, right?
Let bygones be bygones.
Don't mention it.
By the way, we almost met each other before.
What do you mean?
Do you remember the purse I gave you?
I embroiled a new one which is exactly alike.
I remember that.
I was confused that why someone knew
what the purse you gave me was like.
Why didn't you see me?
I went to see you.
But Hao Du arrived in advance.
Although Hao Du is not a good man, he can protect you.
By the way, why were you in Yunzhou then?
Commandant.
Where's Princess?
Her Highness is ahead.
Princess.
Princess!
Mr. Hao is here.
Hao Du?
Changge.
I have a lot to tell you.
Wait for me in the market between 3 to 5 pm.
Go. Hurry up.
Be careful.
Hurry up!
Hao Du!
I've finished my business.
Let's go back.
Wait a minute.
What's wrong, Princess?
I have a stomachache.
We have doctors here.
Doctor!
No need. It's just my period.
An Rou.
Let me do that.
Take it.
Hold on.
The carriage is over there.
3 to 5 p.m, market.
What happened to them?
[Spring Breeze and Evening Water]
Just now someone reported that his Highness came to Luoyang
to inspect the victims affected by the spring drought.
There's a lot of trouble in the city.
Considering the chaos,
I hope that all of you can put aside personal contradiction
and work together.
Mr. Qin.
We don't need to rely on others.
We can find Young Master on our own.
But why haven't we found Li Changge?
Well.
The situation in Luoyang is not clear.
The sooner we find her, the more reassuring we are.
Now that we work together, don't always quarrel.
Cooperation?
I don't want to work with him!
I don't know what he is thinking about.
Do you want to fight against me?
Okay.
I think all of us has put up with you for a long time.
If Mr. Qin didn't stop me, I would have beat you up!
Okay.
Have a try.
I'm old.
If the young men want to fight, go outside.
Don't tear down the house.
Go!
Upstairs!
The view upstairs is good.
On the battlefield, I won in an open and aboveboard manner.
If you're not convinced,
defeat me now.
Close the door!
These young men!
I asked them to fight outside.
We should compensate the owner here tomorrow.
If you had told them just now, they wouldn't have got into a fight.
For young people,
everything can be settled by a fight.
If he can't settle down such a little matter,
he won't be a dependable man.
This guy is really strong.
Bros!
Go on!
He's going to the limit!
I'm willing to admit defeat.
You win!
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad