♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 27
[Luoyang Office]
Xiao Wu.
Wait for me.
Xiao Wu, Xiao Wu.
Don't leave me.
Xiao Wu.
Princess.
Forgive me, please.
Where is Xiao Wu?
I've ordered them to bury Xiao Wu.
Please rest at ease.
I just had a dream.
In the dream, Xiao Wu is still alive.
But I don't know why he's running.
He keeps running and doesn't want to come back to me.
Hao Du,
is he still blaming me?
If not for me,
he wouldn't have been wounded and sick for long.
He'd have lived well.
I promised to give him a cart of rice.
I would take him to Chang'an
to see the blooming spring and picturesque landscape.
Now it's all gone.
Princess.
He's gone with a smile.
He didn't blame you.
Don't be sad.
See him with me tomorrow.
I want to be by his side until the end.
Princess.
Aren't you scared of me now?
After all these things,
I'm not scared of death.
You? I'm no scared.
I was scared of many things in the past.
How ridiculous I was.
Heaven rewards the good.
I've been guided to you by this amulet.
Now I return it to you.
Wish it a blessing to you.
Why do you have it?
It's a long story.
I found it in Hongyi Palace.
Maybe it's God's will.
If God pities me,
please bless the peace of all people.
Sure he will.
God bless Tang.
It's God's will.
Take it.
Hope it works till the end.
Please don't be upset.
Take care of yourself.
I've ordered to find the servant you're most familiar with
to take care of you.
She'll be here soon.
Thanks a lot.
Honestly, it's very lucky for you to come here.
You know what?
Liuyun Taoist Temple is a blessed land in the world.
It's perfect with kindness and insight,
delivers all living creatures from difficulty.
You aren't listening to me, are you?
How rude this prentice is.
[Yuqing's utmost Tao]
[Great virtues match the heaven and the earth.]
Nice to meet you, Taoist Sun.
Master has been talking about you.
Finally you're here.
Go to tell Master Taoist Sun's coming.
Okay.
Let's go inside.
This lady is...
She was picked by me.
She's in a bad mood, touchy now.
Please come in.
Are you better now?
Eat something.
Eat it.
Slow down.
Here we help refugees.
They're very piteous.
We help the poor people.
This way.
Liuyun Taoist Temple is divided into three yards.
Front, middle and back.
This is the pharmacy, opposite Taoist Sun's exam room,
which is connected to the exam rooms in front yard.
This is where Master lives.
Let's go to backyard.
This is the backyard.
It's silent here with many rooms.
You can choose one to live.
If you find yourself boring, come to me and A'Bi.
[Non-interference]
What are you looking at?
What is this place?
Master always meditates here.
We call it the silence room.
[Non-interference]
Shall I live here?
[Dear Brother Xiao Wu]
Princess.
Death is final.
My condolences.
Please don't blame yourself.
He has an unkind fate.
He took care of you a lot.
He's a righteous man.
If you can't reconcile with yourself,
we can ask for a reward for him when we arrive in Chang'an.
He won't care about that.
Besides, he's gone.
It's useless.
Hope one day everyone in Tang don't need to
suffer from war, coldness, hunger, homelessness, or misery.
Hope everyone have food to eat, field to farm
with no theft or danger.
I think it's the halcyon days.
It will.
We'll have that day.
Xiao Wu.
I'll eat this bowl of rice for you.
You won't be hungry anymore with so much rice.
I'm not a disloyal man.
I didn't recognize you.
I apologize to you for my sister.
With me, you can't be starving, can you?
[Dear Brother Xiao Wu]
[Luoyang Office]
Finally you're here, Princess.
I'm so worried about you.
Thank God.
Please take a bath and put on clean clothes.
I'll help you.
Why are you crying?
I'm okay now.
I'm so glad to see you, Princess.
Take a rest first.
I can do it myself.
But...
I'm okay with that.
Okay.
Call me anytime if you need me.
Princess rests here tonight.
Keep your eyes open.
Yes, sir.
Go.
Stop.
Who's the commander?
What brings you here so late at night?
A royal warrant.
I dare not to waste time.
Please receive it, commander.
[I've seen your report. I ordered the crown prince to Luoyang to inspect around counties for the damage for me.]
Thanks a lot.
Please report for me.
Princess Yongan has been found in Luoyang.
She's fine.
Please rest assured.
Yes.
Forgive me, please.
I forgot you're...
I'll send some guards for you tomorrow.
To protect you.
I came here for...
I'll come tomorrow.
Wait.
It's late now.
You must come here for an emergency.
Yes.
I just received a handwritten letter from his Majesty from Chang'an.
Please have a look.
His Highness has left Chang'an to inspect the damage
to show grace on behalf of His Majesty.
He'd arrive in a few days.
Thank you for delivering the letter, Mr. Hao.
I'll read it latter.
In that case,
I won't hurry to go back.
The crown prince is young and naughty.
I have to look after him.
I can help you with that.
But... I've decided it.
You have to stay with me in Luoyang for a while, Mr. Hao.
Princess, you've changed a lot.
What happened is a mixed blessing.
I lost, I gained.
Now I know what Father often said to me.
People live hard. How can we stand by?
I'm his daughter.
How can I stay ignorant?
You've suffered a great deal, haven't you?
I met many difficulties,
and many people to express my gratitude as well.
Difficulties will be gone,
but the gratitude will be< cherished in heart forever.
In the past, I only saw people's appearance.
Now I know I need to see what's in their mind.
Someone seems kind but hides a malicious heart.
Someone has a cold face but a kind heart.
Just like you, Mr. Hao.
Why can't I master it?
Your Tao is different.
You can't do it.
Give up now.
Different Tao?
Where's the difference?
In your opinion, what's my reason to defend Shuozhou?
Fights or surrenders are just the means
to guarantee the citizens stay away from war and live a happy life.
These are the most important.
This is the Tao I stick to.
What's exactly my Tao is?
Senior Qin.
Did Yuan fall asleep?
Yes.
Okay.
We asked Luo Shiba to share messages with us.
But when we sent the message, she never wrote back.
Now she suddenly wanted to see us and would bring a friend to us.
A friend?
We have no progress so far.
Maybe this friend can bring some messages of Young Master.
Luo Shiba, here you are.
Your friend is...
Luo Shiba.
This is your friend?
Everyone listen, kill Ashile Sun to take revenge on the governor.
Wait.
About Gongsun Heng, I have a clear conscience.
Now Changge is missing.
I come here only to find her.
Find her?
It's you who took her to the grassland
where she encountered the misery, isn't it?
Luo Shiba.
You don't know what Ashile Tribe means to us, do you?
How can you bring him to Tang?
I only want to find her.
I'll find a way to find her even without your help.
You...
Ashile Sun.
Answer me.
Did you provoke to post up the notice
that Commandant Li sacrificed for the country?
It's me.
It's the best way to defend Commandant Li.
So what's your purpose to find her?
I have no purpose.
Only because... she's my friend.
Friend?
Commandant Li is your friend?
Senior Qin.
You're confused by him.
Do you believe he's a friend of Commandant Li's?
You should know how the whole city reviled Commandant Li.
It's Ashile Tribe's notice that subsided their rage.
Ashile Sun from Eagle Division is a master in archery.
Commandant Li was shot by him that day but survived.
I felt strange at that time.
Now I know why.
You're old friends.
So you put Commandant Li first.
How about the revenge for governor and his wife?
The war always cause many casualties.
Ashile Sun granted governor's wish to save those citizens.
It's his mercy.
Xu Feng.
It's not the moment for rash actions.
Now our goal is to find Young Master.
She has a special status. We can only search her stealthily.
More hands, more power.
Get prepared, Xu Feng.
Let's go to the city together.
Please.
Thanks a lot.
There's no need for that.
This way, please.
Where's the magistrate of Luoyang?
Why hasn't he welcomed me by now?
He ignored me.
Stop.
Mr. Wei, the refugees are disturbing the order outside the office.
They have enclosed the office.
The people inside can't get out, and we can't get in.
Let's change the route.
Don't catch their eyes.
Yes.
Wait.
Your Highness.
Father asked me to inspect Luoyang.
He wanted me to observe what people suffer.
Now I go to observe it and get in charge.
Mr. Wei.
Go with me to the office.
I'll let people know their crown prince is the best one.
Your Highness.
Food!
Out! Get out now!
We want food!
Give us food!
Out now! Give us food!
Get out!
Food!
We want food!
Get out!
Food! Get out!
Give us food!
Food!
Get out!
We want food!
Food!
Everyone listen to me!
Get out!
I'm the crown prince of this country.
Food!
Give us food!
We want food!
Stop shouting!
I'm the crown prince!
We want food! Food!
We want food!
Prince.
Are you really the crown prince?
You want us to die of hunger.
Everyone!
Come here!
Crown Prince is here!
Everyone!
Come here! It's the crown prince!
Protect his Highness!
Crown Prince is here.
Come here. It's the crown prince.
Prince is here.
Give me food.
Wei Shuyu.
Stop them!
Don't let them get close to me.
Back off!
Don't hurt anyone.
They're all ordinary people without any weapon.
We want food!
We want food! Food!
Prince.
Give some food to us.
Blood.
It's bleeding.
They're killing us.
He hit us.
I'm scared.
Protect prince and retreat.
Prince can't be hurt. Retreat.
The guards beat us.
Back off.
He beat me.
They're killing us.
Crown Prince killed a man.
Back off.
What happened?
Princess, some refugees are creating a disturbance.
No need to worry, Princess.
Will my brother arrive today?
It should be today.
Open the door.
Princess.
It's a mess out there, so please don't go out.
I know them well.
They come from Yunzhou.
I was one of them.
They're just too hungry.
Besides, my brother is coming.
It's okay if they know His Majesty sent prince here to console them.
But it's dangerous...
Besides, you're with me, aren't you?
Princess, Mr. Hao.
Prince has arrived. His Highness is outside the door.
Open the door.
But...
- If...
- If the prince gets hurt, nobody can take the responsibility.
I'll take care of her Highness.
Open it.
Yes.
It's killing.
Police are killing.
People are dying.
Mr. Wei, what should we do?
His Highness left us behind.
We'll die of hunger in Luoyang.
Nobody cares about us.
He's right.
Nobody cares.
Please calm down and listen to me.
His Highness will never leave you behind.
Is it true?
Really?
You're talking nonsense.
His Highness does not care about us.
He's right.
He doesn't care.
We want food!
He doesn't care!
Give food to us.
[Luoyang Office]
The noble who can save you is coming.
Tell us what you want.
Why do you make a disturbance outside the office?
Who are you?
His Highness doesn't care about us.
How can you keep your word?
Yes. He's right.
His Highness doesn't care about us.
What can you do?
Am I right?
Yes. Yes.
Please listen to me.
What can you do?
I'm Princess Yongan of Tang.
You have my words.
This country will never leave you alone.
Please don't worry.
Food, water, clothes and beds, you'll have them all.
We have to face the difficulties of Luoyang together.
Really?
We won't die of hunger.
Yes.
What are you doing?
Your wound will fester if the bleeding doesn't stop.
Don't move.
I don't need it!
Hao Du.
You pretend to be injured and agitate these people.
What's your purpose?
Answer me.
Very good.
You don't answer me.
Never answer me.
Hao Du.
He did that because of starvation and fear.
Don't hurt him.
Do you see that?
Her Highness sympathizes with this kind of people.
How can her Highness leave you alone?
Yes. He's right. Yes.
Brother Shuyu.
Leyan, it's you.
Thank God you're here.
I've been looking for you for such a long time.
I almost missed no relevant inch in the north land.
I'm afraid of losing you.
Sorry, it's all my fault.
I lost you and made you suffer a lot.
Brother Shuyu, it's not your fault.
No one predicts good or bad fortune.
See? I'm fine.
You're losing weight.
I dare not pile on pounds without finding you.
Leyan, tell me what happened from Youzhou to Luoyang.
Many things happened during the journey.
If I haven't experienced it,
I'd never know so much of the world,
and only be a canary in the cage.
Please rest assured.
I won't let you suffer anymore in the future.
What's wrong?
Princess.
Please go to see the prince.
Your Highness.
His Highness asked me to tell your Highness
his Highness is scared and has a fever suddenly.
I'm afraid his Highness can't meet refugees
in South Hill with your Highness.
He's ill?
Yes.
Your Highness.
His Highness was afraid of passing it to your Highness.
Her Highness visits younger brother.
How dare you arrogate to stop?
If his Highness's condition is delayed,
you won't survive even with ten lives.
Don't pretend in front of me.
Sister.
Father sent you to Luoyang
to console the people who suffered from the drought,
and build your image as a crown prince.
You're pretending to be ill.
How could you do that?
Sister, you've seen that.
These people are not some poor men but some gangsters.
Look at them.
With blood all over their faces, they're making threatening gestures.
They've scared me to death.
Just thinking of them, my head is aching.
I'm not going anywhere.
Brother.
I know that as a child, when you're facing such situations,
you'll be scared.
But you need to know that sooner or later,
we have to take on the responsibilities on our own,
especially for you.
I know, sister.
I really understand.
But I just arrived here.
Can you just give me a break?
I know what you're talking about.
Please be assured.
I'll grow up and be a man.
I'm the son of our father.
I heard you.
You need to do what you say.
I've experienced a lot in the past few months.
I've some new understandings.
Since we're taking from people in our land, in return,
we should give them a stable life.
Brother, do you know what is a crown prince?
It means you're the future of the country.
And you'll be the leader of our people.
Be a man, brother,
like our father.
Win the trust from our people.
And be a wise emperor.
Hao Du.
You found Leyan first.
Thank you.
Have you accompanied her all the time?
What do you mean?
Nothing.
I just felt regretful.
If I hadn't been recalled by his Majesty,
I might have been the one who found Leyan.
Does that matter?
It matters between you and me.
Is this because of Li Changge?
Protect the crown prince.
Don't lose his Highness again.
Hao Du.
Leyan wouldn't been left alone in the stage
if you didn't insist hunting Li Changge.
Are you finding yourself some excuses?
I can take the responsibility.
I just want you to know those who are obsessed with something
will easily get lost.
A'Bi.
Mr. Situ.
What's wrong?
What has Changge done to you?
Not really.
Ever since she came into the house,
she hasn't slept or eaten anything.
I've checked her for several times, but she kept staring
at the writing on the wall.
She hasn't moved at all.
Is there something wrong with her?
Look at her.
She is just so stubborn.
I've told her she couldn't make it, she just didn't listen.
I'll check her out.
Good to see you, Mr. Situ.
Master.
Can I talk to her?
[Non-interference]
The night you came,
I was just passing by.
I saw you practicing swordsmanship in the middle of the night.
You've stayed in the silence room ever since you came to our temple.
Do you have any thoughts?
I've been taught by my teacher since childhood.
I've read books from all classes of authors.
I've never liked the thought of non-interference of Taoism.
To struggle with people, you can find your refuge.
To struggle with people, you can achieve your pursuit.
For all these years,
I've held a strong belief in it.
But in these few days,
I started to realize that
I was wrong.
If I hadn't struggled,
someone like my real brother wouldn't have died for me.
someone who has treated me like his daughter
wouldn't have been died for me.
If I hadn't struggled,
someone who has given all he got to me wouldn't have been in danger,
while his dear family
wouldn't have died for me as well.
One senior saved my life,
and taught me to find my own Tao.
Non-interference.
This is the way.
God bless us all.
If you really think in this way, you've spent some good time
in this silence room.
What about now?
Dead people are gone forever.
I've wasted so much time on this.
It's really precious for us to be enlightened.
There are lots of refugees in Luoyang.
We're busy in helping those in need.
If you have time,
you can help me and Taoist Sun.
Everything in Taoism is about people.
We should appreciate the world we live in.
Dwelling in the past
will only bring you more troubles.
[Non-interference]
From the way she talks, master must know that
she is not an ordinary person.
Do you want to hear more about her story?
What are you talking about?
Things come and go.
People come and go too.
I've never asked.
But I do miss the old times.
When I was in her age,
I also regarded myself as the smartest person in the world.
It seems that you and she have some connections.
Tell me about it.
In this world, we all come and go.
We share the same fate.
Will you come to South Hill with me tomorrow?
I heard that there are more refugees than we have here.
Sure.
If we can encounter some rare diseases, that'll be worth trying.
Have some tea.
I'm so glad to see you eat something.
I've been worried about you.
I heard that Taoist Sun has tried so hard to save you.
Would you like to get changed now?
Isn't it beautiful?
Liuyun Taoist Temple is the most beautiful place in Luoyang.
The one you just talked to is our master, Taoist Jingdan.
She has sheltered many refugees suffering from the drought.
She is such a nice person.
She wants to know your plan for the future.
Taoist Sun is going to stay in Luoyang for some days.
Are you going back to your hometown or staying here?
My hometown is somewhere I can never go back.
I'll stay.
That'll be great.
I've got a mate.
Except for us, Tian Jing and Liu'er also live here.
We're about the same age.
We can be good friends.
I'm A'Bi from Family Wang.
What's your name?
Since Changge is no longer in Tang,
I'd avoid some troubles.
I've no family name.
Call me A'Li.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad