THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
My Queen, thank you.
- Congratulations, Your Highness!
I am becoming a father!
I'm...
pregnant?
Everyone, stop!
- Goodness.
- Get out.
- Your Highness.
- Goodness.
Why is the Queen so upset?
She is not upset.
She is just expressing her happiness.
Yes.
Is this what you call pregnancy syndrome?
This is more than just an identity crisis.
My identity will cease to exist,
and my soul will be destroyed.
Is this how my life ends?
I told you that I was
against getting married.
Even if I had accidentally gotten married,
I was never planning to have children.
It's hard for me to survive by
myself in this warlike life,
so how could I become pregnant?
It's as reckless as taking
off your bulletproof vest...
as you dance the samba while
bullets are heading towards you.
That's not all.
Pregnancy and childbirth are so hard
that they can reduce one's lifespan.
You're literally giving up your
life to give it to your child.
Why do I have to give
up my life expectancy...
to a child I don't even know?
Darned Mother Nature. Give someone else...
the provision of nature!
I can't believe I'm pregnant!
EPISODE 17, PREGNANCY IS BEAUTIFUL
You must wait. Your Highness.
EPISODE 17
You fabricated the dead body.
Did you think I would
fail to recognize O Wol?
I did it so that you can open your eyes...
to your true self that you were unaware of.
The Queen has turned her
back on the Andong Kim clan.
In return, the Andong Kim
clan has joined hands with us.
It is your best chance to become the Queen.
Do not try to control me ever again.
How long can a bird that has
been tamed by a human live...
if it chose to leave the birdcage?
There is an announcement that
the King wants the world to know.
What is it?
The Queen...
is pregnant.
That is the sound of the drum
to announce a joyful occasion.
Now that my storeroom is empty,
there is no way for me
to fill my empty heart.
No delicacy can fill my stomach...
No, my heart. What can I fill it with?
I have even turned my back on my family.
I am a loner.
My lord!
- My lord!
- What is it?
An urgent message has
arrived from the Palace.
Did something happen to the Queen again?
The Queen is pregnant!
What is the reason?
Your Majesty. Rather than
searching for the reason,
perhaps you should find a
way to make her feel better?
That is a good idea. How can I do that?
How can I make a woman feel happy?
I should not have asked you.
Who should I ask regarding this?
That is why...
I have invited an expert to help you
resolve your worries, Jong Cheol.
All he has done these days
was eat and think about that.
What are you doing?
She will probably get mad at you like this.
That is when you tell her this.
"I watered my flower."
I do not think I could live if I do that.
I guess she has a temper.
If that is the case,
there is a sure method.
What is that?
You make a silly face like this.
I hate myself for thinking
the same thing as him.
I apologize.
It has definitely been helpful.
No way.
I realized how foolish it is to look
for an answer from someone else.
When I am the only person
who knows about her well.
Why are you crying? I'm
the one who wants to cry.
It is because I am so happy.
You can cry as much as you want today.
Fine. You can cry.
You can cry in my stead.
For the sake of my life,
which I had no choice in.
Your Highness.
You should stop shedding tears of happiness.
Then what should I be doing?
You must personally announce your
pregnancy to the Internal Court...
and receive congratulations.
I don't want to. I cut ties with my in-laws.
Whether you cut ties with
them or you sewed it back up,
if you do not follow procedure,
you will be called to account.
I hate my pregnancy even more.
The Grand Queen Dowager is here.
The Queen Dowager is also here.
They have beaten you to it.
What should we do about this?
Welcome.
I should have gone to you
to announce the news myself,
but as you can see, I cannot get up.
What are my symptoms?
She has severe dizziness
due to morning sickness...
and pregnancy pains.
Yes, that is it.
That is why I came personally.
Please...
have a seat.
It is okay.
Your body must feel heavy.
Please sit comfortably.
Okay, then.
Upon hearing the news, I was so elated.
I even got you a talisman even
though I stopped getting them.
I just wanted to make sure...
that you bring a healthy
child into this world.
It kind of looks like a curse.
I am an atheist. I do
not believe in talismans.
You will realize it when you
give birth to your child.
You will want to believe
something that you never did.
You will become desperate...
and want to make a wish on
the stone people kick around.
You may not fear anything in this world.
But now, you will fear
everything in this world.
Losing a child reflects poorly on the mother.
I talked to the royal physician
and asked him to make medicine...
that will prevent you from a miscarriage.
Make sure to take the
medicine every single day.
If something happens to the child,
you will be held responsible.
From now on, do not behave rashly.
You must be careful for
the sake of your child.
Both of them came to threaten me.
I really feel like throwing up.
Thank you for your wisdom.
This is Prince Yeongpyeong.
Please come in.
You came because you were worried.
I am okay,
but I will not be able to bring myself...
to congratulate His Majesty and the Queen.
I should focus on my path.
I came to the palace to
be of help to His Majesty.
I thought the only way...
I could help him was by
giving him emotional comfort.
But when I saw the Queen, I
realized that I was wrong.
It is your best chance to become the Queen.
Queen Dowager.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
What brings you here,
Royal Noble Consort Eui?
You have joined hands
with the Andong Kim clan.
- It is the clan's wish.
- Do not sell our clan's name...
for your petty fight.
Do you wish to keep your position
as Right State Councilor?
I hope you will make the right decision.
If not, I will gather the
members of our clan...
who truly care about...
the future of Joseon with my father.
My father sent all of them?
Yes.
These are presents for the
child you are carrying.
There is more.
There are more presents in the hall.
That puzzles me even more.
As it is dark, I will light the candles.
I don't care about those candles.
Starting now, my life...
will be pitch dark.
TO LEFT STATE COUNCILOR KIM SEOK GEUN
Once again, they had gone
after the civil servant.
They did not behead the leader.
They could not go after the leader...
because they feared that
it may be seen as treason.
Gosh, the guts of these farmers.
We do not have an excuse to
utilize our men on a large scale.
This is giving me a headache.
By the way, was the cipher
of Donghak believers...
found in the palace?
KIM SO YONG
Seeing how Donghak believers were
able to penetrate the palace,
this is a major problem. We must hurry.
What if we end up with...
a lot of believes because we
did not do anything about them?
You can just focus on your assignments.
Your Highness, starting today...
"TAEGYOSINGI"
you will begin your parental education.
You cannot lie on your side.
You cannot lean on your arm.
You cannot lift your neck while lying down.
Darn it.
You cannot laugh, be startled, get scared,
weep, cry,
or talk excessively.
You must stay away from such unusual tastes.
It's like my body doesn't even belong to me!
Well, that is true.
But I was just getting used to this.
How come everything went back to
square one with this pregnancy?
Especially you, Court Lady Choi.
I thought you decided to stop nagging me.
This is all for your baby.
I must survive first for the baby to survive.
Am I a machine that pops out babies?
Am I a living incubator?
Besides, I shouldn't be the
only one going through this.
What about the dad?
Go and tell Cheoljong to
have his prenatal education!
Actually, the 3rd line of the 1st
chapter in "Taegyosingi" states...
that the father is responsible
to undergo prenatal education.
Once His Majesty finishes
tending his business today,
you and he will both learn...
My day started with the pregnancy.
And it will end with that?
My life is already gone.
No, Your Highness.
- No, Your Highness. Take it.
- Darn it.
Hong Yeon.
After that incident,
the Queen and Kim Byeong In
no longer see each other.
After getting rejected, he must
have heard about her pregnancy.
I bet he has no one to rely on.
Poor thing.
I hope you are eating your meals.
I will see you later.
You should sleep at home.
You seem haggard.
Stress is the cause of every illness.
This will be very bad for the baby too.
Keep a lookout.
Just one spoonful.
My pear blossom wine.
Royal Chef!
Where's my pear blossom wine?
It was spoiled, so I threw it out.
You seem like you're in a good mood.
I am the same as any other day.
You said you stopped smiling a long time ago.
I found my smile back.
I lost my pear blossom wine.
But you found your smile back.
What a coincidence.
Be honest with me, Court Lady Choi.
You're enjoying this, aren't you?
You're taking revenge for your
struggle as you're given a chance!
You do not want to shake me, Your Highness.
Throw it up. Spit out my pear blossom wine!
Please calm down, Your Highness!
You should rather talk it out, Your Highness!
Talk it out, my foot.
My pear blossom wine.
They drank all of my pear blossom wine.
- My pear blossom wine.
- Your Highness!
Give me my pear blossom wine!
- Your Highness.
- My pear blossom wine.
Why are you crying, Your Highness?
I have been waiting for you.
You look cool like a prince on a white horse.
I can't do this and that, but you
can ride a horse and have fun.
You are very upset today as always.
I am glad.
Let us ride together.
You cannot do that, Your Majesty.
Her Highness is pregnant with a royal baby.
You cannot ride with her, Your Majesty.
Your Highness!
Your Highness! It is dangerous!
- Your Highness!
- You cannot do that!
Oh, no!
Where are we?
I always wanted to give you...
something you like and want the most.
The one you cannot find
in the palace but outside.
- A nightlife?
- I meant freedom.
Do you not like it?
You should've just said it's
a walk. Why so grandiose?
We came to a royal villa
to get some fresh air.
Let us go back if you do not like it.
A royal villa is like a summer house, right?
It's nice. It feels like a
rich man is flirting with me.
Now that we're here, I might
look around before we go.
I knew you would like it, My Queen.
This way, please.
It's nice to be a king.
Having a luxurious villa and a garden.
I thought about it all
night. Why you are so mad.
Being pregnant is usually a
blessing to women in the palace.
But why does it make the Queen so upset?
So? Do you know why?
No. No matter how much I
think about it, I do not know.
I do not understand it,
so I decided to accept it.
That a blessing to others
might not be a blessing to you.
That it is just who you are.
I guess Queen Dictionary
was indeed quite useful.
Why are you doing this?
You're making it awkward.
My Queen.
Is it "roar"?
Roar!
As I am writing Queen Dictionary,
there is something I want to know.
What does "all in" mean?
Have I said something like that?
That is the word you shouted at
the gambling place at the market.
All in...
is a very foolish behavior...
to put all your fragile eggs in one basket.
- Eggs?
- I did that foolish thing.
I can't believe at a time when I should run,
I stumbled over a stone
called pregnancy and fell.
Do not worry, My Queen.
I will make sure to cut off
the rotten parts of Joseon.
For our baby...
who will inherit the country.
Fine.
If this child becomes the king
and inherits this country...
I can wield absolute power?
SUNWON'S WORLD
SO YONG'S WORLD
Why didn't I think of it so far?
- What do you mean?
- My baby!
Look!
Everything under the sky...
is all yours.
Let's go back.
I will start a proper prenatal education.
"A proper prenatal education"?
I should teach him how to win a fierce fight.
This baby will have to keep
living in this warlike palace.
Let's go. Start the engine.
We just came.
Even if I write 100 volumes
of Queen Dictionary,
will I ever see a day when
I can understand the Queen?
- Please wait for me.
- Hurry up!
JOURNAL FOR PRENATAL EDUCATION
My baby.
To survive in a palace,
you cannot be lazy about making your people.
Your Majesty!
They are indeed the best warriors in Joseon.
My baby.
You should have your enemies close to you.
1,000 soldiers, you said.
Are you going to build up military power...
and invade Seonjeongjeon Hall or something?
Are you scared?
I guess it is you who are scared...
who prepared 1,000 soldiers for me.
Halve the number of soldiers.
Send the rest to Royal Guard Division.
My baby, you must have a treasury
with your money in secrecy.
These are the newly minted coins.
- How much did you issue?
- A million.
This is the King's political funds?
You can buy power with money.
Lastly, my baby, this is
the most important part.
Get rid of everyone who is not on your side.
Life is a real game. The world is a jungle.
You'll get eaten if you don't
eat others. A slaughter party!
Of course, you will try your
best to establish peace.
But if there's no hope,
you must win no matter
what it takes, my baby.
I am so glad...
that Her Highness pulled herself together.
He is still in your belly. Do you
already have so many things to say?
He will listen only when he's in my belly.
He won't listen at all after he's born.
It is time to go to bed, Your Highness.
I have no time to sleep. I
have so many things to do.
Life is like a treadmill.
Once you stop running even
for a moment, you'll fall off.
Even pregnancy can't stop me.
I guess it can.
I'm a motorboat at heart,
but my body is a pedalo.
It has been a while.
This must have been tough on you.
It is okay.
You completed the book on tactics.
These men have never lifted
weapons in their lives.
So it will be difficult to
turn them into soldiers.
But this will help.
Be careful.
I was not aware that the increase...
in the number of believers was that high.
In other words, a lot of
people must be struggling...
due to oppression.
Lately, they are attracting
a variety of classes...
from ruined noblemen and herb diggers.
Perhaps, like My Queen said,
is the abolition of the social
strata the only solution?
We must be wary of...
a radical idea too.
Of course, it is too far in the future.
I may not be able to do so, but perhaps,
my child will be able to.
Your Highness, His Majesty...
Do not wake her.
She is like a baby.
JOURNAL FOR PRENATAL EDUCATION
YOU SHOULD HAVE YOUR ENEMIES CLOSE TO YOU.
BABY, YOU MUST HAVE A TREASURY
WITH YOUR MONEY IN SECRECY.
LIFE IS A REAL GAME. THE WORLD IS A JUNGLE.
YOU'LL GET EATEN IF YOU DON'T
EAT OTHERS. A SLAUGHTER PARTY!
"Party"?
Par...
I cannot figure out what "ty" means.
"Party".
As the Queen is safe, you were not harmed.
I knew it. The talisman I
got was definitely effective.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Then, I believe...
you did your due diligence to
spread the story I told you.
That cannot be.
You guys are so diligent this morning.
Did you even wash up before
you started to gossip?
You should listen to this. I bet
it will chase away your sleep.
You know the Queen...
That is what I heard.
What? His Majesty and the Queen
faked spending the night together?
His Majesty and the Queen faked
spending the night together.
I heard that they actually do not make love.
I heard they only spend
the night in the same room.
What? Then whose baby is she carrying?
Whose baby is she carrying,
if not the King's?
- No way.
- I heard it was all fake.
You must have heard the rumor
circulating in the palace.
Rumors are always one step
slower than the truth.
That was ancient history.
Rumors should not be taken
lightly at the palace.
They may use that as an excuse to depose you.
All they ever try to do is get me deposed.
They're playing dirty and being petty.
I won't let them kick me out.
- Yes.
- Hong Yeon.
What are you doing with your hairpin?
What is up with this provocative pose?
We must quash the rumor.
- My goodness.
- Goodness.
- I am blushing. I cannot watch it.
- Gosh.
In that case...
This won't be enough to quash that rumor.
We must give them a good show.
This is a bit too much.
But you are not as good as me.
Not enough.
Come on. Get into it.
If I get into it more than
this, we might need a tent.
Is that what you want?
I never said that.
We just need to put on a show for them.
Then, for the same purpose,
I will visit you in Daejojeon Hall.
I have no choice as I might get deposed.
Then,
see you later.
- Did they leave?
- They are so slow.
They are still watching us.
Then, you leave me no choice.
Your Highness, Royal
Noble Consort Eui is here.
Is it your doing?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, the rumor.
It is all thanks to you.
I was reminded of what you
told me a long time ago.
You told me that their spending
the night together was all a show.
Thanks to that, the Queen's
pregnancy will not be celebrated.
Your words...
became an arrow and hit the Queen.
Please stop this.
It is out of my hand now.
Once people begin to spread rumors,
they become irrevocable from
the very nature of things.
And now, it is too late for
you to wash your hands of it.
As long as you are here,
you will not be free.
Your existence itself will be used
to help the standing of our clan.
I advise you to take the lead
rather than being exploited.
It scares me.
It is understandable.
However, you are not alone. So do not worry.
That I was turning into someone like you.
That is what scares me.
Do you know why the clan
is following your lead?
Because you are an innocent
victim whose heart broke...
from losing her child.
However, what if you were
a coldhearted mother...
who caused her son to die,
so she could save herself?
And on top of that, what if
you were a foolish woman...
who got deceived by shamanistic beliefs...
and relies on the shaman
regarding our clan's future?
Will they still see you
as the leader of our clan?
I will write down everything
I have heard and seen here,
so everyone in Joseon will
know exactly who you are.
Words do not have such power.
You will find out how strong they can be.
You once told me that you do
not wish to regret it again.
You do not deserve to regret...
failing to stop the late king's death.
You must regret trampling on his dream.
You should regret ruining your son's dream...
as his mother.
The late king was probably
desperate to escape...
from your shadow.
What...
You know nothing.
How dare you run your mouth?
It is the truth everyone knows.
And I am sure you know that too.
I will not let you trample on
His Majesty's dream as well.
That wench...
I am going to Daejojeon Hall.
Yes, Your Highness.
They say that rumors and
dreams are the opposite.
Rumors?
I did not tell anyone...
about sleeping with the King
as it is a personal matter,
but if you find out, you will be surprised.
At night...
Like this.
It is a hot personal matter,
so I cannot speak of it.
It is so frustrating.
The King is different from what he seems.
He is the king of stamina
that will go down in history.
Did it get recorded in history
like that because of me?
Who could have spread such a false rumor?
The only person to do such a thing
is the Royal Noble Consort Eui.
It's okay.
What? What do you want to
fight with me about now?
Are you confident?
Are you confident that...
you can fight against them
with the King and win?
This is my fight too.
I have a reason to win too.
Then you should practice shooting arrows.
With your current skills,
you will only be a burden.
Then can you teach me?
I...
do not have time to do so.
Your Majesty, the Royal
Noble Consort Eui is here.
Tell her to come in.
I have a request for you.
Tell me.
You must fulfill it.
What kind of request is it?
Please let me leave the Palace.
What do you mean by that?
I cannot find myself inside this Palace.
Please remove me from the Palace...
so that I can live as myself.
I cannot allow that.
You know what it means to live as
a disposed royal noble consort.
I do not care about what others say of me.
No, I will no longer be
bound by those things.
This is my final request, so please allow it.
I do not give you royal permission.
I cannot grant you royal permission.
You and I cherish one another,
but we do not love each other anymore.
I am just...
trapped in the royal villa...
under the name of a royal noble consort.
Your Majesty. All of the
ministers have gathered.
The reason I have called
all the ministers here...
is that I have an important
announcement to make.
As of this moment,
Jo Hwa Jin, Senior First
Rank Royal Noble Consort Eui,
will be disposed from her position
as Royal Noble Consort Eui.
We must stop this.
The Royal Nobel Consort
Eui is no longer one of us.
Your Majesty, please stay healthy.
I will pray for your future.
Your Highness.
Please do not call me that anymore.
This is wrong.
His Majesty must not do this to you.
I asked him to do this.
- Why?
- It is what is best for everyone.
As long as I am in the Palace, I
will get in the way of the King...
regardless of whether I want to or not.
I will make sure that does not happen.
There is still time to take it back.
I will go tell the King...
I cannot trust myself any longer.
If I stay here much longer,
I may lose myself completely.
I pretended not to know...
how you felt about me.
- Your Highness.
- I used your feelings for me.
As much as I longed for the King,
I filled the emptiness I felt when
the King did not long for me...
through you.
I...
I willingly allowed you to use me.
The only thing I could give you...
was that.
Thank you.
And...
I'm sorry.
You should also stop...
hurting yourself by loving the wrong person.
That's what she meant by that.
She is a cool woman.
Is Cheoljong okay?
I'm sure he's not.
Do a round with me.
I am not in the mood to do so.
When we were young,
there was a game that we
played often in Ganghwa Island.
The game where the one who steps
on the other's shadow first wins.
If you do not want to do it,
you can just lose.
Do you remember?
When we were young, I always won.
I remember always winning later on.
I should have been stricter in
determining our hierarchy early on.
It is not that you did not determine
our hierarchy, you could not do it.
Royal Noble Consort Eui worried
about you until the end.
You who do not even know how valuable it is.
It is not that I do not know.
That is why I am distressed.
You should be more distressed.
That is...
the best you can do for Her Highness.
How much more do I have to
be lonely and distressed?
How much more?
My Jong, is he drinking somewhere?
I would've been drinking with
him if I weren't pregnant.
Is being pregnant not bearing
a baby but becoming one?
Why do I keep feeling sleepy?
I will go to Tongmyeongjeon Hall.
You must be careful, Your Highness.
As the rumor is dangerous,
if they find out that the
origin is Your Highness...
Before Grand Queen Dowager hears about it,
I should tell her myself.
- But...
- Do not worry, Court Lady Ahn.
They will never imagine...
I will share the rumor I started myself.
You came without my invitation.
I guess you have a favor to ask.
Hearing such a shocking rumor,
I was worried you might have been surprised.
That is why I came immediately.
A rumor?
Why do you always chase such endeavors?
If you hear what it is, you
would not say so that easily.
It does make me wonder.
What kind of rumor it is for you
to run to me with such excitement.
It is too good to miss.
The expression on your face
after hearing the rumor.
Rumors hardly make me wear
a facial expression...
you want to see.
The baby the Queen is pregnant
with is not a royal blood.
It is Kim Byeong In's child.
You cared for your family so much.
History will say The Andong Kim clan...
is the family who stained royal blood.
It is interesting.
It makes things very interesting.
Hey, did you hear the rumor?
I already heard. A baseless rumor.
His Majesty and Her Highness bedded...
bedded properly. Why are you
bringing it up so belatedly?
That is not what I was going to say.
They say the baby is not His Majesty's.
You will get in trouble for saying that.
The entire palace is laughing at our family.
Adultery between the Queen
and Minister of War...
who are close relatives?
I had high hopes for him.
My goodness.
After Royal Noble Consort Eui was deposed,
I thought it was over for me.
But hearing the rumor about
the Queen, I feel like I won.
The baby was not a royal
blood but a cuckoo's chick.
My family is more important than my own life.
That is why I live for my family.
What do you live for?
I also live for the same
thing as you, Your Highness.
Is that so?
If so, will you do anything
if it is for your family?
Yes, Your Highness.
Then bring the Queen's head to me at once.
It is the order of the family.
What is the reason?
The Queen destroyed the honor...
our family maintained for hundreds of years.
Your Highness.
I do not know what infuriated you,
but I ask for your mercy.
Everyone in the palace spread gossip...
that the King and the Queen
had not actually bedded.
Now they are saying the
baby in her belly is yours.
What?
That is not true.
What everyone believes becomes the truth.
If the dawn breaks and people
move around and spread the rumor,
the Queen will become a sinner...
who is pregnant from adultery...
and lied he is King's to stain royal blood.
The rumor started because of me.
I will receive the punishment.
A rumor can hurt a man.
But a rumor can kill a woman.
What we need to save the
honor of our family...
is the head of the Queen.
If you cut her throat by
yourself and bring the head,
I will not punish you.
I cannot do that, Your Highness.
Please punish me instead.
You said you live for the family,
but you live for the Queen!
Then I will have to ask
you to do something else.
- Is anyone there?
- Immediately,
I will make your regency begin again.
You made a contact with a dangerous thing.
In a book with the Queen's name,
I saw the cipher of Donghak
believers in your handwriting.
A dangerous idea stained
the King and the Queen.
And they are planning to reform the country.
What will happen if the
aristocrats sense the danger?
They will try to keep Joseon as it is now,
even if it takes the lives
of the people in the country.
A massacre against Donghak
believers will begin.
If so, why did you come to me,
not carry it out immediately?
Because it will hurt the Queen as well.
The Andong Kim clan...
is targeting Her Highness.
With the rumor the Queen became
pregnant from adultery with me,
they are trying to kill her for the honor.
They are doing it to attack me.
- I will stop them.
- You cannot stop them.
Even if her life is spared for now,
if her own family attacks her with the rumor,
she will have to be living
with a damaged reputation.
Not only Her Highness, but the
royal baby will also live like that.
Can you not see how the
officials who can do anything...
to threaten your position will dog her?
You are the only one who
can save Her Highness.
What is it?
The way I can save her.
Put down the uprising.
With your own hands,
punish Donghak believers.
Defamation against the woman
of the King who went to war...
to protect the country is not
right, which will quash the rumor.
If you prove you are not part of
Donghak believers by killing them,
the cipher in Dongmongseonseup
cannot threaten you.
This...
is the only way...
to save Her Highness and
your baby in her womb.
You have no time to hesitate.
When the dawn breaks, Her Highness
will be eaten up by the rumor.
I will never...
let her get hurt alone.
I'm not sleeping.
I'm thinking for a moment.
Why are you doing this, not
lying down for your comfort?
I came to comfort you.
But I fell deep in thoughts.
I'm so sleepy.
I will comfort you tomorrow.
You are my comfort.
As the uprising in Sam Nam
has put the country in danger,
I am leaving in a hurry.
While I am gone, please
take care of the politics.
And...
me and the Queen's baby as well.
I believe you will take good care of him.
I have had a comfortable life
without being involved in politics.
I have no other choice.
Do not worry about the
Queen while you are gone.
Taking care of a woman who is left alone...
as her husband went to a war
risking his life is my duty.
I will count you on that...
and leave.
Please take care of yourself.
The sun rose already.
Your Majesty.
I will do the rest.
Is it true that you will go to
quell the uprising yourself?
It is true.
What is going on, Your Majesty?
His Majesty who has been supporting
the people are going to kill them?
Kim Byeong In found out about
the cipher in Dongmongseonseup.
If I do not go now, millions
of people will get hurt.
I will follow you, Your Majesty.
Going by myself was the deal.
Is it not enough to have me as a hostage?
This is a trap.
Do you not think that it is the Queen...
who handed Dongmongseonseup to Kim Byeong In?
You promised me.
If there is clear evidence
that the Queen is our enemy,
you will cut her head off.
What you should cut off is not
the heads of the people but hers.
The Queen is clearly not our enemy.
The Queen turned against
everyone just to be on my side.
If I do not leave immediately,
the Queen will die.
Please calm down. It is not the time
for us to fight against each other.
You said I should be more distressed.
You are right.
I will bear everything.
Your life...
is in danger, Your Majesty.
If I try to live,
everyone will die.
I'm sure I've seen him.
Is it a dream?
Court Lady Choi. Hong Yeon.
Let's go to Daejojeon Hall.
I guess we missed each other.
- Yes, Your Highness.
His Majesty is leaving right now.
He's leaving? To where?
We will be off now.
Wait!
Stop! Hold on!
Why?
Is this the right path?
I do not think it is the
path made for people.
We are taking the shortcut, Your Majesty.
Halt.
You are late.
If you were going to do this anyway,
you could have done it quicker.
Will you get off the horse
yourself? Or do you need help?
I have no place to back off.
There is nothing I can do except do my best.
Do not worry, Your Majesty.
I can handle it by myself.
Everything will be fine if I get rid of you.
MR. QUEEN
THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
This little thing eats so much.
Say "Daddy, please come back soon."
I think it just kicked.
Your Highness, the King...
The owner of that seat is changing now.
What is the point of all of this...
when you're not here?
You have not committed any crimes, you said.
Standing on the side of
the weak is also a crime.
Byeong In. How far are you going to go?
More importantly, come into
this world in good health.
I will take the life of the Queen...
who joined you in taking the King's life.