♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 15=
He's got the whole package.
I...
Is this your Tool Soul?
Yes.
He's a Food Branch Soul Master.
This must be the prerequisite
to use his Soul Skill.
Ou Si Ke.
Got it.
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
Is that your First Soul Skill?
Eat it.
This thing
was created by his Martial Soul?
Eat it up.
How is it?
Not bad.
I'm not tired anymore.
My Soul Power has recovered.
It replenishes stamina
and Soul Power instantly.
Now you all know
why Ou Si Ke is a genius.
Food Branch Soul Masters are uncommon.
Those with such power
are even rarer.
Give me a sausage as well.
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
Must you
shout like that every time?
If I don't, the sausage would be useless.
Really?
Now you know
how awkward I felt in the arena.
Ou Si Ke.
Hurry up, one sausage for everyone.
One...
One for everyone?
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
(Full Recovery Big Sausage!)
What kind of Soul Beast is that?
What a terrifying shriek.
Are these
created by your Martial Soul?
If you don't have them,
you can't use your Soul Skill, right?
Yes.
It's really a package.
You don't know
how many times I've been teased.
What's wrong with that?
It's not even ugly.
I told you
when I first saw it.
Your Martial Soul is special.
As someone in the Support Branch,
I'm envious of you.
How can this be ugly?
Rong Rong.
You're the only one
who has seen my Martial Soul
and praised it.
How can that be?
Don't you think
his outfit is awesome?
What's wrong with your taste?
It's not about taste.
Ou Si Ke's Martial Soul
is indeed exceptional.
Would you like to join
Martial Soul Hall?
I don't want to be a Soul Master.
I just want to go on researching my craft.
Oh, right.
I've heard that Martial Soul Hall is great.
Do you have any stories about it?
Tell me.
I'll write a play for you.
Don't ignore me.
Be careful, everyone.
We may be on the outskirts of the woods,
but we need to keep our guard up.
Headmaster.
Would the Human Faced Demon Spiders appear here?
They are violent.
But
they usually stay
in the deeper parts of the woods.
They're not often seen here.
Good.
What?
Why did you mention
the Human Faced Demon Spiders?
One of them appeared in my village
in the past.
It came
from the Star Forest, right?
Officer Su Yun Tao followed it
and chased it away.
Then he helped my Martial Soul awaken.
You met a violent Soul Beast
even before your
Martial Soul was awakened?
You must be terrified.
Yes, it was terrifying.
Back then, I even hit its eye
with a nail.
You blinded a Human Faced Demon Spider's eye
even without your Martial Soul?
I often threw
flying darts
and nails.
I can prove
that he's really good at it.
Walk faster, everyone.
Be careful.
Why?
If the Human Faced Demon Spider
has returned to the Star Forest,
it would try to take revenge,
and it might attack us.
The Human Faced Demon Spider
has a keen sense of smell.
As long as it remembers a scent,
it can track it, no matter how far it is.
Wu knows a lot about Soul Beasts.
You're right.
The Human Faced Demon Spider may appear anytime.
Tang San.
I think
you should stay close to me.
I'll let Luo San Pao out.
Its nose is sensitive.
It might alert us in advance.
Yes.
San Pao.
What a cute Martial Soul Pig!
It's actually a dog.
Actually, when I first saw it,
I thought it was a pig too.
What's wrong with it?
When I was in Suo Tuo City,
I met Hu Lie Na and Su Yun Tao.
You told me about it before.
At the entrance of Rose Inn.
I saw people from Martial Soul Hall appear
in Shi Lan Ke.
I was surprised,
so I got Luo San Pao
to remember Su Yun Tao's scent.
You mean
Su Yun Tao is nearby?
He's probably right behind us.
Is he protecting Hu Lie Na?
I don't know.
I want to ask him,
but the students...
I can handle the students.
Don't worry.
But, why do you
want to see Su Yun Tao?
The Star Forest is dangerous.
If he wants to protect Hu Lie Na,
he can join us.
He might be able to help us.
Also,
I want to ask him
why Hu Lie Na
came to Shi Lan Ke.
Protect the students.
I'll be back soon.
Then, we'll slow down.
You're the strongest among us.
Keep this with you.
Okay.
Where is he going?
He has something to do.
Let's go.
He'll catch up with us soon.
Wait.
There's something ahead.
Something is approaching us quickly.
Could it be the Human Faced Demon Spider?
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent!
I wonder how old it is.
It's around six to eight meters long.
It's around 1,300
to 1,800 years old.
It's perfect for Ou Si Ke.
Stop it!
Are you okay?
The serpent's smoke is harmless.
It can only scare people off.
Good kick!
It's too fast. I can't catch it.
Qibao Boosts!
Second, Speed!
Got you!
Don't run!
Why didn't you do anything?
It's not for Brother Dai.
What do I have to do with this?
That's enough.
Forget it.
Ou Si Ke, come here!
Hurry, kill it!
But...
Absorb the Soul Ring at once.
How should I kill it?
I...
Here.
Start from its crest.
Hold it.
Don't be afraid. It won't run away.
Stop!
This serpent is mine!
Who's there?
Su Yun Tao!
Why do you come to the Star Forest?
You know me?
Who are you?
Why are you here?
I admire you, actually.
Unfortunately,
you shouldn't have met me here.
Soon,
your teacher
will go to hell like you.
Follow them.
I know he's scary.
That's why I need your sense of smell.
Let's follow them at a distance.
They won't notice us.
Why do you say that this serpent is yours?
I am looking for a Soul Beast
to advance to the Third Soul Ring.
This Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent
is perfect.
Hand it over!
You want this serpent?
Sure.
How much do you want to pay?
As long as the price is good,
you can even take me away,
let alone the serpent.
I was merciful
that I didn't attack you at once.
Sure, got it.
Do it.
Kill the serpent!
How dare you!
What are you staring at?
Absorb the Soul Ring!
No money, no talk.
Catching Soul Beasts depends on your luck.
Please look for another one.
You are bold.
This has nothing to do with boldness.
First come, first served.
That's common sense.
Common sense?
In the world,
there is only power!
You are Lander from Golden Iron Triangle?
You know me?
I feel so honored.
You're trying to impress me with power?
No.
I told you just now.
As long as the price is good,
we can discuss anything.
Though I'm no match for you,
since I'm here,
my dear husband
must be coming as well!
Sister.
The Soul Beast is dead.
There's nothing to fight over now.
Looks like your dear husband
is in trouble.
Does he need help?
Just give me a good price.
Headmaster, you know her?
Her name is Chao Tian Xiang,
also known as the Serpent.
She's a Soul Saint with Seven Soul Rings.
Her husband, Meng Shu,
is also called the Dragon,
a Great Soul Land Master with Eight Soul Rings.
He's extremely strong.
How shameless.
A Soul Saint and a Great Soul Land Master.
They're so powerful,
but they still want a Millennium Soul Beast.
It's not for them, of course.
It's probably for their disciples.
They used to be
a famous pair of Soul Masters.
Then, they aligned themselves
with the royal family of Tian Dou.
Could they be helping someone
from the royal family of Tian Dou?
We'd better not offend them.
Stay away from them as far as possible.
Headmaster.
I want to ask her something.
Our plan is messed up now.
The Dragon was in danger,
and the Serpent is
on her way to save him.
I don't know what kind of Soul Beast
is ahead.
But, danger is approaching.
Plan?
What plan?
Isn't everything going smoothly with us?
Ou Si Ke is already
absorbing the Soul Ring.
Yes, that's right.
Well...
When Ou Si Ke has advanced successfully,
we'll get out of here.
We need to plan ahead.
We're reaching the heart of the woods?
It's right ahead.
Don't get too close.
The time is coming.
Have you decided?
Who is he talking to?
I have nothing to do
with conflicts among humans.
The number of Soul Beasts in the Star Forest
has decreased sharply since 100 years ago.
If you do nothing about it,
what lies ahead of you
is extinction.
Help me defeat the enemy,
and I will give you a future.
I don't trust humans.
You don't have to trust me.
Just believe in the bigger picture.
Believe in benefits
and the results.
I shall wait for you
at the agreed time.
Yan Yan.
Are you okay?
We were just passing by.
We did not intend to disturb you.
Who are you talking to?
Why is it on the outskirts of the woods?
I don't know.
Something attracted it.
Titan Great Ape is not attacking.
It's probably just passing by.
If we work together,
can we defeat it?
Human strength can't rival
that of Titan Giant Ape.
Is it that strong?
We must
avoid treading along this path.
Once we find a venomous Soul Beast for Yan Yan,
we will leave the Star Forest immediately.
Ou Si Ke.
How is it?
Have you advanced successfully?
He has.
Nothing has changed.
Since you have advanced,
you are now a Soul Honour with Triple Soul Rings.
Check it now.
What's the Soul Skill
for the Third Soul Ring?
Rocketing Kiwi!
How did you know it's a kiwi?
I knew it
when I touched it.
Rocketing?
Let me try it.
It's sweet.
How is it? Do you feel like rocketing now?
She hasn't finished yet.
How is it?
Well...
Nothing happened.
I think you need to eat it up.
I did.
But...
You didn't eat its peel.
Try another one.
The peel, too?
I shall award you the honour
of being the first one
to fly.
I'm flying!
I can fly!
How do you control this?
How should I go down?
How should I go...
I'm getting dizzy.
How is it?
I'm fine.
I think I just need
to get used to it.
Listen.
I forgot to tell you
that you can only fly for 15 minutes.
It's rare to see a Soul Master
who can help people fly.
On the battlefield,
even 15 minutes are enough to turn the tables.
Ou Si Ke.
Join Martial Soul Hall,
and your talents will not go to waste.
I'm not interested.
We have the best resources
in Douluo Continent.
Didn't you hear him?
He's not interested.
Headmaster.
After eating the kiwi,
I can fly like you.
I'm proud of you.
Train harder.
But,
when my Martial Soul awakened,
I decided to give up fighting.
I have to take charge of my destiny!
What are you talking about?
Nonsense.
Cut the crap.
Get back to training
and become a Soul Master!
You've always taught us
that
what is said must be done,
and what is done will have results.
I want to be an artist!
If I can't convince you,
can't I beat you up?
Headmaster!
My training has not gone to waste.
You're already a Soul Honour.
Why do you still want to be an artist?
Every day,
all we do is fighting.
You're the one who
made me want to give up
my dream to be a Soul Master!
Talking back, are you?
What did you say?
You dreamed of being a Soul Master?
Good boy.
Excellent.
Here.
Let's test your Soul Power.
Come here.
You've just advanced to the Third Soul Ring.
You need time to accumulate power.
Everyone, test your Soul Power.
If any of you has accumulated enough power,
you can consider
advancing to the next Soul Ring.
Who wants to go first?
Me.
You just advanced to Double Soul Rings.
You have a long way to go...
He's got enough Soul Power.
He can advance to Triple Soul Rings now!
No. He still needs a little bit more.
It's impressive enough.
It's all bright!
Hey.
He was still slightly off the mark just now.
How did you do that?
I used Xuan Tian Strike.
You just advanced to Double Soul Rings,
and you've already gained enough power.
I say, Tang San.
Your rate of accumulating power
is simply matchless.
Wu has enough power too.
Wu has only one Soul Ring.
It's normal for her to advance.
This trip
should have been
a good chance for you
to capture Soul Beasts and advance.
But Master isn't here now.
I think
we should leave the woods now
to be safe.
When Master is back,
you can ask him
what kinds of Soul Beasts
are suitable for you to advance.
Headmaster, we can't leave.
I know you want to look for Du Gu Yan.
But it's too dangerous here.
Let's go back to Star Town first.
Master and I will check in
with our connections in Tian Dou City,
and we'll find Du Gu Yan.
Then, we'll follow the lead
and investigate Ye Zhi Qiu,
and force him to hand in the antidote.
If you insist on staying here,
you won't find her,
and you might die.
You might
even put all of us in danger.
That's enough.
Let's go back to Star Town
as soon as possible.
The last one will be penalized!
We're racing again?
What about Master?
He's probably behind us.
He'll catch up soon.
Let's go.
Okay, let's go.
I reckon one of us will lose.
Stupid.
I have the Rocketing Kiwi.
I won't lose.
Move on.
Kiwi?
Wu.
What are you looking?
Nothing.
Tang San, Wu, let's go.
Okay.
Let's go.
Rong Rong.
I'll show you my playscript.
You're annoying.
Listen.
It's an interesting play.
This time...
Is that a Soul Beast?
Really?
I think the sound
is far away.
Titan Giant Ape!
Did you hear that?
It's probably the Titan Giant Ape.
Lander is over there.
Shi Lan Ke School?
Probably.
We should save them, then.
Usually,
we'd try to help out.
But, that's Titan Giant Ape.
It's one of the strongest in the continent.
If we go, we'd die.
But those are human lives!
The first rule of survival
for Soul Masters
is to not risk your life
for someone you don't know.
Go.
Move.
King of the Forest.
We do not mean to transgress.
If this is your territory,
we will leave immediately.
I swear
we will never
enter the Star Forest again.
Since you're still upset,
I...
I can compensate.
Happy now?
Get out of here.
Go.
I'll help Headmaster.
Go!
Tang San!
How is it?
Everything should be fine now, Ou Si Ke.
Tang San.
Tang San?
He's awake.
Here.
Where's Wu?
She was taken away by Titan Giant Ape.
I'm not lying.
All of us were fighting just now.
Only you were hiding.
I didn't want to die.
Tang San.
It's my fault.
I didn't expect
Titan Giant Ape
would appear on the outskirts of the Star Forest.
No one could have expected it.
Take a rest, everyone.
Prepare to leave the forest.
What about Sister Wu?
Aren't we going to save her?
You saw how strong
Titan Giant Ape was.
If it goes all out,
we will all die for sure.
If we go to save her now,
we're going to be killed.
But, we can't leave Wu alone.
Headmaster.
I'll take you somewhere safe first.
Then, I'll come back to look for her.
Would she still be alive by then?
All of you are my students.
Now that someone is in trouble,
what I should do now
is to ensure that none of you
gets hurt.
I understand.
That's what we'll do, then.
You're giving up, too?
Headmaster is right.
Even if we go after it,
we can never defeat it.
Take a break,
and we'll go back.
Brother San.
By the way,
we fought Titan Giant Ape
over there,
right?
I left my Dragon's Beard there.
I need to pick it up.
Wu is in trouble,
and that's all you care?
You...
Ou Si Ke, you're not hurt, are you?
I'm not.
Please follow me.
Mu Bai.
Follow them.
I'll stay here and take care of the rest.
Since Titan Giant Ape was just here,
no other Soul Beasts
would come here for now.
Okay.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Found it!
Since we found it, let's go back.
Let me check somewhere else.
What...
Are you still
trying to look for your items?
Headmaster is waiting for us!
Brother Dai.
Wu was just taken away.
Tang San must be feeling awful.
Don't yell at him.
Let me help you.
Ou Si Ke.
Give me a Rocketing Kiwi.
Didn't you say that we'd die
if we go after the ape?
I know.
You're going to die.
That's why you shouldn't follow me.
Then...
I promised that I'd stay by her side.
Help me.
Rocketing Kiwi!
Tang San!
Headmaster.
What happened?
Tang San said...
Tang San told us
to leave the Star Forest
as soon as possible.
Once he finds Wu,
he'll come back to us.
If it weren't for Brother San,
I'd have died in the Nightfire Village.
Go ahead.
Brother Ou.
Give me a kiwi.
Are you crazy?
You won't make it in time.
I know it's dumb.
Never mind.
I am dumb.
No.
You can't defeat Titan Giant Ape.
What's the point of going?
When I was in the Nightfire Village,
Brother San didn't abandon me.
Now, I won't abandon him, either.
Give me one.
I can,
but we'll go together.
What?
You want to die too?
Headmaster.
You should go now.
It's safe ahead.
We're reaching the end of the forest soon.
We're safe now.
How about this?
Mu Bai.
Bring the girls back to Star Town.
I'll search for Tang San
and Wu with you.
Okay.
Headmaster, have you gone crazy too?
That's Titan Giant Ape.
You're going to die too.
Yes.
At least I can't
let a student die before me.
Go.
Headmaster.
It disappeared right in front of me.
I'm going too.
Me too.
Are you all crazy?
We're not forcing you to go.
Ou Si Ke.
Got it.
Rocketing Kiwi!
I don't have time.
If you won't let me go,
you can be my Third Soul Ring!
You made the right choice.
Recklessness only results in mistakes.
Leaving is the correct choice.
Besides, you're just
a Support Branch Soul Master.
You don't have
to fight in the frontlines.
What's wrong?
Ou Si Ke belongs
to the Support Branch too.
He's gone bonkers.
You don't have to follow him.
My dad told me
that Support Branch Soul Masters
aren't strong fighters,
so what we need to do
is to find a partner
whom we can entrust our life.
Only then can we
make full use
of our power.
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪