(Gwangju Station)
Hey! Can you go see what's in there?
My goodness.
What if we find
some prehistoric artifacts?
What the... What is this?
Gosh!
Captain!
(Unidentified Skeleton Found
at a Construction Site)
The police are investigating
an unidentified skeleton...
found at a construction site
in Gwangju this morning.
The police have sent the skeleton...
to the National Forensic Service...
for DNA analysis
in order to identify the victim.
The construction workers
at the site have stated...
that they found the skeleton
at about 1m below the ground...
while digging the ground
with an excavator at around 10 a.m.
They called the police right away,
and the police have sent
the skeleton to the NFS.
Those in the political circles
are saying...
the skeleton may belong...
to one of the victims
of the Gwangju Uprising...
and that the blood sample may need
to be compared with the families...
of those who disappeared
during the Gwangju Uprising.
Meanwhile, the NFS is expecting
it will take a while...
for the analysis results
to be available...
since it will be difficult
to determine the cause of death...
and identify the victim
as there are very few leads...
and because the skeleton
was buried for such a long time.
The train is arriving.
Please stand behind...
(Episode 1,
Everyone Running Their Own Race)
Resign!
- Government-funded professors!
- Resign!
End the emergency martial law!
- End the martial law!
Government-funded professors
must resign!
- Resign!
- Who's that?
- What's going on?
- Goodness.
- What's he doing?
- My gosh.
- Look at that.
- What's he doing here?
- What's his deal?
- What's he doing?
- Who is he?
- Oh, my.
- What's he doing?
- Who is he?
- Let him pass.
- My gosh.
- Just let him pass.
- Why is he staring at us?
- What's his deal?
- Who is he?
- Goodness.
- Look at that.
- Just let him pass.
- It's no big deal.
- Why is he staring at us?
- Did he just honk at us?
- What was that?
- He'll run us over with his car.
- Just let him pass.
- What's he doing?
- Come on.
(Release
the Wrongfully Imprisoned Students)
Good day.
What a jerk!
Hey, have you no shame?
You never showed up...
when we were campaigning
to save Kyung Soo.
How could you have the audacity
to set foot in here?
(Kim Kyung Soo)
Because we have to pay back
our debt together.
Let's say we stood joint surety.
Hold on.
I didn't know you cared so much
about Kyung Soo.
Were you two close?
Hey, get lost.
I don't want to talk to a jerk
like you.
But then again, what do you expect?
Med students aren't
real college students, you know?
You jerks say that
you're studying to save lives...
but don't care about the people
dying on the streets.
All you do is study.
What are med students then?
Are they in middle school?
Right, so just study
like you always do...
and play the guitar or something.
Selfish fence-sitters like you
shouldn't come here.
My gosh.
What are you doing here then?
You never protested
and got a job right away.
Oh, that reminds me.
Tell the newspaper company
you work for...
that you guys should make
Molotov cocktails.
These are very good.
You jerk!
- Let's get married.
- Get married?
With who? Me?
We broke up.
Right, I did say we should break up.
But that doesn't mean I let you go.
What does that mean?
I was just testing you.
I asked you out on our first date
and for all other dates.
You only hold my hand
when I tell you to.
I was wondering whether or not
you actually had feelings for me.
So? What's your conclusion?
Let's get married.
My family will take care
of everything.
You can just move in with me.
My dad will pay...
for our living expenses
until you open your own clinic,
- so after your internship...
- I won't do an internship.
What?
Why not?
Don't tell me
it's because of Kyung Soo.
Do you suddenly want to rebel
against society and the system?
- No, it's not that.
- Then what is it?
Just why?
You graduated top of your class.
- I haven't graduated yet.
- What?
Why not?
Because I want to participate
in the University Song Festival!
I won't be eligible once I graduate.
Then what about me?
You? What about you?
Do you want to be a singer too?
No. I want to get married.
I need a husband who's a doctor,
not a singer.
Yu Jin, then let's do this.
I'll pick out a few great catches...
among my med school friends.
- You crazy jerk!
- They'll marry you. For real!
(Green Meal)
The bill has been paid in full.
And...
I had some change left over,
so I bought this.
You didn't have to.
Just a moment please.
Yes, Jang Seok Chul.
Gosh, Yu Jin's got a stronger punch
than In Jae does.
Yes, okay.
I confirmed it.
You paid the bill,
so you should see the patient.
But the visiting hours are over.
You always come after hours.
Go see him quickly.
No. No...
(Intensive Care Unit)
She's turned a corner,
but we're not certain
when her condition will worsen.
I'm sorry to say this,
but I think you should start
preparing to say goodbye.
Seok Chul.
Are you awake?
Home...
I want to go home...
Let's go.
Home.
(Seoul Station)
- I won.
- No, you didn't.
That hurts.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Dried squid and peanuts for sale.
Mr. Soldier!
It's me again, Hee Tae.
(Mr. Soldier! It's me again...)
Do you know how many times
I wrote you?
How could you not call
or write me once?
Don't tell me you were dragged
to Namsan or something.
Get into your positions!
How does it feel to be a member
of the military...
that you hated so much?
Anyone who lets them by,
you're dead meat!
Well, you're always well-known
for your excessive loyalty,
so I'm sure you're settling in fine.
- Hold it up properly.
- Team C, let's go!
Don't tell me you're still upset
because of what happened that day.
Stand straight, you fool!
If that's the case,
let me tell you that thanks to you,
my life is also plenty messed up,
so let's just call it even.
I'm trying my best to untangle
this mess.
I'm not sure how,
but I'll do everything in my power.
So please write me back.
His stomach was pierced
by some construction material.
They tried pulling it out,
so he's bleeding really badly.
Go get Doctor Kim. Now.
What? Okay.
Sir, I'll press down on the wound.
It's going to hurt a little bit.
Gosh, is it just now lunchtime?
It looks like we'll have to
work overtime again tonight.
This is all because of that brat,
Kim Myeong Hee.
What use is it if we request
extra personnel?
She just keeps working
until broad daylight...
when she's on night shifts.
That's why the higher-ups think
that's natural.
Gosh. Darn it! That stubborn brat.
Why does she work so hard though?
It doesn't seem like she cares
about what others think of her.
What do you think?
It's because of the money.
What on earth can she possibly do...
with some few extra bucks?
(Gwangju Station)
Are you here to see a friend?
Thank you very much!
I'm here.
Gwangju.
(New volition for a new Gwangju)
(Host of 19th South Jeolla Province
Athletic Meet...)
(and 61st Preliminaries
of the National Sports Festival)
(Reception)
Where is the
Deputy Director's office?
Hey!
What will you do about this?
If you hold this for a while...
Pull it out
and just stick it in again.
Come on, stick it in somewhere else.
Come on.
Okay.
Gosh, what are you doing?
Are you caressing me or what?
- Move, I'll do it.
- Okay.
Hey, little lady.
I never asked for your help.
You can leave.
What else do you expect
in an emergency room?
You little... Hey, you.
You darned brat.
Hey. Do you know who I am?
I do.
You're a patient.
Let go of me!
(Patient, Jang Seok Chul)
Oh, dear.
I think it would be better...
to just stay put,
for you and the patient's sake.
It's not an easy thing
to transfer a coma patient...
from Seoul to Gwangju either.
To be frank, it'll cost you
an awful lot of money too.
Do you have that much money?
If you give the approval,
I promise to get the money...
You seem like a young student,
and you're going about things
in the wrong order.
We don't take empty promises.
We only take cash.
Come back when you have the money.
It's not an empty promise.
The patient is in need
of urgent care...
I'm glad you mentioned that.
Our hospital is in need
of urgent money.
Goodbye.
But...
Sir.
This patient was born in Gwangju.
Going back home might be
his last dying wish.
I think he should spend
his last moments here...
Get out of my way!
My gosh, Sang Gon. What is going on?
Byung Geol.
Fire this brat now.
What kind of nurse...
assaults a sick patient
in this world?
Hey, I'm not saying this
because he's a friend.
How can a medical worker
assault a patient?
Apologize to him now.
Now you're treating me
like a medical worker?
What?
You pretended not to see anything...
when a young nurse
was being sexually harassed.
But now that I react,
you're suddenly mentioning
my duties as a nurse?
Who are you to talk back to him
like that?
Wait, she's...
My goodness.
My gosh, Sang Gon. Are you okay?
What do you think you're doing
in my office?
It was self-defense.
Since you weren't helping me.
What's that attitude
after making this mess?
I'm not the one who made this mess.
What? Hey...
Hey, is anyone out there?
Take her out!
My goodness.
Can you help him?
That cheeky wench!
How dare she yell at me?
So, about the transfer...
Get out. Get out now!
Hey. Go check over there.
Let's split up and search.
I don't know
if these will last another year.
Hey, little lady.
Are you on your way home?
Goodness, does that line still work?
Of course.
This line has never failed.
Were you busy getting chased again?
How do you have so much energy?
Let's go. No time for chit-chat.
What are you talking about?
I just got off work.
Come on.
We don't have time for this.
Hey, I even got a nosebleed!
Hurry up and ring the doorbell.
My father will be coming out
any minute.
So why do you keep sneaking out
like a cat in heat?
Just go in and beg his forgiveness.
Who is it?
Hello. It's Myeong Hee,
Soo Ryeon's friend.
You go this way,
and I'll go this way, okay?
- Okay?
- Okay.
Well, I'm here
because Soo Ryeon called me...
and asked me to come over.
She called you?
She's been sick in bed
since yesterday evening.
She must've woken up for a bit
this morning.
She called me around 5 a.m.
Around 5 a.m.,
I was already up and working.
Wait. That's wrong.
It was 4 a.m. It was around 4 a.m.
I see. Come on in.
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
Hold on. Is that you, Myeong Hee?
Mr. Lee. How have you been?
I've been good.
Are you here to see Soo Ryeon?
Don't tell me she's still sleeping.
She told me not to wake her up...
under any circumstances.
What? I can't believe that brat.
Lee Soo Ryeon!
My goodness. Lee Soo Ryeon!
- Gosh. It's Father.
- Lee Soo Ryeon!
Lee Soo Ryeon!
She must've completely passed out.
- What should I do?
- Lee Soo Ryeon!
Lee Soo Ryeon!
What time is it? I slept like a log.
Why are you soaked in sweat?
What?
You have the chills.
Well, I must be coming down
with something.
Gosh, I have the chills.
We had to meet up
with a wanted person last night,
and I was the only one
they could trust.
What's happening today?
Today is even more important.
In the evening,
we're going to give speeches.
At night, we're printing out flyers.
I bet, within a couple of weeks,
all your hair will be shaved off.
This is the least I can do
to deserve to be called Joan of Arc.
What does that even mean?
Do you need a license
to protest these days?
If only there were a license,
I'd go and get one.
Whatever I do,
I'll always be my father's daughter.
Guilt by association is nonsense.
Your father being a capitalist
doesn't make you a hypocrite.
Anyway, I'll go wash up.
(Joint Statement Demanding
Democratization of Universities)
Give it a read, okay?
What are you talking about?
I said I worked all night!
Oh, my. When did you get here?
I don't think
it needs any corrections.
- Soo Chan, is that you?
- Myeong Hee?
Goodness, how long has it been?
You've become a real lady.
Soo Chan!
What happened?
I thought you were coming back
next month.
Are you back in Korea for good?
Yes, it seems so.
A dress?
I never wear these.
Why do you keep getting them for me?
My dressing room is already packed.
Why else? I want you to wear them.
Stop dressing
like a North Korean soldier.
What are you talking about?
By the way,
if I'd known I'd run into you,
I would've gotten something
for you too, Myeong Hee.
What? Don't worry.
That's unnecessary.
Myeong Hee,
you could ask him...
to get you those foreign books
when he goes on business trips.
- Hey.
- What?
Soo Chan, Myeong Hee is preparing
to study abroad.
- What? Really?
- Yes.
That's impressive.
You're working too, right?
It's just my dream.
I haven't been accepted
to any schools yet.
And I haven't saved up
enough either.
If you'd cut back on the money
you send home for the kid,
you would've studied abroad
a dozen times already.
It's not my kid.
I have a little brother,
and he's still very young.
You couldn't pretend not to care,
could you?
You must be the pillar
of your family.
Do you see this, Soo Ryeon?
You'll never understand
how us firstborns feel.
"Us first-borns?"
Goodness. Myeong Hee,
you're still so young yourself.
It must be hard being the grown-up.
It was really nice seeing you today.
Call me if you need anything
while preparing for your studies.
Okay. Thank you.
Well... Is it really okay
if I call you?
When I want to ask you something,
I mean.
Yes, of course.
I started a company recently.
Call me at this number
if I'm not home.
(Changhwa Pharmaceuticals,
Lee Soo Chan)
You're the first person
to receive my business card.
Thank you.
- Drive safe.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Take care.
Go.
- Hey, Kim Myeong Hee, come here.
- Come here.
- Come on here.
- What is it?
What's going on?
Tell us the truth, Kim Myeong Hee.
You were with a guy.
Judging from his car,
he must be a bourgeois.
Gosh, it's not like that.
"It's not like that?"
What does she mean?
Why did you call me here?
I'm about to pass out.
Make it quick.
Goodness, can you believe
the way she talks?
Let's see what you're going to say
when you see this.
What is it?
Are you being drafted?
See for yourself.
- Congratulations!
- You got in!
My gosh, is this real?
Guys, is this a prank?
Come on!
It's real, all the way from Germany.
I went to the post office
every single morning...
to pick this up for you.
I don't have time for this.
Hey, I have to go.
Where are you going?
We should celebrate!
I should go tell Father.
- My gosh.
- Bye!
What? Hwang Hee Tae!
How have you been?
Good job.
I'm proud of you.
Have you decided
when you're going to enroll?
Not any time soon.
I have to apply for a passport...
and save up more money.
You see, I got a call
from the Bishops' Conference.
They're giving a scholarship
to just one person this year.
A scholarship?
Yes. I was going to recommend you,
but I was afraid
I was getting ahead of myself.
And you brought me
this good news today.
It's the Lord's will.
That would really help me.
But there's one condition.
You must leave the country
in a month.
In a month?
It's too soon, right?
Flights are expensive too.
You can try again next year
if you want.
No. Please recommend me.
I'll prepare the money somehow.
All right. That sounds good.
Hold on.
Shouldn't you call your family?
Tell them the good news.
Call them immediately.
That's my condition.
The preliminaries...
will be completely different
from the school races.
The fastest runners...
from all over the province
will be there.
The winner can even enter
the National Sports Festival.
Is that right?
Mother,
our Myeong Soo might even compete
in the Olympics at this rate.
But no one in the whole world
can run faster than Hyun Chul.
What? Father?
Grandma, you're being silly again.
(Watch repair)
Hold on. The phone is ringing.
Here.
Hello?
(Public telephone)
Myeong Soo, answer the phone.
It's your sister.
It's Myeong Hee?
Hello?
Goodness. I'm not deaf.
What are you so excited about,
little bear?
Myeong Hee, I'm entering a race
in Gwangju next week!
Can you come?
I'll be there if I'm off duty.
Hey, Myeong Soo.
Can I talk to Mother?
I won't let you talk to her
unless you promise you'll come.
- Move.
- Mother.
Hi, Myeong Hee. What's the matter?
What? Really?
That's great.
But how are you going to afford it?
I'll ask your father...
You don't want me to tell him?
All right.
I didn't call to ask for help.
My son is innocent!
Who are you taking away now?
- There she goes again.
- Take me instead!
- I'm hanging up.
- Take me!
My son is innocent!
- You little...
- Mother!
- You can't do this!
- Mother, calm down.
- You can't take him away!
- Mother!
Hwang Ki Nam, you jerk!
If only you remembered that sooner.
We could've saved each other
so much trouble.
Sir.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
Finish up.
At the opposition party's request...
for the resignation
of the Yushin government...
and the introduction of
the single-member district system,
the security commander commented...
that it is time...
that the parties worked together...
for an advanced political system.
My goodness.
By overcoming crises
inside and outside the country,
political development...
At this rate,
they'll even kick out
all the dogs...
that were kept
during the Yushin regime.
A scared dog barks first.
All they do is bark but never bite.
What if we relax
thinking it's a scared dog,
but it turns out to be a crazy dog?
In these turbulent times,
you should find someone...
who can have your back.
I will be fine
as long as I have you on my side.
What I mean is,
you need a lifeboat you can hop into
when you're in a pinch.
Thanks.
You already have an excellent card
in your hand.
Why look further?
You know what's the surest way
to form an alliance?
Your son is marrying age, isn't he?
I'll lead you to water.
Try and catch the fish yourself.
Of course.
Thank you, sir.
(National New Community Movement
Leaders Summit)
Are you getting in or not?
I am.
Dear student democracy activists.
Punishing the remaining powers
on campus...
should go beyond opportunism.
We should all be
the guillotines of history.
We must expel
all government-funded professors,
who have lived as parasites
of the Yushin dictatorship...
from our sacred campus!
- Yes!
Expel government-funded professors!
"Jang Seok Chul?"
That's a girl's name?
Yes. She's 24 years old.
Would it be possible?
He's the most resourceful member
of the student council.
He's better
than most private detectives, right?
This is not much to go on,
but I'll ask around.
Thanks.
No problem.
- Hey, Jung Hye Gun.
- Hey.
Did you prepare the sample?
It's tonight.
Well, I brought the sample here.
But I'm afraid I can't go with you
to print them.
A friend is visiting from Seoul
for the first time in years.
A friend?
This place isn't open
to just anyone.
Can we trust you?
If you can't,
are you going to torture me
or something?
Well, as long as we confirm
your identity,
we can use all the help we can get.
Gosh, I'd rather be tortured.
Come on.
If you came all the way here,
isn't it because you're interested
in what we're doing?
No. I just came to drink.
Let's go.
Hey. Wait a minute.
Sorry I can't help you.
I'll see you at the rally.
Who on earth is that random jerk?
- What?
- You tell her!
Why should I? You go...
Go tell her.
Well...
- Myeong Hee.
- Yes?
Do you know what day it is?
Oh, the rent.
I forgot.
I'll give it to you right away.
Also, since we're on that subject...
Jin A will stop taking
private lessons from you now.
Gosh, her grades aren't improving
at all.
Then what about the rent?
Oh, you can pay me the original rent
starting next month.
Gosh, why is it so dusty in here?
Look at this dust.
(Plane ticket: 889.5 dollars)
(Regular savings account)
(Balance)
(Regular savings account,
Kim Myeong Hee)
(Changhwa Pharmaceuticals,
Lee Soo Chan)
Call me if you need anything
while preparing for your studies.
You've taken good care of it.
Thank you.
Gosh, this place is already
too cluttered.
That thing is such a nuisance,
so you can have it.
I wonder how much
I can sell this for.
Do you gamble?
You'll sell
your mother's last belonging?
Something's wrong, right?
It's strange.
You're suddenly talking about money
out of the blue.
And you always hated
staying with me here,
but you suddenly dropped by
like this.
It's just because my father
doesn't know I'm here.
That's what's the strangest.
You never came to Gwangju
unless your father called you.
I told you
I have some business here.
I know, so what is that business?
- Something at the hospital.
- Come on.
Seoul is packed with hospitals.
Why does it have to be one
in Gwangju?
Hwang Hee Tae.
You have a girl in Gwangju,
don't you?
Sort of. Are you satisfied?
Turn off the light.
"Sort of?"
- There really is someone.
- My goodness.
- Who is it? Tell me.
- Darn it.
Over here.
(Joint Statement Demanding
Democratization of Universities)
Almost done.
Someone's here.
Darn.
Hey! This way.
- Get them!
- Hey!
- Stop!
- Come here!
- Get them!
- Go after them!
Hee Tae. Get up.
Hey, Hwang Hee Tae.
What is it?
What...
Father.
Good morning.
- Hee Tae?
- Yes.
What brings you to Gwangju?
What the...
Why are you here?
Hey, Jung Tae.
It's good to see you too.
Jung Tae,
don't be rude to your brother.
Bring it if you're done writing.
Oh, okay.
So due to the curfew,
I couldn't go to an inn...
and ended up falling asleep
at that house.
Eventually, at precisely 5 a.m.,
you found me and dragged me back...
to where I am now.
That's all.
Why aren't you working as an intern?
How did you know that?
Are you tailing me?
Don't joke around.
I'm asking why you're not working
at the hospital.
I didn't graduate.
I thought it would be better
than getting expelled.
I waited six years to see
this flower bloom.
I turned on the heater in winter...
just for this flower
in this empty room.
I raised it with the utmost care,
but bugs started living inside it.
I was worried the pesticide
might harm the flower,
so I even diluted it with water.
But the insects eventually
hatched eggs inside it.
No matter how precious it is,
if the roots have been eaten away,
it's nothing more
than a host of parasites.
I only accepted you as my son...
because I believed
you would prove useful.
Instead of becoming
a host of parasites.
So...
How much have you been eaten away?
Father, I...
need money.
What?
I need money to sort out
a situation that I created.
If you help me out
without asking any questions,
I'll do whatever you tell me to do
without asking any questions...
from now on.
Whatever I tell you to do?
Lee Soo Ryeon, come out.
What about the others?
I had this sensation
in the back of my head.
My sense of smell and hearing...
All my senses were telling me,
"It's that way."
Let go of me.
I said, let go!
Why am I the only one
being released?
Hey, stop right there.
What's going on here?
Why are you letting her go
after all my hard work?
Exactly.
What are you doing? Put me back in.
Put me back in right now.
What on earth is going on?
Come on.
What are you all doing?
Chief, you came at the right time.
The senior inspector here...
is releasing the trespasser
that I went to so much trouble...
to catch red-handed...
Watch your language.
She was just visiting a factory
owned by her father.
How is that trespassing?
Pardon?
A factory owned by her father?
Then release the others too.
They were just visiting like I was.
That's enough.
Unbelievable.
You brought the whole gang
to my factory now?
I know I spoiled you
raising you alone,
but this is just too much.
I never asked you to get me out.
I can take care of myself.
You can take care of yourself? How?
By going to prison?
Once you're convicted,
my factory will be stigmatized
as a place that prints flyers.
We'll go out of business.
You're not to leave this house,
not even for school.
End of discussion.
Father. Father!
What? Arrested?
Everyone who gathered
to print out flyers got arrested.
What about Soo Ryeon?
She must've been there too.
She's been released alone
thanks to her father.
Are you happy now?
I heard everything from Father.
You're going to Germany
next month, right?
I don't know yet.
I need money for the airfare.
Ask your lady for help.
I'm no beggar.
Why on earth would I ask her
to give me money?
You're just borrowing it.
That scholarship is
such a rare opportunity.
I can apply again next year.
What if you don't get it next year?
Will you wait another year?
Do you want to lose the opportunity
because of your pride?
There are unpaid bills.
Mr. Choi!
My goodness.
(Regular savings account,
Hwang Hee Tae)
I brought the money.
(Regular savings account,
Hwang Hee Tae)
My, nice to see you.
It's been a while, Mr. Kim.
It's been so long.
How have you been?
My goodness.
They say, when the tiger is away,
the fox plays the king.
Hwang Ki Nam seems to be
enjoying more power...
since the president passed away.
How frustrating.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Okay.
- I'll get going.
- All right.
Oh, hello.
Did your daughter
come back home safely?
Yes, thanks to you.
I feel so bad every time.
We help each other.
You don't have to feel bad.
In these turbulent times,
there are many things
to think about.
Especially for those who are
on their own like you and me,
one small mistake can be
all it takes.
You're right.
We're living in strange times.
Speaking of which,
isn't it time your daughter started
getting ready to get married?
Father.
Father, we need to talk.
Go to your room.
I have nothing to say to you.
Do you want to see
your daughter die?
Please get them out.
If something happens to them,
how will I face the world?
Father.
I can get your friends out
on one condition.
I'll do anything. Anything at all.
Soo Ryeon, it's time...
for you to grow up.
How can I go on a date
with such a horrible person's son?
Go on a date,
and they'll be released.
It's already decided.
He's the son of Hwang Ki Nam,
of all people!
He was once the Head
of Anti-communist Investigation.
So what?
All you have to do is sit with him
for a while and turn him down.
Imagine someone sees me...
with the likes
of a powerful anti-communist's son.
Joan of Arc will be burned
at the stake immediately.
What can you do?
This is the only way
to get your friends out.
Right. Didn't you say
you had something to tell me?
I feel bad for sharing good news...
when you're so devastated.
What is it?
What could this be?
What? "Acceptance Letter?"
Hey, did you get in?
Goodness. When did you even apply?
You never told me.
I wasn't counting on getting in.
I guess I was lucky.
Congratulations.
I knew you could do anything
once you set your mind to it.
It must've been so hard,
working and studying all at once.
I'm proud of you, Myeong Hee.
Thanks.
But this feels
as if you're being drafted.
When are you leaving?
I'm going to try
to leave next month.
What? Next month?
Didn't you say you'd have to save up
for another year?
You're just borrowing it.
Well...
I won
the Catholic Foundation scholarship.
Really?
That's great.
You must be so relieved.
But the thing is...
To get the scholarship,
I must leave next month.
So I have to...
scrape up money for airfare soon.
But flights are so expensive.
Where are you going to get
all that money?
Well... Myeong Hee.
I could ask my father...
No. Forget it.
I shouldn't have said anything.
I can find a way. Don't worry.
So when is this date of yours?
Hold on.
I was just...
struck with a brilliant idea.
You can go on the blind date
instead of me,
and I'll buy the plane ticket...
instead of you.
You just have to meet with him
three times.
And if he dumps you first,
you just have to meet him once.
No one will ever find out
since you don't know each other.
Come on, that's total nonsense.
Why? Let's help each other out
in this difficult situation.
Three dates
for a plane ticket to Germany.
Come on. Don't you think
this is a win-win for both of us?
Ta-da!
What in the world?
Soo Ryeon, I'm going to kill you.
Stop it! My goodness.
Hey!
How about this purple dress
to start with?
- What about this?
- I don't think so.
Who are you?
Are you really Myeong Hee?
What are you doing?
Yes! That's perfect!
Goodness, let me see.
Most of my clothes fit you,
but the shoes are the problem.
Try it on again.
Good. It won't slip off now.
All right.
It's time for the last touch.
This is my good luck charm.
I never failed
to get rejected by a guy...
whenever I wore this.
Gosh, it's perfect.
You look gorgeous.
I don't know what I'm doing
right now.
Come on, why?
Don't you want to go on the date
now that it's about to happen?
No. Going on a date
isn't a big deal.
It's just that the plane ticket
is too expensive.
I don't want to get you
in trouble...
There you go again!
It's not like I'm doing it for free.
We both have nothing to lose
from this.
So just go and get dumped. Got it?
Okay?
Okay.
(Gwangju Park Hotel Cafe, 4 p.m.)
Darn.
Jin Woo... Jin Woo!
- Oh, dear. My son.
- He's been hit.
- Jin Woo.
- What's going on?
What happened?
My son...
- Oh, gosh.
- Jin Woo.
Jin Woo...
Please look at me.
No, Jin Woo...
(Patient, Jang Seok Chul,
Guardian, Hwang Hee Tae)
Hee Tae. Please save Seok Chul.
Hee Tae! Please save her.
Hee Tae!
- Oh, dear.
- What do we do?
- Hey!
- Lay him down.
Did he hit his head?
No.
I just bumped into him slightly,
and he fell down.
Ma'am, please save my son.
- My gosh.
- My son...
I think he's injured.
I think he just passed out,
so calm down.
- Call an ambulance now.
- Okay.
My son. Please...
Hey, little boy. Open your eyes.
Kid. Look at me.
He woke up!
What is your name?
Can you look here for me?
- Gosh.
- I'm so glad he's not hurt.
- Sang Gon, what is going on?
- Byung Geol.
Fire this brat now.
What kind of nurse...
assaults a sick patient
in this world?
Ma'am, please save my son.
That cheeky nurse!
I'm sorry I'm late.
My name is Lee Soo Ryeon.
(Youth of May)
Even when you did everything
I told you to?
No matter what I did,
he did something worse.
You look like you're the one
who went on a date.
- What?
Myeong Soo!
Is he Myeong Hee's secret son?
Stop being so silly.
Soo Ryeon,
do you have time tomorrow?
- How about dinner?
- I have plans tonight.
She's a total vixen.
After struggling with my life
all day long,
I feel free whenever I meet you.
I'll play a song for you next time.
Do you want to meet again
before the flowers wither?