ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Just kill me!
Kill me!
-What's going on?
-He might really kill her.
-What do we do?
-They must be crazy.
-Should we call the police?
-Oh, my goodness.
-He's really killing her.
-Unbelievable.
-My goodness.
-My gosh.
Don't.
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you follow me here?
Go back to the store basement.
Everyone's going to die
when the war breaks out.
Go.
-Come with me.
-You brat.
I said, go. Go before I kill you first.
Go and live.
Just kill me!
Stop saying you'll kill me
and just do it, you loser!
What's your relationship
with the guy who's been sending you
money?
Ji-eun's been starving because
you can't even put bread on the table!
What else could I do?
-Hey, be quiet!
-Why would I?
Ji-eun will hear you. Shut up!
What have you ever done for me?
You've never brought home money
or given me jewels.
And what? Cheating?
How dare you talk like that to me!
Dad!
Let's just go.
Let's go, Dad.
KIM JIN-HUI
MONEY TRANSFER
I took the uploader with Mom.
Mom told me to go and find you
if she didn't make it.
You're
my daughter, Ji-eun?
-Then why didn't you tell me?
-Because I hated you!
I was going to run away with Mom.
I've been waiting for her,
but she won't come.
Darn it.
Just beat me! Kill me!
I want to die!
I don't want to live anymore!
So don't go, Dad.
I'll be alone again if you go.
Go to the basement.
You'll die out here.
I won't go by myself!
Mom always told me
that you were a jerk,
but you wouldn't have hurt her back then.
That you wouldn't have dared.
You were an asshole,
but you weren't that evil.
Who keeps sending you money?
Who the hell is it?
So don't go in there.
Would I still be here if I knew?
-Please.
-I feel upset too!
Just trust me.
Just kill me.
I don't want to live anymore.
Please kill me.
All right.
Let's just die together today.
It's okay! I remember this day.
Nothing will happen.
So trust me, just this once.
Dad.
Ji-eun.
Are you fighting again?
No, Ji-eun.
Let's go to bed, okay?
Dad, what's wrong?
Ji-eun.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't even recognize my own child.
I wouldn't have come here
if I hadn't killed anyone.
Everything has changed now.
Let's go to your Mom.
Oh, no. I won again.
Jae-sun is dead.
You shouldn't have left like that.
I had my reasons.
I'm just worried.
Are you sure your plan is still working?
It's still working, right?
All right.
You know what's going to happen, right?
Seo-hae.
Is it the girl or the world?
You can only choose one.
No.
You won't get what you want this time.
You're not in your wedding dress.
I'm a misogamist.
What a relief.
Don't make the uploader.
If you don't, we'll win.
Han Tae-sul. Are you listening?
Don't make it.
Seo-hae.
Whatever happens from now on,
just trust me.
No matter what happens.
Everything will be fine.
I mean it.
I mean it, too.
The uploader code.
Or I'll shoot the girl.
Five, four, three, two…
Hey, wait.
-What?
-I'm not saying I'll do it.
I'm just curious about something.
Give me a minute.
Two, one.
Hey, I really won't do it
if you don't answer me.
What is it?
You said…
What time is it?
Yes, about right now.
You said you were about
to commit suicide at home.
And before that,
you were crying and hiding in the park.
So?
You even ran away without paying
for the cab fare. How much was it?
Why do you ask?
You get curious about everything
just before you die.
I have this kind of obsession
about details.
It really bothers me. I feel like
I won't be able to rest in peace.
You wrote hate comments online,
didn't pay for the cab fare,
and destroyed the world.
You're a real scumbag, aren't you?
Do you think you can win
by buying time like this?
You're totally wrong there.
Why?
First of all, I'm not just buying time.
Second,
I already told you I was going to win.
You're all talk, aren't you?
No, I'm not.
What? Did you not expect this?
The future can change.
It's boring if it's always the same.
You want to know what happened?
Count to five if you're curious.
Never mind, I'll count.
Five, four, three, two…
Hey, you're getting a call. Take it.
Who is this?
What was that?
Do you know what that sound is?
It's the sound of nails
being hammered to your coffin.
The future is changing.
Didn't I tell you that I saw it?
Enough fooling around.
I don't know what you're playing at,
but it's over.
-Start coding.
-You can't shoot her.
I've already done it before.
That's how I'm here.
Shoot her!
The gun!
You bastard!
Han Tae-sul.
What have you done to me?
Why don't you ask for help again?
Oh, is there no one to help you now?
Your dad's dead,
and so is that kid
who followed you around.
Han Tae-sul's going to die too.
You're used to being alone,
aren't you?
Are you okay?
No, this is impossible.
What did you do, Tae-sul?
Don't look at me like that.
I hate you.
I hate everyone
in this world.
When the sun sets in Seoul…
with nobody in it,
it's red everywhere.
And the night sky…
is filled with stars.
It's so quiet.
It's as if
I'm alone in the world.
Hey.
Seo-hae.
Don't you miss it?
No.
Not at all.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Someone shot Sigma from over there.
Right.
Who was it?
Is everything over now?
Let's go.
Where?
Seo-hae.
What's important…
Wow, I never thought I'd say this to you.
But what's important isn't "where."
What's important is "when."
The uploader.
Yes, the uploader.
We have to take the uploader.
Let's go and finish this.
There's nobody here.
I guess they all disappeared, too.
Darn it. What's going on?
What should we do?
He doesn't know anything yet.
He's going to go upstairs
to find out what's going on.
Nothing good will come from
meeting him, so let's wait.
Jeez.
The person you are calling is unavailable…
Wow. It's huge.
Did you take this, too?
Yes. It was a bit dirtier, though.
But if you make it work…
I'll make sure it can be used only once.
Can you get it running automatically?
I had to get shots and stuff.
No, I need someone to help me.
-Who?
-They're coming.
But why didn't you tell me?
How long have you known?
Since the day I locked you in the bunker.
-Why didn't you tell me back then?
-Well…
Seo-hae, just hang on.
I'll tell you in a moment.
This part is pretty complicated.
See? Look at you.
You always show your emotions
on your face.
If you had known,
your face would've
given everything away to Sigma.
Are you saying I'm emotional?
Who's the one who got emotional
and let Seo Gil-bok go?
What? I wasn't prepared for that
back then.
And I'm not talking about that.
I'm just saying
that you're not good at lying.
Good for you. You're such a good liar.
What kind of a conversation is this?
And when did I ever lie to you?
You lied to me just now.
-When did I lie to you?
-Goodness.
Hey!
My goodness.
Nice.
It seems like you two are bickering
every time I see you.
And when you're not together,
you're always looking for each other.
So… Wait.
What about Sigma?
-He's dead.
-Really?
Yes.
I see.
And is this the new uploader?
-What about the coding?
-Hang on.
-So we just have to send you there?
-Yes.
But we only know how to use downloaders.
-So?
-I'm not saying we won't do it.
But we could make a mistake
and you might arrive there
without your limbs or something.
-We don't have time.
-If it doesn't matter, fine.
Prep our guests.
-Wait.
-Don't worry. Give me your arm.
That hurts. Why does it hurt so much?
Stop making a fuss.
It's my second time, you know.
Wait.
-Hang on. Give me your vest.
-What? Why?
We don't know what may happen.
We could get hit by stuff.
-Give yours to Seo-hae.
-I don't need one.
We should always be prepared.
Everything's ready. Oh, hang on.
Okay. Everything's ready.
Mr. Park. Come over here.
Are you sure
we can trust her?
Yes. She's pretty skilled.
But why are you helping us?
We have nothing to give you anymore.
Just because.
Mr. Han.
When you arrive there,
-you'll come and find me, right?
-Of course.
I wasn't so sure back then,
so tell me exactly the same thing again
when you find me, okay?
-Okay.
-Take care.
And you take care, too.
And I hope we never meet again.
Hey.
For you not to throw up.
Does this hurt?
Yes. It hurts a lot.
Your body is shattered
and put back together.
Really?
No. You just get a bit dizzy
and feel nauseous.
That's a relief.
Let's begin.
It's ready.
Have a nice trip!
Three.
Two.
One.
Hi.
Are you okay?
It feels like I'm still spinning.
What time is this?
The day
I locked you in the bunker.
Probably about now.
Let's go. The Control Bureau will come.
No, they won't come.
-What?
-They're busy looking for you.
They don't care about illegal entrants.
We shouldn't move around.
Is that why you locked me in there?
So we wouldn't get caught now?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me? You little…
Wait. I'm not in a stable state right now.
I feel like my body's shattering.
Let's stay like this a little bit.
We didn't get to rest for several days.
-Come on. Get up.
-Just a little bit.
Come on.
Jeez.
Wait here.
Why? I'm coming with you.
You're locked in the bunker right now.
It's better for you to stay here
without being seen.
Where are you going?
The bathroom. Are you coming too?
-Hey, there's no time to--
-Oh, your shoelace is untied.
Tie that firmly. We'll have to run a lot.
Hey.
Darn it.
Let's go.
Are we going to Mr. Park?
No. There's somewhere else to go first.
DONGDAEMUN POLICE STATION
Why are we here?
Your father.
Sigma told us earlier
where Seo Gil-bok will be tomorrow.
-In the park.
-Yes. So we should catch him
since we have to go back to the church.
It's Dad.
Let's go tomorrow morning. All right.
Dad.
What is it?
You told me to find you
if I needed any help.
If you catch Seo Gil-bok,
take care of him however you like.
And then call this number.
Some strange guy is going to answer,
but you can just hang up.
Can we stop the war if we catch him?
Probably.
All right.
Seo-hae.
Let me hug you.
All right.
I'll be off.
Okay.
Can't you read? It says we're closed!
Do you even know how to shoot a gun?
Oh, and a sniper rifle.
You're not Han Tae-sul, are you?
I'm not sure if you've heard this before.
"The future is already here.
We just don't know it yet."
The future you asked me to tell you this.
"Your daughter is right next to you.
But you've been wasting time
without recognizing her.
So you can stop it now. It's okay."
He asked me to tell you.
If you're free tomorrow,
come to the church.
Did you get it? After checking?
Yes. Why is it so heavy? Gosh.
Some people shoot it while holding it.
-We just have to go to the church now?
-Yes. Hang on.
What?
I can't carry this all the way there.
It's pretty far. I called a cab.
-A cab?
-Why isn't he coming?
Oh, there he is.
Hey! I told you not to be late.
Seo-hae, you're surprised, aren't you?
Well, I…
I had this on.
Don't hit me. I can explain.
Oh, your shoelace is untied.
Tie that firmly. We'll have to run a lot.
THURSDAY, OCTOBER 30
I think it was around now.
ON GOVERNMENT DUTY
Oh, my gosh. What are you doing here?
Where's Seo-hae?
-Just wear this.
-What is it?
Seo-hae will die if you don't.
-What?
-And if you find Seo-hae,
you can't tell her you met me
or that you're wearing this.
Why?
This is the only way to save her.
-What are you talking about?
-Jae-sun. Just trust me.
We trusted each other
and saved Seo-hae
when she was at the Control Bureau, right?
Come to Asia Mart at eight. Don't be late.
Jae-sun.
You were pretending to be dead?
No! It really hurt like hell.
I almost died.
I actually fainted.
Are you mad at me?
You're mad, aren't you?
Please don't hit me…
Anything else you hid from me?
No.
You're lying.
You're good at lying, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
No, there's nothing else.
Come on, get in.
By the way, where do we go now?
Why bother hiding her?
You guys are in the palm of my hand.
Oh, what was his name?
Right, Sun. He's dead.
I had to infuriate her
to make her come here voluntarily.
Don't get too nervous.
It'll be quick.
-Let's go to the second floor.
-Okay.
How lovely is this?
You will make the uploader now. Why?
-Because you love her.
-Seo-hae.
-Get to your position.
-From beginning to end, all of it.
It was all part of my plan.
I'm just worried.
Are you sure your plan is still working?
It's still working, right?
Yes. My plan is just starting,
you asshole.
There was a fight over a cab fare
last night at Gangbuk Police Station.
-This is the only park nearby, right?
-Yes.
Where is this place?
Right here.
And this is where the station is.
Ten kilometers.
It'll only take three hours.
Tell them to keep looking.
Who is this Seo Gil-bok? What did he do?
Mr. Seo Gil-bok?
Yes?
Do you know what that sound is?
It's the sound of nails
being hammered to your coffin.
What was that?
The future is changing.
Didn't I tell you that I saw it?
Enough fooling around.
I don't know what you're playing at,
but it's over.
-Start coding.
-You can't shoot her.
I've already done it before.
That's how I'm here.
Are you really Seo Gil-bok?
Yes, I am.
Shoot her!
Seo-hae.
Can you hurry up?
Hang on.
The gun!
That bastard. How dare he hit her?
You bastard!
You shouldn't have done that.
I shouldn't have let him hit me like that.
Han Tae-sul.
What have you done to me?
Why don't you ask for help again?
Seo-hae. Are you okay?
It's a bit heavy.
It's almost over now.
We should ride the Viking next year.
Hey.
I'll save you, Seo-hae.
Good job.
Seo-hae.
This is
as far as I saw.
Thank you…
for everything
you did for me.
Don't go.
Seo-hae.
Tae-sul.
What's going on?
Seo-hae!
Seo-hae! No!
Seo-hae.
Seo-hae!
Seung-bok.
Why?
Make it.
-Make the uploader.
-Why would you…
She'll die if you don't make it.
And you'll live the rest
of your life in regret. So make it.
It's a good thing.
You'll be able to get another chance.
I'll give you that chance.
So make it.
Don't listen to him.
You made that mistake over and over.
You can end everything. Don't do it.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why?
Tae-sul. Do you know when my birthday is?
If you know, I'll stop.
But you don't.
We've known each other for 20 years.
I've had 20 birthdays during that time.
But you didn't care about me at all.
Do you know how many people
I kneeled to beg
and bowed to because of you?
If you know, I'll stop.
But you don't know, right?
Do you know how much I've suffered
taking care of your messes?
Seo-jin…
Do you know I liked her first?
I knew Seo-jin
before you did, and I liked her first.
You're the one who came between us.
You always stole what I had.
I gave you everything you asked for,
and gave you things before you even asked.
I gave up everything for you!
Why?
Because the company wouldn't exist
without you.
Because I was nothing but your sidekick!
But…
you've never thanked me for anything.
That's how it's always been.
Seung-bok, I…
I really cared for Seo-jin.
I liked her much more than you.
But she still likes you more.
I'm going to start over!
Kim Seung-bok. Stop this.
Stop, you crazy jerk!
Don't look at me like that.
Don't look at me with those eyes!
I'm going to go back.
I'm going to take everything
you have first.
Your research, your company, your girl!
I'll take everything.
You should learn
how it feels
to get everything taken away from you.
Choose.
-Is it the girl or the world?
-No…
No.
Please don't do it. Please.
Damn it.
Just choose!
All right! Fine!
I will.
I got it, so stop.
Seo-hae.
Let's go back.
Let's start over.
Let's go back to the past
and try this again.
Where should we go?
Should we go to Seo Gil-bok's house
so we can shoot him and end everything?
Or should we
just go hide in the bunker?
Or we could…
Seo-hae…
We could just go back
to the beginning.
To before we knew each other.
Hurry up.
Tae-sul…
I'm fine.
Just stop.
Or we'll have to repeat this
over and over again.
So just stop.
Is it done?
I'm asking if it's done.
Think carefully about this.
Seo-hae.
I get it now.
No.
I knew it all along.
This is the only way.
But
I keep fighting it…
because I want to be with you.
Come and find me.
Even if there's no future,
just come and find me.
Don't get sick or get hurt.
Be safe.
And come and find me.
Seo-hae.
Tae-sul!
-The weather is so nice.
-How nice.
Come and catch me!
Hey!
Tae-sul.
Do you remember what I said at the school?
My favorite color is pink,
and my favorite food
are bananas, bulgogi, and tteokbokki.
And my favorite person…
is you.
So don't forget that.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
I'll find you.
I love you.
You call this ramyeon?
The noodles turned completely soggy.
I want you to scarf it down
and make me a new one. Okay?
I'm sorry, sir. I'll get you a new one.
"White wine, Chardonnay, 2018."
Why is there a number at the end?
Why?
Well, never mind the wine.
"Korean meal. Naengchae."
What's naengchae?
I have no idea what these are.
You choose for me.
Which one is the best?
Come on. Which one's the best?
Hey, Han Tae-sul.
Why aren't you answering me?
You…
What?
Here's your water, sir.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
No.
Hey, it's not working. Look.
Smile.
All right.
Here you go.
Thank you!
You're welcome.
Thank you.
I'm home.
SIGMA, SEO GIL-BOK, SEO WON-JU
ASIA MART
PARK HYEONG-DO
SEON-JAE, SEON-HO, BINGBING
QUANTUM &amp; TIME
HAN TAE-SUL
HAN TAE-SAN STILL ALIVE
SEO-HAE
UPLOADER BUNKER
CONTROL BUREAU
HWANG HYUN-SEUNG, JUNG HYEON-GI
Don't look at me like that.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park