Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
JULY 2019, SUMMER OF THIRTY
DAE-SUNG
Hi, Dae-sung. Are you here?
Yes. I'll wait on the first floor.
Okay.
I have high hopes for both of you.
I've told everyone in this hospital
all about you two for three years.
The States wanted you,
but I managed to convince them
to send you back to my hospital.
Thank you.
-Dr. Heo.
-What?
I mean, Director Heo.
Are you happy to have us here?
-I am.
-Director Heo, let's go!
Let's go.
Be careful.
What's the rush?
Dae-sung, what should I do?
I'm so sorry,
but I need to go to the hospital first.
The hospital? Are you sick?
No, it's my dad. He got hospitalized.
-Get in.
-Okay.
You can go downstairs
to get the blood test results.
-Thank you.
Hello. I have a question.
-Where is…
-What's up?
…the Orthopedics Department?
You go first.
The Orthopedics Department is over there.
I see.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
Those who are in charge
of patient Kim Ji-suk in Room 151,
please return to the ward.
Heon, it's been a while.
Yes.
What brings you here?
Dae-sung.
Let's go.
See you.
He's your friend
that's always on TV, right?
Thank you.
I should have said hello sooner.
I'm Woo Dae-sung.
You look better in person than on TV.
Have some juice.
Okay.
By the way, what brings you here?
I know you're very busy.
I saw you on TV.
You're always on commercials
with half-naked women.
-Mom.
-Honey.
Don't.
-What?
-Still, I'll always be here for Sol-i.
Open this for me.
Open it.
Great job.
Here. Take it.
-What? Why--
-Yes, thank you.
Come on. What's wrong?
You get on my nerves.
Did you eat?
No, not yet.
Dr. Seo.
-Are you busy?
-Have you been looking for me?
Who will do the surgery
on patient Shin Gi-heon, Room 1504?
So you were looking for me for a reason.
Solve this riddle if you want the answer.
Which martial arts
does Winnie the Pooh practice?
-Kung "Pooh."
-What? That was fast.
Who will perform the surgery?
Dr. Kim Hyeon-gi will,
and I'll be assisting him.
Why are you asking?
Please do your best.
What? That's unlike you
to ask for a favor.
Is that all?
Bye.
What's it about?
Damn it.
Why didn't Sol-i tell us the room number?
I know, right?
She's not answering her phone either.
-Which room is it?
-Thank you.
Where is she?
Jin-hwan.
What am I looking at?
Ha-young, I think
I need to be hospitalized again.
I'm seeing things.
Cha Heon is in front of me.
Your eyes are fine.
It's been a while.
It's you.
It really is you, Heon.
What? Weren't you going to settle
in the States?
Right. Why didn't you even give us a call?
Sorry.
It's good to see you again.
I'm glad you're back.
I missed you, my friend.
Get in. I'll drive you home.
I'll take a cab.
It's hard to get a cab here at this hour.
Excuse me! Aren't you going to get in?
Where to?
Just drop me off at the nearest station.
Sol-i.
Chiamun Junction.
SURGERY STATUS
SHIN GI-HEON, FINISHED
Mom, it's over.
The operation was successful.
Thank you, Doctor.
-Thank you.
-Good job.
You're welcome. You asked me a favor.
Heon, how considerate of you. Thank you.
You're welcome.
By the way,
how do you know each other?
We're just colleagues.
Dr. Cha barely had any friends
in the States.
So I became his friend.
"Colleagues."
But you're too pretty
to be just a colleague.
-Do you have--
-Mom.
We should go see Dad.
She said they're colleagues.
Is she's the one?
See you.
Excuse me.
Did I scare you?
Yes. A little.
Sorry. My apologies.
Here.
Sit down.
You're Shin Sol-i, right? I'm Seo Ji-su.
Okay.
I have a lot of questions. Can I ask you?
I won't take no for an answer.
Okay.
How did you and Dr. Cha meet?
Why do you ask?
I was wondering if you know her.
Dr. Cha's long-time girlfriend.
"Girlfriend"?
But why do you want to know?
Isn't it funny?
What is?
Who dates such a bore like him?
I don't think he's that boring. Is he?
When he was in the States,
he talked about her a lot.
I think he still loves her very much.
That's why I was curious.
Do you know who she is?
No.
What's all this?
All right. Ta-da.
Bring this to Heon.
He asked the surgeons for extra care
for your dad's surgery.
I was so grateful,
so I woke up early in the morning
to pack this.
And eat this with him
after you deliver it.
I prepared two portions in total.
Mom, it's okay. It's past lunchtime.
Be more empathetic, will you?
Didn't you see how skinny Heon got?
It seems that he doesn't have time
to have a proper meal.
Go.
Hurry.
Seriously.
What are you doing?
What?
You scared me.
Mom told me to give this to you.
Let's share.
I just ate.
Ha-young! Jin-hwan!
-You're here!
-Ha-young!
I missed you.
Hey, Sol-i.
Jeong Jin-hwan.
Why are you still so overprotective
when it's been ten years?
She's right. Jin-hwan, take it easy.
It's been a while
since we gathered together. Right?
Not everyone's here though.
One person is missing.
So I called him over.
-Why did you call him?
-Heon is our friend, too.
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay. I'm not drunk.
Sol-i, you're drunk.
I said I'm not drunk.
Drink this.
I thought you don't drink.
I was thirsty.
Stop. That's enough. Let's go.
Whatever. I'm upset.
So you guys should buy gifts
for our wedding.
Sol-i, buy us an air purifier.
Heon, a fridge.
Dae-sung, buy a washing machine.
Also, the TV that you endorse.
A hot celebrity can handle that, right?
Hey, Jin-hwan,
are you trying to rip me off?
He called me a cheat.
Dae-sung, we're running late.
I told you we have a photoshoot tomorrow.
It's okay. You should go.
I'm sober now.
-Will you be all right?
-Of course. I'm fine.
Go home now.
See you.
You should go, too.
We're going to walk home to sober up.
What? From here?
Let Heon give us a ride.
He didn't drink anyway.
Let's just walk.
Heon, take Sol-i home.
Okay.
-Sol-i. Go home safe.
-Okay.
Ha-young, my legs hurt.
Jin-hwan!
I'll go now.
Get in.
I won't annoy you.
A wish bracelet and a Christmas card.
Are you sure it's a bracelet?
Isn't it a necklace?
Gosh, it's so pretty!
Sol-i.
did you ever regret your decision?
No. I haven't.
Don't you want to know
why I came back?
Don't you really know
who I came back for?
I don't want to know.
Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Get in. I'll drive you home.
I don't know why you did that to me
last night.
You made a big mistake.
Ms. Shin. Something did happen last night.
I'm sorry to give you all this trouble,
Mr. Superstar.
It's okay, Mr. Shin.
What's that huge diamond? Tell me later.
…met in this vast universe
by a special chance
and became one.
-Kiss the bride!
I never once thought
that we broke up.
We're going to make up.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-hyun Yang