[English subtitles are available]
Take a close look at it, Zeke.
This is Liberio where we live.
It is as small as a birdcage
compared to the rest of the world.
We must live here, unable to go anywhere else,
for the rest of our lives.
Zeke, do you want to leave this place?
Yes.
I do.
Oh my, what a surprise.
Visitors this early?
I'll come back later.
Ah, it's okay. We were just leaving.
Oh, Eldians.
What are you doing?
We have the permit to go out.
I’m the cleaner of this tower, and
it's my job to get rid of the filth.
You devils have tainted this place! How dare you!
You, the descendants of devils
who've massacred countless people!
And yet, you still breed like pests!
Damn devils!
Stay in the internment zone, dammit!
You stink.
-Keep it in mind, Zeke.
-Bumped into such filth this early!
This is the outside world.
If you hate this world,
then you must change it.
Zeke.
You must save everyone.
[Attack on Titan]
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Angels planning disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
[#74 Sole Salvation]
So one of these children
will be my successor?
Yes, one of them will be chosen.
There's one who’s falling behind. Who's he?
Ah, Yeager again?
All the other children are desperate
to earn the title of honorary Marleyans.
But I don’t see such drive on him at all.
I don’t even know what he’s doing here.
How was your training, Zeke?
It was really tough.
I see.
But you will surely become a Warrior.
You have special power, after all.
Moreover, you're our boy.
Yes!
Dad, mom, please help me
take care of Zeke again tonight.
Okay.
I baked your favourite pie.
Hooray!
Social dance club again?
Zeke is really lonely, you know.
I'm doing this for the health
of the people in this zone.
I'm sure Zeke will someday
understand the good deeds we’ve done.
This is the Fall of Lago,
which took place 1,200 years ago.
The metropolitan city Lago was destroyed at that time.
The same Titans also caused the Devastation
of Monte and the Ravaging of Valle.
Hundreds of thousands of Marleyans
were killed by the Eldian Empire.
The refugees who somehow managed
to flee from Lago wandered the ruins.
However, the Eldian Empire had
planted Titans on their escape route.
Then as the sun rose, the Titans
started approaching the Marleyans and…
Yes, I get it.
More people died, right?
Has your father properly taught
you our true history?
He taught me that Eldians did
awful things to Marleyans.
Which is why we must atone for that here.
Zeke, do you want to become
a Warrior and fight for Marley?
Yes.
I want to become a Warrior.
It's time for bed now.
Oh! I can continue to read you
the story about the cat family.
Yay!
Begin!
You're so bad at this, Dad!
Dad!
Is that you, Zeke?
I finished early today, so…
Ah, I see.
Then that means we can
focus on studying today.
Yeah...
In other words, the Fall of Lago
never happened.
The Devastation of Monte and
the Ravaging of Valle
are also made-up stories to
serve Marley's purposes.
Eldians have never had such cruel
culture or custom.
Most of all...
Our great founder Ymir would never
wish for it, therefore it's impossible.
That's right.
You finally understand, Zeke!
Yes!
If you don't have the drive, leave!
Marley is looking for those who are prepared
to devote everything to their motherland.
An Eldian like you would never be
entrusted with one of nation's Titans!
Hey!
You over there!
Pass me the ball, please!
Not bad for a little kid.
Eh?
Nice catch!
I’m tired of throwing the ball against the wall.
Would you care to join me?
Red armband!
Then you're...
A Marleyan Warrior you kids
are striving to be.
Though, my Beast Titan is not
that useful in combat.
That’s why I'm here playing ball to kill time.
Tom Ksaver.
My real job is a researcher
in Titan science.
Here, what's your name?
I'm Zeke Yeager!
Zeke, huh?
You’ve got a gift.
You can make a good pitcher.
I'm home!
Dad! Today I…
That's not what we agreed on!
Just what is going on, Grice?
The plan will be ruined if we
can't make Zeke a Warrior!
But according to Owl,
he can’t intervene in the selection
unless Zeke gets high marks.
I got it, okay? I know this is our
once-in-a-lifetime chance!
But it's still possible for Zeke
to earn the position, right?
Yes, that's right.
Zeke will surely…
Ah...
I'm sorry…
Zeke!
You can do it!
You're our boy, after all!
I believe I already said
Marley didn't need you.
Why are you here?
To show my loyalty to Marley
and atone for the sins of Eldians!
Please allow me to participate
in the open training!
What are you doing, Yeager?
Run! Come on, run!
Dammit! It's not supposed to be like this!
Don't say that!
That boy is doing his best.
But still not enough to become a Warrior!
You sure were a mess that day.
It's not funny at all.
Since then, they’ve always asked me to run errands.
I’m hopeless.
To me, you don't look like
you want to be a Warrior, though.
I have to become one.
Yet, I can't catch up with the rest…
It's not your fault.
You must think being a Warrior is ridiculous.
It's a stupid move to shorten your lifespan
and invade other countries for Marley.
Then why did you become
a Warrior, Mr. Ksaver?
I wanted to know the secrets
of the Titans.
I'm a researcher, after all.
They said it all started when the Founder
Ymir came in contact with something.
I wanted to know what
happened exactly at that moment.
I wanted it so much that I've shortened my own
lifespan to look into a Titan's memories.
That's why I'm completely useless in war.
However...
hate and conflict just sound ridiculous
compared to the mysteries of Titans.
That's why we're alike, for we both don’t care
to play this war game along with the others.
We are one of the few sensible people in this world.
This is for the best.
It's okay to stay in the internment
zone forever.
As long as we can stay alive.
We finally got something on them.
They're calling themselves
Eldian restorationists.
There are a lot of them this time.
I heard a traitor known as
the Owl started it.
We’ve already got a few leads.
All that is left to do is to get some proof.
It's only a matter of time to take them all down.
Zeke?
What's wrong?
Hurry up and eat.
M-My stomach is a little...
Dad.
Mom.
Please don't do anything
dangerous anymore.
If they find out, they will
send all of us to Paradis.
To the island of devils...
...where they will turn us into Titans.
Have you learned anything
from me all this time?
Unless someone stands up, everyone is
doomed to die inside these walls.
That's right.
We told you that this is a fight for your
future and the future of all Eldians, remember?
Even if it means I’ll end up like aunt Faye?
Zeke!
For starters, Faye was killed
only because this world is crazy!
We must fight to prevent anyone
from suffering the same fate as Faye!
We must take the strong Eldia back
from Marley and win the right we deserve!
[The available intelligence for now]
[Titan Research]
[The research concerning the unique power of
Subjects of Ymir to become Titans.
A field of study started since the Eldian Empire.
It encompasses not only the biology of Titans themselves,
but also the ways to deal with Eldians
who possess the power and their ideologies.
Though it has been researched for many years,
the truth of Titans still hasn’t been found.]
Unbelievable...
Your parents are restoratonists?!
Your whole family will be
sent to Paradis at this rate...
Yeah.
Mr. Ksaver.
Thank you for playing catch with me.
I'll remember you
even after I turn into a Titan.
Well then, I'm going.
Accuse them.
Eh?
That is the only way.
If you show your loyalty to Marley by
turning your parents in to the authorities,
you and your grandparents
should be safe.
No, I can't do that…
Zeke!
Your parents have done
something awful to you.
They gave up on you and didn't
care about your feelings at all.
They don’t love you.
Zeke...
...you did nothing wrong.
You're a smart and good boy.
Go easy on me, okay, Zeke?
Ah, I suppose it's too much
for an elderly to handle.
Hey, I'm not that old…
Mr. Ksaver!
My term is drawing to a close soon.
Yeah...
I don’t have much time left, but I don't
regret devoting myself to my research.
I should be able to present
my findings in one compilation.
Oh, what did you find out?
The various effects the Founding Titan
has brought to the Subjects of Ymir.
Ooh.
That memory control stuff?
Not just memory, it can also change
our body structure.
About 600 years ago, an epidemic killed
so many people that the population plunged.
But one day, the disease was
eradicated from the Eldian Empire.
The king at the time used the power
of the Founding Titan
and redesigned the bodies of
the Subjects of Ymir.
It proves that wherever we are,
we Subjects of Ymir are like
a part of the Founding Titan's body.
Scary, right?
Then...
Why did you give birth to another devil?
Can the Founding Titan make the Subjects
of Ymir lose their ability of giving birth?
If no more Subjects of Ymir were born...
Titans would vanish from this world
in the next hundred years.
The world wouldn't have to live
in fear of the Titans or suffer anymore.
Moreover, if we'd never been born...
...we would’ve never had to suffer!
Mr. Ksaver?
I never told you this.
But I once had a family.
I was young and stupid back then,
so I took off my armband.
I lived with my wife and we had a child,
all while keeping it a secret that I'm an Eldian.
My wife was a Marleyan.
However, there was no way I'd
be able to deceive her forever.
After she learned that I'm an Eldian...
She cut our son's throat and then her own’s,
and they both died.
I became a Warrior so that I can
kill myself in an honourable way.
But...
Over the last thirteen years.
I've devoted myself to studying Titans.
I'm so happy that I met you
and played catch with you.
You remind me of my dead boy.
And I tried to run away from my sins
using the power of the Titan.
If only I hadn't been born in this world!
I will inherit the Beast Titan.
Not for Marley.
I'll make the plan of retaking the Founding Titan
a success and save the world.
I'll free the people of the world
from their fear of the Titans...
...and free the Eldians from their suffering!
This is the information I never
told Marley about.
It's the way to break pass
the vow renouncing war.
And surprisingly enough, Zeke...
You are the only one who can make this happen.
When a Titan with royal blood makes physical
contact with the Founding Titan’s successor,
he should be able to draw out its power.
But you're not the one who
can wield that power.
The actual decision can only be made
by the one who possesses the Founding Titan.
In other words, your role is to be the key.
You must pass the Founding Titan
to someone you can trust.
Someone who can empathize
with our euthanasia plan.
You should be able to find that person.
I'll always be watching over you.
Zeke.
I will surely find it, Father.
Eren Yeager?
Yes.
Eren possesses the Founding Titan.
And what seems to be the vital
information is hidden in the basement
of his home in Shiganshina district
where he grew up.
Did you hear anything
from Eren about his father?
If I'm not mistaken,
Eren said he used to be a doctor
and is now missing.
How could this happen?
That father actually survived!
Eren...
We're his victims.
You’ve been brainwashed by your father.
I will surely come and save you someday!
You're starting to look like our father.
First off, Eren.
Thank you for agreeing
to meet me all the way here.
My thought is just like what
Yelena told you.
Would you support the Eldian
euthanasia plan?
It was four years ago.
One day, something happened that
opened our old man's memories.
The memory of him slaughtering
the royal family of the walls.
He moved around and smashed
young children like bugs.
I still remember how it felt.
If those children are still alive,
the Founding Titan will get
passed down to the royal family,
and we'll still be bound
by the vow renouncing war.
And we, humanity inside the walls,
will eventually die with it.
We survived because of their death.
I see.
So you believe that Father was right?
No.
Old man was mistaken.
And, I, whom he raised, am also
one of his mistakes.
If no Eldians had been born,
including those in this town,
none of them would have had to die
in the plan we're about to carry out.
There's no better salvation than
never having to be born in this world.
I'll do it.
I will put an end to 2,000 years of history
ruled by Titans with my very own hand.
I will keep going forward
until that day comes.
Isn't that right?
Brother.
Yes!
Yes. You're right.
Let's do it.
I would love to end this
with a firm handshake.
But, well, it would be bad if
we come into contact now.
Here, take this instead.
Eren.
We're going to save everyone.
The only salvation...
Eldian euthanasia...
What did you say?
Euthanasia?
Well, you're about to die inside
a Titan's stinky mouth,
all while hearing the sound of your own
body being chewed to pieces.
That's quite a merciful death
for you, don't you think?
Considering the lives of
my comrades that you stole.
I stole nothing.
I saved them.
I saved the children they would have...
...from this cruel world...
-Looks like you're growing another limb.
-Isn't that right?
Mr. Ksaver!
Please watch over me!
♫ In an instant ♫
♫ In an abandoned world ♫
♫ If you can’t fly, please tell him ♫
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes
I will be immortal ♫
[Preview]
The future we seek won't align.
We have no choice but to fight for it.
In Shiganshina, where everything began.
Next Episode: Above and Below
[#Above and Below]