[English subtitles are available]
Why...
...did you protect me?
It's nothing.
I don't have any particular reason.
I'm the one who killed
your precious comrade.
I'm also the one who beat
the guard with rock over and over.
Falco did nothing wrong.
You should just kill me, not him.
We won't.
But you do want to kill me, don't you?
I don't want to.
Kill, kill, kill, that's all
you ever talk about.
You're just like someone I knew.
E...
[Attack on Titan]
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Angels planning disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling on to
their very last coins ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
[#73 Savagery]
I want to have a quiet talk.
Conflict is not necessary
to solve Eldia's problems.
Hange and others will be fine.
We're just relocating them.
Eren.
We're the ones who wanted
to talk with you.
Why did you decide to attack
Marley on your own?
Have Zeke and Yelena really
won you over to their side?
I am free.
Eh?
Whatever I do,
whatever I choose,
it all comes from my own free will.
So everything you did after meeting
Yelena was out of your own free will?
Yes.
No, you're being controlled by them.
Even against people
from an enemy nation,
you're not the type of person who
would involve the innocents.
And you've always cared and
thought about us more than anyone else.
Isn't that right?
You saved me in that mountain hut,
and wrapped this scarf around me,
all because you're a kind perso--
I said keep your hands on the table.
I talked with Zeke in Liberio.
Just the two of us brothers.
Zeke knows more about Titans
than Marley does.
Armin.
You're still visiting Annie, aren't you?
Did you really do that
out of your own free will?
What?
If memory is what forms a person,
that means part of you has become Bertolt.
You're an enemy soldier who falls
in love with another enemy soldier.
Armin.
Your brain has been taken by Bertolt.
You're the one who is being
controlled by the enemy.
Eren, you--
Mikasa, you too.
The Ackerman clan was designed
to protect Eldia's king.
That moment, when you were
facing death, you obeyed my order.
"Fight."
Your instinct must've been awakened
at that instance.
All because you mistakenly recognized
me as the host you must protect.
You're wrong...
I'm wrong?
In what?
It's not... a mistake.
It's because of you, Eren, that
I was able to become strong.
It's all thanks to you!
Seems like once an Ackerman awakens,
they often suffer sudden headaches.
They say it happens because their true selves
try to resist being forced to protect the host.
Sounds familiar?
No...
That means...
No.
I am...
A clan created to follow orders at
the cost of losing their true selves.
In other words, you're a slave.
Stop it, Eren!
Do you know what I hate
the most in this world?
Those who are not free.
Or livestocks.
Eren!
Just looking at you irritates me.
I finally understand the reason why.
I couldn't stand looking at a slave who
always follows orders without question.
Since we were little...
Mikasa.
I have always hated you.
Eren!
How dare you make Mikasa--
Mikasa?
Your whole action in life was
dictated by your Ackerman blood.
No...
I'm not...
That's all you are.
Mr. Yeager?
It's nothing.
Hey, Armin.
We've never fought before, have we?
Do you know why?
-Because you’ve never been my match!
-Stop it...
Please...
Stop it...
Like I said at the start.
There'd be no need for us to fight
if you tell us Zeke's location.
So just come with us.
Take them.
Yes, sir.
And this brat who killed Sasha, too.
So...
What is it that you wanted
to say anyway?
Is hurting Mikasa the freedom you wanted?
Who is it?
Who is the real slave that
succumbed to a shitty bastard!
Who are you calling a slave?
Let's go.
To where?
To where everything began.
Shiganshina district.
This got to be a joke.
If it's about feeding someone to a Titan,
there's a better guy for it.
Eh?
What do you mean by that?
We will transfer Zeke's Beast
to someone else.
Turn one of those Yeagerists into
a Titan and feed Zeke to him.
I don't know if Eren is really
being controlled by Zeke.
But if they lose Zeke, they'll be done.
Tell Pixis that.
Go.
Are you serious, Captain?
If I rip this guy's limbs off, I'm sure
that geezer will get his shit straight.
Do you enjoy your book?
It's good, though it’s my
seventh time reading it.
I bet you couldn't concentrate
because of our conversation.
You're telling me to concentrate
on the book I've read for seven times?
By the way, do you still have
some wine left?
We've been here for a month.
There isn't a drop left.
Sheesh.
You guys sure thought up quite
a horrible torture.
Keep on reading.
Roger that, Boss.
Whatever Pixis says, I will slice him.
We have thirty fully armed soldiers
surrounding this forest from above.
Even if he transforms into a Beast Titan,
there's no escape for him.
This bearded bastard is our enemy all along.
Now that it's clear, there's no reason to
keep a hostage like him with his limbs on.
It has been long.
Erwin.
Looks like I can finally fulfill
the vow I made that time.
Your deaths meant something.
And finally, I'll be able to prove it.
Hey...
[The available intelligence for now]
[Spinal Fluid Wine]
[A Marleyan red wine mixed with Zeke 'Wonderboy' Yaeger's spinal fluid.]
[When drinking the wine, Subjects of Ymir consume Zeke's spinal fluid at the same time.]
[They will turn into Pure Titans and obey his orders]
[when hearing his 'scream'.]
[This is a cheap and effective way to conquer other nations.]
What was that?
My body went numb for a second.
-Me too.
-So did mine.
Eh? I didn't feel anything...
What's wrong?
It felt like electricity just ran
through my body.
Could it be...?
He really did it...
Zeke...
Farewell, Captain.
You're a caring leader.
You won't kill your innocent soldiers just
because they’ve grown a little bigger, right?
Wine?
Why do we need wine while on duty?
Captain!
This is rare Marleyan wine that only
the Military Police get to drink!
We deserve a little bit of fun.
We got black tea.
Captain!
What a pain.
Fine, take it.
Dammit!
Zeke's spinal fluid was in the wine?
When did he start all this?
There's no sign of them freezing up.
Was that one of his lies?
Dammit, so fast!
They're not moving like normal.
Is this also Zeke's doing?
Varis!
Are you still there?
My friends...
Time to say goodbye.
We couldn't trust each other.
The entire world's forces are about
to gather here on this island.
You have no idea what it means.
You thought you had strength,
time, and choices.
The reason why you have
these misunderstandings...
Levi, it was your fault.
Well...
It's not like you will understand
my true goal even if I tell you.
Hey, Eren.
Only you and I can understand.
Once I'm out of this forest,
I'll be there by your side soon.
Though, I wonder if you still remember
the place and time we agreed on.
Eren.
Go!
Oh, come on!
Not again!
Where are you?!
Where are you, Levi?!
There you are!
What happened to your adorable soldiers?!
Don't tell me, you killed them?
Poor things!
Branches?!
You're desperate, you bearded bastard.
All you had to do
was to sit and read books.
Since when did you get the wrong idea...
...that you can run away from me?
You really think I wouldn't kill my comrades
just because you turned them into Titans?
You didn't even know just how many
friends we've had to kill!
Hey there, bearded bastard.
Look at you, you stink,
filthy, ugly piece of shit.
You shit!
Oh well, don't worry.
I won't kill you.
Not yet.
As you already know, the Supreme
Commander Zackly's assassination
has destabilized the military and
the state of affairs within the walls.
But that has nothing to do with you recruits.
The 109th Training Corps will
operate as planned,
and practice defending Shiganshina district
in the case of a Titan attack.
Do you understand?!
Y-Yes, sir!
They're still making us practice
cutting a Titan's nape with a blade?
It's not like we will get
attacked by Titans anymore.
We're up against humans
outside the wall, you know?
My dad also told me
that we should be training
how to use guns and form
an Eldian army instead.
Times have changed.
Instructor Shadis is stuck in the past.
If there's any hope for Eldia, that would be
when the Yeagerist seizes the power.
Surma, he will hear you.
But doesn't everyone feel that way?
All of us should want Eren
Yeager to lead Eldia.
We need a strong leader who's
capable of making the hard decisions.
Wha--
Hange?!
Long time no see, Instructor.
Sorry to interrupt, but we've
occupied the facility.
We, whom you call the
"Yeagerists," I believe?
You'll be following our orders.
Yeagerists...
You seem to know your place well, Floch.
If you see yourselves as a bunch of pissants
who need to wave guns around to get anyone
to bother with them, then spot on--
Floch?!
I missed.
I thought I'd speed things up
by shooting him in the foot.
What do you want to say?
No, it has nothing do to with you.
We don't need old and useless men whose
trait is just being hard-headed.
From now on...
All you cadets! This is your time!
We Yeagerists have dedicated our hearts to save
Eldia that is on the verge of destruction!
Not for this outdated military,
but for the people on this island!
If you continue to subordinate
yourselves to the obsolete military,
you'll only be able to watch helplessly
as our enemies from outside trample over us!
I ask all of you!
What are you?
Will you live in the future with
Eren Yeager, the leader of Eldia?!
Or will you die here with Keith
Shadis and his old ways?!
We dedicate our hearts
for the future Eldia!
Good!
Then show me your resolve!
Beat Instructor Shadis
until he can no longer stand!
What?
He represents the vices
that we must weed out!
Purge him!
Anyone who can't will be detained!
Enough, Floch!
Don't be stupid!
Hange.
All these children would
be no match for me!
You did well.
We welcome all of you.
Now then, show us the way.
To where Zeke's being held.
Commander Hange.
Hey, let's go.
You awake?
Hey, wait.
Don't move.
There's a wire connected to the detonator
of that Thunder Spear right around your neck.
One false move, and you'll explode from
the stomach outward,
leaving you in two pieces at least.
It sure is tough not being able
to die at times like this.
Not that I sympathize with you.
You toyed with the lives of my soldiers.
Is it also part of your plan to end up
sobbing and being covered in your own filth?
Shut up.
If I don't cut you like this,
you will turn into a Titan again!
Where are... my... glasses?
Huh? How would I know?
You don't need glasses anymore.
Nice, Zeke.
You are becoming a better player.
Going to be a baseball player
when you grow up?
I can't...
Mr. Ksaver...
Because I... have... a mission.
♫ Lost in the blink one second ago ♫
♫ This forsaken world ♫
♫ If you're going to fly, pass it on to him ♫
♫ The countless birds with scorched wings ♫
♫ They scatter the ashes
as they smile in peace ♫
♫ Somebody, spread it ♫
♫ Along with the proof that I'm here ♫
♫ My bone already turned into ash,
but somehow I'm still alive ♫
[Preview]
He recalls nostalgic faces
within his vague memory.
What lies ahead is to realize
the mission he is given…
Next Episode: Sole Salvation
[#74 Sole Salvation]