[English subtitles are available]
It was called gas weapon.
The gas contained my spinal fluid.
Any subject of Ymir who inhaled
even just a small bit of the gas
would be frozen in-place.
He would lose control of his
body and fall unconscious.
All I had to do was give an order.
Through the Path, I could send the power
of Titans to those coordinates.
That's why the Titans from that
village moved according to my will.
It's not "that village."
It's Ragako.
That is the name of the village
that you slaughtered.
At least get the name right, you bearded shit.
Yeah, I wish I didn't
have to do it, too.
But if I hadn’t, they would've found out
that I was aligned to Eldian restoration,
thus making it impossible for me
to bring hope to this island.
...Didn't I already tell you
all this when I first landed?
Why do you keep asking me that?
Because I can tell that you
don't even feel a speck of guilt.
Not that I know whether you
really want to save Eldia or not,
but it's certain that human
lives mean nothing to you.
I bet you're not popular
with the ladies.
Don’t think that you can see through people.
I know.
And I was... popular enough.
Oh, is that so?
Anyway, when can I meet Eren
and begin the experiment?
It’s not up to me.
We're waiting for the order from HQ.
Tell them if they think they have
time to wait, they're gravely mistaken.
We are on the same page about that.
Captain Levi!
What?
Is that true?
[Attack on Titan]
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Angels planning disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
[#72 Children of the Forest]
What a nice place!
It's the first time
I've been in a place like this!
Me, too.
Isn't this great, kids?
Eat as much as you want today.
Yes!
What's wrong Mia, getting jitters like that?
Well, nothing...
You're too nervous, Mia.
Sheesh, can you be more like a village girl?
I-I'm not!
Kaya.
Is there really a Marleyan
POW working here?
It's true, so try to be nonchalant.
Soldiers come here often.
It will be great if we can at least
have a Marleyan acquaintance here.
Mr. Blouse!
Thank you for coming.
Thank you for inviting us.
Well, what do we have here?
Quite a crowd there.
I brought my family along.
You did say it's your treat.
Sorry.
Never mind.
It’s all on me.
Please, come on in.
Dad, I'm starving.
-I didn’t have any breakfast.
-I see, I see.
That's Mr. Nicolo, the Marleyan who
invited Mr. Blouse here.
Try asking him.
Mr. Braus is not a soldier,
Big sis was Mr. Braus daughter
When Mr. Nicolo came to mourn her death,
he said he wanted to treat us the meal
that he never got to make for her.
I personally think they were in love.
Ben.
What's wrong?
Did you get a stomach ache?
Ah, nothing.
Delicious!
I've never had a meal this
delicious in my entire life!
There's still more!
Just wait until you taste the main dish!
Nicolo, you got visitors.
Eh? Who would come at this hour?
The Survey Corps.
It's you guys?
What's wrong?
Something urgent?
I'm busy with entertaining some
important guests right now.
Well, it's fine. You can carry on.
But we have a few questions for you later.
Questions?
About what?
I mean, well, you also have...
concerns, don't you?
About the detained volunteers.
We need you to assist in the investigation.
Okay.
Got it.
You guys can wait here for a while.
Oh, never knew about this room.
I bet it's a room exclusively
for those Military Police.
This is...
the wine that people in the military talk about.
I heard only the officers
have the right to drink this.
What did you say?
We're officers too in
Survey Corps, right?
Yeah.
We should deserve some treat
once in a while.
Just a sip…
Get your hands off that!
What's wrong, Nicolo?
I was just joking around.
No need to overreact.
The Eldians can’t afford such wine!
Nicolo...
You're still saying that?
Drinking wine has nothing to do
with who I am.
Don't touch me, Eldians.
Don't act like we're buddies just
because we know each other.
Then who do you think you are?
In here you are...
"Nothing but a POW"?
Now we're even, Eldians.
What happened to him?
Dammit!
Hell if I know.
Now.
Ugh! My stomach hurts!
Are you okay, Ben?
Did you eat something wrong?
Going to the bathroom might help!
And I may even be able to help my brother!
Good luck.
You kids.
This isn't the way to the bathroom.
We're not looking for the bathroom, Mr. Nicolo.
We came from Marley.
We are Warrior Candidates!
Huh?
We believe this island will soon receive
massive attack from armies around the world.
Please hold on until then.
And also tell this to your
fellow Marleyans.
H-Hold on a second.
Why are the warrior candidates here?
The devils launched an attack
on Liberio district.
We jumped onto a retreating enemy
airship and landed here.
Did you...
...kill anyone?
Like a...
...female soldier?
Yes, I took her down.
But only a few of them.
Gabi!
-We will have our revenge
-Wait!
-for what they did to our home soon.
-Hey!
We definitely won't lose to
those underhanded devils…
Gabi, stop it!
What is it?
So you...
killed her....
So you're the one who killed Sasha?!
Falco?
Hey!
Falco!
Are you okay? Falco!
Falco, wake up!
Hear me!
Come on!
Shit!
Falco!
Nicolo?!
What did you do to Ben and Mia?
She is the one who killed Sasha.
She took your daughter's life.
She's still a kid, but she's a
well-trained Marleyan soldier.
She pulled the trigger
inside the retreating airship
and killed her.
Daughter...?
Mr. Blouse.
Here.
If you can't kill her,
then I will do it for you.
You won't mind, right?
This is bad!
Everyone, come here!
Huh?
What?
The kid who killed Sasha?
What does this mean, Nicolo?
I heard she was on the run.
What are you trying to do?
Hey!
Stay away! Back off!
I'm just going to avenge Sasha!
Don't move!
Stop it.
Falco is innocent!
How is he related to you?
He ended up like this
because he tried to protect you!
Is he someone special to you?
I also had someone special to me!
She's an Eldian!
The descendant of devils!
But she enjoyed my cook more
than anyone else did!
She saved me from this shitty war.
She had me realize that it’s the real me
when I cook something that makes people happy!
Her name is Sasha Blouse.
That is the name of the girl you killed!
I lost people who were special to me, too!
Because Sasha Braus shot them!
That's why I got my revenge!
She's the one who killed them first!
I don’t care about who did it first!
Come to your senses!
You're a Marleyan soldier, aren't you!
I'm sure that devil woman
brainwashed you!
Don't let the devils win!
Nicolo.
Give me the knife.
Please.
That's enough.
Mr. Blouse.
Please put down the knife.
Sasha was a hunter.
What?
I taught her how to use a bow
when she was little,
and we'd go hunting in the forest.
'Cause that's how we lived.
But...
I knew that the time has changed,
and we couldn't keep living that way.
So I made Sasha leave the forest.
Then the world got bigger.
Sasha became a soldier
and went off to attack other lands,
shot people,
and then got herself killed.
I only wanted her to leave the forest.
Turns out, the world was a colossal forest,
where it was still about
killing or being killed.
I believe Sasha got killed 'cause she
wandered too long in that forest.
We've gotta at least get
the kids outta this forest.
Or else...
We would just keep on circling
around the same place.
That's why it is the adults’ job
to shoulder the sins and hatred of the past.
Mr. Nicolo.
Let Ben go.
Good.
Lisa, move him slowly.
Yes.
Show me your wound.
Mia.
Are you okay?
You really...
...don't hate me?
-How dare you killed her!
-Hey! Stop!
-Murderer!
-Kaya!
I thought you were my friend!
-Take her to the other room. Come on.
-Why!? Why did you do it!?
The main dish has gone cold now.
Hange.
Please rinse that kid's mouth for me.
Some of that wine got in.
Eh?
But... it's probably too late.
Is there anything in that wine?
I think...
...it's Zeke's spinal fluid.
[Currently Shareable Information:]
[Marleyan Cuisine]
[Marleyan local cuisine mainly consists of seafood such as fish, shrimp, and shellfish.]
[It covers a lot of cooking methods such as frying, steaming, marinating, or stewing,]
[and it is loved by both people inside and outside of Marley.]
[The red wine produced in southern Marley
is considered a staple flavoring ingredient in the country, but it can also be paired with meals.]
Zackly was killed?
Yes.
The Yeagerists practically have control
over everything within the walls.
It is believed that all the chaos is being
caused by Zeke, through Eren and Yelena.
And then?
Eren will be brought to Zeke, following
the Yeagerists' demand.
Is Pixis really going to
obediently roll with it?
As you thought, the commander
remains steadfast.
The military plans to have
someone eat Eren, right?
By taking advantage of us.
That is right.
I've saved Eren's life over and over.
Many of my comrades died each time.
I did it because I believed it was
the best hope for humanity's survival.
And this is where that
belief has gotten me.
It's like an awful joke.
Just what was that hope
we looked forward to?
All that hardship has led to this farce?
You gotta be kidding me.
This got to be a joke.
If it's about feeding someone to a Titan,
there's a better option.
Eh?
What do you mean?
Zeke's spinal fluid is in the wine?
I don't have any proof.
But...
the survey ships have been packed
with this type of wine since the very beginning.
A short-term surveying voyage shouldn’t
need wine, much less one in such a huge amount.
One more time.
And also...
Just as I started to settle
here as a cook,
I was told to serve it to the military,
-starting with high-ranking officers.
-One more.
By whom?!
Yelena.
As far as I know, she was the
one who started all this.
I'm not sure about the other volunteers.
I-I've never heard about this before.
But that doesn't make sense!
Eldians will freeze once they
drink Zeke's spinal fluid, right?
That's what Zeke said.
It's not like anyone had seen it,
so we can't even confirm it.
But...
The effect of that one lie is enormous.
We won't even suspect getting dozed with
his spinal liquid if we don't see the symptoms.
But... still...
That's just your theory, right?
Yeah.
I have no proof.
But every Marleyan soldier knows about it.
Just how Zeke's spinal fluid
has been used in the past.
Around ten years ago, Marley took down
the enemy nation's capital in one night.
Hundreds of Titans appeared in
the town out of nowhere, after all.
They must be plotting
to do something like that.
Though, why I was asked to give the military
higher-ups that suspicious wine is beyond me.
So when you took that wine
from me back then...
...it was to protect us?
Dunno.
Just what am I doing?
I was supposed to survey the island
of devils and save the world.
Now that I’ve told you all about this,
I'm sure I won't live for long.
But Mr. Blouse.
I still can't be
as forgiving as you, but...
...I hope this can make up
even a little for what I did.
I tried to kill a child...
What's wrong with me?
Nicolo...
Why...
...did you protect me?
It's nothing.
I don't have any particular reason.
I'm the one who killed
your precious comrade.
I'm also the one who beat
the guard with rock over and over.
Falco did nothing wrong.
You should just kill me, not him.
We won't.
But you do want to kill me, don’t you?
I don't want to.
Kill, kill, kill, that's all
you can talk about.
You're just like someone I knew.
What's wrong?
Commander?
Floch?!
Glad to find you.
You should know Zeke's location.
You're going to take us to him.
Listen, we have no intention
to oppose you guys.
We already rejected that offer.
We won't negotiate with the military.
And why is that?
It was Eren's decision.
Commander Pixis would never bet
the fate of the island on our hands.
He's probably busy right now
trying to devise a plan
to steal the Founding Titan from Eren
when they're showing us the way.
You're delusional.
Or is that what your friend
from Garrison told you?
Do I look like one of your
obedient subordinates
who will answer all your questions?
Or should I prove it to you that
I'm no longer your subordinate?
I suggest you come with us
before I do that.
Dammit!
How did they know we're here?
Griez?
Was this Yelena's order?
Nicolo.
You've gotten too close to Eldians.
I knew this day would come.
Thank God I didn’t tell you
how to contact them.
Listen to me, Floch!
There is no time for us
to fight amongst ourselves!
Wine contaminated with Zeke's spinal fluid
has been served throughout the military!
We’ve all fallen into Zeke’s trap!
Even if that's true, the idiotic military
police will just look even stupider.
Is that all?
I didn't say a thing about
the military police drinking the wine.
Could it be...
you guys knew about the wine?!
Please keep your voice down
within the restaurant.
We're taking off.
Yeah.
That voice just now...
Did you come with Floch and others?
Yeah.
I wanted to...
...talk with you guys.
♫ In an instant ♫
♫ In an abandoned world ♫
♫ If you can’t fly, please tell him ♫
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes
I will be immortal ♫
[Preview]
The Yeagerists have captured
Hange and others.
Eren said to Mikasa and Armin
as he gazed at them.
"I want to talk."
Next Episode: Savagery
[Savagery]