Mademoiselle?
Mademoiselle Harmon, vous êtes là?
I'm coming.
Jesus.
Shit!
Je descends, tout de suite.
Yeah.
Fuck!
Je vous en prie.
Ne regarde pas.
Thank you.
Fuck!
I'm sorry.
What are we supposed to do with her?
They're sending someone.
There's hardly a scratch on her.
It's a goddamn miracle.
I doubt she'll see it that way.
You understand, dear,
your mother's passed on?
You know what that means, don't you?
"Passed on"?
Well…
I'm sure she's gone on to a better place,
and, someday, you'll get to see her again.
"Orphaned by
yesterday's collision on New Circle Road,
Elizabeth Harmon
surveys a troubled future."
"Elizabeth, nine years old,
was left without family by the crash."
"Her mother, Alice Harmon,
was pronounced dead at the scene."
And the father?
Doesn't say.
I would guess that,
like most men who live around there,
he was yet another victim
of a carefree life.
Poor dear.
Let's welcome her, shall we?
Welcome, Elizabeth.
Good luck to you, dear.
Here we are.
This is our chapel,
the domain of Miss Lonsdale.
How do you do, Elizabeth?
I also teach etiquette
to the young ladies.
Mr. Fergussen, this is Elizabeth Harmon.
You're all a bunch of fucking cocksuckers!
Jolene.
I got it.
Jolene, that mouth
will be the death of you!
- Oh, fuck you, you cocksucker.
- You can't yell like that.
In there is our classroom.
You'll meet your teachers on Monday.
Two times six.
And this is our day room,
where you will have all your meals,
and enjoy daily socialization.
Good morning, Mrs. Deardorff.
Good morning, girls.
Home sweet home.
Come on, let's get you settled.
We have 21 girls here,
and they are all just as sweet as you.
And here is your special place.
- Shoo! Go, go, go.
- Okay.
You can put your clothes down here.
And your toothbrush can go right here.
And any other personal items, there.
Oh!
Show her to me.
Come on, sit.
I know that, at this moment,
all you're feeling is loss.
But after grief brings you low,
prayer and faith will lift you high.
High enough for you
to see a new path for yourself.
I think, Elizabeth,
you're going to find
a much different life here.
A better one than you might have had.
And I'm sure that you and I
are going to be good friends.
Hmm.
That should do nicely.
Mm-hmm.
I think we'll burn this one.
Get dressed.
We have one more stop.
Mr. Fergussen will take good care of you.
I'll see you at dinner.
The green ones are the best.
What are they?
Vitamins.
Magic vitamins.
I were you, I'd save
the green ones up for the night time.
Otherwise, they turn off
right when you need them to turn on.
If you know what I mean.
Hey, what's your name, girl?
- Beth.
- Jolene.
Your mama and daddy dead?
What's the last thing
they said to you before they died?
I ask everybody that.
We get some really fun answers.
Close your eyes.
I don't remember.
Someday, you might.
If you do, you let me know.
Green's to even your disposition.
Orange and brown is for building
a strong body. Take 'em both.
I thought I told you to wait
and take those vitamins at bedtime.
What is this?
Fish.
Far as we know.
We eat it every Friday.
You gotta eat every bite,
or they'll tell Mrs. Deardorff about you,
and you won't get adopted.
Alice, come on, open the door.
- It's taken me a whole month to find you.
- Good reason.
Whatever this is, whatever you're doing,
it's nuts, even for you.
- I don't expect you to understand...
- What I understand
is you're not taking care of yourself.
So, we'll take…
Isn't it beautiful?
Let me come in and talk to Lizzie.
Make sure she's okay.
Oh, you think I'd hurt her?
She's happy here.
This is where she belongs.
You honestly believe our daughter
belongs in a trailer
in the middle of nowhere?
Who says she's ours?
- Don't do that, Alice.
- And she doesn't like being called Lizzie.
All right, Alice, you win.
I can't fight with you anymore.
And I can't keep chasing you
around everywhere,
if all you do is run away again.
I'm sorry, Paul.
Once I drive away, I'm not coming back.
Miss Harmon, finished already?
Why don't you take the erasers
down to the basement and clean them?
You're all fucking cocksuckers,
and you're the biggest one of them all.
Never met anyone who liked
the taste of soap as much as you do.
Where you going, Harmon?
Good morning, girls.
Good morning, Mrs. Deardorff.
Mary-Sue, aren't you a lucky girl?
You really impressed the Spellmans.
I heard their house is so big.
Let's get your suitcase and pack up.
Nicely, like I taught you.
Yeah, the socks first, remember.
Hmm.
That is not fair. She got here after you.
Most of us are lifers.
- Been here a long time.
- Don't forget your headband.
Nobody's gonna come for us now.
We're too old.
And don't dawdle.
- I wish it was me.
- Or too Black.
- Maybe someone will come through.
- Someday.
What do you want, child?
You should be in chapel.
What's that game called?
You should be upstairs with the others.
I don't wanna be with the others.
I wanna know what that is you're playing.
It's called chess.
Will you teach me?
I don't play strangers.
- Sweet dreams, ladies.
- Good night, Fergussen.
"Good night, good night!"
"Parting is such sweet sorrow,
so I shall say good night
till it be morrow."
You were right.
The vitamins work better at night.
How many you take?
I don't know.
Sometimes I skip a day,
or a bunch of days,
then take two or three.
I like the way it feels.
I bet you do.
You just be careful
you don't get too used to that feeling.
I'm not a stranger.
I live here.
I already know some of it…
From watching.
Girls do not play chess.
That one moves up and down,
or back and forth,
all the way, if there's space to move in.
But that one can only go up.
That tall one can go any way it wants.
And this one?
On the diagonals.
One square diagonal,
plus one square straight.
Let's play a game.
I play White.
Now or never.
That's called the Scholar's Mate.
- How do you do it?
- Not today.
- Show me.
That's called the Scholar's Mate.
How do you do it?
You resign now.
Resign?
That's right, child.
When you lose the queen that way…
You resign.
- No.
- Yes, you have resigned the game.
- You didn't tell me that in the rules.
- It's not a rule, it's sportsmanship.
- I wanna finish.
- No.
- You've got to finish.
You lost.
- Please!
- The game is over.
You cocksucker.
Get out.
Check.
Mate.
Morning, cracker.
Jolene?
What do you want?
I want to know what a cocksucker is.
Shit!
Okay. Um…
Do you know what a cock is?
I don't think so.
It's what boys have.
The picture in the back
of the health book, it's like a thumb.
Well, honey,
girls like to suck on that thumb.
Do you?
Haven't tried one yet.
Isn't that where they pee?
I expect it wipes clean.
You should have green,
leafy vegetables at least once a day,
legumes a few times a week,
and stay away from tobacco
and any and all forms of alcohol.
I also like to inspect my stool
at least, uh, three times a week.
It should appear firm but not hard,
a clear sign of dehydration.
Now, which is why we should be drinking
several glasses of water a day,
nature's wonderful lubricant.
You're gloating.
I'm not.
- It was close.
- I still beat you.
Could have beat me sooner.
- You should learn the Sicilian Defense.
- What's that?
When White moves to king four,
Black does this.
- Then what?
- Knight to KB3.
What's KB3?
King's bishop three,
where I just put the knight.
The squares have names?
If you play well, they have names.
- Show me.
- Not now. Let's play again.
You're mad.
I am not mad.
Just play.
There are other strategies
you'll need to learn, down the road.
The Levenfish Variation.
The Najdorf Variation.
Show me.
Levenfish.
Najdorf.
Let's play again.
Elizabeth!
I'm sorry, Mrs. Deardorff.
- Mom, guess what?
- I don't know. What?
- Mom, I've started my first period.
- Well, what do you know?
- That isn't one you taught me.
- So?
But is that one of those things,
like the Sicilian Defense?
Stop!
Those things are called openings.
Is that one of them?
Yes.
The Queen's Gambit.
I'm playing White?
From now on, we take turns.
It's the way the game should be played.
Then, how come I couldn't go first before?
Play.
Check.
Mate.
Is that whiskey?
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
And don't tell.
I won't.
Modern Chess Openings.
It's the best book for you.
It will tell you all you wanna know.
You'll need to learn chess notation
before you can read it.
The names of the squares.
I'll teach you now.
Am I good enough now?
How old are you?
Nine.
Nine years old.
I'll be ten in November.
To tell you the truth of it, child…
You're astounding.
"Nobody heard him,
the dead man,
but still he lay moaning."
"I was much further out than you thought,
and not waving but drowning."
"Poor chap,
he always loved larking, and now…
He's dead."
"It must have been too cold for him.
His heart gave way, they said."
"Oh, no, no, no,
it was too cold always."
"Still, the dead one lay moaning."
"I was much too far out all my life,
and not waving, but drowning."
This is Mr. Ganz from the chess club.
- Chess club?
- We play at a club.
I'm also coach of the high school team.
Duncan High?
Would you like to play me a game?
You play the color you choose.
This one.
Ah, the Réti Opening.
That's mate in three.
Well, you certainly
know the game, young lady.
Do you have a team here?
The other girls,
do they have a chess club?
So, where do you play?
Down here.
Mr. Shaibel said
you play a few games every Sunday.
What do you do in between?
I play in my head.
In your head?
On the ceiling.
Oh…
Before I forget…
I brought you…
A present.
Go ahead, open it.
Well?
Thank you very much.
Do you want another game?
Check.
Beth…
I've moved my queen to rook four.
Check.
The bishop blocks.
Queen takes king's pawn.
Castles.
Knight takes knight.
Mate in three.
First check is with the queen.
The king must take.
Then, the bishop checks on knight five…
And it's mate next.
Sweet Jesus.
I have to go now.
Would you mind, Beth…
If I took your picture?
I'd love to tell
the kids in chess club about you.
How about you stand next to Mr. Shaibel?
Closer.
That's it.
Say queen!
Queen.
Nine times four is?
Hiya, Marge.
Hi, I'm sorry I'm late,
but I ran into Jean, here.
Oh, Jean, this is Ed Reardon.
The Ed I was telling you about.
- Hello.
- How do you do?
And this is Jack Connors.
- Jean Bassett, from over at Morrisville.
- How do you do, Jean?
- Hello.
- Here, you can sit here.
- Thank you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Would you like something? Malt or soda?
- Hey, Mrs. Deardorff wants to see you.
A well-mannered group, I think.
You notice their good manners right away.
Mr. Ganz tells me
that you are a gifted child.
He has an unusual request to make.
He would like you
to be taken to the high school on…
- On Thursday.
In the afternoon.
He maintains
that you are a phenomenal chess player.
He would like you
to perform for the chess club.
We have a dozen members,
and I was suggesting to Mrs. Deardorff
that you come along
and play all of them in a simultaneous.
In a what?
At the same time.
We like to give our girls a chance
for experience outside
whenever we can, but…
I'm a bit wary of letting Elizabeth
go off to the local high school.
Oh, well, I would chaperone.
I'd pick her up, take her to the school,
then bring her back.
I was thinking a young lady
might also accompany her.
Well, I assumed that you would come,
as my guest.
Oh.
No, I…
I couldn't possibly
abandon my duties here.
Well, what if Shirley Munson,
club treasurer
and one of my best students,
she comes along?
What do you say, Elizabeth?
Do you want to play chess
at the high school?
Yes, I'd like to.
Okay.
It's settled, then.
Mr. Ganz and, uh…
- Charlotte?
- Shirley.
Shirley, yes.
They will pick you up,
let's say after lunch on Thursday?
Perfect.
I'll see you then.
Elizabeth.
I'm told that you've been playing chess
with our custodian.
With Mr. Shaibel.
Yes, ma'am.
This is very irregular, Elizabeth.
Have you gone to the basement?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, we can't have that.
As much as Methuen believes in excellence,
we can't have you
playing chess in the basement.
I believe that we have chess sets
in the game closet.
I'll have Fergussen look into that.
That'll be all, Elizabeth.
Mind your manners at the high school.
Helen Deardorff.
- There's one missing.
- That's it.
Next.
It's my turn, Harmon.
Where are the green ones?
You don't get them anymore.
There they are, right behind you.
I know where they are, Harmon,
but I'm not gonna give you any.
New state law.
No more tranquilizers for kids.
- Go figure.
- Harmon.
"Go thou further off."
"Bid me farewell,
and let me hear thee going."
- What?
- Beat it.
Did Fergussen give you any green pills?
Extra ones?
No, honey, I wish he would.
But they got the state after them
for what they've been doing
with those pills.
They're still there.
In the big jar.
That a fact?
I ain't noticed.
You're having withdrawal symptoms?
I don't know.
What are those?
Withdrawal, like…
I don't know, you getting edgy?
Yeah, you are.
You look around,
there's gonna be some jumpy orphans
around here the next few days.
Harmon.
You all right?
- Do you play the King's Gambit?
- No.
It's my favorite.
Did you know chess is older than checkers?
- No.
- By, like, 400 years.
Wait!
Can I talk to Beth?
- Just for a second, wish her luck.
- Sure, go ahead.
Good luck.
Take your seats and be quiet, please.
Charles Levy will take board number one
since he's our top player.
The rest of you can sit where you want to.
There will be no talking during play.
Do I start now?
With board number one.
And then I go on to the next one?
That's right.
They can't respond
until you've opened at every board.
What surprised me was how bad they played.
They left backward pawns
all over the place,
and their pieces were wide open for forks.
A few of them tried stupid mating attacks.
But I took care of them.
This boy, Charles Levy,
he was supposed to be the best.
I had his pieces tied up in 15 moves.
I mated him in six more,
with a knight-rook combination.
Mr. Ganz told me I beat them all
in an hour and 20 minutes.
It felt good.
I've never won anything before.
You should get back.
You can have the rest.
- Jolene.
- Hey.
Do you have any more vitamins?
Don't be rude.
This is Samantha. She just got here.
Haven't you got even just one?
How'd the exhibit go?
You do okay?
- Fine, but I need...
- I don't want to hear about it.
Hello, Samantha.
Jesus. Renounce him, so all can hear.
I cannot renounce him, sire. Nor can you.
He is my king and yours as well.
He is the son of God.
And that is your answer?
Yes, sire.
Tribune Gallio,
we decree that you be taken immediately
to the palace archery field
and put to death for high treason.
No, Diana.
No, there's no reason for it.
Sire, Marcellus is my chosen husband.
I ask to go with him.
Bathroom.
Hurry up.
Stand back! You're not on trial!
There's no evidence against you!
Then if it please you, sire,
I'll provide evidence.
A traitor!
And a conspirator against the state!
No, not Marcellus!
That's why he hasn't come to you.
Stop it!
But in you,
noble blood has turned to poison.
You corrupt Rome
with your spite and malice.
- Stop! Stop it!
- You should be Caesar!
Stop it!
As for me, I have found another king.
I want to go with my husband…
Into his kingdom.
Then by the gods you shall!
Go, both of you!
Into your kingdom!
They're going into a better kingdom.
They're going into a better kingdom!
They're gonna meet their king!
They're going to meet their king!
All right, girls.
Let's all have some cocoa
and discuss what we've learned.
- Elizabeth!
- Mama?
Elizabeth.