♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 20=
What happened?
Who did that to you?
It has nothing to do with you.
You'd better figure out
how to beg for mercy after being
beaten up by me.
Find me a shirt.
Okay. This way, please.
Wait for me on the stage.
Is he sure that he can fight?
Brother Dai, are you sure he
still can fight?
Get on the stage.
Let's go.
Young Master, it's better that you
quit the battle now.
Shut up. Bring me my shirt.
Yes.
He has suffered from a serious injury.
We should be able to win this time.
Not sure.
Once the battle begins, Ning Rong Rong
performs Support Branch Martial Soul.
Tang San uses Blue Silver Plant to
control his movement.
And the rest take turns to
attack him with me.
Don't give him a break.
Act quickly to end the battle.
But he is your brother.
He was injured.
That's too harsh.
I am the commander.
I will conduct all the moves.
Brother Dai. Brother Dai.
How about me?
Wait for us down there. Prepare
to treat at any time.
Are both of us not joining the fight?
Support Branch Soul Masters
don't have to fight.
But we have prepared it for so long.
That's right.
He is here.
Ou Si Ke, give me one sausage.
The fight hasn't even started yet and
you already feel hungry?
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
Here you are.
Thanks.
Take this.
What do you mean? Trying to bribe me?
Or do you want to surrender?
This is the Soul Skill of Ou Si Ke.
Your Soul Power will recover
after eating this.
Since this is a Soul Battle,
we Seven Devils will do it
fair and square.
Otherwise, others might think we're
taking advantage of you.
And we don't hope to win in a
one-sided battle.
Win?
You're overconfident.
I don't have to utilize the full power
fighting with all of you.
Ready?
Yes!
Let's go!
Mutated Martial Soul?
Attack again.
Zhu Zhu Qing.
Take the sausage.
Regain your Soul Power.
Give me one too.
Are you injured?
No. I'm hungry.
But it is for Soul recovery.
It is not a snack.
Let it be.
You don't have anything else to do anyway.
That's so irritating.
It makes me feel like we are
not part of them.
That's why I said.
What's the point of being a Soul Master?
Attack again.
I think it is no use to attack head-on.
Keep attacking.
Do you feel hungry or want to recover?
We won't win fighting that way.
What should we do?
We need to come up with a tactic.
What can we do?
Yeah. What can we do?
Five of them can't even wear him down.
What's the use of adding both of us?
I have an idea now.
I need your cooperation.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Failure is not a big deal.
Tell us.
How are we gonna do it?
He couldn't take it anymore.
Increase in speed.
All of you are too weak.
You lose.
Sister Qing.
Is there any point
to continue the fight?
As promised.
You need to go with me if you lose.
Seven versus one. We are not yet done.
What can the three of you do?
And both of us too.
You are just Support Branch Soul Masters.
Do you want to join the fight?
I will leave it to you both.
What is this?
Props.
What?
Props for magic shows.
You never saw that?
Ridiculous.
Ma Hong Jun.
Martial Soul bursts in a sudden.
You are just betting the farm.
Done playing?
That's enough!
Wu.
Speed Boost. Strength Boost.
Good idea. Anymore?
No more.
We shall end the fight then.
Yes. You lost.
I lost?
When battling in the Soul Arena,
those who step out of the
arena lose the fight.
First, we use props to attract
your attention.
Then, I use my Blue Silver Plant
to control your movement.
Lastly, Wu kicks you out of
the arena.
You use all the tricks
to force me to step out of the arena?
That's right.
The purpose of diverting your attention
and releasing the smoke bomb
is to kick you out of the arena.
According to strength, you lost.
According to the rules, you lost.
Okay. You can stay.
Let's meet again in Martial Soul City.
Wait. Martial Soul City?
Let's meet in the grand final
of Douluo Continent Soul Master
School Contest.
What contest?
Soul Master School Contest?
The teamwork just now,
did all of you ever practice it?
We find you before when we
practice together.
But...
I know.
I always thought that
Support branch Soul Masters
shouldn't join a battle.
So I didn't think much about it.
I was running out of ideas just now.
So I planned to give it a try.
I'm sorry.
I know you are supposed to be the
commander.
You can blame me if you're
not satisfied.
Master.
I'm the one who let Tang San and others
practice tactical exercise.
Dai Mu Bai.
Being strong is not only about power.
It can be the techniques and brain.
I started to doubt
whether my insistence
is a mistake.
Why do you think that way?
I always believe that
a Soul Master needs to have absolute
power to win.
But after experiencing what
happened today,
I'm not sure whether
my thought was right anymore.
Your Soul Skill is White Tiger.
Placing power as a priority is
not a mistake.
But you can't depend solely on power.
Battle requires the techniques.
You have to defeat the opponent with minimal
damage and loss.
Isn't that better?
I never thought about that before.
What I learned since I was a kid
is to win whatever the cost is.
The loser doesn't have the right to speak,
nor the right to survive.
That's why you're so
desperate for power.
Yes. At the Rose Inn,
Tang San defeated Mr. Zhao with
his strange tricks.
I feel so irritated.
Because he broke my rules.
Human is alive but rules are not.
You shouldn't be limited by rules.
A few days ago, Ning Rong Rong
and Ou Si Ke
defeated Ma Hong Jun together.
I thought that's because they
have been lucky enough.
But in today's battle,
I saw everyone helping each other.
Then I realized that as a team,
cooperation is the most important thing.
Master, as the leader of Si Lan Ke,
do you think I'm not good at giving commands?
Your frontal attack is the most powerful
among the seven of you.
Although you are good at the
sneak attack,
in an excellent team,
the Power Attack Soul Master
is the core.
The Support branch Soul Master is the base.
The Sensitivity Soul Master
is the eyes.
And the Controlling Soul Master
is the Soul.
I got it.
From now on, the commander of Si Lan Ke
is Tang San.
He can do better than me.
No. I'll just give commands
on the battlefield.
But you are the leader.
The leader of Si Lan Ke Seven Devils
will always be Brother Dai.
You are a man. Come on.
I can finally join the battle.
And we won.
Frankly speaking,
I... Since...
From the moment I knew I'm
a Support branch Soul Master,
I felt that I couldn't go up the stage,
and I could only stand at the side.
But today I proved to myself that
I'm a man.
Glad that you know you're a man.
Stop crying. You're already ugly.
Crying makes you more ugly.
What are you talking about?
Wasn't I cool on the stage?
I look handsome, right?
Thanks for the help just now.
We are teammates.
Wu.
Does your leg still hurt?
Ou Si Ke's Martial Soul can help me
to regain my energy.
But I still have to take
good care of my injury.
It's okay. It will be fine
after two days.
I'll carry you.
I might be heavy for you.
Come.
How do you feel?
Not heavy at all.
Are you okay?
Now I find that you're a
little bit heavy.
I'm all right.
Let me down now.
I was lying. You're not heavy at all.
Tang San has learned to tell lies.
Tell me. Tell me.
Wasn't I stunning?
When I called you
and we cooperated well, wasn't that cool?
Yes.
Wu. Hold my ears.
From now on,
when you pull my left ear,
I will go to the left.
When you pull the right one,
I will go to the right.
But will that hurt your ears?
Let's try it.
How do you feel? Interesting?
Interesting.
Let me carry you.
Does your leg still hurt?
Not anymore.
Go away.
Let's try.
What happened?
Someone is following us.
Since when?
Since we battled in the arena.
Was it not enough to watch during the fight?
Uncle. It's been a long time
since we last met.
You have been hurt badly.
Dai Wei Shi might hide his strength.
He is too powerful for me.
And you can't make it too overt.
Quickly go back to treat your injuries.
Use the remaining time to recover.
One more thing.
I saw Yu Tian Heng from
Tian Dou Imperial School.
I guess he also comes for those people
from Shi Lan Ke.
Things are getting interesting.
Stop touching it. Drink some water.
Your wounds are still swelling.
It must have been hurt badly.
These few days
you must rest properly.
Do you hear me?
So jealous of you.
I want to get some rest too.
I'm tired too.
You don't need that.
You don't have any injuries.
I walked back here yesterday.
Wu was carried by Tang San
along the way.
If you asked for it,
I'm sure Ou Si Ke would carry you too.
I don't need that.
He cried and laughed non-stop along
the way yesterday.
Nobody noticed that.
He was like a weirdo.
But he keeps protecting you.
So what?
It means that he likes you.
Then do you like
Brother Dai too?
What are you talking about?
Last night in the arena,
you were attacked
for trying to save Brother Dai.
You were protecting him all the time.
That indicates that you like him too.
Wu was right.
I helped him because he is my teammate.
Really? But I can see
you are blushing.
I feel hot.
Hot?
But we don't feel it.
Yeah.
I feel hot and also hungry.
Come. Let's get some food.
Stay here and wait for us.
I want to go too.
Wu.
If I am killed by her...
Let's go.
You must take revenge for me!
Slowly.
Wu.
Tang San.
Let me put on the medicine for you.
Did you buy it from Suo Tuo City
early in the morning?
If you can get better quickly,
I will feel relieved.
Come.
It might hurt a little bit.
Try to endure it.
Does it hurt?
I will do it gently.
It seems that it doesn't hurt that much
when I am staring at you.
Keep staring at me then.
Because I'm your brother.
Brother.
You.
You only call me that when
nobody around.
I didn't.
Can you help me braid my hair too?
Wait a second. Let me dress
your wounds first.
Let's eat later.
Wu.
You're back.
Tang San.
What are you both doing?
Braiding hair.
You let him braid your hair?
Anything wrong with that?
Yeah. Anything wrong?
Girls can't simply let a guy
braid their hair.
But I'm her brother.
Yeah. He is my brother.
Wu. I'm done.
Your braiding skill is the best.
He is smiling.
Take care of your wounds.
Don't move around.
Thanks for helping me
take care of Wu.
I'll take my leave now.
It's our duty.
Why?
We are supposed to ask you that.
What are you talking about?
Don't you feel it strange?
Yeah. You're very strange.
How does that have anything
to do with me?
I meant you.
What's wrong with me?
Tang San often helps you braid your hair?
Yeah.
Do you like Tang San?
Yes, I like him.
Did you hear that? I knew it.
He is my brother.
Of course I like him.
Not the kind of feeling
between siblings.
Don't act like you don't know.
Which kind of feeling do you mean?
Wu, listen carefully.
Do you have any other feelings
on Tang San?
Other feelings?
What do you mean?
I mean, other than treating
him as your brother,
do you think both of you might
go any further?
Any further?
What is that?
Okay. I understand now.
She is not pretending.
She is dumb.
I'm not dumb. I'm smart.
Tang San.
Brother Dai.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the smithy.
Headmaster wants to meet us.
Let me inform Ou Si Ke and the rest.
He only called both of us.
How come?
He said someone wants to meet us.
Master. Headmaster.
I was there too during the
battle last night.
You guys fought very well.
I'm Yu Tian Heng.
Tang San.
I'm from Tian Dou Imperial School.
As the name suggests, Tian Dou
Imperial School
was founded by the royal family of
Tian Dou Empire.
All the previous headmasters of the
school were the kings of the empire.
It is the top school in the empire.
Amazing.
Soul Master School Contest is
about to start.
Are you interested in the contest?
What kind of contest is that?
It is held by Martial Soul Hall.
All Soul Master Schools in the
Douluo Continent
will form teams to join the contest.
There are two major battle zones,
the Tian Dou Empire and the Xing Luo Empire.
The grand final
will be held at the
Martial Soul Main Hall
in Martial Soul City.
How does that have anything
to do with us?
I hope
both of you can join the team formed by
Tian Dou Imperial School.
If you reach the grand final,
I'm sure you will meet
your brother.
He is the leader of the
Xing Luo Empire's
Seeds battle team.
Don't you want to battle with him
again in the arena?
But why us?
Someone suggested both of you.
I came all the way here to confirm.
And I had witnessed the
battle last night.
I had to admit that both of you are
eligible to join the team.
Who suggests us?
Du Gu Yan.
You guys...
I'm from Tian Dou Imperial School
as well.
Yu Tian Heng is our leader.
I have confidence in both of you.
It turns out that both of
you are good
and able to defeat Dai Mu Bai's brother.
I didn't know your brother is
so powerful.
He had been injured during the battle.
And there are also seven of us against him.
That's good enough.
He is not anyone but Dai Wei Shi.
In this contest,
he is recognized as the contestant
who is qualified to compete
for the highest ranking
in Douluo Continent.
Impressive.
But I'm more curious about
the person who hurts him.
What do you mean?
Are you suspecting I hired someone
beforehand to hurt him?
Stabbing someone in the back
is not my style.
I prefer to fight face to face.
That's all about the contest.
If both of you are willing to join our team
you can quit Shi Lan Ke at any time
and go back to Tian Dou City with us
and join the Imperial School.
I won't quit Shi Lan Ke.
And also,
rather than joining your team,
I prefer to participate in the
contest on behalf of Shi Lan Ke.
Only recognized schools can participate
in the contest.
He is right.
Without support from the royal family,
Shi Lan Ke is not eligible to
join the contest.
This contest is a great opportunity.
If both of you want to join,
Shi Lan Ke school won't stop you.
I'm not going.
If it's about the death of Xiao Chen Yu,
don't worry.
The school will help you settle it.
How did you know about this matter?
The school will investigate
your records
and help you resolve all the problems.
I'm still not going.
Why?
Because my Master
and my buddies are here.
This is my school.
How about you?
Let me remind you.
You and your brother will battle anyway.
If you choose to join us,
Tian Dou Imperial School will
stand by your side.
We still stay here for one night.
Please reply to me within one day.
But when we walked into the room,
Tang San looked gentle
when he braided her hair.
My impression of Tang San
was that he always
treats everyone gently and politely.
He is always cool and calm.
Does he ever get angry?
Of course, he did.
He was so mad once before.
How did you know about that?
You start to gossip again.
Regarding this...
You never know that
in my family,
everything must be done
according to rules.
Everyone in my family is
as dull as dust.
They are restricted by rules.
Nothing is interesting about them.
The rules in my family,
I bet all of you won't believe it,
are as high as a wall.
Even higher than me.
So you joined Shi Lan Ke
to release your instincts?
Haven't you smelled that?
The sense of excitement and freedom
in Shi Lan Ke.
If I go back,
that means I will be restricted again.
Am I right?
This is not the point.
Aren't we talking about
Tang San just now?
Does he ever get angry before?
Of course.
When we sat for the school
admission test,
Wu was injured after being
attacked by Mr. Zhao.
Tang San only had
double Soul Rings at that time.
But he had defeated a Soul Saint
with Seven Soul Rings.
Two Soul Rings defeated
Seven Soul Rings.
How is that even possible?
Tang San must be a monster.
Why is he a monster?
He is my brother. He is my brother.
But this matter had taught us a lesson.
It's not a big deal if Tang San gets angry.
But if you irritate Wu
and make Tang San angry,
something horrible may happen.
That's why I said
the most dangerous person among
the Seven Devils
is you.
What are you talking about? I'm so cute.
You fool. You are the most important
person for Tang San.
A normal person
will surely avoid from
Tang San who is in a towering rage.
But...
It seems pretty good to have a guy
like Tang San.
Of course.
He is the best guy in the world.
Have you met every guy in the world?
I don't have to do that.
I know he is the best one.
She had completely fallen for him.
Sister. Let me braid your hair.
All right. Brother.
You are imitating me and Tang San.
I'm going to tell him now.
No, please.
We won't do it anymore.
I know there is a shop in Suo Tuo City
that sells very delicious carrot soup.
But the portion is too big.
I'm still on my diet.
I can't finish such a large portion.
What if the soup is wasted?
I will help you finish it. I will
help you finish it.
You help me finish it.
I feel the same as you do.
Treating this place like my school.
I don't want to leave, either.
You can just reject them.
I remember I told you that
after the battle with my brother,
I would reveal my true identity to you.
My brother is Dai Wei Shi.
He is the heir of the first
succession line
of Xing Luo Empire.
Then... Then you are the...
I'm the prince of Xing Luo Empire.
Since I was a kid,
I lived under my brother's influences.
Everyone said that he is far
better than me.
But in Xing Luo,
the strongest becomes the king.
Everyone wants him to be the king.
While I'm the one who was forgotten by people.
So I came here,
Shi Lan Ke,
to make myself stronger
so as to surpass him.
I never wanted to fight for the throne.
I just want to be recognized.
I want to let them know that
I'm not a loser.
Brother Dai. You are strong enough for me.
If what they said is right,
defeating my brother in the arena
will be the best choice to prove myself.
But I don't want to quit Shi Lan Ke.
And I don't want to leave
everyone as well.
Do you mean
that everyone in the Xing Luo Empire
looks down on you?
Because my brother is stronger
since he was a kid.
Zhu Zhu Qing also feels that way?
I have an engagement with her.
She came here to call off
the engagement.
Let me ask you.
Now the engagement has been called off.
Why is she still here?
I...
If she looked down on you,
why did she choose to fight together with you
during the battle with your brother?
In the arena,
why did she risk herself to protect you?
So deep inside her heart,
you've already surpassed your brother.
Sometimes being strong
doesn't mean everything.
No matter how strong he is,
he won't become our leader,
and he couldn't be Brother Dai
who practices
and battles together with us.
Don't worry.
No matter what is your decision,
we will support you till the end.
I found it.
What is that?
Memory book.
The signature of the students
when they graduated.
Which year?
I don't remember.
Because the school refused to join
the royal family and Martial Soul Hall,
capital is still the main problem.
That's why we don't have many students every year.
All of them are the students
of Shi Lan Ke?
Almost everyone here
is a famous Soul Master.
Yeah.
I remember the founder of this school
once said
that Shi Lan Ke didn't have capital,
power,
and prestige.
The only thing we can do is
to give the best to the students,
providing them with a bright future.
This is the responsibility
of every Master in Shi Lan Ke.
Seems like you already made
your decision.
Yes.
It is hard to decide.
Only by looking at this
can I be more courageous.
Look.
Is Zhao Wu Ji also a student from
Shi Lan Ke?
Yes.
Are we at the right place?
It doesn't look like a school at all.
They don't even have a dormitory.
The qualifications are bad.
I don't know why Tang San rejected us.
Never mind.
The most important person is
Dai Mu Bai.
He should be okay.
I think he was tempted just now.
What did Tang San say to you just now?
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪