♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 21=
Never mind.
Our priority on this trip is still Dai Mu Bai.
He shouldn't be a problem.
I think he was tempted just now.
What did Tang San tell you?
Do you know Ye Zhi Qiu
from Cang Hui School?
Never heard of it.
Cang Hui?
It's a little unknown school.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Did Cang Hui School get ahead of us?
They came to Shi Lan Ke to recruit talents?
A petty school like that
is no match for us.
Yu Tian Heng.
Have you made up your mind?
You mentioned
that as long as I joined
Tian Dou Imperial School,
your people would side with me
in the conflict against my elder brother.
Yes, Tian Dou Imperial School promises you.
What's so funny?
If I fight my brother,
it means the power struggle
between the heirs of Xin Luo Empire.
How can a school have the authority
to support me?
So this promise
didn't come from the school.
Am I right?
You didn't dare to even tell the truth.
Tang San's decision will be mine as well.
Hold on.
Fine, you're right.
Captain.
Never mind, we can tell him.
Dai Mu Bai, someone wants to see you.
If you agree to join
Tian Dou Imperial School,
in the future, in the power struggle
of Xing Luo Empire,
you will have full support
from Tian Dou Empire.
Even if you need military support,
we can provide it.
So the tournament and the school
are only the pretext to use me
to interfere with the power struggle
of Xing Luo Empire.
No, don't think that way. It's too extreme.
We truly want to help you.
"We"?
Who actually wants to help me?
It's Xue Qing He.
Who is that?
The only heir to the throne
of Tian Dou Empire.
Xue Qing He, the Crown Prince.
The sudden announcement of the contest
shocked the entire Douluo Continent.
Every Soul Master School is preparing for it.
But Xue Qing He thinks
there is a conspiracy behind the contest.
What conspiracy?
I have no idea either.
You may ask him yourself.
Why didn't he come to see me?
His Highness thinks
too many parties are involved in this case.
Besides, the inside of Tian Dou City
isn't as peaceful as it seems.
He can only meet you in private.
So the proposal to recruit us
was false?
No. We are indeed
recruiting new members.
That's all I know.
For more details,
you may ask the Crown Prince.
Yan Zi, what's wrong?
I think she's been poisoned.
Poisoned? How is that possible?
We've been travelling together.
Why wasn't I poisoned?
She needs to eat this now.
It'll cure her.
Weeping Forsythia.
I've never seen this before.
This is my Second Soul Skill.
Vitalizing Weeping Forsythia.
Try it out, it's delicious.
No. I'm afraid it's bitter.
It's not bitter at all.
It can even cure poison.
She is awake!
See? She's awake!
What happened to me just now?
Where are we?
He said you had been poisoned.
Poisoned?
Why don't I remember that?
It's all right. You are cured.
This can't be right!
My Weeping Forsythia
cures everything!
Maybe you should have another one.
I doubt the capability of your Martial Soul.
Maybe she fainted because of hunger.
I have some sausages.
Do you want some?
Maybe we should get a doctor.
Never mind.
Du Gu Yan's identity is special.
I'm taking her back to Tian Dou City.
If she has been poisoned,
her elder will definitely handle it.
I was supposed to go with you,
but under the circumstances, I must go now.
You two depart later.
Make it to Xi Si City in ten days
to meet His Highness.
His Highness?
Xi Si City?
What is it?
Xi Si City Soul Arena.
Accept the Fiend Battle Team's challenge.
Once you overcome the challenge,
you're qualified to go to Cang Hui School
in Tian Dou City and see me.
Why are we meeting in Xi Si City?
The meeting between His Highness
and Dai Mu Bai is a top secret.
First of all,
Xi Si City is on the way to the Capital.
Secondly,
there is no Governor in that city.
The city is not owned by anyone.
The place will provide more cover.
Remember
to reach Xi Si City in ten days
to meet His Highness.
Rong Rong, where is Wu?
Her legs haven't fully recovered.
Sister Qing is looking after her.
Do you know
why Headmaster wants us to come here?
I have no idea.
I don't know.
What are we going to do here?
Why is she still here?
She was hurt in the fight
against Dai Wei Shi.
I couldn't just kick her out.
Should we avoid her?
She will find it out sooner or later.
Where is Yu Tian Heng?
He left.
I'll get to the point.
Do not mention Xue Qing He.
Martial Soul Hall is organizing
the Soul Master School Contest.
Tian Dou Imperial School
formally invited Tang San and Dai Mu Bai
to join their team
in the contest.
Not bad!
Impressive, Brother San.
Even Tian Dou Imperial School knows him.
After much consideration,
we've decided to let you
go to Tian Dou City
and participate in this event.
But Headmaster,
joining Tian Dou Imperial School
means quitting Shi Lan Ke School.
The goal of Shi Lan Ke School
is to train up the best Soul Masters.
The best Soul Master
needs to hone his skills and face challenges
to make progress.
Martial Soul Hall
is providing the greatest platform,
and as your headmaster,
I must show you the world.
But Headmaster...
I know.
I also hope
you guys will always be the students
of Shi Lan Ke.
But I can't force you to give up
this great chance
just to keep you in Shi Lan Ke.
Wouldn't that be too selfish of me
to do such a thing?
So,
not only Tang San and Dai Mu Bai are going there,
all members of our school
will go to the Capital together!
-Really?
-It's real?
You should see for yourselves
how many geniuses there are
in Douluo Continent.
Get ready, everyone.
We'll set out tomorrow morning.
Yes!
This is great!
If we go to the Capital,
I might get to meet my father.
I must tell
Wu and Sister Qing now.
Master.
He said
that the school
shouldn't become the shackles
that bind you.
If it can give you a brighter future,
even with the school as your stepping stone,
he must let you fly high.
Even if he loses all the students,
it is worth it.
I'm not leaving Shi Lan Ke.
I won't either.
Set out with that belief.
This is an eye-opener
that will let you grow.
I wish we could participate
as the students of Shi Lan Ke School.
There might be other opportunities
in Tian Dou City.
I'll go to pack things up.
Headmaster.
Are you really taking them
to Tian Dou City?
Do you want to get in my way?
No.
I'm going back to the Capital.
We are going in the same direction.
You will travel faster without us.
I'm not in a hurry.
You haven't given up on Dai Mu Bai?
I won't quit so easily.
I know what you did to Dai Mu Bai.
If you try to harm my students again,
I will stop you.
Master.
We'll pass by Xi Si City
on our journey.
Are you still thinking
about challenging the Fiend Battle Team?
Master, I want to find my father.
I want to know what he's doing.
I want to know what happened to him.
This is probably my only chance.
Very well.
I'll inform Lander,
so he won't stop you then.
Thank you, Master.
By the way,
don't tell the others about my plan.
What about Wu? Won't you tell her?
I don't want her to be worried.
I wish I could
take everything about the school with me.
Come on.
♪The twilight shows up at daybreak♪
♪The youth rides a horse♪
♪When the world turns around♪
♪The sky is reflected in the eyes♪
♪Overcome the trial in abyss♪
♪Yet remain unchanged♪
♪Walking upright in the world♪
♪The breeze in spring is tender♪
♪Have the belief to save the day♪
♪Go on a great adventure♪
♪Join hands and look at the world♪
♪Overlook the sky♪
Wait!
♪Join hands and look at the world♪
♪Overlook the sky♪
♪The light is so brilliant♪
♪The dream is burning in my chest♪
♪The wind whizzes past my face♪
♪The rain drenches my shoulders♪
♪Despite all the difficulties♪
♪I have a fire in my heart♪
♪Every ordinary moment♪
♪The years leave marks on the face♪
♪Rage not for tomorrow♪
♪Only hold on for friendship♪
♪Get through the sea of clouds♪
♪Get the wind and clouds moving♪
♪Looking light years away♪
♪To seek the memory of the former life♪
♪Keep the smile after the threat♪
♪No one can stop our vow♪
♪Join hands and look at the world♪
♪Overlook the sky♪
♪The light is so brilliant♪
♪The dream is burning in my chest♪
♪The wind whizzes past my face♪
♪The rain drenches my shoulders♪
Hold on a bit longer.
We'll reach Xi Si City soon.
What's that ahead?
Let's have a look.
What happened?
We should bury them.
We can't leave them here in the sun.
Here, Brother Dai.
Come.
Soul Arena Badge?
It's copper.
This man was an experienced Soul Master.
But why was he tied here?
Maybe he ran into bandits?
We must hurry to Xi Si City.
Everyone, stay alert.
-Yes.
Brother Dai.
He...
Give me some water.
Here.
This...
He is alive!
It's the same as that guy.
Which means
the other man died from dehydration.
Isn't this too cruel? What hatred can it be?
Master.
Ou Si Ke, come.
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
Tang San, this helps him recover his strength.
Yes.
He is dead.
Triple Soul Rings.
He was a Soul Master too.
I like this place.
This looks funny.
It's adorable.
Gang, I'll look for a cheap inn first.
Show the others around the city.
Don't take too long.
Master.
This looks pretty.
Take me with you. I know how to bargain.
You're the best.
Go with me.
That way.
Stay close to each other.
Don't get separated.
Xi Si City Soul Arena.
Accept the Fiend Battle Team's challenge.
Once you overcome the challenge,
you're qualified to go to Cang Hui School
in Tian Dou City and see me.
Brother, you look upset.
I'm all right.
Did someone upset you? I can teach him a lesson.
Why do you want to fight so much?
What's the matter? She is my sister. I spoiled her.
You're overindulging her.
Have a look!
The wonder of Xi Si City!
Interact closely with fluffy Soul Beasts!
Have a look!
Look!
You can pet them.
They are so cute.
Have a look!
They are so adorable
that they can heal your heart!
The wonder of Xi Si City!
Aren't these Sand Beasts?
Wu, you also know about Sand Beasts?
I saw them once when I was little.
They mostly live in the desert.
These Soul Beasts are tame.
It sounds that they are rare.
All right, stop playing around.
Let's go there.
We'll wait for Headmaster.
It's less crowded there.
Sure.
Come.
Let's go.
The wonder of Xi Si City!
Adorable!
Take a seat and have some rest.
Stop looking, keep moving.
Sit.
You sit.
Master, how about
we gather some money and buy one?
The girls seem to like it a lot.
Each girl can pet it for one day.
We can sell it in Tian Dou City
and make a profit.
It can cover some expenses for our school.
Can we get one?
The Sand Beast is not a pet.
You can't buy or sell it.
Why?
The merchant is their owner.
That's right.
Their relationship is equal and cooperative.
The merchant will attract the customers,
and the Sand Beasts contribute their talent.
Talent? What talent?
Silly.
Their talent is being cute, of course.
How is being cute a talent?
In that case,
I'm also cute.
I am talented.
I am interesting.
Isn't that right?
So how do they split the profit?
All the money goes to the Sand Beasts.
All the money?
The Sand Beasts use money?
Do not underestimate
the intelligence of Soul Beasts.
A full-grown Sand Beast
has the intelligence of a child.
The merchant will send the food
out of the city for them
to the Sand Beast herd.
That means
the Sand Beasts are social animals.
The merchant delivers food for them
without charging anything.
What benefit does he get?
The benefit for the merchant
is the protection by Sand Beasts
when he crosses the desert.
Protection?
But they look so adorable.
They seem harmless.
What if
the merchant bullies them?
Not just the merchants, even Soul Masters
wouldn't dare to hurt them.
Why?
Actually,
Sand Beasts have the ability
to control sandstorm.
When they feel threatened,
the Sand Beasts are capable of destroying a city.
They are invincible in the desert.
But the Sand Beasts are friendly and tame.
So attacking them is unprofitable
for the humans.
Then a mutual relationship
started to form between humans and Sand Beasts.
I see.
Humans and Soul Beasts
can live in harmony.
Of course.
In that case,
if all the Soul Beasts could
form a mutual relationship with us,
there would be no more hunting!
Am I right?
This is only an exception.
As long as Soul Masters still need
to hunt down Soul Beasts
to advance their Soul Rings,
humans and Soul Beasts
will always be at war.
We just have to restrict
the hunting and killing
to those fierce, awful Soul Beasts.
Wouldn't that solve it?
Do you think fierce Soul Beasts should die?
We are Soul Masters.
Soul Masters and Soul Beasts
are destined to be enemies.
It cannot be changed.
Yes, they are enemies.
Brother Dai, have some milk tea.
Thanks.
We lived in the wild for a few days.
We finally get to take a break.
When you went out,
Headmaster informed us
that we'll be going
to Tian Dou City tomorrow morning.
Yu Tian Heng said
that Xue Qing He wanted to see you.
Won't you stay for another day?
Forget it. We're leaving.
You don't want to meet him?
The Crown Prince of Tian Dou Empire
meeting the Prince of
Xing Luo Empire in secrecy,
what good can it do?
I never wanted the throne anyway.
Even if I want to compete for the throne,
it's none of his business.
You're right.
Come in.
It's been a long journey for Mr. Tang.
I'm glad that Mr. Dai is here as well.
Who are you?
I am Ma Xiu Nuo. I'm nobody.
I've been here waiting for you for a few days.
To be honest,
there are some issues in Tian Dou City.
His Highness couldn't make it here in time.
He sent me to express his apology.
His Highness?
You work for Xue Qing He?
Yes.
You're one of the royals too?
My father is a low-ranking officer.
I don't have any positions at all.
I'm far from being a royal.
An officer? It is quite important.
What does Xue Qing He have to say?
His Highness promises
to meet both of you in Tian Dou City.
I'm not interested.
You don't have to reject me now.
Your brother is very powerful.
With the help of His Highness,
you'll stand a chance to fight for the throne.
He should stay out of Xing Luo Empire's problem.
I'm merely a messenger,
please calm down.
What are you doing here?
Wu, were you talking to someone?
I wanted to ask you to check out the market,
and I saw Hu Lie Na at your door.
I've passed on the message. I'm leaving.
Was he your new friend?
He seemed to be rich.
Don't trust everything you heard.
Ignore him.
You have something to do?
It's nothing.
Go with me to the market.
So the man came to deliver a message
from the Crown Prince of Tian Dou Empire?
The Crown Prince wanted to see Brother Dai.
It had nothing to do with me.
Two princes,
is it a political marriage?
A political marriage
is between a prince and a princess.
It's not meant for commoners.
Understood?
They look delicious.
Do you want some?
What's wrong? You don't want to try it?
I'm just checking them out.
Let's go back.
It's all right. If you want...
Can you hear it?
Someone is sobbing.
Let's have a look.
We're getting closer. Stay cautious.
Did something happen?
Did someone bully you?
She can't hear you.
Is she deaf?
No. She is insane.
How did it happen?
Her husband died in the Soul Arena.
Then she lost her mind!
You aren't locals?
Haven't you heard about the Fiend Battle Team?
No.
What's wrong with the Fiend Battle Team?
In the Soul Arena,
those who fought the Fiend Battle Team
have mostly died.
Those who survived were tied up
and left in the sun outside the city.
What happened?
The Fiend Battle Team did that?
If they are so brutal,
why would the Soul Masters want to fight them?
Their families were captured.
If they don't fight,
they will lose their entire families.
Where is the authority?
Xi Si City has no Governor.
The city is in anarchy.
In this city,
it's the survival of the fittest.
Is the Fiend Battle Team very strong?
They are almost all
Quadruple Soul Rings Soul Sects.
What do you think?
Quadruple Soul Rings? And more than one?
Tang San? Wu?
Wang Sheng.
Who are you?
Young Master, what's wrong?
Tell them you're all right.
I'm all right.
Where is Xue Qing He?
His Highness is in Tian Dou City.
Why doesn't he come to Xi Si City?
He planned to come here.
But the Prince wanted to
have a word with His Highness.
He couldn't make it in time.
In Tian Dou City,
will he look for Dai Mu Bai?
Sure, certainly.
Why does Xue Qing He want to meet Dai Mu Bai?
I don't know.
Why is the robe on the floor?
Young Master, I was shocked.
What happened?
I heard you yell.
I didn't yell.
Let's go.
If I keep staying in the inn,
I won't have time to check out the city.
I heard there are many specialties.
I could buy them as souvenirs.
What is it, Young Master?
That girl...
She looks familiar.
Forget it, let's go.
I might be mistaken.
I feel like our days in Nuoding School
were merely yesterday.
Time flies.
Back then, the attached students
were like a family.
We took part in the election
of the Soul Master Association.
We went to class together.
It was a pleasant time.
Wang Sheng, what are you doing here?
I escaped here.
Why did you escape?
I've been keeping something from you.
I feel guilty.
Do you remember Xiao Chen Yu?
Sure.
He captured me with a cage.
Luckily, Tang San saved me.
Actually, I killed Xiao Chen Yu.
I'm going to kill you!
After I escaped,
I found that they framed you as the killer.
I feel sorry for letting you take the blame.
Why did you kill him?
He made me betray you.
He even wanted to kill me.
Since I had the opportunity,
I wouldn't let them get away.
I must take revenge on them
for what I went through.
He deserved to die.
Actually, our fellow students
are true friends.
Did you just arrive today?
Yes.
Have you been to the market?
What did you buy?
Nothing.
Nothing interested you?
There is.
I like that candy.
The candy?
Come with me.
Here you go.
Is this your shop?
I don't have the time.
Why didn't you pay?
In this city,
if you want something,
just let me know.
I can get it for free.
Wang Sheng.
I think they are afraid of you.
The weak fears the strong.
Take it.
I can't take this.
Why not?
If you don't pay for it, it's robbing.
I don't want that candy.
Since you've arrived,
why didn't you come to us?
"Us"?
Didn't Master Ye
tell you?
You should come to us
when you arrived in Xi Si City.
You know Ye Zhi Qiu too?
Why should we go to you?
Wu, it's getting late.
Let me walk you back.
But...
There is nothing funny.
You can't compare this place
with Tian Dou City.
What is this?
It looks funny.
We've never been to Xi Si City before.
Maybe they are beasts that pull carriages.
They are ugly yet cute.
They look interesting.
So you are on the Fiend Battle Team.
Yes.
I'm one of their members.
After I left Nuoding City,
I wanted to attend another Soul Master School.
But I couldn't afford the fees.
Then I considered going to Martial Soul Hall.
But the people there
looked down on me.
They said I wasn't gifted and wouldn't take me in.
Then,
I wandered from city to city.
I ran out of money soon.
Later, I found
that some cities would open up
some underground Soul Arenas.
The Soul Masters would fight there.
You kill or get killed.
Though it's dangerous,
you can make a fortune if you win.
So I joined.
But I completely lost at the first time.
I was about to be killed.
Do you know what happened next?
I can't guess.
My Martial Soul mutated.
My ordinary Tiger Soul
turned into a Blood Tiger Soul.
God gave me a chance!
After the mutation,
the force behind the Fiend Battle Team found me.
They told me
that whoever works alone will be bullied.
But if we stick together,
it will be different.
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪