FINAL EPISODE
You didn't have to walk me home.
It's because we're a guy and a girl today.
I wouldn't if we were friends.
You live too close to the station.
What do you mean? It's so far.
No, it isn't. It's super close.
We're here.
Get home safely.
Ju Kyung.
Yes?
I'm...
using my wish.
PRINCE COMICS
Seo Jun, I'm sorry.
We still have a few dates left.
You should head inside.
Do you still like Ju Kyung?
Did you ask her out?
No. We're going out.
I know you're lying.
What do you know?
I told you I met her yesterday.
Why did it have to be yesterday?
- Because of the first snow.
- What's that supposed to mean?
You guys aren't going out, are you?
You must be a little nervous.
- No.
- You little punk.
I can't believe they hugged each other.
But we broke up.
I haven't missed you at all.
Hey, you're up.
Yes.
Who gave you these flowers?
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
I saw it in your room, and I brought it out.
I didn't want it to wither.
I totally forgot about it.
Flowers are pretty when they're in a vase.
But I feel bad for them when they
wither without receiving any love.
Are you busy?
I'm at your agency.
Can we meet after you finish practicing?
I'll wait for you in the lobby.
I'LL WAIT FOR YOU IN THE LOBBY.
Seo Jun.
Why didn't you leave
after seeing me not reply?
You've been waiting here for hours.
Well...
- You see...
- Yes, I see you. What is it?
Did you eat?
Should we go eat?
Are you asking me out on a date?
I'm busy today.
I need to tell you something.
You can save that for next time.
I'm too busy today...
to go on a date.
Let's just settle with this.
Seo Jun.
By the way, did you hear?
Soo Ho's going back to the States tonight.
- What?
- He apparently came here...
to take care of things
after his dad got better.
You'd better get going if you want
to catch him before he leaves.
Why are you just standing there?
You should get going. You
don't want to miss him.
Go. Get going already.
Go on.
See you.
The doors are closing.
What's this?
Why are you suddenly studying so hard?
Blow out the candle. I'm
not going to sing a song.
Happy birthday to you
I thought you weren't going to sing.
Ju Kyung.
Yes?
Which number are you going to pick
for the questions you don't know?
Let's see. Number three?
Then I should pick
everything else but that one.
Wait.
Here.
Don't get too nervous and good luck.
Thanks.
Here. Good luck to you too.
Okay.
2021 COLLEGE SCHOLASTIC ABILITY TEST
Here we go.
1, 2, 3.
- You guys.
- Why do you all look so awkward?
You guys look too sad.
- Look more natural.
- Okay, fine.
- Let's be cute.
- Ready?
- 1, 2, 3.
- Goodbye, Saebom High School!
- Okay.
- Ju Kyung.
Aren't you going to take a photo with me?
My gosh, Seo Jun.
Why are you interrupting?
Okay, Seo Jun.
We'll take a photo of you
together. Stand right here.
- Go on.
- Stand there.
- My gosh.
- Nice shot.
- Get ready.
- Stand close to each other.
- Stand close.
- 1, 2, 3.
My gosh.
- My gosh, come on.
- Give me a proper pose.
- Let's try one more time.
- Hey, let's take a proper photo.
Here we go. 1, 2, 3.
Soo Ho's going back to the States tonight.
BICYCLE CROSSING
Taxi!
My gosh.
Soo Ho! Soo Ho!
Are you gone already?
You jerk.
Why did you come back if
you were going to leave?
Why did you follow me around?
My gosh.
Ju Kyung.
Don't go.
Please don't go.
I won't let you go.
So please don't leave.
I'm not going anywhere.
Don't you dare.
So don't cry.
- Don't go.
- I won't.
I didn't show it,
but I was insanely nervous.
- About what?
- That you'd refuse...
to see me.
Liar.
It's true.
You were planning to leave today.
What do you mean?
I heard you were going
back to the US tonight.
Why would I?
What's with your luggage?
I was unpacking.
What do you mean? Seo Jun
said you were going back...
He said that?
Well...
Did you run over here thinking I was leaving?
- No, that's not it.
- To stop me?
That's not it.
Ju Kyung. Ju Kyung!
- Why are you running away?
- I am not.
Didn't you come to see me?
I have to go home. It's very important.
That's not the way.
I'll take you home.
Do you hate me?
Won't you let me see your face?
You were coming back anyway.
You came back anyway.
So why did you do that?
Because it would be...
too hard for you to wait.
It was much harder...
than waiting.
It was...
so hard for me too.
That's why...
I was looking for a way to come back.
Even if my dad didn't wake up,
I would've come back to you.
What if I had gotten over you?
I would've followed you around.
What if I still said no?
I would've cried and begged,
and tried to seduce you.
Ju Kyung.
Please look at me.
I'm sorry for making you...
suffer.
Why are you sorry?
I know how you felt.
I do, but seeing you again,
I'm reminded of how much it hurt.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
You were hurting too.
It must've been so hard in that faraway land.
You had no other family.
You were in the hospital
alone, unable to do anything.
It must've hurt so much.
I was so worried, that I
wanted to fly over, but...
An 18-year-old has no money.
We were too young,
- weren't we?
- Yes.
Don't cry.
Come here.
It's shocking enough that they were dating.
It's amazing that they're getting married.
I know. Who else could handle
my sister other than Mr. Han?
What are you staring at?
What? It's just...
you've changed a lot.
You even drive now.
I still have this too.
You didn't throw it away.
We're the same.
What?
We haven't changed...
from before.
From before, when?
When you were a crybaby?
I cried once. Stop calling me a crybaby.
You really are a crybaby.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I wouldn't have known if I didn't
see the writing on the wall.
I wanted to tell you on a
special day, but couldn't.
You should've just told me.
I liked you when I was a kid too.
I used to wait for you at the
comic book store every day.
I guess it wasn't one-sided...
if you remembered me.
I didn't like you.
I only remember you as the
comic book store crybaby.
That's sad. I guess it
was an unrequited love.
How do you feel? Are you still sick?
What do you mean?
I wasn't sick.
You ended up in the ER.
How's your constipation?
It's fine.
You should exercise often
and eat a lot of fiber.
You need probiotics and lots of water.
You need to do that regularly
so you don't get constipated...
Hey. Must you kill the
mood by talking about that?
It's so embarrassing.
It's because I've been under a lot of stress.
People with active digestive
systems are usually very active.
Pull over. I'll walk home as a workout.
Yes. Over there. You can drop me off there.
Pull over there.
- Hey.
- Are you on your way home?
Yes, I am.
- Aren't you tired?
- Not at all.
Is it hard to talk because you're driving?
- Want to call me when you get home?
- No.
It's fine.
I want to keep hearing your voice.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Why?
I want to go see you.
It seems like a dream...
that I can see you tomorrow.
For me too.
When you start the chorus,
- give a drum roll.
- Here.
- To explode.
- Yes.
And here, the guitar...
- Don't pause on D, go right in.
- Go right in.
Why did you have to come out right then?
You made me look lame.
- What do you mean?
- Unbelievable.
Today was my last chance, you know.
What I didn't do two years
ago... Telling her how I feel...
and getting rejected.
I finally got to do it.
What are you doing here?
I'm not busy today,
so I'll let you say what
you couldn't yesterday.
I honestly don't know what to say.
As if.
It's already written all over your face.
You've always been one to wear
your heart on your sleeves.
All I can say to you...
is that I'm grateful and sorry.
As if that's something to be sorry about.
I was aware...
that you weren't over Soo Ho.
So don't be sorry.
You had no room for me in your heart,
but I tried getting greedy for once.
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who should apologize...
for confusing you by telling you how I feel.
You must want me to mean that,
but that'd be ridiculous.
I should at least tell you how I feel.
Your brother once said to me...
that getting rejected helps you to move on.
Don't worry though. My debut is imminent,
so I won't have time to think about you.
I'll move on quicker than you think.
Keep holding that expression
though, and I'll go.
- Should I?
- Okay, let's finish our drinks.
- It'll be on me.
- Got it.
Let's go.
Are you playing me for a fool already?
- Please let me go.
- I'll bet all my aroma candles...
on you having not-so-innocent intentions.
What will you bet in return?
Stop that already!
What are you doing in that suit of yours?
I wanted to practice walking
Hee Kyung down the aisle.
What for? She and Joon Woo
will be doing that themselves.
Breakfast is ready!
Why though?
A lot of couples do that these days.
You're here again, Soo Ho?
Did you sleep in again?
You've been here almost
every day for the past month.
Why don't you just marry her instead?
You must think you're immune to pain.
It'll be nice to get it over with.
I won't allow it so easily.
When should I pick you up today?
It's all right. You'll probably be too tired.
I'll be fine.
It's what I expected from you.
Back is the man who is
young, rich, and handsome.
I envy how you don't have
to work to earn money.
Your CSAT should be what
you only think about.
I studied until after midnight last night.
Nobody's more desperate than I am right now.
As if Go Woon will wait
until you get into college.
Must you be so annoying, you jerk?
You jerk? To your sister?
Why do you keep acting
like his brother-in-law?
Now, dig in.
Sure.
MOVE ENTERTAINMENT
NEW IDOL GROUP MAKEUP CONCEPT CONTEST
A makeup concept contest
for a new idol group?
Chen, filming has been pushed back a little.
- Can you wait?
- Sure.
Just a second. Hello?
Ju Kyung, are you and Seo Jun dating?
No.
Of course. I knew he had high standards.
That's right. And because
of his high standards,
he'd never date just about anyone.
Mist.
Enough!
I didn't know I was at a
sauna. Go easy on it, will you?
Why does she have to follow us everywhere?
She only takes up room in the van.
It's not like she does any work.
She's an intern and needs to learn the ropes.
I know, but why does it
have to be on my time?
Even professionals can't meet
all my demands perfectly,
so it annoys me to bits
to have a rookie tail us.
What a brat.
I knew you'd be kind and understand.
Then, since I'm hungry,
get me a roll of gimbap.
With cheese.
I delivered dumplings in high school...
and now I'm buying someone else's gimbap.
Hurry up, will you?
Sorry.
Are you kidding me? Don't
you know I hate cucumbers?
You should've had them taken out.
Sorry. I didn't know you disliked them.
Should I buy you another?
Just get in and pick the cucumbers out.
I'm starving.
What is it?
Pick out the cucumbers for me.
Do it yourself.
Ju Kyung, I'm Chen.
Must I spend my time picking out cucumbers?
Do it yourself, darn it.
You have hands, don't you?
I didn't study makeup to
pick out your cucumbers.
How dare you abuse your power?
Are you out of your mind?
- Do you want to get fired?
- I'd rather quit...
than get fired by you,
you obnoxious brat!
What? How dare you!
Why? What's going on?
- It's her.
- Seriously?
Who do you think you are?
What did you do to her?
That's enough!
Chen, you too.
Stop playing the victim, darn it.
You must be out of your mind.
What did you just say?
Hey.
Who are you laying hands on, you thug?
Kang Soo Jin?
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
Have you been well?
I guess.
What about you? How have you been?
After dropping out of school,
Mom and I went to stay with my aunt overseas.
My parents got divorced, you see.
You must be attending college then.
No, I've been doing volunteer work overseas.
I only recently got back from Haiti.
I see.
No wonder.
No one had heard from you, so I got curious.
That's because I never told anyone.
Now that I'm back, I
wanted to apologize to you.
It's why I asked around to
figure out where you worked.
Ju Kyung,
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry it took me so long to apologize.
I'm really sorry.
This isn't so that you'd forgive me.
Soo Jin...
I must've been a mess back then.
It seemed like you had what I couldn't have,
so I felt like I lost again.
Stealing what you had and
stomping on your relationship...
seemed like a way of winning.
I always had to be on top of everyone.
That's what I was taught.
Getting away from my father
finally let me see...
how deeply I hurt you back then...
and what I had lost.
I regretted my actions...
and tried to apologize to you,
but it didn't seem right
to say over the phone.
I also thought you'd ignore my calls too.
You should've called.
I would've loved to hear from you.
Maybe I should've.
I'm all right.
It doesn't faze me anymore.
Those memories...
don't hurt me as much anymore.
I guess that's why I don't even hate you.
Still, I'm glad that I was able to see you...
and apologize in person.
I'm happier for you, you know.
You're free now.
Your hands have healed as well.
They're pretty.
I know.
Your kick is still just as threatening.
I let my temper get the best of me.
I hope I didn't make things worse for you.
All they can do is fire
me anyway, so I'm good.
- That song?
- Of course.
It was my personal choice.
I've been a fan of Leo's
songs for a very long time.
You and Se Yeon made that song together.
And I think it'd be meaningful
to let Seo Jun sing it.
Don't you feel bad about leaving
it as a plagiarized song?
I'm sure you're upset about it too.
Why are you so serious?
I just can't believe it.
I've never studied music.
The only lessons I got were from Se Yeon.
Seo Jun already told me everything.
He told me it's easy to tell
how much you love music...
judging by the instruments
and equipment you own.
If we don't like your song,
we're not going to release it.
So don't get too ahead of yourself.
I want to hear Leo's
version of "Missing You".
Don't feel too pressured
and just send us the song.
Okay?
Okay then. That's enough about work.
Can I open my wedding gift?
Sure.
Why is it so heavy?
You chose the best gift ever.
Congratulations on your wedding.
I have so many things to fix at home.
I want to hear Leo's
version of "Missing You".
Passcode confirmed.
The purple sky
And the cool breeze makes me feel more lonely
All the familiar memories
Start coming back and
remind me of you tonight
I have so much to thank you for
Our hearts used to flutter
As we smiled at one another
I fear
Who's the guy? What's his name?
Soo Jin already gave him
a good kick in the face.
I'm glad she did. If I were
there, I would've beaten him...
You wouldn't have beaten him to a pulp.
Fortunately, I didn't get fired.
But I am getting punished for it.
I need to finish this.
I'll call you back later.
What are you doing?
I'm washing the makeup brushes and sponges.
You're doing it all alone?
What are you doing?
This is latex. If you wash it
with hot water, it shrinks.
I'm sorry.
You need to divide them into
natural and synthetic brushes first.
You need to wash them differently,
so don't get them mixed up.
Okay.
Was your name Lim Su Jeong?
No, I'm Lim Ju Kyung.
Were you the one who yelled at Chen earlier?
I'm really sorry about that as well.
I'm glad you did that.
She looks down on our employees way too much.
I told her to get her
makeup done somewhere else.
Director.
About the makeup contest...
for Move Entertainment's new idol group...
Can I enter the contest as well?
Ms. Lim Kyung Ja, can't you read?
- Pardon?
- It says all the employees...
are allowed to enter. Didn't you see that?
Thank you! I'll do my best!
But my name is Lim Ju Kyung.
Hey, look at him.
He's so handsome. Who is she?
- Do you think she's his girlfriend?
- She's probably just a friend.
Did I keep you waiting?
Honey, what took you so long?
I waited for you.
Honey, did you eat?
Here. Try a bite.
- Let's get back to this.
- She's his girlfriend.
Did you just get jealous?
Honey?
I didn't get jealous.
Don't go around with a smile
on your face from now on, okay?
I think those middle school
kids made you get jealous.
Honey.
Cut it out, Soo Ho.
Honey, why don't you try
calling me "Honey" again?
Forget it.
- Should I give it a try?
- Give what a try?
Are you going to call me "Honey"?
I haven't done a lot of makeup on guys,
so I'm not used to it.
- It tickles.
- Stay still.
Let me try this properly.
It doesn't always come
out the way I imagine it.
You're a terrible model.
- Soo Ho.
- Okay, fine.
Stay still.
Okay, nice! I love it! 1, 2.
Good. Look over here. 1, 2, 3. Okay. 1, 2.
I love how you guys are posing
right now. Give me a smile.
Look here and give me a smile.
1, 2, 3, 2, 3.
Okay, nice. Good.
You guys are so handsome!
Teenage girls are going
to go crazy over you guys.
Will you guys stop overreacting?
It's because you're doing great.
Let's stir up the music industry.
I love that frown on your
face. Seo Jun, that's great.
"MISSING YOU", FINAL VERSION
Let's just send it.
YOUR EMAIL HAS BEEN SENT.
Here you go.
MOVE ENTERTAINMENT
NEW IDOL GROUP MAKEUP CONCEPT CONTEST
Were you okay? Didn't you get angry?
No, it was nice to see her again.
You're too nice.
But I'd like to meet Soo Jin too.
I've always wondered how she's doing.
This one's pretty. Try this on.
- Do you think so?
- Yes.
This one's pretty too. Try this on as well.
How much did your sister give you
for a bag? How much can you spend?
She gave me a credit card.
Then buy both. Just buy everything.
No, I can't. I also need to
buy clothes for the wedding.
- I'll take this one.
- Okay.
What should I wear for my
sister's wedding? This or this?
I like this one.
Never mind. I like this
one. No, I like this one.
- This one looks best.
- Why did you even ask?
By the way, you know how you went
on a trip with Soo Ho recently?
Yes. What about it?
Did anything happen?
- Like what?
- I mean...
You know what I'm talking about.
Did anything exciting happen?
Anything exciting?
Oh, I almost lost my cell phone...
No, I'm not talking about that.
I'm asking if anything happened
between you and Soo Ho.
What... What are you talking about?
We got on an early train
and came back at night.
What? Why are you guys a
pair of goody-two-shoes?
- You're not in high school...
- That's enough.
Don't be embarrassed.
Why aren't you meeting Soo
Ho today? It's your day off.
He's meeting Tae Hoon today.
What? Tae Hoon? Why didn't
you tell me earlier?
- Let's go join them.
- Just let them have fun.
But I miss...
Well...
He owes me something,
so try calling Soo Ho.
Okay.
BOYFRIEND
- He isn't picking up.
- What?
- Try again.
- Okay.
He's not picking up. I
guess they're busy talking.
Why do I feel so suspicious?
Tae Hoon's partying every day
now that he's going to the army.
- We're going somewhere hot today!
- Unbelievable!
I can't believe this!
He's going somewhere hot?
What's the matter?
APGUJEONG GOMTOM
What the... Isn't this a hookup bar?
What?
A hookup bar?
APGUJEONG GOMTOM
Tae Hoon, you're dead.
Did he pick up?
He won't pick up.
What?
Where are you? What are you doing?
I'm partying it up with Soo Ho. So what?
- Partying it up?
- What? Partying it up?
- Hey. You'd better...
- I'm busy. Bye.
Hey. Hello? Hey. Tae Hoon!
- What did he say?
- This piece of trash!
Did you call?
- Out of our way!
YOUR TAXI IS ON ITS WAY.
Tae Hoon! You're at this hookup
bar with Soo Ho, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
You posted a picture about
going somewhere really hot!
- You're partying it up?
- Hey.
- Where's Soo Ho?
- Let go!
We went there.
- A hot sauna?
- That's right!
What?
It's Ju Kyung.
You partied it up...
Somewhere really hot.
It was hot. Super hot.
It was very hot.
Hey. What's wrong with him?
Something's wrong. He feels like jello.
I gave him a few drinks in the sauna.
- What should we do?
- Soo Ho. Wake up.
Jju Kyung.
- Jju Kyung? What the...
You're wasted.
I'll take you home.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
- Get up.
Get home safely.
Bye.
It's Jju Kyung. My Jju Kyung is here.
Yes. Taxi.
Taxi.
No, not there.
Let's go.
Bye.
Gosh.
I'll go too.
Wait! Doo Ah. I mean... Sorry.
Anyway, why are you here?
What do you mean?
I mean, we broke up.
Why do you care if I go somewhere hot...
or party it up?
I did not care!
You know you dumped me 17 times.
You can beg all you want.
I won't take you back.
- Then why are you following me?
- It's late...
It's dangerous. I can't let you go alone.
Whatever.
I love you.
Soo Ho.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Come here.
Don't you dare drink like this again.
Ju Kyung.
Where are we?
This? This is your home.
- I'm dizzy.
- Careful.
Okay. Careful.
Gosh. Okay.
Wait. This...
I was lucky enough to get
it, but you can have it.
You know my secret now, so
I should be nice to you.
So this is where you put it.
Look at him smile while he's
drunk. This will not do.
I said not to smile like that.
Who are you?
- What?
- Who are you, that you came...
into my home?
- I'm Lim Ju Kyung.
- Lim Ju Kyung?
My girlfriend's name is also Lim Ju Kyung.
You're pretty too.
Am I?
Then will you break up
with your girlfriend...
and go out with me?
No.
I belong to Lim Ju Kyung.
What a shame.
Then I'll get going now.
Good night.
Wait.
Come here.
I love you so much
Oh dear
Stop it. You're making me cringe.
I love you so much
Oh dear
You're a completely different
person when you're drunk.
Ju Kyung.
You know...
that song I wrote with Se Yeon?
Seo Jun is going to sing it.
Really?
Would Se Yeon...
like that too?
Of course. That's a given.
Really?
Yes, really.
I'd be super happy if it were me.
I really...
hope you're right.
Ju Kyung.
Wake up.
It's late.
I tried to wake you.
You're the one who didn't wake up.
I love you.
- Are you okay?
- What?
I meant to leave once you fell asleep,
but I fell asleep too.
I was just about to wake you.
3 MISSED CALLS FROM MOM
Mom called.
I didn't say I'd be late.
Why didn't you go home?
I said you were sleeping over at my place.
Enjoy yourself, my friend.
Aren't you going to call her?
Well...
Soo Ah covered for me.
She did?
I'll drive you home. Where's my car key?
Where did I put it?
But you drank.
Right.
I should call a designated driver.
I'll just call a cab.
I can't get a car. Is
it because it's so late?
I'll hail one on the street.
Can't you stay?
It's...
late.
Don't go.
Are you cooking? I'm amazed.
For this simple dish?
I'm just adding stuff and pan-frying them.
I can barely cook a pot of ramyeon.
Then the cooking will be my job, I guess.
It looks delicious. Here.
I'm starving.
Ta-da.
You should slow down.
It's really good.
Was it seasoned with magic?
Try the salad too.
It's like I said. Fiber
is good for constipation.
Just a second.
Here.
Because who I see...
is Lim Ju Kyung.
You still had this?
Here.
Do you know how to tie hair back?
I'm willing to try.
Is this not right?
Why didn't you throw this out?
I'm glad I didn't.
Why don't we watch a movie
after I get off work today?
Not today. I have something
important lined up.
Something important?
When I close my eyes, the
image of you grows clearer
I end up missing your glowing face even more
Where you've been staying up this long night
I'll rest for a moment and stay by your side
On this exhausted night, tears let it blossom
When my song reaches the sky
Gradually
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
You sounded amazing.
What if you get arrested for
pounding on girls' hearts?
You and your cheesy comments.
Leo, what did you think?
I almost barfed.
Because it was that sick.
- Do you have a death wish?
- Of course not.
Pretty Boy 1 and 2, get arguing.
I wouldn't mind some blood, sweat, and tears.
What? You're not going to vomit again, right?
Come on.
Anyway, wrap up the recording.
I'm getting married tomorrow,
- so I'll head home.
- Congratulations.
You got lucky with your fiance.
I know. I should make my
Grapefruit a happy man.
- I'm off.
- Take care.
Darn, I'm starving.
Want to grab a bite?
Is this enough?
I can't sing on a full stomach.
Your vocalization isn't
as good as it used to be.
I saw you wiping tears away
while hearing me sing earlier.
When did I ever?
Will I not get to see you
often once you make your debut?
Of course, I'll be too busy.
You should get in line.
I'll be just as busy too.
I'm thinking about studying.
- Studying what?
- Music.
I never properly learned how to write songs.
So I've decided to start with the basics.
Wait. Will you be taking the CSAT then?
Poor Ju Kyung. She'll have
to provide for her boyfriend.
I can take the test right now and
still get into a decent college.
What a show-off.
Anyway, I'm having some coke.
Soda isn't good for your
throat, so stick to water.
Okay, fine. I'll drink water instead.
No wonder your singing
isn't as good as before.
You're like a nagging wife.
A singer should take care of his voice.
LIM HEE KYUNG, HAN JOON
WOO WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
BRIDE: LIM HEE KYUNG
GROOM: HAN JOON WOO
LIM HEE KYUNG, HAN JOON
WOO WE'RE GETTING MARRIED
Who on earth is it?
Who have you been texting all day?
- An older student from school.
- An older student?
Male or female?
Male.
Male?
Hey! Are you giggling?
You should wait for me until
I get into college next year.
No one told you not to get into college.
- It's not like I didn't want to.
- Whatever.
Okay, fine. I'll let you flirt a little.
Enjoy your college life to some extent, okay?
Hey, Ju Young.
What?
I'm aware of how much you like me...
and that I won't find
anyone as decent as you.
So don't you dare flirt with
any girls at the academy.
You'll pay for it.
Go Woon!
Look at you, Ju Kyung. The
studying and the internship...
truly paid off.
A bride shouldn't speak in that tone.
Stay still, will you?
My Hee Kyung couldn't be more stunning.
What's wrong with me?
I honestly shouldn't cry.
Talk about the roles being reversed.
How adorable.
- What's that, Dad?
- His eyes are puffy from the tears.
They're less puffy now and...
Why do you keep on crying?
You just had to marry a
man exactly like your dad.
- All done.
- Really?
Is this really me?
- Hyun Sook.
- You're here!
- Hello.
- You look amazing. Congratulations.
- Where's Seo Jun?
- I came with Go Woon.
Seo Jun's busy getting ready for his debut.
You look stunning.
- Divine Hyun Kyu.
- Yes, Mighty Tae Hoon?
What gives? Why didn't
you bring your girlfriend?
She's busy, you see.
You lied, didn't you?
You lied about having one...
to get out of going to the military together.
Where did you find this odd ring anyway?
- Is it your dad's?
- My dad's?
I got it in Dongdaemun...
- and it's 18k gold.
- Whatever.
As if you'll know.
Hoon, you look incredible in that suit.
Hold on. Why are you
calling him like that again?
You only used to when you dated.
- Are you two back together?
- What?
When did I call him Hoon? You
should get your ears checked.
That's odd. You don't call
him Hoon for no reason.
- What do you mean it's odd?
- Hey, it's been so long!
- Unbelievable.
- Hey, Hyun Kyu.
It's so good to see you again.
Soo Ah, your hand is
bigger than I remember it.
What do you think you're doing?
How dare you take my girlfriend's hand!
I didn't mean to... Wait, girlfriend?
Stop it.
You've always been at each other's throats,
so when did this happen?
You said it would never
happen. I can't believe this.
- I told you to be careful!
- No way.
- Honey!
- Honey?
Are you ashamed of me or something?
- Whatever.
- No way.
Guys.
Watch us become the sweetest couple.
- No...
- Please don't.
Hey. Don't you dare!
What do you think you're doing?
- I can't believe it.
- Unbelievable.
Hoon, let's go.
- I can't watch this.
- Are you kidding me?
Ju Kyung.
Hey, you're here.
Are you done with her makeup?
I don't know why I'm so nervous...
when Hee Kyung's the one getting married.
Are the contest results
out? Today's the day, right?
Yes, the results were posted.
So how did it go?
Well...
Good or bad?
- So you made the cut.
- No, I didn't.
- You didn't?
- The others are more experienced,
so it only makes sense.
You must feel defeated. I
know how hard you tried.
Still, I feel good about it.
The internship will be over
once lectures begin again,
so I wanted to do more than
just run errands all the time.
I learned a lot while putting
the presentation together.
I'm proud of you.
I was wrong to go with
the model I chose though.
- Why?
- People asked me more about you...
after seeing your photo.
They asked me where I found you.
So it's because of you that I didn't pass.
- Is it?
- Yes.
- What can I do to make up for it?
- I'm not sure.
Soo Ho, my best friend.
You guys are so pretty and handsome today.
- It's like you're getting married.
- Exactly.
Soo Jin.
My gosh, is that Kang Soo Jin?
You haven't changed one bit.
Long time no see, Kang Soo.
I haven't heard anyone call
me that in a long time.
I'm glad you came. Soo Ah
wanted to meet you too.
Have you been well?
I heard about your dad.
- I'm relieved.
- Me too.
Thanks.
I missed you.
You should've called.
I'm sorry.
How cute.
Hee Kyung, your ring is here.
Thank goodness it got here on time.
- Try it on to see if it fits.
- Okay.
- It's a bit tight.
- What?
- It won't come off.
It's because you drank yesterday.
What kind of bride drinks
before her own wedding?
It really won't come off. Take it off for me.
- My goodness.
- Let me see.
Gosh, it really won't come off.
Why don't I just wear it?
You can't do that.
Exchanging rings is the most
important part of the wedding.
- He's right. Here. Let me try.
- You want to try?
I'll get it off for you.
I think my finger might come off.
- Honey, be gentle.
- Gosh, it hurts.
- Be gentle.
- I'll get it off for you!
- My gosh, it hurts!
- My goodness.
You got it off!
There it is.
It's time for the bride
to go to the waiting room.
I got you.
What's going on?
- What's wrong?
- What is it?
Darn it.
Hee Kyung, congratulations...
What's going on?
- Isn't it the bride's waiting room?
- What's the groom doing there?
Hello.
My gosh, what's all this?
I didn't know grooms also
had waiting rooms these days.
Bravo. Mr. Han, you look amazing.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
- I'll take a photo of everyone.
- Stand next to the groom.
- Okay, let's go.
Be careful.
You can sit here.
I'll take a photo now.
1, 2, 3.
What's wrong?
- My goodness.
- Are you okay?
- My goodness!
- Please let go.
It's time for the groom to get
ready to walk down the aisle.
Okay.
Please! I'm the groom!
- Come on!
- This isn't working!
Has her face gotten bigger?
What are we going to do?
Should we call someone?
Should we call 911?
- 911?
- But she needs to go right now.
What?
It's finally time to see...
the bride and groom walk down the aisle.
I'd like everyone to face the back.
Okay then. Let's give them
a round of applause...
and welcome them...
with excitement as we keep
our voices up on note C7.
Let's welcome the bride and groom.
This is the most beautiful
wedding I've ever seen.
Let's give them a round of applause!
I love your voices.
Now that the wedding has come to an end,
it's time for the officiant to
give them his words of blessings.
The fact that I was given the opportunity...
to officiate Han Joon Woo...
and Lim Hee Kyung's wedding...
makes me feel unbelievably
grateful and honored.
Let me tell you something
about the groom, Han Joon Woo.
The moment he set foot
into Saebom High School,
I saw a halo,
and I could instantly tell
that he had the competence...
to lead our school to create...
a new history!
Now let's see how much the
bride loves the groom...
by hearing her shout her
love for him three times.
Han Joon is my man! Han Joon is my man!
- Han Joon is my man! I love you!
- Congratulations!
- Kiss! Kiss!
- No...
Let's congratulate them
with a round of applause!
Amazing!
I'll go wash the sponges.
Seo Jun.
Hey, you're here too?
You look great today.
It's not just today.
I look great every day.
Seo Jun, are you done?
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
I see you're on your toes today.
Which color do you think we should use?
Pardon? Me?
Who else would I be talking to?
Well...
In order to match the color
of his hair and outfit,
I think we should use one
that's a bit more matte.
Why don't you give it a try?
- Me?
- Who else would I be talking to?
Here. I heard you guys are friends.
Give it a nice finishing touch.
About the concept proposal...
You did pretty well for an intern,
Ju Kyung.
- What are you doing?
- Hey.
She just said my name and
complimented me, right?
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Look at this girl.
You don't know how it feels
for a geek who succeeded.
Finish it already.
Okay.
Do you have tremors?
It's my first time doing
this at a real event.
You did it well last time.
It's different.
You can't mess it up even if you mess up.
My lips are too sexy for that.
Stay still.
All done.
Thanks.
I didn't do anything. Perform
well. I'll be watching.
Don't be nervous.
You too. Good luck.
Good luck.
Your hand is sweaty.
You're nervous, aren't you?
I am not. I've got nerves of steel.
I don't get nervous.
Let's go!
- Let's do this.
- Hands in.
We've worked hard, so let's do our best.
- Let's do a cheer.
- Okay. 1, 2, 3.
- Let's do this!
Hey.
- Did you finish?
- Yes. I did Seo Jun's lips.
What about me?
It's starting.
The purple sky
And the cool breeze makes me feel more lonely
All the familiar memories
Start coming back and
remind me of you tonight
I have so much to thank you for
Our hearts used to flutter
as we smiled at one another
I fear you'll turn into a
star and disappear again
I'll cherish you in the void in my heart
When I close my eyes, the
image of you grows clearer
I end up missing your glowing face even more
Where you've been staying up this long night
I'll rest for a moment and stay by your side
On this exhausted night, tears let it blossom
When my song reaches the sky
Gradually Come to me like an eternal dream
Become a star and stay by my side
You rock!
As if I roamed in the darkness for years
And finally found light
All the hardships that weighed me down
Melt away like snow
My dream of hope gave
me the strength to fight
- The countless tears
Relying on my hopeless dream
I gave my heart and jumped in
It starts today
A new world slowly appears before my eyes
And in it, I'll run afresh
My future that I feared
You're awesome!
One by one
They're coming true
The dreams that I had
wished for so desperately
They come to me
Within reach
I didn't finish yet.
- Did you finish?
- Not yet.
You're so slow.
You said you were a master of speed-reading.
I'm focusing carefully on each page.
Do you just look at the pictures?
That's disrespectful.
I really am a master of speed-reading.
You're so arrogant.
They wrote this really well.
They revised "Killer of
Darkness" into a zombie story.
They did a great job.
Really? I wondered why they
felt the need to change it.
I feel like it lost the charm
of the original that created...
an eerie fear of the unknown
beings by making them zombies.
True. The original is good in many ways too.
You know the book from 1921 by Ed Seller...
- "Dead of Night."
- So you do know.
- How could I not?
The writing style is still not outdated...
Okay, okay. Let's finish
reading. I want to see the rest.
Flip the page.
I'm done. Flip the page.
Seriously.
What are you two doing?
Nothing. Gosh, this thing.
Sorry. Continue what you were
doing. I'm going to go eat.
I'm going to eat a multi-course meal.
Shall we continue?
Silly. Forget it.
Found it.
THANK YOU GO WOO RI AND DAYOUNG
FOR THE SPECIAL APPEARANCE.
THANK YOU ACTORS AND STAFF FOR
FOLLOWING RULES TO STOP THE SPREAD.
THANK YOU FOR SUPPORTING
AND WATCHING "TRUE BEAUTY".
TRUE BEAUTY