Ms. Hong.
What are you two doing here?
I can explain. What happened is...
Gosh, my back hurts.
So why did you follow me?
Are you saying I got beaten
because I did something wrong?
You went out...
in the middle of the night
looking like you could kill someone.
How can I not follow you?
That idea popped into my head.
See?
But I have enough self-control.
"Self-control?"
Throwing anyone you come
across isn't called self-control.
My gosh. Even when you are
possessed by an unrested spirit,
you're still your violent self.
You could've woken me
up before I threw you down.
You said you've been
watching from the start.
That's because...
Gosh, forget it.
Who's the one that went out...
without any precautions as
soon as the exorcism was over?
I haven't had to deal with the
habit of an unrested spirit for a while,
so I just let my guard down.
You kept nagging at me
saying I need to make sure...
I stay stuck at home.
That's enough.
If it weren't for me, the guard
would've called the police.
Hey!
Just eat.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
Ms. Hong!
(Daebak Realty)
I forgot to give it back to you.
I had the same exact necklace...
since when I was a kid.
I lived my life thinking
I got it from my uncle.
But come to think about it,
I think it must've been your mother.
I still have no idea...
what happened 20 years ago.
But I could live an
ordinary life to this day...
all thanks to that necklace.
It's belated, but I wanted to say...
thank you.
To be honest, I also don't
know exactly what happened...
twenty years ago.
My memories aren't
complete, just like yours.
That's why I had to find you.
If I could find you and learn
what exactly happened on that day,
I thought I could find a
way to send my mom away.
We were both after the same thing.
I got too worked up...
and said things I
shouldn't have said to you.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
This is yours.
You can live an ordinary
life like you used to.
(Daebak Realty)
You surprised me.
I'm sorry.
Why are you out here?
I got scared.
Let's go.
Ji A.
"Ji A?"
Thank you.
If you let me stay just for tonight,
I'll go to a friend's place tomorrow.
Ms. Hong, I'll get going.
Get a good rest.
Thank you.
- Is Soo Jung all right?
- She's doing better.
She'll stay here tonight,
and go to a friend's tomorrow.
What?
It's not too late for you
to take her, so can you?
- No, I can't. - Why not?
I have a little something
called a private life.
- What about me? - She asked you.
She'd feel better to be with
someone who's closer to her age.
It's not like I've met her before.
Why did she call me by my name?
Chief Heo, you can take her, then.
Of course, I'd love to.
- But... - Didn't you see her?
My gosh.
After what she just went through,
wouldn't it be tough for her to
be with a guy even if it's him?
It's just for a night.
Offer her your consolation.
Consolation? Me?
The least you can do
is have a drink with her.
In the middle of the day?
Do you drink?
Sorry?
I'll find another tenant soon,
so move as quickly as possible.
Do you think it'll all be over once I move?
To be honest,
I doubt he'll give up easily
since he even killed someone.
No, I mean that spirit.
I don't think that spirit will let me go.
What do you mean?
To be honest,
I saw her on that day.
I saw her face at the very last moment.
Her eyes were...
crying out to me for help.
She asked for help. She
asked me to save her.
But I was too scared.
I got too scared and
pretended like I didn't know.
I told myself I saw something wrong.
I told myself that they knew each other,
so nothing bad will happen.
She's here! She came back.
I sent away that unrested spirit yesterday.
No, she's still here.
She has been following me
and bullying me since that day.
She died because of me!
She'll follow me
around until the day I die.
Get a grip.
Why would she bully you if
she died trying to save you?
What?
On that day, Lee Hyun Ju
got back on the elevator...
because she couldn't let
you be alone with him.
It won't be easy to do anything
bad if there were two of you.
She also came before
you as an unrested spirit...
because she knew Ma
Kwang Tae would come back.
I didn't know.
I really didn't know.
Lee Hyun Ju.
The person who saved you...
wasn't just a random woman
who was killed in the parking lot...
or the seventh-floor neighbor.
Her name was Lee Hyun Ju.
You of all people...
must remember her.
She was an actress of 12 years...
who had nothing else to brag about...
but her performances.
Despite barely having...
any time to sleep due to making ends meet,
she was on cloud nine when she found out...
that she'd perform in front of
an audience for the first time.
I'm sorry.
I truly am.
Make your choice.
Will you be a pathetic woman
tormented by guilt your entire life?
Or will you live your life
to the fullest for her sake?
I hadn't absorbed any memories for a while.
This is too excruciating.
They've still failed?
(Dohak Construction)
Every time they go there,
they claim to have seen a spirit.
Have they all gone insane?
- What was that? - It's a ghost!
They saw her. They looked her in the eye.
Gosh. I knew it.
I told you there was a
ghost in Daebak Realty.
Look at them running away.
(Jungbu Police Station)
You don't have to
believe what the spirit said.
But you must believe what I am telling you.
Sir, what are you craving for lunch?
We haven't had...
lunchboxes in a while.
- Okay. I'll buy them right now. - No.
I'll go.
Here's your bulgogi and shrimp lunchbox.
Thank you.
How's your shoulder by the way?
It's fine now.
How did you hurt it again?
I fell.
Just my luck.
Just your luck?
I also packed two beverages for free.
Why, thank you.
Your kitchen is more
spacious than I thought.
What is this design?
How unique.
Oh, that?
I bought the set after opening my shop.
I see.
"M" for Ma Kwang Tae.
- Here. - Thank you.
My pleasure.
(Lunchbox)
What has the chairman been up to?
You punk.
Eat up. It's on me.
You scumbag.
Don't be frightened.
We're not here to hurt you.
I'm telling you.
A spirit really resides at Daebak Realty.
To make matters worse,
it's Ms. Hong's mother.
That's nothing new.
Did you find out anything else?
Well... I do.
Of course, I do.
The mechanism of the exorcism.
It's quite simple.
She summons the spirit by lighting incense.
Then the psychic becomes
possessed by the spirit.
Lastly, she stabs the psychic. Game over.
Game over?
That's it?
Look at you guys.
What is this? It's that simple?
"Simple"? Not at all.
It's extremely dangerous.
It is?
They risk their lives every time.
That's why a preliminary
inspection is a must.
A preliminary inspection?
Yes, that's right.
It's something they do
before the official exorcism.
It's like a rehearsal.
Late at night, they go
to the haunted house.
Ms. Hong and Oh In Bum.
Just them two. Gosh, it's just them.
On top of that,
this is an extremely
terrifying and dangerous task.
Just them two?
(From sunset to sunrise)
Ji A.
Are you leaving?
Can you do me a favor?
No.
We must.
Let's just leave this to the police.
The police won't believe me
until they have firm evidence.
We must catch him red-handed.
You're talking about a murderer.
No. I won't allow it.
I'm terrified too.
But I must do this.
But still, luring him
yourself is just too dangerous.
I can't let him roam around freely.
Sooner or later, there
will be other victims.
And some of them will be murdered as well.
My gosh.
Ms. Hong, say something.
Are you sure you won't regret this?
Yes, I am.
Set up the cameras as soon as you can.
Ms. Hong.
Thank you, Ji A.
Is this because of the
memory you've absorbed?
Once the exorcisms were over,
you never took part in anything.
It's because of Bae Soo Jung.
Sorry?
Has she grown on you already?
We need to catch Ma Kwang Tae...
for her to be free of guilt
and live her life to the fullest.
I know very well how it
feels to be tormented by guilt...
all your life.
She still has...
a chance.
(Lunchbox)
You have nothing to do here.
Just go back to your office.
You're much more shameless than I thought.
I didn't expect you to return.
I have nothing to hide anymore.
That's why I came back.
Haven't you heard?
Ms. Hong and I reconciled.
She gave this necklace back to me.
She wanted me to have it.
What?
Chief Heo, Ma Kwang
Tae has entered the lobby.
(Out on Delivery)
Why are you doing this?
Be quiet.
You and I aren't dating.
You snuck in here with the
passcode you secretly found out.
Soo Jung. I'm sure you'll like it too.
Why won't you just do what I say?
Do you want to end up
dead just like that wench?
Is that why you killed Lee Hyun Ju?
Yes.
I really hate women who don't listen to me.
I also hate men who don't listen to me.
Are you okay?
Oh, my gosh!
Be careful!
That scumbag! Oh, my gosh.
Hello. There's a trespasser.
He has a knife too. Please hurry.
Ma Kwang Tae!
Hello? Is this 911?
Ms. Hong.
(Ma Kwang...)
(Ma Kwang Tae)
What a lowlife.
Are you okay?
Who on earth are you guys?
Why won't you just do what I say?
Do you want to end up
dead just like that wench?
Is that why you killed Lee Hyun Ju?
Yes.
I really hate women who don't listen to me.
Everything looks good.
You guys can go home now.
What?
But a man died. We can't let them go.
No, they can go. He died in a car accident.
I'll call you if I need
to question you again.
Let's go.
But still. I don't think we
should just release them.
No, they can leave.
I witnessed the scene myself.
And we got the murder weapon as well.
Let's wait until we get
the report from the NFS.
(Kind, Present, and Swift Police)
Ji A.
Go and get some sleep
and forget everything.
Thank you so much for everything.
Well, Soo Jung.
Can I drop you off at your friend's house?
No. You must feel uncomfortable in my car.
No, Ji Chul. I would appreciate it.
Thank you. I mean it.
Are you sure?
Let's go.
- I'll drop you off. - Sure.
(Daebak Realty)
We aren't open...
The door was opened.
We found Lee Hyun Ju's DNA on Ma Kwang Tae's knife.
And on his computer,
we found many videos and photos he took of Bae Soo Jung...
and many other women illegally.
That's great news.
I thought I should let you know what happened.
All right.
Is that all you came to say?
To be honest, there's something I'd like to ask.
This is something Ms. Hong drew in the interrogation room.
And...
this is the knife Ma Kwang Tae used to kill Lee Hyun Ju.
Only the culprit and the victim would know the mark on the knife.
How did Ms. Hong know that so accurately?
I'm sure she already explained herself...
when she drew you this picture.
Can she really see...
the memories of a spirit through an exorcism ritual?
I still find it hard to believe.
You always believe only the things you can see.
Why did you kill them?
I didn't want them to become burdens.
Isn't it obvious?
Was there something I wasn't aware of then?
There is a karmic connection to everything.
I'll take that.
Okay.
What's that?
I want to study for the police employment test.
The police?
There are way too many bad people in this world.
To this day, I lived my life just hoping...
I'd never run into one.
But no matter how careful I am, I can always come across one.
So I decided to just catch them myself.
Gosh, Soo Jung. You're so cool.
Why do I see Ms. Hong in her?
You're going to perform an exorcism on Oh Sung Sik's spirit?
All of a sudden? What are you talking about?
It's not a sudden decision. I gave this a lot of thought.
In order to find out what happened 20 years ago,
I have to look into his memory.
You don't even know if he has memories of that day.
I never know until I give it a try.
You can't do that.
It's too dangerous.
Did you forget what happened last time?
When Oh Sung Sik possessed In Bum, he broke Do Hak Sung's arm.
What will you do if he ends up killing him?
I'll stop him so that it doesn't happen.
Is it because Oh Sung Sik is In Bum's uncle?
Ms. Hong.
In Bum doesn't know his uncle is still here as an unrested spirit.
It might be better for him to live his life not knowing it.
Do you really think so?
If you live obliviously to the truth that's out there,
do you think that'll be it?
And it's not only because of In Bum.
I also had this thought after I met Bae Soo Jung.
That 20-year-old girl...
risked her life to catch that murderer.
But...
even though I said I wanted to let my mom go,
I never did anything about it.
What do you mean, you didn't do anything?
You've done everything you could, but it simply didn't work out.
Once we find a suitable psychic...
We've never done an exorcism on Oh Sung Sik.
You've changed.
I made myself clear and said you shouldn't do it.
If you really want to do this,
you'll need to fire me first.
This is driving me crazy.
I get what Ms. Ju is worried about,
but I need to do it.
This is the only way.
The problem is if I'm going to tell In Bum or not.
What would you do, Mom?
I have no idea. My head hurts.
It might be a better idea not to do this.
I know I dressed you up, but you look perfect today.
Really?
I have to look good today.
You do look good, like a celebrity.
Do you want to see?
You're right.
I don't look too bad.
I can't believe this.
This is my last date with her right after our first one.
A con artist and a police officer.
Cheer up, Ji Chul.
Boarding academies are different from the army, right?
They can stay out once a month,
and they can use their phones too.
It's the army. It sounds like the army.
I can't do this.
I need to join an online community...
of people with girlfriends in boarding academies.
Go ahead.
Make sure you brace yourself and see her off.
Don't start bawling in front of her academy.
Can I really hold back my tears?
I don't think I can do that.
You can do it!
In Bum, get ready and come out.
- What? - I'll buy you a meal.
A meal?
Is she asking you out?
Stop talking nonsense.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
How do I look? I wanted to go with black and white.
Are you playing a game of go?
Whatever.
What do you want to say? You look serious.
Just say it.
Do you remember the time...
when Do Hak Sung caught you and hung you upside down?
How can I forget?
Hey, wait!
The unrested spirit on him suddenly possessed you...
and attacked him.
We both know that. Why are you telling me this again?
That unrested spirit is...
your uncle.
- What? - Your uncle, Oh Sung Sik,
became an unrested spirit and remained next to Do Hak Sung.
Stop joking around.
Stop joking!
When did you find out?
From the moment I saw him.
I've never forgotten the face of my mom's last client.
Had I revealed who I was early on,
you would've told me this sooner.
Let's help him find peace.
Why are you hesitating?
For this exor...
No.
This time,
I don't want you to get involved.
He was your uncle.
Absorbing a stranger's memories is painful enough.
A beloved's memories...
will be excruciating.
You promised you'll give us an apartment unit.
- What? - I set the place on fire...
and killed people.
Give me the apartment.
He may not be who you think he was.
I even considered hiring another psychic without you knowing.
Perhaps, I may be able to find out...
how to send my mom away by reading his memories.
That's why...
I must absorb them myself.
But remember what you said?
- "No matter..." - No matter how gruesome the truth,
I wanted to find out.
Frankly, I'm terrified.
Like you said,
I'm scared I'll find out that he was a worthless man.
But I've been in the dark, suspecting him and feeling afraid...
for the last 20 years.
I'm done with that.
So don't worry.
After all, I'm a special psychic.
Unrested spirits stuck on people are different from ones in houses.
Do Hak Sung must cooperate or the exorcism won't work.
But will he?
We'll make him.
Any ideas?
That's our specialty.
Right. Scamming people.
We're professionals.
Scammers.
I'll meet him myself.
Chief Heo, you do the rest.
Will he agree to see you?
He will.
I'll say I'm here to talk about selling Daebak Realty.
I'm here to clean.
Is anyone here?
Sit down.
(Chairman Do Hak Sung)
I heard you're here about selling Daebak Realty.
Did Ms. Hong finally make up her mind?
Yes.
Oh, is that so?
Gosh.
She has decided...
never to sell to you.
What are you talking about?
I had a question.
I knew you wouldn't meet with me, so I had to be sly.
You must have a death wish.
Please. Of course not.
Okay.
You.
You've met my uncle before, haven't you?
And who's he?
Oh Sung Sik.
Oh Sung Sik?
Oh Sung...
Oh, that shantytown arsonist?
I heard you came to him right before he died.
Why?
Do you not know?
If I did, would I be asking you?
I didn't look for him.
He called me over and asked for some money.
- What? - He demanded an apartment...
since he set the place on fire...
and ultimately got the area chosen for redevelopment.
He threatened to tell the police that I had ordered him to do so...
if I didn't abide by his demand.
Don't you dare lie.
My uncle...
was never the type who'd do something like that for money.
Actually,
people do all sorts of things for money.
Come in.
How's it going?
We've already hired some actors.
- Get it over with. - Yes, sir.
It's been a while since we scammed someone.
It was thrilling and exciting.
Why the long face? Were you not able to set the camera?
Never mind. Let's go.
There are three key places.
First, the large meeting room. Second, the emergency stairs.
And third, the chairman's office.
But oddly enough, the last one's not working.
What do you mean? I did my job.
Is that so?
Then why isn't the camera working? It was brand new.
Don't worry about his office.
An unrested spirit already lives there.
Oh, right.
Okay. We're done setting up everything.
Just a little push,
and the rumors will spread like wildfire.
First, the intranet will go nuts.
After that, it'll rank first place in ghost story websites.
Once the rumors are posted in tabloids...
Do Hak Sung will hear about it.
And this actually works?
Just trust us and be patient.
This worked every single time.
That's right.
Three days from now, Dohak Construction will call you.
This is Hong Ji A from Daebak Realty.
Dohak Construction?
Already?
Sure. Okay.
What did they say?
I'll be seeing them tomorrow.
What did I tell you?
This is how good we are.
Sure.
(2002, From Golden Construction to Dohak Construction)
(Ceremony for the Redevelopment of Golden Apartment)
Hello.
The chairman is waiting for you.
Okay. I'll take care of it.
We'll talk again next time.
Bye.
Sit down.
A strange rumor has been going around our company lately.
People are claiming to have witnessed a ghost.
I heard you're an expert in this field.
I need the help of a professional.
So what's your take on this?
Based on the amount of energy I'm getting,
I'm sure you felt it too.
What?
An unrested spirit is lingering around you.
- And? - I'll drive it out.
An exorcism?
- How much will that cost? - I don't need your money.
I just need to do the exorcism.
That's right. You can't ask me for money.
Unless your scam is planned thoroughly,
you won't be able to make any money off it.
That's how the world works.
I thought I checked all the security cameras.
I don't know how that happened.
We can't change what already happened.
Let's go with plan B.
Don't look at me like that. Just hear me out.
Don't we just need Do Hak Sung to perform the exorcism?
So what? Are you suggesting that we should kidnap him?
Bingo.
Do Hak Sung kidnapped us, hung me upside, and beat me up.
- Why can't we do the same? - Yes. He has a point.
I'll pretend that you never said that.
We don't have any other way. Do you have any other plans?
I'm thinking. Shut your mouth.
Good evening.
What are you guys doing here?
What's with the mood here?
Were you badmouthing me or something?
- Ms. Hong. You have a visitor. - Okay.
Gosh. My heart is breaking.
But how come we're keeping this from Ms. Ju?
I'm not sure.
I need the money urgently for my business.
So I want to sell the factory that closed down quickly.
But everyone who came to see the factory...
saw a ghost there, so no one wants to buy the place.
It's driving me crazy.
So you didn't see the ghost yourself?
Yes, I did. I saw it myself.
That's why I'm here.
The electricity is cut off there, and I locked up the warehouse.
No one can get in there.
Is anyone there?
Who is it?
Come on out.
Then, I don't remember what happened next.
When I woke up, I was at the hospital.
Did someone die at the factory?
Gosh, no way. I'm the owner there. I would know if someone died there.
I'll go and check it out.
You don't have to do it today.
I just want to get some air.
(Daebak Realty)
See you later.
Yes?
When will you tell Ms. Ju?
Only when I have a definite lead.
If I tell her without a lead, she'll just nag me.
It's not because you don't trust her?
Ms. Ju is...
the only person I trust in this world.
Am I late?
What did you want to talk about?
You are as expected. You are a bold woman.
You get right to the point.
Gosh. This place is scary.
Can you see anything?
Everything seems fine so far.
Gosh. Why is it so cold when electricity was cut off...
in this cold storage warehouse?
I knew it. Is it because of the unrested spirit?
No. There's no unrested spirit.
This place doesn't have any traces of unrested spirits either.
What? Then, why is it so cold in here?
Naturally, the warehouse is in the middle of the mountain,
so it's bound to be cold here.
That's probably why people said that this place was haunted.
Gosh. Seriously?
We had to drive pretty far to get here at this hour.
Isn't it better to have one less unrested spirit in the world?
That's true.
What?
Ms. Hong came to see me.
She threatened me and said that there was a ghost next to me.
And she told me that she would get rid of the ghost for me.
So?
What did you say?
I'm asking this out of pure curiosity.
What's her angle?
What did you say to her?
Why are you curious about that?
Don't tell me that you agreed to it.
What are you guys doing?
What are you plotting?
So you don't want to tell me.
Then, you leave me no choice.
Is anyone out there?
Darn it. It's freezing in here.
Oh, no.
It's freezing.
Use me at least to stay warm.
I'm your heating pack.
Are you stupid?
You can only bring up my body temperature...
when it goes down after dealing with the unrested spirits.
Even so, I want to keep holding your hand.
Ms. Hong.
If we die here...
like a pair of fools,
would we turn into unrested spirits too?
I don't want that.
Don't say stupid stuff like that.
We're not going to die.
I will not die before I see my mother off.
I cannot die.
Mom.
(Daebak Realty)
(Sell Your Haunted House)
It was me? You despised me?
Is it because I didn't stab you as you asked?
Why are you here looking like that?
Why would you go alone? It's dangerous.
Why do you keep going out alone? Am I that unhelpful?
It's time.
If I went this far, In Bum has to believe me.
What the heck is that brat up to? I need to see this for myself.
That's my only condition.
Do you think you're the only one Oh Sung Sik met with...
at Ilsung Hospital right before he died?
I'm in my right mind.
This is something that has to be done.
Wait, you didn't call another psychic, did you?