You're here. Didn't you enjoy the macaroons?
In Bum. That kid from 20 years ago is...
you?
Was it you?
Yes.
Tell me. What happened on that day?
Tell me what caused...
my mother's death on that day.
- Tell me! - How would I know?
I'm here to find that out too.
- What? - What did your mother do...
to my uncle on that day...
to cause his death? I wanted to know.
Are you suggesting that Oh Sung Sik died because of my mom?
He was the one who attacked her on that day.
Your uncle took his own life.
He couldn't deal with the guilt after murdering someone.
You can't just claim whatever you want.
Do you want me to tell you why Oh Sung Sik died?
Because you're a psychic.
If it hadn't been for you, your uncle and my mother...
would be alive.
No one would've died.
The one who killed my mother is...
you.
That's enough, you two.
Get out.
I never want to see you again.
Hey, In Bum. Hey.
(Daebak Realty)
The one who killed my mother is...
you.
Did you already know about it?
I found out a few hours ago.
I received a call from Mr. Jung...
and was shocked.
Maybe he tried to con us by using his history.
He was the first person.
It must've been tough.
I've only done it once, and it's already unbearable.
But you've been doing this singlehandedly for that long.
He could truly empathize with me...
about this painful ordeal I've been going through.
The mere thought of knowing that I wasn't alone in this...
gave me a great sense of comfort.
I even felt sorry toward him.
What a scumbag.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I didn't know he caused your death.
I worked with him...
and even thought that he was a decent guy.
I'm sorry for being so stupid.
Now,
I have no idea...
what I should do.
Uncle.
I don't know anything anymore.
Were you truly an evil person?
Or...
was I the root...
of everything?
Don't you dare run away.
(Oh Sung Sik's Grave)
Have you been well?
What have you gotten yourself into?
Nothing.
Some men turned this place upside down.
They were looking for something.
What was it?
Yesterday, a woman stopped by too.
(Oh In Bum)
(Lunchbox)
Welcome.
Here's your food.
I had some leftover fried shrimp, so I put them in as well.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Aren't you getting in?
No, it's going up.
- Darn it. - Hello.
Oh, you're from Unit 602. You're late.
Has anyone rented out the unit yet?
We only recently put it on sale.
Can you just give me back my deposit?
I'm too terrified.
- Last night... - Talking about spirits again?
You're a grown woman. Why are you so scared of them?
But someone died there.
I'm not the murderer.
If you're that terrified, come home early.
You're always out until late.
Don't blame the house.
Better yet, how about you find some potential tenants?
Really?
Then can I rent it out to my acquaintance?
Open the door!
Help me!
Please open the door.
Help me.
Hey, aren't you getting in?
Please open the door.
Help me! Please open the door!
Please open the door!
Hey!
What's going on? Wake up!
Hello?
Is this 911?
(Daebak Realty)
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.
In Bum, please pick up, will you?
You startled me!
- What do you want? - Well...
Did In Bum and Ms. Hong go on a trip or something?
- What? - I just haven't seen them lately.
- Are they seeing each other? - Don't be absurd.
What?
Daebak Realty 24-1.
Something is definitely going on between them.
The atmosphere is ice-cold.
It feels like I've been stabbed with a knife.
- Mom? - The deliveries are overdue.
Deliveries?
Right, I should go.
I should go now.
Goodness, here she is.
Hey.
Like you asked, I've been keeping an eye on her.
But she hasn't been doing anything.
She didn't order any food yesterday.
I'll go check on her. You can go now.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Ms. Hong!
Hong Ji A!
Gosh. Where did she go?
Ms. Hong?
- You startled me. - Oh, my.
When did you get here?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
You called?
My battery died.
How long have you been down here?
What time is it now?
Did you even eat?
I thought you weren't hungry.
I didn't eat anything for two days. Of course, I'm hungry.
Relax.
- I've been thinking. - Stop thinking.
Once I found that kid, I thought...
I would be able to find out what happened that day.
But he remembered less than me.
So no matter how much I think about this, books are my answer.
The saying, "Knowledge is power," must come from somewhere.
So did knowledge yield any fruit?
There are way too many books.
My ancestors' Record of Exorcism is way too extensive.
And there are way too many ancient texts.
They should have at least written it in Korean...
once the Korean alphabet was invented.
Everything was written in Chinese.
Do you know what's more frustrating? The prepositions are in Korean.
At a glance, I feel like I could make sense of it.
Gosh. This is just torture. Seriously.
Why do you think my battery died?
I used up all my battery, looking up Chinese letters.
My gosh, I looked and looked,
but I can't find anything on that egg ghost.
Did they use a different name back then?
Please eat.
I'll find another psychic for you.
I'll get going.
Make sure to keep your phone on.
I said, I got it.
Stop reminding me.
Bye.
(Flower Shop)
- Hello. - Hi.
I'm going on my first date. Can you recommend me a flower?
Gosh.
Hello.
You look prettier than in your picture.
It's our first date in person.
So I prepared a flower that resembles your beauty.
Gosh. That was so cheesy. Goodness.
No.
Hello. I'm Heo Ji Chul.
Gosh.
What should I say to her? This is driving me crazy.
What should I say?
Ji Chul?
Hello.
They went like, "Chief Heo."
They were trying to stop me. "No, Chief Heo."
And they were laughing like this.
When I was saying hello, he just went like this.
So I went like this.
After that, no one laughed!
And then, it got all quiet.
My story is boring, isn't it?
- No. - Should we get going then?
Ji Chul.
You said you work at a real estate agency, right?
Yes.
(Daebak Realty)
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Do you guys specialize in handling haunted houses?
Yes. Please come in.
They all seem to know when we open like spirits know everything.
Go in.
(Daebak Realty)
(From sunset to sunrise)
You've seen the spirit yourself?
Yes. A month ago, someone was murdered...
in the building I live in now.
The spirit of the deceased keeps showing up and is torturing me.
Did you know the deceased?
No.
I've only seen her drunk a few times. That's it.
Darn it.
Why won't this open?
Is it broken?
What? She's drunk.
Finally.
What? Who are you?
You came to the wrong unit.
No. This is my house.
- This is Unit 702. - This is Unit 602.
Oh, my. Goodness. I must be losing it.
I'm sorry.
I live upstairs in Unit 702.
Are you in college?
She was pretty famous in the building.
Her hairstyle and outfits always stood out.
People saw guys carrying her home because she was drunk.
Did you kill her?
- Pardon? - If you saw her only a few times,
why would she want to bother you?
She's asking if you know anything about the murder.
I was...
the last person to see her.
Soo Jung, are you sure...
you didn't see the guy's face in the elevator?
Or did you notice any unusual?
No. He was wearing a mask and a hat too.
I really thought they knew each other.
This is frustrating.
Please help me. I have no place to go.
I can't keep staying with my friend.
We must check if the house is indeed haunted first,
so you must wait.
I'm telling you that it is.
I've seen her several times.
You might be mistaken.
You didn't tell them I referred them to you, right?
No.
But she can't get rid of the spirit right away.
She must check first.
I see. That's called a preliminary inspection.
She must check if there is an unrested spirit at the house.
If Ms. Hong said she'd do a preliminary inspection,
she's going to take your case.
- Really? - Of course.
- You trust me. Don't you? - Yes.
But why can't I tell them that you referred them to me?
You said you were the co-CEO.
Well,
I don't know how to explain this to you.
You know, Mr. Oh. I mean, Chief Oh, right?
Chief Oh In Bum.
My junior caused a huge mess at work.
So people at work are on edge.
I see.
You should try some of it. You lost a lot of weight.
Thank you.
Grandma, why did Uncle...
commit suicide?
Who said that? He didn't kill himself.
You might believe that because you are his mother,
but the world thinks otherwise.
The police already closed the case.
- And there's also evidence. - Evidence?
This is proof.
Why would my kind-hearted son kill himself?
My gosh.
(Military Mail)
The fire that broke out on November 15 in Yongnam Village...
was a deliberate act of arson I committed.
After the announcement of unexpected redevelopment,
I couldn't stand the thought of how I'll be kicked out...
from my house into the street without reasonable compensation.
When I got drunk, I did something I shouldn't have.
I wish to confess everything I did and pay for my crimes.
I'm so sorry.
She was right.
Ms. Hong's mother passed away because of my uncle and me.
Where are you going?
I have to go.
There's something I need to do.
Bye.
Get your act straight!
Hey! How many times do I have to tell you?
It's not like I'm playing around.
Do you want to see me get mad?
Why can't you do this if you have those boys?
Jung Pil runs an employment agency, right?
Contact him too.
Old habits never go away. That thug.
Write this down.
Name, Yang Chang Hwa. Age, 32.
He left home ten years ago, and he went out of touch.
He's the son of this family I'm staying with!
Hey! It's me, Kim Tae Jin.
Find him now.
What?
He was a thug who returns favors?
A month ago,
Lee Hyun Ju, a tenant here...
was killed in the underground parking lot.
Since then, people have been seeing an unrested spirit in this building.
It's also unfortunate because she made a police report...
saying she saw a suspicious man lurking around the building...
and also said she feels the security is too lax,
but they all ignored her.
Has the culprit been caught?
The CCTV near the elevator is the only camera that caught him.
But it only got the top of his head.
He changed his target during the act.
Sorry?
One second.
You're right.
Does she think she died in Bae Soo Jung's place?
Is that why she holds a grudge?
But why did she hop back inside?
I need to go see the place.
(From sunset to sunrise)
- We need to talk. - I have nothing to say.
(Daebak Realty)
We would've caught the culprit already...
only if the CCTV worked on that day.
It's probably someone who knows this building very well.
He knew this CCTV was broken.
We lost someone's life over a petty repair cost.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Goodbye.
- Sir. - Yes?
- May we put up some wanted posters? - Yes, go ahead.
I guess kids keep tearing it down.
Goodness, are you all right?
I recently hurt my shoulder a little.
Let me get it.
Goodness, thank you.
So you haven't caught the culprit yet?
Goodness. We couldn't find any lead or clue,
but there's a rumor of ghost sightings here.
I heard about that too.
Goodbye, then.
- All right. Thank you. - Sure.
- Goodbye. - Goodbye.
Do you feel like it's unfair?
Do you blame her?
But you can't turn back the time.
You need to forget it.
You don't belong here anymore.
You're done, right?
I saw the unrested spirit.
Please call Hyung Sik.
She was just talking to a ghost, right?
Is that what it looked like to you?
I thought she was talking nonsense in the middle of the air.
Look at my goosebumps. This is real.
(Land, Private Properties, Commercial Buildings, Rent)
What do you have to tell me?
On the day I first came here,
I remembered something I had forgotten all my life,
the memories I have of this place.
Die. Die!
Uncle.
To this day,
I lived my life without any idea...
why my uncle had to die so suddenly.
But on that day, it felt like I finally had a lead.
I thought everything would become clear...
once I found out what exactly happened here...
on that night 20 years ago.
Hey! Are you okay?
- Gosh! You're bleeding? - Aren't you Jung Hoon?
Why am I here?
Are you crazy? Did you do that?
You little punk. Why did you do something so dangerous?
Gosh, look at him.
Grandma.
(Our houses may be deprived, but not us!)
Uncle, I really...
I know.
It's okay.
I know very well that you didn't do that, In Bum.
I believe you.
He was the only person who was on my side.
I must've wanted to have the same amount of trust in him...
as he did for me.
Perhaps, that was why I couldn't accept the fact...
that he had taken so many lives...
and committed suicide.
Is that it?
Is that why you came here?
I wanted to sincerely apologize.
Had we never come here that day,
your mother would've still been alive.
I'm truly sorry.
I'm also sorry...
for deceiving you.
Okay.
Are you going to stop looking into your uncle's death?
No.
There are still too many unanswered questions.
Then what will you do?
I'll have to think about that.
But one thing for sure is that...
I can no longer stay at Daebak Realty.
Right.
Does this mean we'll continue to scam people?
Let's look for something legitimate to do.
We should also move out.
No! We're not moving.
- Why not? - Soo Jung is Ms. Hong's client...
right now.
What?
Assemblyman Han.
Thanks to your help in the Bangso-dong's redevelopment,
I truly feel so reassured.
I will do my best...
to make your future rosy.
I'm not here today to be flattered by you.
- Sorry? - I heard...
that there are still many residents who are refusing to move out.
Oh, that?
There aren't that many anymore.
It'll all get sorted out soon. Don't you worry about that.
What if there's a change in the market?
They can easily withdraw their permission...
on the redevelopment.
I don't want to suffer because of your mistakes.
Get this over with before the election.
In the past, you were lucky enough...
to hit the jackpot in these redevelopment cases.
I guess your luck has run out.
(Daebak Realty)
(Lee Hyun Ju)
The parking lot will be blocked off, right?
Yes, I've already talked with the landlord.
When is In Bum arriving?
Did you mean Hyung Sik?
He should be here soon.
- Hello. - Hey.
Hyung Sik!
- Long time, no see. - Likewise.
In Bum, get the salt...
Sorry?
Make sure you pack plenty of salt.
This unrested spirit won't be easy.
Okay.
Hey. I'm home.
Don't be sorry.
Your parents came all of a sudden. I understand.
I'm grateful that you allowed me to stay there until now.
Okay. Good luck with your studies.
Hello?
A Young.
Now.
I apologize for the long wait.
That wench got in my way that night,
so I couldn't come to you.
Finally. It's just the two of us here.
Darn it.
You... Darn it.
What?
Why...
Stop it now.
Don't move.
Drop your dagger and get up.
I don't have time for that.
Hey.
Who are you to come between me and Soo Jung?
Drop it and get on your feet.
The next shot is for real.
Hey. Are you okay?
What?
We're the police.
Hey, get up. Get up.
My goodness.
Gosh.
Trespass?
That's a misunderstanding. I'm really innocent.
Then, why were you there?
I went there to see Soo Jung.
"Soo Jung?"
What about you? Why did you go there?
Bae Soo Jung is my client.
Are you saying that you are her muscle?
Ms. Bae, is she telling the truth?
Of course, she should be here too.
That's the guy.
Pardon?
- What did you say? - The guy...
who killed the lady from Unit 702 in the parking lot.
He's the guy.
Are you telling me...
that he's the culprit of the parking lot murder case?
Gosh. Goodness.
When I questioned you, you said you couldn't see...
his face because of the mask and the hat.
When you questioned me, I wasn't sure if it was him.
But I am certain now.
Why are you doing this to me?
- Sit down! - Sit.
Did I upset you in any way?
Sit. Sit down.
Let's separate the victim and the attacker first.
"Attacker?"
I'm really innocent. I really am.
(Trustworthy Police)
Wait outside.
Don't worry.
I'm going to wait right by the door until the questioning is over.
Why would I want to harm Soo Jung?
You must've been close to Ms. Bae.
Actually, we are dating.
What?
She told me her passcode, so I could enter when I wanted to.
I had never told him my passcode.
What?
Soo Jung comes to my restaurant practically every day.
Naturally, we became close.
- I see. - I treated her like my sister.
And she treated me like her brother.
Sir, aren't you married?
Right.
So I went there today to break things off with her.
But Soo Jung couldn't accept it.
It's all my fault.
I understand why she was upset.
Ridiculous.
A real estate agency that performs exorcisms.
Okay. Let's sum it up.
With Ms. Bae's request,
you went to send off the spirit at the parking lot.
You went to the parking lot,
burned the incense, scattered some salt,
entered Ms. Bae's house, and made a mess.
You did all of these to get rid of the spirit?
Fine. Did you get rid of the spirit?
I don't remember anything.
Psychics can't remember what happens when they're possessed.
Unbelievable. Do you think this is a joke?
You'd better answer my questions!
You'd better do your job right.
What?
If you watched the elevator security footage...
of the day the murder happened, you would've figured out...
that Bae Soo Jung was the culprit's initial target.
But Lee Hyun Ju who got off the elevator...
got on the elevator again.
When his plan went south, he changed his target.
The culprit...
was extremely enraged against Lee Hyun Ju...
for messing up the dream he had for a very long time.
So the murder became a revenge killing.
He murdered her at the blind spot he spotted before the act.
Let go.
But Lee Hyun Ju didn't make it easy for him.
There was a struggle.
The culprit was severely injured that his shoulder was dislocated.
So the spirit told you everything?
You have a wild imagination.
You don't have to believe what the spirit said.
But you must believe what I am telling you.
Not every stalker becomes a murderer.
I can't investigate someone just based on suspicions...
and treat him like a suspect. Okay?
I can't do that even if you might be right about this.
I must follow a proper protocol to confirm my findings.
What's this?
The knife the culprit used to stab the victim.
(Kind, Present, and Swift Police)
Soo Jung, are you all right?
Are you two acquainted?
She's his girlfriend.
I only found out after Chief Heo called.
I thought you wouldn't do it if I asked you to.
I'm sorry.
Let's go, Soo Jung.
Why does he get to leave?
He broke in and entered,
but this was his first offense, and there was no damage.
Aren't first offenses also crimes?
How much more damage does she have to suffer?
Let's go.
Ji A.
"Ji A?"
Are you sure you can let Ma Kang Tae go?
What else could we do?
When you saw the footage from the elevator,
you also said it looks like Lee Hyun Ju died instead of her.
And since Ma Kang Tae is Bae Soo Jung's stalker,
it makes perfect sense.
There's no evidence. Nothing.
We have Ms. Hong from Daebak Realty as a witness.
How are we going to tell anyone that she heard it from a ghost?
This is driving me crazy too.
What happened?
Soo Jung was so shocked that she won't even look at me.
It's all because of that jerk.
What about the exorcism?
Is Ms. Hong all right? Is she hurt?
She's fine, of course.
But Soo Jung is really...
It must've been freezing without me.
What are you doing?
What do you mean?
If you're going to be like this, go work as her psychic again...
instead of pestering me!
My head is already filled with what happened to Soo Jung.
Why won't you read my messages? You're making me worried.
It'd be okay to pop in and see her,
right?
No, I'm overreacting.
(Daebak Realty)
(Changhwa Restaurant)
You came out here worried about Ms. Hong again.
What are you saying? I came out to get some air.
What are you so worried about?
She looked completely fine to me.
She was brutally murdered.
It's unbearable when you get memories like that.
Don't you remember what happened after that water ghost?
Yes, right. I remember.
I thought the worst might happen and got really scared.
I was scared too.
Scared I might kill that murderer.
Hey, Ms. Hong.
Is Soo Jung...
Is she still angry at you?
No, that's the aftermath of a ghost's possession.
(Blue Theater Works)
("Pride and Prejudice" starring Lee Hyun Ju)
(We're delayed indefinitely due to the main cast's personal affair.)
(We will fully refund your tickets. We're sorry for the inconvenience.)
Ms. Hong.
What are you two doing here?
I can explain. What happened is...
(Sell Your Haunted House)
Haven't you heard? Ms. Hong and I made up.
Did she grow on you overnight?
In Bum, get ready and come out.
Did she ask you out on a date?
You're going to perform an exorcism on Oh Sung Sik's spirit?
Are you sure you won't give up?
Is it because Oh Sung Sik is In Bum's uncle?
You wanted to know the truth no matter how gruesome it is, right?
I'll make sure something like that doesn't happen.
We were both after the same thing.
You can live an ordinary life like you used to.
Why won't you listen?
Do you want to die like that brat?
Back then, was there something I didn't know?
There is...