♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 37=
Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
What's that?
Two Soul Masters trust each other,
and their Soul Power turns into a new power.
There will be a huge enhancement
by complementing each other.
When Master taught "The Principles of Soul Burst",
there was this theoretical knowledge.
You forgot it?
I...
After watching these matches,
everyone except Wu,
come to me
for additional theory classes.
No.
I remember
I took notes in every class.
This...
Master.
Tell me about this...
What's wrong?
This seems to be formed by Martial Soul.
Your intuition is accurate.
Tool Soul?
Whose?
Cang Hui Battle Team, including me,
has five people in total.
Except for a few of my friends,
there's a guy
who has never shown his Martial Soul.
But Shi Nian
insisted to let him join the battle team.
So this arrow
is that person's Martial Soul?
Shi Nian told me to take this
to Martial Soul Hall.
Since we're cooperating,
I think I should tell you about this.
What are you going to do in Martial Soul Hall?
I don't know.
Someone will meet me there.
It makes sense now.
What makes sense?
Does the person know you?
He'll recognize this.
I'll go on your behalf.
Are you sure?
It might be dangerous.
Let me go, since it's dangerous.
Aren't you afraid?
Great.
The combination of speed and power.
Let me assist on the side.
This is my battlefield!
You watch it on the side!
I won't lose to this kid!
See how I will crush him!
Again!
You lost.
Step aside.
This is my battlefield too.
Step aside!
Your Highness!
How are you?
If he doesn't get treatment immediately,
he may die.
Tell him when he's awake.
I have a partner who I can trust
and the determination
to live and die together.
As for him,
he has nothing but himself.
This is why he was defeated.
The first match in Group A,
Shi Lan Ke wins.
Xing Luo Royal Battle Team is out.
This is the power
of Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
If you become my disciple,
I can teach you more skills.
Thanks for your advice.
But without Shi Lan Ke
and Zhu Zhu Qing,
I can't use Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
They are the source of my power.
You're amazing, Brother Dai.
You finally defeated your elder brother.
You guys are amazing.
Great.
You two not only overcame your opponents,
but also yourselves.
Thanks for your recognition.
But if it's a duel,
he's better than me.
But I have you all.
I won't lose.
Fine. Don't talk about us.
You have Sister Qing.
What's wrong?
I'm telling the truth.
My father said
Martial Soul Fusion Skill
requires good understanding
between two people
to perform.
You see.
Those who are able to use
Martial Soul Fusion Skill so far
have been couples.
That's true.
What nonsense is this?
We are a team.
That's why we trust each other.
A team?
Brother Dai and I are teammates too.
Why can't we do it?
Try it.
Rong Rong.
We can try.
What does it have to do with you?
We're in the Support Branch.
What fusion?
Fuse into a big supportive sandbag?
That...
Master.
We won today.
Can you take us
to a big meal?
Right?
Yes.
There have been indeed a lot of expenses
along the way so far.
Yes.
Of course I'll treat you.
Great!
You're always stingy.
Why are you generous suddenly?
They finally made it to the final.
They make Shi Lan Ke glorious.
After watching the matches today,
of course we need to celebrate!
Right?
Wu.
Wait for me here.
Go together.
Do you know
what I've just figured out?
I don't know.
I want to go with you anyway.
The library where Master and I entered
requires a token.
I know.
You told me
that Hu Lie Na had given it to you.
The person who stole the records
was also in the library.
What does it mean?
It means
he has a token too?
Senior Du Gu and other Grand Soul Land Masters
are all hiding in Martial Soul City.
This is the headquarters of Martial Soul Hall.
But no one found them.
You mean...
Someone in Martial Soul Hall
must have joined hands with Cang Hui.
And this person has authority.
That's why he can play these tricks
under
the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
We might meet
this person in a moment.
Think about it.
Isn't it dangerous?
Yes.
So you shouldn't go.
When I'm in danger,
will you stay with me?
Things have changed in the Star Forest.
The Grand Soul Land Masters
are not in Martial Soul City.
No matter how dangerous it is,
we won't meet someone with Nine Soul Rings.
Promise me.
If there's danger,
you must leave immediately.
Okay.
I run the fastest.
Follow me.
Drink some water.
Thanks.
Do you want to go back and rest?
No.
Tian Dou Imperial School
will fight Martial Soul Hall next.
Out of the three seeded battle teams,
only these two are left.
We can't miss this battle.
Yeah!
We might fight against one of them
when we enter the final.
Why are you so confident?
No. Xing Luo Royal is out.
Won't Shi Lan Ke get to the final?
If we get to the final,
it's because Brother Dai is awesome.
What does it have to do with you?
I'll show my talent in the next match!
Enough.
I'm watching.
-I'll see what you do.
-Where are Brother San and Sister Wu?
Why don't we see them?
Tang San?
Don't keep bugging your Brother San.
Can't you give them
time to stay together?
You smile so happily, Sister Qing.
Am I right?
Should we go away
and let you and Brother Dai
stay together?
Stop playing.
I'm not.
They're here.
Why haven't we seen
a single patrolling guard
so far?
I think they were sent elsewhere purposely.
I think I've been here before.
Didn't you just come here once?
This is the direction to the main hall.
Let's go.
Bi Bi Dong's seat.
So,
we can only sneak in
when she's gone to the arena.
I think so.
But there's not even a guard.
I wonder if Brother Dai has won.
I think we've entered
the core of Martial Soul Hall.
Be careful.
Soul Bone.
It's the same as the spider legs on my back.
Isn't the prize for the champion of the contest
two Soul Bones?
Are these the final prize?
Are they withdrawing from the contest?
I'm Yu Tian Heng,
the captain of Tian Dou Imperial Battle Team.
Speak to our captain!
How long do we have to wait?
I'm here.
Captain.
Are you the captain
of Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team?
When will your team members
arrive?
There are only three people on our team.
Where's the last one?
I saw her before.
She went with Shi Lan Ke before.
Why isn't she in the arena?
No need.
You plan to challenge our team
with two people?
I suffice alone.
Enough.
Two versus six.
Martial Soul Hall versus Tian Dou Imperial.
The match begins!
Be careful!
Calm down.
Got it.
Captain of Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team,
Xie Yue.
Tian Dou Imperial School,
Yu Tian Heng.
Flying Snakes!
Take down their captain!
Leave this to me!
I'm coming.
Put the arrow there.
That's it. Let's go.
What does this arrow do?
Hurry up and leave.
The chief told us
not to kill anyone in the arena.
That's why you're alive.
Do you want to continue?
I lost.
How long will it take?
Soon!
Enough.
I surrender.
It has ended.
If you're interested,
you can drop out of your school
and join Martial Soul Hall.
You can advance to the next level.
Martial Soul Hall wins.
Tian Dou Imperial Battle Team is out!
Any of you saw
the Soul Rings of those three people?
Hu Lie Na attacked last.
Quadruple Soul Rings.
The one with fire
also has Quadruple Soul Rings.
But their captain...
I really...
His Soul Rings didn't appear at all.
In other words,
he defeated Yu Tian Heng
without using Soul Skills.
Prepare to attack.
You can leave now.
I've done everything
that I was told to do.
Go back and tell Shi Nian
to follow the plan.
What plan?
You don't need to know.
Who are you?
A normal officer
of Martial Soul Hall.
Do you know Cang Hui's purpose?
Of course, it is to assassinate Bi Bi Dong.
We didn't see any guards
along the way.
You sent the guards away?
You'll leave traces.
I sent the guards away
in order to steal things.
What do you mean?
I commit suicide afterwards.
So,
no one will know
there's a problem with the Soul Bone.
He committed suicide just like that?
Let's get out of here!
Let's go!
I know who's the spy.
How do you know?
Accompany me to the library.
I want to confirm my guess.
The top-secret information
of the Star Forest
is in this row.
I won't bother you.
Please wait.
I want to ask you something.
I've come here twice.
I see that you would make a record.
All borrowed materials
are recorded.
When I came to check the documents last time,
some pages in the middle were stolen.
I want to ask,
whose token did that person use?
You said before
that this token has very high authority.
Only you and your friend
came to the library that day.
But they were obviously stolen.
I remember clearly
that no one else was here that day.
All right.
I want to check the record
of this document being borrowed.
When?
In recent years.
All of them?
Yes.
Thank you.
For checking the borrowing records,
I need to inform
Miss Hu Lie Na, according to the rules.
Okay, thanks.
You can leave now.
This can't be borrowed.
I know.
I'll read it here.
I won't take it away.
What are we looking for?
There should be two people in the plan
to assassinate Bi Bi Dong.
Two people?
Yes.
One is the Grand Soul Land Master behind Cang Hui.
It might be my father.
The other one
is the spy in Martial Soul Hall.
The guy in black smoke who assassinated
Su Yun Tao in the Star Forest.
What about the one
who committed suicide just now?
He just had Triple Soul Rings.
He can't
kill Su Yun Tao easily.
Not to mention
having a direct conversation
with Azure Bull Python.
Right.
I'll investigate my father,
starting with Cang Hui later.
As for the guy in black smoke,
he just appeared once.
In the Star Forest?
Yes.
Master said
that Azure Bull Python rarely appeared.
It's almost a legendary story of the Star Forest.
Yes.
Not many people know him.
So how did that guy in black smoke
know the exact location
of Azure Bull Python?
Yeah.
How did he know?
This document, "The Secret of Star",
records the approximate location
of Azure Bull Python
and its basic characteristics.
It really has.
After so many years, Martial Soul Hall
must have a lot of secrets.
But it's impossible for everyone
in the Martial Soul Hall
to memorize all these secrets.
So if the guy in black smoke
really comes from Martial Soul Hall,
he must have checked the information here.
And not only once.
But it seems
there are more than two people
who match these criteria.
No.
There's only one person.
I found it.
That guy in black smoke
hid a few Grand Soul Land Masters
in Martial Soul City.
It can be said that he's powerful.
And he not only wants
to assassinate Bi Bi Dong,
but he also has to face Azure Bull Python.
So he should be
someone at the same level.
So,
he's also a Grand Soul Land Master
with Nine Soul Rings?
Yes.
And what you said just now
reminded me of something.
Me?
Things have changed in the Star Forest.
The Grand Soul Land Masters
are not in Martial Soul City.
No matter how dangerous it is,
we won't meet someone with Nine Soul Rings.
Things have changed in the Star Forest.
Almost all the Grand Soul Land Masters
of Martial Soul Hall
have been sent away.
And the one who stays in Martial Soul City
should be
the guy in black smoke we are looking for.
Only one person then.
That's right.
In recent years,
this is
the only Grand Soul Land Master
who has checked "The Secret of Star".
The Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
It turns out
that he's the spy in Martial Soul Hall.
Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
This officer
might have stolen some Gold Soul Coins
and committed suicide out of guilt.
But,
an officer
committed suicide for some Gold Soul Coins.
This is strange.
Do we need to search the city?
No need.
During the contest,
this matter shouldn't be made public.
It'll tarnish the image of Martial Soul Hall.
I'll investigate this matter.
The spy in Martial Soul Hall
is the Grand Chrysanthemum Master?
It's very likely.
Another Grand Soul Land Master.
Why did he join forces with Hao Tian Soul Master
to kill Bi Bi Dong?
I don't know either.
You said
the arrow had merged into the Soul Bone?
That Soul Bone is the prize for the champion.
In other words,
the role of the arrow
will only be revealed after the final.
After the champion is revealed,
Bi Bi Dong will present the award in person.
But what impact
can a Soul Sect with Quadruple Soul Rings have
on Bi Bi Dong?
We have to ask the mastermind.
How do we ask him?
Hao Tian Soul Master's whereabouts are unknown.
But the Grand Chrysanthemum Master is there.
We can't ask him directly
how he is going to assassinate Bi Bi Dong, right?
Capture him and ask.
Capture who?
The Grand Chrysanthemum Master?
He's a Grand Soul Land Master with Nine Soul Rings.
Don't worry.
I'll think of a way.
Think of a way?
How many Soul Rings do you have?
You want to capture
a Grand Soul Land Master?
You don't need to care about this.
Don't let Shi Nian find out anything.
By the way,
if you have news about Hao Tian Soul Master,
tell me immediately.
Don't seek death.
I'll try.
Who's there?
Mr. Xie Yue, Mr. Yan.
The chief let us use the Soul Arena
as our training venue.
Leave here.
Yes.
I heard someone died.
An officer in the hall
sent the guards away and stole money.
He committed suicide out of guilt.
He already stole the money.
Why did he commit suicide?
The reason is still unknown.
It's under secret investigation.
Secret investigation?
Chief.
I want to ensure the stability of the contest.
During the contest,
I don't want
people to criticize Martial Soul Hall.
If there's anything wrong
with my decision,
please reprimand me.
Do as you say.
There's one more thing
to report.
Chi Huo School, Shen Feng School,
and Lei Ting School,
these three schools
were established at the same time.
Their school policies are similar too.
All are focused
on the same type of Martial Soul.
You mean
these three schools
are supported by the same force?
I think so.
But the purpose
of their establishment is not clear now.
To test.
What?
To test the road to the ultimate Martial Soul.
Chief, you know about this too?
If there are only two empires
and one Martial Soul Hall
in Douluo Continent,
isn't it too lonesome?
There are other forces?
Why didn't I hear of it?
There are certain things
that only the chief will know.
Have you ever considered
the origin of Soul Masters?
Why does the advancement of Martial Soul
need the Soul Beasts?
What's the inner connection
between Soul Masters and Soul Beasts?
Aren't the Soul Beasts natural?
Natural Soul Beasts?
And they just fit
for the advancement of Soul Masters?
Is that a coincidence?
Does this Douluo Continent exist
for Soul Masters only?
The rule today is simple and straightforward.
Seven versus seven.
Real team battle.
The opponents who get to this point
are strong.
But for this battle,
I don't want
to talk about tactics and response.
The opponents standing on the stage now
have defeated you once
in Tian Dou City.
It was the only time that you failed
in the contest.
Did it feel good?
No.
Get back your victory
on the stage now!
The match begins.
Do you know what Evil Phoenix is?
All flames
must surrender to me!
This is not Flame Branch Martial Soul.
It's Wind Branch.
Jiubao Boosts!
First, Strength! Second, Speed!
Do you think it's familiar?
The same tactic.
With the support of the Wind Branch,
it's completed more thoroughly
and stronger.
The air is almost burnt out.
This is bad.
The air in the flame area
is getting thinner.
Their power will gradually disappear.
You can't fly.
The flame can burn out the air,
but also make the air current rise.
I really can't fly.
I just use
the flame to float in the air.
Though the Wind Branch is added,
the tactic you use
is the same as last time.
Huo Wu.
You underestimated us this time.
Stop the flame.
It's too late!
The rise of the plant takes time.
I just grab your attention,
and wait for a chance to defeat you.
We surrender.
Well done.
Defeat the enemy in one shot.
Their opponents
didn't have time to respond at all.
What's more amazing is
that they didn't communicate at all
after they had got on the stage.
They completed this tactic
with trust and tacit understanding.
You're right.
They've now grown up
and made us proud of them.
Shi Lan Ke will win!
Tang San.
Huo Wu said she had something important
to tell you.
What is it?
Give me your hand.
This is for you.
Try to blow it.
It can't be blown out.
Let me try.
It really can't be blown out.
It's not hot either.
What's this?
Do you know about
Lei Ting School from Xing Luo Empire?
Of course.
They enter the final too.
They're in the same group as Martial Soul Hall.
But they are out.
They're missing.
Missing?
Shen Feng School and Lei Ting School
both went missing
after being defeated.
They just went home after the match.
No. I'm sure
they didn't go home but missing.
Because we're allies.
They won't leave without saying goodbye.
I'm pretty sure
that our team will disappear soon.
What does that have to do
with this flame?
This is the Nature of my Martial Soul.
If it goes off,
it means I'm dead.
I leave this to you.
I hope that after we disappear,
you'll know whether we
and all the missing people
are dead or alive.
It also leaves us some hope.
I hope you can find out the truth
and save us.
Who else did you tell about this?
Only you.
Martial Soul Hall and the two empires
may be behind this.
Only Shi Lan Ke
is a real folk school.
That's why you trust us?
Who do you think might have done it?
The power to make so many
Soul Masters disappear
must be immense.
Even a Grand Soul Land Master
with Nine Soul Rings
may not be able to do it.
I'll leave this flame with you.
If I really go missing
or even die,
I hope your school
will survive
and find the truth.
I think
it's a false alarm.
All the schools that have been out
are missing?
It's not just Shen Feng and Lei Ting then.
Yu Tian Heng and Du Gu Yan?
My brother?
I'll go to take a look at Tian Dou Imperial.
I'll go to see my brother.
I'll go with you.
Okay.
How is it?
There was no one
in the lodging for Xing Luo Empire.
I went to the place
where my brother trained too.
No one was there.
Tian Dou Imperial's place
was also empty.
Huo Wu might be right.
All the schools that have been out are missing.
Could it be a coincidence?
Maybe they went back after the defeat.
Impossible.
Senior Du Gu
is still in Martial Soul City.
Du Gu Yan won't leave
without saying goodbye.
Venom Soul Master is in Martial Soul City?
How do you know?
Are you hiding something from me?
I just don't want
to involve you guys.
My brother is missing.
It concerns me now.
Let's check on Huo Wu.
We'll talk about it on the way.
Let's go.
Huo Wu, are you there?
No one's here.
We just met,
but she's missing now.
It is still burning.
She's alive.
Even the school teachers are gone.
They took so many people away
in such a short time.
Could it be done
by the Grand Chrysanthemum Master?
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪