♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 36=
The participating battle teams are not
allowed to engage in personal fights.
He attacked first.
I heard that you
have Quadruple Soul Rings now.
Why are you still so weak?
You've been teaching my useless brother.
It must be exhausting for you.
I'm sorry.
But if I were you,
I would quit the contest.
If I ever meet you during the contest,
it's not your claw that I will break.
Instead, I will take your life.
Are you okay, Brother Dai?
Such a huge library.
The library houses documents
from different years
in different rooms separately
to facilitate research.
Both of you are
looking for records of Martial Soul Hall
from ten to twenty years ago.
Half of them is in this room,
and the other half is in the next room.
This is just part of the library?
A tiny part.
If you want to visit every room,
it will take more than one day.
What exactly are you two searching for?
I can help you.
This room
and the next?
Can we check them by ourselves?
You have the token.
Of course.
I'll leave you two alone.
Master.
We can check the records
about them chasing my mom back then.
We can check
who else was in it
other than Qian Xun Ji.
Based on your power now,
it's meaningless even if you know it.
I'll remember their names.
Promise me.
You'll never take revenge recklessly.
I promise.
Master.
You found it?
No.
I have some questions for you.
Go ahead.
Do you know
what Bi Bi Dong's Martial Soul is?
Death Araneae and Soul-draining Araneae.
She also has Twin Martial Souls?
Bi Bi Dong is the only one
who has completed the training
of Twin Martial Souls.
All Araneae Souls?
She has fused her Twin Martial Souls together.
It's quite a miracle.
So the thing that controlled me
was probably Invisible Web.
What controlled you?
She pointed her finger at me,
and I started to levitate.
I couldn't move.
Then?
How did she find out
that you're Tang Hao's son?
My Martial Soul, I guess.
You used Hao Tian Hammer
in front of her?
No, I didn't.
She just pointed her finger at me,
and my Martial Soul
came out
of its own accord.
Why do you mean by "came out"?
Explain!
Twin Martial Souls.
Hao Tian Hammer.
You're the son of Tang Hao?
It doesn't make sense.
She controlled you with the web.
I can understand.
But to force your Martial Soul to come out
is impossible.
But that's what happened.
Martial Soul is the manifestation
of a Soul Master's inner power.
Do you remember this?
Yes.
The first sentence in our textbook.
So your Martial Soul belongs to yourself.
No one can manipulate it.
But Bi Bi Dong is a Grand Soul Land Master.
If thousands of Grand Soul Land Masters
join forces,
their power might be catastrophic,
but it can never manipulate
someone's Martial Soul.
This is related to the Nature of Martial Souls.
But Bi Bi Dong just did that.
Did she make another breakthrough?
Wait.
What happened
after she had learned about your identity?
She let me go
and said that she'd see me in the arena.
That's all?
She also added
that she hadn't joined the chase back then.
She wouldn't deign to lie.
Let's find the documents and check them.
By the way, Master,
about the documents on my side,
their dates are wrong.
The young ones have better eyesight.
There are still some left on my side.
All right.
I won't bother you.
I'll check somewhere else.
Okay. Call me if you find anything.
Got it.
Master.
What are you looking at?
Someone took away
the records about the chase back then.
Did you see his face?
I only heard the footsteps.
The person disappeared.
Someone powerful then.
My dad, perhaps?
He's investigating this too.
Ye Zhi Qiu mentioned
that he would also be in Martial Soul City.
It doesn't make sense.
Why does Tang Hao need these documents?
Because he's like me.
He's trying to find out
who took part in the chase back then.
Your dad
was the target.
What else does he want to know?
Didn't he see
who was chasing him?
You're right.
He experienced it himself.
There's no need to investigate.
Let me see.
The date is right.
Here.
This is the period after the chase.
The chief of Martial Soul Hall, Qian Xun Ji,
died of severe injuries.
The whole city held a big funeral.
What about the incidents
that preceded it?
This is the closest.
Martial Soul Hall sent elite forces
to the Island of the God of Sea.
The result lies in the missing part.
This is just the beginning.
Whether Martial Soul Hall found
the Island of the God of Sea,
how is it related to us?
Isn't it just a myth?
Have you ever thought about one thing?
Almost no one knows
who your mother was.
She couldn't have fallen from the sky.
Where did she come from?
How did she meet your dad?
You suspect that the Island of the God of Sea
had something to do with my mom?
Let's check if your dad
was on the team
sent to the Island of the God of Sea.
My dad was the leader.
I think the voyage
had something to do with the chase later.
Venom Soul Master.
It's me.
Who are you?
Are you a Grand Soul Land Master too?
Don't worry, Elder Sword.
I'm Ning Feng Zhi,
the chief of Qibao Amber Clan.
Tang San told me about you.
We've also been invited to Martial Soul City.
It seems like
we have a common enemy.
The strong and powerful
have gathered here.
We can work together.
Strong and powerful?
The one who has planned all this
is aiming at something big.
But that guy
still hasn't shown up.
What's going on?
I didn't notice it.
Who did that?
This is his goal.
It's really something big.
When do you have to return the token?
It might still be useful for us.
No deadline in particular.
Let's keep it.
We'll return it once we're done.
Headmaster.
The schedule has been announced.
Martial Soul Hall just sent us this thing.
So quickly?
Are Er Long and the rest back?
Yes.
Who's our opponent?
Chi Huo?
Again.
Then this time,
we have to win.
Cang Hui School.
The enemies tend to meet.
What about Tian Dou Imperial School?
Tian Dou Imperial School's First Squad
is in the same group
with Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team.
We'll never encounter them until the final.
That group looks competitive.
There are three seeded battle teams in total.
Two of them are in that group.
Tian Dou Imperial School's First Squad
will fight Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team
in their first match.
The draw is quite incredible.
Who will we fight in our first match?
Xing Luo Royal Battle Team.
That means
we'll face Dai Mu Bai's elder brother again.
Brother Dai must be happy.
What happened?
You think the schedule is not good?
Please check on Dai Mu Bai.
What happened to him?
Brother Dai.
My elder brother
awakened his Martial Soul
earlier than I did.
When I had my First Soul Ring,
he had Double Soul Rings.
When I had Double Soul Rings,
he had Triple Soul Rings.
I've been no match for him ever since I was small!
Now that I have Quadruple Soul Rings,
I'm finally as strong as he is.
I want to defeat him once.
But my Martial Soul is broken.
How is he?
He still refuses to come out?
Other than Zhu Zhu Qing,
no one can stay.
Master,
my Blue Silver Plant
was burnt once.
But I still can use it now.
You've told me
that Martial Soul is the manifestation
of a Soul Master's inner power.
So Brother Dai's Martial Soul
shouldn't be completely broken.
It's true.
As long as you still have Soul Power,
it will recover.
But for someone as proud as Dai Mu Bai,
when he thinks that he's lost
and he can never
defeat his brother...
So,
his despair
manifests in his Martial Soul.
If he can't get himself together,
his Martial Soul will never recover.
But he's like this now.
What to do?
We will discuss
the matter about Dai Mu Bai.
What can I do then?
Just go back.
I'll discuss this with Master.
Go.
You're right.
He has to overcome himself.
There's a way,
but it's risky.
Senior, why are you here?
What happened?
The reason why they poisoned me
is this.
Assassinate the chief of Martial Soul Hall,
Bi Bi Dong?
In this letter, he offers the antidote.
As to Ning Feng Zhi
and the Grand Sword Master,
he offers resources
to help Qibao Amber Clan
achieve Martial Soul mutation.
All in all, just one goal.
Assassinate Bi Bi Dong.
What did Uncle Ning say?
They were hesitant.
You know very well
that Martial Soul Hall is a big monster.
It covers Douluo Continent.
More and more Soul Masters are affected by it.
If this continues,
Tian Dou Empire and Xing Luo Empire
will be devoured by it gradually.
Even if you kill Bi Bi Dong,
Martial Soul Hall will still exist.
Bi Bi Dong is the Greatest Soul Master
in Douluo Continent.
She is the symbol
of Martial Soul Hall's power.
If she's dead,
the legend of Martial Soul Hall will be gone.
Ning Feng Zhi said
that Qibao Amber Clan
had always been oppressed
by Martial Soul Hall.
If Bi Bi Dong is dead,
perhaps it'll save
the two empires and many more clans.
But Bi Bi Dong is powerful.
Five or six Grand Soul Land Masters
have been secretly summoned
to Martial Soul City.
Five or six Grand Soul Land Masters?
With many Grand Soul Land Masters
working together,
I think
even Bi Bi Dong
won't stand a chance.
Where do you plan to take action?
In Martial Soul City.
It's the headquarters of Martial Soul Hall.
It won't work.
There will be even more
Grand Soul Land Masters
in Martial Soul Hall.
The letter states
that this problem would be solved.
Soon,
Bi Bi Dong will be the only one
with Nine Soul Rings
in Martial Soul City.
How?
I don't know.
It seems like
he'd find a way to send them away.
Send the Grand Soul Land Masters away?
What kind of matter will...
The conflicts between humans
have nothing to do with me.
In the Star Forest...
Master once said
he had seen the man in black smoke
speaking to Azure Bull Python.
The King of Star Forest?
Impossible.
Soul Beasts and Soul Masters
are irreconcilable.
Azure Bull Python
will not do his bidding.
I still don't think that's right.
He should decide it for himself.
But I...
Headmaster.
Master.
I have a plan
to rekindle his fighting spirit.
How?
But you have to take some risks.
I still don't think that's right.
Master, tell me what to do.
I'm willing to try.
Are you worried about the Soul Beasts?
I'm thinking
about what Du Gu Bo told me.
To assassinate Bi Bi Dong?
The Grand Soul Land Masters
of Martial Soul Hall
have really been sent away.
It seems like
their plan to assassinate Bi Bi Dong
might succeed.
And Venom Soul Master was poisoned
by Cang Hui.
Perhaps
the assassination plan...
was devised by your dad.
I'm worried about that too.
If it's really your dad,
what will you do?
I don't know.
Will you take revenge following him?
But Bi Bi Dong said
she hadn't joined the chase.
Perhaps your dad
wants to destroy
the whole Martial Soul Hall?
Even though Martial Soul Hall is guilty,
there are still
a lot of people who don't know what happened.
Do they deserve to be punished too?
I used my last strength
to create this interspace.
Other than you, no one can enter.
Not even your dad.
Because I hope you can protect him.
I couldn't imagine
how strong his hatred
towards Martial Soul Hall would be
after my death.
I hope you can accompany him.
Don't let him fall into the abyss of revenge
or lose his humanity.
I have to find my dad
before the assassination.
Do you have any clues?
I can only think
of starting from Cang Hui.
Look for Ye Zhi Qiu?
Tomorrow we'll fight Xing Luo.
When we're done,
I'll look for Ye Zhi Qiu.
Before that,
let's help Brother Dai
win this battle.
Okay.
Seems like he still doesn't want to meet people.
I have a plan. Follow me.
Let's go.
You know something is trending
in Tian Dou City?
Portrait.
Portrait!
I've been practicing a lot lately.
Brother Dai,
can you be my model?
Brother, look at me.
This angle. A bit more.
Yes, now smile.
Smile.
Smiling.
The journey of life
is filled with ups and downs.
Right?
Yes.
The trap we fall into today
will be the stepping stone tomorrow.
Right?
Yes.
Without a storm,
we won't be able to see the rainbow.
We won't be able to see the rainbow.
Rainbow.
Have you seen a rainbow before?
No.
How do you know you'll see the rainbow
after the storm?
I said it
just to comfort Brother Dai.
But you haven't seen it yourself.
How can you convince Brother Dai?
I...
Didn't we agree out there
that we'd act together.
I'd help him
to get to his peak
from his lowest moment?
Right?
Yes, act together.
But you can't exaggerate.
You need facts to back it up.
Right, Master?
Master.
Yes.
You two, get out.
You have never seen rainbow.
How can you help?
So what? I can't say that?
Dai Mu Bai,
Zhu Zhu Qing went to take revenge
on your brother.
She went to look for my brother?
Why?
She wanted to help you get the throne.
Is she crazy?
Bring her back!
She said that it was Xing Luo politics,
so Shi Lan Ke School shouldn’t intervene.
Dai Wei Shi will kill her!
Perhaps not.
He will! I know him well.
The throne is what he wants very much.
I'll ask Headmaster to help.
But a school in Tian Dou
cannot meddle in Xing Luo politics.
But we need to rescue her!
You can go.
You're the Prince of Xing Luo.
You have the right!
I... I can't.
Then leave it to God.
By the way,
Zhu Zhu Qing said that if she failed,
you should stay in Tian Dou
and never return to Xing Luo.
Staying alive
is more important than everything.
Why are you here?
Where's Dai Wei Shi?
You aren't qualified
to call his name.
Dai Mu Bai is a better candidate
to inherit the throne of Xing Luo Empire.
Shut up.
I've decided
to support Dai Mu Bai
in his fight for the throne.
Your Highness.
Let her continue.
Power is not the only thing
that can govern the empire.
You
do not deserve to rule Xing Luo.
Your sister has her thoughts.
She's just throwing tantrum.
This has nothing to do with the tribe.
Dai Wei Shi is notorious for his cruelty.
There must be tribes who dislike him.
If I rally them,
a lot of people will definitely join.
Have you considered the consequences?
When you attacked Dai Mu Bai,
did you consider the consequences?
Don't meddle.
Your speed is much faster,
but it's not enough.
I'll break your leg first.
Trash.
Wasn't it a lesson for you?
You want to be the hero again?
The issue between us
has nothing to do with Zhu Zhu Qing.
Let her go.
Sure,
but as I said, I will break her leg.
Go away!
Losing once doesn't mean I'll lose forever.
No private duel outside of the arena.
If you fight again,
you're testing the limits
of Martial Soul Hall.
Weaklings are weaklings
no matter how hard they try.
I'll be the first to fight in the match.
You still dare to fight?
See you in the arena.
How's your injury?
I'm okay.
Your brother is strong, but he's just one person.
We're a team.
We can win.
In this match,
I'll ask for a duel.
You can't win in a duel.
The timing is tight. You won't make it.
But I can help you.
I have to be your pupil?
I'm just offering you
a new solution.
To be my pupil or not,
you can think about it.
What solution?
Have you heard of Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
You mean combining the Martial Souls
of two people?
Temporarily.
Your power will increase drastically
in a short time.
Why haven't I heard of it?
Because Martial Soul Fusion Skill is hard to do.
First,
you need premium herbs
as your foundation.
You ate Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum,
so you can do it.
Secondly,
two Soul Masters
have to trust each other completely.
It's hard to find someone like that.
What should I do?
Two Soul Masters use their Martial Souls
at the same time
and try to fuse their Soul Power.
Complete trust is hard to achieve.
Both of them have to be perfectly in sync.
Be patient.
You won't get it the first time.
Impossible.
Pigeon post from the Star Forest.
The two Beast Kings have commanded
Soul Beasts to go out and attack.
They seem to be heading
towards Martial Soul City.
Chief.
It's an emergency. We have to act fast.
What do you think of Blue Silver Plant?
The Martial Soul.
It has always been considered
as a useless Martial Soul.
The Soul Beasts from the Star Forest.
How do you plan to deal with them?
The two Beast Kings are powerful.
The contest is about to begin.
I can't go.
Chief,
you don't need to go out.
Martial Soul Hall has
many Grand Soul Land Masters.
They can deal with it.
You aren't going?
Someone has to stay in Martial Soul City.
Besides,
I've been the referee.
I can't miss the final.
Then,
the Grand Ghost Master and you will stay.
Other Grand Soul Land Masters will go now
and chase the Soul Beasts
back to the Star Forest.
I shall convey your order.
You're going to the Star Forest too?
But the chief
wants you to be the referee.
Anyone can be the referee.
We need more force for the Star Forest.
True.
I'll stay in Martial Soul City.
Go ahead.
I'll inform the chief.
A lot of schools here.
Be careful.
The chief and I stay in Martial Soul City.
Nothing will happen.
The Beast Kings of the Star Forest are
heading towards Martial Soul City?
Don't worry.
I heard that the Grand Soul Land Masters
in Martial Soul City
are all going there
to fend off the Soul Beasts.
No way. I have to get there quickly.
It's too far.
When we get there,
the battle will be over.
The people from Martial Soul Hall just left.
The Grand Soul Land Masters
are much faster than us.
What's wrong?
So many Grand Soul Land Masters.
I'm worried that the Soul Beasts
might be killed off.
It won't happen.
Why?
Azure Bull Python
and the guy behind all this work together
in order to
distract the Grand Soul Land Masters
in Martial Soul City.
Since all of them are on their way,
the goal is attained.
They won't really fight so hard.
What if it's not the case?
Azure Bull Python is smart.
He won't sacrifice
the Soul Beasts like this.
You're worried about the Soul Beasts?
I just want
Soul Beasts and humans to live in harmony.
One can only obtain the Soul Rings
by hunting Soul Beasts.
So, Soul Masters and Soul Beasts
are meant to be enemies.
I keep them enraged.
You will command them in the arena.
Win every match
at all costs.
If you do what I say,
I promise
you won't be like them.
What about him?
He doesn't have to fight?
He serves another purpose.
Take this.
Go to Martial Soul Hall.
What do I do?
Someone will tell you
when you get to Martial Soul Hall.
Who?
You ask too many questions.
How can I find him?
He knows who I am?
He only recognizes this.
It's really the final.
Such a spacious area.
The strongest schools in Douluo Continent
are gathered here.
You can say
the eyes of Douluo Continent
are all on us.
Then,
are we going to be famous?
Famous? Seriously?
Look, up there!
Who?
The chief of Martial Soul Hall,
the Greatest Soul Master
in Douluo Continent, Bi Bi Dong.
Don't you know?
Douluo Soul Master School Tournament
has come to the important stage.
Different teams in Martial Soul City.
Only the strongest
can enter the final.
Before the first match,
let's hear from the Chief.
The champion
will receive two Soul Bones
from Martial Soul Hall.
With the highest compatibility.
I will award you myself!
Kids, work hard.
First match in Group A.
Shi Lan Ke School from Tian Dou Empire
versus Xing Luo Royal School.
The rule is
five-versus-five group battle.
May the Soul Masters on both sides
present yourselves.
Five versus five. Pick five people first.
Brother Dai and I have no problem with it.
Sister Qing too.
Who else?
Tang San.
I...
I know this is a stupid request,
but I really hope
that I can handle this battle myself.
No way!
You can't fight five people by yourself.
Fine, we'll leave the arena to you.
Are we really not fighting?
Believe in him.
No need to involve the others.
Two versus two.
Settle everything in one battle.
Can the rule be changed?
Only if both sides agree.
One more condition then.
What?
We can fight to death
in the arena.
Okay!
Xing Luo Empire can have two princes,
but there can only be
one emperor.
Get ready.
If things get worse,
we'll rescue them.
All right.
We can start now.
Two versus two.
You need one more person.
I alone suffice.
The rule cannot be changed now.
You need to find one more person.
You, come here.
Once the battle starts,
stand here and don't attack.
Start!
What's that?
Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪