Ms. Kim.
Yes?
A while ago,
you told me never to stir you up again.
That was...
I...
want to stir you up.
What?
That's...
Please don't do this!
Little child,
please watch me go.
No!
Ms. Kim!
Ms. Kim, I will explain.
I can explain.
- This is... - I just remembered.
I just remembered who you are and what kind of a person you are.
What do you mean?
You are a narcissist who only loves himself.
You think everyone else is just a background.
"How dare you think of having me?" That's what flashed in your mind.
That's why you pushed me, right?
Ms. Kim, you are mistaken. It's not like that.
Mr. Lee, you know what?
If someone asks me when I had my first kiss,
I would have to choose between when a kid named Sang Cheol...
kissed me as a joke in kindergarten and this moment.
Ms. Kim.
- Mr. Lee. - Yes?
I'm taking a day off tomorrow.
- What? - I don't think...
I can manage to look at your face.
I'll get going then.
Wait, Ms. Kim.
By the way, I'm done for the day.
Don't you dare follow me.
I'm glad she has no clue about it.
I'm not glad at all.
This is not how it's supposed to go.
(Episode 6)
So he pushed you as soon as your lips touched.
Yes. So I...
I read it on the internet. And I couldn't believe it.
Do you have any idea as to why he did that?
I do. It sounds like he has a sexual desire disorder.
What? Sexual what?
It's nothing to be surprised about.
A lot of young men come to our clinic with that issue.
They are so stressed out...
that their bodies reject it. It's like that.
You're being ridiculous.
I am not. Suffering from sexual dysfunction is no crime.
In my opinion, I think it's a psychological problem.
- What? - He showed...
such an extreme behavior right before the kiss.
I think he's traumatized by either women or kiss.
And that caused him to show a rejection symptom.
"Traumatized"?
Should we go for another round?
Let's go!
Stop, girls. I will stop here.
What? We have to go for one more drink.
Please cut me some slack. Tomorrow is my day off.
That's why you have to drink until you nearly die.
When will you have another chance like this?
No. I can't spend my sweet day off recovering from hangover.
I'm going to have a blast tomorrow.
I'll get going then.
Take care going home.
You know that story Mi So read on the internet.
I think it's about Mi So and Mr. Lee.
Mi So and Mr. Lee?
Are you saying that rich man suffers from sexual dysfunction?
Can't a rich man suffer from sexual dysfunction?
Stop!
That's not the point, is it?
The point is that there's something going on between the two.
He showed such an extreme behavior right before the kiss.
I think he's traumatized by either women or kiss.
Perhaps...
there might be a reason for it.
What if there was?
My gosh, you are funny.
Ms. Kim, you must've...
been really excited to kiss me.
Since you anticipated it so much, you must've been very disappointed.
(Miss Kim, you must've been...)
Ms. Kim, I am sorry.
(Ms. Kim, I am sorry.)
The simpler the better.
The first step is always the hardest. It gets easy after.
Saying sorry isn't so difficult now.
(Ms. Kim, I am sorry.)
Sorry? Did something happen between us?
I don't know what you are sorry about.
What happened between us?
Is she going to forget that sweet yet dynamic moment?
This sentence is very tough to interpret.
What do I say?
Your secretary is here.
Why? Why did she come when it's her day off?
She must've felt uncomfortable too.
Why are you here so early in the morning, Mr. Yang?
Don't you usually wait outside?
Yes, sir.
But Ms. Kim told me that she can't come to work today,
so she asked me to...
tie your tie for you in her stead.
- What? - She told me...
that there's nobody to tie it for you if she's not here.
No! Stop right there.
- Don't come any closer. - I can do it well.
No.
Just stay still.
I'll do it for you, sir.
(Bucket List for Day Off)
I'll make sure that I thoroughly enjoy every moment of today.
The first place I need to go to is an amusement park...
Mr. Lee!
Since you've worked as hard as a cow all this time,
I'm giving you a stuffed cow.
Its name is "Hardworking Cow".
Hey, Hardworking Cow.
Let's not look at each other today.
It's because you keep reminding me of someone.
Oh gosh!
Why did I close my eyes? Why?
How embarrassing!
I apologize for being late!
Goodness.
You're 14 whole minutes late.
I apologize.
Hey, now. Are you starting to slack off already...
because Ms. Kim isn't here?
No, it's not that.
My family moved to Yangpyeong last week,
so I live quite far from work now.
Hey.
Stop talking about your family affairs...
that nobody is interested in...
and get ready to work.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm going to a real estate agent later to find a new place to live.
I'm thinking of getting my own place somewhere near work.
If I do that, I'll never be late again.
Stop talking about your living affairs...
that we seriously have no interest in...
and get ready to work.
Yes, ma'am.
By the way, why is Ms. Kim taking a day off?
I don't know. Maybe something is going on with her?
Nothing is going on with her.
Hello, sir.
Stop talking about someone who isn't here,
but work harder to make up for the fact that she isn't here.
- Yes, sir. - Yes sir, do not worry.
- I'll be going now. - Go ahead.
Get out of my way.
Hello.
I'm so bored.
What are you doing, Ji In?
Let's meet up today if you have time.
You have a PTA meeting at the preschool?
What are you up to, Eun Min? If you have time, we should...
Oh, you went to get fillers on your face?
All right, I hope they turn out great.
What am I going to do when I quit my job?
Hello, I'm Kim Mi So, who went on a date with you last time.
I'm sorry, but about the child kidnapping case from back in 1994...
that I asked you to look into.
May I ask how it's going?
(Reporter Park Byung Heon)
Yeah, I'll try to find that boy first.
Hello.
May I ask who you are?
You're the one who came to see the vice chairman last time, right?
Yes.
(Writer Lee Sung Yeon, Plans for Book Concert)
Are you the writer participating in the book concert?
Yes.
Mr. Morpheus.
Goodness!
- Yes. - Hello.
I'm your fan, Mr. Morpheus.
It truly is an honor to be seeing you in person like this.
What's going on here?
I'll be going, then.
- All right. - Sure.
Goodness gracious.
I finally understand why Morpheus hid his face all this time.
It must have been because he was just too handsome.
As soon as he unveils himself...
gosh, my heart is racing.
He's so cool.
Doesn't he seem exactly like the type who is a bestselling author?
I didn't really care for his novels, though.
Aren't they mostly catered to women?
What are you saying?
It's because everyone likes them that he's a bestselling author!
Yes, that's right. His books are such page-turners...
that you lose all perception of time.
By the way, Mr. Morpheus came by the other day and now today.
Maybe he's close with the vice chairman?
I don't think so.
Didn't it feel like there was some tension in the air just now?
Perhaps.
What kind of relationship do those two have, though?
I know...
their huge secret.
You see, those two are...
brothers.
- What? - What?
The author Morpheus...
is the eldest son of the chairman of Yumyung Group!
I just stopped by the Planning Department's meeting.
I took a look at their plan, and the concept didn't seem too bad.
You don't need to report those kinds of things to me...
because that is just one of the many projects that my company is running.
Do you really have to phrase it like that?
It's merely the truth.
Well, fine.
I'm sure this is nothing to you, since you're so high and mighty.
But I don't think Mother and Father have the same attitude toward this.
The two of them are quite happy about the fact...
that we're working together.
That's why I came.
To tell you not to unnecessarily stir the pot and create strife...
when they think we've made amends, and are so happy about it.
Isn't that something that you should be telling yourself?
What?
Because I'm not the one who creates strife.
Did Ms. Kim Mi So go somewhere?
She's using her paid time off today.
I see.
I'm a member of your fanclub and a Morpheusian.
And my username is "FallenForMorpheus".
Do you remember me, by any chance?
I've made a lot of posts on the fan cafe.
I'm sorry. I'll be sure to remember from now on.
I'll remember this too. Forever.
Mr. Author!
Could you give us your autograph?
- Make it out to "Bong Se Ra." - And "Lee Young Ok."
Me... me too, please.
Me too, please!
(Distant Afternoon)
Please give me your autograph.
Goodness, when did you buy that?
You didn't even take off the plastic.
- Bong Se Ra. - Lee Young Ok.
FallenForMorpheus.
- Just a second. - Move.
Please give me your autograph.
Good thing Ms. Kim used her paid time off today.
Yes, Ms. Kim?
Yes, I'll made adjustments to his schedule.
Yes.
By the way, what are you doing on your day off?
What? Why are you staying at home?
Well, all right.
Call me if you need anything. Okay, bye.
She should go hang out with someone on a day like today.
Is there anything you need?
Cancel all my schedule today. I have an urgent business.
Okay.
No one replies my text, and I have nothing to do.
If I think about it, I don't have anyone to hang out with or plans...
on a day like today all because of the vice chairman.
It's because I have to set everything in my life to him.
Goodness, Vice Chairman.
Are you talking about me?
Gosh, you...
I mean, what brings you here?
I thought you'd think about me like you do now, so I came here...
to see you myself.
Shall we hang out together today?
- What? - I took my day off today...
to hang out with you.
You don't have to.
I'm busy today.
You seem to be just walking around the neighborhood, so what's so busy?
I'm busy walking around the neighborhood.
What?
How did you know that I was home?
I heard Ji Ah talked to you on the phone.
Be honest. You wanted me to come see you, didn't you?
You're great in every way,
but you're great at getting wrong ideas too.
Right, I'm great in every way, so trust me and leave your day to me.
I'll entertain you today.
I'm busy today.
I plan to go somewhere further from here from now on.
In those clothes?
Give me a chance to make up for it.
Especially for you,
I've planned out a schedule too.
We'll eat at a premium lounge restaurant...
as we listen to an orchestra's performance.
We'll get on a yacht to have some cruise time.
We'll move quickly to the airport from the riverside by a helicopter.
We'll go to Japan on my private plane.
We'll have sushi for our late night snack and come back.
Hold on.
I have no intention to do all that.
Why?
It's my holiday today.
I'll spend the day as I please.
I won't do as you say.
Then I'll do as you say for today.
- You won't be able to. - I will.
- You won't. - I will.
Well, then.
- You want to go on a bus trip? - Yes.
Not a trip to Europe or the Mediterranean,
but a trip on which you take a bus and tour around the city?
- You mean, that kind of trip? - Yes.
Ms. Kim.
Don't try to go against my style, and just do what you want to do.
That's what I really want to do.
I always get on crowded buses on my way to or from work.
I've wanted to travel on bus to its final destination...
in broad daylight without much thought.
But it must be hard for you...
because you hate to ride on a car driven by a stranger.
That's why you always make me drive for you whenever you have a drink.
It's hard for you to do this, isn't it?
Let's go.
Are you really going to ride on this?
I told you that I'd do what you want today.
Really?
I'll pay the bus fare.
Two people, please.
Not enough money.
Does it inform you of this humiliating information too?
I'll pay.
Here.
This was designed without considering tall people like me.
Hold this.
Sit here.
No, you should sit...
Never mind. I'll sit.
Did you just see that? He has such weak legs.
You should've sit here instead if you'd be like this.
He must have no strength in his legs.
The sun is still up.
I know.
The weather is hot, so why don't we go have some chicken and beer?
I can't.
I have to go see a realty dealer to look for a new house.
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay, bye.
You're going, right?
Chicken and beer, my foot.
Gosh, Mr. Ko.
We're having some chicken and beer over there. You want to join?
You just said you wouldn't go.
When did I?
You'll go with us, right?
Let's go release our stress from today's work.
Working is best to release your stress in my opinion.
Nothing is better than finishing off the work perfectly...
when it comes to blowing out your stress.
Enjoy yourselves then.
Maybe next time.
Well, then.
Let's go for some chicken and beer already.
I'm not going.
You just said you wanted to go for it to cool off from the heat.
I said I wanted to go drink with Mr. Ko,
not with you.
You're so slow-witted. Goodness.
Gosh, I just want to flick her on the forehead like this...
if I can.
It's clean and nice.
- Can I move in right away? - Sure.
Oh, right. Do you want to check out the rooftop too?
It's got a great view.
Can I use the rooftop too?
Sure. It's for public use.
A young man lives in the rooftop house,
and he's made a small garden to grow lettuce and cherry tomatoes.
He must be very diligent.
He is diligent and frugal.
He has such strong vitality.
His monthly rent was originally 500 dollars with a deposit of 10,000.
He persuaded the landlord real hard and made it down to 420.
Is that right?
I'll follow you after this call. Go look around the rooftop first.
Okay.
It came off again.
My suit keeps getting worn out because I have no other suits.
What a miser.
Mr. Ko.
Why you...
What are you doing here? Did you stalk me?
What? That's not it.
Right, I only have one suit.
What's so curious about it that you followed me here?
I didn't stalk you.
I'm here for househunting.
I want to live in one of the studios here.
What?
Well, goodbye.
Hold on.
People think I'm workaholic and hot,
and I'm the most charming male employee in Yumyung Group.
If you ruin that image of mine,
I won't let it slide.
Don't worry.
Can I ask you about something?
What on earth happened about the button?
I'm sure you dropped the button at that time.
In case of emergency,
I bought a lot of spares beforehand.
What great food you want to have...
that you're making us travel this far?
We're going to my favorite restaurant.
It's there.
(Go Skin)
"Go Skin"?
It really makes me want to go home.
Then go home.
I'm going to where you're going.
I told you I'd do everything you want today.
Excuse me. Can we have two servings of pork skin?
Okay.
Try some.
[VIU Ver] tvN E06 What's Wrong With Secretary Kim?
"What’s Wrong with Vice Chairman Lee?"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Did you just kick it because I didn't give you the piece?
Of course not. It's a misunderstanding.
By the way, do you like this place?
It's not that I like it, but I used to come to this place...
whenever I dined out with my sisters and Dad.
My family was burdened with debt,
so we couldn't afford to go to a Korean beef restaurant.
I see.
What kind of person is your father?
You ask me a lot of questions unlike the other days.
He's a rocker.
What?
He's the guitarist of a band.
I told you once that he was badly scammed...
while running an instrument store at Nagwon Arcade, right?
You told me.
You said that was why you began working at a young age.
Right.
Ever since then, to earn money for my sisters' tuition,
he rashly tried to work at a construction site and got injured.
He also borrowed money from a loan shark to make a big hit...
which did become one in a different sense.
It all happened because he forced himself to do what didn't fit him.
Still, he's doing what he wants now,
and my sisters have achieved their dreams, so it's good.
Haven't you felt resentful towards your family?
No. It's not like they did it on purpose.
People say that it's valuable...
to sacrifice yourself in your life.
But it's actually not.
You just lose yourself...
by suffering and sacrificing.
In any circumstances, the most important thing is...
yourself.
Never forget that you're most precious and the top priority...
in any moment.
Why are you laughing?
I guess the past nine years were indeed a long time,
seeing how the comment out of your narcissism...
came to me as a comfort.
What do you mean, "narcissism"? That's rude.
Eat up.
Give it to me. I'll grill them.
What?
You're on a holiday, and I'm fitting myself to your style today,
so I'll try doing this too.
What do you want to do next?
I don't know.
They're cute.
You still like stuffed dolls.
Have I told you that I like dolls?
You wrote it in the survey before...
that you wanted to receive a huge stuffed doll from someone you liked.
Oh, right. That happened.
Can I try this?
Of course.
Let's do this.
Good.
It's the first round, that's why.
I chose to pick you today.
That was close. My hands aren't getting warmed up easily today.
It's for certain this time.
Move, Ms. Kim.
It's frustrating just to watch you do it.
This is harder than you see. It's not easy to succeed.
I've figured out its principle as I watched.
Angle...
and timing are most important like this.
I guess knowing principles and playing actual games are different.
I couldn't focus because I had to explain.
Exact angle and precise timing.
Right now.
I'm going right away.
Please.
Gosh, please.
Just one more round.
It's got to grab the doll.
- Yes. - Almost.
- How much is this machine? - Sir.
- Let's go now. - How much is...
Let's withdraw some cash and try...
No, that's enough.
You're coming to work tomorrow, right?
Of course.
I'll return to fitting myself to your life again.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Goodbye.
Hardworking Cow, guard home safely today as well.
How have you been, Byung Heon?
Hello, Mi So. I've been lively,
bright, and well.
I was out in the field yesterday, so I'm calling you late now.
I'm sorry, and about the child abduction case in 1994...
- which you mentioned last time. - I'm listening.
It doesn't seem like what you're looking for,
but the son of Yumyung Group's chairman...
was abducted for four days in 1994.
It happened in the redevelopment district which is now Yumyung Land.
In the redevelopment district?
Yes, the company blocked all reporters from covering the case,
so there's no data except that he was in fourth grade at that time.
I searched...
and found out that the eldest son was in fourth grade then.
Things weren't so pleasant when I was in fourth grade.
I'm sorry, but nine years old...
- means you were in 2nd grade. - I was in 4th grade.
I was so smart that I skipped two grades.
I was in the same class with my brother.
No, the vice chairman was in fourth grade too.
Ms. Kim.
What are you thinking?
- Hello. - Get in already.
All right, let's go.
Well, Mr. Park.
What? A kidnapping?
Yes.
Have you heard anything about it from Mr. Lee?
Young Joon and I have been friends for a long time,
but he's never mentioned anything like that to me.
He also rarely talks about his childhood.
So you don't know anything about it, then.
Right.
But can I ask you what prompted you...
to look into this case?
I don't recall exactly,
but I think...
I was locked up inside an empty house for a day.
What?
There was a boy beside me in that house,
and I think it was Mr. Lee.
Well, you said both Young Joon and his brother were in fourth grade.
Did that boy tell you his name by any chance?
He did, but I don't remember.
Why do you think that it could've been Young Joon?
Ms. Kim.
Yes, sir.
You said you're afraid of spiders and absolutely hate them.
I feel the same way about cable ties.
So please don't use them in my office.
Please, okay?
- It's not okay. Let me see. - No...
It's just...
my hunch.
Why don't you just ask him directly?
I thought about that, of course.
But...
he probably hasn't mentioned anything about it...
for a reason.
It's nothing exciting, you know.
He could've been scarred by it,
so I can't ask him.
I'll just be happy about finding my childhood friend.
And...
please pretend that you didn't hear any of this, sir.
Gosh, don't you worry.
Like you said,
there must be a reason why he's never talked about it...
for the past nine years.
Ms. Kim.
Did you have a good day off yesterday?
Yes, I did.
(Vice Chairman Lee Young Joon)
Mr. Lee got here early today.
He said he has a lot to do as he was off yesterday.
Why is she staring at me like that?
She'll wear out my handsome face.
Right, I wouldn't even have a face now if people's gazes...
could wear it out.
Did you need me, sir?
Yes, Ms. Kim. I have too many books in my study,
so I'd like to get rid of what I don't read.
- Would you be able to help me? - Of course, sir.
- When works for you? - Anytime.
- Then how about tonight? - That sounds good.
Why are you so cooperative all of a sudden?
You gave me the strength I needed,
so I'd like to help you in any way I can.
What?
Sir.
Is there something you want to tell me?
I'm so happy that we met again like this.
Me too.
I'll be off, then.
We saw each other last night,
and she's that happy about seeing me again today?
Is she head over heels for me now?
Seriously?
- That's crazy. - What's going on?
Why are they laughing?
Gosh, I hate it so much.
- I want to barf. - Are they talking about me?
You'll find it hard to believe, but there's only one.
- Ms. Kim. - My gosh.
- Could you spare me a moment? - Sorry?
Why... What's the matter?
Those two...
You were talking about me, right?
Sorry? No, I wasn't.
Don't lie to my face. I totally heard it.
"You'll find it hard to believe",
"but there's only one." Those were your words.
You must've been telling them I only have one suit.
No, not at all.
Our intern was telling us...
how good the food at our cafeteria is,
so I was just telling him...
that it's the only cafeteria in the country that has a chef...
who used to work at a hotel restaurant.
Then...
why did you look at me and laugh earlier?
I have a naturally smiley face. Look.
Anyway, you'd better be careful.
I'll be watching you.
- What... - What's going on?
What did you two talk about?
- Nothing important. - You'd better tell me.
Ji Ah, are you...
flirting with Mr. Ko?
Flirting, my foot. He makes my blood boil.
What are you talking about? My blood is boiling.
My goodness.
- Gosh. - What's he doing?
Are you heading out for the lunch meeting?
The car is ready, sir.
It's not about work,
so you don't have to come. Just enjoy your lunch.
Yes, sir.
Just a moment, please.
I just wanted to fix your tie, sir.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you sooner.
What?
I was talking about your tie.
What's wrong with Ms. Kim?
She's definitely acting weird today.
It seems like her feelings for me...
have deepened about three times.
Was she moved last night because I was so good to her?
We'll get it this time.
I'd be in big trouble now if I won a toy for her last night.
Had that happened, her feelings for me would've deepened tenfold.
I got it. Oh, no.
I got it. I did it.
Please...
My gosh, he's so bad at it.
- What did you just say? - You're horrible at it.
Move over now. Mr. Jobless.
What? "Jobless"?
Yes. My mom said that those who don't go to work are jobless.
You kids are saying that because you don't know who I am.
I bet at least 1 or 2 of your home appliances...
and your toys...
were made by my company.
In simple terms,
I'm rich.
Why are you playing the claw machine to win a toy if you're rich?
Exactly. Can't you afford to buy 100 of it?
Wrong. Then it wouldn't be a fair play.
A toy like this is only valuable when you win it.
Kids.
I need to focus.
All right, here I go.
My gosh, it's coming up.
Ms. Kim.
- There's a guest for you. - Pardon me?
I wanted to thank you for helping me enjoy my day off.
His name is Remember Me.
Oh, this is...
I'm sorry I didn't remember you.
I get that you're moved,
but it's just a stuffed toy. Why are you tearing up?
Ms. Kim.
We're stepping out to pick up coffee. Would you like one too?
Oh, I'd like one too.
Actually, I'll go pick them up.
I'll be right back, sir.
Her eyes filled with tears. Was she that moved by it?
3 lattes and 3 Americanos, please.
Sure.
Hey, I want to go home.
Stop crying, Mi So.
I'll give you something delicious if you stop crying.
Something delicious?
Here, it's caramel candy.
Eat this, and don't cry.
Promise?
Enjoy.
Oh, Ms. Kim. I feel bad. I should've gone.
You bought caramels too?
I want to give them to someone.
Who? The guy you're seeing?
You keep saying that.
It's just someone I want to thank.
He won't remember me, but still...
By the way, have you heard?
I got a text from my friend who used to be in Morpheus' fan club.
Apparently, Morpheus was kidnapped as a kid.
What?
It's in a blog post, which he wrote before he became famous.
He deleted the post right away, but some fans kept the screenshot.
No way.
Can I see the post?
("Story from Long Ago" by Morpheus)
"In the allies of the empty redevelopment area,"
"I could always catch a whiff of cement."
"The black steel gate always made a screeching noise..."
"when it was being opened."
(Keep Out)
"It was impossible..."
"to peek through the frosted honeycomb-patterned windows."
"I prayed while looking at the ropes hanging across the living room."
"If I could cross them and escape this living room..."
"Just like the abandoned stuffed bunny there,"
"I was abandoned, and I gradually lost my liveliness."
- Hey. - You're dumb, aren't you?
No, I'm not dumb.
I'm only five,
but I can read books better than my older sister, Mal Hee, does.
I'll visit soon to see you.
Really? You'll really visit me, right?
- Yes. - I'll never forget your name.
Your name is... Lee...
- Lee... - You fool. You forgot again.
I'll tell you my name again.
I'm Lee Sung...
That's right.
Lee Sung...
His name was Lee Sung Yeon.
That's right.
Lee Sung...
His name was Lee Sung Yeon.
Yes, it was my brother.
Sung Yeon was the one who was kidnapped.
Then can I ask you something, sir?
How did you get the scar on your ankle?
Why are you asking about that suddenly?
It seemed like you had bad memories you wanted to forget...
and also because of the scar on your ankle,
- I assumed that it was you... - That scar...
I somehow ended up with it as a kid.
Was that why?
Pardon?
Did you stare at me like that all day long because you thought...
that I was the boy you've been looking for all these years?
I'm sorry I was mistaken.
Have you been well?
I came to sign a contract, and I thought I'd stop by.
I came by yesterday too, but you weren't here.
It was my day off.
I see.
I thought about calling you,
but I thought it would be better to talk to you in person.
That's why I came here.
I wanted to apologize about not telling you...
that Young Joon and I are brothers.
Mi So, what's wrong?
Is something wrong?
So you are saying...
we were locked in there together. Right?
Do you have absolutely no recollection of...
being there with me?
Actually, because of the shock of being kidnapped,
my memory got fragmented.
How much do you remember then?
Do you want me to tell you what I know?
Yes.
He and I...
have been in bad terms ever since we were young.
What?
Young Joon, I mean.
Just like now, he was very boastful.
He was better than me at everything,
and we were always compared.
Then when I was in my fourth grade,
Young Joon skipped two grades and we ended up in the same class.
That clever boy...
quickly won over my friends.
Later on, he sided with them and bullied me.
He laughed at me for being weaker than him.
What?
I fought a lot with my brother's friends.
They said I was rude and picked fights with me.
But I guess you were fine because you were with your brother.
No.
He was worse.
He's the worst sort of man.
One day, Young Joon took me to a redevelopment area.
He said he would go buy drinks and told me to stay there.
Young Joon didn't come back.
And while I was waiting for him,
I got kidnapped.
Mr. Lee.
I am so happy to see you again.
I am sorry for recognizing you too late.
Mr. Lee, I am here.
Go to the study first.
Okay. I will start sorting out the ones that will be published...
as revised editions.
(Applicants for Mr. Lee Young Joon's secretary)
(Resume)
Why did I look like a country bumpkin?
Why did I write these?
Did you want to brag that your college examination grades...
were in the top one percent?
This is so embarrassing.
(Resume)
(Cambridge Graduate)
(Certified Professional Secretary)
(Resume)
Why did he choose me instead of these people?
Do you want to know...
why I hired you that time?
What?
Yes.
Because you are Mi So.
Because you are Kim Mi So.
(What's Wrong with Secretary Kim)
What appointment do you have?
Who am I?
What are you doing?
Crush?
You are interested in each other, but you're not yet dating.
Instead of trying to get her memory back,
she should build memories with me.
The reason why I came here is because...
Cooperation and unity.
No, I've come to turn our feelings...
- into a relationship. - What?