[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 9]
[Zero Gravity Cybercafe]
Who ordered Fish Flavoured
Shredded Pork Rice?
Buddy, was it you?
I'm sorry.
Is this your Fish Flavoured
Shredded Pork Rice?
Did you order this?
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
Geez.
Fish Flavoured Shredded Pork Rice?
Then who ordered
the Fish Flavoured Shredded Pork Rice?
It smells great. Did you order it?
No, I didn't.
Little Box?
Handsome, is this your rice?
I'm sorry.
Little Box?
Buddy, is this your rice?
-It's not mine.
-I've called you many times.
Why didn't you answer me?
Quickly take it.
I have more deliveries to make.
Excuse me.
Sorry. Sorry.
Is this person Liang Chen?
Wait a minute.
Why did I run away?
He's here.
I should see what he looks like.
Right.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
It's too messy. It won't do.
I'm too ugly.
Forget it.
[Where did you go?]
[I'm sorry.]
[The power suddenly
went out just now.]
[What a coincidence!]
[The cybercafe I went to
had a power outage, too.]
He must have discovered me.
It's so embarrassing.
I really want to see what he looks like.
[Are you going to
Liang Chen's birthday gathering]
[tomorrow afternoon?]
[I'll go if I have time.]
[How about you?]
Is he going or what?
So
are you really her?
Next team.
Jing, go!
[Lucky draw box]
Next team.
Lu Jing, you are so unlucky.
I should've drawn it myself.
At least I wouldn't be the last one.
We definitely can't go to
Liang Chen's birthday party.
Hello, viewers and friends.
We are now live at Liang Chen's
birthday party in Guangzhou.
Today, the fans are
especially enthusiastic.
-All done.
-Thank you.
[Will he come?]
Your candy.
Thank you.
Ms Liang, what's
wrong with you today?
Why are you so nervous?
Do I look nervous?
You reach for the candy
whenever you're nervous.
I know you well.
It's only a birthday party.
It's no big deal for you.
I felt like having candy, that's all.
I'm sorry.
Can we change the order?
No.
I have something really urgent.
Can you do me a favour?
I'm sorry. I really can't help you.
Lu Jing, I've asked them.
No one is willing to switch with us.
Lu Jing,
there's another way.
What is it?
Why don't we give up
on this competition?
Why is the accuracy
of this model so low
on the test data set?
We'll be on stage soon.
Can we not dwell on this problem?
This is not about the competition.
It's about one's attitude
in conducting academic research.
Okay.
Hello, can I take a look?
Thank you.
According to the training graph,
I can see that your model is overfitted.
You should reduce
the number of iterations.
Why didn't I think of that?
Can you tell us more in detail?
We have been
working on this problem
for months.
-Yeah.
-Sure.
Why don't we add each other on WeChat?
We'll talk about it later.
But
can you do me a favour?
Next, we have contestant number seven.
Hello, I'm Lu Jing.
Hello, I'm Zhou Zhou.
We are year four
undergraduate students
from Nanze University.
Our topic this time is
the big data of the deep sea.
All right. Let's have a round
of applause and cheers
for Liang Chen.
Thank you, everybody.
Liang Chen,
do you have any words for your fans?
Thank you for coming today.
In the past year,
did you work hard
to bring yourself
closer to your dreams?
Yes.
Over here.
It's finally time for the long awaited
lucky draw.
Everyone, please take out your tickets
and carefully check the number.
Because after this,
we'll pick one lucky
audience to go on stage
for an interactive session
with Liang Chen.
Alright. Liang Chen, if you will.
I heard there's a lucky draw today.
What's your number?
Number 187.
Who is it going to be?
Where is number 187?
Is number 187 here?
Quickly come to the stage.
It'll be over soon.
You can't go in.
We have tickets and we can't go in?
No. There's no space left.
My girlfriend is in there.
If I don't go in and keep her company,
she will break up with me.
All right, go in.
Thank you, buddy.
Thank you.
Unfortunately, he is not here.
Next, we'll have Liang Chen
draw a new number.
Number 88.
Where is number 88?
It's me. It's me.
Way to go, Lu Jing.
That was some quick thinking.
Quickly come to the stage.
How do you feel now?
[Happy Birthday.]
I'm very excited.
I'm thankful that
number 187 didn't come.
Number 187?
Aren't you number 187?
You guys have met
before on the airplane.
She was in the business class and
you were in the economy class.
And now, you've missed the chance
to be on stage with her.
Seems like you two aren't fated
to be together.
Alright, I know everyone
is fired up.
It's time for today's
question and answer session.
Raise your hand
if you have something to ask.
But
only one question for each person.
Anyone?
Me, me.
Let me take a look.
Okay, the man in the orange shirt
in the first row.
Yes, you.
Liang Chen, may I ask,
do you normally have time
to watch live broadcasts?
I watch it sometimes.
I watch it too.
Okay, thank you. Please sit down.
Anyone else?
Me, me.
Over here. Me, me.
Okay, the last row.
The one on the left
of the energetic gentleman.
Yes, you.
May I ask
who your favourite broadcaster is?
Hello.
Can you hear me?
[I hear you.]
[His voice is quite nice.]
Excuse me, is this earring yours?
What's wrong?
It's just that he sounds familiar.
Can you repeat yourself?
I'm sorry, I didn't catch that.
I'd like to know
who your favourite broadcaster is?
I like
Herman, the broadcaster
of Beautiful Soul.
She likes you! She likes you!
Who do you usually play with?
I'm sorry, fan.
Next.
I...
She plays with me.
Hello, everyone. I'm Ding Jia Yun.
I'm Liang Chen's best friend.
Chen Chen, happy birthday.
Thank you, Jia Yun.
What a surprise.
I never thought you would come.
What a surprise!
I never thought Jia Yun would come.
Jia Yun, just now you said
you play Beautiful Soul
with Liang Chen.
What's that about?
Actually, we play it
together with our friends.
Liang Chen plays well.
And she always gives us surprises.
No. I'm just a dabbler.
♫ Happy birthday to you! ♫
Let's wish Liang Chen
a happy birthday!
Happy Birthday!
Lu Jing, what's wrong with you?
The birthday party isn't over yet.
Where are you going?
It's pointless. I'm leaving.
All right.
Ke Ke, give me my smartphone.
What are you looking at?
I just remembered
I have something to do.
[Happy birthday.]
[What does it mean?]
[Did he find out it's me?]
[Sorry, it's my mistake.]
[Lucky me.]
[I thought today is your birthday.]
[I guess not.]
[I can't lie to him.]
[But I can't let him know either.]
[I was watching the live broadcast of
Liang Chen's birthday party today.]
[She said she likes you.]
[Well? Are you happy?]
[Really? I like myself too.]
Would it kill you to
express your happiness?
[When will you teach me
how to play hopscotch?]
[I'm free tonight.]
[See you tonight.]
Lu Jing, wait for me.
Luckily, Jia Yun came just in time
to rescue you.
Or else I'm not sure
how I could handle the situation just now.
It was an off-the-cuff rescue.
You don't mind, do you?
Of course not.
Thank you.
Let's have dinner tonight
to celebrate your birthday.
Tonight?
Everyone is here
and there's no work
arrangement tonight.
I...
All right.
Where are you going again?
The cybercafe.
You haven't eaten yet.
I'm not hungry. Help yourself.
Wait for me!
Thank you.
The birthday party is a success.
Not bad.
Why is the signal so bad here?
Here's your birthday present.
Thank you, Jia Yun.
You're welcome.
It's too much. I can't accept it.
How can you not
accept a birthday present?
Right?
Take it.
Thank you.
Ms Liang, let me take a look.
I didn't see it just now.
It's gorgeous.
Ms Liang, quickly try it on.
Let me put it on for you.
Thank you, Jia Yun.
You're welcome.
[Zero Gravity Cybercafe]
How many hours?
Same as him.
Would you like to apply for a card?
There's a discount for top-ups.
WeChat or Alipay?
Alipay.
Scan here.
Done.
You sit over there.
The power button is on the desktop.
Jing,
you think I didn't know
how to boot up the computer?
Lu Jing,
you've been holding your phone and
acting strange the whole night.
What exactly are you doing?
This is the most tortuous
conversation in the world.
I'm right in front of you,
yet you're texting me on WeChat.
Do you really have to
do it through the satellite?
The bars are full and
the phone is working.
Did something happen to her?
She?
Who is she?
So you went without food all night
because of Box Spirit?
Sir.
Thank you.
[Where are you?]
[Are you all right?]
This is sugar free. Give it a try.
Okay.
Let's wish Chen Chen a happy birthday.
-Happy birthday!
Thank you.
I'll study hard
and serve our motherland.
[I'm sorry. I'm in the
middle of something.]
[I might not be able to
go online tonight.]
[I'm sorry. I'm in the
middle of something.]
[I might not be able to
go online tonight.]
Let's watch it again.
I've already cried once.
Then cry again with me.
I want to have another piece.
[Finally, I finished my work.]
[Are you still on tonight?]
Have you been playing
Beautiful Soul recently?
But I'm still terrible at it.
My boss is good at it.
Why don't we team up tonight?
Do you have something on tonight?
Not for the time being.
Then let's play.
Jia Yun,
I might drag you down.
Never mind, I'm here for you.
Shall we watch it again?
Look at my eyes.
I can't watch any more of it.
[Finally, I finished my work.]
[Are you still on tonight?]
[Are you busy?]
[Then I'll team up with my friend.]
So she is playing with that man.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Isn't this the Box Spirit
that you brought back last time?
Why didn't you play with her?
I don't feel like playing today.
If I carry her again,
I'll be a dog.
It's late.
I'm going back.
Get some rest.
Okay.
[I saw you online.]
[You saw wrong. I've logged off.]
I knew it. He's angry.
Good. That's it.
The boy on the left, be happier.
Smile.
Lu Jing, we're at an award ceremony,
not a funeral.
A big smile, please.
Give me a smile!
Ready and
three, two, one.
Dear Ke Ke,
I want to ask you a serious question.
Okay, go ahead.
Are there any unique items
in Beautiful Soul recently?
The ones that will be seen
as generous gifts?
Are you going to send it to
the guy you reported your schedule to?
Yes.
Ms Liang,
why should you go to such lengths
for an internet friend?
You don't even know
if he's tall or short or slim or fat.
I'm really worried
about your love life.
Didn't you say that
he'd always be two metres tall
in your heart?
What?
It's Herman. You said it yourself.
Herman? Are you lying to me?
It's a lie.
You're actually playing with Herman?
Why didn't you tell me?
You didn't ask.
I know.
There's this awesome backpack
that was launched recently.
It's very rare
and very suitable as a gift.
Okay, I'll go find it.
What happened to you and Box Spirit?
She found someone else to carry her.
A man?
Maybe he is just a friend.
Is my technique not good enough
or am I not quick enough?
Am I not enough for her?
I get it.
You're jealous.
I didn't know you'd be
this childish when you're jealous.
No, you're imagining it.
Wait for me!
Lu Jing, you...
You're really childish!
Just say it.
Ms Liang, your skill...
You're very persistent.
It's too hard.
Why don't you just buy one?
Buy?
Is it for sale?
Why didn't you say so?
You didn't ask me.
What's with the long face?
Lu Jing.
[Zero Gravity Cybercafe]
I'm not going.
We have nothing to do anyway.
Come on.
All you ever think of
is surfing the internet.
Can't you do some reading
and write a few lines of code?
[Will you be online today?]
[No, I'm not in the mood.]
[When will you be online?]
[I want to send you a gift.]
[What gift?]
[You'll find out when you go online.]
[Wait for me.]
[Let's go.]
[What are you doing?]
[Let's go to the cybercafe.]
All you ever think of
is surfing the internet.
Can't you do some reading?
Can't you write some code?
Then I'll go myself.
Lu Jing, can't you be a human?
I thought you were busy.
I wasn't.
You haven't got this
new equipment yet, right?
This is very hard to get.
Did you win it yourself?
Wait a minute.
How could you possibly
win it on your own?
Did you buy it from someone else?
Keep it to yourself.
Don't say it out loud. I have my pride.
Let me return your courtesy.
Hold on a second,
I'll give you something nice.
Okay.
You wouldn't trade this helmet with me
all these years,
and you're giving it to her?
Lu Jing,
some friend you are.
Tell me. How many times
have I asked for it?
Did you ask me for it?
What do you mean?
I treat you as an
important guest in my life.
But you treat me as
a passer-by in your life.
Ke Ke, I'm here to take my coat.
Give me a second.
Jia Yun,
don't you have work today?
My schedule is cancelled.
I'm here for my clothes.
I left it here.
You're playing Beautiful Soul
with someone else?
-Carry on.
-Okay.
I'm off.
Goodbye, Jia Yun.
Bye-bye.
I'm back.
What were you going
to give me just now?
Where is he?
Is he disconnected?
[Grenade]
What's wrong with him?
What are you doing?
I heard something over on her side.
A man said
he left his coat at
her place last night.
Isn't she using a voice changer?
Are you sure it was a man?
What's going on?
Is he mad again?
Or
is he
disconnected?
Ms Liang, take a seat.
I'll return the laptop first.
I'm still using it.
Why did you shut it down?
I thought you were not using it.
Where is she?
She logged off.
Let it go, my guest.
Of course you have to forgive her.
Buzz off.
[Hello, Lu Jing.]
[Are you still online?]