The Long Ballad
Episode 44
I tell you
Lucky for you this time
Next time
But no such luck
This pastry
Is for your princess
Such an exquisite dim sum
What a pity
What do you mean
Nothing interesting
I just want to tell you
Don’t think there is a Young Khan
Support you
I forgot who I am
Things to do for the princess
No one can stop
Changge
Did you see Changge?
She went to Xiu Niang to learn embroidery
Said it was for the princess
Haven’t come back yet
What happened
Nothing
It’s time for dinner
Otherwise
Let’s go find her
The store said Changge
Already left
Then where else would she go
Mimi
Do you know something
Shouldn’t the prince
be in Tai Chi Palace?
Why come
Such a remote place
The prince said there are many people in the palace
In case someone recognizes you
It’s not good
So he choose
In this country house
Also for your cousin’s sake
When did you follow the prince
A long time
When is
Too long
I can’t remember it
We’ve arrived
If it’s too long you don’t remember
How should it be
Before changing the yuan
What am i doing to you
No impression at all
The princess is too worried
The prince is inside
Let’s go in and say
Say
Who on earth sent you?
What’s your purpose around the prince
Let’s go in and talk to the prince
The princess is indeed the princess
No wonder the master ordered me to be careful
It’s a pity
Brother Sun
Where did you all go
I haven’t seen anyone for a whole day
Where’s Changge?
You didn’t see Changge today?
No
I thought
You guys are out to play
Curfew is coming soon
If Changge hasn’t come back
That must be an accident
Let’s go back to the house first
I suspected to be Princess Yicheng
She poisoned Zhixi
Frame Changge unsuccessful
So I think she use force
I’m going to find her
Wait a minute
It’s useless to use force
Maybe
I can still ask She’er for help
They won’t believe you
Unless you kill me
You will pretend to assassinate me in a while
Only this way
It is possible to win
Yicheng’s trust
Get close to She’er
Not right.
To save Changge
This is crazy too
Late at night
The one who barged into my mother’s room is you?
Who’s making a ruckus this night?
Where is Changge?
What a joke
Your person isn’t here
But came to ask me
The whole city of Chang’an
You’re the only person who would play tricks
Ashile Sun
The reason why I didn’t expose your identity in front of the tribes
is to save your face
Now
You actually disrespect me just for the Li Tang Princess?
If this spreads out
you’re lose your reputation in the Grasslands
Ashile Sun you’re insane
Ashile Sun
She saved your reputation
You still want to kill her
Brother Sun
Are you alright
I said I’m going to find someone
Let’s juggle with a fake knife
Look at you now
How painful it must be
How smart is Yi Cheng
Even if it is really thorn
It may not be trusted
Not to mention fake knives
Mimi has been merciful
Minor injuries
Now just hope
She can go well
Detect the news of Changge
You still wait for the medicine
Discuss again
Don’t use this
This is our Monan
Best medicine
Very effective
What are you doing?
I’ll help you
I got it
Brother Sun must be shy
Right
I do it myself
Then I will
Put it here
Call me if you need help
I’m at the door
Tell me
Tell you what?
You stood up to my mother for?
Today you’re one of my mother’s people
So you’re also my person
Tonight, you’ll have to serve me
Come
Why?
Why do you use yourself to save Changge?
You think I can’t see through you?
You just want to get close to me to know where she’s at
Say it
What is your plan
She’er
I won’t tell Mother
Changge was taken away by your mother
I beg you
I beg you to help Changge
Why are you framing my mother
No
Poisoning of Zhixi
Your mother gave it to me
Her purpose
Is to blame Changge
She’er
I know
You waited a long, long time
To be reunited with your mother
Now I let you do it for me
It’s hard to go against your mother’s wishes
But I really don’t
Have another way
Now only you can help me
Save Changge, ok?
I beg you
I am willing to come back to you
Serve you
To save Li Changge
You are willing to sacrifice yourself
If there is no Changge
I would be dead on the grassland a long time ago
I’m not helping you
I also want to know the answer
I know it’s Mother
Behind the scenes
I just don’t want to face it
Maybe it’s time to reveal the answer tonight
This in my eyes
Such a weak woman
Why step by step
Take control of the royal court
Princess
Sheng Xin has succeeded
Good
It’s not in vain that I love him so much
Li Changge can’t die yet
I want to use her
To blackmail Li Shimin
She is the key to tearing up peace alliance
Don’t let her run
Yes
Also
Sheng Xin
No need to go back
Li Chengqian is by my side
What
What?
Don’t understand me
Yes
Subordinates understand
The subordinates will go to the western suburbs wooden house
Wait
Let Shengxin and Li Chengqian
Make a formal farewell
It’s never too late for you to deal with
So as not to trouble yourself
The subordinates knows, Princess
Changge is at the wooden house in the western suburbs
You really found the information
Go to Wei Manor to tell Wei Shuyu to save people
This
What about you
You go first
I am here waiting for you
Go
No longer have to struggle, Princess
You can’t escape
Your life must of cost a lot of money
You still want to use me to blackmail Great Tang
You people think too highly of me
Take her away
Go
Don’t be afraid
I’m here
You can’t kill me
I’m the Crown Prince’s person
Li Changge’s identity once the cover is blown, it’ll create chaos
Do you guys not want to live anymore?
You can’t kill him
He’s a registered person at the East Palace
If you kill him none of us will be clean
With Mobei here
We can’t create trouble with Great Tang
Are you guys going to stop or not?
Let’s leave
Someone
Mobei’s people is trying to rebel against the Crown Prince
They want to kill
Someone
A’Sun
Go
Stop chasing
Can’t catch up
Check to see if anyone is alive
Yes
A’Sun
You shouldn’t kill Shengxin
We should not provoke them
If I can’t find you tonight
I even kill Yicheng
Stop acting recklessly
Oh my goodness
I’m going to see a doctor
No way
Today’s matter
You didn’t see it
Brother Sun, I’m a girl
Give me the medicine
Okay
Here
Bear with it
Go get the medicine
Oh okay
I shouldn’t let you hurt again
I’m fine
Just this matter
I’m afraid It’s not all that good
Tang still needs you if the alliance isn’t sucessful
He won’t give up easily
its just that it requires the edge of a blade
it’s the same as the grasslands
Check and balance each other
I won’t kill Yicheng now
but I won’t make it any better for her
Changge
Do you trust me?
Your medicine
Thank you
What’s dead
Who’s dead
Your Highness
It’s your attendant Shengxin
What
Fast
Open the white cloth
Show me
Who
Who killed him
I will find out
Give an explanation to His Royal Highness
Catch him for me
Within an hour
If you still can’t catch
The murderer who killed Shengxin
You
You all sit together
Princess
Princess, not good
Shengxin is dead
Li Changge has escaped
Who leaked the whereabouts
Subordinate incompetence
Haven’t found out yet
No need to check
It’s me
Mother
Who is he
One of my guards
No matter when
You can go in and out at will
Discuss with Mother
How to kill the guard
What do you want to say
I heard you talk last night
Mother
I just want to know
Everything you do
It’s for our Ashile Tribe
Or for the former Sui
In your heart
I’m Ashile Tribe’s Khatun
Or the princess of the former Sui
Or your mother
No matter what status I am
I will always be your mother
Our mother and son are connected by blood
The king of the grassland and the former emperor of the Sui Dynasty
For me
All have the same purpose
That’s my son
Must dominate everything
Have you asked me if I am willing?
You are my son
This is your birthright
Your responsibility
Mother
I used to think you were vulnerable
Now feel you are so strange
If the guard of Mobei Princess is available
Please come out
Search
I didn’t expect you to have the courage
Is a man who dares to be a dare to be
But since it came out
Please come with me
Good
But I have a word
Need to declare
You say
I was the murderer last night
Tegin of Eagle Division from Ashile Tribe
Ashile Sun
He is Ashile Sun
He killed someone
I came here with Ashile Tribe’s Khatun
and Young Khan.
Placed t the side of Mobei Princess
Waiting for an opportunity to kill
Intent to assassinate the East Palace
My son who I think about day and night
Thought I was strange
Mother
Sorry
You say
Should I hate your Uncle Khan
Why do he want to separate our mother and child
Why
Want my son to rebel against me
I dare not
Dare not
You ruined my plan
Are you going to take me
Give to Great Tang
Mother
I just feels uncomfortable
Don’t want to hide
Khatun, not good
Great Tang brought troops here
Said to capture Young Khan
What
Khatun
Ashile Sun assassinating the Eastern Palace
Has already been explained
Say you and Young Khan
Behind the scenes
What a joke
Just by his one-sided words
Great Tang
Want to be an enemy of Ashile Tribe
But don’t panic
Wait for me to find out the truth
Naturally, you can be innocent
But now I need to bring Young Khan
Go back for questioning
Otherwise
It’s not easy to explain to the Crown Prince
Dare you
Mother
Our Ashile Tribe
Is always upright
Since Great Tang wants a truth
I am not afraid of the shadow
She’er
Princess
Young Khan is...
He is punishing me
A’Sun
Changge
You are hurt
What are you doing
It was you last night
Gave me a tranquilizer
Do you know what A’Sun is going to do
Brother Sun didn’t
Tell me the plan
He just begged me for help
I should have thought of it
He likes you so much
He can do anything for you
He wants
Help you pull down Ashile’s subordinates
I
Can you help me
Go and beg His Majesty Tang Emperor
Let him save their lives
In fact, killing Young Khan to death
It’s not good for him
I don’t care about Yicheng
What do you want
I can’t do it
Changge
You are now
Are the only one who can do it
And the only one who can ask His Majesty Tang Emperor
A man with a high hand
I know better than any of you
The saint
The so-called saint
For the prosperity of Great Tang
I don’t even care about my own life
Not to mention being an Ashile
Now Sun takes She’er as a hostage
Sent to Great Tang
He lost his life
Won a bargaining chip for the peace alliance
No matter how difficult the road is
The harder I am, the more I will go
There must be a way
National Affairs in the Six Secret Teachings
Back
I only wants one
Know the constraint equilibrium
Let go of the murderous prince
Father picked the wrong person
I only remember the laws of martial arts
Good good
Advisor Fang
Since today
Guilty
Ji Ling Zhong Shu Men
4 or more
And Shang Shu Jiuqing Yizhi
So
Injustice
The death of the Prince’s playmate
You must be innocent.
Can’t get a life in vain
Nowhere to go
All three are close ministers
I don’t shy away
Your Majesty
In a humble opinion
It’s better to take advantage of the momentum and pursue the victory
Although the dead is the prince’s attendant
But Ashile Tribe
Has assassinate one of the East Palace
That Ashile Tribe
Deserved to be put to death
After all sorts of smooth sailing
To
The alliance of the various ministries of the desert can be achieved
Unexpected
Someday
Will identify with Duke Du
Ashile’s Khatun
In the Sifang Pavilion
Now her only child is detained
She didn’t respond
This is not normal
It seems that
Not like Duke Du
As expected
Your Majesty
Rumors spread in the city
It is said that Ashile Tribe’s troops stationed in the western border
Various ministries in the desert are threatened
Shouldn’t have come back then
The patriarch has no news
Yeah
It seems
We really shouldn’t have come to Chang’an
Originally wanted
Find a backing for your own people
But now Nijia is gone
This is what caused trouble to the upper body
What about Monan?
Can’t be spared
Ashile Tribe
Is going to our hometown
It’s hard to ride a tiger now
Where is Father?
How is Father?
Can you cope
Princess
The leader makes the princess
Just stay in Chang’an
Can’t go back temporarily
Father said so
It must be me
You you
You guys
How did I tell you
Don’t provoke the Ashile Tribe
The current scourge
That’s you
Provoked
Fortunately
Our Tiele Tribe is spared
You see
What are the benefits with Great Tang’s peace alliance
I advise you
Hurry up and go tomorrow
If they really fight
Datang can save you
Makes sense
What can I do
Yes, you have to protect yourself
Can’t and union
Leave tomorrow
Then let’s go tomorrow
Go
Leave tomorrow
Just go
Yes
That’s right
As long as people are gone
That person must have withdrawn their troops
I want Ashile Tribe
There are plenty of adults
Shouldn’t be embarrassing for you
Yes yes yes
Will forgive us for sure
Hurry up
Then we
Start tomorrow
Leave tomorrow
Princess wants to see you
I know, Changge
I heard you got hurt
Are you okay?
You
Do you know the news about A’Sun
Chengqian went crazy
Have to kill him
But don’t worry
On this knotty eye
He will be fine
You in the end
I’m fine, Leyan
You don’t have to worry about me
Right
Ashile Tribe is going to send troops
What’s the answer to Tai Chi Palace
This time
The news of the troops was too sudden
Father hasn’t received the military report
Military newspaper came from the border
Takes time
But this journey
Faster than the scout’s footsteps
Such a short time
Spread all over Chang’an
This disturbing method
Leyan
Dare you stay with me again
Take a risk
Thank you everyone
No envoys were suspicious
Thought these
Is the head of the family
Autograph
Even Princess Monan
Thought she received the letter
Is written by Yi Nan
They have confirmed
Chen Bing, Western Region of Ashile Tribe
Should be these two days
Will leave Chang’an
I think it’s Commander Yang
Ghost
I beat you to death
You traitor
It’s pretty hard
Such a vicious traitor
Even united with the Ashile Tribe
Murder me
Use me to destroy the peace alliance
I’m taking him away today
Right
The table of letters inside
All forged
You take it
Sure enough, it was Yi Chengshi’s trick
Look at her now
What else to say
She’er
You will understand
Mother’s painstaking efforts
Princess
Not good
Chihe seems to have something wrong
My subordinate just saw
Li Changge
With Princess of Tang’s guard
Leave the hall
So I went to the Tiele Tribe’s residence to check
No one was there
Mess on the ground
Subordinate
Also found this
This is the ornament of a key member of the Tiele Tribe
Doesn’t belong to Chihe
In Great Tang
Can wear this kind of ornament
Zhixi
Zhixi is still alive
Mimi Guli
She didn’t even use poison
I want Mimi Guli
Watching Buzhen and Mu Jin with her own eyes
How did they die
In addition
Li Shimin wants to touch my son
I want his daughter
And the whole Great Tang will be buried with me
Yes Princess
People
Why are you saying this
What exactly is Great Tang going to do?
Just call us over
Ashile Tribe wants to be true
What to do if you send troops to attack
Yeah
What’s the use of keeping us closed?
If you really let Ashile Tribe
End our tribe
Home broken
What are we allied with?
All messengers can rest assured
News from Ashile Tribe’s soldiers
Is false news
This fake news
Princess
False news you told
What does it mean
Ashile Tribe did not send troops
Does not at all
Plan to attack the desert
Bring them in
He is Zhixi from the Tiele Tribe
He’s not dead
He is still alive
What the hell is going on
Why is he still alive
I obviously saw him
Already dead
See it with my own eyes
I’m Zhixi
I’m not dead
This Chihe
He was long ago bribed by the people of Ashile Tribe
Bribe
After the ambassador to the Tang Dynasty
He kept instigating me
Let me oppose the alliance
In order to break the alliance
He still wants my life
If it’s not for the envoy of Mobei
I’m afraid
I really have become an injustice
Mobei Princess
You have something so late
Come in and talk
I’m going to make a long story short
Ashile Tribe wants to use poison
Take your life and blame me
Thus tore up all parts of the desert
Harmony with Great Tang
What
Nonsense
The messenger does not have to make a judgment first
Am I talking nonsense
You will know tomorrow
This medicine
Bleeding in the nose and mouth after eating
And the symptoms of poisoning death
Yes-kind
But it won’t kill you
What are you trying to say
What am i talking about now
You won’t believe it
As long as tomorrow
When someone takes your life
You will understand
Do you want to change
You figure it out
Even if what you said is true
Then why do you want to help me
I’m not helping you
I’m helping the whole desert
If there is no backing of Great Tang,
We will always only
Was led by the nose by Ashile Tribe
I really don’t understand
Actually at the beginning
I don’t believe in the words of Mobei Princess either
But who knows the next day
Actually as the princess said
Envoy Zhixi
Your maid is unwell today
Let me come over and help send off early
Good
But
Why would Mobei Princess
Know all this
Also prepared in advance
The pill of Zhixi’s suspended animation
Yeah
To
Want to plant it on me
Threatening my maid
It’s a pity they underestimated
The relationship between me and the maid
That day
The princess saw my strangeness
It’s time to play for the princess
Put the poison on
Zhixi’s food
Blame it on Li Changge afterwards
Otherwise
Think about your brother
Mimi
What’s wrong with you
You look flustered
I am fine
Is Yicheng threatening you?
Changge
She wants me
To poison Zhixi
Blame you
Destroy the alliance
Too vicious
To destroy the alliance
She actually killed him
Since she threatened you
Then you just follow it
Avoid her making things difficult for you in the future
But
It doesn’t matter
I have a way to fake it
Don’t worry, I will protect you
I won’t let you have an accident
Just let Zhixi die in a fake death
Clarify afterwards
Will Zhixi be willing to fake his death?
Can only bet
But
I bet he will
If I hadn’t seen it with my own eyes
Heard it
I don’t believe in all of this either
The reason why I keep hiding
Did not show up
Just want to see
What other unseen things will Ashile Tribe do?