The Long Ballad
Episode 43
Why is she seeing Zhixi early?
Zhixi.
Why didn’t you answer when I call you for a long time?
Someone!
There is the trouble!
Someone, come!
Someone!
Take a look.
Zhixi died terribly.
He was fine yesterday.
How could this happen?
Wait.
It’s poison.
Take him away.
Mobei Princess.
Even if Zhixi didn’t want
to form an alliance,
you didn’t have to be cruel.
What?
It was Mobei Princess?
It was under the hands of the Mobei Princess?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I’m talking nonsense?
I’m not talking nonsense.
I saw it with my own eyes.
The maid of Mobei Princess
went to see Zhixi early morning.
Zhixi is dead.
Among all of us,
only Chi Xi does not recognize the alliance.
You kill him.
This is too vicious.
If it is the tribes of the Great Desert
don’t recognize it,
it’s impossible
you will one by one
kill us all here?
If we don’t sign,
we get killed?
Yeah.
Everyone quit down first.
This case happened in my Great Tang,
naturally by me
Great Tang officials are responsible for the investigation.
You came just right on time.
The perpetrator,
it was
the maid of Mobei Princess.
She gave it to Zhixi.
She saw him early this morning.
After I went in to see him,
he was already dead.
Who else can it be?
Envoy is less restful.
Since I’m here
I will definitely check it out
Give an explanation to the envoys.
What did you find
There is no comment on an important case
Farewell
Young Master Wei
What are you hesitating
Now that we have found physical evidence
Just report it directly
Even if you are afraid of implicating Mobei Princess
You can’t hide it and not report it
Yeah
Mobei Princess
Is the one who contributed to the peace alliance
If she is suspected
The covenant will be affected
But you can’t hide it without reporting it
If Great Tang is covering up the suspicion
Only really affected
The foundation of the peace alliance
Important place for case handling
Idle people are not allowed to enter
A maid
Dare to poison people in this place
Say
The culprit behind you
Was it her?
There is no evidence and basis.
Vicious words slander others
You all killed someone
Can’t others tell me?
Since you want your maid
Be your substitute
I fulfill your wish
Young Khan
In the public
Pointed a knife at a woman
The great desert’s face
I’ve lost all of you
Everyone is the warrior of every tribe
Battlefield kills
When to bully a woman
Interested
No rest, everyone
From this maid’s room
Found a bottle of poison
After inspection
The envoy indeed died of this poison
Personal evidence and physical evidence
What else to say
I said
Don’t bully women
Young Khan
Are you going to protect the real murderer?
I haven’t finished talking just now
Although the medicine bottle is from
Found in the maid’s room
But doesn’t belong to this maid
This medicine bottle
It’s from Young Khan of Ashile Tribe
That’s right
This residence in Central Plains
Mostly built with wood
Recruiting rats and insects
I prepared this bottle of poison
The medicine is indeed mine
I did give it to Zhixi
Young Khan this
This medicine is really yours
But I saw this maid with my own eyes
Walk out of Zhixi’s room
Now medicine bottle
Searched her room again
This
How does this explain
You mean
I instructed this maid from Mobei
to assassinate Zhixi
Then I planted and blamed her
I just elaborated
The facts you have seen with your own eyes
Everyone has many doubts in this case
We will check them one by one
Give everyone an innocence
Everyone is a great guest of Great Tang
We Great Tang
Will be polite
Before the case is cleared
Young Khan must not leave
His room half a step
Guarded by Tang officials
Cooperate with the trial at any time
The maid
And don’t leave the Sifang Pavilion
If you flee without authorization
The murderer
Young Khan, please
This matter is getting more and more complicated
Who did it?
It could be great
if such peace can exist and last forever
May every citizen of Great Tang
Have food and clothing
They’ll definitely will
His Majesty governs the country and loves the people
Great Tang will once again become peaceful
Old man
Let me help you
Old man, are you okay?
I’m fine
My grandson is still waiting for me to cook
Old man
Let me help you
It’s not convenient,
you have to accompany your wife
No no no
Old man
My wife would agree, let me help you
I’ll help you
Thank you
What a great man
I always thought
We were connected as mother and son
I just understood today
It turned out not to be like this
She’er
Left me for too long
He never knew what I did
What I mean to do
He stood up today
Took the blame for Mimi Guli
Just ignore me as a mother
Should I should punish him
Or punish myself
Princess
Rest assured
I will take care of this matter
Make sure Young Khan is unharmed
Right
To
If the night is too long, there will be more dreams
We want to speed up
Subordinates understand
Changge
I want to see She’er
Can you help me
Beg Young Master Wei
To let me see She’er
What do you want to see him?
I did not expect
He will stand up for me
I was his playmate when I was young
Also a slave
But he really treats me as a friend
In fact, he is quite pitiful
OK then I will help you
But come back soon after you see him
Don’t be known
Stand still
Why are you here
I’m afraid you can’t get used to
Great Tang’s food
So I made you lamb noodles
Eat while it’s hot
Delicious
Why did you take the blame for me
You being like this
Katun will be upset
You are not afraid of damaging
Ashile Tribe’s reputation
She’er
Mimi
You made your own food
Have you been
Listening to me
Why should you admit
That poison is yours
How do you know it’s not mine
Is it really your poison
The Mimi I know
Is a kind and enthusiastic
Love to help weak women
How could she kill someone?
Ever since youth
Everyone treats me on the surface
Respectful
Just because I’m Young Khan
Only you
You really treat me like a friend
That was the time I missed so much
Since you left
I haven’t paid my sincerity anymore
Today’s matter
I just want to protect for the first time
I just want to protect someone
She’er
Thank you
But we can’t
This is my business
I’m leaving
She’er
Actually in this world
Many people are not
As you see on the surface
Such as
Just like me
Maybe
Maybe I am not
So kind as you imagined
I hope
You don’t care
Encounter anything
All judge by their own hearts
Because
You are different from other grassland people
What are you doing being clumsy?
Wipe it clean
Good good good
Khan
I am Mu Jin
Khan, I want to ask you
If yes
You blink
It’s Yicheng who hurt you
Right now Ashile Tribe
Is controlled by Yicheng
Commander Lei
Has Khan awake?
Still asleep
Khan
This is Dingxiang
Prince Sui of the former Sui Dynasty
Is it also here
Khan
I am alone now
There is no way to save you
But I will find a way
Notify A’Sun
Yes
A’Sun is not dead
If he knew
Where you are now
He will definitely come to save you
Lending you the fish token
Private allowing Mimi Guli to see Sheer
Already violated
This time, Uncle Kobu took the initiative to confess
Just leave it alone
Since you know
I came to commit a drug case
Then you must know
It’s not that simple
Changge
Banye Kobe has already admitted by himself
He took it
The medicine of Ashile Tribe’s Young Khan
Then put it in
In your maid’s room
Things have reached this point
The real culprit can only be him
I don’t believe you really would
Take Ashile Sheer for this
Since you must
Bring out the real murderer
Then this thing can’t
Take it so hard
But the man has committed suicide
Wei Shuyu
Sometimes something
It’s not that you see
What the ear hears
It must be the truth
The truth
Changge
Not all the truth
Have to get to the bottom
Sometimes the truth
Will only cause more trouble
What are you afraid of
Nothing right now
More important than the peace alliance
It’s better to stop here
Also
Your maid
It’s really not that simple
Her hands and feet are not clean
You have to be careful
Best not to stay by your side
I have my own measures
I advise you not to trust others
The most life-threatening
Often around
Betrayal by someone close
I’m just worried about you as a friend
And now by your side
Protect you
Inseparable person
It’s not a friend of Great Tang
I trust them
They trust me too
This is the same as that of Great Tang or the grasslands
It doesn’t matter
Changge
I’m just worried about you
I really didn’t mean anything
You worry wrong
If you just said A’Sun
I can too
Tell you plainly
Whether it’s him
Or my maidservant Mimi
Life and death friends
Is worth me
Friends you’ll make in your life
This time
I have experienced too many things
I understand this world
It’s not all black and white
Some people have their difficulties
If we must let this trust
If there is a price
I’ll recognize it too
Crown Prince
Few of you
Why are you so inconspicuous?
Crown Prince
If you are curious
What is the curator of Sifang?
Just tell me
To bring you here alone
Have to walk so much
My lone foot hurts
Why does the prince follow me
Orphans and relatives are here
Just come over and take a look
Relatives
For a peace alliance
These desert ministries
I’ll be a family from now on
Go
Your Highness
I want to go to the restroom
It hurts
Go there
Li Changge
So boring
You always do this
If I scare Sister
She will cry
You should try to scare your father
Then cry for you
You are really boring
Always talk to me about my father
I didn’t even tell my father
You are here
Very loyal
Still stern
Yeah what don’t you know
Need you to tell him
Your sister’s marriage
To be set soon
If you are idle
You go back and help
I have something else here
Don’t hinder me
A sister is going to marry
The adopted son of Minister Du
I’m not a hundred
I hope this world
The best man comes to marry my sister
Why are you looking at me like this
I can understand now
Why your father
I’m going to make you a reserve
That’s naturally because of loneliness
Wencheng Wude
Tian Zong Talent
Is a rare man in the world
Don’t go
That
Tell me
Why did Father set me up
You are not good
Shut up
Not smart and can’t do it
But you will always see
Others’ good
The so-called Junji
Is to treat the people around you
Love and care
Only those who love close
To love the children of the Quartet
Presumably he doesn’t want to
Let some things happen again
If we say
In other words, it’s you
I should save the people around me
Praise me, praise me
To
Best compliment
Talk more about me
Tell you
I can do a great job
To
If you are a man
It’s worthy of my sister
If I was a man
I can’t marry your sister either
Because my surname is Li
Also right
So
Li Changge’s surname Li
It’s the Li from Tang Dynasty
Yang Cheng
You try to check
Genealogy of Li Jiancheng
I don’t want to go empty this time
God helps me revive the Sui Dynasty
Turned her into
Delivered to me
Congratulations to the princess
Sheng Xin
Yang Cheng will try
Send the letter to the East Palace
You just have to act according to plan
If we recovery
You are the head
Worship the king
Li Tang can’t give you everything
I can give you
Thank you Princess
Go
Yes
The defeat of the owner of Mobei
It’s true that I miscalculated Khan
Mimi Guli’s thoughts
Since this chess piece
Failed to play the role it should have
May also disrupt
Young Khan’s mind
Not as good as
Let’s abandon her
After all it’s me
Elaborately educated those who came
What a pity to abandon it
Forget it
As long as Buzhen is still in our hands
Mimi Guli
How can I be afraid
This person
As long as there is desire and fear
Just weak
Will be led away
Li Changge is like this
Ashile Sun is like this
It’s a pity
She’er is the same
Princess
It’s time for Young Khan
To understand something
Since She’er is free
I should go visit
Katun
Young Khan would like to see you
Sure enough, mother and child are connected
Subordinates retire first
I have caused trouble to Mother
Please Mother punish me
Sit down
Our mother and son finally get together
How can I bear it
Seeing you being imprisoned
Never tell me
You’ve caused me trouble
I know
I suddenly commit the crime
It must be Mother’s painstaking efforts
These
Does not count for anything
Come
Eat
Your favorite pastries
Mother
Do you know who poisoned him?
Are these important?
If the truth is not important
What is important
Recovery of the Sui?
Sorry
These I shouldn’t ask
No
It’s not that you shouldn’t ask
But you should have understood
Since your Uncle Khan
Separate us mother and child
You are always outside
Savage growth
You have your way of doing things
Mother doesn’t blame you
It’s just that the world is cold
Unpredictable
Mother has no chance
Teach you well
Just let you go further and further away from me
Mother
I just want to guard Mother
Filial piety
I also want to do what I think
That’s why
You grow up
Mother is getting old
Many times
I have more than my heart but I don’t have enough energy
Don’t figure you can understand
But Mother hopes
Can you understand one thing
That is no matter what Mother does
All for you
My child
Buzhen
What are you doing when you wake up
I’ll play with you later
Buzhen
You are Buzhen
You know me
I am your sister’s friend
You’re my sister’s friend
Commander Lei
Get up
Take good care of Hi Majesty
Naturally nothing will happen
Buzhen
I’m leaving
Don’t tell anyone
You saw me
Sister is alright?
Very good
Lied to the military and sneaked into Dingxiang
This time
I want to see how Ashile Sun can save you.
Changge.
What are you doing?
Why are you so careless?
Buy instead if you can’t embroider.
Leyan’s marriage
is going to be settled soon.
I can’t appear in front of the civil and military officials as the envoy of Mobei.
Since I can’t attend her wedding
I have to embroider her something.
Better fan
But you see
it’s so hideous.
What are you laughing?
It looks great.
I think it looks the best.
I must find the best embroider in Chang’an.
I can’t even embroider good-looking ones.
When
can I fan it for you?
(A’Sun is waiting to be Changge’s husband)
Who said I’m giving it to you?
Here in Great Tang
I also need three books and six rituals from my parents.
But both of my parents aren’t here anymore.
I don’t know if my mother would like it.
She will.
The heavens can also be your parents
They will recognize their daughter’s husband
I swear to Sirius
I will treat you good for eternity
and forever.
Your words,
it’s not that I don’t believe it.
It’s just a pity
That my mother can’t see you in person.
Alright, enough talking
I’m going to head out,
to look for the best embroider pieces
I’ll go visit your mother for the marriage.
Tian Yuan’s scenery is so nice
Let’s go again next time
Will we be blamed for not returning to the palace the for the past few days?
Rest assured
I’ve already let His Majesty know
Really
When
Why don’t I know
Then you’re saying that
If in the future
you’re going to listen to me
Or listen to Father
I...
Buy some candy
Look
They’re selling sweet candies
I remember the first time I ate them were at Luoyang
Do you recall?
I remember
You also gave me it as a gift
I still have the one you gave to me
You still kept it?
Stop
Then wait for me, I’ll buy it for you
How much is this
2 coins
Thank you
Leyan
I thought I lost you again
Why would I
I know you must
I know you’ll be able to find me
Why are you sitting here
I accidentally twisted my foot just now
You hurt sprained your ankle?
Wait
Earlier I saw this chain
this sword
is particularly in line with your temperament
Do you like it
I...
I like it
Leyan
From now on
I won’t ever let you leave my side
I’m not worried at all now
Because of you now
Are your feet okay
Come
Madam.
I am Ashile Sun.
Long time so no see
Today I came to
ask for your permission
and I hope Madam
will give me permission to marry Changge as my wife.
There are three reasons for Sun to marry Changge.
First
Since you’ve left Changge for a long time
Changge no longer have anyone
If no one
worries about heart warm feelings
but loneliness will accompany.
If she doesn’t have anyone to lean on,
I, Sun
is willingly to accompany Changge.
Second
I, Sun have practiced martial arts since childhood
I believe
I have some achievements.
Although Eagle Division is no longer an active group
But I believe that
I can protect Changge
Won’t let her starve
Won’t let anyone
Hurt Changge a tiny bit
In my heart
Changge is more important than life
Third
If a person asks what to pursues in his life
I’m afraid it’s illusory
Through twists and turns
You’ll have to try your best
until the end
All I want is
for there to be peace
This is Changge’s wish
I hope
this is also your wish.
Until the end of the peace alliance
Sun wants to take Changge back
and stay away from endless wars
and have a happy life from now on.
Right now
I can’t get any decent dowry.
But Madam don’t you worry,
Sun swears to Sirius.
Whether it’s money
or the heart
Sun will be bound to Changge
and commit to everything.
Sugar candies, but sugar candies
Finally found the princess
You are?
I am the Crown Prince’s subordinate, Sheng Xin.
Your Highness said he asked me to pass on a message
He wants to see his cousin
The princess does not need to be nervous
Your Highness dared to keep such a private matter
And told me
It shows the trust in me
I never dare to say anything
Otherwise, the princess and your highness
You can take the head of this servant at any time
Long story short
Your Highness can’t appear
Just me
Find the princess now
Said he found some
Important things
Hand it over to his cousin
I am afraid that he won’t be able to win the trust of the princess
Your Highness is a bit difficult
I still wants me to just say
He wants to find his cousin
The princess will believe me
If the princess is suspicious
Not as good as a person
Walk with me
Not really
Crown Prince said
This matter must not be delay
I also ask the princess to go to the meeting place immediately