Do you believe
that a perfect relationship exists?
To me, relationships
are all about "take and give."
We all have merits of our own,
but that also means
we all have flaws.
It's naive to believe that
one can fulfill your every need.
I'm not one to ask for much.
I only wish for what
that certain person can offer.
That's right.
I'm currently in a relationship
with three guys.
Easy and fun to be around.
It's almost as if he looks up to me.
He's the younger guy,
aka Pocket Boy.
Intellectual and mature.
He understands my situation
regardless of what that is.
The mature boyfriend.
Last but not least...
is the sexy man who knows...
what women want.
That makes three.
You may be getting your entire fill
by receiving...
what all three men have to offer,
but the three men are left
to share you among themselves.
How's that fair?
It was always the guys
who came up to me first.
- Then...
- You're...
Now...
- My girlfriend.
We're each giving each other
what the other person needs,
so I don't see an issue.
Do the men know that others exist?
The fact that they don't know
makes this perfect.
(Love Scene Number)
What the...
Why are you always here
instead of at your own place?
Well, because your place is cleaner.
And better stocked.
Still, you should've told me
that you were coming over.
As if it's anything new.
- Aussie cheese fries?
- Double the bacon.
- Nice!
- Stop.
Humans are supposed to use tools.
Gimbap. That's what I'm craving.
Are you kidding me?
Not the kind you buy,
but the kind you make at home.
The homemade gimbap by Do Han Wool.
They're better than drugs.
Gimbap.
Gimbap by Do Han Wool.
Forget it.
Gimbap...
What? Why are you throwing a fit?
- Give me this.
- Not that one.
- I want it!
- It's a limited edition.
It wasn't easy for me to get that.
Choose from the others I have, okay?
Like what?
How about I take Buk-boogie instead?
What? Of course, you can't.
No can do then.
I'll...
just have to steal it.
Hey. Wait. Nam Du Ah!
Sorry.
Right.
I'll get going then.
Then there's the fourth guy.
My friend, Do Han Wool.
(Da Ham)
I bet you miss me.
You can come over.
Right now, of course.
My mom and dad? They went on a trip.
Just know that I won't wait long.
Wash your hands first.
Du Ah, how about
some eclairs for breakfast?
It's 10 a.m.!
Didn't you say you had a class?
What? Darn, I'll be late.
Your clothes.
Don't forget your clothes!
I've never seen these before.
- They're eclairs.
- Nice.
Is it good?
Nothing is better for breakfast
than sweet desserts.
Wait. That reminds me.
I brought the books.
Here.
Gosh. Thank you, Du Ah.
I'll make good use of them.
I've written a lot in those though.
These aren't just
ordinary books.
I asked for these
so that some of your energy...
will rub off me
and help me get a good score.
If that's the case, I'll give you
some of my other books too.
Did you know...
that we only get to experience
a limited amount of joy in life?
I wonder if I should be
getting my fill just with you.
He never seems to say
the same flirtatious line twice.
Crafty and creative. Nice.
Du Ah, are you free?
What is it, sir?
This. Would you like to
join my team?
"Society of Clinical Psychology
Symposium".
Yes, but it's not just
any symposium...
I'll take this.
No, I meant we should
participate together. Du Ah.
I want to take
the professor's class,
but I don't know what to do...
since I'm only in my second year.
If you didn't take
developmental psychology,
you won't be able to take it.
The professor asks each student
when you took that class.
It may be difficult to take it.
I took that class last year.
Really?
The professor's teaching style
and the exams...
are very similar to that class.
They're very...
soft.
What?
Well, yes.
(Department of Psychology
Teaching Assistant's Office)
I want to write a dissertation
about polyamory.
- What?
- For the symposium.
I'm almost done
with the dissertation plan.
By polyamory, do you mean...
The practice of being
in multiple open relationships.
You don't restrict your partner
from having multiple relationships.
A type of relationship
where you maintain relationships...
with several partners?
You mean...
That's right.
A close friend of yours, a writer,
wrote about it.
An increasing number of people
around the world...
are choosing not to get married.
That just proves that
there are flaws...
in the current marriage system.
Times have changed, and that means
people will change as well.
This is the perfect time
to research this.
So?
Please introduce me to her.
I want to interview her.
("Love Without Ownership")
I came here to interview you.
Sure. You can do that.
But first, let me ask you
a few questions.
Ask me?
Why did I... No. Why did my book
catch your attention?
I'd like to know that first.
What are you curious about?
After reading my book, this is what
people are the most curious about.
"Why did they become polyamorists?"
"How did they date..."
"multiple people at a time
and even get married?"
That's what they're curious about.
But you can't explain it.
Of course not.
This is just an inclination.
It's the same thing as asking why
a guy likes a woman.
Exactly.
It's an inclination.
You're just born with it.
But how they began...
and their method of doing it...
are different.
What about you?
Me?
You're not in
an ordinary relationship, are you?
How is it?
You're not going to show this video
to anyone else, are you?
If you're worried,
should I turn this off?
Once I'm done,
you'll do the same, right?
- Of course.
- Then it's fine.
I'm in a perfect relationship.
I beg to differ.
Before deciding what kind
of relationship is the most ideal,
you should determine
the sincerity...
Coming. I'm coming.
Okay, I'm coming.
This is you, right?
It's you, isn't it?
What is this?
This was posted
on our school's online community.
This is your house.
"I'm Exposing the Double Life..."
"of an Extremely Intelligent Student
from Social Science Class of 2017."
"From the outside, she looks like
a perfect, golden child."
"But the truth is,
she's in a messy relationship..."
"with three guys..."
"and is deceiving them."
This should be taken seriously.
Someone who came to your house
took this photo...
and spread such a ridiculous rumor
about you.
"A week from now,
on the 19th at noon,"
"I'll reveal her identity."
Then there's only six days left.
Let's tell the administrators
to delete this post immediately.
What are you talking about?
Do you want everyone to know
that it's me?
I can ask them.
Or it could be anonymous.
No.
It's useless to ask them
to delete it right now.
Then you'll let this be?
It's very unlikely that anyone
will know that this is me.
Deleting this post immediately...
will only provoke this individual.
By the way,
why are you so nonchalant?
Do you know who took this?
- Perhaps.
- Who is it?
I'll take care of this.
You can go home.
Don't be absurd.
What will you do on your own?
Then what can you do?
I'm the one who found that post.
I'm not leaving
until you explain it to me.
Hey.
These are the suspects
who could've taken this photo.
There are three in total.
It steadily grows...
Yeon Sang Woo, a senior of mine
and a graduate student.
Han Si Han, an engineering student,
class of 2018.
Yoo Da Ham, a fourth-year student
from K University.
- They've been here at least once.
- Stop it.
So that post is true?
You were dating three guys at once?
- So what?
- How could you be so fearless...
as to bring a guy home
when you're living alone?
Hey, you're a guy too.
And you're here with me.
Are you comparing me with them?
What's so different about you?
Han Wool,
I don't understand why you're
reacting this way. It baffles me.
There are consequences.
Don't you see the consequences?
It all happened because...
Are you saying it's because
I was careless?
No. That's not what I meant.
Whatever.
I can take care of it.
You really should go home.
Du Ah.
What's your relationship
with those three anyway?
I said, I can take care of it.
I'll find out why he did this...
and what he wants first.
Then I can stop him.
I don't care.
Just end your relationship
with all of them right now.
Then he'll reveal
who I am right away...
without waiting for a week.
Like I said, he wants me
to recognize myself in the picture.
He wants to see how I'll react.
If I end my relationship
with all three of them...
without even knowing who posted it,
he'll do something
even more provoking...
to corner me.
Go home. It's late.
I have to get up early tomorrow.
Tell me if you need anything.
I'll help you.
Okay. I will.
A perfect relationship.
A perfect relationship, my foot.
I've been completely fooled.
What do I do?
Who is it? Who did it?
It's one of the three.
Think. Think, Du Ah.
I can find him. There are only
a limited number of suspects.
Who's the most likely?
By analyzing, I can find him.
It's one of the three.
Among the three,
suspect number one is Yeon Sang Woo.
Are you okay? Why are you crying?
Are you not feeling well?
What's wrong?
He fell in love with me
the moment he saw me.
He's an open-minded grown man
who can accept whatever I say...
without prejudice.
He's been at my place twice.
That means he's had two chances
to take the picture.
Can you get my cardigan
from the kitchen?
Yes, sure.
I'd say he's had
more than enough chances.
Next,
suspect number two is Han Si Han.
Hey, Du Ah.
Yes?
There's something
I want to show you.
Okay. What is it?
This is an app I developed.
Your name, Du Ah, means love.
Whenever anyone in the world
searches for a word that means love,
a heart will pop up.
Do you mean
that's how you feel about me?
He's an innocent, younger guy...
who told me he'd had a crush on me
for two years...
since he entered university.
He's been at my place once.
That means he's had
only one chance to take the picture.
But if he really wanted to,
it wouldn't have been impossible.
The last suspect, Yoo Da Ham,
is the only one
who doesn't go to my school.
From the moment we first met,
we were strongly attracted
to each other.
He's an immensely sexy man.
He's been at my place...
a lot of times.
Countless times, actually.
Therefore, he's had
the most chances...
to take the picture as well.
People behave...
more morally in the morning
than in the afternoon.
It's called
the morning morality effect.
That means I have a higher chance
to catch his lie in the morning.
What's up? What are you doing
at my school so early?
Actually, there's been a bit of
an incident at my school lately.
A freshman girl broke up
with her boyfriend,
and he spread
her personal pictures...
all over social media.
In the end, the cops showed up
and everything.
- The cops?
- Yes.
Apparently, the girl made a report.
The guy should have just accepted
the breakup and dealt with it.
The thing is, she turned out
to have been two-timing him.
That's not an excuse.
What she did is wrong,
but he shouldn't have
reacted that way.
Has that been troubling you?
Yes.
I'll see you soon.
See you.
Da Ham.
Yes?
Do you want to come over later?
Wait!
Gosh, I'm sorry.
- I shouldn't drink alcohol.
- What?
I'll lose muscle mass.
This is my mom's favorite bottle.
You haven't had any alcohol
in a while, so it'll be fine.
- Cheers.
- Okay.
Let's do a love shot.
- Bottoms up.
- The entire glass?
Yes.
Gosh, you're amazing.
Incredible.
What is this?
October 12, Monday.
- This is my house.
- Morning body check.
Hi, Da Ham.
I love you.
Who is it?
Gosh, why is he...
What are you doing here?
Someone's in there, right?
I said I'd take care of it.
Is he one of those three guys?
I should find out who it is.
Is that important right now?
If he's the one who posted that,
you could be in danger right now.
- Hey.
- He's a neighbor.
He's a neighbor from downstairs.
I think we were a bit loud.
We were loud?
I'm sorry for causing a ruckus
at such a late hour.
I should go home.
- I'll call you. Goodnight.
- Okay.
Bye.
[Kocowa Ver] MBC E01 'Love Scene Number'
"The Mystery Online Post"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
What do you think will happen
if you get involved?
That'll be even more dangerous
since you'll be provoking him.
Why aren't you asking them
right away?
I told you.
They wouldn't confess that way.
Are you sure it's not because
you don't want to admit...
that you were betrayed by
those guys you looked down on?
What do you know about me
to say such things?
Do you know...
what I'm thinking?
You're right.
What do I know?
Don't skip your meals.
Okay.
Come to the elevator right now.
A plaid shirt?
Du Ah.
Hi.
What brings you to my house?
I've always wanted to visit.
Here you go.
Du Ah...
Goodness, I forgot to buy beverages.
I'm totally parched.
Could you buy me some beverages?
Okay.
- Right now.
- Okay. I won't take long.
Okay.
It's not in the gallery.
"DA"?
"Du Ah"?
Is it me?
What?
Why did he screenshot
all my photos from my social media?
Right, the plaid shirt.
The plaid shirt...
No, these are different.
These aren't it.
What the...
(Lovely Si Han, I miss you so much.)
A Ra?
(Si Han, I hope you like it.)
Ji Min?
(Si Han, it's the belt you wanted!)
Su Jin?
Are these all...
Gosh.
I got us some beverages.
What did you get?
Actually, these should
be set to the side.
Don't. Don't!
I'm not interested
in doing this with you.
Du Ah, I'm sorry.
I must've been insane just now.
This isn't who I am.
I hope you don't...
I'll...
Du Ah, I didn't mean it.
Yes, Professor. I'll be right there.
Just a moment.
(Photos)
(This folder is empty.)
Why has the cloud been wiped clean?
This is where Sang Woo
saves his photos.
Did he delete them on purpose?
What the...
Oh, hey. Is Sang Woo not here?
Yes, it seems like
he stepped out for a moment.
Did you have an appointment?
Oh, I must be here early.
I guess he'll be here.
He'll soon be here, right?
Anyway, take care.
Sure thing. I'll see you around.
No, it's fine. It's no big deal.
I found her intriguing.
- Du Ah?
- Yes.
I get this from students these days.
They have strong egos...
but nothing of substance.
Du Ah's like that too.
She thinks that what she learned...
is the way of the universe
and wants to apply...
technological terms
and theories everywhere.
I guess I know the type.
It's adorable,
but her thoughts
are still quite young.
She believes she has
great insight on things,
so who am I to burst her bubble?
Kids her age are all like that.
- Su Min.
- Yes?
- Did you see the post?
- Which one?
The three-timing girl from
Social Science Class of 2017.
No way. Who is it though?
I don't know,
but aren't her legs to die for?
No wonder she's able
to date three guys at once.
Did a peeping Tom take this?
- Beats me.
- Is there more about her?
I think I have an idea
of who it is though.
Who?
Du Ah?
Sorry.
What's that?
You see, I suddenly
had this wild thought.
"Could that be the only photo
which was taken of me?"
Perhaps, did he try to get
more photos of me and...
Are you talking about your house?
Yes. A device could've been set up.
It's why I bought this gadget.
Can this small device
help you locate anything?
It detects electromagnetic waves.
So if there's a camera in there,
a light will bounce off of it...
no matter how small the camera is.
Have you checked?
Have you given it a try?
No.
I was too scared to go inside.
It terrifies me to think
that a device could be in there.
It's why I can't
get myself to go in.
Give me that.
I'll do it instead.
I'll see if there are any cameras.
No, wait. I'll come with you.
I want to.
Come on.
Wait. What was that?
Nothing's there.
How did things get this far?
I'm just glad nothing is here.
So how did it go...
with your search?
Don't ask. It's so annoying.
Tell me what's going on.
You're running out of time anyway.
What is it that you want to hear?
Anything.
Why though?
So that you can laugh at me?
Fine, we'll laugh together.
You asked me
why I didn't confront them...
even though I knew
it was one of the three, right?
Yes, you're right.
I didn't want to admit that
I was wrong.
But...
do you know what's hilarious?
I've been completely fooled.
I thought that I was in control...
and that I had all three of them
perfectly under control.
Far from it.
They were fooling me the whole time.
All of them.
All three of them.
I thought that the younger guy...
had been head over heels
for me for years.
In reality, he was a psycho...
who uses women who like him
as ATMs.
Are these all...
I believed that the old guy...
was generous enough
to embrace all my weaknesses.
But her thoughts
are still quite young.
Sure, I'll introduce you to her.
We're close.
While pretending to be easy-going,
he talks behind his girl's back.
Such a mean pervert.
The other guy, the good-looking one,
turns out to be a huge narcissist...
who loves no one but himself.
It's not me that he wanted.
He was just intoxicated
by himself...
having sex with
an attractive, smart girl like me.
While I thought the three of them
make one perfect man,
all three of them
turn out to be trash!
Trash?
Aren't you the one...
who fooled them first?
There was no trust there
to begin with.
What were you expecting?
All of those guys wanted me first.
I gave them
as much as they wanted...
and expected to get
just as much in return.
Is this some kind of deal?
Dating is a relationship
between two people.
It's important that partners benefit
equally from the relationship.
That's the value of dating.
"Benefit"?
Who cares about that when dating?
Are you sure...
you're not the one with prejudice
or fantasies about dating?
Emotional stability, a bond,
comfort, admiration,
fun, and sexual satisfaction.
Those are the benefits.
I wanted all of that,
but no one man could give me those.
That's why I dated more than one.
Is that so wrong?
I worked hard to get what I want.
Was that for your partners?
Or for yourself?
Du Ah, dating is not research.
You do it with your heart,
not your head.
So? Are you saying I was wrong...
and deserved what happened?
No.
I feel sorry for you.
Did you break up with me...
to live like this?
- Han Wool.
- You must be tired. I'll be going.
Wait.
(Did you guys see this
on the forum?)
(Video of the three-timing girl
at S University)
(S University's online community
is blowing up about this girl.)
- What a horrible person.
- Disgusting.
- It's sick.
- I hate people like that.
- I heard she's in our department.
- I feel sorry for the guys.
I'm scared my girlfriend
might be like her.
- What a disgrace to our school.
- You should die.
How awful.
- I loathe people like her.
- I hope she dies.
What's wrong?
Come in.
- Do you feel okay now?
- Yes.
So? Did you check
what made the alarm go off?
No.
I was too scared.
I'll go check. Wait here.
No, don't...
Oh, I'm at Han Wool's.
Why on earth
did I sleep here last night?
Right, now I remember.
Han Wool?
Do Han Wool?
Maybe he went
to the convenience store.
(Buk-boogie)
Hey.
Where's your dad?
(Buk-boogie)
Is this password-protected?
Yes, I knew it.
It's not like
he has anything to hide.
What's with all these photos?
Why does he have this?
Could this be the original?
What...
Hold on.
Do Han Wool...
Where is it?
It's not here. Why isn't it here?
It's not in his closet!
Why?
Where are you right now?
(Where are you right now?)
(Currently online)
Han Si Han?
I have something to say...
regarding the online post
associated with this photo.
Meet me at 11 a.m. tomorrow...
under the big tree at Changrim Park.
(Where are you right now?)
Well,
is this direct message true?
Is Du Ah really the girl
that's dating...
three guys at once?
I didn't send the message.
Gosh. I'm not getting any replies.
Yes.
I also think we'd be better off
just as friends.
If we start dating each other,
we might fight and break up.
And I don't like that.
Let's just continue to be friends
like we have been all this time.
I'm okay.
Love and hatred.
When love meets a sense of betrayal,
it turns into resentment.
So Du Ah admitted that
she was seeing the three of us.
And she thinks one of us
wrote that post?
That's it. Right?
Yes.
Based on what?
It has to be one of you guys...
because the person who posted that
has recently been inside her house.
Where are you going?
I don't understand
why I should stay.
I see. So it was you?
Don't talk nonsense.
I just found out about it.
- You know what?
- Get your hands off me.
- Hey.
- Just sit down.
Tell me the truth. You three had
no idea about that post?
Of course, not!
An online community forum?
Who does that? It's so petty.
Fine. Let's say
one of us found out.
Why would anyone post that there?
It's like disgracing yourself.
You might not know this
because you're young.
If you post anything on that forum,
it only takes seconds...
for everyone at school to find out.
Right. Why would we post
something like that?
- Do you have evidence?
- First,
let's check the facts.
What's your relationship with her?
My relationship with her?
Well...
Let's do it by a show of hands.
Raise your hand
if you held her hand.
My goodness.
We're not some five-year-olds.
What is this?
Darn it.
First base, anyone?
Beyond first base?
Did you sleep with her?
You didn't?
Hey!
What did you just say?
"Hey"? How dare you talk to me
like that? You jerk.
There are some things
you should just keep to yourself.
Gosh. Do you want to
duke it out, pretty boy?
- Gosh. Do you think you can fight?
- You jerk!
- Come here. Fine. Let's do it.
- Sure. Go ahead.
- How many times?
- Gosh.
How many times did you do it?
- Why does that matter now?
Wait a minute. Yes, it does matter.
You only kissed her a few times.
That's not a serious relationship.
I don't think she was serious
with you two. Aren't I right?
Hey.
What about you? Having sex doesn't
mean it was a serious relationship.
You were just friends with benefits.
- What? Friends with benefits?
- Hey.
- Were you there?
How do you know
it wasn't more than just sex?
- Hey, were you there?
- He's guilty.
He's overreacting
because he's guilty.
He was just some warm body
she had sex with.
She didn't see him as a real...
Hey, what are you doing?
- Stop that.
- Stay out of it.
Come on.
Geez.
- Hey, let go of me.
- Hey.
- Hey!
- You, come here.
Gosh.
To me, Du Ah was...
a woman who had so much respect
from me before my girlfriend.
And we were perfect for each other.
We had the same styles, habits,
palate, and everything.
We saw eye to eye on everything.
I was a year younger than her,
but she always respected me.
Same here.
I didn't feel any age gap with her.
We were truly equal
in our relationship.
Since I wanted a serious
long-term relationship with her,
I didn't sleep with her right away.
Waiting has nothing to do with
cherishing her.
If you love someone, don't you want
to touch her and make love to her?
(Du Ah)
Hey, stop crying.
Du Ah.
Who on earth are you?
What?
No matter how hard I tried to think,
or understand what you did,
I don't get it.
Why did you do it?
It was you of all people.
Why did you post my photos...
and write something like that
on that forum?
Please make me understand
why you did it.
Calm down. And say that again.
What are you talking about?
Do you think I posted it?
That's my tablet PC.
Check what's in the gallery
on your tablet PC.
These photos...
Why are they in my tablet PC?
Are you asking me that?
I really didn't know
why these photos...
Hold on.
No.
No. This is a misunderstanding.
I really didn't know about this.
I think the photos
I have in my phone...
got synced to my tablet PC.
Why did you do it?
Why are you asking me that?
There's no way
I would do something like that.
I'm telling the truth. Listen.
I just found out that
I had these photos in my phone.
I found out because
you pointed it out.
You know that
I sometimes take photos...
because I accidentally
tap the wrong buttons.
Then, where were you just now?
Just now?
I was with them just now.
The three guys you were dating.
Why would you meet those three?
There's not much time left.
- We must sort this out.
- Without telling me?
You wouldn't have told me
if I hadn't asked, would you?
You're doing this...
and you want me to trust you?
I didn't tell you first
in case you get the wrong idea.
When I figured out
which of them did this,
I was going to tell you then.
So which of the three was it?
I don't know.
Maybe finding the culprit
wasn't your goal at all.
Not only did you make that post,
but you wanted to...
meet the three guys
and ruin my messy relationships.
What are you saying?
- Why would I do that?
- Because you hate me.
Because you think...
I ignore your feelings
and do as I please.
You think I hate you,
so I want to ruin
your relationships with those guys?
Wasn't that the reason you
wrote that post in the first place?
Yes. It's true that I resent you.
How could you do this to me?
I asked if you broke up with me
just to do this.
I was serious.
When this happened,
you first suspected
those three guys.
You nonchalantly dated
three guys at the same time,
and suspected them
as soon as something happened.
I resented you for leaving me
just to do something like this.
Are you done talking?
What makes you so special?
I'm not special.
That's why you dumped me.
You did the right thing.
I'm actually
a really selfish piece of trash.
I wished that
you'd suffer as much as I did,
and when I saw what happened to you
after what you did...
Yes.
You had it coming.
That darn post.
It should've been me who wrote it!
Do Han Wool!
Excuse me.
Wasn't that Do Han Wool guy
a bit suspicious?
Could he be the one
who wrote the post?
- I thought so too.
- Isn't he actually...
the one who knows most about Du Ah?
He's obviously
the most likely suspect.
It's possible that all this...
was Do Han Wool's big picture.
- What big picture?
- Let's say that...
- he has feelings for Du Ah.
- Yes.
And he found out that
she's dating three guys.
- Yes.
- How would you ruin that?
You're right.
We shouldn't just
sit back and watch.
The three of us
should get together for a chat.
Sure.
What's his name? Sang Woo?
Where'd he go?
He's over there.
What are you doing?
Is that alcohol? My gosh.
Give me that.
Let's have a real drink. It's okay.
Let's go and have our chat.
I resented you for leaving me
just to do something like this.
I'm not special.
That's why you dumped me.
What a jerk.
What's going on?
We are victims.
We're bleeding a gruesome amount.
We're victims.
Yes.
How could she do this to us?
Why are you crying again?
That's enough!
Yes. Let's get together.
We must think of
our pride now at least.
None of us are to see
Nam Du Ah again.
- Yes!
- Let's do that.
Let's ditch her. Delete her number.
Delete her number.
Don't call her.
And don't take her calls.
- Delete it.
I deleted it!
- You deleted it!
- You deleted it.
Let's cheer each other on.
1, 2, 3.
- Let's do this!
- Let's have a drink.
- What's this?
(Du Ah)
Don't do it.
Of course, I won't take it.
- I'm a man.
- Yes, you are.
(Du Ah)
Am I your second choice
or something?
Forget it.
It's an alarm.
Should we order more alcohol?
- Ma'am!
- Hold back.
Come on. Let's not do this.
We should not let Du Ah control us!
We can't go down like this.
Why won't anyone pick up?
Now I can't find out who posted it.
I have just one day left.
(The double life of
a class 2021 history major)
No. Don't give up.
Like Do Han Wool said,
I should contact
the forum moderator.
I'm hungry.
I didn't eat anything all day.
[Kocowa Ver] MBC E02 'Love Scene Number'
"Friends or Lovers"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
What a jerk.
Why do you always look at my
tablet PC without my permission?
It's mine, you know.
You never keep it locked,
and you always put it wherever.
So I kind of thought of it as mine.
That's right. Han Wool never
locked his tablet PC.
What if someone knew it was his,
found my photo in there
either by coincidence or on purpose,
and sent it to his or her
cell phone?
(Accept)
Yes, that's totally plausible.
(October 19, 2020,
Revelation D-Day)
Why didn't I think of this?
- Du Ah.
- Let me see your tablet PC.
What? Okay.
Where's the photo?
October 8, 4 p.m.
Yes, my memory was right.
- Hey, hurry up.
- I'm out.
The day Han Wool came over
to my house.
- Let me go to the bathroom.
- My gosh, come on.
Then it happened four days
after that day.
Did you show your tablet PC
to anyone...
between October 9
and October 12, 7 p.m.?
Did anyone look through
your tablet PC?
Wait a second.
Did you take it to school
or leave it anywhere?
Think about it carefully.
I know you had it with you
over the weekend.
Friday. What about on Friday?
I only had one class, but it got
canceled, so I stayed home.
What about Monday?
I went to school that day
because I had a team meeting.
Did you go somewhere
without your tablet PC...
during the team meeting?
Think about it carefully.
That's when it happened.
That's the only time anyone could've
stolen that photo from you.
I remember going to the bathroom
with Jun Su.
And you didn't take
your tablet PC with you?
No.
How many people were on your team?
Three in total including myself.
Lee Ju Yeon?
What did you say?
But what are you going to do
after you find out?
Just tell me.
I'll deal with it on my own.
It might not be her.
And even if it is,
don't deal with it on your own.
Han Wool.
Lee Ju Yeon.
She studies the same major as you.
Same major as me?
I'm off now.
Du Ah.
About what I said earlier...
I was a bit too harsh.
I'm sorry.
Was it all a lie?
You meant every word you said,
so you don't need to be sorry.
I'm so honored
that I got to interview you.
I'm a huge fan.
I really loved the lecture
you did last time.
Another student was supposed
to interview me,
but she suddenly had to deal
with a personal problem.
By any chance,
are you talking about Nam Du Ah?
Oh, right. You guys study
the same major.
Did something happen to her?
I can't tell you specifically.
But I heard she's getting ready
to sue someone...
because that person uploaded
her personal life online.
Did someone say
something false about her?
Well, I wouldn't say it was
completely false.
But even if it's true, she can still
sue that person for defamation.
She shouldn't have done anything
to get her in that position.
Why would she file a lawsuit
when she's the one at fault?
Why do assailants always have
the same kind of argument?
What?
How did you...
How did I know it was you?
The photo.
The photo you sent
from Han Wool's tablet PC.
That was the key evidence.
- "Who's the culprit?"
- Then our team should...
"Who stole that photo
and uploaded a post online?"
The source was the tablet PC.
The tablet PC was left unattended
on Monday during the team meeting.
- Ju Yeon.
- That left me with two suspects.
His teammates, Hong Jun Su
and Lee Ju Yeon.
Let's go to the bathroom.
I'm not sure if you meant bad
from the very beginning.
At first, you could've done it
out of curiosity.
You looked through his tablet PC
since it wasn't locked,
and you happened to find
a photo of me in there.
Then you sent it to your cell phone.
You could've done all that
impulsively.
But three days later,
you used that photo
to upload a post online.
And that wasn't you
being impulsive or curious.
You did it out of malice.
You thought it was safe since that
photo was from Han Wool's tablet PC.
Then you trimmed the photo
and uploaded it...
so it'd be hard to recognize
who it was.
And you were careful
with what you wrote...
so that it wouldn't get you
in any legal trouble.
If anything went south,
you were going to frame Han Wool.
You minimized the possibility
of your getting in danger,
and at the same time, you managed
to attack me very successfully.
Do you have nothing better to do?
- Hey.
- Why did you bother to do all that?
And...
how did you know
that I was dating three guys?
You want to know why I did it?
You think everyone is a joke,
don't you?
You look down on everyone.
You don't treat people
as human beings.
You think of them like tools
or nice scenery.
That's why you didn't even think
it was necessary to hide it.
It was so obvious.
The guys are dumb
to have gotten fooled.
There wasn't a grand motivation
behind what I did.
I just don't like you. That's why.
Girls like you are the reason why
people badmouth women.
You go around dating anyone.
You're so easy
and have no morals or ethics...
Gosh, I'm sorry.
I couldn't bear to hear what was
coming out of your mouth.
- Hey!
- What do you mean I'm easy?
I'm not easy at all.
I don't date just anyone.
I picked my guys. They just
happened to be more than one.
- That kind of attitude is...
- But...
how is that the reason why
women get badmouthed?
If you think I did something wrong,
you should badmouth me.
If people blame my actions
on my gender,
that only shows how uneducated
they are.
Girls like you are the problem,
not me.
Girls like you make
a ridiculous generalization like...
"Women are their own enemies."
And you conveniently give
an excuse to some fools.
If you don't like how I behave,
just say it to my face.
And if you don't want to face me,
just badmouth me to your friends.
What you did was a foul play...
because you knew
that the method you chose...
was the most humiliating way
to attack me as a fellow woman.
And that's what you were going for.
You are so annoying.
Yes. So what?
You're so irritating.
It would've been nice
if this was the end of it.
But this is unfortunate.
Pardon?
Your photo got posted, after all.
("The Identity of the Double-Life
Sexy Brainstorm Revealed")
These jerks.
I should have talked
with everyone from the get-go.
If I had done that...
- "Identity of the Double-Life..."
- "Sexy Brainstorm Revealed".
This lame post wouldn't
have been up in the first place.
Did you think I wouldn't know?
Or did you do this on purpose?
Every sentence in this post
is poorly constructed and immature.
This is quite embarrassing
to read this, Da Ham.
"She was..."
"a coldhearted woman,
unable to love anyone by nature."
"Coldhearted"?
(Cool-hearted)
"She exploited
men's fatefulness for her."
"Cool-hearted"? It's "coldhearted".
You knew what that meant
when you typed it, right?
It means I'm a cold person.
- Listen...
- Whenever you misspelled words,
it was such a turn-off.
Did you know that?
Oh, right. Si Han,
you provided the photo.
Did you think I wouldn't know
it came from you?
DA? Du Ah's Folder?
You saved every single photo
I posted on my social media.
I posted the photos
but deleted them right away.
And you're the only one
who would save them.
Of course. Sang Woo, you were
the one who came up...
with the idea, right?
Du Ah is planning to go to
a graduate school next year.
- Let's write that.
- Graduate school.
And among the three of you,
you were the only one...
who knew I was preparing
to attend a graduate school.
All of you were sloppy
with the post.
Then, did you call us here,
so you can tell us that?
You lied. You said
you wanted to see us.
I didn't want to "see" you
in a good way.
What did you expect?
Now that you know
we were behind that,
- you called us here, so...
- We're breaking up.
How can I be in a relationship
with guys who exposed me like this?
How could you break up
with us in a group?
Efficiency isn't the key here.
You should know
there are etiquettes in breakups.
Don't expect any etiquettes from
a girl who dates three guys at once.
Were we even in a relationship?
Do you think you can just toy
with people's hearts?
Which one of us dated you first?
Why does that matter now?
No.
After all we've been through,
we deserve to know the truth.
Will that help you
put an end to this?
Well, we want to hear
your answer first.
Number 1, number 2, and number 3.
Why did you end up
dating three guys at once?
Because I was dating three of you
at once, we never got into fights.
That's why our relationships
were good.
My expectations from you
were within your capacities.
What was out of my capacities?
Well, do I have to
spell it out for you?
You must.
I believe relationships require
etiquettes and protocols.
"Etiquettes and protocols"?
You shouldn't deceive
or betray your partner...
out of your consideration for them.
That's basic etiquette.
Just like we started dating
through communication and agreement,
breakups should follow
the same protocol.
That's what you need to do for us.
So you need me to follow
the protocol now, right?
I need to explain to you
why I chose this kind of method.
Yes. You must explain it to us.
Darn it. I didn't want to
talk about this.
Having a guy who had
a crush on me for a year...
is so valuable...
because he makes me think
that I'm a good woman.
He makes me feel better.
But when I wanted to rely on someone
and needed help,
he couldn't do that for me.
Not at all.
So I satisfied
that part of my life...
by dating a mature man...
whom I could rely on
and ask for help.
But unfortunately, I wasn't
sexually attracted to him at all.
And the third guy was able to
satisfy my sexual needs.
Of course.
As for the lacking qualities...
of the third guy,
the other two guys...
definitely filled in for him.
How could you use my feelings
to boost your ego?
A mature man is still a man!
I have needs too!
You don't think you can talk to me?
Have you ever tried to talk to me
other than sleeping with me?
Hey, why aren't you
answering your phone?
What is this about?
I don't want you to be shocked.
Like the culprit warned you,
there was a post
on the online community forum.
I know.
- You know?
- Yes.
But the writing seemed
a bit different. It's weird.
I think...
Do you have anyone in mind?
The three of them are inside.
- Who?
- The writers behind the post.
Han Si Han, Yeon Sang Woo,
and Yoo Da Ham.
- What?
- Let's talk later. Bye.
Hey. You can't just go in like that.
Are you in trouble now?
I called them here.
So I can break up with all of them
like you suggested.
- Break up with them?
- You told me to stop all this.
You wanted me to break up
with all of them.
This all worked out.
I can't date guys
who exposed me like that.
So you called all of them here?
Yes. That's the easiest way
to deal with this.
Why do you think
they wrote a post like that?
Why?
So you can say
you should've written that yourself?
Hey.
Why do you keep acting
like the victim?
I didn't leave you.
If you were so hurt by our breakup,
you shouldn't have been my friend.
You didn't have to see me.
If you hated me that much,
why did you stay friends with me?
How could I not see you?
I wouldn't be able to
live without you.
After that incident
the day before my enlistment,
you were the one who went
radio silent at me.
I called you right before
I had to enter my boot camp.
I left voice messages at
the payphone, but you never called.
And you wanted to stay friends
when I got out on my first leave.
As if nothing happened.
I couldn't live without you.
And to stay by your side, being
your friend was the only option.
What other choice did I have?
"Partners benefit
equally from the relationship"?
People you've
exchanged benefits with...
made posts like that.
Is that your value of love?
Let me ask just one thing.
Have you ever loved anyone?
Du Ah, are you free?
That post. About the girl
in the class of 2021.
It's you, right?
What do you mean?
Stop pretending.
I could tell right away
from the photo.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
I'm not trying to
rebuke or criticize you...
for what you did.
If you're already dating three guys,
do you think
you could squeeze me in?
I don't go around spreading gossip.
I'd always had feelings for you...
for a while now.
You really know nothing about women.
There's no way
you can get a woman to date you...
by starting a conversation
with blackmail and slander.
If you wish to win her over,
put in some effort.
What does she like,
what is she interested in?
What could you do to please her?
At least try to figure that out.
You didn't even give me
a chance to try.
Trying to win that opportunity
is where the work begins.
No one is left now.
Perhaps there was no one
from the very start.
That's fine. You're 23 years old.
You can try this and that
and every kind of relationship.
You can still bounce back.
It's easy to recover.
But then you could get
badly burned and give up altogether.
But what's wrong with that?
That's life too.
The whole process
is the history of dating.
Is it?
It's okay.
They say that loving yourself...
is a romance that lasts a lifetime.
Ditch everything else
and love yourself.
Do you know what your tragedy is?
You think too much.
You think you're so smart,
you use your brain too much.
While others think 2 steps ahead,
you think 3, 4 steps ahead.
I don't torture my brain on purpose.
It just works that way.
Anyway, there's a certain timing...
when you must be
especially mindless.
When is that?
When you're having sex.
I should be mindless
when I'm doing it?
Sex should be just that. Sex.
Don't give it any more meaning.
The moment
you crossed the line with a friend,
Nam Du Ah got locked up
in this fence.
"Can I handle these emotions?"
Your heart puts on the brakes.
The brakes.
When that man
suddenly said he loves you.
What did you think then?
Everything in life has a timing.
Timing can bring people together,
but it can also distance people.
I'll write to you every day.
Okay.
Take care.
No.
I won't write.
Don't join the army.
If you join the army,
who am I to eat with,
watch movies with,
and hang out with?
I have no friends.
I'll visit you often.
No.
Can you just not go?
We were closer than anyone,
and the best of friends.
The reason
our relationship changed...
was that Han Wool enlisted.
I love you.
Just once, before he enlisted,
That was our first and last time.
I couldn't believe in love.
Rather than ruin our friendship
with an imperfect affection,
I thought it was best
we remain as friends.
I decided from my own perspective.
Han Wool.
Let's go inside. Let's talk inside.
Did you drink?
With whom?
Just someone.
I'm sorry.
For what?
This wouldn't have happened...
if I had been more careful
with my tablet PC.
I know it's too late,
but I feel like I should apologize.
And?
I'm also sorry for
always apologizing...
after speaking my mind out loud.
And?
I'm also sorry for
being so emotional with you...
when you were the one
having the hardest time.
It's okay.
It's all in the past now.
But still,
how could you not contact me
for a whole week?
I'm sorry for that too.
I'd also like to apologize.
Because you were always
so nice to me,
I let myself cross the line.
I just thought you'd still
be there for me...
no matter how mean I was to you.
I shouldn't have done that.
No, you were nothing like that.
But Han Wool.
You should be apologizing to me
about something else, you know.
What?
The day before you went to the army,
you told me you loved me
all of a sudden.
It's true that I was confused.
When I heard that you were
suddenly going to go to the army,
I found myself feeling peculiar.
I kept wondering...
why I was feeling that way.
Especially on the very last day.
But that's when you suddenly
told me you loved me.
I love you.
I was flustered.
I couldn't give you an answer,
but you seemed so resolute about it.
And that's why it scared me.
You know I tend to think too much.
I don't think I was brave enough...
to take our relationship
to another level.
But...
after I ran away from you,
I felt lonely.
You know you're my only friend.
After I ran away from
my only friend, schoolmate,
and the only guy...
I felt a connection with,
I suddenly felt so lost.
That's why I tried
to come up with a way...
to fill your space.
And that's why you dated
those three guys?
- Yes.
- You're stupid.
It's impossible
to fill my space.
Whatever.
Du Ah.
Then how about now?
What?
I'm right here next to you.
You don't need those guys
to replace me anymore.
Will you let me...
stay beside you again?
Han Wool.
Yes?
I think there's an expiry date...
for all relationships.
You're so precious to me.
I love you and care for you so much.
But I think that's because
we're friends.
We're so perfect as friends.
And I don't...
want to ruin what we have.
You think we're perfect as friends?
Just be honest with me.
Whether I remain as a friend
or your boyfriend,
do you feel like
you can live without me now?
I should go.
I'm sorry.
You'll be fine.
My gosh.
Friends or lovers.
Why was I so caught up
with the labels...
that determined relationships?
All the leaves are brown
And the sky is gray
I've been for a walk
On a winter's day
I'd be safe and warm
Come on.
Don't spill food when you eat!
- Brat.
- "Brat"?
Am I your brat?
I'm turning. Hey, I'm turning.
Buk-boogie. Hey, Buk-boogie.
On me?
Oh, my! I think it likes me.
I didn't know how to love him.
But I realized that
if I wanted him by my side...
and didn't want to lose him,
I should have been honest.
I should have been honest
when I needed to be honest.
And I realized that too late.
(Present)
I'm sure a coincidence
will bring us together again.
That fool.
(Buk-boogie)
Hey.
All you do is sleep, you know?
Hello?
Is this Do Han Wool?
(Restricted number)
Yes, this is he.
I have a package for you.
Du Ah.
(Bomb)
"Bomb"?
This is so typical of Du Ah.
(Ddo-boogie)
"Ddo-boogie".
There are no coincidences
in the world, you fool.
Hey, Du Ah.
Hello.
(Number 23 is over!)
(Love Scene Number)