Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent Season 1
Episode 9
When does Shi Lan Ke School
have something to do
with Martial Soul Hall?
Shi Lan Ke School
has no relation with them at all.
Is Su Yun Tao from
Martial Soul Hall there too?
Is he the one you want to meet?
Yes.
Yesterday, I stalked him.
I saw him
entered the City Main Office
of Suo Tuo City.
And now the city
is full of this notice.
They have admitted
Shi Lan Ke School's
teaching qualification?
Really?
I heard that Governor
always wants to dominate
Shi Lan Ke School.
However, your Headmaster rejected it.
That's true.
Governor decided
to target the school,
but he changed his mind suddenly.
And now the officer of
Martial Soul Hall appears.
This means that
Governor is oppressed by
Martial Soul Hall.
That's why he has to admit
the status of the school.
But Su Yun Tao is just an officer.
Is he able to influence
Governor's decision?
He is the direct disciple
of the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
His identity is prestigious.
The chief of Martial Soul Hall?
The invincible of Douluo Continent?
Why does he approach Headmaster?
Our Headmaster
is poor and ugly.
What's his intention then?
Are Su Yun Tao and Hu Lie Na
still in school?
When we went out just now,
Su Yun Tao has left.
Perhaps Hu Lie Na still stays.
I'm still worried.
Bring me to the school.
I want to see your Headmaster.
Sure.
Master,
it's okay for you
to meet with Headmaster.
However, his behaviour
is quite strange.
You have to get prepared.
Headmaster.
Someone is here to see you.
I've been looking for you
over the years,
yet I couldn't find you.
Where have you been?
Why are you looking for me?
To return me the money?
Regarding this matter,
don't say in front of them.
Gang.
Gang?
Since Golden Iron Triangle
has disbanded,
where have you been?
I was in Nuoding School,
working as a guest teacher
without any contribution.
But for this time,
I come here to send my disciple Tang San
and his sister, Wu for admission.
Is Tang San your disciple?
Why are you willing to send him here?
Because I have trust in you.
These two kids are talented.
Why didn't you inform me
before sending them here?
I hope that
they could enter into this school
with their ability.
You seem to have great confidence
in them.
Brother,
I have something to tell you.
Well.
Come to my place.
You all go and look for
those villagers
who need to do house maintenance
and help them out.
Remember to collect cash
when you finish that.
Issue a receipt
if they don't have cash.
Don't worry. I'll handle it.
Gang, come.
I've missed you so much.
Let's go.
Come.
Gang?
Come, Gang.
Please come in.
This is where I live.
It looks kind of shabby,
but it's a lovely place.
Welcome in.
Sure.
Here.
Have a seat.
Thank you, brother.
I heard that you insisted
to run the school by yourself.
You only accept kids
that pass your test.
And they have become
great Soul Masters.
I do my best to teach them.
However, it's hard to keep
the school going.
I have to rely on the village
for the school
and help them with cleaning jobs
to square away teaching funds.
I can see that
they are the last batch of the school.
Well, stop complaining that you're poor.
To be honest, I'm somehow
envious of you.
Envious of your free life
and establishing an independent school.
Envious of me?
Stay here then.
Tang San and Wu wants to go to the city.
They are waiting for me.
I'll leave now.
Little brat.
What happened?
Ou Si Ke.
Get out of here. Don't eavesdrop.
Don't be angry.
I just want to reconfirm
the relationship between your school
and Martial Soul Hall.
You're asking about
the new girl from Martial Soul Hall,
right?
She came here for Dai Mu Bai.
Su Yun Tao brought her here.
He is the one who has awoken Tang San's
Martial Soul.
I heard that he is
the disciple of Bi Bi Dong,
the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
Sending a girl to Shi Lan Ke School
by himself,
is this normal?
Please be rest assured.
Shi Lan Ke School and Martial Soul Hall
have no relation.
It's the same with other powers.
As for this admission test,
besides Hu Lie Na,
there's also a girl
who came with a purpose.
Dai Mu Bai
is tall, composed like a nobleman
and he has strong strength.
He's popular in Suo Tuo City.
It has nothing to be surprised that
many girls go after him.
It's good to be young.
As for the older men,
they have only their speeches.
Don't judge the book
by its cover.
So?
You should have rejected those from
Martial Soul Hall to stay here.
I only take her as an observer.
Don't worry.
Besides,
she has helped the school a lot.
Her identity in Martial Soul Hall
is vague.
This happens to Tang San too.
But the school couldn't reject
any students
for this reason.
I'll stay.
In Shi Lan Ke School?
Don't you need a teacher?
My school is very poor.
I can do it for free.
I don't take advantage of others.
Do you want me to beg you?
You're doing this for the sake
of Tang San?
I need to observe the girl.
Make sure that
she won't lead trouble to Tang San.
I've never seen you
care about someone like this.
It never happens before.
He had kowtowed to me
and acknowledged me as his teacher.
I have to be responsible for him.
Besides, I've promised his father
to take care of him.
His father?
Who is it?
It's fine.
It's good to keep away
from secrets.
As long as you promise
to teach for free,
I won't ask anymore.
Didn't you say that
you don't take advantage of others?
You're not like others.
Sit down.
Drink some water.
How is it?
How many Soul Rings have you obtained
all these years?
I still remain at two.
That's impossible.
The fist I hit on you just now
was a test.
Yet it's tough.
You can't take it with Double Soul Rings.
Are you still studying
the Martial Soul Theory?
Operation means to enhance strength,
the most suitable environment
to cultivate Soul Power...
It looks boring.
Everyone is here?
Let me introduce a new teacher to you.
This is my bosom friend of many years.
He is also the master of
the Martial Soul Theory.
You can call him...
Call me Master.
From now onwards,
Master will be teaching you all
the Martial Soul Theory.
I hope that you could learn from him.
Don't disgrace our school.
Yes.
We have a new observer this year.
Introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Hu Lie Na.
I'm from Martial Soul Hall.
Well.
That's all for the introduction.
Our admission has officially
accomplished.
Go and prepare yourself.
Our class will start tomorrow.
Please come in.
Hurry up.
This is the male dorm.
Brother Dai's bed.
And this is mine.
Choose your bed from the rest.
By the way, where does Wu live?
Girls dorm is beside here.
But the school stipulates that
male students are not allowed
to disturb female students.
Got it. I'll sleep here.
Sure.
Besides,
I really can't believe that
Headmaster has
such a handsome and charming friend.
Our Headmaster is so stingy.
I've never seen
any of his friends since I was young.
Since you were young?
He is my foster father.
Back then, he would fly me to the sky
during my birthday.
He would bring me everywhere
I wanted to go
and show me the world.
Since then,
I've decided
to bring him to any places
he wants to go
when I have the strength.
However, when my Martial Soul awakened,
I realized that we have
different Martial Souls.
And then I knew that he fostered me.
What's your Martial Soul?
Can you fly too?
My...
It sure can fly
with the wings of imagination.
Am I right?
Forget about Headmaster.
Let's talk about Master.
How many Soul Rings does he possess?
Seven or eight?
Does he have nine instead?
Does this really matter?
Of course.
Our Headmaster is the Soul Saint
with seven Soul Rings.
How about Master?
He only has two Soul Rings.
What?
Two Soul Rings?
Asking a Soul Master with two Soul Rings
to teach us?
What's wrong with Headmaster?
Numbers of Soul Ring
couldn't decide one's strength.
If that's the case,
tell me then.
What could decide one's strength?
The theory teacher is studying
is the most powerful one
on Douluo Continent.
So, were those tricks you used to fight
with Mr. Zhao
also taught by him?
No.
What did he teach then?
Theory.
Theory?
The reason I came to Shi Lan Ke School
is to learn to become stronger,
not for theory study.
In my opinion,
it's not enough for one
to merely have power.
Without the support of theories,
he will never become
a powerful Soul Master.
Who are you referring to?
Tang San.
Sir?
Master...
Come out.
Old Hei, let me do it.
Thank you.
Brother Dai,
why do you have beef with Tang San?
I don't.
Let me put it in this way.
Why don't you like Tang San?
He is smart.
But at the wrong place.
You're referring
to those tricks he used
when confronted with Mr. Zhao?
Not only that.
After he has won over Mr. Zhao,
there was black smoke emerging from him.
Didn't you find it strange?
No.
As long as he won, right?
But I don't want my partner
to win the fight
with heretic means.
I think Tang San is quite nice though.
Last time, he saved me
with all his might
when I was about to die.
I can see he's righteous.
You're so naive.
How could you trust him
with small favours?
Tang San
has so many things that
I can't see through.
Well, time will tell.
You'll understand him later.
Brother,
our class starts tomorrow.
Do you want to hang around in the city?
I'm not going. Go yourself.
Let's go.
Stop working.
Let's go together.
Don't isolate yourself.
Go with me.
Let's hang out.
Let's go.
Stop being angry.
Go.
Tang San?
Tang San.
I've no idea that you know this.
My dad taught me.
He said this can help with my stamina.
When I was in Nuoding School,
I used to forge iron to make a living.
Brother Dai...
Tang San, are you sure
you want to work here?
Don't worry, Sir.
I've thought it over.
I could train my stamina
with forging the iron.
It won't affect my study.
Well.
But, once I found that
you're lagging behind,
I won't allow you to do this again.
Sure.
Old granny, what are you doing?
Eighty Gold Soul Coins are big bucks.
I can't owe you this.
There is a famine in the village.
If it wasn't you who helped us,
perhaps we would die of hunger.
Your favour is too big for us.
Don't thank me.
It's just a small deal. I mean it.
We'll find all means
to return the money to you.
You don't have
to return the money though.
Don't mention it again.
No way.
This food is enough.
We'll definitely find ways
to repay you.
I've never thought that
he used the admission fee
to help the needy.
One of
the Ten Core Competing Power of Martial Soul
that I've researched and proposed
is the Theory of Martial Soul Mimicry.
Soul Master with Plant Branch Martial Soul
is not necessary to absorb
Soul Ring from
Plant Branch Soul Beast.
As for those with Beast Soul...
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Under certain conditions,
both of them can combine.
Theoretically,
the more the Soul Ring,
the stronger the strength.
It's said that the possessor
of ten Soul Rings
will become an immortal.
Headmaster.
You're back?
What have you learnt
in these days?
Master taught us about
Ten Core Competing Powers
of Martial Soul.
What are they?
Firstly...
Tell me, Dai Mu Bai.
Say whatever you could recall.
What? You can't remember any of them?
It's impossible to win over rivals
with theory.
Without the conclusion of
pioneers' experience,
perhaps you won't even know
what does Martial Soul mean.
Anyhow, I don't believe in
those theories that haven't been proven.
His theories have been proven.
My Martial Soul is Blue Silver Plant.
Yet I'm able to absorb
the Soul Ring of Thorn Apple Snake.
This is the so-called
Theory of Martial Soul Mimicry.
I would rather believe that
only through hard training
can truly improve myself.
As for the mimicry theory or something,
just let those who need it to learn.
You all may go back.
Headmaster...
Dai...
Don't force him
if he doesn't want to learn.
Everyone has their own choice.
Dai Mu Bai
is too arrogant and confident.
It won't benefit him
if he still behaves like this.
It's because my level is too low.
That's normal for him not to follow me.
I can't let his bad behaviour
goes unchecked.
I've received news just now.
Perhaps this might be an opportunity.
What is it?
Headmaster,
today is our rest day.
Why do you call for us
in this early morning?
Well.
Yesterday,
there was a businessman
who came to seek help.
According to him,
when he was on his way to do business,
he passed by a village.
And he found something strange
happened in the village.
He claimed that
if this can't be settled,
he'll never dare
to take that path again.
Therefore, he entrusted us
to do the investigation.
How much money do you collect from him?
This is not about the monetary matter.
As a Soul Master,
we're responsible to provide help
for those villagers.
You must bear it in your mind.
You're right.
Let's set off now
and try to reach the village
before lunch.
Let's go.
Tang San, how far is it to go?
I'm exhausted.
It seems it may take some more time.
Do you want me to carry you?
Sure.
Up.
What's wrong? You don't want it?
It's fine. No need.
Tang San.
Did Master tell you anything before?
Nope.
I was planning to go working
this afternoon.
Yet I can't go now.
Working?
I forge iron to make a living.
Brother Dai and I saw you that day.
Ou Si Ke,
did Headmaster
always accept
this kind of task to help others with chores?
Not always.
But, Headmaster did mention that
we have to grow from the battle.
What is our battle?
Our battle is
to help others to do cleaning chores.
I couldn't know
what he's thinking about.
Is this task
part of the battle?
I've no idea.
Maybe this is a mysterious course.
Did this happen before?
Shi Lan Ke School
doesn't have fixed schedules.
We'll learn
whatever Headmaster teaches us.
It may seem somewhat random.
But the outcome is extremely useful.
This must be the wisdom of Headmaster.
You seem to admire Headmaster a lot.
Of course.
Headmaster is the one who raised me
and teach me how to use Martial Soul.
Although he's kind of stingy,
however, he's doing it for the sake
of the school.
In this world,
Headmaster
is the one I most admire.
I can understand you.
I have a great teacher too.
If it wasn't him,
I would die
in the hands of Xiao Chen Yu.
Tang San,
according to the theory of drama,
both of us have similar backgrounds.
I don't think our background
is similar though.
We must be under the same concept.
I don't think so.
You've given me this.
It's a token of our friendship.
- Don't.
- Token of friendship.
Please don't.
This is just a gift,
nothing special.
Tang San.
As long as you're in school,
I have your back.
Why haven't we reached yet?
Everyone,
when we were in school just now,
I've told you
the village ahead of us
has something strange happened.
What is that?
You may have to investigate
the actual situation.
Find your own answer.
This is the first collaboration
you have.
Hopefully, you could trust each other.
Take note of this,
this is also counted as your exam.
The consequence
will impact your results.
Walk till the end,
you'll reach the village.
Aren't you going with us?
This is your task.
Accomplish with your own force.
Sure.
Let's go.
Okay.
The observer is not necessary to join.
I'm willing to be an observer too.
Sure.
I'll burn all your things then.
Headmaster is right.
We must grow from the battle.
I have to grow.
I have to fight.
Wait for me.
I'm willing to go with them.
Mark my words,
you're just an observer.
I know.
I won't trouble them.
Are you really letting them handle all?
You've started to worry about them?
Until now,
I haven't taken in anything.
How am I going to investigate?
Just hang in there.
After entering the village,
follow my instruction.
Why?
Our team will be scattered
without one's instruction?
I mean why should I listen to you?
Because I'm the strongest.
Is it the cocky guy the strongest one?
You can leave if you don't want to.
I'm also part of Shi Lan Ke,
why should I listen to you?
You're eligible only if you defeat me.
Calm down, please.
Aren't we have to trust each other?
Why do you start quarreling now?
What happened?
A small gift for you.
Calm down.
Brother Dai.
Let's move.
What's wrong?
Do you find that
there is lots of chickens
in this village?
Anything wrong?
I used to live in the village back then.
Villagers will keep some
chickens and ducks
and also dogs.
But, there are only chickens
in Nightfire Village.
This...
Does it matter?
I don't think it's strange.
I mean...
Look at the ground.
It's too clean.
So what?
Perhaps it's nothing.
Let's go.
Wu.
This cottage
looks like it has been burnt.
It is all burnt.
Did anyone try to put out the fire?
That's strange.
Look.
The grass around the cottage
remains green.
Yet the cottage is burnt.
It seems like the fire
was blocked inside the cottage
by something.
Therefore, it didn't spread.
If your words are true,
this is fishy.
Brother Dai, what's the situation now?
Let's go and find
the village head first.
I have a sense of impending doom.
Why?
I can't tell.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here,
I'll protect you well.
Let's go.
Come.
Let me do it, sir.
Seek help?
No.
But we've received a distress message
from Nightfire Village.
It's from a businessman who passed by.
He said that in the night,
the village was caught in a big fire.
And there was a black monster
leaped up from the fire
and rushed straight to the village.
I see.
It was just
a normal house fire.
I reckon
the businessman
might not understand what has happened.
And makes you come here.
Well.
I'll treat you to a meal tonight
as my apologies.
I'm sorry
to trouble you all.
Sir,
how about the black monster?
Don't say it.
Nightfire Village
has been standing here for hundred years
calmly,
silently
and steadily.
How could it be a monster here?
Sir,
perhaps you don't know about this?
What do you mean?
I'm the head of this village.
I should know everything.
You're right though.
Sir,
the burnt house you said,
is it located at the entrance there?
Yes.
Sir,
when did it happen?
A few days ago.
Were you there?
I...
I was sleeping at that time.
When I reached there,
the fire has been put out.
Did you realize that
only one cottage was burnt in that area,
and the plants around it
remain in good shape?
It's just like...
Just like there's something
in the cottage
blocking the fire
from spreading out.
Your imagination is kind of rich.
That was because the villagers
put out the fire in time.
Why do you
have so many questions?
Sir...
Sir,
I think
the businessman must have
seen it wrong.
He must be regarding the villagers
who try to put out the fire
as the black monster.
Think about it.
In the windy and pitch-black night,
the fire was raging.
It must have stretched the shadow.
This must be a misunderstanding.
I think that
your words do make sense.
I'll take this as an idea
to write my story.
Your analysis makes sense.
That's that truth.
But, sir...
But, sir.
We came all the way from our school
because of the distress message.
It's hard for us
to go back empty-handed.
He's right, sir.
We can't explain to our Headmaster.
Well...
Sir...
It's fine.
I'm fine.
I...
I don't want to drink anymore.
I know you're kind, right?
You're caring about Nightfire Village.
Well.
I'll still treat you to a meal tonight.
Besides, I'll give all of you
one Gold Soul Coin each.
That's great.
Thank you, sir.
A reward for helping.
Sure.
Tang San, what do you mean?
Headmaster asked us to come
for investigation,
not for cheating money.
I didn't say I quit.
Why did you stop me just now?
Didn't you see that
the village head doesn't want us
to investigate?
If you keep on asking him,
he'll get annoyed
and hinders us from investigating.
That's why you purposely said that
you want to quit investigating.
Let them loose their guard first.
We'll go to other places
to investigate.
This village is indeed strange.
Brother, drink some water.
Tang San, you're smart.
But without the help of
the village head,
how are we going to investigate?
The village is big,
there must be other clues.
We still have time before night falls.
Let's look for
villagers who are willing to help.
Sure.
Okay.
You all go yourself.
I don't want to join.
Whatever.
Set off now.
Let's gather before the sky turns dark.
Sure.
Let's go.
Afterwards, I hope that
you could discuss with me
in advance.
Because I'm the Leader of the team.
Brother Dai,
sometimes it's impossible
to discuss in advance.
We should refine the plan then.
If you always do things
without informing,
the situation will be beyond control.
You've witnessed the situation then.
I don't have...
Stop explaining.
Go now.
No need.
I've got it.
Sir,
during the fire that night,
you were there.
Why did you lie to us?
I've no idea what you're saying.
The villagers told us
the monster is in the village.
They want us to help too.
Who said this?
Tell me.
I want to speak to the person.
It's not important.
Sir,
tell us now.
What was the black image,
which is neither a Soul Beast
nor a beast,
appeared that night?
Sir,
Only if you tell us the truth
can we help you.
That's right.
All right.
That night,
I was there
and
I've witnessed
a black figure
leaped up from the house
and rushed out.
Red eyes in the smoke?
Perhaps it was the blaze.
Why didn't you investigate it?
Villages
are dry places.
It's normal for it to catch fire.
Besides, after that night,
nothing strange had happened.
Furthermore,
if I find someone to investigate,
it will not only consume manpower
and resources
but also cost me a lot of money.
You're right.
Sir,
do you think that
we're cheating your money?
Isn't that true?
Sir,
we're here to help you.
If we can't find the culprit,
we won't take a single cent from you.
Sir,
are there any survivors
from the affected family?
Yes.
It's a kid.
Ma Hong Jun.
Ma Hong Jun?
Where is he now?
He must have suffered a lot
from this accident.
Don't further traumatize him.
Tell me, where is he now?
I...
I've no idea.
Since the accident,
he became weird
and refuse to meet people.
I haven't seen him for days.
How old is he?
Around 15 years old.
How does he look like?
He has a round face and he's short.
He looks adorable too.
Everyone got it now?
Let's spread up to look for Ma Hong Jun.
Bring him back once you find him.
For those timid ones, just stay here.
Sir,
how many chickens are there
in the village?
Chickens?
I've no idea.
Well...
We have many
chickens, chicks,
roosters and hens here.
Were there any casualties in that fire?
Yes.
Ma Hong Jun's father died in the fire.
Has he been buried yet?
Yes.
At the west of the village.
Thank you.
Tang San.
Hold on.
Why did you ask about the chickens?
I'm thinking that
will Ma Hong Jun go to the grave
as he misses his father?
That makes sense.
Go and check it out.
I'll wait for you here.
You're not going with us?
Yes.
I would rather spend my time
writing new scripts.
I don't find it interesting
being a Soul Master.
Only art.
Only art
could be immortal.
Why do you
still stay in Shi Lan Ke School?
I come
to collect ideas for creation.
Let's take you as an example.
Both of you are good materials for me.
Us?
Yes.
For example, you.
You're pretty and adorable.
Why do you come to Shi Lan Ke School?
Why do you choose
to become a Soul Master
regardless of challenges?
What's your reason?
All of these are the contradiction
and conflicts in drama.
Do you know that?
I want to find out
the nature of Martial Soul.
Nature?
That's so profound.
I want to venture into a new path.
What path is that?
I want to find out
could Soul Master obtain Soul Ring
without hunting for Soul Beast?
This...
might be hard.
Over the past thousands of years,
all Soul Masters get upgraded level
through Soul Beast hunting.
But I want to try.
I'll accompany you.
Both of you
can go now.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪