Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent Season 1
Episode 8
I'm not from Shi Lan Ke.
I'm just an inn staff.
I...
To put it simply,
Shi Lan Ke School and I have a history.
Rose Inn helps Shi Lan Ke
organize the admission exam,
which means it's just as guilty.
I have nothing to do with it.
Whoever joins Shi Lan Ke
will be my enemy.
Should we save him?
Is this part of the exam?
You think so?
I know
some might think
this is the admission exam.
Tell me now.
How can I let them know
that I'm serious?
I...
I don't know.
I'll kill you
to prove it.
Come here.
This is your last moment.
At least look dignified.
I'm not one of them.
I have nothing to do with them.
It doesn't look like an exam.
Shi Lan Ke picked this inn.
You only have your bad luck to blame.
Quadruple Soul Rings. Soul Sect.
My vine
can't reach him.
I'll finish my business,
then I'll entertain you two.
Let him go.
Supreme Palm.
Nether Spikes.
Ou Si Ke!
See it now?
This is what happened
when you want to join Shi Lan Ke.
Shi Lan Ke
won't come and protect you.
If you stay,
you'll be my enemy.
Can I quit?
Those who want to quit,
do it now.
Why did you kill him?
He's just a staff.
He's not related to the school.
Bad timing then.
His fate has been decided.
Killing people
doesn't make you stronger.
It only shows that you can't control
yourself.
Audacious kid.
Everyone can leave
but you have to stay.
Are kids nowadays this reckless?
Wu.
Speed can increase power.
First Soul skill.
Acala's Statue.
Wu!
Wu.
Sorry, brother.
I made you worry.
It's my fault.
I couldn't protect you.
I'm sorry.
If forbearance means I'll lose someone,
then even if
I'll die,
I will avenge my sister.
Without using Martial Soul?
What technique did you use?
Again.
This is Gravity Squeeze.
You'd better stay put.
Seven Soul Rings!
He's a Soul Saint.
Brother.
Tang San.
Who are you?
Are you okay, Wu?
No need to continue.
You guys passed.
What do you mean?
This is a test
from Shi Lan Ke.
It tests your ability
and your bravery.
You little freaks all passed.
You kill someone just for a test.
Hey, time's up.
Did you really think that I was dead?
How was my acting?
Come.
Weren't you...
Let me introduce myself again.
I'm Ou Si Ke from
Shi Lan Ke.
Remember me, Ou Si Ke.
How was my acting?
Tell me.
It's almost
real.
You know why?
I studied my character
diligently.
I even gave myself
the role of inn staff.
I came up with his back story,
his manner of speech,
his behaviour,
and the details of his murder.
I pondered over them.
Look.
When I die,
every detail has to be on point.
The detail
is what makes it so real.
Understood?
I don't get it.
It's fine.
When school starts,
we can discuss
about arts.
I'm very...
Ou Si Ke,
stop rambling.
When you were fighting
against Mr. Zhao,
you used two skills.
But they weren't Soul Skills.
What then?
They weren't Soul Skills indeed.
Just some tricks up my sleeve.
Shi Lan Ke
doesn't like dirty tricks.
It's not dirty tricks.
A Martial Soul Battle
without Soul Skill.
Isn't this cheating?
Tang San only has two Soul Rings.
To fight someone with seven Soul Rings,
we needed other strategies.
Martial Soul Battle has to be fair.
He was cheating.
Dai Mu Bai.
The rules say that
if they can defeat me,
they pass the exam.
Tang San did it.
We can't
reject someone just because
we haven't seen his techniques before.
Don't you think?
So,
everyone here now
has passed the exam.
Besides,
the potential
and will power you showed
are freakish.
Excellent.
Dai Mu Bai.
Tell Headmaster that
I'm leaving.
Wait.
Let me introduce to you all.
Mr. Zhao Wu Ji,
one of our earliest
graduates.
He also used to
teach here.
Used to?
Due to the lack of funds,
we can't hire teachers anymore.
But Mr. Zhao
still helps us with the admission exam.
Maybe it's because I look like a villain.
No, not at all.
You have potential.
Work hard.
Shi Lan Ke won't let you down.
Goodbye, sir.
All right. Rest well.
I'll show you the school tomorrow.
Let's go.
I'm not here for enrollment.
I'm here for you, Dai Mu Bai.
Are you afraid of a duel?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Stop.
You can't win.
Purple? Millennium Soul Ring.
Triple Soul Rings. Soul Honour?
I killed a Millennium Supreme Tiger
and obtained the third Soul Ring.
White Tiger Vajra Transformation
will boost my combat power
and defense greatly.
Speed too.
I won't give up.
I will defeat you.
Boring.
Miss, I have an idea.
You already paid up.
You passed the exam too.
Why not study here?
I'm not here for enrollment.
Look,
in school,
we are always together.
You can duel
Dai Mu Bai at any time.
Also, Dai Mu Bai is strong.
What does it mean?
What?
It means Shi Lan Ke School
is good.
When you study here,
you'll defeat him in no time.
That's true.
In that case,
you'll
need to pay again.
But I already paid up.
You paid the registration fee
this afternoon.
You fought Dai Mu Bai
once.
And now, you need to
pay the tuition fee.
After you pay up,
the teacher
will train you.
You'll improve
and defeat him.
No?
Oh...
Rest well.
School tomorrow!
Hey.
How did you hurt Mr. Zhao?
When I saw you lose consciousness,
I lost control of myself.
Everything was out of reflex.
Not using Martial Soul?
But I might have
combined both Xuan Tian Strike
and the Martial Soul.
I didn't expect it to negate
the opponent's Martial Soul.
Xuan Tian Strike?
It's a technique from Xuan Tian Records.
It augments my breath.
Under Xuan Tian Strike's protection,
Mr. Zhao's damage against
my Martial Soul has decreased.
His palm
didn't hurt as much.
Try again, perhaps?
What?
Impossible.
Combining them
makes them repel each other.
Don't try again then.
How did it work that time then?
What exactly is Xuan Tian Strike?
How much loss
do we have to cover this time?
What's up?
You were just watching just now.
So?
It means
it doesn't count.
It's not about money.
You know that, right?
Doesn't the school need funding?
It's not the case.
Bring me to the school tomorrow.
I'll talk to the headmaster.
Headmaster.
The girl who wanted to duel Dai Mu Bai
paid again.
The more the merrier.
Of course.
This
is the money from the girl
who just watched.
She wanted to talk to you.
I feel like
she means trouble.
Careful. We're almost there.
This is Shi Lan Ke.
Miss,
why are you using this for laundry?
This is not an ordinary plank.
This is...
This...
Here.
Shi Lan Ke.
Is this the school?
Yes.
Are they students?
They are...
They are villagers.
She enrolled.
So we take anyone in now?
She passed the exam
and she paid twice.
No reason not to take her in.
Is this village the school?
No,
the school is in the village.
Where's the dorm?
We don't have that.
Careful.
Slow and steady.
Headmaster!
You're the headmaster? Headmaster?
Yes.
I'm the headmaster of Shi Lan Ke,
Lander.
On behalf of Shi Lan Ke's
students and staff,
welcome.
Students and staff?
Other than the freshers,
I only see 3 people.
Our Headmaster is very petty.
You're dead meat.
We're poor.
This is what we have.
We'll tell you more later.
Mu Bai.
See if something
needs to be repaired there.
Bring them over.
Sure.
Come with me.
Repair?
Come.
Repair what?
You stay here.
Dai!
The Hu girl
treats you differently.
You don't know her?
No.
Think harder.
Maybe you forgot.
Headmaster didn't want to take her in.
Then she asked for a private talk.
She said she could help the school.
What can a girl do
to help the school?
Does our school have a problem?
Our biggest problem
is nosy students.
This is directed towards me, isn't it?
So this Hu girl
is coming for me?
But why?
Also,
the way she looks at you
is different.
Perhaps she has met
with Headmaster before?
A private talk...
Maybe
she is Headmaster's
long-lost daughter?
She's back now.
This story is too intriguing.
Quality content, Dai.
Quality content.
In that case,
you should eavesdrop.
I probably should.
I'll see you then.
Ignore him. He's crazy.
I can't believe
the famous Devil's School
hides in a village.
It's not hiding.
The rent here is cheap.
That's because you want to stay neutral.
Hence there are restrictions everywhere.
You know a lot.
Shi Lan Ke School
might be the only neutral school
on Douluo Continent.
Without sponsorship,
you guys are poor.
We're poor
but we're free.
I heard
the governor of Suo Tuo City
wants to cancel your school license.
He'll act soon.
Surely you want to know
how I got this information.
I know who you are.
Come with me.
No.
Wait, yes.
But...
Brother Ou.
We want to go back to town.
Can you be our guide?
Ou Si Ke will do.
We'll leave soon.
What are you looking at?
This Hu girl
went in with Headmaster.
You're stalking Headmaster?
Why are you bothered by it?
I'm just curious.
An artist draws inspiration
from his life.
Okay?
I need to stay
curious and excited.
A strong curiosity towards life
compels me to study
any
novelties that I encounter.
Look!
Over there.
Anything can happen
there.
My imagination can even
make a spectacle out of it.
When I write,
it will flow naturally.
Well, if it's purely fictional,
isn't that lying then?
It's all gibberish.
You don't understand.
People nowadays
don't want to believe
anything real.
They prefer
something dramatic.
This is the charm of art.
Got it?
I tell him...
Then...
When I'm composing,
I'm more of a lone wolf.
I'll tell you once I'm done.
What is he talking about?
Maybe he doesn't want to be disturbed.
Let's go somewhere.
We can wait.
Since you're waiting,
check this out.
Hurry up.
What is this?
My heart and soul.
Careful.
Don't come here, Headmaster.
Please.
This guy has been following you.
In fact, he's been protecting you.
Right?
What did you do to him?
Nothing.
He's just immobilized.
If I'm not mistaken,
he's an officer
from Martial Soul Hall. Like you, right?
Yes.
So?
Martial Soul Hall likes my school now?
Martial Soul Hall
has nothing to do with it.
It's a personal matter.
Someone from Martial Soul Hall
wants to join another school?
I remember you said
Shi Lan Ke welcomes everyone.
Except for Martial Soul Hall.
The governor of Suo Tuo City wants
to revoke your school license.
I can help.
Are you threatening me?
You're mistaken.
It's a favor.
In exchange for your enrollment?
I'll audit.
I won't be a student.
Don't worry.
Audit?
Yes.
I will also pay
for auditing.
I know
the school needs funding.
Martial Soul Hall
has the best resource on Douluo Continent.
Why do you wish to join Shi Lan Ke?
For Dai Mu Bai.
Dai Mu Bai?
Are you two related?
Not at all.
We might be in the future.
You're not allowed to recruit
for Martial Soul Hall.
I swear not to.
You'll only audit. No lectures for you.
Thanks, Headmaster.
He's not allowed to enter the school.
As you wish.
Don't worry.
The school is safe.
Headmaster will protect me.
I will stay in Suo Tuo City.
Find me if anything.
An officer takes orders from you.
Where does that guy come from?
It's him.
Do you know him?
He's Su Yun Tao,
an officer from Martial Soul Hall.
He helped me to
awaken my Martial Soul.
Martial Soul Hall?
This is complicated.
My play.
How is it?
Do you like it?
This...
Yes, this.
I wrote this.
My biggest dream
is to be
an actor in a circus,
performing the play I wrote.
I will bring art
to every corner of Douluo Continent.
When that day comes,
I'll die without regret.
Excuse me,
but one question.
You're a Soul Master, aren't you?
Yes.
But...
Having a Martial Soul
doesn't mean I have to be a Soul Master.
Don't you think
my dream serves a greater purpose?
Art!
My dream is to make art.
I'm sorry.
We're not good with arts.
It's fine.
Everyone is equal in front of art.
So,
how's my play?
It's not bad.
How so?
Just tell me honestly.
The play is good
but the villain inside is weird.
He has no motives.
You...
I made that up.
Spot on.
In this play,
the villain's motive and plot
are the weakest points.
You noticed straight away.
You're good, Tang San.
Are you professional?
No, I made it up.
Even more impressive!
Instinct is an artist's
greatest weapon.
Don't you know?
We should discuss
the villain's character.
How about it?
We want to go to the town, Ou.
I'll guide you two.
Let's discuss on the way.
Wu!
Do you like my play?
Yes, yes.
Did you notice the plot twist?
He thought he knew that.
Do you like it?
Rose Inn
Normally,
those who guide freshers
will wait here for announcements.
Why is the door locked then?
Lander founded Rose Inn.
It was meant to make a profit
and fund Shi Lan Ke school.
No one visited the inn,
so every year
it becomes the place for the admission exam.
It only opened once,
then it closed down.
Why is the school so poor?
Let me tell you.
In Suo Tuo City, the Seven Clans
and other parties
tried to fund us,
but we refused them.
Why?
Headmaster said:
"I don't want
Shi Lan Ke to be sponsored by anyone
because
the school
will then become a pawn.
I'm responsible for my students.
And
I don't want
my students
to take sides
and have their path set in stone
before they discover who they truly are.
This is plain irresponsible.
Do you understand?
It sounds dumb, right?
It's decent.
I quite...
Pick your own path, right?
Of course.
I already know
where I want to go.
I will be an actor.
I will write plays.
I will create arts.
Did Headmaster encourage you
after knowing your decision?
He also said that
if I didn't change my dream,
he'd burn all my plays.
That reminds me that
I should stow away
my plays later.
Thank you.
Master!
We passed the exam.
What happened, sir?
After I ushered you two in yesterday,
someone from Martial Soul Hall
entered Rose Inn.
This is Rose Inn.
Let me show you what I wrote.
Are they here
for what happened in Nuoding?
No one came to us.
Only students were present yesterday.
Good then.
You're still wanted.
Be cautious.
Noted.
Hi.
Are you Tang San's teacher?
I'm from Shi Lan Ke,
Ou...
Ou Si Ke.
By the way,
amongst the students,
did you notice someone
with a bamboo hat?
bamboo hat?
Yes.
Oriental hat.
She's called
Hu Lie Na.
You know, this girl...
If she ever acts,
she's perfect
for a cunning and complex villain.
This reminds me of Headmaster.
Headmaster has always been single.
Based on my observations,
he has zero luck with girls.
But this time, he spent
a long time
talking to her in a room.
It's his own room.
There's a stranger inside too.
Something's fishy.
Please summarise everything in ten words.
She was then talking
to Headmaster privately in his room.
Ten words.
Ten words!
Right?
Exactly ten.
Master...
I feel like
the stories I want to tell
should be told succinctly,
with easy-to-understand words.
That's how it should be.
The audience will understand
my stories better.
Thanks, Master.
Thank you.
You gave me an epiphany.
Headmaster is what Hu Lie Na wants.
She might be from Martial Soul Hall too.
When did Shi Lan Ke
become associated
with Martial Soul Hall?
We're not related
to Martial Soul Hall at all.
Su Yun Tao was there too.
Was he who you wanted to meet?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪