I was scared to death.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
That's what technology is for.
I didn't want to put you in danger. Sorry.
And what if I am?
We're partners,
so we should share the danger.
-You really piss me off.
-Ms. Hong.
The real boss behind Babel.
I know who it is.
Really?
Yes.
Who is the real boss?
Who is this chairman?
I don't know.
Jang Han-seok!
Jang Han-seok.
But we thought he was living
a quiet life in the States.
No.
He was behind this the whole time.
CHAIRMAN
Let's call him.
Cha-young, over here!
Aren't you getting a call?
What? A call?
No. I'm not getting any calls.
I should report this to the police.
Mr. Cassano told us
never to report this to the police.
Mr. Cassano will take care of it.
Put it back in.
Okay.
There's no answer.
That's odd. He would answer
if he wanted to know what happened.
Right.
Who are they?
They are Mr. Cassano's shadows.
Take these three to the warehouse.
I'll be there soon.
-Yes, sir.
Why didn't you bring them with you?
I told them to keep an eye on you
just in case.
Thanks, Joon-woo. You should go home.
No. I want to stay with you.
Just go!
Mr. Jang.
Today was an exception,
but you shouldn't come next time.
Okay. I won't.
Why does he look so pitiful?
Can you two help clean…
Your car door was open,
so we just took these out.
We'll clean up here.
So it'll look like nothing happened here.
You cannot tell the other tenants
what happened.
-Yes, ma'am!
Ms. Hong and I will take the killers' car.
You two can take my car.
-Okay.
-And pick up the empty shells, too.
Don't worry.
When it comes to picking up empty shells,
Korean men are the best.
Salute!
He almost got me!
How did he beat the three of them
all at once?
EPISODE 11
Damn it.
What is this?
This is just like the movies.
Will this actually kill them?
I've never done this before.
But they might die sooner than I thought.
Okay. Pay attention.
We have some bookkeeping to do.
First, you were the ones
who set the villa on fire
and killed the researchers, right?
Yes! It was us!
Yes, we did it!
Next.
You also killed Director Gil and
investigators from the prosecution, right?
Damn it.
-Yes!
-We did it! We killed them.
-Stop it!
-Stop!
Stop!
Here's the most important question.
The four people who committed suicide.
You set it up, didn't you?
-Yes. It was us.
-Yes.
We did that, too.
Stop it. Please stop it!
-Please!
-Stop it!
-Don't!
-Stop!
Do you finally understand
the pain they felt
as they lay dying in the car?
We only did what we were told to!
We were following Jang Han-seok's orders!
Where is…
Jang Han-seok?
The only thing I know
is that he's in Korea.
We've never seen his face!
-Are you sure he's in Korea?
-Yes!
He gives us orders through the phone.
And when he calls us,
he uses a voice changer.
Yes, sir.
Don't come to the plaza.
Go to the underpass
-where you abducted them.
-Yes, sir.
Stop lying.
I'm sure you know where he is.
We're telling the truth.
We really don't know where he is!
This is all they know.
I guess they're useless now.
Should we get rid of them?
-Don't kill us.
-Spare us.
Don't kill us.
You bastards deserve to die
over and over again.
People usually
don't reflect on their past actions
when they avert a crisis.
Especially people like you
don't have a sense of guilt to repent.
Just hand us over to the police!
We'll face the punishment of the law!
The punishment of the law?
And who will that benefit?
Let's go.
-Don't kill us!
-Let us out!
Let us out!
Yes, Mr. Cho.
Yes. Locate the cell phone
of the number I sent you.
Okay.
I know that they are helping us,
but I get mad whenever I see them.
Those two, you mean?
Whenever I see them,
I'm reminded of my father's incident.
I can understand that.
They killed your father,
but you can't do anything.
You remember what I told you
when we caught them, right?
When you're in a war,
it's the most effective to use
your enemy's hunting dogs.
We're using them
because I accepted what you told me.
Once they become useless to us,
I'll help you throw them
into the tiger's cage. Just wait.
Where did you learn to fight like that?
I had martial arts training as a kid.
My teacher was a former GIS member.
"GIS"?
-Italian special forces.
-I see.
That explains why you looked cool
when fighting.
I trained my ass off.
It was the only way
for a weak Asian kid to protect himself
among bigger racist Caucasians.
I had to fight.
What will you do with those three killers?
I'll show them mercy
since I don't want to make use of them.
Today, I'll show mercy
by letting them face
a less painful punishment
than they deserve.
-Cheers.
-Drink it up.
-All right.
-Cheers.
-I will.
-Bottoms up.
-Is it true?
Mr. Tak beat those thugs
with a pair of scissors?
-Watch.
-Okay.
He used his scissors like this.
From the first moment I saw him
I could sense that he had this
special energy within him.
Gosh, I'm hot.
Were you in some kind of organization?
-Gosh, no. What organization?
-Were you?
It's just that in my hometown, Chungju,
-people called me Lightning Scissors.
-Gosh.
You're fast as lightning,
hence the nickname.
There's a monk we call "Lightning Moktak"
for hitting the moktak fast.
Gosh, you should consider
yourselves lucky.
Do you know how scary those thugs are?
When did you get here?
You should be careful around people
with the Gurkha knife tattoos.
They go around the redevelopment sites
And anyone that doesn't listen to them
ends up dead.
They come to your house at night
and beat you to death.
Gosh. Anyway,
I wonder when Mr. Martial Arts over there
will show us his skills.
What a series of disappointments.
Well, I guess Mr. Lee does lack
this critical blow to end the fight.
That's right.
He can beat neighborhood thugs,
but he's not that good.
Anyway, when it comes to fighting,
Mr. Tak is ranked number one
in the plaza now.
And Mr. Cassano is the second best.
No, I don't agree.
I think Mr. Cassano's moves
are graceful like Donnie Yen.
It's embarrassing to say this,
but Vincenzo Cassano's movements
are sloppy like Stephen Chow's.
That's not true.
They aren't sloppy at all.
Mr. Cassano is like a bat out of hell.
How odd.
Just a few hours ago,
I did something I'd never imagined,
but it seems I can drink just fine.
Ms. Hong, you belong in the Mafia.
Let's drink until 2 a.m.
and call it a night.
You said it. Just until 2 a.m.
Hey, it's 3 a.m.!
Should we wrap it up?
Let's drink until 4 a.m.
We have a lot of food left.
Right.
We can't throw these away, right?
You know makgeolli…
is like a black hole.
Once you start drinking,
you end up in a black hole.
You know…
I'm sorry about what I did
at the underpass.
I hugged you, remember?
You were flustered, right?
Don't apologize.
You were worried.
But…
after hugging you…
something got iffy.
My heart went like…
It went like this.
I couldn't tell…
if my heart pounded like that
because you were in danger
or because I had feelings for you.
I need to test this out.
Gosh, be careful.
I'm not that drunk.
Get up.
What?
-Get up.
-Why?
Okay.
I'm going to hug you for ten seconds.
Let's say I'm testing to see
if I have feelings for you.
Don't move.
Okay. I won't move.
Stay still.
Okay.
I was wrong.
It was because you were in danger earlier.
I'm so thirsty now.
Mr. Cassano, we have a lot of makgeolli
in the warehouse.
I would appreciate it if you brought them.
You're here.
Have you been well?
Yes. I've been well.
You seem tired.
I had a lot of work.
You should take it easy.
You don't want your handsome face
to get haggard.
You're eating your meals
and taking your medicine, right?
Of course.
Otherwise, you'd scold me again.
Your doctor told me the other day…
that you beat lung cancer 28 years ago.
Yes.
It seems the only thing I have
in this world isn't that healthy.
Did you not have any family…
back then?
I did. I had a son.
But my days were numbered,
so I had to send him away.
To where?
Very far away.
To a place where my son
would grow up happily.
Without his mom…
he wouldn't have been happy anywhere.
Mr. Hong told me a long time ago
that you accepted
the cancer and the sentence
because of your guilt
over abandoning your son.
I'm sure your son is doing well.
So don't feel guilty and get better.
Don't give up on yourself like this.
Okay?
Okay.
I'll do that.
I'll try.
Shouldn't we still come up
with some sort of plan?
Don't worry.
Vincenzo and Cha-young can never find me.
They won't get anything
from interrogating those three killers.
But wouldn't they come
after me and Ms. Choi
to find out who you are?
-Can you endure torture?
-What?
-"What?"
-Pardon? Sorry?
You know, like being hung
upside down and being electrocuted,
or being beat senselessly
with a baseball bat.
No. I cannot endure that kind of…
Yes. I can endure it.
Damn it.
They were my most useful hunting dogs.
It's hard to find hunting dogs like them.
Unless you want to have him stuffed
as a trophy,
we can just chase him away.
Why don't we handle
Vincenzo differently this time?
How?
Let's take the easy route.
There's the fact that
Vincenzo is in the Mafia.
-You were so cool.
-Stop that. You're embarrassing me.
-Gosh, it wasn't anything special.
-Can you teach me that?
Don't tell people…
Hey.
Vincenzo Cassano. Good morning.
Hello.
Wait.
When you need muscle
or help with getting your money back,
tell me anytime.
He beat up the thugs who came
to demolish the plaza yesterday.
He told us that he used to be called
Lightning Scissors of Chungju.
I see.
Good day.
What?
What kind of response was that?
Shouldn't he at least look surprised?
JIPURAGI LAW FIRM
LAWYER HONG CHA-YOUNG
Mr. Cassano, I need to talk to you.
Please let me be your bodyguard.
Don't.
She says no.
You don't need to pay me.
I just want to help you.
-Mr. Lee.
-Yes?
I don't need a bodyguard.
No, you will need one.
He says he doesn't need one!
I'm not rich or well-educated,
but I would like to have a job
that is meaningful.
I want to help you with the talent I have
to bring down bad guys.
What if you get in trouble
and lose everything again?
When will we have babies then?
I'm not trying to lose anything.
I'm doing this because
I want to make Dal-rae proud of his dad.
How old are you?
Why are you trying to live life like
a Hong Kong action movie?
Should I let them have their way then?
I must show them
that I will put up a fight
no matter how insignificant I may be!
Okay. I got it. Let me think about it.
-Don't even think about it!
-Okay, I won't.
Mr. Cassano, please trust me
and let me be your bodyguard.
-Mr. Cassano.
-Come here.
Mr. Cassano.
Are you testing me right now?
Don't lift me above your head!
I'll leave you if you do!
Yes, Mr. Cho.
I tracked down the number you gave me,
but we have a problem.
So the records
of Jang Han-seok's burner phone
and the killers' phones have been erased
from the cell towers, right?
Yes. When he got to them,
they were erasing all the records.
Not everyone can do that.
I'm sure the higher-ups pressured them.
But luckily, we got the locations
of the last contact.
This is when I called Jang Han-seok
with the killer's phone.
Take a look.
Yang-dong, Giseong-gu, Seoul…
Yang-dong?
Wait, that's where the underpass is.
That means Jang Han-seok was near by then.
My gosh. Where was he hiding?
What a rat!
He's such a sly and annoying rat!
If this is our only lead,
how will we find Jang Han-seok?
-You come here often.
-Yes.
My chef has sent you some risotto today.
I feel bad taking free food.
We're having a meeting now.
We'll eat afterwards.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
I'll look into the routes people can take
to approach the underpass.
-You do that.
-Okay.
Isn't this crazy though?
He could have been watching us.
It means he was in the area.
Why are there two dishes?
You said not to bring yours the other day.
But, still…
I'm sorry. I'll make sure
to bring yours too next time.
Okay.
-Thanks.
-Sure. Sorry.
-Sorry.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
-Thank you so much.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Okay.
I'm sorry. I'll go now.
-Okay. Thank you.
-Thank you. Sorry.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
Thank you.
We can't track his phone's location.
There's nothing we can do for now.
This would be a piece of cake
for an intelligence agency.
An?
What are you doing?
-What's this?
-Don't touch that.
Bye.
NANYAK TEMPLE
Are you Jeokha?
Yes.
We're from
the Administrative Headquarters.
-I see. Hello.
-I see.
How may I help you?
Someone has blown the whistle
on Nanyak Temple
on the Jogye Order webpage.
A whistleblower?
What do you mean?
They said
you forced people to make hefty donations
and rarely held services.
Pardon?
This is not true.
-This is slander.
-I'm sorry.
But we must follow the protocol
and investigate.
-Please excuse us.
-What…
But…
Wait.
I'm feeling down.
I should have my vitamins.
Can I have one?
This is for women.
There's a different product for men.
I see. Okay.
You could've bought men's vitamins too.
To locate Jang Han-seok,
we need to pressure Wusang
or Chairman Jang Han-seo.
But I doubt we'll get anything from them.
We need to find someone
who knows Jang Han-seok's face.
That won't be easy to do.
Someone who knows…
Jeez!
Ms. Seo?
It's the monthly game day today.
I was wondering if you could attend.
The tenants get together
and play games to bond.
The losers buy lunch.
I see.
We skipped last month's game day
as there was a lot happening.
Why don't you all join us today?
What kind of game do you play?
Mafia.
Pardon?
Do you not know how to play Mafia?
I'm good.
You guys can go have fun.
Mr. Cassano. Please join us.
If you don't come,
I won't go either.
She really wants you to come.
Why don't you join us?
If you don't know the rules,
I'll explain them on our way.
-They are very simple.
-I said no.
Let's go play the game.
Let's go. We need something
to uplift our mood.
-I'm good.
-Let's go.
-Let's go. It's fun.
-It'll be fun.
-I'm really good.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
-I said no!
It’s morning.
COP, CITIZEN, MAFIA, COP, MAFIA, CITIZEN
CITIZEN, CITIZEN, DOCTOR, CITIZEN, CITIZEN
CITIZEN, CITIZEN
Well, this is obvious.
Hey, Vincenzo Cassano.
You're a Mafia, right?
I also believe that
the handsome lawyer over there is a Mafia.
I'm not a Mafia.
I think you are
No, I'm not.
I don't look anything like a Mafia.
I think he's denying it because he is.
I don't think Mr. Cassano is a Mafia.
Hold on.
He must also be a Mafia.
You can tell by the way he smiles.
Gosh. I think
that pawnshop lady is a Mafia.
Look at her face. She looks sly.
That's just how I look.
I think the owner of Byebye Balloon
is in the Mafia.
By the way, who invited
the Byebye Balloon guys?
We just figured we should come
since we're family now.
-Don't you agree?
-Right.
I think…
That Park Saeroyi wannabe is a Mafia.
Don't call me that!
Look who's talking.
You look like a North Korean soldier.
I don't look like that at all.
You rebel scum!
What? "Rebel scum"?
All right. Stop it.
We must vote now. It's nighttime.
Okay. Put your heads down.
-Put your heads down.
-Seriously.
Excuse us.
Excuse us!
What? We're closed.
Who's Mr. Vincenzo Cassano?
It's me. What is this about?
I'm from the International Crimes Division
of Namdongbu Prosecutors' Office.
You're under arrest for attempted murder,
aiding and abetting, and blackmail.
You have the right to consult an attorney,
explain yourself,
and to a writ of habeas corpus.
What are you talking about?
You're in the Italian Mafia.
You're a consigliere.
Yes, we're looking for the Mafia members,
but this is a game.
-It's not real. It's a game.
-Arrest him.
Get up.
-My goodness.
-What? Is this true?
-What's happening?
-What?
Finish your game.
You can represent me.
-Come with me.
-Isn't this a game?
He's really leaving.
-I'm coming with you as his lawyer.
-What?
-No!
Where are you going?
He's in the Mafia.
My cell phone was vibrating
inside my jacket.
I thought I was in a horror movie.
You really dodged a bullet.
You know what? Whatever they try,
they can't find me. Never.
-Sir.
-Yes.
How about you entrust me
with Babel Pharmaceuticals?
You want to run the company
without my interference?
No. That's not what I meant.
I have learned a lot from you,
so I think I can do it by myself.
Right.
I bet you have your own ideas, too.
No!
Should I slit your throat,
so you stop thinking?
Sir. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
No. Maybe I should die.
Sir! No!
That way, Babel will be yours.
Sir. I'm so sorry.
I just wanted to lessen your burden.
That's all.
I'm sorry.
My burden isn't Babel Pharmaceuticals.
It's you.
I'll never ask something like that again.
I'm sorry.
If you ask me something like that again,
I swear…
I'll kill you.
I mean it, my brother.
Gosh, I lost my temper again.
From now on, I will think more carefully
before I speak.
I'll get going first.
Finish your breakfast.
I lost my appetite because of you.
Oh, no!
I've acted so cheeky with him.
It's so embarrassing!
I saw it in movies. The Mafia is so cruel.
They kill people with guns
-and hang people in front of their houses.
-Right.
What did I tell you?
I told you he wasn't ordinary.
By the way, when he was getting arrested,
they said he was a corn salad.
What does that mean?
Toto told me…
that's what they call
the top Mafia member. Corn Salad.
What a savory and refreshing title.
You know what?
Why don't we ask him for help?
-With what?
-With finding the gold.
They are real pros at stuff like this.
That's right.
We're not getting anywhere.
Then let's tell him about the gold bars.
I'm sure he will give us a solution.
Then let's tell him we'll give him
a small cut and get him to help us.
But he was arrested.
He can't help us from prison.
Why did the prosecutors from Namdongbu
arrest Vincenzo?
I think he's being set up
by Wusang, Babel, and Namdongbu.
I knew his mess would catch up with him.
Stay out of this. It's a headache.
No. We must take Vincenzo Cassano
from them and handle him ourselves.
Forget it. We won't get anything from it.
Let them handle him.
Sir.
Don't you have any pride?
Pride?
Why are you bringing that up now?
Clearly, the head of the International
Crimes Division in Korea is you.
But those people in Namdongbu ignored you
and handled this on their own.
Small-time prosecutors who know
nothing about international crimes.
By taking Vincenzo from them,
we will clearly show them who's in charge
and that the head
of this whole operation is you.
He's right!
Thank you, ma'am!
Director Tae.
-Director Tae.
Bring him here now.
We'll deal with Vincenzo.
Director Tae.
-Director Tae.
-Thank you, ma'am.
The consigliere of the Cassano Family.
Look at these bodies.
You sure know
how to work your knife, don't you?
How many people did you kill?
Arresting him without any definite
evidence is a violation of the law.
Here's the evidence.
These photos show no ties to Mr. Cassano.
And you need more than a few photos
to arrest him.
I have more than a few photos.
You've been causing
a lot of trouble these days.
Given the circumstances,
you will be subject to deportation.
If the grounds for deportation are clear.
I can make whatever grounds I want.
That again?
Predetermine the punishment
and fabricating evidence?
Watch your tone.
Please, escort them out.
You can't do this!
Let's go.
Sit tight. I'll do whatever I can.
It's fine.
I can take care of myself.
-Go.
-Let's go.
Wait!
An?
Who are you?
I'm from the International
Organized Crime Bureau
of the International Security
Intelligence Service.
I'm Team Leader An Gi-seok.
AN GI-SEOK
No way.
I'm here to take Vincenzo Cassano
into our custody.
But we're the ones who caught him.
Please cooperate
so that Vincenzo Cassano can
cooperate with our bureau.
The cause is confidential,
and you will hand over
all the evidence you have as well.
This is our warrant for his custody
from the Ministry of Justice.
Hey…
Let's go, Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
Ms. Hong Cha-young.
You little… Damn it.
Why you…
The International Security
Intelligence Service?
Yes. They took him because they had to
keep an eye on him for national security.
What? Why would they…
Why would they want him?
I don't know what it is exactly,
but I'm sure there's something big
behind this.
I think you should pay more attention
to keeping your identity concealed.
We're up against an intelligence agency.
When it comes to intel,
they're better than us.
That's what they do.
Right. You have a point.
My gosh. Do you think Vincenzo
could be a spy or something?
-He must be a spy.
-That's what she just said.
So…
you've been surveilling me the whole time?
I'm sorry.
It was my mission, so I had no choice.
I know everything you've been up to
including your attempt to find out
who Chairman Jang Han-seok is.
Then, how come you didn't do anything?
I would have arrested you
if you violated the law.
But Mr. Consigliere
fought for justice, the weak,
and Buddha.
So I didn't do anything.
I see. Buddha was one of them.
What do you plan to do with me?
I take it you will continue
to fight against Babel. Am I correct?
Yes.
I'm on your side. I want to help you.
No, listen. This makes no sense right now.
Will you really help us?
Yes. I will help you
for the good of our country and justice.
As you know, I'm in the Mafia,
and you work for an intelligence agency.
That doesn't matter.
I respect you, Mr. Consigliere.
Why?
Because you repented your past sins
and are devoted to fighting evil.
Then we'll gladly accept your help.
-It's settled, then.
-Deal.
But I have three conditions.
-Gosh. Three?
-Number one.
you must include me
as an official member of your group.
-Okay.
-Number two.
Keep my identity secret
from the other tenants.
Okay.
Number three.
-Give me a hug.
-Okay.
What?
-What?
-It's embarrassing to say this…
but it's just such a huge honor.
He said it's a huge honor. Come on.
Give the man a hug.
What are you talking about?
How about a handshake instead?
Good.
Okay, but you're too close.
I can't believe…
that I'm in the presence
of a real consigliere.
I have no regrets now, Mr. Consigliere.
These photos…
It's the evidence we got
from the Namdongbu Office.
What is it, Mr. Consigliere?
-Oh, my God.
-What's the matter?
These photos are…
probably from the man
Jang Han-seok sent to Italy.
A prosecutor can't get these photos.
What if he gave Jang Han-seok
these photos in person?
It's highly likely that he saw his face.
Gosh. I got goosebumps.
If we can find this informant,
we can get to Jang Han-seok.
We should find him then.
-An.
-Yes?
I mean, Mr. An.
You can help me with this, right?
Of course.
Thank you. See you later.
Thank you. Let's go, Ms. Hong.
I'll look forward to working with you.
See you at the plaza.
I'm rooting for you, Mr. Consigliere!
Always! We can do this!
The Korean man
who was asking about you?
Yes.
See if you can get a photo
or a video of him.
I heard he met with Giorgio
at Hotel Caruso.
I'll look into the security cameras there.
Do it as soon as possible.
How long do you think it'll take?
Three or four hours will suffice.
WELCOME BACK
MAFIA'S CORN SALAD VINCENZO!
-I'll just leave.
-No way.
Mr. Cassano! This way!
Okay.
A hero of Geumga Plaza is born.
Come on.
Is this a wedding hall? What is all this?
Let us welcome
the return of the great Mafia,
Corn Salad Vincenzo!
Everyone wants to hug you today.
-We want a strong leader!
-Yes!
We don't want a weak leader
who's all talk and no action.
-The Mafia have their turf, right?
-Right.
Make our plaza your turf.
-Yes.
-You're our Corn Salad.
Please, lead us
so we can fight back harder.
Well…
What we need is the ability to fight,
not peace.
I'm so happy that you are in the Mafia.
-Let's do this, Corn Salad!
-Corn Salad!
-Corn Salad.
-Wait.
It's not a Corn Salad.
It's consigliere.
-What?
You said Corn Salad was the title
for the scariest Mafia member.
-Corn Salad?
-Hey.
Well, I said it was consigliere.
Let's move on.
A round of applause!
You're supposed to eat tofu
after your release.
I'm good.
-No.
-No. You have to eat it.
-Just one bite.
-You have to.
Take a bite.
-Isn't it great?
-Good!
Gosh.
I'm glad that we didn't cross him.
We could have really died.
He won't try to get back at us, right?
He won't
because we already look so pathetic.
Consigliere.
I'm glad that you got out.
I feel like I'm one of the residents
in Jongno,
welcoming Kim Du-han on his release.
"Stand up, Du-han.
Du-han, you're the pride of Joseon!
No. Get up! You must!
You are…"
-Mr. Nam.
-Yes?
-That's enough.
-Okay.
With all the support you have,
why don't you make your own family here?
Geumga Family, Mr. Corn Salad.
Yes?
It's Luca.
-Luca.
He's super-fast.
Professionals sure are different.
He really is a Mafia.
By the way, will we be able to find out
who he is only with this video?
-Can you find out who he is?
-Gosh.
This is a piece of cake.
How long will this take?
Five hours will be more than enough.
That's pretty impressive.
Then again,
think about all the taxes we pay.
What are you doing, An? Get their order.
Okay. Truffle porcini spaghetti.
Okay.
Kimchi fried rice.
Okay. They want kimchi fried rice.
Wait. Who orders kimchi fried rice
at a pasta restaurant?
You were here, Mr. Cassano.
Hello.
What's the matter?
I WANT TO REPORT A CORRUPT TEMPLE
And you don't know who posted this online?
It was anonymous.
So they couldn't tell us who wrote this.
This is defamation.
If it's a false accusation,
we can sue them for compensation.
What happens
if you can't prove this is not true?
We will be suspended, and the temple…
might have to close down.
This is so unfair.
He's been devoted to the teachings
of Buddha all his life.
First, we must find out
who wrote such lies online.
By the way, Mr. Jang, it's very loud.
Are you sure this is okay?
Hunting is allowed in the nearby
mountains. I can shoot here.
I see.
-Damn it.
-You're not even that far,
but you can't hit your target.
Well, that's because…
You should try it. Go ahead.
-Me?
-Yes. Do it.
Okay. All right.
-I'll try it. Okay.
-Go ahead.
Gosh. I'm kind of embarrassed.
-Just do it.
-Okay.
What was that?
I was the best marksman
during my military service.
The gun is working fine.
How did he do that?
My brother has
no intention of
putting me in charge of Babel.
Vincenzo keeps outsmarting him.
He's not that good, either.
Well…
Vincenzo has had the upper hand lately.
Like the incident at the underpass.
Exactly. He would've been killed
if he'd been caught there.
I wish he was caught.
That's what you really want, right?
-No, what I meant was…
-You want to oust your brother
and run Babel by yourself, right?
Don't say stuff like that.
But you are worried
about the aftermath, right?
You don't know how to run the company
without your brother.
Don't worry.
I will support you, so Babel can run
smoothly like a well-oiled machine.
Will Ms. Choi Myung-hee back me up too?
Ms. Choi…
isn't the type to take risks.
Forget her, then.
But…
-do you really think I can do this?
-Of course.
I'll risk my life to serve you.
You and I aren't some moths
flying into fire knowing they'll die.
We will be phoenixes instead.
Then let's come up with a plan…
without anyone knowing.
Damn it.
Mr. Cassano.
The issue Nanyak Temple's having…
Did you do it?
Yes.
Wait, what? Well, that's…
I wanted to get the gold
out of there quickly.
I'm sorry.
I should apologize.
I've been taking too much time.
You must've been frustrated.
No, I was rash.
I shouldn't have done that.
I was just impatient.
Let's discuss it before we do anything
just like we've been doing.
We're friends.
Yes. I understand, Mr. Cassano.
It won't happen ever again.
Write on the bulletin board
that your accusations were false.
We can't do that to the monks.
I'll post a correction.
Please do. I'll get going.
Okay.
Mr. Corn Salad.
We need to talk.
What did you just say?
Gold!
-"Gold"?
-Gold.
We received information
that there is 12 billion won's worth
of gold bars hidden in this building.
But we don't know the exact location.
We've searched every corner
of the building for a month.
Who told you that there's gold here?
A neighborhood beggar, Gilbert.
I see.
A homeless guy.
Isn't this your specialty?
Does everyone at the plaza
know about this?
Yes. Except for you three
from Jipuragi Law Firm.
If you help us,
we'll all chip in and give you a cut.
Hey!
Why are you so rude?
I wasn't being rude.
Gosh! There's gold in this building!
-Yes.
There's gold here?
-Gosh. Who knew I'd see gold bars?
-Mr. Cassano.
-Be quiet.
-Okay.
Okay. I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
-By the way…
-Yes?
…how is that gold yours?
It must belong to someone.
Finders keepers.
Right, my keeper?
That was witty.
-That's so funny.
-I'm good, aren't I?
Please help us.
Okay. Bye.
How dare they think it's theirs?
How dare they?
What's this?
REPORT ON KIM SANG-YUN
PERSONAL INFORMATION ON KIM SANG-YUN
Kim Sang-yun, 41 years old.
A former VP
of a multi-national arms company, DO Arms.
He's working as a weapon lobbyist
and an informant in Europe now.
No wonder his intel was good.
But I'm glad that he's in Korea.
Let's start looking
for Jang Han-seok again.
What is it?
We should meet today.
I've got important information.
Stop lying.
I'm serious.
Babel Pharmaceuticals and Chemicals
won't compensate the victims.
What?
Okay.
I'll go meet Joon-woo.
Find out who Jang Han-seok is.
Okay.
Who are you?
Yes, I did those things,
but you only collected
negative information.
Jang Han-seok will get the wrong idea.
I made a lot of donations
and saved a lot of people.
Will I end up killing you or…
sparing you?
Just kill me.
You want to know
who Jang Han-seok is, right?
But I cannot tell you.
Even if I save myself
by telling you who he is,
I'll be dead in a week.
What if I find you a way
for you to survive?
It won't work.
And I don't trust you.
So you'll keep your secret
and stay loyal to him.
What a fine lobbyist.
I've been tortured by the Russian Mafia,
terrorists, and rebels.
This isn't my first rodeo.
I can endure all kinds of pain
you throw at me.
I guess you don't know this.
There's a limit to pain,
but there's no limit to one's fear.
The first round is a tie.
Round two.
I'll go first this time.
Wait.
The second round is also a tie.
Round three.
I'll go first again.
The third round is also a tie.
Round four.
Stop. Stop it! I'll tell you everything.
I'll tell you who Jang Han-seok is.
He's…
He's a lawyer at Wusang.
His name at Wusang is…
Jang Joon-woo.
Give me the intel now.
I'll show you this document
in exchange for information about you.
Hey, you can't do that.
Forget it then.
Okay.
REPORT ON BABEL'S
COMPENSATION WITHDRAWAL
This is the report
from Choi Myung-hee to Mr. Han.
I got it from the bin
in the boss's office.
THERE IS NOT ENOUGH CAUSE TO COMPENSATE…
Babel Pharmaceuticals and Chemicals
will make an announcement
on withdrawing their
compensation next week.
But Chairman Jang Han-seo promised
to compensate them on TV.
Damn it. Those assholes!
All right. You tell me something
about what you're up to.
Yes.
Just listen. Don't say anything.
Jang Joon-woo is…
Jang Han-seok.
Jang Joon-woo, your junior and intern,
was Jang Han-seok all along.
What will you do?
You'll stick to the plan, right?
Jang Joon-woo.
Mr. Cassano?
Kneel.
-What's going on?
-Kneel.
Do it.
Can you tell me
what's going on here?
That's enough.
Jang Han-seok.
Damn it.
You got me.
How did you find out?
You can hide the fire,
but you can't hide the smoke.
I guess there was still some smoke left
even when I had the fan on high.
Say your last prayer.
I don't pray.
Kill me already.
You Mafia bastard.
As you wish.
It's time for you to make a decision.
I guess a war broke out.
I heard that you're ready to bring
all six charges against the Babel Group.
The entire country will be in an uproar
if this is exposed.
I'll help you kill my brother as you wish
so just leave me and Babel alone.
If you choose the wrong one,
you'll end up falling to your death.
I really am going to kill you soon.
Run if you're afraid.
I'll follow you there too.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son