♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
My real name
is Qian Ren Xue.
As long as you come
from the Martial Soul Hall,
you are my enemy!
Tan San.
Goodbye.
Wu, why did you...
You are so foolish!
[Episode 155]
Who is it?
Senior Du Gu,
you're finally here!
I've been with Father all this time,
in case my brother hurts him again.
The poison has taken effect.
At most, he can last for half an hour.
He is severely intoxicated.
The medication I have with me
isn't effective for that.
It's a mixed poison made up
of seven different poisons.
No wonder even I couldn't find the antidote.
I can make the antidote,
but I need time.
Old Freak.
How long can he live
if we fight poison with poison?
At least twenty-four hours.
But if we still can't rescue him,
he will die for sure.
Let's start.
Dean.
How is the school?
Once we defeated the enemy,
we immediately came here to meet you,
and saw people from the Qibao Amber tribe
and Tang's clan
fighting with the imperial soul masters.
We snuck in under the cover of the chaos.
The power of Tang's clan
is what the Martial Soul Hall overlooked.
Let's go back to the school first.
We can only start our counterattack
after we get the support of Emperor Xue Ye.
The palace is heavily guarded.
We need to leave quickly,
or else more people from
the Qibao Amber tribe and Tang's clan
will be hurt.
Chief!
Are you alright?
Granduncle.
You come right in time.
Please take our clan's disciples
to protect the Qibao Amber tribe as they retreat,
and meet us at Shrek School.
Alright.
So fast.
He really is the fastest soul master in the world.
Little Freak.
I'm ready.
We will break out immediately
and go back to the school.
Rescue Emperor Xue Ye!
Kill everyone else!
Stop! Don't run! Catch them!
Some of these people
are actual imperial soul masters.
We just need to drive them away,
no need to fight to the death.
Third Skill, Burst!
Surround them! Don't let them get away!
San.
Go out of the South Gate.
I will block them.
Don't let them get away! Stop!
The Martial Soul Hall?
Catch them! Stop!
[Soul Land]
Little Freak.
What should we do?
We'll have to break out by force.
Let's go.
Kill!
Shiny
Gold Twirl!
Emperor Xue Ye is about to die.
We need to break this formation!
Random Skill!
Assembly of Buddha!
Martial Soul Fusion Skill?
Kill!
Qibao, reinforced with Amber!
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ Looking beyond, conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
Where is Emperor Xue Ye?
Uncle She.
Order everyone
to lock down the palace.
We can't let Tang San and the others
escape with Emperor Xue Ye.
Xue Qing He must inherit the throne!
Is the Qibao Amber tribe planning to revolt?
They are not the ones revolting.
The Crown Prince, Xue Qing He, is!
Your Highness.
Someone evil from the Martial Soul Hall
disguised himself as my brother,
and poisoned Father in secret.
Luckily the Qibao Amber tribe and Tang's clan
helped us,
and thus Father had a chance to escape.
This Fourth Prince
is really different from the rich playboy
he was disguised as.
It was the Martial Soul Hall.
Your Majesty!
Father.
Send my order.
Starting today,
Xue Qing He is dislodged as the Crown Prince.
Fourth Prince Xue Beng
will rule in my place in the interim.
We...
We listened to the evil people,
and almost killed Your Majesty.
Father!
We must take His Majesty
to somewhere safe immediately.
Warriors!
You are all elites chosen by Father.
I trust your loyalty to the royal family.
Now Father is harmed by those evil people
from the Martial Soul Hall.
They wanted to usurp the throne.
Please immediately eliminated the traitors
and keep our people of Tian Dou Empire
safe and sound!
Yes!
It's too late.
Tang San and the others are gone.
What?
We made one wrong move
and lost everything.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 155 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1466 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2341]
[Total scene: 57832]
[Total CGI: 27573]
[Total plan of action scene: 12219]
[Total scene model: nearly 553]
[Total character model: nearly 995]
[Total props model: 13376]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Does His Majesty know about this?
Xue Ye is heavily poisoned
and will definitely die.
How many people
did we lose?
Send my order.
Assemble all of the Martial Soul Hall's troops,
and destroy the power
of the Tian Dou royal family.
Xue Qing He should be a fake?
[Tan San, you won this time, yet we'll meet again]
We are still too late.
[Soul Land]
[10AM every Saturday]