♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Little Freak.
What should we do?
We'll have to barge in by force.
Let's go.
Kill!
One wrong move
and we lost everything.
[Episode 156]
Chief.
Thank you for your hard work, elders.
How many people did we lose?
Nobody was seriously injured.
Old Rhino and everyone
in the Hall of Defense
are all strong and fierce
that they blocked the front like a wall.
Chief Tang.
Thank you for your help
so we could evacuate safely.
How is His Majesty?
Very bad.
We need to find an antidote quickly
and stabilize the situation
of Tian Dou Empire.
Xue Qing He is a fake?
That woman is very decisive
and powerful.
This time,
if it wasn't for
the Century Millennium Soul Ring
that Wu gave me,
I would've been defeated
by her Six-winged Angel Martial Soul.
But...
when I taught her,
what she had was the royal family's
Swan Martial Soul.
Could it be that she also has Twin Martial Souls?
Bibi Dong mentioned before
that the Martial Soul Hall
has six Century Millenium Soul Bones
which have been passed down for a thousand years.
I'm guessing
that Qian Ren Xue has at least one piece.
It's likely that this piece
gives her the Disguise Skill.
There's a skill like that?
I've never heard of it before.
With only one piece
can she be so powerful.
If she had all six...
When all six soul bones are used at once,
they will create a type of soul bone armor
like you had last time,
called Angel's Armor.
Its amplification power
is beyond what you can imagine.
It really is
a godly item.
Qian Ren Xue is extremely gifted
and talented at learning.
If she has all six soul bones
and assists Bibi Dong,
then wouldn't we...?!
There are extremely high requirements
for a soul master to use all six soul bones.
First, they must have
the Six-winged Angel Martial Soul.
Next,
they must be extremely gifted.
Rumor says
that when you absorb the last soul bone,
your soul power
must be at level 100.
100?
In the history of soul masters,
that is just a legend.
Once your soul power reaches level 90,
every one level up is extremely difficult.
It's extremely hard after level 95.
I wonder how the ascension from level 99
to level 100 is like.
Xue Ye is extremely intoxicated
and will surely die.
As long as we announce
to the public that the emperor is dead
and blame his death on Xue Beng,
it's not too late to teach them a lesson
after Young Master ascends the throne.
You underestimate Tang San.
He and Du Gu Bo
taking Xue Ye with them
means that they have the confidence to heal him.
Send my orders.
Assemble all the Martial Soul Hall's troops,
and destroy the power
of the Tian Dou royal family to the last bit.
My lord.
You have lurked in the palace for 20 years.
Are you going to...
We cannot hesitate,
or else things will get worse.
Once we're done,
we will leave Tian Dou City immediately.
There will be opportunities in the future.
Chief.
I have already detoxified all the poison
inside Emperor Xue Ye.
But
he was intoxicated for too long,
so his organs
are badly damaged.
He can only live
for another two to five years.
Does His Majesty
know about this?
I didn't tell him.
He is asleep.
With the help of my medicine,
I assume he will recover by tomorrow.
Elder,
Old Freak.
Thank you both.
Please get some rest.
Chief Tang.
What should we do now?
I guess
that Qian Ren Xue
won't fight us with force.
Her best choice
is to find a way
to assassinate the emperor
and ascend the throne.
But she has to face the threat
of our 5,000 soul masters.
Then
are there any other possibilities?
Destruction.
Destroy Tian Dou City as much as she can,
especially the palace.
If Tian Dou Empire's power is severely undermined,
the Martial Soul Hall
will have much more chances later on.
Oh, no!
We're too late.
Angel feather.
It was her.
She used the soul masters
of the royal family of Tian Dou Empire
and killed them all when she'd been done with them.
You really are cruel, Qian Ren Xue.
(Tang San.)
(You won this time.)
(But we will meet again.)
A defeat is a defeat.
We can start everything over.
Given the circumstances,
we still have a major advantage.
I didn't lose to Tang San,
but you.
If you hadn't rushed things,
I wouldn't have taken a risk
and started attacking early.
Sis...
Sister?
No.
I should still call you Your Holiness.
In this world,
I only have one relative,
my grandfather.
From now on,
you rule the Martial Soul Hall,
and I will rule the Elder Hall
and the Dou Luo Hall.
You won't have the right to give orders
to any elder of the Elder Hall.
What did you say?
Go see your grandfather.
If he agrees with you,
I will, too.
[Soul Land]
San.
Any plans for the coming days?
I'm going to go back
to the Hao Tian tribe first
and tell them what happened.
I will also bring the God of Ironsmith, Lou Gao,
to the Hao Tian bribe
and ask my uncle to help him
create powerful hidden weapons.
And then?
After the battle with Qian Ren Xue,
I've discovered many of my weak points.
I want to stay and train
in the Hao Tian tribe
to increase the attack power
of the Hao Tian Hammer.
You should go back to the Hao Tian tribe.
But I don't think you should train there.
Teacher.
Do you have any suggestions?
I will listen to you.
I do.
It's just that
I don't want you to take any risks.
Teacher.
You taught me before
that the higher the pressure,
the easier it is to bring out
your potential.
If I don't improve my skills sooner,
how will we
face the Martial Soul Hall in the future?
I knew you would say that.
Fine.
Then I will tell you.
My suggestion
is for you to go to an extremely dangerous place
where you can quickly improve your skills.
Where is it?
That place
is called Haishen Island.
It's an island full of soul beasts.
If you can pass the challenges
and successfully return,
then
all aspects of your skills
will improve greatly.
That place is quite challenging
despite the many chances to improve.
Has anyone been there before?
The Martial Soul Hall once sent
2,000 soul masters
to that island
in order to recruit the soul masters there.
But
not only did they fail completely,
they also lost two Grand Soul Land Masters.
After that,
the Martial Soul Hall never tried again.
This...
Grandfather.
You went to see her?
Actually,
she is also very pained.
After all,
she is not the one to be blamed.
Her feelings toward you
are different from what you imagine.
Grandfather.
Are you not going to help me either?
I can't.
Even though she's a bit radical,
she didn't do anything wrong.
She is still the pope of the Martial Soul Hall.
Besides,
her influence
in the Martial Soul Hall
surpasses mine.
What?
That...
That's impossible.
Xue.
You must never forget.
This world is about the survival of the fittest.
Those who are stronger
have a bigger say in matters.
She will bring the Martial Soul Hall
to new heights.
You need
to help her.
No matter what,
she is still your mother.
Grandfather.
I want to ask you for one last favor.
I want to be the Judicial Elder
of the Martial Soul Hall.
The Judicial Elder cannot participate
in any Martial Soul Hall missions
and must kill
all the top opponents of the Hall.
Have you considered it carefully?
Because of the young person
that defeated you this time?
From now on,
I won't meddle in the affairs
of the Martial Soul Hall.
Also,
I only have you, Grandfather.
I don't have a mother.
From today onward,
Fourth Prince Xue Beng
will be the crown prince
of Tian Dou Empire!
(Tian Dou City is gradually
becoming peaceful again.)
(But the battle between Tian Dou Empire
and the Martial Soul Hall)
(has officially begun.)
(How should I maintain the peace?)
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 156 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1473 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2356]
[Total scene: 58160]
[Total CGI: 27605]
[Total plan of action scene: 12219]
[Total scene model: nearly 554]
[Total character model: nearly 996]
[Total props model: 13376]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to be with ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
You're going to Haishen Island?
That's quite a challenging place.
Are you really sure?
They are almost here as well.
The seven of you
are our trump cards in the battle
against the Martial Soul Hall.
Since we're going,
we will definitely pass the challenges
and find a way to safely return.
I do like freedom.
But that was from when I was young.
[Soul Land]
[10AM every Saturday]