[theme music playing]
[festive music playing]
[girl] Billy, wake up.
Huh?
Did you hear that?
Hear what?
- [soft clattering]
- [gasps]
It's him.
[gasps]
[creaks]
- Shh.
- [Santa on TV] Ho-ho-ho...
[Santa continues, indistinct]
[whimsical music playing]
Then we'll have
these Christmas presents delivered
in no time at all.
[kid] That's amazing, Santa.
I've got another question...
Hm.
...deliver Christmas presents
to all the children
- around the world.
- [Santa] That's right.
[rustling]
[gasps]
[growls]
[burps]
[creature chewing]
[gasps]
[intense music playing]
- [growling]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
[shrieks]
[screaming]
[squeaks]
- [growling]
- [breathing heavily]
[sniffing]
Leah
good.
[crying]
[retching]
[sniffling]
William...
- [William whimpers]
- [sniffing]
[intense music playing]
...good.
[slurping]
[gasps]
Stay good.
[footsteps leaving]
[creature grunting]
[intense music playing]
It... It's just what I wanted.
Billy...
what would have happened
if we weren't... good?
[festive music playing]
[creature growls]
[festive music continues]