[theme music playing]
[dramatic music playing]
[coughing]
[indistinct chattering]
Hey, Snow, it's... it's good to see you.
Did they come in?
Oh, uh, it's getting harder and harder
to bring the real stuff in from Earth.
It's getting expensive.
Maybe I could interest you
in some synthetic analogs.
[Snow] Maybe you should
shut the fuck up and give me my stuff.
Order another two kilos.
I'll be back in a month.
[indistinct chattering]
[Snow] Thanks.
You're Snow, the albino.
- No, I'm not.
- Now, don't fuck with me.
I'm not fucking with you.
My name is Jelda Conley.
They call me Whitey.
Bounty hunters, right?
What's he done, this... Snow guy?
No, it's not me wants him.
It's the merchant, Baris.
There's a big reward for his balls.
Balls? As in, testicles?
[chuckles]
- Now, why the hell would Baris want those?
- My job ends at the taking.
Now, whether you're him or not...
I challenge you.
Listen...
I've never killed anyone who didn't try
to kill me first, so just move on.
I said I challenge you!
Everyone here heard it!
That puts me within my rights.
So stand up.
- [slice]
- [grunts]
I mean you no harm.
Unless harm is meant.
Best I get gone.
Well, thanks for the help.
Oh.
Found him. Get the team together.
[growling]
[footsteps approaching]
Shit.
Sorry.
- Not used to company.
- That's okay. I'm not hungry.
But I wanna travel with you.
My name is Hirald.
I'm crossing the Thiran plain.
It's not easy.
I have no problem with that.
I'll think about it.
Don't you have a day tent?
You can share mine.
[cawing]
Not much... but it'll protect us
from the worst of the heat.
Always been a fast healer.
Uh...
[Snow]
You should know why Baris is after me.
Why he wants my...
Testicles, yes.
There's something unique
about the gonadotropin-releasing hormone
your body produces.
Your cells are regenerative.
And hence, immortal.
Your hand will grow back in...
a week?
[Snow] Maybe less.
I work for Earth Central Intelligence.
They want the same things as Baris,
but I'm no bounty hunter.
- They wish you to come willingly.
- Why?
Because whoever decodes
your reproductive system
controls, in effect, immortality.
This knowledge could destabilize
the entire Protectorate.
Why not just kill me? Problem solved.
Earth Central does not suppress knowledge.
Morality's a human construct.
I thought AIs didn't give a shit.
They were created
to protect the greater good.
Will you come?
Two days should bring us to my home.
We should keep moving.
Here.
[creaking]
[Snow]
I found this place about 200 years ago.
Been improving it ever since.
[dramatic music playing]
Just how long have you been alive?
Make yourself comfortable.
You'll find clothes
in the back and a shower.
There's plenty of water here.
[sighs]
Mm...
Whose dress is this?
My wife's.
She killed herself 123 years ago.
Why?
She grew old.
I didn't.
[alarm ringing]
Snow?
[guns cocking]
Time to get your hands dirty, Baris.
Shall we?
[Trot over radio]
Meck? Are you in position?
Meck?
- Trot
- Check on her.
[ominous music playing]
Snow's here. He got Meck.
[intense music playing]
[crack]
- Stop!
- [woman grunts]
Jharit.
Baby.
[Trot] What was that?
Fucker killed Jharilla.
He's coming your way.
[intense music playing]
[choking]
That was my wife you killed, you fucker.
After I've snipped your sack,
I'm gonna take my time
cutting all the rest.
[gasps]
It makes no sense, Snow.
You've been alive for centuries.
And yet you choose to live here,
on this backwater shithole of a planet.
Well, now you'll die here.
[groans]
[dramatic music playing]
[gasping]
[inhales sharply]
You're synthetic?
No.
I was in an accident a long time ago.
Underneath the synthflesh and ceramal...
there is a spinal column, nerve tissue...
and a mostly-human brain.
Me.
I've been alone a long time too.
[dramatic music playing]