[theme music playing]
[man panting]
[ominous music playing]
I'm gonna die here.
[dramatic music playing]
[explosions in distance]
[beeping]
Shit.
Man, looks like we both
had a rough landing.
[beeping]
[computer] Life Hutch, activated.
Warning, damage detected.
Communication network, functional.
Maintenance robotics...
error.
Piece of shit.
Maintenance robotics, error.
Maintenance robotics, malfunction.
Wait!
[yells] Stop! Hold on! Halt program!
Halt program!
Unable to comply.
[ominous music playing]
[groaning]
[beeping]
[commander over radio] Prometheus CVW2.
ECMs are online. You are clear to engage.
[male pilot] Nova 6, en route.
[female pilot] Nova 9, en route.
Nova 4, en route.
[commander]
Acknowledged, you are go for weapons hot.
Copy that. Going hot.
Payload is Divine Flash 12 Judgment 2.
Armed and ready to hunt.
[commander] Nova Squadron line up,
echelon formation. Hit them fast and hard.
[suspenseful music playing]
[panting]
[robot whirring]
[metallic footsteps]
[ominous music playing]
[grunts softly]
[thud]
[grunting softly]
[commander]
731, 731, hostile fire incoming!
[male pilot] We lost Rocket 1!
[Terence] Firing!
Come on, come on. Come on.
[grunting]
[alarm wailing]
[dramatic music playing]
- [dramatic music playing]
- [metallic footsteps]
[suspenseful music playing]
[powering down]
[computer] Mayday message received.
Life Hutch 817-RD9G. Rescue inbound.
[dramatic music playing]
Warning: maintenance robot malfunction.
- Warning: maintenance robot malfunction.
- [coughing]
No shit.
Warning: maintenance robot malfunction.
[theme music playing]