[theme music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[train horn blaring]
[footsteps approaching]
[footsteps leaving]
[ticking]
[yawns]
[thump then metal screeching]
[door opens then closes]
What are we stopping here for?
[indistinct whispering]
- [gasps]
- Please get back on board, sir.
- What happened?
- Just a brief stop.
Now, please, sir, return to your cabin.
- Is something wrong with the engine?
- Nothing of consequence.
The boiler. Just need to build up
another head of steam.
Then, surely, I have time for a smoke.
Yes, but... don't wander.
Once we're ready to go, I'll call for you
to get on board, but only twice.
Then we go no matter what.
[indistinct whispering continues]
[dramatic music playing]
[rustling]
[insects chirping]
[ominous music playing]
Oh.
[chuckling]
[railman] All aboard!
[rustling]
[footsteps leaving]
Shit.
Hello! Hello! I'm here!
Can you hear me?
Hello!
- [railman] All aboard!
- Wait.
Wait! I'm here! Wait!
Please! Wait!
[suspenseful music playing]
Fuck!
Fuck, fuck, fuck!
[rustling]
- [creature growls]
- What?
[rustling continues]
[creature growls]
Hello?
[growling continues]
What the...?
Oh, my God.
[shrieks]
- [Lairo screams]
- [creatures snarling]
[grunting]
Oh, no. Oh, no, no, no.
[panting]
[gasps]
[Lairo screams]
[creatures growling]
[roars]
Get back!
- [creature growling]
- Get back!
Oh, my God.
[grunting]
The train.
Hey!
Wait!
Please, wait!
[shrieks]
[snarling]
[whimpering]
[roars]
[heavy breathing]
[dramatic music playing]
[railman] Get lost!
Begone!
Get back!
Get off!
- Get moving!
- [snarling]
Let's go!
Come on!
[roars]
- [panting]
- [train horn blaring]
Get up here.
They... They don't like fire.
They don't like it at all.
What are those things?
Near as I can tell,
most of them used to be people.
Maybe some got lost crossing the plains.
Or maybe others got off the train
at the wrong place.
I don't know.
This... This has happened before?
Happens every now and then.
The train loses steam always at this spot.
And then it's like
a kind of door opens up out there.
I figure it leads to some other world.
[dramatic music playing]
Sir... best not to mention this to anyone.
They won't believe you anyway.
[creatures growling]
[theme music playing]