[theme music playing]
[thunder crashes then rolling]
- [officer] That's it. Let's go.
- [man grunts]
[indistinct chatter]
[Mantus] Ma'am.
Ma'am, I'm gonna need you to answer me.
Ma'am, please pay attention.
The more you withhold information,
the harder this gets for you.
How long have you been here?
Ma'am!
Do the landlords know you're living here?
- Tell us who else is helping you.
- [Ruth] Please.
[Mantus] Are there any more
families in this area?
Stop.
[Mantus]
You realize what you're doing is illegal.
We're not hurting anyone.
We're just trying to live.
[Pentle] Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
That's all of them.
They were all inside
when we breached the door.
Hell, I don't even think these kids
have ever seen outside.
See this?
They made a bassinet out of a drawer.
Resourceful.
- Did you get photos for the prosecutor?
- Got them.
- [Briggs] Good.
- [Pentle] Mm-hm.
All right then. Go ahead, take them in.
- I'll deal with the kids.
- [Pentle] Got it.
Come on, lady! Let's go!
[Soran] Get up!
- Move.
- [Ruth] Please, please.
Sir, we're not doing anything wrong.
- [Pentle] Out!
- We're just trying to live.
They're just children.
- [Soran] Quiet!
- Please! They haven't had breakfast!
- [Soran] Open it up.
- [Ruth] They need to have breakfast!
[thunder rolling]
[dramatic music playing]
Sorry, kids.
[gun cocks]
[man over radio]
Possible 808 down city from Angel Tower.
Mother and partner. Armed.
Harboring at least two
unregistered offspring.
730 east side of Mott at Canal.
Gang of four, ages 8 to 10.
Situation resolved.
Request disposal units.
[opera music playing]
[vocalizing]
[cheering]
[Alice]
I thought you weren't gonna make it.
I wouldn't miss this.
Was it a bad one?
- What, the call?
- Mm.
Usual crazies.
Just breeders, not armed or anything.
It was... easy.
Well, I can't imagine stopping
the rejoo treatments just like that.
I mean, why give all this up?
I've just spent 20 years
perfecting that solo.
And it was beautiful, Alice,
just beautiful.
[Briggs chuckles]
So not having kids
seems a small price to pay
for getting to live forever.
Well, we can't keep letting people
into this party if no one ever leaves.
[Alice] That reminds me.
I have my boost tomorrow.
Can you take me?
Yeah.
Yeah, what the hell.
Pentle can cover for me.
Great.
You know,
if we weren't gonna live forever...
I'd marry you.
If we weren't gonna live forever,
I'd let you get me pregnant.
Your face. Don't be so serious.
There she is. Alice, darling,
you simply must come with me.
No protesting.
[crowd applauding]
[Maria] Everyone, everyone.
Here's to Alice.
In the final moments, it was her execution
of Telogo's infamous solo
that made our performance resonate
so strongly with the critics.
For over a century,
Banini's interpretation
of the work has been...
I never thought anyone
would conquer that ancient dinosaur.
[crowd laughing]
So to commemorate the end of an era,
a small token...
[crying]
...for Alice!
- Our slayer of dinosaurs.
- [crowd cheering and applauding]
[Alice] Are you okay?
Yeah.
I just need a little rest is all.
Hold my hand.
[inhales deeply]
[gasps then exhales]
[dramatic music playing]
[Alice] I feel so good.
- Come on.
- What, right now?
Oh, yes, right now.
You know how I feel
after a rejoo treatment.
Alice, just hang on.
Just hang on.
Hang on.
[ominous music playing]
Stop.
Why?
I'm sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I just...
I can't do this. Not right now.
[Alice scoffs]
Such a bore.
[dramatic music playing]
[Pentle] She couldn't stop it from crying.
Didn't know what to do with it.
Didn't know how to make it calm down.
Well, that's when the neighbors heard.
Thought it was a dog at first.
What did these breeders
think would happen?
The noise those things make.
I don't know if going off rejoo
makes them stupid...
- [Soran] Come on.
- ...or if they're just born that way.
You child killer.
- Murderer.
- [Soran] Hey, that's it.
Coward!
- [Mantus] He's got my gun!
- You fucking monster!
[Mantus] We got him.
[Pentle] You okay, Briggs?
That guy nearly blew a hole in you.
[Soran] Weapon secured. Weapon secured.
[Pentle] You okay?
Briggs?
[thunder rolling]
[dramatic music playing]
[child crying]
[breathing deeply]
[ominous music playing]
[door opens then closes]
[gasps]
Oh, yes, this is a fine, fine piece.
You'd never guess
it was over 200 years old.
[coins clattering]
Bet you sell a lot of those.
Mm. Not many. Not now.
Not many collectors around
for that sort of thing.
Not anymore.
Yeah. Of course.
Did you want to look
at the rest of the dinosaur stock?
No. Not a collector.
[engine revving]
[dramatic music playing]
[birds chirping]
[car door closes]
[gibbering]
[ominous music playing]
[gasping]
It's okay. Sit.
Please, sit.
I just want to ask you some questions.
- Smoke?
- No.
Ah, right.
Bad for the, uh...
Why do you do it?
Why do people like you
keep having these kids?
Why?
Because I'm not so in love with myself
that I just want to live forever and ever.
And this is living?
Here?
- Keeping it locked up...
- Her.
Her name... is Melanie.
[Melanie gibbers]
- [gibbering]
- Okay.
[dramatic music playing]
You're smiling.
She's cute.
You feel something, don't you?
You've got to know
this can't possibly work.
I've been alive 218 years.
I've seen... too much.
But she makes everything new.
I love seeing things
through her little eyes.
[gibbering]
They're so bright.
They're so full of life.
Not dead.
Like yours.
[Melanie gibbering]
I remember her first steps.
I remember her first laugh.
I remember the first time
she called me Mommy.
I remember all these moments
because I know I won't have many.
[gibbers]
[gibbering]
She wants your hat.
[continues gibbering]
[giggles]
She wants to put it on your head.
It's a game she plays.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Melanie crying]
No! No, no.
No, please. Please, she's just a child.
Please don't, she's just a child.
Please. Don't shoot her.
Take me. Shoot me instead.
I'll make room. Do it. Do it!
Kill me instead. I'll make room.
[gasping and whimpering]
[footsteps leaving]
[crying]
[Melanie crying]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[gasping]
- [groans]
- [thuds]
[theme music playing]