♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 29
Well.
He's really strong.
Come on, buddies!
We have nearly defeated him!
Bet is a bet.
You win.
You're more powerful than I thought.
You're now the winner.
You don't need to taunt us.
If we had been powerful,
why would our governor have sacrificed himself?
Gongsun Heng is a hero.
You know nothing!
I just... I just envy him
having bros like you to fight for him.
His sacrifice is worthwhile.
Why are you laughing?
At that time,
I was drinking with Changge like this.
We later became brothers.
Brothers?
How can you be her brother?
Can't I?
You're really an interesting guy.
Come on. Let's drink!
Don't you drink?
Ask someone to clean up here
otherwise we might be driven away.
Cheers!
Come on!
Just set it here.
Okay.
Come with me.
Your Highness.
Mr. Wei, you're here.
See.
It's grand here.
When I saw the palace,
I knew that as long as it was lightened,
even the palaces in Changan would be overshadowed.
Your Highness, the curfew is in force
so how could you do such an absurd thing?
Oh, yes.
There's a curfew here.
So there's no high buildings with lights along this road, right?
Your Highness.
It's the routine.
Please do not let others get the goods on you.
If you keep it secret, who else knows it?
Can Father monitor me far from here?
Have you thought
how many people could notice the brilliant lights here?
Could they all keep it secret?
Do you want to be impeached by the officials?
It's enough!
As long as you can keep it secret,
nobody else will care about it!
Curfew...
The rest of Luoyang is all under curfew.
By the way, what I've done
is all to pray for the refugees.
[The Grandest]
From now on, Ziwei Palace will be out of the darkness.
Your Highness...
[Luoyang Office]
Princess, what about telling Mr. Hao first?
If he finds out I let you leave alone,
he might kill me.
He looks scary but he won't hurt you.
What are you afraid of?
Just tell him I've gone to South Hill
and he won't press about it.
I'll make an early return.
- Princess!
- Do what I've told you.
Are you going to South Hill again?
Mr. Hao.
She hopes you can accompany her to streets and markets.
Though she's been in Luoyang for long,
she has no time to wander around here
for worrying about the crown prince.
Weren't you going to walk around?
Let's go.
Is he an old hand at flattering kids?
Yuan really likes him.
We fail to get Young Master's news as we're in Luoyang.
Mr. Qin might be sad about it.
Though Yuan is a kid, she's sensible.
We're not sure about whether
Mr. Qin plays with her or Yuan makes him happy?
Miser.
Whom are you calling?
You're envying him.
I'm not.
Need another fight.
Good!
Pretty nice!
I want to go there.
- Okay.
- Awesome!
Once again!
Nice!
I want to go there!
Colored umbrellas!
Colored umbrellas here!
I want it!
One, please.
[Cheese Zhang]
I want one!
So do I!
Don't be crowded!
Don't jostle!
Hao Du.
As the shop is quite popular,
the food here must be delicious.
Please give me one!
Two, please!
So many people there stop me getting inside.
Could you buy it for me?
Mind out.
Don't push!
I want to buy it as well.
Fine.
Then stay here.
Don't leave here.
- One more, please!
- Hold on.
Here's the money.
I have the money for it.
Princess!
Ready or not?
Is it my turn?
I want to buy some!
Which taste do you want?
Sweet.
- Sir! Ready or not?
- I want it, too!
Hurry up! Two, please!
Excuse me.
Changge.
So many people here. Let's find another place to talk.
Leyan.
You have changed a lot.
How dare you come out like this in the past?
You're the same. Always make fun of me.
I don't.
I'm just happy for you.
You always hid behind others.
You were too timid and needed protection.
You're quite different now.
I know what I want.
I want to be the princess of Tang.
A real princess.
I don't want to see people starving
or kids having no rice to eat.
I want to be like you.
I want to be a girl fearing nothing.
Leyan, you're really different.
Someone told me
I could walk around for I was a man.
But I still can walk around as I'm a girl.
No matter who you're,
the one who likes rabbits or the one who wants to be a princess,
you can be whoever you want.
- And mine!
- Don't push!
Don't push me!
Is mind ready?
[Cheese Zhang]
- I want two, please.
- Princess!
Leyan!
Don't push!
Ready or not, Sir?
I've experienced so many things all the way here.
I thought I would embrace you
and cry bitterly after I met you.
Well, now for me, it's not a big deal.
Quite right.
We've all grown up.
Changge.
Where do you live?
How can I find you later on?
I'm now in Liuyun Taoist Temple.
You don't need to find me specially
for I'll sometimes come to South Hill.
It means we can meet again.
By the way, Hao Du is now in the town.
You need to be careful when you're out.
He'll catch you as soon as he sees you.
Hao... Hao Du... Changge, I have to go now.
Be cautious.
Watch out!
Oh, come on.
♫ My fate brings me nothing ♫
♫ but loneliness. ♫
I... saw someone was selling sugar figurines
so I went to buy one for I was greedy...
I wasn't on purpose to leave...
I know I'm wrong. Sorry about that.
I won't do that again.
Here you are.
♫ Love you at our first meeting. ♫
♫ It's a lifelong matter for me. ♫
♫ What is love? ♫
♫ It's our common instinct. ♫
I... I thought I lost you.
You didn't.
I...
You said it's for me.
Not mad now?
Hao Du.
You're not as cold as your look.
Is that right?
Hao Du.
Where are my desserts?
- I've eaten them.
- Eaten?
I didn't ask you to do so.
Nothing left?
Answer my question.
Hao Du.
Hao Du!
Mr. Du.
Greet to your Highness.
Why are you here?
His Majesty has gotten the news of Princess's arrival in Luoyang
but he is still worried about you.
That's why I'm here personally
to see whether you're fine or not.
You... His Majesty could be at ease now.
Never mind.
Thanks for your care.
As it's getting dark,
you'd better have an early rest.
You didn't let his Majesty down at last.
As you've found her, I could be at ease now.
Father.
We haven't seen for just a few days.
What's the matter...
As I'm old,
it's easier for me to get sick.
But it doesn't matter.
Place what's in your hand properly.
Let's have a talk in the main hall.
Yes.
Father.
You're not only to visit Princess here, right?
Yes. But also to deal with my privacy.
Tell me what she has experienced.
I finally found her as I was in Luoyang.
She's suffered a lot.
She walked from the border to Luoyang all the way.
Well, it's good that you've found her.
It's not peaceful here.
Escort her back to Changan early next morning.
What?
Any problems?
No.
But...
Don't beat around the bush. Get to the point.
Letting her stay in Luoyang to appease people
is better than asking her to go back.
Someone told me that his Highness...
As Princess is here,
the refugees could be under the control.
What's wrong with Crown Prince?
He...
He's felt unwell for a long time
and everything about the disaster relief
is all up to Princess.
People here trust Princess more.
In order to stabilize the situation,
please allow her to stay in Luoyang
and do what she likes.
I will give her a close supervision.
Nothing will go amiss.
Hao Du.
You really take her into consideration.
Of course.
She's the princess after all.
Is it the only reason?
When I was as young as you,
I always failed to know
my mind or the mind of others.
Father.
- I didn't.
- You don't need to explain.
I won't interfere in young people's matters.
Have some tea.
Princess?
Or Leyan?
What do I want?
Good!
Nice job!
Come here.
Here you are.
You... It's you!
Your Highness, we meet again.
Your Highness.
Mr. Wei is here again.
I'm chatting with my old friend.
Why is he here?
Sorry for hindering your time.
Farewell, your Highness.
Don't leave!
Your Highness!
I see!
If you're free,
why not go to South Hill to help my sister?
How can a man like you let a lady zoom around in South Hill?
I'm ashamed of you!
Your Highness!
Madam.
Greet to Madam.
Here's what's sent from Ziwei Palace.
[The Book of Songs]
As I've seen you, what else should I complain?
It seems to be a good choice
to ask Sheng Xin go to meet him.
Cui Tong.
Yes.
Everything in Luoyang is dry recently.
I'm afraid it'll have a blazing fire.
Yes, Madam.
My girl,
I don't think you should always come to see me.
Don't worry. Hao Du won't know it.
Changge.
Minister Du is now in Luoyang. Be cautious as you're out.
I think you'd better stay here
rather than go out.
I could do nothing with the past.
But from now on,
I'll keep you safe at all costs.
I'll look after myself.
You too.
Here you are. Be careful.
Slow down.
Thank you, sister.
You need to have a good rest.
- Your wound can't be delayed anymore.
- Okay.
Have a try.
It won't hinder your action.
Thank you so much.
My wound is almost healed.
It's said you're a noble from Changan.
I don't think you're a noble.
I think you're a Bodhisattva.
Oh, my wife. She's a princess. How noble she is!
The heavens bless our nation!
Your Highness is as kindhearted as a Bodhisattva!
Don't be like this.
It is said those from Liuyun Temple are very kind.
I think there's still a Bodhisattva here!
He's right!
That's it!
We've seen all the nobles from Luoyang
only except the crown prince...
Actually, he cares for you.
That's why I'm here to look after you.
That's why it's said
his Highness stays in Ziwei Palace in seclusion
with the lights on all night.
Well, he's praying for us.
But it's a palace of the former dynasty...
Is it really a blessing for us?
Forget it. Just remember he's praying for us.
- He's right!
- I agree!
His Highness must do it for the good of us!
Thanks, Bodhisattva!
Ms. Quan, what are you doing?
It's said there's an abnormal astronomical phenomena in Luoyang
and a conflagration will break out in three days.
Though it's hearsay, we still need to be on guard for many people here.
Changge.
About the conflagration...
Don't be too worried.
It's just a hearsay.
These refugees have left their hometown
and now they can have an unclaimed field to farm.
It's a way of living for them.
Here's not the unclaimed lands.
It's Liuyun Taoist Temple's fields.
The rich in Luoyang are worried about their unknown backgrounds
so they dare not let them farm.
But Master cares nothing about it.
She lends them not only fields
but also grains and foods.
She's really a Bodhisattva of Luoyang.
Changge.
Brother Shuyu.
Last time, we parted in Weishui.
How are you these days?
I'm fine.
Everything is okay.
I'll be fine as long as you're okay.
When did you come back?
Why hadn't you told me?
And why are you now with Yan?
Where had you gone?
- And...
- Wei Shuyu.
You have too many questions.
Fine. I'll ask nothing.
I won't ask you.
Everything will be fine as long as you're okay.
As you're here, will you leave again?
I don't know.
It's not my home.
I can go nowhere.
You can come with us!
After the things here are settled,
we can return to Changan together.
You, Yan and I can stay together like before.
Changge.
Li Changge has died.
You can call me A'Li.
No matter what you are called,
you are always my Changge.
I'm really glad to see
you're the same as before,
staying together and looking after each other.
Chang...
A'Li.
Can we have a private conversation?
I still have many refugees to nurse
so I can't chat with you.
As you come with Crown Prince,
you must have many things to do.
But...
Anyway,
I won't leave here at once.
You can take Leyan out of here first.
We still have chances to chat later on.
Master.
Luoyang became rife with rumors these days.
It's said there must be a conflagration in three days.
As the good and the bad mix up together,
if someone wants to make a trouble,
I'm afraid it'll do harm to us.
I hope you could have an early plan.
Don't worry.
Everything has its own fate.
It's good for you to know what to do.
No.
I don't know what to do.
A'Li.
Even if it's a fish, I dare not tell you
I can control all its actions.
So how can I control humans?
Reckoning accurately or finding a foolproof way
all depends on one's skills.
The Tao should be the core.
What does it mean?
How can't you save someone in need right in front of you?
If you decide to save, it means you can't plan for the future.
Then so what?
Tao only depends on your heart.
Take the consequences.
Everyone in the world should obey it.
[Luoyang Office]
Brother Shuyu.
Brother Shuyu?
What are you thinking?
Nothing.
By the way,
Crown Prince parties in Ziwei Palace everyday.
If he keeps on doing so, things will go wrong.
He's spoiled.
If you...
If you don't know what to do, go to tell Minister Du.
He fears them the most.
Nowadays,
the refugees in South Hill start to discuss it.
If he keeps acting recklessly,
what should we do?
Does Changge know he's here?
Are you worried she will make troubles with him?
You don't believe her!
I promise she won't do such things.
I know.
Your Highness.
Have you found him?
Report to Your Highness.
He says that you need to pick him out first
and then he will come to meet you.
Okay.
Nice.
It's so interesting.
Tell me! What are the rules?
You can do whatever you want
except getting close or talking to them.
Can't get close...
Fine.
Watch what I do, then you try!
Yes.
Do it.
It's you! You're the one I want!
Your Highness is so smart.
Sheng Xin greets to your Highness.
Stand up.
Nice.
I want you to stay with me!
Your Highness, please let us all stay with you.
More people, more fun.
You're right.
Okay. You can all stay.
Thanks, Your Highness.
Minister Du.
[East of the city; South and North street]
Thank you.
Do you want to find Mr. Li?
Well, maybe he isn't at home.
He isn't in Luoyang?
Yes, he is.
Maybe he's at the tea-house in West Market
or at the tavern in the South Market.
He could be anywhere in Luoyang except his home.
He's in Luoyang but out of home all the time?
No one can tell whether he'll return during the curfew.
I've heard that he married a shrewish woman.
How can't he hide outside?
Minister.
Mr. Wei.
Why do you come in a hurry?
Report to Minister Du.
I've already dealt out all the relief funds and materials.
Now the situation here is getting better.
But...
Go ahead.
But Crown Prince hasn't come out since he moved to Ziwei Palace.
It's Princess Yongan who's in charge of everything.
People are starting to gossip about it.
And...
And he mixes with a group of jugglers all day...
Absurd!
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
What about you, Sheng Xin?
It's glad to hear that.
Unfortunately, I forgot to bring a recorder with me;
otherwise I would let him record all that you've done for the people
and report to his Majesty.
Minister Du.
My father is busy with affairs everyday.
It's unnecessary to let him know such a trifle.
There's a hearsay
your Highness indulges in the lavish lifestyle everyday.
At this rate, his Majesty will finally know it.
Minister Du, I feel grateful to listen to your advice.
Thanks for the trouble.
He's my friend in Luoyang.
If you're unsatisfied with it,
I'll ask him to go back where he comes.
I hope you can behave yourself.
Your Highness.
If you want me to leave,
you can tell me straight.
As I've seen you, what else should I complain about?
It's my great honor
to see such a brilliant person like your Highness.
I've told him that
I'll ask you to go back where you come.
As you're a young musician of Taichang Temple in Changan,
where else should you go back except Changan?
Thanks, your Highness!
I've already searched there and here.
Where's Ashile Sun? Aren't we going to find her?
He went out before dawn.
He has a map of Luoyang.
He goes to find and then crosses out one by one.
As he finished, he'll then start a new round.
How can he find her by the aimless search?
Everything depends on us.
Sorry.
Unaware.
You smart girl.
Wait for my good news!
Let's go.
[Great virtues match heaven and earth.]
A'Li, do you like the dishes today?
A'Li, it's no good for you to stay here all day.
Let's go to buy some medicines and you can limber up.
I think it's pretty nice to stay here. A self-cultivation.
Then it'll be good.
That's it.
Sit well, please.
- Okay.
- A'Li...
[Liuyun Taoist Temple]
Don't be narrow-minded.
Do you know what I've learned today?
I feel tired after walking all day.
Well, massage my legs and then I'll tell you.
Are you unwilling?
I think you're really pert.
We rent the house and asked for news.
So don't you think...
Cut them.
Then you won't be tired.
Any clues?
I'll let you off this time.
Yes. There's one.
It's said a Taoist called Sun Simiao
came from the grasslands
and saved a young lady at pains.
Isn't Commandant Li a young lady?
What else?
Why are you not surprised?
I don't think you know it.
Cut the crap!
Any other news?
His whereabouts are always unknown.
It's known he will diagnose refugees
but no one knows where he's now.
Any shelters for the refugees in Luoyang
A place called Liuyun Taoist Temple in South Hill.
Liuyun Taoist Temple?
Why did he run away again?
Anyone's here?
Sir.
There's no visit today.
Only people with acute diseases are allowed in.
Could you do me a favor? I'm here to find a lady.
Is there anyone called Li Changge?
Or Li Shisi?
Li Changge?
There's no Li Changge here.
I think you've come to the wrong place.
Please leave at once.
What about Sun Simiao? Is Sun Simiao here?
How can you call Taoist Sun's name?
That's it! Taoist Sun!
Has he saved a lady?
He's saved innumerable people
so how can I remember all of them?
Please forgive my offense.
Changge!
You intruder! I'll call others to catch you!
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad