[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 28]
You really didn't hear what we said?
Feeling guilty now?
Were you speaking ill of me
just now?
How could I?
Do I look like that kind of guy?
Let's get down to business.
Why are you here today?
Ling Yushi.
What's your relationship?
We're friends.
Friends?
How long have you known each other?
How much do you know about her sister?
Why do you look familiar?
The air turbulence in the Graveyard was so strong.
I've just got out. I'm all mixed up now.
I'm drawing a blank here.
Why do you want to learn so much about her?
To help her, of course.
Don't you think we need to help her?
Look,
she's nice and beautiful. She's also talented.
It's a pity
she's got something on her mind.
Her sister's incidents must be a blow to her.
How're you going to help her?
Lie to her.
Lie?
It doesn't hurt if I
get one more elder sister.
You're so kind.
We thought as soon as she woke up
she would figure out what happened to me first.
It turned out that
you are her priority.
That what she's like.
She seems to be rash
and headstrong.
But she's warmhearted and kind.
She cares more about me than anyone else.
She asked me a lot of things.
I worried I might give it away.
So, I said I couldn't remember.
What do we do now?
Let's go ahead with it.
Yiyuan,
will you do me a favour?
She used to annoy me.
But now,
well,
since you had asked me to find out about her sister,
my memory came back
as she told me about her.
Qianqian, it turns out that
I've been to the Scarlet Tide Continent before.
I met you there.
We fell in love at first sight.
We agreed to get married.
We travelled together
to Ling Town,
where we met Ling Yushi and Qin Lie.
Yushi
had been missing her sister so much that
she mistook you for her sister.
We got along well with each other.
I had pity on her.
So, I regarded her as my elder sister.
We didn't expect that
Ling Town got a massive attack from the spirit beasts.
We helped them fought with the beasts.
There's a spirit beast in the far north
called the Love Eaters.
They feed on the feelings of beloved ones.
We were attacked by this beast.
We got lost and never managed to
recognise each other ever since.
Are you lying to me?
If you've changed your mind
and don't want to be with me anymore,
you can call that a lie.
I shouldn't suspect you.
We won't get separated anymore.
I've always been thinking about you.
Even my feelings were eaten up.
I still remember you.
Why don't you remember me
like I do?
Does that mean I love you
more than you love me?
No, it doesn't.
The beasts which attacked us
were a mother and a son.
The son ate you and I got its mother.
She ate up more feelings than her son.
Oh, that's why.
You've suffered a lot.
That's nothing.
Let's go to find my sister now.
Don't give it away.
Sister.
You really are my sister.
I'm sorry.
I forgot who you are earlier on.
I'm your sister.
Never say sorry to your sister.
Sister,
although I can't remember what happened in Ling Town.
It doesn't matter.
I can call you my sister again.
If I ever forget, I'll do it again.
You'll always be my sister
no matter what.
Ok.
We'll return to Ling Town together.
There there. Stop crying.
Did I act that well?
I was just moved by you.
You pretended it so well.
I almost started to believe
you've picked up your memory.
Don't you forget.
I'm a talented student of the Illusory Demon Sect.
Just stop acting.
When she hugged me,
it really felt like she's my sister.
If she asks me to do anything,
I'll do for her.
Don't...
Don't cry.
Please don't cry.
Fine.
Let's cry together.
I'll look after her. You can have some rest.
The Night Fairy,
what do you want to tell me?
Is it about Gongmu Lie?
I need to know
what happened after I left you.
Kid,
are you lost?
Where's your family?
Gongmu Lie.
Qin Lie.
Tingyu.
Yes. I do love Qin Lie.
I don't need a reason. I just love him.
I see.
Song Tingyu,
thank you.
We'll protect Gongmu Lie
together in the future.
You are me
and me you.
When I was on the Land of Far North,
looking at the moon obscured by the clouds,
I was ambitious.
I made up my mind
that I would get to somewhere higher
to enjoy the star-lit sky.
We first met
in Ling Town
during the Moon Festival.
I had the same ambition.
I also hoped to see what's behind the clouds.
You're the only one
who shared the same goal with me.
We were heading toward the same goal
but we took different paths.
Only at that time.
I was willing to die for Ling Town.
You wanted to fight for Nebula Pavilion.
But after we fought so many times,
we ended up being on the same boat.
Just a coincidence.
You asked Li Mu to take me here.
Wasn't it because you want to humiliate me?
Every time I see the bright moon,
it always reminds me of you
who gave this opportunity.
You're Du Shaoyang.
You don't need my help.
Even if I hadn't requested the extra sword token,
you would still be able to sit here
and enjoy the moonlight.
When did you start to respect me like this?
I realised that only if we work together,
can we achieve great things.
We're friends but we're also enemies.
Neither of us is willing to be outshined.
We just can't work well together.
Only one of us
can shine brightly.
But only if we cooperate,
can we fight against the darkness.
In the beginning, you
were just a novice in Ling Town.
But you were willing to
fight hard for what you cared about.
As the Pavilion Master,
I was always hesitant.
Maybe at that time, I really envied you.
I envied that you were just nobody.
Everyone
can choose what to fight for.
It's terrible
if one doesn't know where his dream is.
There we are, Senior Brother.
You didn't even ask me to join you!
Am I your buddy or not?
Why don't you go to sleep?
It's a lovely night.
What're you talking about?
These nonsense about the moon and stars.
Senior Brother,
you're dashing.
Let me guess,
at least three ladies like you.
Even if Song Tingyu doesn't admit it,
I know she likes you.
Shut up. Let's drink.
I wish I could be as talkative as you.
I've been interrogating Duan all day.
I got nothing from him.
What do you want to know?
Let me help you.
I'll blow him up if he doesn't say anything.
Just stop it.
Those Bombs are expensive.
You think you're playing fireworks?
I don't care about money.
Look at yourselves.
You're dull but women still like you.
I'm rich, handsome,
and powerful.
Why doesn't anyone like me?
That's just not fair!
There there, Brother Chu.
You're Master of Love in the Void Realm.
Please take my respect.
You're flattering me.
Willing to give in like this?
What does that mean, Saintess Song?
Qin Lie already starts to strike up a relationship
with the Terminator Sect and
the Illusory Demon Sect
as soon as he comes to the Land of Chaos
from the Scarlet Tide Continent.
Seeing someone who
used to be nothing but a murderer of your father
outshining you,
you must feel bitter.
I always know you
are good at sowing discords.
I'm just wondering
what made you say so
today.
After all, you still love...
Qin Lie?
He's nothing to me.
You really think you're friends now?
You're willing to let go of the grudges
just because you drank together?
I never sell you short, Du Shaoyang.
You're as ambitious as Qin Lie.
What now?
Going to regard him as your Big Brother?
Hoping that he could help you?
Siqi,
why don't you wake up?
You said you were going to stay with me,
no matter what.
I'm so worried
seeing you lying here.
I worry that you might not ever wake up again.
You won't blame me,
teach me,
plot against me anymore.
You said
you didn't want me to make any choice
I would later regret.
What do I have to lose
if I won't feel regret?
Siqi,
as long as you wake up,
you can do whatever you like.
Shaoyang.
Siqi.
I don't want you to go.
Who said
"Siqi, as long as you wake up,
you can do whatever you like."
I see.
Men like you are just liars.
No men will accept
a request like this!
But Yushi is in trouble.
I won't just sit around and do nothing.
That's her own business.
Qin Lie should help her. It has nothing to do with you.
Men can't help with this.
You can't, either.
You just woke up. I can't let you go.
Qin Lie looked down upon you.
I want to stand up for you. So I woke up.
Everyone will soon know about the fact
that we got out from the Graveyard alive.
We can't stay here any longer.
As long as we get back to the
Heavenly Slaughter Continent,
the Illusory Demon Sect will make sure we're safe.
Let's stick to our plan then.
Don't linger
no matter whether we win or lose.
That's a tough guy.
Thank you.
No worries. Just leave it to us.
I've bought off the manager.
We'll leave this afternoon.
How did you manage to do that?
Duan Qianjie bribed him with
ten thousand spirit stones.
How much did you give?
Ten thousand?
I offered ten times of this.
Guys, bad news.
They're auctioning
a piece of breaking news at the auction house.
What news?
Our whereabouts.
It's you?
Of course not.
I don't dare to offend him
even if I took ten thousand spirit stones
from Duan Qianjie.
How could you
cover up big news like this?
It's complicated.
Who's selling the news?
Who is the most well-informed
on the Land of Chaos?
My people.
I know how to find them.
Leave it to me.
We need to split up.
8000 spirit stones from the Xiahou Family.
Brother, 10,000 premium spirit stones
from the Celestial Artefact Sect.
Tell me only it's over ten thousand.
What's the big news they want to sell? That's a lot.
Do you live here?
Who are you?
You've earned so much.
Why don't you buy a house?
That's none of your business.
You will go with me first.
Let us go! Help! Help!
Let go of us!
Help! Help!
Wanna fight with Yushi?
You like her.
I'm not interested in her.
Well,
how about me?
That's my robe.
It's got your scent.
I don't want to have sex with you.
You're infected by the Voodoo insect.
You don't have that in your heart then?
Then why do you feel butterflies?
I'm thinking about killing you.
Why don't you just
have a bite of me?
Then you can decide if you want to kill.
You're too naive
to seduce me.
I'm just shy.
You're not even good-looking.
You're so mean.
You will only be able to trade
a bottle of wine with your body.
Wanna get the Scripture of Nine Hells?
You wish.
Fine.
Shall we make a deal?
You want to bribe me
since you can't seduce me?
What's this?
No one can get ancient dead bodies
from the Graveyard of the Gods.
But one can always get some other
treasures.
There's nothing like this
spirit stone in this world.
Since there's nothing like it,
how could it be a treasure?
I'm the Senior Sister of the
Celestial Artefact Sect.
I'm the student of Master Mohai.
Even if you have no regard for
the Scarlet Tide Continent,
you must respect Master Mohai.
I admit he's not bad.
Now you can believe
I am able to recognise it if
it doesn't belong to this world.
Tell me about it.
This is called the Shadowless Stone.
You can steal everything valuable
in this world without being detected.
Even masters several levels above
won't find out about it.
Can I trade this for your Scripture
of Nine Hells?
I don't need to steal from others.
It is said that
you can steal women's hearts with it.
You can't win everyone's heart.
Get away from me.
Or I'll take off all your clothes
and send you to the manager.
Fine, you win.
What if Sister can't handle those three kids?
She will be fine.
Here they come.
Where are the kids?
They're in the room.
Tang Siqi hasn't returned yet?
No.
Did she fail?
She can't be.
Let's go out and have a look.
What's going on?
It's just a fight.
Such a big audience.
Let's do it quickly.
Wait a minute.
Give us the Scripture of Nine Hell first.
That's unfair if you won't take it out
or give me either.
Right then.
I see. You like it this way.
You were plotting against me?
I told you.
The Shadowless Stone can help you
steal everything in this world.
You didn't believe me.
You can steal women's hearts
with this stone.
You can't win everyone's heart.
I know I'm not good-looking enough
to seduce you.
I was just pretending.
I just let your guard down
so that I can steal from you.
Manager.
Here I am.
Wanna escape?
Farewell.
You betrayed me
even if I gave you ten thousand?
Someone gave me twenty thousand.
What's wrong?
We're getting pleased too soon.
Look up.
A bad penny.
Here we are, again.
Who are you, Duan Qianjie?
I forgot to tell you.
These cities near Heavenly Calamity Continent
are also under my jurisdiction.
Our Master once told us
there's a mysterious inspection department
regulating all the sects.
You're the one in charge.
Can we re-launch the teleportation?
Maybe I can help you with that.
We've now returned it to you.
Thank you.
What do you want exactly?
Her.
Duan Qianjie,
we don't want to fight with you.
Besides,
you don't want to kill us, right?
Give her to me.
Or...
The Spirit Pillars.
It doesn't work.
Is yours broken?
Master Duan,
you've always been hoping to compete with me.
How about...
I'm not interested anymore.
I only want her now.
Fine. I'll go with you.
Shut up.
I don't know why
you sent troops to besiege us.
You're spies.
I've never seen someone
so shameless as you are.
You're the one who stole from my sister.
You're just abusing your power to
take revenge on us.
She's right.
Bullshit!
I don't care if you're in charge here.
I don't know about
this stone, either.
I don't care about who you are.
How could you offend the Chu family
and the Terminator Sect?
Since you killed my people,
I'll charge you with the crime of treason.
Will you be able to
take that?
Ridiculous.
Step aside.
What's going on?
This is the Realm of Ruins outside all realms.
This is the birthplace of the Nether Race.
I'm Chongming, the current Mother of the Earth.
She's my daughter, Wuchun.
He's the successor of the
Gongmu family, Gongmu Lie.
You two were forced to sleep
in order to save your race.
Men are born to be kind and evil.
I'm afraid that even if you can wake up one day,
your memories will have been all wiped out.
They can be used by someone evil.
Therefore, I took down your story
with my last power.
I've kept them in the Scripture of Nine Hells.
I've set a rule for it.
The second volume of the Scripture will only open
when Wuchun and Gongmu Lie reunites
and the four spirit artefacts
are collected.
Here are the four spirit artefacts.
The Mother of the Earth rules the Nether Race.
The title gets passed on to each generation.
The Realm of Ruins is full of dazzling treasures.
We're grateful to be born on this land.
We don't dare to keep these treasures by ourselves.
We need to make good use of the resources.
Hence, we trade with the leader of the Human Race,
the Gold rank force.
We supply the Human Race with gemstones,
so that their living standard got improved.
I come to find the Mother of the Earth.
Do you recognise me?
The Young Master of the Gongmu family, Gongmu Lie.
You were a kid when we first met.
You're a grown-up now.
Why do you pay a visit again?
I heard that the Ghost Eye Race,
one of the Nether Race
can collect information of all kinds.
What information do you want to know?
About my father.
The god of war, Gongmu Hao.
It is said that your father died \nduring the war of the God Race.
I don't believe it.
You think
the Gold rank force hid the truth from you?
No one in the Spirit Realm will speak about it,
not even my grandpa.
The world is such a chaos.
That information is true and false.
His spirit never dies.
Stop beating around the bush.
The Realm of Ruins never interfere
with the Spirit Realm.
The Ghost Eye Race only gather
information of our race.
If you won't help me,
I'll make one more step further
to destroy the Realm of Ruins.
Where's Wuchun?
She's my daughter. You've met before.
Why's she involved?
Wuchun will be the next Mother of Earth.
I want to know what she will do about this.
I love you.
I am your true love.
I am.
I am. I love her more than you do.
Don't force me!
Both of you said you love me.
How...how
would I know who to choose?
What is she doing?
Telling who is sincere and who is not.
She is the most insincere person in this world.
Choose me!
I am the one that truly loves you!
It's not my fault.
Both of you said
you truly love me.
But you run for your life at this critical time.
Gongmu Lie wants us to help him
find about the truth of his father's death.
How are you going to deal with it?
We never interfere with the Spirit Realm
other than supplying them with gemstones.
If we don't agree, he will destroy us.
I thought you would
control your temper as an adult.
Answer my question.
What difference would it make
even if you know the truth?
You can't find him. You can never get him back.
Why?
Because you don't have enough power.
Unless
you have the Crimson Fire to guide you.
I have.