[English subtitles are available.]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 27]
Chu Li, from the Terminator Sect.
Where's Tang Siqi?
Let me introduce him.
This is the Third Heavenly Swordsman,
Yan Baiyi,
the youngest Sword Holder
in the history of Mount Heavenly Sword.
Yan Baiyi.
After we came here,
we went separate ways.
I was looking for you guys,
and I found her first.
But she already got poisoned.
The Black Voodoo Cult.
They wanted to take her away
so I fought back.
But I couldn't do it alone.
Luckily, Yan showed up and saved me.
But we couldn't get Siqi out.
Why did they take her?
According to Yan,
The Black Voodoo Cult use voodoo insects
to control people,
and turn them into killing machines.
Yan, is there any antidote
to the poison?
You can kill the person
that placed the insects.
Then the voodoo will lose its effect.
That's the only way.
The Black Voodoo Cult travel secretively
and they're good at hiding their identities.
It's difficult to find them,
unless you've crossed paths before.
Please help us, Yan.
We need to find them
and rescue Siqi.
If she means this much to you,
I will most definitely help.
I will go with you.
Let's go.
Xuanxuan,
this is the Ling Borough.
We grow up here together.
Do you remember that
we used to play here
and make Qin Lie into a snowman?
Stop.
Could you stop looking at me like that?
It's a bit too much.
I'm not your sister, seriously.
You took me for the wrong person.
This is your hometown?
How did we end up here?
Cut this nonsense out.
My hometown?
This is the Graveyard of Gods.
What tricks are you pulling,
bringing me here?
Wait. Don't get angry.
Let me figure out what's going out.
Sis, maybe you got it wrong.
Maybe she just looks like her.
Don't you guys always say that
I look like Hua Yuxin?
It's exactly because you look like him,
that she said you're on her mind.
That just proves
she is Xuanxuan.
I don't follow.
Do you remember
the Armament Sect's secret state?
The Imaginary Beast.
Yeah, our Spirit Consciousness has great potential.
Everything we see and hear,
everything we think and do
is all controlled by it.
Back then, Qin Lie walked
into the Imaginary Beast's belly first,
so his Spirit Consciousness brought us
to the Purple Mist Sea, the place he yearns to go.
There should be something similar
behind this door.
Xuanxuan was the first
to walk into this door.
Her Spirit Consciousness
brought us to the Ling Borough.
This means that deep down,
she wants to go home.
Oh, I see.
If she's the one who brought us here,
let's just wait and see
where she'd like to go,
and who she'd like to see the most.
I'm sorry.
I just miss my sister too much.
And you really look like her.
So I mistook you for her.
It's fine now, you figured it out.
But,
why did we end up here?
I don't know.
But now that we're here,
we might as well keep walking
and see what we'll see.
Alright.
Deep down,
who is the person you wanna see the most?
Father.
He's your father?
So he's her father too.
Xuanxuan.
Father.
Being apart from loved ones is hard.
Being on the other side is even harder.
I can't bear that
I will forever be apart from my beloved family.
The roads ahead of you might be long and lonely,
feeling scared is nothing but normal.
But my daughter,
please be courageous and carry on.
Father, don't you blame me
for leaving the Ling Borough behind
for my selfish pursuit of love?
No, I don't.
A mother's love for her daughter
is obvious and clear.
But a father's love
is like a snowflake,
you need to look closer
to see how beautiful it is.
Where are we? Who does she wanna see?
Yuxin.
Xuanxuan.
Gee, I do look like him.
You asked me to come here
but kept me waiting for this long.
I'm leaving.
Xuanxuan.
Marry me.
What took you so long?
Do you know how many years
I've waited for that?
My love for you
is as pure as snow.
But you're dead now.
Yuxin.
Xuanxuan.
Why did all those men disappear?
Don't disturb him.
Did you hear anything?
Stop asking him.
He would tell you if he did.
I thought you could help us figure things out
so I followed you here.
Who would knew
the great Qin Lie from the Scarlet Tide Continent,
has absolutely no power here?
Can't even protect your woman.
Du Shaoyang, you...
Let it go.
Don't argue with him.
I don't wanna argue with you either.
I should have killed you in the Nebula Pavilion.
I should have never agreed to work with you.
Du Shaoyang, watch your tone.
You're right.
I should have killed you a long time ago.
Looks like you two are not getting along.
Du, let's get out of here.
Wait.
I might have a way.
Do you wanna try it out?
Xuanxuan.
Yuxin.
Xuan.
Xuanxuan.
Sister,
Yuxin is dead, isn't he?
I couldn't find him.
I couldn't even find his body.
Yuxin.
Where are you?
I haven't even got the chance
to tell you I like you.
How could you leave like this?
Yuxin.
Please come back to me.
Wake up.
You're not Ling Xuanxuan,
you're Pan Qianqian.
Where's Yuxin?
Hua Yuxin.
Come home.
Come home, please.
Come back to me.
Hua Yuxin,
come home.
Yuxin,
come back, please.
You wanna use the Spirit Pillars
to check what's behind that door?
Where am I?
Why can't I remember anything?
My face hurts, why?
We just got attacked
by unknown forces.
We were all knocked out.
Do you really not remember anything?
No.
That's good.
Yeah, that's good.
What's over there?
Yushi. Yiyuan.
Yushi.
Qin Lie.
Xuanxuan.
She's not xuanxuan.
She's from the Illusory Demon Sect,
she just looks like her a lot.
Qin, what are those over there?
They're the bodies of the Ancient Gods.
The bodies from the legend?
Legend has it that the three Masters are
legendary figures in primordial ages.
The Master of Thunder ranked the first,
the Master of Fire the second
and the Master of Ice the third.
Records show that,
the Master of Thunder is the strongest among them
and found a way to control thunders.
The other two Masters
has also reached the Genesis Realm.
As for their race,
although they're human
but their powers reached the highest realm.
So who do you think
these bodies belong to?
Me.
Alright.
The Third Heavenly Swordsman, Yan Baiyi,
has almost never showed up in public.
Nobody knows his age or appearance.
That's why you chose him to deceive us.
Am I correct?
Young Master of the Black Voodoo Cult, Ye Yihao?
I was watching you guys,
[Ye Yihao, the Black Voodoo Cult]
but I didn't notice
when you found out about me.
The Nebula Pavilion.
What's so special about it?
Tang Siqi was poisoned
but Shaoyang looked calm.
I was already wondering why.
Plus, the first time that
I worked with him against a common enemy
was in the Nebula Pavilion.
I noticed those hints,
so I waited quietly
for an opportunity.
Qin Lie.
I don't know
why you didn't follow us right away.
Perhaps you were waiting for enforcement.
But that gave me the time
to tell him everything.
Then,
I whispered it to Yushi.
You poisoned Tang Siqi,
and used it to threaten Du
to get close to us
and attack us from the inside.
I also told them that
you use bells to control poisoned people,
so we need to
restrain your hands once we strike.
How impressive given you're
from the Scarlet Tide Continent.
I underestimated you.
Why plot against us?
You have the Demon Sealing Tombstone.
That's the only way to get out of here.
But, I'm curious about one thing.
I have your girl,
aren't you afraid that I would kill her?
Or maybe, between women and friends,
you choose friends.
Between you and Qin Lie,
of course I pick him.
Such a touching bromance.
Since you've chosen your friend,
don't blame me for hurting your woman.
Siqi.
Xie Jingxuan.
Huang Shuli.
You joined the Black Voodoo Cult?
I follow whoever treats me well.
You conniving bitch.
To think about...
That I even had a crush on you!
I liked you back then.
Qin Lie, let me take the bodies
and use the Tombstone
to open the gate, or I'll kill you.
This is the Graveyard of Gods.
Let us both die here,
right next to the ancient Masters.
What an honor!
Siqi, wake up.
Siqi.
Siqi, it's me.
Siqi,
it's me.
It's me.
Huang Shuli,
how dare you betray your sect and join a cult!
I'll help our Master get rid of scums like you today.
Qin Lie, the Tombstone.
You guys leave. I'll cover for you.
Xuanxuan.
Wuchun.
Turns out, you're me and I'm you.
Hurry. Let's go.
Xuanxuan, follow us.
I got you.
Yushi.
I'm fine.
Where's Xuanxuan?
Yiyuan. Yiyuan.
Stop yelling. I'm right here.
Is everyone okay?
Siqi.
Where's Song Tingyu?
Over there.
Who're you?
Watch out.
He tried to kill us back in the Graveyard of Gods.
Don't.
You can use thunder.
Who the hell are you?
If I wanted to kill you,
you would all be dead now.
Stop talking
or you'll die.
We just overcame great difficulties,
so we'll live a long life.
Follow me.
In your dream.
The Sculptures of Nine Hells.
What?
I heard the Sculptures of Nine Hells.
summoning me from here.
But when I got here,
it already disappeared.
I long heard of the Nether Queen,
Mother of Earth
on the Scarlet Tide Continent.
It's you?
Interesting.
Guess I didn't waste my time coming here.
I trust him.
The Lone Ranger, Duan Qianjie.
Duan Qianjian, your reputation precedes you.
I heard you like to go around picking fights.
Why don't you have a go at me?
I don't mind,
but never met you before.
Well, you met me today. Let's have a fight.
I don't wanna do it today.
Where's the Mother of Earth?
Siqi has a voodoo insect in her,
so she's trying to cure Siqi.
She can deal with voodoo insects?
Interesting, indeed.
I'll wait for her.
You also have voodoo insects?
I wanna have a fight with her.
If she wins,
I'll give this back to her.
Seriously? How shameless.
You're a dude. Don't pick on women.
Please tell her I'll wait for her to have a fight.
Wanna fight me? You're not qualified.
It's not up to you.
You don't get to decide.
The Eye of Frost!
Don't you dare hurt him!
There's a deadly flaw in the Eye of Frost.
You come out at the exact place
where you disappeared.
I just need to wait there
to take your life.
The Eye of Frost? More like the shell of a turtle.
That's why I said, you're not qualified.
How arrogant!
You, go get her.
My power can only
suppress the poison for now,
I can't get rid of it.
You go take care of Duan Qianjie.
Du and I will take over here.
Be careful.
Duan.
She's your sister?
I knew you were following us
in the Graveyard of Gods.
Do you know her?
Why else would I knock her out?
It is because,
there are things you don't want her to know?
You're a smart one.
Yuxin.
Yuxin? Is he your lover?
He must be.
Yuxin.
So pretty. Follow us.
- Let us take care of you.
- Yuxin.
- Let's go.
Stop it.
Attack.
You can't even stand firmly,
yet you dare to do this kind of thing.
You nosy bastard.
You dare to ruin this for me?
I'm in a good mood today.
I don't wanna kill you.
Don't waste time talking. Let's go.
Go away.
Stop following me.
I thank you for your kindness.
No need.
Didn't know you're a nice dude.
Then why didn't you just take her
to the Ling Borough?
She lost her memory.
Couldn't answer any of my questions.
Was I supposed to put up a missing person notice,
and sort out everything for her?
The Heartless Slave.
Did she get into trouble with Xie Yi?
Xie Yi?
Master of the Eight Extreme Temple?
I heard he's an arrogant moron.
What happened after that?
What else could have happen?
I left her with the Illusory Demon Sect.
They only have women there.
It was easy for the both of us.
Those in the Illusory Demon Sect
only practice low-level illusory arts.
Except for the Master, Yu Linwei,
she is the true artist of illusion.
So, Master Yu used illusory arts
to give Xuxuan a fake identity as Pan's daughter
and a disciple of the Illusory Demon Sect?
That's correct.
Any way we can undo that?
No idea.
What does Master Yu think?
You know nothing.
So what?
May I ask why you insist on having a fight with me?
You're the only one with real skills
in this group.
But I won't take advantage of you,
you're tired today,
so I'll come back tomorrow.
Is it how people hit on girls here?
Challenge them to a fight?
You talked shit about my brother
and tried to pull his girl.
No man could put up with it.
Stop talking.
May I ask
if you know Li Mu?
You called my Eye of Frost a turtle shell.
Talk business or get lost.
I asked you to look out for them.
That's how you do it?
What?
I even followed them to the Graveyard of Gods.
That's because
you wanted to check it out.
I just wanted to see
what kind of garbage you brought back
from the Scarlet Tide Continent.
What do you think?
Horrible.
Nobody is good enough in your eyes.
There's somebody.
Ling Shiyu.
I didn't expect the extinguished Nether Race
to have a descendant.
I would really like to see her power.
Qianjie,
The Heaven Fighting Race is coming back soon.
I can sense them coming closer and closer.
Now we need to nurture the talents.
Please don't just think about having fun.
Qin Lie's real identity
might be Gongmu Lie.
What?
The Graveyards of Gods that everyone wants to go,
is nothing but a trap set up for Gongmu Lie
by someone called the Night Fairy.
It's getting more and more interesting.
You mean,
Duan Qianjie is one of the four people
in the Soul Suppressing Orb?
So he knows Uncle Li...
Duan looks hostile and cold-hearted
but everything he did was to help us.
He also knows about the flaw
in the Eye of Frost.
That's why
I ask him if he knows Li Mu.
Uncle Li is fine.
But I have a complicated relationship with Du,
and Duan is so difficult.
There's a kid, too.
The kid is easy.
Was Sanla easy to deal with?
The good thing is that
we're now one step closer to the truth.
Four people guarding the Soul Suppressing Orb.
Only the kid
hasn't showed up yet.
It can't be Sanla, right?
I feel like it's a part of god's plan.
Everyone that shows up in your life
has connections
to your past.
The other day when I went inside
the Night Fairy's subconsciousness,
she called me Wuchun
and wanted to kill me.
In the Graveyard of Gods,
when she heard your voice,
she called you Wuchun and wanted you dead too.
They all call me Wuchun
and you Gongmu Lie.
Is it because we look like them?
Or we are them?
What are the relationships between
the Night Fairy, Wuchun
and Gongmu Lie?
I'm afraid
only the Night Fairy knows.
And she,
she is the first one to call me Gongmu Lie.
Right.
There's one more thing.
What is it?
Never mind.
I just suddenly thought of Xuanxuan.
Don't worry.
I will always be here for you.
We will help you with Xuanxuan.
Hua Yuxin was such a nice man.
No wonder you say I'm a lot like him.
Alright.
Stop crying.
You'll just make Yushi even sadder.
I'm sad too.
Why don't you care about my feelings?
Qianqian, no,
Xuanxuan has suffered too much.
She lost such a great guy.
If I ever lost Lianrou,
how sad would I be?
Oh, I already lost her.
Oh, no. I never had her.
I'm taking her back to the Illusory Demon Sect.
It's better to let her have a fresh start
than reminding her of her losses and sufferings.
It's just that Xuanxuan can't get over Yuxin.
Even if now she lost her memory,
she still has
these indescribable feelings for him.
I know her well.
After she wakes up,
she will definitely get to the bottom of it.
Right.
She will definitely come after me.
What should I do?
Yiyuan,
I have a favor to ask you.
What favor?
Lie to her.
How?
You're here.
Qianqian,
you're here for Yiyuan?
Yeah. I need to speak with him.
Did I interrupt something?
No, no, no.
Not at all.
You. Follow me.
Don't follow us.
Don't worry.
Yiyuan might look a bit dumb,
but he's actually quite clever.
Just like Yuxin.
I'm just wondering,
if Xuanxuan really forgot about you.
If she remembered me,
she would definitely have me as her sister.
Qin Lie,
go talk to Duan Qianjie for me.
Ask him what happened
when she was in the Illusory Demon Sect.