♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 24=
Two of them are missing.
Over there.
Constraint of Spider Web.
What is this?
There'll be greater despair
after we gave some hope to it.
Everything should come to an end.
Phoenix Firing Line!
White Tiger Protection Barrier!
Let her go.
It'll be wise not to struggle.
At least, you won't suffer.
Enough with the pep talk.
Kill them all.
Now is the time!
White Tiger Intense Light Wave!
Blue Silver Cage!
We won!
How great!
We're the Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke!
They're just like...
Like us back then.
Open the door
and let us in.
We'll leave after we put the stuff.
What're you doing?
They're all here to send us gifts.
They're too passionate.
Who can stand them?
Where are the others?
Wu was dragged
into the traditional song and dance
event in Xi Si City.
There are so many people,
I barely managed to escape.
Where's Dai Mu Bai?
Brother Dai is inside.
Headmaster said his hand
is recovering fast.
We'll leave in these days.
Okay, I'm going to check on him.
Is anyone there?
Open the door.
Brother Dai, I...
Why are you here?
I asked Brother Dai out
because I like him.
You really like him?
I'm hesitating.
Hesitate? What're you hesitating about?
You're hesitating if you should like him?
You saved me twice.
You are very capable too.
You have a bright future.
If it was not because of
Martial Soul Hall,
I might have chosen you.
Choose me for what?
What does it have to do
with Martial Soul Hall?
Tang San,
I hope in the future,
we will never be on the opposite sides.
You...
You were pretending to be asleep?
I was trying to hold in,
so I dare not breathe.
She had been staring at me like that.
It was abnormal.
She likes you, doesn't she?
Definitely no.
That feeling
is like a hunter looking at his prey.
You can feel it even with
your eyes closed?
Of course.
I was born a hunter.
This kind of sense is nothing to me.
Where are the others?
They're attending
the celebration in Xi Si City.
The people seem to be quite passionate.
Then when will we leave?
Headmaster said
we can leave anytime when
your condition is stable.
I'm fine now.
Tell Headmaster
we can leave anytime.
Brother Dai,
I don't know if Hu Lie Na
will come again or not,
do you want me to stay here?
It's okay. Headmaster is here.
What can she do?
Kill me?
All right.
How about this?
I'll ask Ou Si Ke to accompany you.
I'll find Headmaster first.
Wait a moment.
All right.
Wait for me.
Tang San,
come over here for a chat.
Well done for defeating
the Fiend Battle Team.
You passed the test.
I didn't challenge the Fiend Battle Team
for the test that you had given me.
I look only at the result.
Your true intention
is not that simple.
Don't you get it now?
I was just following the orders
from the headquarters
to make use of their hatred
and bring them together
to do the things that
they believed were right.
I told them that much
just to give Wang Sheng's team
a goal.
The truth is
you don't care about them at all.
You just gave them an excuse.
All the sanctimonious talk
is just a lie for you to use the drugs
that caused mutation of Martial Soul
on the Fiend Battle Team to turn them into
your puppets.
You're smart and I admire that.
We are on the same path.
I can put up with you even if you're
being disrespectful to me.
So, what are your true intentions?
I can only say that so far,
the first step is to
win the championship
in the Soul Master School Contest.
I heard
that Tian Dou Imperial School
is also interested in you.
This is good.
After all, there'll be a battle between
Cang Hui and Tian Dou.
You will play an important role then.
Is the real master behind Cang Hui
the Hao Tian Soul Master?
Of course.
Can I see him?
You can see him
as long as you get into the final of
the Soul Master School Contest.
I see you as one of us.
That's why I told you this.
I've said what I can.
There are things that you shouldn't know
because you are not qualified yet.
Or you don't believe me?
To be honest, I don't trust you.
I don't need your trust,
your obedient will do.
Not to obey me, but to the headquarters.
Otherwise, you'll end up dead
just like Bu Le.
You killed Bu Le?
I didn't want to kill him.
I was ordered by the headquarters.
Anyone who spills the secret must die.
Including you and me.
You!
I have to remind you.
It's impossible
for you to get into the final now.
You have to be stronger if
you want to see Hao Tian Soul Master.
I can't let everyone risk it with me.
I have to finish the rest of
the path on my own.
The people are happier now
without the Fiend Battle Team.
I always think about
what is the purpose for
Soul Masters to be stronger?
Is it to have a more astonishing ability
or for wealth and power?
Is there a right answer?
Everyone's answer is different.
But there are many Soul Masters
who lost themselves in the process of
getting stronger.
If the purpose of being strong
is for such smiles,
the result may be different.
To be strong for others.
I've never thought about it.
You can think about it on the way.
You need to find your own goals.
Brother San. Brother San?
You seem to have a lot on your mind.
Not at all.
Shall I watch Wu for you in the future?
What?
If Wu talks to other boys in the future,
I'll stop her for you.
Why is that?
I'm helping you!
Why are you helping me?
Brother San.
This thing,
where did you get it?
I've promised my dad not to tell.
Okay, it'll do as well since you can make it.
Have you ever considered
selling it to us?
This is free. I'll give it to you.
No, this is not what I want.
I want to buy your workmanship
of making the Godly Godly Crossbow.
Soul Masters from the Support Branch
don't have the ability to kill.
So this Godly Crossbow is a
perfect tool for us.
Although the Godly Crossbow
is very powerful, its power is limited.
How do you know?
Recently, I've borrowed
Tang San's Godly Crossbow and tried it out.
I found that its speed
and strength are too weak
to be used to deal with those with
Five Soul Rings and above.
It'll be hard to deal with
those with Four Soul Rings,
especially the Soul Sect
with defense expertise,
not to mention to break their defense.
But even so, it's still strong.
Sell it to us.
I never thought about selling this.
Take your time, because I have to
show it to my dad in Tian Dou City.
Only then can I set a price.
You'll be rich in no time.
Rong Rong, how about my stick?
Do you want it?
Your stick?
You can keep it for yourself.
Didn't you see?
It can shoot out smoke and fire.
Rong Rong, wait for me.
Rong Rong.
Tang San, what's going on with you?
Did that person show up in Xi Si City?
Sir, how can you tell?
It was written all on your face.
No matter what happens,
you have us by your side.
Sir, I want to get into the final
of the Soul Master School Contest.
Do you think I can make it?
Of course, but
you're not fighting alone.
Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke
is a team of Soul Masters,
and I have faith in this team of yours.
You can focus on preparing the battle
after we reach Tian Dou City.
Headmaster and I will think of a way
for you to meet qualifications
of the contest.
I have made plans about
the flow of the contest.
I'll remind you about the match system
and the strategies.
I'll also analyze your opponents
in the contest.
If you have set a goal
to enter the final,
then you should work hard for it,
kid.
I can't see
the desire to win on your face.
Then why must you enter the final?
That person said my dad
might show himself.
We should
talk about this privately after
we reach Tian Dou City.
Let's go.
We can get out of trouble one day.
At that time,
I'll tie all people in the city here
to kill them all under the burning sun.
Yes, they deserve to die.
They deserve it.
The sandstorm is coming.
Master Ye Zhi Qiu, you're here.
We have disappointed you.
Please give us another chance.
I can't say I'm disappointed.
Master Ye, Master Ye.
We'll fight it back after we recover.
Are you Tang San's friend?
Yes.
Tang San is the one who
turned us into this.
It's also due to Wang Sheng's
incompetence.
Master Ye, just leave him here,
and let him die on his own.
We can go now.
Go?
Where to?
Find a place to treat our wounds.
There's no need.
But we can't use Martial Soul
in such conditions.
Master Ye, what's going on?
Your mission is over.
Master Ye, give us another...
How long have you known Tang San?
I knew him from the Beginner
Soul Master School in Nuoding City.
Who are the parents of him and Wu?
I don't know. I only know
that Tang San's father is a blacksmith.
Where did he get the
weapons that he used
to defeat you?
He made them himself.
How did he know all these?
I don't know.
That is to say,
actually, you know nothing.
No, Tang San worked in a smithy.
Yes, he forged iron before.
Worthless information.
Master Ye, I'm loyal to Cang Hui.
I'm willing to do anything.
I'm willing to be at your service.
Be at my service? You?
I'm a Mutant Soul.
Is Mutant Soul valuable?
We can have as many Mutant Souls
as we want.
We can make Mutant Souls
as long as we have the drugs.
But you clearly said that
we are fighting to
change the fate.
If I didn't say this,
how could I make
you all work hard?
Is... is this a lie?
You only get it now?
No, Master Ye.
I'm begging you, don't kill me.
Master Ye.
I'm begging you, please don't kill me.
Actually,
I don't want to kill you.
I can work for you.
I'm very useful, please don't kill me.
The world is like this.
The truth is always cruel.
Master Ye, please don't kill me.
I'm begging you, don't kill me, Master...
I'm just like you.
Nothing but a tool.
Tools
are meant to be controlled
and used by others.
Nobody can escape it.
I'm exhausted.
This is the capital of Tian Dou Empire,
Tian Dou City.
It's huge.
How many people live here?
Countless people are coming in and
out of Tian Dou City every day.
It's undoubtedly the center
of the empire.
We should hurry to
Tian Dou Imperial School
before it gets dark.
Don't stay in the wild
at night anymore.
That's great. I can finally take a bath.
Bath?
Let's go.
Headmaster,
isn't it this way?
Who told you the Imperial School
is in the city?
It's over here.
Bath, bath, bath.
Hurry up, Rong Rong.
You didn't talk much since
we left Xi Si City.
I'm fine.
Everyone, we are here at last.
In front is Tian Dou Imperial School.
Which part of it is the school?
The whole mountain.
What?
All of the Martial Soul research fields,
Soul Beast research departments,
Soul Arenas,
and facilities that you can
think of are here.
Now you know why the school
is not in the city.
Because it's too huge.
Wow, that's so cool.
It's not just the school is huge,
the students are strong too.
Then such a huge school
must be better than our school.
What are you saying?
How can you admit defeat
before you fight?
That's right.
Okay, okay, keep up.
Hurry up.
What can I do for you?
We're from Shi Lan Ke School. We were invited.
Shi Lan Ke School?
I've never heard of it.
It's a small school. It's normal
that you haven't heard of it.
Who invited you?
Yu Tian Heng.
Senior Yu?
Please wait here, I'll report it.
Are you crying?
Ou Si Ke.
I never thought that
I can come to Tian Dou Imperial School.
Dad,
you passed your Martial Soul to me.
I will carry your strength and spirit
to live a better life.
I won't give up.
I won't give up, either.
I wanted to be an artist
since I was young.
I never thought that
I'll have the chance to
come to Tian Dou City.
Tian Dou City has the treasure of art
and it is a sacred place
for all of the performers.
Hong Jun, you know what?
Don't give up.
Try your best.
You can do it!
Everybody, please follow me.
Let's go.
We are Shi Lan Ke School, remember it.
It's huge. How great!
Come inside, please.
Have a seat, please.
I'll inform Senior Yu.
Their... Their
classroom is too big.
This is their classroom, right?
So big.
This is not a classroom.
This is just a reception hall.
Reception hall? This big?
There are a few reception halls
like this in the school.
How did you know?
Of course I know.
My dad brought me here before.
I'm the little princess of
Qibao Amber Clan.
Let's sit down.
Let's sit.
Tang San.
Is this edible?
Yes, it is.
Do you want to eat?
Here, have a bite.
I'll eat by myself.
We've been eating dried food
throughout the journey.
Here, Tang San.
Have this one.
Tang San, hand me the water.
I choked.
Eat slowly.
I'm very hungry.
Finally, I have some fresh fruit to eat.
Are both of you all right?
Look, I'll show you a performance.
Cool!
Hu Lie Na, why aren't you eating?
Up to her.
Where are the mysterious masters?
Mysterious masters?
Mys... Mys...
Are you all
invited by Senior Yu, Yu Tian Heng?
We...we...
Yes, we are.
I heard Senior Yu have invited
some mysterious masters
to join our Imperial Battle Team.
I wonder when they will arrive.
We have already arrived.
Here, eat this.
Why you?
What's wrong with us?
You can ask Senior Yu.
Everyone is here.
Junior, you are here as well.
Headmaster Lan,
let's go to the
Academic Affairs Department.
The chief of the Academic Affairs Department
is waiting for you.
Okay, stop eating.
Let's go.
Okay.
Senior,
you invited these people
to join our Imperial Team?
Yes.
I'll introduce each of them
to you later.
I have to go to the
Academic Affairs Department first.
Senior Yu,
we have so many talents
in Tian Dou Imperial School.
It's more than enough to
form two battle teams.
Of course, I would agree if you asked
the strong ones to join
for the fame of the school.
But you're letting these guys
replace
the students of our school.
What are you talking about?
You all invited me.
I haven't agreed yet.
That means you still have some
self-consciousness.
That's because I'm afraid that
some teams are too weak
and they will affect me.
How dare you look down on us!
We're Tian Dou Imperial School!
You look down
on our Shi Lan Ke School first.
What a small school is that?
I have never heard of it!
How dare you come
to mix with us in our Imperial School?
Your Senior
begged us here.
You!
What are you doing? Come here!
What are you doing?
Senior.
They are not qualified
to join our teams.
The qualification is judged by
the Academic Affairs Department.
Is this how
the Imperial School treats their guests?
I'm sorry, everyone.
Xue Beng has royal blood in him.
He has deep feelings for the school
and he doesn't know you all well.
I'll scold him later.
Is his name Xue Beng?
From the name, we can tell
his temper must be bad.
But it's true that
we look shabby.
It's no wonder that he misunderstood us.
It's my bad.
I should let you all change first.
How about this? I'll bring you all
to clean up at the quarters.
Are they all waiting for us?
Yes.
The chief of Academic Affairs Department
is waiting personally.
It'll be rude
to drag this any longer.
Let's do this.
We'll bring
Tang San and Dai Mu Bai first.
Others can rest up here.
Okay then, I'll show you the way.
All right.
Let's go.
Hong Jun.
I'm telling you
that the yellow fruit is very delicious.
It's huge here.
Hurry, hurry up.
Each of us can pick a room
and have a good bath.
One room for each person?
What a luxury!
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪