♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 25=
It's so spacious here.
Come over quickly.
Everyone can choose a room
and take a good shower.
One room each?
It's luxurious.
Where is Hu Lie Na?
Could it be that she went
with Headmaster and the rest?
She has been always
weird.
Just ignore her.
Pick a room and have a shower. Let's go.
-I want to take a shower too.
-Let's go.
What's wrong?
You can't take it
even though you've just been separated for a while?
Wait for me.
Chief,
people from Shi Lan Ke School have arrived.
Thank you for coming all the way here.
I'm the chief of Tian Dou Imperial School,
Meng Shen Ji.
You're Mr. Meng.
Nice to meet you.
Tian Dou Imperial School
has a lot of concealed talents.
Meng Shen Ji has Eight Soul Rings.
He's just a step away
from the limit of Soul Masters.
He's very famous.
His Martial Soul is Black Demon.
He's also in the Control Branch like you.
This must be Headmaster Lander, right?
Thank you for coming a long way.
Please have a seat, everyone.
Take a seat.
Let's start with the official matters.
I trust the decision
of Yu Tian Heng.
Since he's chosen
two students from your school
and thought that they are qualified
to join Tian Dou Imperial School's battle team.
Then, we should settle
their registration as soon as possible.
I would like to ask...
Yes.
Can I keep my identity
as a Shi Lan Ke student?
No.
I don't have the plan to change school.
I heard
that you want to fight your elder brother
in the battle ring this time.
Yes.
But, you're not qualified
to participate in the contest
if you don't join
the battle team of Tian Dou Imperial School.
I can challenge him
even if I don't participate in the contest.
Tang San.
Yes.
What do you think?
I don't want to change school either.
During the journey from Xi Si City
to here,
I have been thinking
that if I abandon
my school, teachers, and brothers
just because I want
to participate in the contest,
I'll do more things
that defy my principle
to fulfill
my other desires in the future.
I don't wish for that day.
You're a good boy.
Take a seat.
Tian Heng, in this case,
they can't join
our Imperial School's battle team.
And they can't participate in the contest.
It was my mistake
that I didn't manage to persuade them.
Your Highness, how come you're here?
I didn't know that you're coming.
I'm sorry that I didn't welcome you
at the entrance.
Mr. Meng, don't worry.
I decided to come suddenly.
It's my fault.
Please wait for a while.
I'll be there soon.
I'll wait for you then.
Don't follow me.
Wait for me at the foot of the mountain.
Yes!
Dai Mu Bai.
I heard that you defeated your brother.
He was injured. That doesn't count.
When he visits Tian Dou again,
please ask him to come to me.
I should be able to talk to him.
Do you know him?
I'm Xue Qing He.
This name is familiar.
I'm the Crown Prince of Tian Dou Empire!
You're the Crown Prince?
I don't look like one?
Then, you're Soul Master too?
Yes.
But there's something wrong
with my Martial Soul.
I have Double Soul Rings only.
It's very hard for me
to advance anymore.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
I'm different from the Dai family.
The royal family of Tian Dou
depends on our brain, not muscles.
Mr. Meng.
Your Highness.
I came here for them.
Is there any problem
for them to join the Imperial School?
They don't want to leave
Shi Lan Ke School.
When we rent them,
and their names will be temporarily
under our Imperial School.
After the contest, they can return to Shi Lan Ke.
Everything has a precedent.
I vouch for them.
Your Highness,
do you value them so much?
I value
the identity of Dai Mu Bai.
Do you think that I'm deaf?
You're using me.
I'm not using you.
You want to defeat your brother, and I
hope that Xing Luo Empire
can have a less dominant heir.
We're just fulfilling each other's need.
If his brother becomes the Emperor of Xing Luo,
I think there'll be a lot of disputes
between the two countries.
Nobody wants to start a war, right?
Okay.
Then, I'll arrange
the renting procedure tomorrow.
Thank you.
Nice to work with you.
The sunset of Tian Dou is an unmissable scene
in the Imperial School.
Sunset is approaching soon.
Shall we view it together?
I'm not interested.
For my sake.
Just have a look.
If the young people talk
while you two seniors stay here,
they may feel awkward.
How about both of you leave first?
We'll follow your arrangement.
Let's go.
He's been leading all the conversations
since he appeared.
A simple person can't be the Crown Prince.
Only this scenery
is never boring.
You sent Ma Xiu Nuo to us?
Yes.
He died in Xi Si City.
I know.
He was killed by the Fiend Battle Team.
But you guys defeated the Fiend Battle Team,
it can be considered as revenge for him.
Cang Hui School is behind the Fiend Battle Team.
Do you know it?
Yes, I do.
The royal family will just leave it at that?
A school is not important.
The person behind Cang Hui
is worth thinking over.
Who controls Cang Hui School?
You're nervous.
Who is it? I want to know too.
I heard that it's Hao Tian Soul Master
who has gone missing.
You heard?
The Grand Soul Land Masters
are the strongest in the world.
I have no way to find out more about them.
What else do you want to ask?
It depends
on what else you want to say.
I heard that you're from Martial Soul Hall.
Yes.
I have been thinking
why would Martial Soul Hall want to organize
the Soul Master School Contest.
To promote the legacy of Martial Soul
and to strengthen
the communications between schools.
Just that?
What do you think?
I'm just asking.
Look.
That's the clan of Martial Soul Hall
in Tian Dou City.
It's the tallest building in the city too.
The royal city
is suppressed by them.
Both of you,
please get to the final round in the contest.
The champion this time
can be any school,
but absolutely not Martial Soul Hall.
To be honest,
do you think you can be the champion?
I want to enter the final round in the contest.
How about you, Brother Dai?
If I get to the final round,
it means that I need to fight my brother
face to face.
He's also battling in the Xing Luo area?
Yes.
Xing Luo Royal Battle Team
is qualified to enter the final round directly.
Don't have to fight and enter the final round?
I didn't know that they have this rule.
Because these two countries
have
their own official Soul Master Schools.
Therefore, the two teams under those schools
will take up two places in the final round.
A rule like this
is biased towards the royal schools.
This is just to protect the reputation
of both royal families only.
If we join
the Tian Dou Imperial Battle Team,
then we don't have to take part
in the preliminary round?
And we can enter the final round directly.
Not necessarily so.
There are two teams
in the royal school.
Normally,
team one will be the main team
and can enter the final round directly.
Team two will be the auxiliary team
and they have to compete with other teams
in the preliminary round.
I don't care which team it is.
We'll enter the final round
with our ability.
I'm confident.
But, we don't have
much time left.
I have to advance to Quadruple Soul Rings
before the final round,
so that I can really confront my brother.
Let's do this together.
All of you, come out!
He is the guy whose surname is Beng?
My surname is not Beng, it's Xue!
Oh yes, Xue Beng!
[*Avalanche]
This looks good.
No.
How come your family
gave you a disaster name?
Don't talk nonsense.
Right?
Where is the most arrogant guy?
The one who argued with me!
Ask him to come out!
Why do you want to see Brother Dai?
He dared to look down
on the royal family of Tian Dou.
I'll make him pay the price.
I want to see
how arrogant he can be
without the Crown Prince!
Brother Dai is not here.
If you want to fight, I'll fight with you.
You want to fight with me, little one?
What do you mean?
Don't get angry.
Don't destroy other people's yard.
He's here to look for a fight!
Don't worry.
I can control myself.
Look.
Brother Dai and Tang San
are not around.
I should be the one
to fight, right?
I'm very good.
I like to fight.
Let me do it.
You're a girl. You shouldn't fight.
We are here.
I'm very good.
I'm really good at fighting.
I can defeat him
in a second.
-Let me do it.
-It's true.
I'll do it!
It's true that I can do it.
You're a kid.
In a second...
Let me tell you, now...
Let me do it.
Me!
In a second...
-Since I learn...
-Let me do it.
I can defeat him in a second.
Trust me.
Can you let me fight a bit?
All of you are so arrogant.
Fight against me together!
Both of them are Triple Soul Rings.
But he is so weak
in front of Wu.
Because they
always fight with the opponents
who are stronger than them.
Training like that
has made them excellent.
Tian Dou Imperial School
is the top school
in Douluo Continent.
Those students have been
in a protective environment.
They can't beat our students
in real battles.
Tang San is back.
Wu.
Your new clothes are beautiful.
By the way, help me braid my hair.
Who is this?
He wanted to challenge you.
Challenge me?
How about we have a fight now?
Who beat him?
He was heavily beaten.
Wu beat him up.
If they hadn't stopped me,
and if I had fought with him,
he would have been
knocked out by me.
Sure.
You can feed him to death if you fight him.
Yes!
I'm hungry.
Why do you look at me?
You want me to make food for you?
I...
Rong Rong is hungry.
Rong Rong, I'm at your service.
You can tell me if you're hungry.
Right?
You can tell me
a small matter like this. I can...
Rong Rong, don't be angry, okay?
I'll make food for you.
I'll make food for you now.
Okay?
I'm not hungry. I don't want to eat.
Rong Rong, don't be like this.
Okay.
It's late now. Go back to rest.
Rong Rong,
in the future, if...
If there's something like that
in the future, I'll do it!
I'll settle it, okay?
Don't be angry, Rong Rong.
Please don't be angry anymore.
You talk too much.
I talk too much?
So, Prince Xue Xing
is making a fuss about the student being beaten?
It's okay if it's a normal student.
Xue Beng is from the royal family.
The student was the one
who started the fight here.
What is the plan of the Prince?
He wants to meet
the girl who beat Xue Beng.
Bring all of them.
We'll go together.
Who beat you?
Tell me.
The girl.
I heard that Chief Meng
wants to arrange the registration
of these outside students.
It's on a rental basis.
They will join
our school's battle team temporarily.
This is also the instruction of the Crown Prince.
The Crown Prince's idea is good.
But, he's too young
and easy to be deceived.
They beat the descendant of the royal family
when they just arrived at the school.
How can we accept
such rude students?
I think we should forget
about their entrance to our school.
Tang San and Dai Mu Bai
are the ones who will be entering the school.
They didn't fight.
She alone beat you?
Yes.
Okay then.
If you want to enter our school,
you have to chase this girl out
down the mountain.
Then, just forget about it.
If Wu leaves this place, I'll leave too.
Yes. Please remember
that we're invited by the Imperial School.
We didn't request
to enter the school.
Chief Meng,
you see their attitude too, right?
What do you think?
Prince Xue Xing,
regarding their entrance,
the Crown Prince gave the order.
How come you're here?
Don't you want to know
why Martial Soul Hall
wants to organize the contest for Soul Masters?
I'm the direct disciple
of the chief of Martial Soul Hall, Bi Bi Dong.
Even if you know the reason,
why do you want to tell me?
Martial Soul Hall wants to strengthen
the cooperation with Tian Dou Empire.
This is the chief's idea.
There are many people.
I think it's not convenient
to discuss it here.
Then, do what you need to do.
Looks like you are
loyal to the Crown Prince.
Prince Xue Xing,
I'm just a teacher.
I don't care about anything
outside of the school.
Don't forget
that this is Tian Dou Imperial School.
The royal family is the supporter of the school.
Uncle, you're right.
Therefore, we as the members of the royal family
should think more
for the school.
I invited two geniuses
to join our school's battle team.
It's also assisting our school.
They are talented in beating people?
I heard that they didn't
beat Xue Beng.
They are from the same school.
They are all the same.
Uncle,
a school is to nurture Soul Masters.
Real battles are more important.
It proves
that the people I invited are stronger.
They deserved to enter the school.
The guy said something rude just now.
He disrespects people of higher status
and offended the royal family.
Uncle,
I guess your news is not complete.
Let me introduce him to you.
He's the Prince of Xing Luo Empire,
Dai Mu Bai.
We are all royals.
I think the point about disrespect
is not valid.
How come a school in Tian Dou
can allow the Prince of Xing Luo to enter?
The Prince of Xing Luo
joining our school in Tian Dou
shows that Tian Dou Empire
is modest and open-minded.
What do you think?
They messed things up as soon as they arrived.
They have bad intentions.
Uncle,
these students are young people.
It's nothing new that they fight.
Looks like you insisted on your decision.
Uncle,
you're old and wise.
Of course, your words are reasonable.
But, when it comes to young people,
it's better that they stay active.
Who is outside?
Mr. Du Gu,
these are the students from Shi Lan Ke.
Ou Si Ke!
Let go of my student!
What is your name?
Don't touch my student.
Wu.
One, two,
three, four, five...
Nine.
Nine Soul Rings.
There are not many Grand Soul Land Masters.
He's not among them.
Who are you?
Blue Silver Plant.
You're Tang San?
Yes.
Mr. Du Gu, I invited them.
Uncle, I agreed with you.
They're not suitable to join
our team.
I make a mistake.
It's not your fault.
You don't have enough experience.
You have to learn more.
Yes.
Mr. Du Gu,
please let them go.
I'm not here to help you.
I'm looking for Tang San.
Mr. Du Gu, you know Tang San?
I take him away today.
I don't care about other things.
Mr. Du Gu,
I invited them to come here.
You will be ruining
the reputation of Tian Dou Empire
if you bring him away just like that.
How can the royal family of Tian Dou
gain trust from others in the future?
You should think for the empire.
Okay.
For the Crown Prince's sake,
I'll come another day to bring him with me.
You can't escape.
I didn't expect
that the matter would turn out like this.
I'm sorry.
Your Highness,
how come I haven't heard of the name
of the Grand Soul Land Master just now?
Mr. Du Gu
is the secret weapon of our royal family.
Your Highness, this is a top secret.
It's okay. Since I apologize,
I need to be sincere.
Why did he want to capture Tang San?
I'm not sure.
But, don't worry.
I'll settle
all the misunderstandings.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Tang San,
Yu Tian Heng said that you wanted
to participate in the contest.
I don't want to ask for the reason.
Do you have any ideas?
Shi Lan Ke School doesn't have
official recognition.
So they're not qualified
to participate in the contest.
No matter what,
I invited all of you here.
How about this?
Bring them to Lanba.
You explain the situation to them.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I'm not sure
who the Grand Soul Land Master
behind Cang Hui School is.
If you have any information,
please inform me.
I'll continue to investigate.
That's it.
This way, please, everyone.
See you.
We haven't finished our conversation.
Why don't you follow them?
I don't belong
to Shi Lan Ke.
Lanba School has a long history.
It was a very famous school.
The school was built
in the middle of a forest.
Apart from the lecture buildings,
the rest is surrounded by the forest.
I heard
this is the biggest plant area
in Tian Dou City.
It was a wonderful scene.
The magical school and adventure in the forest.
I feel like I can discover
many stories there.
Stupid, he said it was in the past.
If you can
take over Lanba,
you can use their name
to participate in the contest.
Take over?
I thought we should join them.
Nothing to join.
You'll know
when we arrive at Lanba later.
What about Du Gu Yan?
The Crown Prince said
the surname
of the Grand Soul Land Master is Du Gu too.
Yes, you're smart.
Du Gu Yan
is the granddaughter of Mr. Du Gu.
But, what does it have to do with Tang San?
I want to know about that too.
This is Lanba School.
They're better than Shi Lan Ke.
At least there's a big entrance here.
How much do I have to compensate?
It was already broken. Don't worry.
Although Lanba School looks bad now,
it was famous in the past.
No one is guarding.
It was an accident.
Don't worry.
This is the current condition of Lanba School.
The new headmaster just took over this place,
and all the teachers resigned.
The students left too.
There's no one inside?
Yes, the headmaster is still here.
As long as you can convince the headmaster,
you can
use the name of Lanba
to participate in the contest.
This...
How come this place is so shabby?
There's no one.
Be careful.
The admission requirement
set by the new headmaster
is that he only looks at talents.
It's okay if you have no money.
We're the same.
We don't care if someone is rich,
as long as the student is talented,
we accept the student.
Are there many students
at this school?
There were a lot of students at first.
A person can change his fate
by becoming a Soul Master.
Then, how come this place
became like this?
Later, the big schools realized
the poor students are more hardworking.
They loosened their restrictions.
They took away
most of the prospective students of Lanba.
Later,
Lanba had
a financial problem.
The students and teachers were leaving.
Day by day,
it became like this.
Why didn't the headmaster of Lanba School
leave?
As long as the headmaster is here,
the school will remain.
Actually, a lot of schools
wanted to merge with it,
but the headmaster of Lanba
had rejected all of them.
The headmaster is a stubborn person.
You have to be prepared.
Don't tell him you're the Prince of Xing Luo Empire.
The headmaster had arguments
with Xing Luo Empire previously.
Brother Dai,
they said
you're the Prince of Xing Luo Empire.
After the green old man made a mess,
I've almost forgotten about it.
Yes. Why did the Prince of Xing Luo
want to come to Tian Dou Empire
to study?
My brother is too dominant.
No school in Xing Luo dared to accept me.
Misfortune prince and his fierce brother.
This is...
an adventurous story. It's great.
Brother Dai,
do you have the opportunity
to be the Emperor of Xing Luo Empire
in the future?
I have to defeat my brother first.
We defeated him once,
right?
I need to fight him one-on-one.
Then, we have hope, Brother Dai.
Brother Dai,
after you become the emperor,
I can be
the manager of the royal theatre.
I don't want to destroy the royal theatre.
Don't be like that. At that time,
I will write scripts
that are based on your story.
I'll portray you as a hero.
Try me.
Try it.
Okay.
Brother.
Headmaster, are you here?
I'm Yu Tian Heng
from Tian Dou Imperial School.
A few talented friends of mine
would like to ask
if they can use the name of Lanba
to participate in the contest for Soul Masters.
You can raise any request.
He doesn't want to answer.
Looks like he rejected us.
How about this?
I'll ask for help from the Crown Prince.
Let's see if there are other ways.
Let me try.
Hello, Headmaster.
I'm the headmaster
of Shi Lan Ke School,
Lander.
I understand that I came abruptly.
Lander? Is it really you?
It's a headmistress.
Yes.
Er Long?
It has been a while.
Take a sip of this hot tea.
Try it.
Is this still the taste
that you liked previously?
Thank you.
You don't want to take a seat?
I'll stand for a while.
The tea is good.
I have never thought
that you'd appear again.
Actually, I'm following Boss Lan.
Shi Lan Ke School belongs to him.
Regarding the contest this time...
Maybe you should tell her.
You can tell her.
I'll drink tea.
This...
Tell me.
It's about the students outside.
They are talented.
They want to participate in the contest
and get the opportunity
to train themselves.
We would also like to use
the qualification of your school.
I didn't expect that you'd be the headmistress.
What a coincidence.
Are you married?
I have been running around. I'm not married.
I'm not, either.
Then... both of you continue to chat.
I'll help the students settle down.
The original dorm for students
is on the west side.
You can clean it up yourself.
I know it. Don't worry.
It's okay.
Gang,
discuss our situation
with Er Long thoroughly.
Discuss thoroughly.
Everyone,
we'll stay here today.
Clean up the rooms.
Settle down first.
Thank you.
Since you know Headmistress Liu,
there's hope for you
to participate in the contest.
Let's meet during the contest.
We'll win.
Headmaster.
What's wrong?
Hurry and clean your room.
I'll clean it later.
Can you tell us
about the relationship
between the headmistress and Master?
There's nothing to know about it.
You're the only one who is curious.
Tell us, please.
All of us want to know.
This...
Let's go.
Headmaster, please tell us.
Please tell us.
What's their relationship?
It seems like our adventure
just happened yesterday.
I dream of it every night.
It has been many years.
The reunion of Golden Iron Triangle
is not easy.
Tell me.
What have you done
for all these years?
Who did you meet?
I have a lot to tell.
It's okay.
You can tell me slowly
and I can listen slowly.
Three of us formed a team
and caused a lot of trouble.
We also defeated a lot of great people.
The name of Golden Iron Triangle
was famous back then.
Famous.
Yes.
I want to know one more thing.
Golden Iron Triangle
is considered iron or gold?
You're stupid. It's just a name.
Your name is Ma Hong Jun.
You're Hong or Jun?
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪