Sub by kisscambodia
Episode 23
Mr. Shangguan.
Can you take the case
about Yun Ji Hospital?
No, I can’t take that case.
Why?
Lawyers have their own
strength and weakness,
and their own majors.
Intentional injury cases
are not my strong suit,
let alone it concerns medical disputes.
I won’t take cases that I’m not sure of.
You’ve cooperated with Yun Ji for years
and won all the medical dispute cases
that you took.
Your capability is proved.
Please reconsider it.
Cong Rong.
You want me to take it
for the case’s sake
or for your selfish purpose?
The online loan case
will be opened soon.
Put your mind to that case.
Don’t let me down.
What have you done exactly?
Even an unemotional man like him got mad
and raised his voice so loud.
I just want him to take a case.
Cong Rong.
Come here.
Um.
Come in.
Sorry, Mr. Shangguan.
I was too anxious just now.
I shouldn’t trouble you.
Is Wen Shaoqing your boyfriend?
Um.
Yes.
That’s why
you help him with the lawsuit?
I admit that
I have a selfish purpose,
but that’s not all the reason.
I had an internship in the hospital,
and know doctor-patient relationship
is tense.
It’ll incur disputes
if not handled well.
We can understand
patients and their families,
but doctors shall also
be respected by patients.
As for this case,
from a fair standpoint,
I don’t think Shaoqing is wrong.
That’s why I’ll help him
and clarify the truth to people.
OK.
Prepare for the trial
of online loan case first.
I’ll take care of this case.
Really?
Thank you, Mr. Shangguan.
For more details,
I need to talk with my client.
Let him come here when he’s free.
OK.
I’ll call him here right now.
By the way,
you must go all out
for the online loan case.
Rest assured.
I’ll be well-prepared.
Civil Case Indictment
It’s my first time to get an indictment.
It’s intriguing.
You brat.
You’re in great trouble,
and still have the mood to joke?
Sit.
Here is the situation.
The patient’s family
sued the hospital and you.
It’s fine for the hospital to go through
medical malpractice identification
by the Medical Association
and cope with relevant issues.
Chen Cu has briefed it to me.
There should be no problem, right?
In the meeting,
we had the same judgement,
but it would be a trouble for you.
I know.
The hospital is under great pressure.
I respect the hospital’s decision.
But I’m itching
to come back for work.
I know you wanna be back for surgeries.
The seniors here watched you grow up.
They all care about you,
and don’t hope anything goes wrong
with your career.
How about the hospital hires
a good lawyer for you?
Sir, have you forgotten Cong Rong’s job?
I’ve really forgotten it.
Alright.
Director Yan,
see you around.
OK.
Take care these days.
See you.
OK.
Boss.
Here!
What are you doing?
You should be on duty.
Chen Cu is performing a surgery.
He knew you’d come,
and asked me to bring you
the breakfast he prepared.
Anything else?
Boss,
when will you come back?
What?
You wanna be punished to copy books?
Truth to be told,
not being urged to learn,
I’ve been perturbed all day.
Please come back.
Dr. Wen.
Even if you won’t be a doctor,
you can give us lectures.
What nonsense is that?
It’s his fate to be a doctor.
He will still be back as a doctor.
Yes.
Boss,
we’re waiting for you.
Me too.
We’re all waiting for you.
You brat.
Rest assured.
I promise I will.
But before that,
go back now for your work.
Yes, sir!
Go.
Go back to work.
Go. Go.
Bye-bye, boss.
Boss.
I’m waiting for you.
Bye-bye.
Come to the Law Firm this afternoon
to sign the commission contract
Daren Law Firm
Hello.
Do you have an appointment?
Yes.
The lawyer, Miss Cong Rong.
Wait a second, please.
Let me have a check.
No need.
He’s Mr. Shangguan’s client.
Mr. Shangguan is waiting
in the reception room.
Can’t you get another guy?
You are in luck to have him, OK?
You’re picky.
I bear a grudge with him,
remember?
This is the golden lawyer of our firm,
Mr. Shangguan Yi.
I’ve heard a lot about you.
The outstanding young doctor
in Yun Ji Hospital,
Wen Shaoqing.
We’ve met several times.
Cong Rong.
Yes?
Although Dr. Wen isn’t a stranger,
you should still serve him water.
Sorry.
I’m gonna get it.
She said you could handle the case well.
I count on you then.
I’m flattered.
Litigation comes with risks.
Before it’s ruled by the court,
no one can surely win it.
I usually say these to patients’ family.
Surgery comes with risks.
The success is not guaranteed.
I’m not used to putting myself
in others’ shoes,
but I can understand you.
To be frank,
I didn’t hope you’d come to me.
Nor do I hope to see you
on my operating table.
From now on,
I’m your attorney.
Tell me what happened in detail.
When
and where.
The cause.
The process.
And the result.
The more details, the better.
Here’s the story.
The patient in Bed 3
had been in bad condition.
We provided him ANH by IV,
but his family didn’t agree anyway.
I’ve mostly learned about it.
Let’s call it a day.
Be seated for a while.
Excuse me.
Sorry for keeping you waiting.
Mr. Shangguan.
We count on you for our company’s case.
Is it over?
I’ve mostly learned about it.
You may talk with him
about contract details.
Um.
This way, please.
OK.
Why was it so soon?
Because I was eager to see you.
Is it fun to tease me?
Nope.
Sign it.
The commission contract.
Shall pay Party A _ yuan
for the law service
Why is the fee item blank?
I’ll fill it out after you sign it.
If you offend me,
you’ll pay with everything you own.
I don’t need to read it then.
I can’t tell
if you mean to trick me.
So, stop struggling.
Just fill it out
and sign it.
Wen
What?
Signed it wrong?
It’s fine.
I’ll go get a copy.
No.
I usually use a blue-black pen
for medical cases.
I’m not used to this color suddenly.
I’m going to fetch another one.
No, thanks.
I’ll make do with it.
You don’t have to.
Bite your finger and write with blood.
Wen Shaoqing
Make a fingerprint.
Can I not do it?
I wanna keep the first...
Fingerprint isn’t needed
for wedding now.
It’ll be recorded electronically.
How did you know I’d say this?
Come on.
Client: Wen Shaoqing
What’s wrong?
If...
I mean,
if I lose the case
and can’t be a doctor,
will you still be with me?
I’ve studied law for so many years.
Do you know the influence on me?
What influence?
Be indifferent to the world.
But I’m willing to protect
what is right,
and those I care about.
I promise you will still be a doctor.
Thanks for your protection, Miss Cong.
Wen Rang
Darling
Chengcheng.
What’s the matter?
Wen Rang.
You called me at a wrong time,
understand?
Here we go.
It’s already up.
Almost.
Honey.
Are you really happy
or just being lovesick?
Wasn’t I like this
when you just knew me?
But you haven’t been like this for long.
What was wrong with me?
Was I being haunted?
I was so spoony
and sentimental.
Now this is the right way to live.
Do you not miss Wen Rang anymore?
I don’t miss him at all.
That’s a lie.
I’ve figured it out.
Look.
Wen Shaoqing and you
have your own work to do.
That won’t change.
Love shouldn’t be
the full part of my life either,
right?
Are you really gonna forget him?
I’m trying.
Love should be finely matched.
If I’m always the one pursuing him,
wouldn’t I be a simp?
Good girl.
Come.
Let’s have some goodies.
Let me play it again.
Let’s go. Hurry.
Let me try again.
Go. Go. Go.
One more time, please.
Boring.
The building has burned out.
No way to go back.
Is that a pun?
Are there more beers?
Get me another one.
Tell her if you love her.
She already has a boyfriend.
So soon?
How come
I screwed things up suddenly?
Suddenly?
I don’t think it’s sudden at all.
Look at you.
You believe all things are fated,
but you never strive for it.
Piss off.
Don’t you want to hear?
So be it.
Haven’t I taken initiative in love?
I tried to chase Jiang Yao
when she left.
You were madly in love with her.
Shouldn’t you go with her?
You’ve never changed for anyone,
neither for Jiang Yao,
nor for
Zhou Chengcheng.
Am I that mean?
Aren’t you?
You said,
“I shall not change
and go with the flow.”
You just can’t let go of your pride.
You are lofty.
Alright.
I’m making some food.
You are insightful.
Um.
Exit the mission
Are you sure to reset
the Paris Simulation Mode
I’m leaving.
Won’t you eat?
Nope.
Wen Rang!
You said I didn’t take initiative.
Play the game again.
Text me when you get home.
Um.
Go home now.
Uncle?
Uncle.
Are you calling me?
Cong Rong and I are peers.
Her boyfriend is your nephew.
So, I should call you Uncle, right?
Yeah.
Is your bicycle broken?
Yes, a thief stole the front wheel.
Get in the car.
I’ll give you a ride.
Thanks.
Am I good-looking?
Not bad.
How... How have you been?
I’m good.
You look good as well.
Right?
Me?
I’m pretty good.
I made up with my dad.
He said I’ve got much more mature.
Do you have a boyfriend now?
Yes.
Be careful this time.
Don’t find a man
like your last boyfriend
who cheated on you
and left you alone crying in the lobby.
He won’t.
He is the son of my father’s friend.
I know him well.
Look at you.
You believe all things are fated,
but you never strive for it.
Zhou Chengcheng.
The light is green.
I nearly missed it.
Zhou Chengcheng,
I didn’t finish my words.
By the way,
back then,
I misunderstood Jiang Yao.
Please say sorry to her for me.
Also,
my dad is doing antique business.
He may cooperate with Jiang Yao on it.
Please introduce her to my father.
Pull over.
We... We haven’t arrived.
It’s stuffy in the car.
I’m gonna take a walk alone.
I’ll send her profile to you.
To tell her,
I have to put in words first.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Burang Barbecue
Buddy!
What’s the matter?
Can you keep the noise down?
Sorry.
I’m in a hurry to open my store.
Please understand it.
Renovation is not allowed after 7 PM.
Now it’s almost 10 PM.
How can I sleep with the noise?
You must mistake it.
That’s the rule for residential area.
This is the business district.
Go sleep at home if it’s noisy.
Come on!
Keep working!
Why there’s a door here?
I’m gonna mend up the wall with sand.
I’ll let you know.
You can’t!
What do you mean?
You can’t mend up the wall.
Buddy.
My store is next to yours.
It’s not safe.
Install an anti-theft door then.
It’s on me.
Who are you?
None of your business.
I said you can’t make a wall here.
Are you making a trouble?
I don’t have to let you know.
I can just build it.
Are you hitting me?
I’ll call the police!
Do it then.
I’ve got time.
Do it!
Are you crazy?
Then what?
Wait here.
Wait and see.
Wen Rang
Delete the contact
Hello?
Who is the guy next to your store?
The bookstore owner is ridiculous.
What happened?
Is he crazy?
Come here and settle it right now.
Or I won’t rent your store.
Are... Are you alright?
You drank again?
Yeah, with my friends in a bar.
Where is he?
He went to hospital for medicine,
and let me talk with you.
You got injured, too.
Why didn’t you go for medicine?
No need.
Get up.
You need some medicine.
You make people worry about you.
My family doesn’t know.
Who will worry about me?
I...
I’m afraid to pay both his medical bills
and yours.
On your feet.
You better break up with your boyfriend.
He’s so unreliable.
It’s rainy and he allowed you
to go out alone at midnight.
You have poor eyes for a boyfriend.
I do have poor eyes.
Never get better.
A Castle in the Clouds
Is he good to you?
Yes, he’s kind.
You all said I’m immature.
I’m trying to get mature,
not to bother others
when I can handle it.
It’s late.
I didn’t ask him to send me,
because I wanted him
to have some more sleep.
Dress it up by yourself,
or go to the clinic nearby.
Let him do it
if he wants to mend up the wall.
Really?
Does the door mean nothing to you?
You used to keep me out by a chain.
Isn’t it good to mend it up?
OK.
Mend it up then.
I’ll talk to him about his renovation
in the middle of night.
I’m leaving.
We meet again.
We are Wen Shaoqing’s attorneys.
This is the lawyer, Mr. Shangguan.
I’m Cong Rong.
Ms. Cong.
We ask you out
just to talk about the case frankly.
We demand a compensation
of 600 thousand.
600 thousand?
You think it’s too much?
My family is still in ICU.
We also need money.
Wait.
These are two things.
Don’t confuse them.
Many witnesses could prove that
you stirred up the fight.
Your claim is unreasonable.
Mr. Shangguan.
You need evidence to prove it.
The doctors on the scene
all sided with him.
I think they colluded to slander us.
As you see,
we have support from netizens.
He is a doctor.
Whatever the reason is,
doctors shouldn’t fight back.
You did hit him.
Any intentional assault is illegal,
regardless of status and occupation.
To affect justice with public opinion
is impossible.
You...
We can
drop the charge.
And we can talk about the compensation.
It’s nothing about the compensation.
The truth is what we want.
Dr. Wen did nothing wrong...!
I’ve learned about your demand.
We’ll respond to the complaint.
I’m sure your unreasonable demands
won’t be backed up by the court.
If nothing else,
I’ll take my leave.
I’m leaving
to meet another client.
They are really hard to deal with.
We may talk at the firm later.
OK.
I’ll wait for you at the firm.
Ms. Cong.
Anything else?
Why don’t you reconsider it?
You know that doctor.
You may convince him.
He doesn’t want to lose his job
for some money, does he?
Cong Rong!
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
My hand got hurt.
What happened?
Are you alright?
Let me see.
We need to go to the Orthopedics.
A fracture, I guess.
Let’s go.
Qin Chu
Hello, Qin Chu.
What’s up?
Cong Rong’s hand fractured.
She looks pale.
We’re now in the Orthopedics.
Come here now.
Shenzhen Yun Ji Hospital
Have a cast
and you’ll recover soon.
Boss is here.
What happened?
Show me your hand.
What brings you here?
It’s fine.
I fell when going downstairs
and hit the ground with my hand.
You’re no kid,
but still so worrisome.
For fear that you’d be worried,
she didn’t tell you
she met the patient’s family.
This is the CT.
I have things to do.
I’m leaving.
Thanks.
Distal radius fracture.
It’s not very serious,
but you still need a cast.
OK.
I know this, too.
Zhong Zhen.
Yes?
What are you waiting for?
Go to the doctor for a cast list.
Be careful. Be careful. Be careful.
Blow it.
Don’t move.
Sit here.
Take a seat.
I’m gonna see how many people are ahead.
Don’t touch it.
Rong.
You two lovebirds are so pathetic.
One is suspended.
The other has a fracture.
Are you two being cursed?
I...
Boss.
Cong Rong says it hurts badly.
Come and have a look.
Take it.
How do you feel?
I’m fine.
He is lying.
Rong.
How come
you suddenly fell and had a fracture?
My boss is suspended.
So, you got upset
and fell down in a trance?
Shut up.
Come with me.
Not to line up?
Slowly.
Take a seat here.
Too many people are ahead.
We won’t wait.
I’ll do it myself.
You?
You are not an orthopedic surgeon.
I’ve learned it.
You said a Jack of all trades
is a master of none.
It’s just a cast.
I... I’d rather wait.
Don’t you trust me?
Boss.
Haven’t you finished?
Zip it.
Dr. Wen is applying a cast!
Come and see!
I come here twice,
and get watched twice.
Last time to pull a tooth.
Now to apply a cast.
I’ll never come again.
Boss.
You applied it well,
but I still have to blame you.
Since my cousin was with you,
she’s got hurt many times.
I feel bad for it. OK?
If I have a girlfriend,
I’ll wrap her in cotton
and take her with me in my pocket.
Do you mean a Barbie doll?
It’s a metaphor.
I’ll take good care of her, anyway.
She won’t get any harm.
Am I right?
Shut up and no one sees you as a dumb.
Go out, guys.
Right.
This is my family affair.
You guys go out.
Outsiders shouldn’t be here.
And you.
Go out.
Is the height OK?
It’s fine.
That was about my work.
It has nothing to do with you.
Don’t blame yourself.
He is right.
I didn’t protect you well.
We’ll quit the lawsuit.
No.
You have to pay me for the service.
Cong Rong.
Thanks.
Does it hurt?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Finally we hold hands♪
♪Intimacy is assurance
of your tenderness♪
♪The unforgettable smile♪
♪I want to remember it each second♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪