CASE SEARCH
IMMIGRATION CONTROL BUREAU
CASE REPORT
Jung Hyeon-gi's mother was reported dead
two days after death.
Her relative reported it.
Who made the notification?
-What is it?
-He's a judicial police officer.
The Immigration Control Bureau.
-Why would they get involved?
-It is strange.
What's his position?
His name's Hwang Hyun-seung,
and he's in Team 7 of the Control Bureau.
Team 7, Control Bureau?
Thanks. I'll treat you later.
But something's odd.
What is?
There are only six teams
in the Control Bureau.
Who are you?
Are you Hwang Hyun-seung's daughter?
Yes. Why?
I'm from the police.
I want to ask you a few questions
about him.
-I don't have any drinks or anything.
-It's fine.
Your father worked for
the National Intelligence Service?
Yes.
I heard he retired five years ago.
Has he gotten any other job since then?
I don't know.
Did he ever say anything
about going back in the field?
We haven't talked
since my mother passed away.
I didn't invite him to my wedding
or to my child's first birthday party.
When did you lose touch with him?
We didn't lose touch.
I stopped contacting him.
It's been ten years.
He didn't take care of my mom
when she had cancer.
He even made her cook breakfast
when she was sick.
He was busy
catching some illegal immigrants
that he didn't come home often.
So I was alone when my mother passed away.
"Illegal immigrants"?
Yes.
Could you give me his number at least?
All right. Thank you for your time.
Did something happen to him?
No, I just need to talk to him.
Just a second.
Actually, I received this last month.
I don't know who did it,
but a pool villa was reserved
under my family's names.
There's no one else but my father
who would've done such a thing.
TO HWANG JI-YEONG
This is Jaae Hospital.
To connect to ARS service, press one.
SEO-HAE
Hey, Seo-hae. Did you have fun yesterday?
I'm sorry. I was so busy.
Seo-hae, let me talk to your mom.
Okay. Hang on.
Hello?
Yes. We had fun.
No, we ate at home.
But…
something strange happened.
Was there some kind of a problem?
No, it's nothing.
I'll tell you when you get home.
All right. Sorry about that.
Okay.
I'll see you later.
What?
Oh, you want a cake? What kind?
A chocolate cake? Okay.
You know, guns are useless
in a small space like this.
You bastard!
Who are you?
Garlic got cheaper this year, right?
-Yes, garlic is cheap.
-Garlic's cheap this year.
If one thing gets expensive,
something else gets cheap.
What's with him?
Help! Over here!
Help!
CONTROL BUREAU, TEAM 7
"Control Bureau, Team 7"?
But there's no Team 7.
ILLEGAL ENTRANT GANG SEO-HAE WANTED
"Gang Seo-hae"?
FATHER: GANG DONG-GI
MOTHER: LEE EUN-HUI
"Father, Gang Dong-gi"?
Hey! What the hell is this?
Who are you?
SISYPHUS
Security system error.
-Security system error.
-Stay inside!
-Stay where you are.
-Stay still, you jerks!
Go back inside!
Don't come any closer.
Stay still, you jerks.
You jerk!
Go back inside, you assholes!
-Stay inside.
-Wow.
Go back inside, you jerks!
What's going on here?
-Stay still!
-Hey!
I didn't kill anyone.
You're lying.
I met the future you here.
You were regretting things.
So stop this now.
-That's nonsense!
-Your mother
didn't blame you until the end.
We're all the same.
We're filled with regrets.
But we can do better from now on.
Hey!
Darn it.
DANGER
ELECTRICAL HAZARD
Delivery!
I brought your food!
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Check the location of the intruder.
I found the intruder.
He's running to the lobby.
-To the lobby!
-Yes, sir.
-To the lobby.
I'm sorry.
Seo-hae…
Gang Seo-hae!
Seo-hae!
Seo-hae, are you okay?
Seo-hae, wake up.
Are you okay? Oh, no.
Seo-hae!
What have they done to you?
I'm going to kill them all!
I'm sorry, Seo-hae.
I should have come for you sooner.
Get off.
What?
Why did you come? It's dangerous.
You're the only one who can protect me.
So I came to save you.
Let's go. We should hurry.
Hang on.
Darn it.
Darn it!
Seo-hae.
We have to go.
It's been a while.
Follow me.
Let me explain.
No, I think
it's better for me not to know.
Get out and go left. You'll get to Area C.
If you pass the area,
you'll arrive at the back gate.
Nobody will notice you.
Should I thank you?
I heard you paid for the funeral.
You didn't have to do that.
Well, it was technically my fault
those things happened to your father.
Thank you
for not reporting my dad to the police.
He was able to keep his honor.
-Seo-hae.
-You should go.
I sent them toward the back gate.
Give me my mom's medicine.
Area C.
We're here.
Kim Seo-jin!
Darn it!
You said I die on October 31.
Right.
That's why I came here.
I guess we won't be able to go to Hawaii.
I heard it's amazing there.
I was looking forward
to going there with you.
You know,
I had so many things
to apologize to you for.
But I didn't get to say anything.
I had so many things
to thank you for, too.
There are so many things
I'm sorry and grateful for.
I wanted you to know that, Seo-hae.
Sir, isn't that the exit?
Jeez, Mr. Han!
There you are.
It's nice to see you.
Stop!
Or I'll shoot.
You punk.
Hey. I'll spare your life.
I promised to do so.
And I'm not going to die today, you jerk.
Hey, Han Tae-sul!
Gosh, I don't know
if I'm glad to see you or not.
I can't really make up my mind.
Well, I'm really glad to see you.
It's been a long time.
Hey. I've been through so much here
because you reported me.
Wait! Just a minute.
Come on. Think about it.
How are you going to get out of here?
We're in the middle of the city.
Are you going to take a cab or what?
Are you going to take the subway
back to Asia Mart?
You'll get caught right away.
Think carefully.
Someone's waiting with my car upstairs.
He leaves if I don't come back in an hour.
There are only about five minutes left.
Hey. Are you trying to play
another trick on me?
I'm telling the truth.
Look, 4 minutes and 42 seconds.
Let's leave together.
Come on.
We can all go to Asia Mart together.
My car's really nice!
All right. The thing is,
Seo-hae's not well. Help us out here!
Help us.
Please.
I swear I'm going to kill you
after we get out of here.
Let's go.
Seo-hae…
Where is it?
Hey, Sun. Where are you?
In front of the hospital.
The whole place is in chaos.
What about Seo-hae?
I got her.
Meet me at the back gate in one minute.
-And keep the car running.
-Where?
The back gate, you idiot!
-Where's the back gate?
-Get to the elevator.
-Where?
-Here. Come on.
She got the shot.
"The shot"? What shot?
She'll die pretty soon.
Is that the car? Hurry up! Get in!
Hey! Get out!
Why are there so many people?
-What…
-Hey, get in.
Move.
Hurry up! Get in!
Seon-jae!
What's going on?
Die.
Dad?
-Seo-hae!
-Dad.
Hurry up! Get in!
SEOUL GANGBUK POLICE STATION
EDDY KIM EXPANDING THE BUSINESS
It's an article about my morning schedule.
Right… But…
Then how did
your iris get scanned at Jaae Hospital?
How would I know that?
Check the security camera footage!
Well…
You don't have any footage?
You really don't know anything about this?
I told you, I really don't know!
-What time is it?
-Almost noon, sir.
This is driving me crazy.
What's my next schedule?
The completion ceremony
for the IDC in Paju.
And after having lunch with the governor,
you come back to Seoul…
Seo-jin.
Seo-jin! Are you here about
what happened at the hospital?
You weren't picking up my calls.
Are you okay?
Sir.
They asked me if I entered the hospital.
Security records say I did.
I think it was Tae-sul.
Did you already know?
No. How would I know that?
What's going on with Tae-sul?
-I have to know today.
-Know what?
Who kidnapped Tae-sul
at the conference, and why?
What happened on the day of the party?
Why did we lie to Tae-sul?
Why did he run away?
And what happened yesterday?
You don't have to know that.
I believed everything you said,
and I did as you asked.
So tell me now.
The things that Tae-sul said…
All that nonsense…
You probably don't believe me,
but it's true.
We're not the only ones
living in this world.
Is it true?
-Why weren't you picking up?
-Boss.
Put him over here.
-You'll be okay, Seon-jae.
-What happened to him?
Hey! Call the doctor! Hurry!
And you, Bingbing, get the icebox.
Darn it.
-How many?
-Just bring them all!
Hurry up!
Hey. You're going to be okay.
What about the downloader?
The emergency generator's on.
Take good care of him, okay?
Darn it!
Right…
Darn it.
How is he?
I got the bullet out
and stitched the wound up.
But his pulse is too weak.
I don't think he'll make it.
If he does, he won't be able to walk.
You should stay with him tonight.
Hey!
Check her, too.
There's no cure for her.
Just hold her hand.
Hey, you quack!
You can't just leave like that!
Hey! Shut up.
Didn't you hear him? He can't help her.
Almost everyone who comes over dies.
There's no point liking her.
Get out.
How can I save Seo-hae?
She's going to die.
So what do I do?
Didn't I tell you
that I was going to kill you two
once we got out?
But I feel like killing you right now.
So get out. We can talk tomorrow.
Is that so?
All right, then.
What? Are you going to
call the cops again?
Fine. Do it.
But I won't let it slide this time.
Really?
The downloader must be important to you.
It's the first thing you checked.
Why?
Are you expecting something important?
Let me guess.
Something did feel odd
when I first came here.
I wondered why you were running Asia Mart.
You risked your life to come to the past,
but why aren't you thinking of living
a luxurious life like the others?
Why are you working as a broker
when you don't even earn much?
You're waiting for someone.
Maybe someone who didn't make it
when you did.
Hey. Shut up.
Fine. There's no need
for such a friendly conversation.
Here.
How's that?
What the hell?
What have you done?
I'm the one who coded this program.
Of course I made a backdoor just in case.
How can I save Seo-hae?
Get the downloader back on.
Or I'll blast a hole in your skull.
How do I save Seo-hae?
Fine, kill me. Just shoot me!
But if you do, you'll never be able
to run the downloader again.
Is that really what you want?
Come on.
Tell me!
All right.
She's disappearing.
What?
She's wandering around different timelines
like a ghost.
She will completely vanish in two days.
So?
It's obvious.
-You have to bring her back.
-How?
Darn it.
There was this advance team
dispatched here long ago.
They were the first ones
to come here through the downloader.
And I was one of them.
Then Sigma was on that team too?
Yes. That jerk was one of us.
We each had a mission when we came here.
Back then,
the Control Bureau didn't exist.
Who's Sigma?
-Are you curious?
-Just tell me! Who is he?
I don't know.
Even if I do,
there's no reason to tell you.
All right. Fine.
I'll just destroy the downloader.
Hey!
The injection she got…
Someone on the advance team
brought it here.
Agnes.
KIM AGNES
She's the one who made that drug.
Ask that woman how to save her.
And she might know who Sigma is, too.
Wait. I forgot something important.
Even if you get lucky enough
to bring her back,
she won't be the same girl
that you used to know.
What?
Something will be different about her
if you bring her back.
It's only natural.
If you want something,
you have to offer something in return.
Whether it's the eyes or the nose,
or memories.
And what if you get the cure
and just run away?
What about my downloader?
So I'm going with you.
Okay?
Let's go
before she disappears.
Sun!
-There's a cure.
-Really?
Yes. I'm going to go get it,
so take Seo-hae home.
Bingbing, the gun.
Take him to the server room
and tie him up.
Me? Why?
What are you doing?
Well, it's hard to trust you, Mr. Han.
So we need to hold a hostage.
He'll be kept here while we're away.
-He has nothing to do with this.
-That's why he's a hostage.
He wouldn't be if he was involved.
Hey, he won't even care if I die.
Is that so? That's even better.
If that server doesn't reopen
within 24 hours,
you, this girl, and this guy…
You're all dead.
Bingbing, if he tries anything funny,
just shoot him.
All right.
DO NOT ENTER
You were going crazy,
so I had to handcuff you.
I held the funeral for your mother.
You should've done it yourself.
You're her son.
I was worried about you,
but it seems like you're doing fine.
Hey.
You're in Team 7
of the Control Bureau, right?
Can you tell me what this is about?
ILLEGAL ENTRANT GANG SEO-HAE WANTED
Why is my name
and my daughter's name on this?
And what's this photo?
I don't get what this is.
Hyeon-gi. Are you forbidden
from talking to civilians like me now?
Answer me!
What's going on?
Why is Seo-hae's name on that poster?
Why is a nine-year-old's name
on a wanted poster?
Hyeon-gi.
Just tell me anything.
Tell me for old time's sake.
Jung Hyeon-gi!
ILLEGAL ENTRANT GANG SEO-HAE WANTED
-You're home.
-Where's Seo-hae?
She went to bed, of course. It's late.
Get changed. We have to go.
What? Why?
What's going on?
I'm not sure, but we can't stay here.
Let's go.
Honey!
What…
Who is it?
-What's this for?
-Go to Seo-hae's room.
If something happens,
point the gun and pull the trigger.
What's going on? Who is it?
Honey. I don't know, either.
Just go inside.
Honey!
Honey. Go inside.
Honey… All right.
Are you Mr. Gang Dong-gi?
Who are you?
Put that knife down.
I'll be faster, you know.
Both of you, stop it.
It'll only take 10 minutes.
Five.
I'm Han Tae-sul.
You know who I am, right?
I need to talk to you urgently.
Could I go inside for a minute?
Let's hear him out first.
I don't know what's going on, either.
-But we should at least hear him out.
-Honey, how…
So what you're saying is that
a time machine is made in the future,
and Seo-hae rode that
to come to the present?
Yes.
And you're saying that some people…
The Control Bureau.
You're saying that they're coming
to get us right now?
This is ridiculous.
Honey. Is this some prank?
Are you two in on this together?
-Eun-hui.
-Stop it.
This doesn't make sense!
Here.
Seo-hae was wearing this.
Thank you.
Oh! I have the exact same necklace.
What a coincidence.
It might be a bit awkward in this
situation, but let me show you something.
Could I see that for a minute?
The way that uploaders
and downloaders work, to put it simply,
is like copying files on a computer.
They copy data in the future
and send it here.
But the original data and its copy
can't exist at the same time
because the copied data is given
a temporary status.
So…
if the data overlaps like this…
It was hard for me to believe it too.
Some stranger suddenly came up to me
and talked about protecting me
and saving the world.
When I wasn't such a valuable person.
I said, get down!
She was running around everywhere
trying to save the world,
but I only stood and watched.
I didn't know what to do.
No, even when I knew,
I was busy running away like a coward.
Did something happen to her?
Your daughter…
Your daughter is not well.
I thought you should know,
so I came to tell you.
I want to see her myself.
Hey.
Why did you bring this guy?
Because he's Seo-hae's father, of course.
Why don't you bring all her neighbors
and friends while you're at it?
Who is he?
No need for you to know.
She said
she got it
when she fell from a bike as a kid.
That's right.
This is impossible.
Seo-hae talked about you often.
She said you were really strong,
that you taught her
how to survive after the war.
According to her,
there's going to be a nuclear war soon.
Everyone's going to die.
She said that's why she came here
to change the past.
What's happening to her?
She's disappearing.
What do you mean?
Like that necklace? Why?
The Control Bureau did this to her.
Then what do I do?
We have to bring her back.
Go on. Hurry up.
Will you be okay?
Of course not!
But there's no other way.
I can't be of any help right now.
So hurry up.
Bingbing, you know what to do
if I'm not here in 24 hours, right?
Just shoot everyone.
Okay.
Let's go.
Just hang in there.
I'll be back soon.
YEAR 2035
Dad.
Take two pills after your meals.
It says you could get a stomach ulcer.
What's a "stomach ulcer"?
It's when there's a hole in your stomach
so it hurts a lot.
Then eat some more.
I'm fine now.
Dad.
Yes?
Who's Han Tae-sul?
Can I stop the war if I save Han Tae-sul?
Who told you that?
I don't know anyone like that.
And how can you stop a war
that already happened?
I can take an uploader and go to the past.
Gang Seo-hae! You promised
you wouldn't talk about that again.
You know who Han Tae-sul is, don't you?
-No, I don't!
-Why didn't you tell me?
-Why didn't you--
-I made a promise
with your mother.
You're lying.
You can't do it.
-I can.
-No!
How do you know that?
I know because I saw it. I saw it myself!
I saw you dying!
I saw it with my own eyes.
Whatever you try to do there,
you're going to fail.
Everyone you meet is going to die.
And everyone is going to try to kill you!
You'll have to keep running away
from them!
Seo-hae.
The past is much more terrifying
than the present. All right?
So don't ever mention this again.
Dad?
Dad.
Take 20mm of medicine twice a day.
Don't forget to take them after meals.
We only have 12 canned foods left.
If you ration it well, you'll have enough
until you're healed.
I'm taking half of the guns and bullets.
You said I'm going to fail,
but I'm still going to try.
Because I haven't done anything yet.
You asked who told me
if I could save the world
by saving Han Tae-sul.
It was me.
It was written in the journal
that I wrote to myself.
I might have ignored it
if it was from someone else.
And you might be right.
But I want to believe what I said.
I miss Mom so much,
and I feel so bad for you.
I wrote that I could succeed this time.
I can change everything.
I'll be back, Dad.
I love you. Thank you for everything.
My goodness.
All right.
Yes, they're all illegal entrants.
They're going to be adopted abroad.
How kind.
But isn't that illegal?
If you're that curious,
go in and ask her yourself.
Aren't you coming inside?
What if I run away?
Just run away, then.
I don't want to go in.
I'm not exactly on good terms with her.
Wow, I can't believe you're
actually afraid of someone.
Do you owe her money or something?
Hey. It's nothing like that.
I'll be looking around, so go ahead.
I'm not going in there.
My gosh. Don't fight, kids.
HWAMI ORPHANAGE
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
Agnes.
She's the one who made that drug.
Ask that woman how to save her.
SOCIAL PROCESS OF DOMESTIC ADOPTION
ISSUES OF ADOPTED CHILDREN
AGGRESSIVE CHILDREN
PTSD AFTER CAR ACCIDENTS
Damn it.
What the hell?
Who do we have here?
Aren't you the CEO Han Tae-sul?
Yes, that's my name,
but I'm not the CEO anymore.
That's right.
But what are you doing here?
Well…
Some evil person made a scary drug,
and there's someone who's suffering
because of it.
I came to ask
if there's any way to cure her.
Ms. Kim Agnes.
How did you find me here?
Was it Park Hyeong-do?
Is he the one who told you?
Was his name Hyeong-do?
I see. Well, anyway…
I don't know what he told you,
but what you're looking for isn't here.
This is just a plain orphanage.
All right. Stop fooling around.
I don't have much time.
Kim Seo-jin.
Those papers over there.
You wrote them.
I read them once when I couldn't sleep.
You were one of them.
So you were on the advance team?
What a surprise.
Give me the cure.
There's no such thing.
You made the drug.
The one used to torture people at the
Control Bureau. You must have its cure.
All right. Let me tell you something.
The last time I met you was
at Jaae Hospital,
when I ran into you
while running away from there.
So I have a bit of a grudge
against you right now.
Actually, a huge grudge.
Who is it for?
Seo-hae.
Why would I save her?
Because you're the one
who made her like that.
And I don't want to lose her.
You shouldn't have come here today.
Why?
-It's cute.
-Hi.
Hello.
Where's the director?
She left in the middle of a conversation.
She went into her office.
It's not my fault.
What do you mean?
HWAMI ORPHANAGE
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
He's here
right now.
Who?
Who's here?
Sometime in her past.
Go there and find her.
If you fail, you can't come back.
Why are we lost in your past?
Something is wrong.
I took the uploader from the future…
We don't believe
what illegal entrants say.
Mr. Han will never see you again
if I tell him what you did to Han Tae-san.
You're the last piece of the puzzle
for my plan.
What do you want from me?
Shoot me.
I don't want to see it anymore.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs