ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Seo-hae, listen to me.
Please.
Not today. Please, Seo-hae.
Not today.
Please.
Tae-sul…
-What happened?
-The camera must've been turned off.
He ran away.
Taxi!
Darn it!
Darn it.
Hey.
What about Sigma?
He's gone.
Darn it.
SEO-HAE
-What about the girl?
-I don't know.
Please leave a message…
Is she not picking up?
Isn't there a GPS tracker on her phone?
No, because of the Control Bureau.
Darn it.
Jeez.
Let's go, Bingbing.
Hello? Seo-hae?
Thank you. I survived thanks to you.
You jerk…
Why are you taking it out on me?
You made the decision.
What about Seo-hae?
Is she mad at you?
I didn't do anything.
She left of her own accord.
I don't think she'll come back to you.
After all, you just protected the person
who killed her father.
That's terrible.
Anyway, I owe you one today.
I'll take good care of your brother.
I swear I'm going to find you and--
And now I'm warning you.
Of course,
you're a precious resource to me.
So I won't kill you.
But you'd better not dig up my past again.
If you do,
I'll find all the people that you two love
and send their bodies back to you.
I'm telling you again. Don't find me.
I'll find you.
That's what our relationship
should be like. Okay?
Shut up, you bastard!
That asshole…
Gosh, my ear hurts.
He always had quite the temper.
-Mr. Hwang.
-Yes.
-You know the next step, right?
-Yes, sir.
All right,
you've all done a good job in politics.
Just enjoy everything from now on. Cheers!
-Cheers!
You know,
many great people
used to be nothing special in their past.
They never imagined
that they'd end up doing something great.
You know Edison, right?
He'd always lost against Tesla,
but what happened in the end?
He eventually won.
Tesla met a miserable end.
I heard he died in a motel room.
Am I right?
People these days only think
of electric cars
when they hear the name Tesla.
But they all know Edison.
I believe that you can become
such a person, Eddy.
Someone like Edison.
Your names are similar, too.
Isn't a war going to break out
if we make the uploader?
Tae-sul said so.
A war?
No.
Did he say I'm going to start a war?
How?
How would I do that?
That's nonsense.
Everyone's blaming me for everything.
The war was going to happen anyway,
and the uploader saved people.
The uploader that you made.
You might not know it now,
but the uploader saved lots of people.
Dr. Kim's mother survived
thanks to the uploader, too.
You see,
there's a cure for ALS in the future.
The sooner you make it,
the more people will be saved.
I don't really beg people to do things.
Someone else is going to beg you.
You have to make it.
Please.
Seo-jin.
So it won't work
without Han Tae-sul's code?
I'll get that code.
You just focus on the machine.
Why don't you have some snacks?
Oh, thank you!
We won't have to run
experiments for a while.
-Why?
-Then what do we do?
Let's finish the machine first.
Let's increase the capacity.
Here's the blueprint.
-Then how will we operate…
-That can come later.
Just focus on the machine.
Why don't you eat your snacks first?
-Thank you!
-Thank you for the food.
We have to increase the capacity.
RECENT CALLS
SEO-HAE
Please pick up.
Please pick up!
The person you are calling is unavailable.
Please leave a message after the beep.
SEO-HAE
Seo-hae, where are you right now?
I didn't get shot, and I'm fine.
So don't worry about me.
Don't wander around by yourself.
You'll get lost.
If you see any big buildings around you,
just send me a photo of them.
I'll come and get you.
I'll find you.
FEBRUARY 17, 2032
All right. I'll take the photo.
Look over here. You look so pretty.
One, two, three.
Seo-hae,
why don't you smile a little more?
All right. One, two… Just a little more.
Seo-hae, can't you smile more?
What's this awkward look?
Come on. I look pretty happy,
considering the world ended.
Let's measure your height.
Dad, I'm not growing anymore.
-I'm all grown up now.
-No way.
You should be at least 170cm to look good
when you meet a man like me.
-You should grow two more centimeters.
-Give me that.
Look here, Dad.
All right.
Let's see.
You finally smiled properly.
It looks good.
Aren't I good at taking photos?
You are.
FEBRUARY 17, 2032
Sis, I'm leaving now.
I just wanted to say goodbye.
Thank you for everything. Thanks to you…
Are you crying?
Answer me. Where are you?
Hello?
Darn it.
-I see.
-I knew it.
Right. I thought so too.
Do you really have to do that?
-What?
-I'm just telling the truth.
Is it girl talk?
That's where our old house is,
and that's where your grandma's house is.
Where's the uploader?
It's…
Achasan Station…
Here it is.
We have nine stations left to go.
What's this?
Use it as a last resort.
Open it when you have no other option.
Is it the girl or the world?
You can only choose one.
I saw a grave.
It was my grave.
That's where I found my diary.
Then I touched something.
I've been having that dream since then.
What dream is it?
It's about what's going to happen.
I remember now.
ACCESS POINT
TEHERAN-RO 255-7, GANGNAM-GU
ACCESS DATE
QUANTUM &amp; TIME HEADQUARTERS
You!
Come here.
Who is it?
I don't know.
You little…
That crazy bastard.
Mr. Park!
Why did you bring a gun? Who's it for?
What are you doing here?
-I was just passing by.
-Why pass by here?
Actually, Seon-ho told me to follow you.
Whatever. Just go.
Did you do everything I told you to do?
We're on it. I'll get to it later.
-Do you have anything to eat?
-No.
Are you waiting for someone?
-Who would I be waiting for?
-Who is it?
I'm not waiting for anyone.
Was that guy really Sigma?
Yes. He was really Sigma.
We could've stopped the war
if we just killed him. Right?
You idiot.
If he dies, we'll go out of business.
Maybe you're right.
Anyway, what's with the gun?
You little…
It's just for self-protection.
Plus, this is a democratic society.
I'm free to do whatever I want.
Stop being so nosy
and just mind your own business.
-Carrying a gun is illegal, though.
-I like illegal stuff.
So be quiet.
What was that?
That crazy jerk.
What's going on?
Hey, come out here.
Hey!
Come out!
You.
You're the guy who threw
a rock at me the other day, right?
It's you, plate 1148. Right?
Hey! Come on out here. You asshole.
Come on. Hey.
You jerk.
You're the guy who's been sending
my wife three million won
every month, aren't you?
What have you been doing with my wife?
Come on out, you jerk!
So you're refusing to come out,
you bastard?
Hey!
That crazy jerk is you!
Why did you come here?
You're the one who sent her
all that money, aren't you?
You asshole.
Just ram into him!
Oh, my gosh.
That jerk…
He's coming! What are you waiting for?
He's totally crazy.
All right, you jerk.
Mr. Park!
All right. Today's the day
you die.
Hyeong-do!
Stop it!
Stop this.
Have you lost your mind?
I'll kill you if you hit her.
I'm warning you. If you hit her
one more time, I'll really kill you.
Get lost.
-Let's go.
-What the heck is this?
-Let go of me!
-Let's go.
You jerk, 1148!
If I see you ever again, you're dead!
Let go of me! Stop coming here, you jerk.
That jerk… Let go!
Damn it.
SHELTER
I had nowhere else to go.
This is the only place I know.
Seo-hae, wake up.
Gang Seo-hae.
There's only one thing
you need to learn now.
How to survive.
No. I want to go home.
I promised your mom that I'll raise you
to be healthy and strong.
Hold it.
Stretch your arms out.
Keep your eyes open.
Keep your arms out straight.
That's it.
It's heavy.
The trigger will feel light.
Look ahead of you and shoot twice, okay?
Bang, bang.
Let's try it.
All right.
There's a monster in front of you.
Good job.
Breathe in and hold your breath.
Shoot.
Get ready again.
Hold your breath and aim.
Shoot.
Again!
Pick it up!
I won. I finally won!
I won!
DAD, MERRY CHRISTMAS
I LOVE YOU
Dad! Merry Christmas!
Hey! Come over here!
What are you doing here?
This is the only place you'd be.
How did you know this place?
Don't you get it?
I made this place.
A place for your family.
It doesn't matter how much it costs.
The air purification system
is the most important.
And we need a hydroponic system.
It should be earthquake-resistant
like nuclear power plants.
Make sure it can even endure
a nuclear bomb.
All right. You can see everything
on the blueprint, right?
Aren't you going to put that down?
You're not going to shoot me.
It's heavy.
Hold this instead.
Let's talk.
Go. I don't want to talk to you.
I'll leave in ten minutes.
I'm exhausted.
-Get out.
-Fine. Then I'll leave in three minutes.
Come over here.
I want to show you something.
You said medicines are the most important.
Antibiotics.
They're kept in cold storage.
Don't take these too often, though.
There's also an armory here, just in case.
And this room…
There are frozen bananas as well.
Even dried bananas.
Over there.
The shelves are full of frozen bananas.
And from there to there,
it's filled with tteokbokki.
it's filled with bulgogi.
And these
have been grown with a hydroponic system.
You need fresh food, too.
And one more thing.
The door.
Even when it breaks down,
now you can close it…
from both the inside and the outside.
It'll close no matter what.
So your mother will be safe now.
What happened before won't happen again.
You really
made this bunker?
I thought hard
after you told me about the bunker.
But there wasn't anyone
around you or your father who would have
the brains and wealth
or the initiative and drive
to make such a thing.
Except for me.
I'm not in the mood for jokes.
I felt like I had to do it.
No, I wanted to do it for you.
Even if we fail this time
and a war breaks out again,
the nine-year-old Seo-hae
and her parents
will be safe.
Three minutes have passed.
I'll get going now.
Well…
Should we turn off the lights now?
No. I want to keep them on.
Oh, you want to keep them on.
Why is this bed so small?
I should've ordered a bigger one.
You're ridiculous.
This bed felt so big when I was little.
But it was actually small.
Move your body like this.
Push with your right hand
and pull with your left.
Like this?
Put your feet at a 45-degree angle.
Keep your back straight.
Is this okay?
-Do it properly.
-I am doing it properly.
Am I doing it right?
There shouldn't be too much lubricant.
The gun might explode if the oil hardens.
And there shouldn't be anything
on the barrel. Or any cracks on it.
If you've checked everything…
It should feel smooth
when you pull it several times.
My target was over there,
and I practiced from over here.
How long did you stay in here
without going outside?
For nine years.
From when I was 9 until I turned 18.
At first, I didn't know that I wouldn't
be able to leave for a long time.
I couldn't tell if it was day or night,
summer or winter.
Every day was the same.
At first, I was curious about
whether the war was over
or what had happened to my friends.
But eventually, I didn't feel anything.
I didn't even realize
that time had passed.
But before I knew it, I became an adult.
Bang.
Seo-hae.
Yes?
Should we just live here together?
-Stop joking.
-I mean it.
There's enough food and medicine
for a hundred years.
And nobody will know that we're here.
If I'm gone, there won't be any uploader
and there won't be a war.
Then it will be peaceful out there.
People will be busy living their lives,
so they won't even care about us.
You said that before.
You see…
I had nightmares every night
while I was here.
About the day my mom died,
the nuclear bomb that I heard…
But you know what scared me the most?
The fact that the nightmare doesn't end
even when I woke up.
The scene, the sound…
I kept seeing and hearing it.
I prayed every night
for someone to end my nightmares.
And I felt like you could end them.
That's why I traveled in time to meet you.
What if…
What if we lose?
Then we'll start over in the next world.
We just have to get one step closer
each time we try.
We've come a long way,
and we'll get one step closer this time.
And if we keep doing that,
we'll be able to win in the end.
As long as we don't give up.
So we can't run away.
All right.
Seo-hae.
What have you done?
Seo-hae, wait.
Hey!
Wait here.
I'll come back after finishing everything.
Han Tae-sul. Open this door.
You're right. I can't keep running away.
What happened?
I saw the future.
You'll die if you go alone.
No, I can win. So don't follow me.
Just stay here. That's how I can win.
Open the door. Open this now!
I wanted to say goodbye properly.
I'm sorry, Seo-hae.
Don't go.
Don't go. Please.
Han Tae-sul!
FILTERS
VEHICLE TYPE
SEARCHING
The vehicle just passed Hangang Bridge.
Put it up on the screen.
43D 3494
-It's Han Tae-sul.
-Track him.
Yes, sir.
But he's not with the girl.
-What?
-Han Tae-sul's alone.
How long has it been?
It's been 18 hours
since she was last spotted.
Sir.
We have a problem.
The girl disappeared.
According to the records,
she should be with him right now,
but we can't find her.
What should we do?
Well…
HAN TAE-SUL
How did you get my number?
You should've taken better care
of your personal information.
-Are you--
-Listen to me carefully.
Everything that happens from now on
will be as I planned.
So you're going to be
playing into my hands now.
Why don't you try fighting that?
You bastard.
What are you waiting for? Find the girl.
Yes, sir.
It's getting interesting.
How will I win this time?
Darn it. I guess she wouldn't come here.
Where on earth is she?
Darn it.
Are you here?
Hey!
You scared me.
What are you doing?
Are you Chinese? Are you Japanese?
Food.
Jeez.
-You're Mr. Choi Jae-sun, right?
-What?
I'm from Immigration Control Bureau,
Team 7.
We have a few questions to ask you.
Please come with us.
Why? Can't we just talk here?
Your mother…
and your little sister
are in the US, right?
If you don't cooperate,
they can be forced to return to Korea.
Just come with us!
Hey, let go of me!
Just let me go!
Let go of me, will you?
Stop it, guys.
He's telling you to let go of him.
Sit.
Hi.
I'm Seo Gil-bok.
I guess you wouldn't know that name.
Sigma.
Have you heard that name?
Why does the war break out?
Sigma explodes a nuclear bomb.
Please don't kill me.
Who said I'm going to kill you?
Sit down.
It's nothing like that.
Sit back down. Don't worry.
Why would I kill an innocent person?
Do I look that evil to you?
What? No.
Or did Han Tae-sul tell you
that I'm the bad guy?
Oh, I guess he did.
You can't know the truth
by hearing just one side of the story.
How far do you know?
About what?
About me.
I heard that you're going to start a war.
Me? Why would I do that?
A war does break out,
but that happens all the time,
all over the world.
I'm just trying to earn some money
with uploaders.
Think about it. You can earn a lot
with those in the future.
Fine. Let's say what they said is true.
Let's say it's all my fault.
But does that affect you?
You don't care much about this country.
And it's not like you're some hero.
Why didn't you go to the States?
Because of Seo-hae?
She's a decent person
apart from being so nosy.
I like her too.
She's kind and she's a great fighter.
She's attractive.
Right.
But if we don't do anything,
Seo-hae's going to die
because of Han Tae-sul.
I don't want to hurt them,
but they keep coming at me.
I'll have no choice but to kill them.
I only want Han Tae-sul.
I don't need Seo-hae.
So take her and leave Korea
so she won't bother me.
What if
she doesn't listen to me?
Are you going to let her die, then?
Try to convince her, lie,
drag her, beg her.
Do whatever you can.
Then you can be together with Seo-hae.
And she'll live.
And Han Tae-sul
won't be near her.
She was last spotted near Hangang Bridge.
Can you think of anywhere nearby
she could be hiding?
You're trying to take her.
I can't trust
you people.
You little…
I guess I was too kind to you.
You can just die here, then.
I'll bring your mother and sister too.
This is your last chance,
so think carefully.
You keep thinking of the day
your family left Korea, right?
You keep regretting
not leaving with them, don't you?
Since you remind me of my past,
and you seem like a decent guy,
so I'm giving you one last chance.
All right, then.
Wait.
Yes.
You swear
you'll let Seo-hae live, right?
I promise.
All right.
I'll do it.
Don't drag her here.
Make her come of her own accord.
What should we do about Han Tae-sul?
I'll get him myself.
Where are you heading?
There's only one place he could go to.
Right.
A delegation consisting of congressmen
and Korean branch managers of US firms
have left from Incheon Airport
to visit the US this morning.
The delegation will assist the President,
who is in the US for a summit,
and promote economic revitalization
through cooperation with firms in the US.
I came to give you this.
It's the medicine for your mother.
He said that you'll get the rest
when everything is over.
And here's the address of the bunker
for you and your mother.
Thanks.
Are you all ready to move? Can I help?
It's just me and my mom.
There's nothing much to prepare.
It's fine.
Six months should be enough.
I heard the fallout will be gone by then.
I got everything ready
for you to go abroad after that.
You prefer Baltimore, right?
Your college friends are all there.
Seo-jin, should I come with you?
Why?
Well, you might need some help…
You know there's nothing between us now.
-You're making me uncomfortable.
-Seo-jin.
We already talked about this. I--
Seo-jin, don't just cut me off like that.
You can just contact me
when you need help.
You can just use me. I don't care
however you treat me.
So just let me stay by your side.
Seo-jin, can't you at least
pretend to think about it?
I can wait for you as long as it takes.
-How much is there left?
-I'm done with that side.
We just have to finish this side.
Time goes by so fast.
It's tomorrow already.
What do we do during the war?
We can't even go abroad.
We'll just have to get lots of sleep.
We really have tough lives.
Can't you read? It says we're closed!
Darn it.
You're up.
-What's the date today?
-October 30.
You've totally lost it.
You're getting all mixed up.
So why the hell do you keep going there?
Shut up and just give me the meds.
I don't have any.
-You don't?
-Of course not.
If you want to live longer,
stop wandering around so much.
And if you want to die soon,
you can move around.
Bingbing!
The doctor's leaving.
Just get lots of rest.
The war's tomorrow anyway.
All right, thanks. You get some rest too.
Where are you going?
He told you not to move.
You're going there again? Seriously?
No, I'm not.
Who'll take care of the shop if you die?
I'm not going to die!
The woman we saw,
she's your wife, isn't she?
You've been sending her three million
every month, right?
Why do you keep going there?
You always tell us
never to go looking for ourselves!
-You little… Move.
-No!
I saved your life last time.
Don't you know give and take?
I have to get something in return.
That's why you take something first
before you give anything.
People can take things
and pretend nothing happened. Move.
You'll die if you go there!
You're dying today, aren't you?
You said you were in jail
at the time of the war
because you killed someone.
The war's going to break out soon.
Who did you kill?
Did you kill yourself
to stop him from beating your wife?
Why can't you answer me?
Move.
Don't go!
-What's with you?
-Mr. Park!
Hey, look who's here.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Where's your girlfriend?
Right. Relationships are difficult,
aren't they?
-Give me a gun.
-A gun? Why?
To kill Sigma.
My gosh. How will you catch him?
You should've done it back then.
Why are you doing this
after letting him go?
-Just sell me a gun.
-No. I can't.
Seoul is going to be bombed soon,
and everyone's going to die.
Then guns are going to be really valuable.
Plus, I'm never selling any to you.
Money is just going to be toilet paper
once the war breaks out.
It's not money.
Open it.
Sir, it's medicine.
Antibiotics.
It's enough for over 50 years
after the war.
You've experienced it before,
so you know how precious it is.
Come on.
Give him a gun.
Do you even know how to shoot a gun?
Have you ever seen
a cornered mouse fighting a cat?
The mouse doesn't fight the cat
thinking that it'll actually win.
It knows it's going to die anyway.
But it fights
because it wants to go courageously.
There's a crack. Give me another one.
All right, let's say that you succeed
in getting to him.
But how will you kill him?
Like you said,
you're just in the palm of his hand.
Why? Because he's done this
so many times before.
It's not smooth. Give me another one.
Give him another one.
-All right.
-Oh, and a sniper rifle.
You're not Han Tae-sul, are you?
I'm not sure if you've heard this before.
"The future is already here.
We just don't know it yet."
Look at this bastard.
Excuse me. Just a moment.
-Where are you going? Working late?
-Yes.
Oh, why don't you just head home?
Pardon?
Just go home and keep your doors locked.
And make sure to close your windows.
Let's go home, everyone.
Everyone, go home.
The person you are calling is…
All Quantum &amp; Time employees.
Go home.
Why weren't you picking up?
I'm here.
-Welcome.
-Right. Where are you?
You said everything's your plan.
Then you should be able to find me.
You will make the uploader now.
You used this to explode the nuclear bomb.
Someone else will do it.
Aren't you scared of dying?
I am. But…
What scares me more
is surviving alone in the world.
Is this part of your grand scheme?
I saw the future.
The future where I win.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park