Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 17
Engagement?
Yes. Count Cheng’an said so.
I dare not ask more.
By the way, Your Grace,
do you remember
the servant by Count Rong’s side
in Rong’s mansion
back then?
The one
who was glib and loyal.
Yes, I do.
Why do you bring him up?
Today in Count Cheng’an’s mansion,
an old butler
looked exactly like that servant.
Strangely,
he didn’t seem to recognize me at all.
Is that so?
Perhaps we are old.
He didn’t remember your look.
These two are the best in our shop,
but you are still not satisfied.
Though I like them,
I don’t know which one I should buy.
Certainly, this one is good.
As the saying goes,
you get what you pay for.
I’m telling you a secret.
This is a limited edition.
Limited edition?
Exactly.
I’ll take this one!
Sure.
Your taste is bad, isn’t it?
Last time, we fancied the same one.
Since my taste is bad,
you are no better than me.
Things have changed.
Moreover,
you guessed it right last time.
I know nothing about it.
You can boast as you please.
Boast?
Sir, tell her. Do I know these things?
Of course you know.
You are an expert.
In that case,
sir, did you lie to me just now?
That’s not true.
Well... They have their own merits.
They have their own merits.
Look.
The gloss of this plate
is not so bright as that one,
but it’s more natural, isn’t it?
Moreover, take a close look.
Isn’t this one more translucent?
It must be the superb glass
imported from foreign countries.
The boss is unaware of its rarity,
so he priced it wrongly.
Really?
Why bother lying to you?
I’ll take it if you don’t.
Sir, I’ll take this set.
Yes, miss.
Have a check.
If it’s fine,
I’ll deliver it to your mansion.
Have a check?
Easy peasy. Four words.
Look. Listen. Compare. Touch.
First, look.
Look at its appearance carefully.
The shape. Gloss. Pattern.
If there are any visible defects.
Second, listen.
Knock it.
Is the sound good?
It sounds good.
That means it’s a good plate.
Next, compare.
You two are so intimate.
Are you picking dowries?
We are picking dowries,
but I will not marry him.
Nor will I marry her.
What do you mean by that?
Am I not good enough for you?
So what if you are?
Will you marry me?
You...
You rogue!
Shameless!
Why did I have such a dream?
Count Cheng’an!
Will he get in danger?
Your Grace.
Why do you look so pale?
Do you feel unwell?
Let me take you there and have a rest.
I’m fine.
I’m gonna supervise Ban Heng’s training,
lest he’ll slack off again and run away.
No worries, Your Grace.
I will not allow him to run away.
Your Grace! Your Grace!
Your Grace!
Your Grace! Bad news!
Something happened
in Count Cheng’an’s Mansion!
What happened there?
It seems someone died there!
Someone died?
Your Grace!
Young Master.
Where is my sister going?
Someone died in Cheng’an’s Mansion.
Someone died...!
No!
If Count Cheng’an is really dead,
my sister will be known
for predestined widowhood!
It’s my fault.
I should’ve reminded you of this.
Who is your murderer?
I swear I’ll avenge your death.
Your Grace.
Tell me.
Who on earth killed him?
Yesterday, Butler Rong was impacted
by an uncontrollable carriage.
He had died before the physician came.
Hua.
I...
Come with me.
Hua.
What’s on your mind?
Why don’t you talk to me?
We are done from now on.
If you don’t love me,
why do you come here?
If you don’t worry about me,
why are you shedding tears?
I...
You wished us
to be frank to each other,
didn’t you?
But now,
why don’t you be frank and tell me?
I dreamed my family was confiscated.
I don’t want you dead.
Dream?
Yes.
I’ve been having these weird dreams,
the break-off of my engagement,
the blindness of Xie Qilin,
and the death of my grandmother.
I dreamed all of these things.
More terribly,
all these dreams have come true.
So,
you dreamed I got killed.
That’s why you come here?
You deliberately refused me,
for you feared I’d get implicated?
I’ve been all alone.
Not until I met you,
did I know there’d be
another way to live.
Hua, as long as I can be with you,
I don’t fear death.
If my family really falls...
You have me.
I won’t let that happen.
Hua.
Rest assured.
From now on,
I’ll guard you all the time,
and the whole Ban family.
Because you all are my family.
I will never allow any harm
to my family.
Thank you.
Hua. Hua.
Go get a physician!
Hua.
Hua, you woke up.
The physician said you were weak
due to anxiety.
And you had a cold.
You need some medicine and a good rest.
I’m going home.
Okay, take the medicine
and I’ll send you home.
No bother.
Be good and take the medicine.
Why are you laughing?
I know you wanna stay with me.
What do you mean?
If you don’t,
why do you refuse to take the medicine?
You don’t wanna recover too soon,
so you can stay longer with me.
You bookworm.
You’re good at coaxing.
Have you arranged Butler Rong’s funeral?
Yes, as you required, Young Master.
But I suspected
there’s something fishy about his death.
Investigate and figure out the truth.
Report to me any time.
Yes.
Well...
How is Her Grace now?
She’s fine.
She just needs some more rest.
Should I prepare
some chicken soup for her?
Darling.
Count Cheng’an is supposed to
come and propose.
When he comes,
what betrothal presents
should I ask from him?
The matchmaker hasn’t come yet.
Now are you thinking about the dowry?
I can’t marry my daughter to him
for nothing.
Since Hua was born,
I’ve been thinking to be father-in-law
and put on airs.
Now my dream is about to come true!
The dowry should be
the first consideration.
Besides what we’ve prepared for Hua,
we need four chefs,
and eight or ten embroiderers
from the south.
Eight or ten?
To match with Hua,
we should make more outfits for him.
Hua gets used to her own bed.
A new bed should be customized
and delivered to her.
So many things?
We can have him marry into our family,
lest we move all the things there.
That’s a good idea.
Yeah.
Hua doesn’t have to leave home!
Right!
The thing is that,
will she be reluctant to marry
for fear of implicating him?
You brat.
Dreams aren’t necessarily true.
She dreamed our family was confiscated.
Now we got promoted.
She’s a Princess.
I’m the Prime Minister.
Father. Mother.
Hua, you are back.
Hua.
You look radiant.
Count Cheng’an
has taken good care of you.
It’s my honor to care for Hua.
Rocky. Take Ban Hua back to her room.
Yes.
Why should I go back?
Your Grace.
-I’ve learnt new massage skills.
-Go back.
I can help you cure the cold.
Yes, go back for a rest.
Greetings. Mr. Ban. Mrs. Ban.
Today I come to see you
for the promise I made
to Princess Royal.
Please allow me
to marry Ban Hua.
Count Cheng’an.
You and I are on good terms,
but it concerns my daughter’s happiness
in the future.
I need to discuss it with my wife.
Right?
Father. You didn’t say so just now.
No one sees you as dumb.
If I can have your approval,
I promise I’ll love her all my life,
and never betray her.
If I break my word,
I shall have a miserable
and lonely life,
and my fame shall be ruined.
You bet so big?
Count Cheng’an.
Ban Hua doesn’t love books.
You two share no hobby.
Once married,
you’ll be together for decades.
Have you made up your mind?
Rest assured, Mrs. Ban.
She is no ordinary girl.
I won’t treat her
in an ordinary way.
As for what she likes,
I’ll learn to appreciate and understand.
As for what she doesn’t like,
I’ll never push her.
Some decades
is far too short for us.
If there’d be afterlife,
I’d still marry her as my wife.
You make me want to marry you.
Darling, so your decision is...
My wife and I...
have agreed.
As for Ban Hua,
it depends on you.
Thanks for your kindness.
Count Cheng’an.
My sister is a handful.
You may pay more attention to her.
Go to see her.
Have a good talk with her.
Go ahead. Have a good talk.
Sure.
Du Jiu.
Do you think it will work?
Sir, you prepared it wholeheartedly.
I believe
Her Grace will not turn you down.
What if she says no?
Then we can try other ways.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Your Grace.
They have important things
to talk about.
Please stay here.
What are you doing?
They have important things
to talk about.
Please don’t disturb them.
It’s wonderful.
Your Grace, what is it for
to invite me here
for your zither playing?
Your Grace. Are you all right?
Why is your face flushing red?
Do you get infected by me
and have a cold?
I’m fine, Hua.
It’s too hot in the room, maybe.
Let’s get some air on the balcony.
You picked a good room.
Look.
From the balcony,
the best night view here can be seen.
Hua.
Today, I actually...
I asked you here...
To tell you...
That...
We may...
We may get...
Have you got it?
Your Grace.
What are you talking about?
Hua.
Marry me.
What are you doing?
Young Master. What brings you here?
It’s a big moment for my sister.
How can I miss it?
But,
I haven’t had enough
of being single.
As long as you agree to marry me,
the wedding day is up to you.
What if I wanna be single all my life?
Well,
can you allow me
to be by your side all my life?
It’ll be too hard for you, won’t it?
Certainly not.
Being with you,
I can’t be happier.
How could it be hard?
Then could you tell me
since when did you fall for me?
I’m quite curious.
I...
You can’t even answer this,
and you want to marry me?
You mistook me.
I think,
I fell for you
at the autumn hunting.
When you took advantage of me
in the bush?
No.
I mean the time
when I got drunk
and shot the arrow with you.
Then it came to me that
it should be the skating.
I’ve been into you unknowingly.
So, you’ve been into me
since then.
That explains.
You helped my family over and over.
Yes.
Then I get along well with your parents,
and your brother.
From them, I feel the long-gone warmth.
I got to know
you are the one of my life.
Count Cheng’an
looks shy and gentle,
yet he’s so good at love words.
Scholars are indeed different.
Yeah.
I suppose
my sister has got his virgin
when she was in his mansion.
No. No. No.
Let me ask you, Your Grace.
If my family
gets in great disaster,
what will you do?
I will definitely stand out
and guard your family.
If I die accidentally,
what will you do?
I’ll protect all your families,
and keep you in my mind
for the time to come.
Count Cheng’an.
You are really silly.
Why do you say so, Hua?
If you die,
I’ll definitely remarry.
For the sake that
you’re simple-minded,
I may agree to marry you.
What’s wrong with you?
I’ve agreed, haven’t I?
Great! Hua.
I thought you’d turn me down.
I could barely breathe.
You are sincere to me.
How can I turn you down?
You scholars are so silly.
Du Jiu.
Get me the love knots.
On my way, Young Master.
-Hurry.
Cheng.
We’re here to back you up.
Put it on.
♪I meet you♪
♪When the flowers bloom like rain♪
♪I’ll wait for you here♪
♪We hit on at the first sight♪
♪You give me the courage♪
Let me help you.
♪To love forever and ever♪
Hua.
May we grow old together
until death do us apart.
No worries, Your Grace.
We’ll never be apart.
♪However cold it is♪
♪Lean and kiss in the moonlight♪
♪Heart to heart♪
♪Share my coat with you♪
♪To be against the cold wind♪
♪Travel through time to see you♪
♪Again I dress up for you♪
♪Share weal and woe♪
♪For the everlasting wish♪
So, Ban Hua said yes?
Thanks to Your Majesty’s blessing.
That’s great.
The Ban family acts wild,
but they do show respect to me
when it comes to my request.
Thanks to Your Majesty’s efforts.
Prime Minister said
if it weren’t for your matchmaking,
they wouldn’t even allow me
to go to their mansion.
Don’t take it to heart.
My cousin is
just stubborn.
My kindness to them has paid off.
Finally,
what I promised my aunt is fulfilled.
By the way,
have you got any clue
about Princess Royal’s murderer?
Your Majesty.
I’ve ordered
to investigate it separately.
No exact information for now.
Prime Minister Ban will be your family.
You must get it to the bottom
and uphold justice for them.
I’ll thoroughly investigate it
and find out the murderer
as soon as possible.
Young Master.
Why can you never parry this strike?
I bear no grudge with you.
Why trying to kill me with every blow?
You even strike harder.
That’s the way of sword training.
If you don’t try all out,
how can you do better?
That doesn’t make sense.
Come. Let’s sit down and talk.
Are you sitting?
Do you have guts to slack off?
Hua.
We haven’t talked for long.
Let’s have a word or two.
Then continue the training.
A word or two?
First word.
I think
you agreed to marry him too soon.
You want me to marry him
all the time, don’t you?
Yes, that’s true.
But you should make the process harder.
The harder you make it,
the more he loves you.
Isn’t it hard enough?
Never enough.
I’m a man.
I know what men are thinking.
Too late. I’ve agreed.
I think another man
is needed to meddle in it.
Shi Jin is a good choice.
He’s been admiring you.
No.
He could be the man in black.
We must be on guard.
How so?
I can’t talk with you.
Softy.
Continue.
Yes.
Listen, make it harder day by day.
No worries, Your Grace.
I’ll never forget this.
Softy.
No wonder
I can’t parry the last strike of yours.
You make the blow harder and harder?
Of course. Or how can you do better?
I’m going to Count Cheng’an.
Hua. Have some more talk with me.
Have some more...
Young Master, shall we?
Noodles
Hua, this is the restaurant.
Is this the West Noodles Restaurant?
Noodles
Do you think it’s too average?
No.
It’s said that
their noodles are very tasty,
usually sold out before noon.
Have you come here before?
I passed by, but didn’t try it.
Sir, two bowls of plain noodles.
Sure.
The noodles are simple but so delicious.
He didn’t lie to me.
Who?
Softy.
She told me that
the noodles here were very delicious.
Back then,
I didn’t really have a chance
to dine in such a noodles restaurant.
If I knew it earlier,
I’d be a regular here.
Noodles
Any other delicacies here?
Yes, vegetarian dumplings.
Wait for me.
How come you are here, Your Grace?
Lord Shi.
Are you here for noodles?
Seems I’m too late
to honor my promise.
The noodles are really tasty.
Lord Shi.
Your Grace.
Hua. Dumplings are ordered,
and will be served soon.
You called her name, Your Grace.
Isn’t it too rude...?
You mistake it, Shi.
I asked him to call my name.
You don’t know it, Shi.
I’ve engaged with her.
What’s wrong with the address?
Is it true, Your Grace?
Yes, Lord Shi.
I’ve agreed to marry him.
Sir, pack up the dumplings for me.
Yes, sir.
Your Grace.
Lord Shi. It’s going to rain.
Hurry and go for a shelter
from the rain.
Noodles
Shi.
How did you get drenched?
Go get changed.
Feixian.
Count Cheng’an is
no longer your concern.
Shi Jin. Could it be...
You’ve known the woman he will marry?
Ask no more about it.
How can I not ask?
He’ll marry another woman.
My heart hurts like being stabbed.
Who is the woman?
How did she
force him to marry her?
Why do you think
she forced him to marry her?
What if Count Cheng’an really loves her?
What else would you say?
But in the whole capital,
only I deserve to marry him.
Shi Jin. Tell me the truth,
so that I can give up.
Give up
or you’ll retaliate?
You’ve underestimated me.
I’ll take back what I want
with my own hands.
People in Daye will know
I am
the only perfect match for him.
Miss Shi.
Greetings, Miss Shi.
Greetings.
Miss Shi.
Who do you think
is the fiancée of Count Cheng’an?
Shouldn’t it be Miss Feixian?
I’ve asked all the nobles
in the capital,
but no one knows it.
It’s weird. Isn’t she of noble blood?
Don’t make wild guess.
When Count Cheng’an comes,
we can ask him about it.
What will you ask him?
Your Grace?
If I remember it correctly,
Your Grace isn’t invited
for this poetry party.
Are Your Grace interested in poems?
I’m not interested.
Count Cheng’an insisted,
so I come here.
Thanks for your invitation, Miss Shi.
I come with my fiancée
without prior notice.
Please pardon me, ladies.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪