Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 18
If I remember it correctly,
Your Grace isn’t invited
for this poetry party.
Are you interested in poems?
I’m not interested.
Count Cheng’an insisted,
so I come here..
Thanks for your invitation, Miss Shi.
I come with my fiancée
without prior notice.
Please pardon me, ladies.
So it’s Princess Ban.
It’s too mysterious.
If I may ask,
when were you engaged?
None of your business.
I’m not asking Your Grace.
You are not asking me.
Are you asking my fiancé?
Hua, it doesn’t matter.
Just a few days ago,
I proposed to Her Grace.
I humiliated myself.
Excuse me.
Miss Shi.
Let’s make it clear.
His Grace and I come over
by appointment.
But Miss Shi
leaves with tears in your eyes.
If you’re seen by outsiders,
they may think I’ve bullied you.
Bully me?
I’m afraid Your Grace thinks
too much of yourself.
I’m the granddaughter of the
prime minister to three emperors,
the younger sister
of the Crown Princess.
I’m proficient in zither, chess,
calligraphy, painting, verses and odes.
What do you have to bully me?
Hua.
What am I working so hard for?
I lost to that ignorant woman.
Why is it her of all women?
On beauty,
I will never lose to Ban Hua.
Ban Hua.
I won’t give up.
Count Cheng’an
must be mine.
Miss, go back to your room,
otherwise, master will get angry again.
My wedding has been delayed
by three months.
I’m idle at home.
Let me make steamed chicken
with scallion oil,
and let my brother have a taste.
No. Master specially ordered
not to let you in the kitchen,
otherwise, he’ll dock my wage.
Don’t worry.
If he docks you one tael,
I’ll compensate you with two taels.
All told, you can earn some money.
Is… Is it okay?
Yes, it’s very okay.
Mr. Shi.
Young Master,
I tried my best,
but I couldn’t stop her.
I see, let her do it.
You may leave.
Yes.
I knew you like
steamed chicken with scallion oil
I made.
But it shouldn’t be me to have it.
It should be your future husband.
But I haven’t married His Highness.
Is it proper if I
send a dish to him?
Today, you just cook.
But you must cook it
as well as you can.
After you finish it,
come with me to the side yard.
My sister heard
Your Highness was coming,
So she made her specialty for you.
Did she?
Your Highness, please have a taste.
Steamed chicken with scallion oil
I cooked by myself.
I don’t eat chicken.
I’ll cook other dishes next time.
What else don’t you eat?
I will avoid those.
Don’t bother.
My sister cooks very well.
It’s no trouble at all.
I eat nothing other than
what the royal cook makes.
“I eat nothing other than
what the royal cook makes”.
I’d rather feed the dog
than offer it to you.
-Bite it!
Come on!
It’s losing.
-Bite it.
-How can it defeat mine?
We win at last.
-Bite!
-Bite it!
I’m leaving. Have fun.
Go away.
The flavors of scallion
complement the chicken perfectly.
It’s tasty and refreshing
while not greasy.
This is the number one steamed chicken
with scallion oil I’ve ever eaten.
Where did you buy the chicken?
Tell me.
It’s my family specialty,
not sold on the market.
It’s not sold?
I can’t buy such delicious chicken.
What if I want to eat it again?
Would you give me this as well?
Unexpectedly,
he is the one who understands me.
The mourning period for my aunt
has ended.
I ask you to come
to discuss the marriage of our children.
Hua is born beautiful.
No matter how you’re dressed,
you always look appealing.
Your Grace,
You look in high spirits because of
the happy events. It’s enviable.
I’m lucky to be with Hua.
Naturally, I must make some changes
to be worthy of Her Grace.
Hua’s true feelings
and true characters are very rare.
Count Cheng’an, you must thank me
to bestow you
such a great marriage.
Your Majesty, I will never
forget your kindness.
Duke Ban,
have you fixed the wedding date?
Your Majesty,
I think we should
listen to the kids’ opinion.
Then what’s your opinion?
Your Majesty,
I’ve made an agreement with
Count Cheng’an.
He can only marry me in his life.
Otherwise, I’ll repudiate him,
taking away all my dowry
and half of his property.
As for the wedding date,
I haven’t made my decision yet.
I’ll let Your Majesty know
when it’s decided.
Your Grace, it’s against common sense,
isn’t it?
Well,
Duke Ban won’t agree surely.
I don’t agree.
Look, Ban,
it’s against ritual and law.
It’s ridiculous.
What do you know about ritual and law?
So, as you say,
Count Cheng’an would better
marry into her family.
Your Majesty,
I’ll only marry Her Grace
in my life,
and won’t have a concubine.
No matter how many terms
Her Grace proposes,
I’ll accept with pleasure.
Count Cheng’an is right.
It’s your business.
You must decide for yourselves.
Once the date is decided,
we must hold a splendid wedding.
Your Majesty,
about my daughter
and Prince Luos’ marriage,
you may…
I’ve ordered the Astronomical Bureau
to choose a new date.
A splendid wedding will be held too.
Your Majesty,
thank you for your kindness.
Silk flowers! Silk flowers!
Buy some silk flowers.
Young lady,
these are the most popular
silk flowers in the capital.
Would you like to buy one?
Please buy one.
Your Grace.
No.
You’re so beautiful!
Not half so beautiful as you are.
Young Master, you and the madam
are really close.
Mammy, I haven’t married him yet.
I’m dim-sighted and say it wrong.
Please forgive me.
Never mind.
She is about to marry me.
It’s just a matter of time
to call her madam.
Wish you a long lasting
harmonious union.
Have a lovely baby soon.
Mammy.
I’ll buy all of your silk flowers.
Thanks. Young Master and Young Lady.
Thank you very much.
Your Grace, you’re going to
wear them all the time, aren’t you?
As long as you like it, why not?
What’s up?
Nothing. I could be wrong.
The man seemed to be Jiang Luo.
Come on.
Jiang Luo is suspicious.
I must find out what he’s doing.
Feixian.
Your Highness, you’re engaged.
You mustn’t be rash.
The engagement is my father’s will.
I can’t violate it.
You know I only love you.
I’m wondering
how true
your love is?
You invite me here today.
Seems you need my help.
I want to destroy a person.
If it’s Ban Hua, I’d love to.
Are you serious?
Where did Jiang Luo go?
But I have conditions.
If you can do it,
I
must satisfy you.
Ban Hua!
A prince to be married
does such a thing.
Aren’t you ridiculous?
Ban Hua, if you dare to tell,
I must skin you.
Are you scaring me?
I don’t buy it.
What do you want?
I want you to apologize to her.
Well, are you unwilling to?
Do you want me to tell His Majesty,
and ask him to give the order?
Fine. I apologize.
Feixian, I’ll never be disloyal to you.
Don’t worry.
I’ll keep all the words I said just now
as long as you…
Ban Hua!
Now you’re making an apology.
Are you done?
Get out if you are done.
Don’t worry.
Although I don’t like you,
I’ll keep this a secret.
I’m not going to ruin your reputation.
But I shall give you some advice.
The day has eyes, the night has ears.
Jiang Luo is getting married.
You don’t need
another woman’s husband
to please you, do you?
Jiang Luo is perverse.
Avoid him as possible as you can.
I have many disagreements
with Jiang Luo and Shi Feixian.
It doesn’t matter to have one more.
Yes.
They’ve always been hard on you.
Even if you don’t mess with them,
they’ll mess with you.
But it surprises me that
they had a secret meeting.
What did they want?
Was it because
Jiang Luo tried to escape marriage?
Then why did he want to see
Shi Feixian?
Was it possible that Shi Feixian
wanted to see him?
No.
Shi Feixian is still infatuated
with His Grace.
She had no reason to see him.
Then what’s the reason?
Long live Your Majesty.
You may rise.
It’s this place again.
This time I must see clearly of him.
How dare you!
The dream was not all bad.
Your Grace.
Your Grace. Don’t you feel well?
Why do you get up so early
in order to draw here?
Don’t talk nonsense.
I’m doing something big.
Your Grace,
what strange dream have you had?
Share it with me to amuse me.
Be serious.
Today, I made up my mind.
From now on,
I will never sleep late again.
Now that Rong Xia
is going to marry me,
I must be determined to work hard
and never let our family
broken-down.
You’re right. Work hard.
Where did you get so many books?
Hua.
Even if you’re good at reading,
you don’t have to show off.
There’re so many books.
When will you finish reading them?
My family aren’t as rich as yours.
These are just ancient books,
calligraphy and paintings.
Don’t worry.
After you marry me,
I’ll share everything with you.
My family gets nothing else,
but we do have money.
I won’t let Your Grace get starved.
Thank you in advance.
Your Grace, are you joking?
Ode to Spring River
The Ode to Spring River
under your butts alone
is worth hundreds of taels of silver.
Hundreds of taels?
You read and write poems every day.
When did you earn so much money?
You just don’t know.
These are all left by my parents.
Our master and madam were
proficient in verses, odes,
calligraphy and painting.
They were a fairy couple
in harmony.
Du Jiu, if you have spare time,
dry some more books in the sun.
You haven’t married her yet,
but you start to help her
instead of your own family.
A grown man can’t be kept at home.
In harmony. Fairy couple.
I’m screwed.
I’m not good at zither-playing, chess,
calligraphy and painting.
What should I do in the future?
I wonder
if Your Grace can play zither?
Radiant
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
The string is broken.
Your zither isn’t in good quality.
Playing zither is like
practicing martial arts.
It’s difficult to make achievements
without years of hard work.
Do you really want to learn?
You don’t have to put forth
so much strength.
Rub gently. Pluck slowly.
Wait. Wait.
Come on, do me a favor.
My hair is tangled.
I’m afraid Huahua is not
as naughty as you are.
Can you hurry up?
Don’t be anxious.
I’ll be gentle.
I won’t hurt you.
Enough.
Playing zither is boring.
I want to learn something else.
Well.
I wonder if Your Grace play go?
I’ll put it
here.
No, no, no, no.
I’ll put it here.
You’re smiling. There must be a catch.
Then I should…
Here.
I’ll put it here.
Are you sure this time?
Trying to deceive me again?
I won’t be fooled this time.
Playing go
is like my grandfather going to war.
Arranging armies and embattling
are all about schemes.
I’ll put it here despite what you said.
Fine, if you’re determined.
Next game.
I lost again?
It’s impossible.
I was having the upper hand.
Did you scheme against me?
Hua, don’t be anxious.
Weigh your strength before
attacking your rival…
Stop it.
I am really troubled by you.
Well,
let’s play the last game.
This time,
you let me take back one move.
I’m sure I can win you.
But, Hua,
I’ve already
let you take back 20 moves.
How about I yield on this game?
20 moves already?
Were there so many?
Your Grace, I think
playing go is boring, too.
It’s not practical.
Right. Playing go is social grace.
It’s not practical for you.
Do you paint?
Are you painting
a steamed bread?
Of course it’s not.
This is a goldfish. This is a turtle.
You can’t blame me.
Turtle is hard to draw.
And the goldfish
has a long tail
which is hard to draw, too.
The flowing tail is the beauty
of a goldfish.
You’ve just started to paint.
It’s really a bit difficult.
Let me teach you how to
use the writing brush.
You’ll learn it soon
with your intelligence.
Moisten the edge of the brush first,
you’ll catch
the glistening light of waves.
If you had taught me early,
what couldn’t I learn?
This one is him. The other one is me.
They look well matched.
Look.
Painting is like
practicing martial arts.
Talent is important,
but it still needs a long time
to practice.
Few noble ladies are good at painting
in the capital.
Shi Feixian is the only one
who has made some achievements
through years of hard practicing.
Rong Xia,
the painting you’ve drawn
isn’t about you and me.
It’s about you and Shi Feixian,
isn’t it?
You misunderstood me.
I mean Shi Feixian has spent
ten years on studying calligraphy
and painting since childhood.
Your painting is not bad.
It’s just slightly inferior to hers.
Why don’t you teach her?
Don’t teach me anymore,
in case I become your eyesore.
I…
I won’t let you two have this.
Hua.
I…
Ban’s Mansion
It’s weird.
I feel different today
from yesterday while I play zither.
It must be because
you’re intelligent.
A word to you is sufficient.
Really?
Well…
I say nothing but the truth.
In Daye,
few people are better than you
in playing zither.
Over time, you’ll leave your name
in the history book.
Good.
From now on,
I will practice harder.
I must prove myself
to those who laugh at me.
Your Grace,
you’ve been playing all morning.
Your hands must be sore.
Why don’t you let me
give you a massage?
Don’t bother.
My hands are not sore
even when I play with swords.
This is a piece of cake.
Ban Hua.
How about I spend 12 more hours
on doing horse stance every day,
and you spend six hours less
on practicing zither?
You’re noisy.
Don’t interfere with my practice.
Step aside.
Master.
-Master.
-Are you all right?
I’m old.
I’m unable to stand that.
Could you at least
show your father a little pity?
What’s the matter with you?
Why don’t you let me practice?
Is it because
I’ve been playing it badly?
Daughter,
it… It’s not so badly.
It’s…
it’s just a little…
a little
unpleasant to the ear.
-Master.
-Are you all right?
Master, are you all right?
Take care. Take care.
Gentlemen, what…
Hua, what was happening?
Why did you lie to me?
No. Hua.
Actually, at one point…
I’ve been playing it badly.
Bad playing is bad.
Good playing is good.
You should state it outright.
I’ve never
been a person who doesn’t
listen to good advice.
Rong Xia, I hate being lied to,
especially by you.
Don’t teach me if you’re unwilling to.
Could I really stop teaching you?
As the saying goes,
a physician doesn’t cure himself.
It’s feared that skills might be
disturbed by emotions.
I thought it was wrong to teach you,
but if I don’t teach you…
Then don’t teach me again.
Don’t teach me today.
Don’t teach me tomorrow.
Don’t teach me in your life.
Cheers.
Heng.
I know we should consider it
in the long run.
But these days,
we fight crickets and eat out.
We’ve been keeping up our energy
for long.
It’s time to teach me
how to get along with Hua.
Let’s not regard each other
as an outsider.
I am the only one
who can handle her.
Do you know
in the world,
which man has
known my sister for the longest time?
Of course it’s you.
No.
It’s my father.
Do you know
in the world,
who knows my sister best?
That must be your father.
You’re wrong. It’s me.
I’ve been pissing off my sister
every day since childhood.
On the experience of confronting,
I’m unique in the world.
So, next,
you do whatever I say.
Yes, I’m stupid.
I don’t have any experience
on pleasing girls.
I’ve been following the art of war,
but I failed for so many times .
If you’re willing to teach me today,
I must learn with an open mind.
Heng, can you tell me
what the method is?
Since you don’t have enough experience,
let’s get more experience.
What is Rong Xia thinking?
What stops him from seeing me?
No girl would like such a man
except me.
I’m so mad.
Bad news, Your Grace.
Your Grace.
The young master took Count Cheng’an
to the brothel.
How dare you!
Today I must have a
good conversation with you.
Your Grace. Calm down.
He is a count after all.
Don’t beat him to death.
Rong Xia, come out.
Rong Xia.
The princess. She is the princess!
Your Grace, could I have your autograph?
In my lifetime,
I can actually see a living princess.
I’m really honored.
You… You know me?
Of course.
Your Grace are an idol for all of us.
Your chivalrous act of rescuing Yun
has widely spread
all over the brothel.
That’s right.
There’s such a
generous and kind princess
in the world,
and she is so beautiful.
We all dream of seeing you.
Your Grace, your hairpin
is so beautiful.
Your dress is beautiful too.
No problem.
If you do me a favor,
in the future,
I’ll give all these to you.
You are welcome, Your Grace.
At your disposal.
I’m looking for my fiancé.
I want to know where he’s hiding.
Your Grace, this way.
Your Grace, the man you are looking for
is right here.
Sister, have you had dinner?
Ben Heng, where’s Rong Xia?
Tell me frankly.
I promise you’ll live till tomorrow.
My brother-in-law?
He is not with us.
Believe me.
He’s really not here.
Ask them if you don’t believe me.
That’s the truth.
Ever since you’re engaged,
nobody in Daye dares to
invite Count Cheng’an
to the brothel.
None of us dares to lie to you.
Then where is Rong Xia?
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
It seems that
I’m really not good at archery.
♪The rain pours down on a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
Rong Xia,
what’re you doing here?
Didn’t you go to the brothel?
I’m engaged.
It’s inappropriate to go to the brothel.
It’s disrespectful to Your Grace, too.
You have some consciousness.
I’ve been practicing for a day.
I just got it.
If you teach me archery,
and I’m obviously bad at it,
but you’ll lie to me that
I’ve made great progress.
It will discourage the learner.
It’s really inappropriate.
You really wanted to learn zither,
chess, calligraphy and painting,
but I didn’t take it seriously.
I’m the one who made all the faults.
Can you forgive me?
Being angry is bad for your health.
I want to learn zither, chess,
calligraphy and painting, because…
Never mind.
Your Grace, it’s not a good example.
I wonder how you passed
the imperial examination?
Alright. Alright.
I receive your instruction today.
Now I’m ready to listen to your advice.
Could you give me a chance
to learn archery from you?
Of course.
I’ll show you
what a good master is like.
Mingyue House
Host.
Young Master Ban.
What’s good here?
I’ll have all of them.
I’m lucky today.
I won a round sum.
Will my sister go to the brothel or not?
Surely I know that.
Young Master Ban, did you make a bet
on the princess again?
It’s not what it sounds like.
Firstly, the bet was to test
my sister’s true heart.
Secondly,
It was to deepen her feelings
for Count Cheng’an.
At last, it won some
pocket money for me.
It was good business.
All right. All right.
I’ll prepare you some good food.
You’re getting married tomorrow.
Why do you eat out at this time?
Is it because Jiang Luo
breaks the promise of marriage?
Of course not. Don’t talk nonsense.
I’m just worried
I can’t eat this soup any more.
So I come to taste it again.
You made me happy for nothing.
Happy for nothing?
What were you happy about?
I was happy to see your misfortune.
How can’t you know that?
What kind of man are you?
You just can’t bear to
see a happy person.
Do you think
it’s really happy to marry Jiang Luo?
Well,
I know this restaurant best
in the capital.
You’re lucky today.
I’ll treat you to whatever you like.
Thanks for your kindness.
I have money, too.
Waiter.
Help yourself. Come on.
No, thanks.
I’ve ordered too much.
Come on.
Then I’ll reluctantly do you a favor.
Hurry up.
This is good.
-Here.
-This is delicious.
Have some more. This.
Sister. You will be married tomorrow.
Why don’t you go to bed early?
Shi Jin.
I…
I don’t want to get married.
Girls always feel a little uneasy
before their wedding.
Don’t worry.
I have a good relationship
with Jiang Luo.
I will visit you a lot.
I’m not…
I just…
I just don’t think Prince Luo loves me.
But Feixian said I thought too much.
Shi Jin, you’re close to His Highness.
Do you think he really likes me?
Why is he marrying you
if he doesn’t like you?
But I suggest you to stay away
from Shi Feixian.
Is it because of the Crown Princess?
You’re over-worried.
Feixian said,
it was our elders’ business.
It has nothing to do with us.
No matter what’s in Jiang Luo’s mind,
I promise you,
nobody can shake your position
as the prince’s wife.
Ban’s Mansion
Actually,
archery is not difficult.
You are a quick learner.
Writing and painting are difficult.
But you are good at them.
As for archery, as long as you
practice hard,
I’m sure you’ll become the
second best archer in Daye.
From now on, you’ll teach
me painting
and I’ll teach you archery.
If you don’t like that,
you don’t have to learn that.
Painting and calligraphy are supposed to
contribute to our peace of mind.
You don’t have to learn that.
But if we’re together in the future
and I don’t know anything,
how can we be in harmony
and make a fairy couple?
Hua, you’re wrong.
First,
we will surely be together
in the future.
Second,
you are good at lots of things.
You like riding, archery,
beautiful dresses
and delicious desserts.
I like all of those, too.
You and I have been much closer.
I’ll take care of the rest, okay?
Since you say so,
it’s okay.
Though I like zither, chess,
calligraphy, and painting,
I can reluctantly give them up for you.
Could I reluctantly give archery up?
No, you can’t.
All right. I’ll listen to you.
I must practice it hard
in order to become a brilliant student
of yours as soon as possible.
For the sake of your obedience,
I’ll give you a reward.
How do you want to reward me?
Stay still.
See you at the range tomorrow.
Ban’s Mansion
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪