Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
WE CAN'T DELAY
MY WEDDING OR YOUR UNIVERSITY
I'M YOUR ENERGY DRINK
CHEER UP!
THERE'S HAVE TIME
TO ACHIEVE YOUR GOAL
CSAT! D-100
LEVELS 1, 2, AND 3 ORDER FRIED CHICKEN
GOOD LUCK
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DROOL TODAY,
CRY TOMORROW
Please write down
the university and major of your choice.
-Okay.
DESIRED UNIVERSITY SURVEY
Should we do the other ones first?
Yes. Actually, I'm really bad at math.
Should we study English?
No, let's do Korean Language.
At least, we can read the questions.
Yes, you have a point.
By the way, Dae-sung,
did you write in your career prospects?
No, not yet.
What are your career prospects, then?
I didn't write them yet, either.
What do you like to do?
I like to draw,
and…
Let's solve the questions.
"The natural sciences of Epicurus
enable a non-deterministic understanding
of the universe and the human world."
"The natural sciences of Epicurus…"
What does this mean?
It's in Korean, but I don't understand it.
I'll take a look.
All right. Let's see.
You guys are brave.
Both the teacher
and the student.
Hi, Ha-young.
Long time no see.
How did you know I was back here?
I was discharged a few days ago,
then I got admitted again yesterday.
Ms. Moon told us to submit
the university and major of our choice
with our career prospects.
DESIRED UNIVERSITY SURVEY
I don't need it.
This is a math worksheet.
We'll cover one more course
with this for CSAT.
I even wrote down the processes and notes,
so take a look.
I don't need it.
I'm studying plenty of stuff
with my tutor.
You really don't need it?
No, I don't.
Jeez.
That temper of hers.
I'm the only one who put up with it.
What did you just say?
I won't go to KEIST.
I applied there
because you wanted it so badly.
Even if I get accepted,
I won't go there.
Then what do you want to do?
It will be nice to major in Mathematics
and be a professor.
I want to go to medical school.
Heon.
Don't you know what your dad went through?
It's my life.
I'll decide what to do with it.
Heon.
God, this is exhausting.
Why are you here?
What are you doing?
Ha-young ripped this to pieces
because I made her angry.
Will you give up like this?
Give up what?
Ha-young.
How can I like someone like this?
I could faint any moment.
-I can't be with her.
-That's--
What about you?
Do you know how much time
Sol-i spent whining here?
She whined as if KEIST was in the States,
not in Daejeon.
-How was the early admission interview?
-I'll probably pass.
You're so full of yourself.
I won't go there.
What? You won't go there?
Really? Why not?
I'll go to medical school.
You're something else.
Also,
I want to be by Sol-i's side.
What?
You're not Heon. Who are you?
Bring Heon back.
So you shouldn't avoid Ha-young, either.
Trigonometric functions
are variations of formulas.
It seems difficult, but it's easy
when you think of the law of cosines.
Okay.
Solve it on your own.
Tell me when you're done.
Okay.
What are you doing?
Well…
I…
Will you believe me if I say
I was only trying to wipe the sweat?
off your face?
If you stop chewing your pencil,
I'll believe you.
Hey, Dae-sung.
Hi, Brother.
Did you just finish training?
Yes.
One second.
SAEMAEUM NURSING HOME
Hello?
Grandma disappeared?
I'll be right there.
Let's go.
-Grandma!
We'll go this way.
-Thanks.
-No problem.
Grandma!
-Grandma!
Did you see an old lady around here
by any chance?
She's about my height
and her hair is bobbed.
No, we haven't.
-Thank you.
Grandma!
Gran…
Is that her?
What? Yes!
Grandma. Put these on.
Thank you.
By the way, young man,
when will my Dae-sung get here?
He'll be here soon.
He must be hungry.
I'm hungry, too.
Grandma, I want to have kimchi stew.
My Dae-sung likes kimchi stew, too.
I want to make it for him often,
but he's too busy
with his swimming practice,
so I rarely see him.
He is
going to be become a world champion.
What's wrong, young man?
Are you starving?
I'll prepare a meal for you.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Heon,
I'm
going to start over.
Swimming. I'm talking about swimming.
I see.
Anyway,
I'll make Grandma's wish come true.
Okay.
Good luck.
What will you do?
I won't go to KEIST.
Honestly, I hoped you'd go there.
What?
Anyway, that's good news.
Take good care of Brother.
Don't lower your guard.
If you give Sol-i a hard time,
I'll come running.
Then we won't see each other.
Because I won't give her a hard time.
Man, what a jerk.
MILKY SKIN WOO DAE-SANG
Meet me in the school backyard.
I'll wait for you.
Sol-i.
Hey.
This is
where we first met.
Do you remember?
Yes. You're right.
Who knew this school was so scary?
Must one be ready to offer up a leg?
That's right. This school is the scariest
and so am I.
Sol-i.
I like you
a lot.
-Dae-sung--
-One more thing.
Ths.
Look. Saved by my t-shirt, right?
When I first saw you,
I just thought you were cute.
But before I knew it,
I started having feelings for you
ever since you came to watch me swim.
Dae-sung, good job!
You're the best!
I loved the way you smiled.
So I wore the bear costume
and ran alongside you.
I sprayed snow on Christmas Day.
Sol-i.
Look at me.
Dae-sung.
From now on…
I won't like you anymore.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I was happy every day.
Truly.
Thank you
for everything.
Goodbye,
Sol-i.
I like Shin Sol-i.
NOVEMBER 2008, WINTER OF NINETEEN
Don't forget your identification slip,
your ID, or your pen,
especially your computer marking pen.
-Yes, ma'am.
Do your best on your exam.
-Okay.
All right. We can't put it off any longer.
My wedding!
-Our university!
2009 COLLEGE SCHOLASTIC APTITUDE TEST
VENUE 43-8
IDENTIFICATION SLIP
Number five.
Listen to the conversation
and choose one that doesn't match.
Sub by Netflix & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Eighy-eight.
-We'll both do well. Good luck.
-Okay. Good luck.
Sol-i's not answering her phone.
What do I do?
Isn't it obvious? I'll help.
By the way, when will you write it?
That's only for people
who will be parting ways.
-Cheers.
Make sure to head home separately tonight.
All right?
Sol-i.
Would you be able to remember
what happened tonight?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-hyun Yang