NAMES ARE THE SHORTEST SPELLS
IN THE WORLD
Master, I still can't cast
the Protection Spell.
Qingming.
In this world, is there someone
you would protect with your life?
My mother.
Then think about her.
Again.
Again, Qingming.
Qingming, leave me.
-Don't let the fox demon's son get away.
-Run!
-Get him.
-Mother!
Mother!
Why did you stop?
Master.
Can I stop learning
the Protection Spell?
You can't only attack
and not know how to defend.
Master.
Try me.
Isn't it the same if I can just teleport?
When I'm under attack, I can just move.
As long as I can defeat my enemies,
I can protect myself.
That's just a shortcut.
It will not work
against someone very powerful.
Even though you are
my most gifted disciple,
the Protection Spell is the most basic and
most powerful move of a Yin-Yang Master.
You can't become a true Yin-Yang Master
without learning it.
Qingming.
In this world, is there someone
you would protect with your life?
Do you?
Yes.
SNOW HOUND, GOLD SPIRIT, MAD PAINTER
MAD PAINTER
With my blood, I'll command the spirits.
Snow Hound.
Gold Spirit.
Mad Painter.
-Incarnated.
Must protect...
The Protection Spell!
Master!
It's my honor to serve you.
I have no regret.
Master.
Is there really no cure
for the Evil Serpent's poison?
The Evil Serpent is
the evilest creature that has existed
since the beginning of heaven and earth.
It feeds on
the world's obsessions and greed.
As long as desire burns in the world,
the Evil Serpent will not be extinguished.
There is no cure for its poison.
But didn't the Gold Spirit
sacrifice his life
to kill the Evil Serpent?
That was only the Evil Serpent's shadow.
Its body is immortal
and cannot be destroyed.
Where's the Evil Serpent's body?
In Imperial City.
Someone used their body as a vessel
to contain the Evil Serpent.
300 years ago,
the four sects of the Southern Territory,
Eastern Isles,
Western Region, and Northern City
sealed the Evil Serpent's body
within Imperial City
and cast statues of the Azure Dragon,
Vermilion Bird,
White Tiger, and Black Tortoise
to protect the world ever since.
Whenever the Evil Serpent's
shadow resurfaces,
the four sects will send
their best masters
to Imperial City to slay it.
This responsibility has carried on
for generations.
Now, it's your turn.
Go to the Eastern Realm.
Let me teach you one last lesson.
When you're gone,
I'll be all alone.
Qingming.
Grief and joy,
partings and meetings, life and death,
you'll face them all
in this brief flash of life.
Master.
Don't leave me all alone.
You and I are different.
Your blood carries the fate of the world.
My life has come to an end.
But you must make the world
remember your name.
I don't care if the world remembers me.
No.
Your name is
Yin-Yang Master.
The Evil Serpent's shadow has resurfaced.
Masters from the four sects
are on their way.
They'll arrive in Imperial City soon.
Your Highness,
you sound worried.
I'm worried about you.
-Come and take a look!
-So many...
-We'll cross over first.
-Careful. Just leave it there.
-See you later.
-All right.
-Nice.
Demon.
Were you the one playing the flute?
You're bold, demon.
The Hermetic Pipa is a sacred relic
given by the emperor to Jingyun Temple.
How dare you steal it?
Master.
The woman I loved
was a Pipa player
in the palace when she was alive.
I just miss her so much,
so I want to hear
the sound of the Pipa again.
He doesn't mean any harm.
He was just using the Pipa
to ease the pain he was feeling.
Nonsense.
A demon is a demon.
Who says they have feelings?
Of course they do.
If the Pipa is returned
to its rightful owner,
will you spare his life?
If he's a human, yes.
If he's a demon, no.
Nice sword.
You...
It's indeed a treasure.
You don't understand music. Hands off.
You're a master of music.
You play it then.
You're a master, but you side with demons.
What a disgrace.
If you can't win, don't get into a fight.
If you don't want to play, don't play.
Is it necessary to tell someone off?
Sir, remember to see me again
in a few days.
Ms. Yanrou, I'll get going.
Master Qingming.
Were you waiting for me?
I want to repay you.
What for?
No one has ever told me
that demons have feelings too.
Please let me be your Spirit Guardian.
What's your name?
Killing Stone.
Boya has returned.
-Boya.
There's an imperial decree.
"According to the will of heaven,
this order is given to you.
The Evil Serpent's shadow has resurfaced,
its body will awaken soon.
Jingyun Temple has protected Imperial City
for hundreds of years,
overcoming demons and monsters,
defeating thieves and criminals.
The Evil Serpent slayers
are hereby summoned
to the palace immediately.
By the Empress herself."
This way, please.
Tomorrow is the Heaven Worship Ceremony.
Please rest early, Master Boya.
Thank you.
This way, please.
What are you doing here?
I'm here for the Heaven Worship Ceremony.
How is a master like you
who sides with demons
qualified to attend
the Heaven Worship Ceremony?
And how is a master like you
who acts before he thinks
and speaks before he acts here?
Is it because of your pretty face?
Master Boya.
You seem to like the view
from the top of the tower.
Do you want to go there again?
Your diabolic tricks are useless.
Do you dare to have
an official fight with me?
Yes, but I don't want to.
You don't dare to.
Master Qingming.
Are you afraid that
you won't be able to defeat him?
Miss,
you must be Master Longye
from Southern Territory.
I've heard of
Master Boya's valiance and bravery.
He's the ideal man of all the young women
in Imperial City.
It's late.
Masters, please rest.
Master He Shouyue.
Master Hongruo is old.
He's already resting.
If you keep talking loudly,
I'm afraid you'll disturb him.
Yes.
Master Longye,
what are you doing?
Well...
It's a habit of mine.
I always scatter Magic Bugs
before I sleep as a precaution
to keep the demons away at night.
There's no need.
I put Barrier Magic around
the Department of Celestial Observation.
No demons can get in or out.
How thoughtful.
Master Qingming,
rest well.
Master Qingming.
Who is Master He Shouyue?
He's the Imperial Priest
in charge of everything in
the Department of Celestial Observation.
It seems like
I'm not the last one to arrive.
Did Master Hongruo oversleep
due to old age?
Princess Changping has arrived.
I heard this princess is outstanding.
An expert in strategies.
She's almost 30 years old
with no plans of getting married.
There are also rumors
that she knows black magic
and manipulates
the Empress into obeying her.
Master Longye, please behave yourself.
-Greetings, Your Highness.
Rise.
Where's Master Hongruo?
Master Hongruo is dead!
The Heaven Worship Ceremony
is in a few days,
yet such a thing happened.
Changping, I'm ordering you to lead
the investigation and catch the killer.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I am getting old.
Host the Heaven Worship Ceremony
on my behalf as well.
Yes.
Our priority is to slay the Evil Serpent
and worship the heavens.
The power of
the Four Guardians is weakening.
The Masters must capture
the demons and harvest their spirits
to awaken the Guardians.
He Shouyue,
you are the Imperial Priest.
Take Master Hongruo's place.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Someone used their body as a vessel
to contain the Evil Serpent.
Who?
The Empress.
The doors and windows
were locked from inside.
Judging by the wound,
it was the work of a demon.
But the Barrier Magic around
the Department of Celestial Observation
is unbroken.
There's no trace of
any demons entering or leaving.
It could be a powerful Master
skilled in the art of teleportation.
What if the demon is inside
the Department of Celestial Observation?
Master Qingming.
What you're saying is rather shocking.
There were only four of us
in the Department of Celestial Observation
last night.
Master He Shouyue
was here last night too.
My tracking tadpoles can detect demons.
No demon can hide from it.
Shall we try it?
Do it.
It seems like there are no demons here.
No wonder there's a rumor like that.
What rumor?
That I'm the son of a fox demon.
-Guards.
-Yes.
Seize Qingming.
Hold on.
Your Highness.
Qingming...
didn't kill Master Hongruo.
How can you say that, Master Boya?
Because last night,
I placed magic ears in Qingming's room.
I was listening to it all night.
He never left the room.
Thank you for defending me, Master Boya.
But Boya's words
aren't enough to exonerate you.
What if I had more evidence?
Someone put this on me
to draw the tracking tadpoles to me.
This little thing.
What is it?
It's a listening bug
used for eavesdropping.
It has the same function
as Master Boya's magic ears.
I can't believe
that so many demonic objects
are in the Department
of Celestial Observation.
Master Hongruo
was the only participant
in the last Heaven Worship Ceremony.
I heard that your master, Zhongxing,
was also an Evil Serpent slayer.
Did he give you any details
before he died?
My master died suddenly.
There are also rumors
that she knows black magic
and manipulates
the Empress into obeying her.
The tracking tadpoles
are sometimes too sensitive
and prone to errors.
I hope you don't mind, Your Highness.
There's no room for errors
in slaying the Evil Serpent
and worshiping the heavens.
You must awaken
the Guardians within three days.
-Yes, Your Highness.
Master Boya.
Thank you for your help earlier.
A gentleman should be honorable.
I'm just stating the facts.
The honorable Master Boya
has my gratitude.
However,
why did you hang
so many magic ears in my room?
In the middle of the night,
I wonder
what you were trying to eavesdrop on.
That doesn't seem very honorable.
Wait for a moment.
You placed so many magic eyes in my room.
In the middle of the night,
I wonder
what you were trying to peek upon.
It seems
a bit despicable.
Good morning, Master Boya.
Do you want a drink?
You're drinking early in the morning?
You're not leaving yet?
There's no rush.
Don't panic, Master Boya.
That is my Spirit Guardian, Honey Bug.
I can't believe
you're using demons as Spirit Guardians.
Why do you hate demons so much?
Demons feed on people.
It's a heinous crime.
Honey Bug,
whom you tried to kill just now,
only feeds on dew and honey,
while humans
feed on chicken and fish.
Do you think that's a crime?
That's twisted logic.
I think
that demons
are simpler and more honest.
In that case,
why be a Master?
Just be a demon.
That's doable.
According to legend,
my mother was a fox demon.
Qingming.
I know you're good with words,
so you tease people for fun.
But if you don't want us to fight again,
from now on,
stop joking about this.
Master Boya.
Do you want a drink?
You don't capture demons,
yet you summon so many...
female Spirit Guardians daily
and indulge in debauchery.
How improper.
There's no rush.
That'd better be the case.
Thank you for your concern, Master Boya.
I visited you late at night.
Please forgive me.
It's late.
Is it an urgent matter?
Master Shouyue,
have we met before?
I've been serving
the Empress for a long time.
I've never left the palace.
So I don't think we've met.
Regarding Master Hongruo's death,
what are your thoughts?
Are you suspecting me?
You were the one who set up
the Barrier Magic
at the Department
of Celestial Observation.
You're also the one taking the place
of Master Hongruo.
There's no need to suspect me.
I'm Master Zhongxing's Spirit Guardian.
He left me here
to protect the Empress.
But Master is already gone.
Are you also...
I'll be gone soon as well.
My master told me
that the vessel containing
the Evil Serpent
is the Empress's body.
It must be protected at all costs.
How improper.
A SNAKE SEEMINGLY WITH WINGS ON ITS
STOMACH WAS SEEN AT LONGEVITY PAVILION
A STRANGE SNAKE SOUNDING LIKE A BULL
WAS SEEN AND ATE OUR HOUSE PET
So many strange things
are happening in Imperial City.
Yes.
How troubling.
When did you gather all this information?
When you thought
I was living a life of debauchery.
I'm a bit unlucky.
I was assigned the Azure Dragon,
the grumpiest among the Four Guardians.
Since ancient times,
people have respected dragons.
In order to wake him up,
an average demonic power won't work.
Even ten days' worth of work
wouldn't be enough.
Then why are you so carefree?
To become a demon,
one has to absorb the world's obsessions
and greed.
I just need one with
the most extreme emotions and desires,
then I'll get
twice the result with half the effort.
Unlike you guys,
who leave early, return late,
taking quantity over quality.
That's so exhausting.
Are you saying we're stupid?
Yes.
Master Qingming.
DEMONS HAVE INVADED THE DEPARTMENT
OF CELESTIAL OBSERVATION
Your Highness!
Master Boya.
Please take off Her Highness's clothes.
I beg your pardon?
That's improper!
Do you want to save her
or do you want to be proper?
I'm not doing it.
-Do it yourself if you want to.
-All right.
As you wish.
What do you mean by...
Master Boya.
What now?
In a moment, if I ask you for anything,
no matter how simple
and reasonable it sounds,
please do not obey me.
Not only that,
but you must stop me.
Boya,
pour me some water.
What's wrong?
Boya,
I want to drink water.
Give it to me!
Qingming.
Stop messing around.
Qingming!
Qingming.
Pull it.
No.
I'm serious.
Pull it now.
Qingming.
Why didn't you pull it when I told you to?
You told me not to do what you say.
You're too obedient.
A single demon spirit
can wake the Azure Dragon.
What kind of demon
has that sort of power?
This worm is called Obsession.
It feeds on people's desires.
So it's not the worm that's powerful,
it's the Princess's desires.
Now that the Azure Dragon is awake,
are you, Master Boya,
willing to join me for a glass
of plum cherry blossom wine?
Master Qingming. Master Boya.
The Princess is awake.
Is this your home?
Yes,
and no.
Boya.
There's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
When you heard I was a fox demon's son,
why did you react so strongly?
Because my mother was killed
by a fox demon.
I left home when I was little.
I became a disciple at Jingyun Temple
in order to kill
all the demons in the world
so that humans
would never experience the pain I felt.
I'm the exact opposite.
For as long as I can remember,
all of the pain I've suffered
was brought to me by humans.
Villagers spread rumors
about my mother being a fox demon.
And people
saw me as a freak.
Since I was little,
the only one who treated me kindly
was my master.
However, I was the one who ended his life.
You don't believe me?
Let me show you.
Qingming.
Master.
In this world,
is there nothing you desire anymore?
There is.
But in this life,
I have loved,
and I have been loved.
That is enough.
When you go to the Eastern Realm,
bring her the Fangyue Sword.
Do it, Qingming.
Do it before the Evil Serpent's power
completely consumes me.
SNOW HOUND, MAD PAINTER
-Greetings, Your Majesty.
We didn't know you had arrived.
Please forgive us for being rude.
Thank you for today, Master Qingming.
Her Majesty has come to see me.
I won't keep you.
-We bid our leaves.
Someone broke
the palace's Protection Circle.
Boya!
It's me.
Longye.
Master Shouyue.
Qingming.
Longye tried to assassinate the Empress.
If you want to save her,
you're an accomplice too.
No, it really wasn't me! It wasn't--
Summon the physician!
Tell me.
Who wants to kill the Empress?
The Empress is...
Who's the culprit?
The Princess.
Your Highness.
Why did you lie to me?
You don't really believe
that I'm Longye's accomplice, right?
The hair demon has killed
two Masters already.
What kind of demon
has this much power?
The hair demon is not powerful.
The one who controls it is powerful.
You don't suspect demons
and you're suspicious of humans?
You said Master Hongruo's death
was due to the mishandling
of the hair demon,
an accidental death.
What about Longye?
Longye discovered our secret.
What if they find out you are the Empress?
She had to die.
Even if someone is controlling
the hair demon,
what exactly is their motive?
To unleash the Evil Serpent.
Nonsense.
I must release the Evil Serpent.
But as long as the Masters are here,
they will kill the Evil Serpent.
So you want to kill Qingming
and Boya too?
Before Longye died,
she told Qingming the truth.
So we can't let them live.
Longye told me before she died,
that the Princess was the culprit.
Who's the culprit?
It's the Princess.
That's impossible.
Why would she do that?
She wants to break
the Evil Serpent's vessel.
The Empress's body
is the vessel.
That's ridiculous.
What good will releasing
the Evil Serpent do?
Would Longye use
her last breath to tell a lie?
The night Master Hongruo died,
the Princess wasn't at
the Department of Celestial Observation.
If we're to suspect anyone,
He Shouyue is more suspicious.
Yes.
I used to be more suspicious of him
than you.
But he's fundamentally
incapable of harming the Empress.
Why?
Because he's the Spirit Guardian
left by my master to protect the Empress.
Once a Spirit Guardian
and a Yin-Yang Master form a bond,
it is for life,
unbreakable until death.
Then all of you are lying
to frame the Princess.
Boya.
Between me and the Princess,
who do you believe?
I've only known you for a few days,
but the Princess and I grew up together.
Are you sure?
You told me
that the Princess was raised
outside the palace
and she only returned at 18.
You had to collect so many demon spirits
to awaken the Guardians.
But her desire alone was enough
to awaken the Azure Dragon.
Do you really know her?
If you don't believe me,
let's confront them.
What's the use?
You'll just believe
whatever He Shouyue says.
Aren't you just as devoted
to the Princess?
Let's confront them separately then.
Good luck.
The one who needs good luck
isn't me.
I don't have much time left.
What we're about to do
is something no one has ever tried.
If you regret doing this,
you had better kill me now.
Don't let me suffer so much.
Boya.
This is the Yin-Yang sigil
my master used to create
Spirit Guardians when he was alive.
Hold the sigil in your hand,
call his name,
and give him an order
that he is absolutely unwilling to do.
If he refuses to do it,
then he is not
my master's Spirit Guardian.
Or...
Like you said,
he has already betrayed Master.
Qingming.
What's the matter?
Can this magic ear
help me control the Princess?
You talk too much.
If you encounter any dangers,
just give me a shout.
If you encounter any dangers...
I'll give you a shout too,
so you can watch.
Boya.
One of us
will face the real culprit.
You must be careful.
Take care.
Your Highness.
Master Qingming.
The Evil Serpent will awaken soon.
Does Your Highness know
where the vessel
that contains the Evil Serpent is?
Only Her Majesty knows that.
But Her Majesty is currently unconscious.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
Once the Evil Serpent awakens,
I'll be able to find it.
Before my master died,
he gave me a sword.
This sword
once slew the Evil Serpent
and was soaked in its blood.
It can sense the Evil Serpent's location.
The sword's name
is Fangyue.
Where is Fangyue?
Master Boya.
Master He Shouyue.
I have
a favor to ask.
I'd like you
to draw your blade
and cut off your right hand.
Master Boya.
What are you talking about?
HE SHOUYUE
He Shouyue.
Draw your blade
and cut off your right hand.
Your Highness.
Put down Fangyue.
What exactly are you?
I...
Your Highness.
Why did you kill the Princess?
The one who broke my heart
was originally a painter in the palace.
But he was obsessed with another woman.
In order to prove his love to her,
he didn't hesitate
to kill me.
I hated her.
But I was under control
and couldn't act freely.
Today, I'm finally free,
and I was able to kill her.
Sixty years.
I have waited for sixty years.
I'm so happy.
I finally got my revenge.
I'm so sad.
I'm so happy.
"Spirit Guardian."
Where's Fangyue?
I...
My mission
is to protect the Empress.
The Princess only returned to the palace
when she was 18.
When you go to the Eastern Realm,
bring her the Fangyue Sword.
Boya.
HE SHOUYUE
Stop.
He Shouyue,
why did you betray the Empress?
-I didn't betray--
-He didn't betray the Empress.
Because the Princess is the Empress.
The one behind the curtain
was a paper doll controlled by He Shouyue.
The Heaven Worship Ceremony
is in a few days,
yet such a thing happened.
Changping, I'm ordering you to lead
the investigation and catch the killer.
Because Master Hongruo participated
in the last ceremony,
he could have revealed
the Evil Serpent's secret anytime.
So He Shouyue manipulated
the hair demon to kill him.
Then you put the listening bug on me
to listen in on me
and spread fear at the same time.
But the Barrier Magic around
the Department of Celestial Observation
is unbroken.
It could be a powerful Master
skilled in the art of teleportation.
That made the Masters suspicious
and guarded against each other.
But...
When I mentioned my master...
I heard that your master, Zhongxing,
was an Evil Serpent slayer.
Your Majesty couldn't
control your emotions.
The tadpoles sensed the urge
of the Evil Serpent in your body
and pointed towards you.
Originally, as long as He Shouyue
takes Hongruo's place,
you can cover everything up.
To awaken the Four Guardians,
there must be four Masters.
We need to send someone
to inform the Western Region
-to send another Master immediately.
-There's no time.
-He Shouyue, take Master Hongruo's place.
Yes, Your Majesty.
But you didn't realize
that Longye had been
privately investigating.
She was suspicious
of the Empress's true identity.
She sneaked
into the Empress's chamber at night
and discovered the secret.
As long as Qingming is alive,
I cannot be at peace.
What if they find out you are the Empress?
That was why you had to silence her.
Summon the physician!
Before Longye died, she actually told me
that the Empress was the Princess.
The Empress is...
The Princess.
I thought she meant the Princess
wanted to kill the Empress.
You're very smart.
You have calculated every step correctly.
Back then, I consumed Mermaid flesh
to make my body immortal,
so I could contain
the Evil Serpent indefinitely.
But while I achieved
the immortality everyone dreams of,
I would never be able
to leave Imperial City again.
Imperial City
may have trapped the Evil Serpent,
but it also trapped me.
I kept changing
my identity for hundreds of years,
from flower seller to singer,
mulberry picker, and nun.
Until I was chosen
by the Emperor and was cherished by him.
After the Emperor passed away,
I became Empress.
To keep my immortality a secret,
I became a princess
who lived outside the palace
and just returned.
I separated the Evil Serpent
from the world with my body.
The Evil Serpent could no longer devour
the desires of the world.
It can only feed on my emotions.
The people I met and fell in love with
grew old
and died.
My memories faded,
as did my desires for this world.
Until I met your master.
He kept this secret even until death.
That's why I'm even more confused.
Why do you want
to release the Evil Serpent?
I need its power of immortality.
But you're already immortal.
Your Highness,
you sound worried.
I'm worried about you.
If you need me,
I'll find a way to survive.
Your Highness.
Qingming.
Boya.
Master, why can't I find my mother?
The Yin-Yang Teleportation Technique
can only take you to places you can see
or already know.
Boya!
Boya.
-Boya.
-Qingming.
Qingming.
Where are you?
Inside a tomb.
I don't know where.
Let me see you.
There's no time for this.
The magic eye.
Use my magic eye!
Boya!
Boya.
How long
have you been this way?
Hundreds of years.
I can't remember anymore.
What's your original name?
Fangyue.
It has been so long
since someone said that name.
Fangyue.
I'll always remember your name.
Zhongxing.
Can't you stay?
I'll always be with you.
The Evil Serpent is awake.
It's not enough.
It's still not enough.
What are you planning to do?
...if only they could be here.
What's that sound?
The Evil Serpent is
consuming human desires
and getting bigger and bigger.
The Vermilion Bird is not yet awake.
It was He Shouyue.
We can't let them leave Imperial City.
Out of the Four Guardians' watch,
the Evil Serpent will become
even more terrifying.
You want the Evil Serpent
to leave Imperial City?
Not the Evil Serpent.
It's you and me.
Let's leave Imperial City together.
Let's break out of here
and spend our lives wandering the world.
I'll accompany you.
All right.
Let us
die together then.
-Your Highness!
With my blood, I'll command the spirits.
Killing Stone.
Mad Painter.
Snow Hound.
-Incarnated.
Mad Painter, protect Master Qingming.
Snow Hound, come with me.
It's not working.
We must activate the Protection Barrier.
Qingming,
the Princess is still inside
the Evil Serpent.
We can't stop He Shouyue this way.
I have one last idea.
I'll summon the Vermilion Bird
with my flesh and blood.
Boya.
With all Four Guardians guarding the city,
He Shouyue won't be able
to leave Imperial City.
Then find a way to rescue the Princess.
I can't protect you if you're unconscious.
-I...
-I trust you.
Let me be your Spirit Guardian.
Boya!
Master Qingming.
It's my honor to serve you.
I have no regret.
Master Qingming, go.
Master Qingming, go save Boya.
Leave this to me and Killing Stone.
Boya!
How long are you planning
to stay in this illusion?
Master is already dead.
Zhongxing.
Grief and joy,
partings and meetings, life and death,
you'll face them all
in this brief flash of life.
But in this life,
I have loved,
and I have been loved.
That is enough.
In this world,
do you still desire anything?
I entered this world empty-handed.
I will leave empty-handed.
What about me?
If you leave this world,
what is left for me?
You and I are different.
You are different from all of us.
Your blood carries the fate of the world.
But you must make the world
remember your name.
I've had so many names.
I can't even remember my names.
No.
I still remember your name.
I will always
remember your name.
Your name
is Fangyue.
This blade has been with me
for a long time.
It's my gift to you.
Can't you stay?
The Evil Serpent is still inside you.
You've already developed feelings.
I can't stay.
What about you?
Have you developed feelings?
I see.
Does it have a name?
Not yet.
Let's call it Fangyue.
Let it keep you company
from now on.
Let Fangyue do
what I can't.
Boya!
Qingming.
Let me show you
the real Protection Spell.
What if there's no one
in this world that you want
to protect anymore?
Your Highness, what are you doing?
You are immortal.
You'll only suffer.
Without the Evil Serpent,
I'm no longer immortal.
You're lying.
I've never lied to you.
So,
I hope you won't lie to me either.
You said
you would always protect me.
Fangyue.
The purpose of a Yin-Yang Master
is not to subdue,
but to protect.
Qingming,
find something you would
want to protect in this world.
Leave your name in this world.
Thank you.
I should be thanking you.
I am
a real Yin-Yang Master now.
Before my master died,
he told me to go to the Eastern Realm,
where he would teach me one last lesson.
At first, I didn't understand,
but I do now.
When I first became his disciple,
I often heard my seniors say
that when Master was young,
he lived in Imperial City for a while.
I was curious and asked him
about his experience in Imperial City,
but he always remained silent
and was reluctant to talk about it.
Today, I finally understood.
It wasn't because he was forgetful
due to his old age.
He used a lot of strength
to create a Spirit Guardian
as powerful as himself.
He used spells to attach all
his feelings for Fangyue
before he turned 20 on He Shouyue.
Protect...
Fangyue forever.
Your Majesty, what's on your mind?
I'm thinking about someone
I'm unable to see.
Your Majesty, if it's your will,
I can transform into anyone,
so you can see him.
But you're not him.
Your Majesty, just tell me
whether you want me to or not.
But my master never expected
that the Spirit Guardian would turn
into the person she misses
to satisfy Her Majesty's wish.
He Shouyue did not betray Master.
Master ordered him
to protect Fangyue forever.
But he got caught up
on the word "forever."
So he sought to
become immortal at all costs.
It was the only way
he could fulfill his duty
of protecting Fangyue forever.
In my next life,
I want to be human.
Being human is too painful.
In my next life, I want to be the moon.
Then I will protect the moon.
I'll protect you forever.
Good and evil coexist in the world.
Just like Yin and Yang,
reinforcing and restraining each other.
Perhaps humans and demons
both have desires,
which can be good or evil.
After a few decades,
perhaps the Evil Serpent will resurface
somewhere in the world again.
At least, we have protected
the world right now.
After a few decades,
let's fight side by side again.
You've always laughed at me
for being preachy.
Now you're the same.
Didn't you resent me for hanging out
with Spirit Guardians all day?
Yet you were willing
to become my Spirit Guardian in the end.
That was the Vermilion Bird,
not me.
Killing Stone once asked you
if you were the one playing the flute.
Our fate
started with the flute.
Today,
let me play the flute
to send you off.
My bow and arrow were originally
meant to kill enemies.
But right now,
I hope the arrow flies above the vast sea
to guide you home.
QINGMING SHINES BRIGHTLY
LIKE A STAR
BOYA'S BOW
SPRINGS WITH JOY
QINGMING SHINES BRIGHTLY LIKE A STAR
BOYA'S BOW SPRINGS WITH JOY
MAY THOSE WHO CARE FOR YOU
IN THIS LIFE
BE BY YOUR SIDE RIGHT NOW
Subtitle translation by: pp Hsiung,
Peter Walters, Fan Yingqiao