♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad Episode 31
Keep guard.
Okay.
- Report me if anything's wrong.
- Yes, sir.
Who're you?
Who're those people?
How dare you!
People with no duty can't enter the Ziwei Palace.
So...
they are the people with duty?
You asked for it!
Say it!
Who're you?
Why are you pretending to be the guard in Ziwei Palace?
There're so many men of sacrifice in Luoyang.
Since you're not afraid of death,
who're you working for?
Since you want to commit suicide,
it means you know
you'll suffer under our torture.
Think about it.
Just tell us who you're working for.
They've put out the fire.
It seems we don't need to be here anymore.
Take this guy away.
As for your old friend,
it's a bad choice to look for your friend now.
Madam!
Bad news, madam!
Something's wrong!
Madam!
Why're you so anxious?
Bad news, madam.
It's reported that there's something wrong in the Ziwei Palace.
I heard someone saw our master.
What happened in Ziwei Palace?
I heard there was a fire.
I shall leave now, madam.
[Luoyang Office]
Princess.
Father.
Someone poured kerosene outside the Ziwei Palace.
I'm afraid someone did it on purpose.
Who wants to kill my brother?
Who is the last one to see his Highness?
You only need to tell us
the situation when you last saw his Highness.
As long as you can tell us clearly,
you'll atone your fault.
Princess.
Minister.
Although I didn't see his Highness,
I saw a group of people dressed like refugees break into his room.
Some assassins have broken into the Ziwei Palace?
Did you see their faces clearly?
Minister.
There was smoke everywhere.
And I stood far from them.
So I didn't see clearly.
Minister.
I saw a girl dressed like a Taoist nun.
She ran out of your Highness's room.
I'm not familiar with her, so I remember her face.
Will she be the accomplice of those assassins?
Did you see the girl's face clearly?
She's pretty.
There's a nevus under her eye.
Will it be her?
God damn it.
Minister Du!
Minister Du, listen to me.
Minster Du!
Father!
Minister!
Why are you still standing by?
Prepare a carriage to Liuyun Temple!
Yes, sir!
Now we haven't found my brother.
I hope nothing will happen to Changge.
I'll inform Changge.
No.
If you meet Hao Du, you...
Brother Shuyu.
I didn't mean that.
I mean, if you meet Hao Du and Du Ruhui,
they won't listen to you.
You can stay here.
If they have a confrontation with Changge in Liuyun Temple,
they won't suspect you and you can continue to support her.
Okay.
I'll prepare food and a token to leave the city.
Be careful.
Okay.
Help!
A'Li!
Ms. Quan, help!
A'Li, help!
Taoist!
Taoist, help!
Be careful.
Help Minister Du get in.
Taoist Sun is in the room.
Okay.
Catch her.
Yes, sir.
Sir!
If you want to see a doctor,
I'm afraid you head towards the wrong direction.
I heard Liuyun Temple harbors refugees and does good deeds.
Since I'm here now,
of course I need to walk around,
so that I'll praise your kindness in the future.
Thank you.
But we have both external and internal beauty.
These good things mean nothing to us.
What?
It seems you don't want to just walk around.
You want to fight with me?
I have an important business.
Please do me a favor.
I'll do you a favor.
Do you a favor, it means do myself a favor.
Now it's late at night,
I don't want to fight with you.
Please step aside.
I've stepped aside,
Whether you can pass here,
it depends on whether you have the ability.
What?
You don't want to walk around now?
Where are you going?
You tried to stop me,
so I should behave well.
Or to say,
you want to stop me
after I leave Liuyun Temple?
Where did I get this apprentice from?
Someone in the martial world is looking for her,
while someone from the imperial court is also looking for her.
She's really somebody.
Princess?
Why are you here alone?
I worried about Minister Du,
so I came here to see him.
But I got lost somehow.
How's Minister Du now?
Take me to see him.
Did you see anyone suspicious?
Suspicious?
No.
I'm here alone.
Hao Du.
It's getting dark.
I'm a little afraid.
Let's go back now.
Okay.
I'll send you to Liuyun Temple first.
This way, Princess.
Father.
Minister Du.
Don't bother us.
You two,
check around to see if there's anyone suspicious.
Changge.
Leyan?
Why are you here?
Changge,
Minister Du found you have appeared in Ziwei Palace.
He doubted if you're related to this.
But now he has an acute disease and was sent to Liuyun Temple.
I'm afraid you'll meet, so I'm here to find you.
Leave here.
If I leave now,
I'll never have a chance to explain.
Where's the crown prince?
We haven't found him yet.
But you must be safe now.
Changge, if you're still alive,
I'm sure you have the chance to explain.
Someone is chasing you?
It's Hao Du.
I'll stop him.
Just leave.
What about you?
Relax.
Minister Du won't harm me.
Trust me.
Be careful.
Go.
Yes, sir.
You...
Why are you back?
How did you know it?
My Prentice.
I've settled many troubles for you.
But they're from the imperial court.
I don't want to piss them off.
So I can only wait here.
But if they go out of here,
I have no reason to stop them.
Thanks.
Who are you?
How do you... Did Du Ruhui leave?
I think he's gone.
But I heard, because that guard didn't catch you,
he spitted out more blood.
Taoist Sun was so anxious that he almost fainted.
Prentice.
What if those soldiers come to catch you again?
They won't.
They won't expect I'll come back again.
My Prentice is so interesting.
Be careful, madam.
I've settled him.
Here, be careful.
This way.
Have a seat.
Did he confess?
Yes, he did.
He is a soldier of Sui.
He canceled his registration.
He created a new identity and sneaked into Ziwei Palace.
Who did they work for?
And where did they take the crown prince to?
He is an abandoned soldier.
He didn't even know who his leader is.
But it must be related to Sui.
People of Sui?
You mean...
They work for Dingxiang.
Dingxiang.
Madam, you helped us a lot.
I really admire you.
Where's he?
Take me to see him.
Mr. Qin.
We'd better not engage in the thing my madam settled.
We've been working all night.
What about having breakfast together?
This way.
Father.
Taoist Sun said you need to have medicine according to time.
You're still thinking about Li Changge?
Li Changge didn't die.
I saw her with my own eyes.
I don't know whether it's good or not.
She is living in Liuyun Temple now.
If Master and Taoist Sun want to protect her,
we can't just take her away.
But we don't know whether Li Changge took the crown prince away.
What if...
In my opinion,
if Li Changge really took him away,
we don't need to worry about him now.
Even if we went through so many things,
Li Changge still remains a good relationship with Princess.
She won't harm the crown princess
and let Princess experience the same pain she had before.
You're right.
But we can't let Li Changge use him as the hostage.
We can't block the news that the crown prince disappeared for long.
We should catch Li Changge and find his Highness.
There're many people in Luoyang.
It's hard to catch Li Changge, and...
And Princess Yongan is trying to stop you and protect her.
Right?
Princess.
Now his Highness is missing.
There'll be a chaos in Luoyang.
Please don't wander outside, Princess,
in case you disappear as well.
Don't worry.
Now my brother is missing.
I won't cause you any trouble.
Now the rumors have turned into reality.
No one knows what will happen.
I'll deploy forces now.
I can't take care of you.
Please don't seek troubles for yourself.
Didn't you ask all the guards to look for my brother?
Why do you still deploy forces?
Are you looking for someone,
or are you catching someone?
Hao Du.
The most important thing is to find my brother.
As for catching someone,
I think you can put it off.
How do you know the disappearance of his Highness is none of her business?
Someone did this on purpose in Luoyang.
Who will benefit most from this?
It must be those who want to cause troubles in Tang.
Okay.
Then let's be straightforward.
What are you doubting?
Li Changge is in Luoyang.
Yes.
Thank you for not lying to me.
My father saw her.
But I can prove she's innocent.
It is none of her business, because...
I don't care what she said and did in front of you.
It may be part of her plan.
So please stay here, Princess.
Don't get involved in it.
Young man.
What are you thinking?
I've made this move for a long time.
It's your turn now.
I thought you got message from that man,
and wanted to investigate the fire in Ziwei Palace with me.
What are you thinking?
I don't even know where you come from.
How could I investigate a serious matter with you?
Then why do you take me to play chess here?
This place is good.
It's bustling.
We need to be calm and focus when playing chess.
Only in busy places can we exercise ourselves.
I have something to do now.
Goodbye.
You've come home with me.
Now you want to leave?
I think it's not suitable.
Besides, by following me,
you just want to know my relationship with people in Ziwei Palace, right?
You want to look for your old friend, right?
Come back.
Have a game of chess.
As an old saying goes,
watching chess is like watching people.
After you've played chess with me,
I can nearly know your characteristic.
Maybe at that time,
I can do a serious business with you.
I don't know how to play chess.
You have much callus on your hands.
It means you have fought in wars for many years.
Playing chess is like leading a troop.
I've told you the rules.
Since you know how to battle,
you must know how to play chess.
Come on.
This doesn't count.
Let's start again.
Okay.
Princess, I'm still afraid.
Don't be afraid.
Just do as I said.
They daren't harm you.
If they want to break in,
just scold them.
You can say,
you've been worried and caught a cold.
Now you're sweaty and only wearing underwear.
They won't come in.
But do remember, cover your face.
Just keep pretending until I'm back.
Understand?
Princess.
Ms. Quan.
I'm sorry.
Liuyun Temple is closed and won't receive guests today.
Ms. Quan.
Princess.
Chang...
Where's A'Li?
Why are you looking for A'Li?
I have a serious matter to talk with her.
Where's A'Li now?
A'Li... She's not in the temple now.
[Hao Du is deploying forces.]
[Meet me in the tea house.]
Ms. Quan.
If A'Li comes back,
please give this letter to her in person.
Tell her I'll wait for her until dawn.
Please.
Okay.
Leave.
Any news?
Just as you predicted,
Princess Yongan fell in the trap.
You don't need to look after me.
Just go.
Find the crown prince.
Yes, sir.
Playing chess is like leading a troop.
Among the generals I know,
only one person will deploy troops like this.
Governor of Shuozhou, Gongsun Heng.
But it's a pity.
I heard Gongsun Heng committed suicide to protect people in Shuozhou.
He's a real hero.
But I heard there's an able man working for him.
His surname is Qin.
He's still living.
What's your relationship with him, Mr. Qin?
You got involved in the chaos in Luoyang.
What do you want to do?
You've been dealing with me in the manner of Gongsun Heng.
But you won't expose the manner that you're familiar with.
So you have already lost.
I invite you to the trap, but I won't unmask you so soon.
I just want to see
to what extent you can deploy in Gongsun Heng's manner.
If you use your familiar manner,
maybe I can't defeat you.
However, you're not honest enough.
In record, I'm Senior Qin's nephew.
The truth is...
his partner.
At the seventh line outside,
you're hesitating whether you'll put a chessman.
It's because you're afraid you'll expose your manner.
But a general shouldn't hesitate.
People will see through you.
Actually, you want to put it here.
But it's the manner of the people on the prairie.
No, I'm from the Central Plains.
Interesting.
A'Li.
The princess came here just now.
I said you weren't here.
So she left this.
Thank you, Ms. Quan.
[Hao Du is deploying forces. You need to leave. Meet me in the tea house.]
Ms. Quan.
I need to meet the princess.
Relax.
I'll be careful.
It doesn't matter who I am.
I came to Luoyang to find my old friend.
So, now can you tell me
the old friend from the noble family?
No, I can't.
It's not important.
The reason why I look for her,
it's not because of her identity.
People say you're afraid of your wife.
Actually, you regard your wife as your partner.
So you respect her.
If your wife is gone,
I guess you'll look for her no matter how difficult it will be.
Am I right?
I thought you are looking for a man.
But you're looking for a girl!
I like it.
Okay.
I'm willing to find your beloved one.
Beloved one?
Isn't she?
I guess she must be very pretty.
And she is very adorable.
Yes.
See? I'm right.
You care about her very much,
and you don't want to leave her behind, right?
You don't like other girls.
If you're forced to stay with someone,
and you can't leave each other until you're dead,
do you hope this girl to be her?
Even if many beautiful girls in the world like you,
you still like this overbearing and bad-tempered girl.
She's not a girl.
Is she an old lady?
I really admire your taste.
She's a capable woman.
No matter who she is, in all,
she's your beloved one.
I won't play with you.
I've used up all my strategies of playing chess.
I won't play now.
Mr. Li.
You want to betray your words?
Don't say so.
It's not like that.
It's him?
Mr. Qin.
With your unclear identity,
I suggest you to stay away from these.
It's early now.
Come on, have a seat. Let's have another game.
Come on.
Mr. Li.
I have something urgent.
I'll visit you some day later.
I still want to play!
You're leaving suddenly?
Brother Shuyu.
Did you get it?
It's in the bag.
But, Leyan,
it's strange.
How could things go so well?
According to Hao Du's habit,
he must have noticed it.
Well, take it and wait for me at the gate.
I'll wait for Changge secretly and inform her to meet you.
But...
Mr. Wei.
You underestimated me.
Hao Du.
Why are you here?
Now the crown prince is missing.
The criminal is in Luoyang.
You took Princess out secretly.
If there's... How do you know I'm here?
If I don't know this, how would I protect you?
You...
[Token of Luoyang]
Where did you get this token
and who do you want to give it?
I stole the token.
Do you want to catch me?
Damn it!
Chase her!
Let him go.
I said, let him go.
Changge.
He is?
He...
He saved Changge in Youzhou.
He is Changge's friend.
He saved Changge?
Yes.
He kidnapped me and saved Changge from Hao Du.
No matter who he is,
he saved Changge for so many times,
he is trustworthy.
♫ The heart gradually responds, gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, we expect an encounter. ♫
- Changge.
- Sun?
It's a trap.
Your friends were caught.
I followed the man that wanted to catch you.
I didn't imagine you're really here.
Then, Leyan...
There're imperial officers.
Relax, she's safe.
Just leave here.
You don't hate me?
♫ There's always a moment ♫
I hate you to leave without saying goodbye.
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
This way.
♫ It turns into eternity. The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
What's this place?
The most famous tavern in Luoyang.
They can't believe we're hiding in the most crowded place.
How could you be so familiar with this place?
I played chess here with a friend.
Play chess here?
Changge.
It's so difficult for me to find you.
You've been looking for me from the tribes until now?
I'm sorry for you.
I shouldn't blame you.
I owe you so much.
Then don't leave.
You can pay it back.
I just saved you.
Shouldn't you give me a toast?
Thank you so much for saving me.
I just want to thank you.
I didn't say I would marry you.
Who'll benefit more,
we still don't know it yet.
Sister?
I just heard your voice.
I didn't believe it was you.
Ghost.
You're a ghost!
Shut up.
Why are you here?
Don't you know you've caused a big trouble?
Sister.
You're alive.
Congratulations.
Long time no... Answer my question!
I...
I sneaked out.
It's said this tavern is interesting.
Western dancers with golden hair and blue eyes will dance here.
So I'm thinking...
I...
So,
you sneaked out.
You weren't kidnapped.
Boy.
Think clearly.
Have you been staying here?
Do you know there was a fire in Ziwei Palace?
I...
I heard about it.
But why didn't you go back?
I...
When the fire broke out, I've fallen asleep.
I heard about it later.
If I go back now,
Minister Du will punish me.
You naughty boy.
Li Changge!
I'm the crown prince now.
How could you do this to me?
I'll hit you if you keep talking.
Li Changge.
If you dare to touch me one more time...
Sister, sister!
I'm your brother.
Just calm down.
I won't say that to you.
Li Chengqian. We can see what a person will be since he's little.
You really don't get any better as you get older.
You're a crown prince, but you did such a ridiculous thing.
I feel ashamed for Li Shimin.
How could he have a son like you?
You didn't learn a little from your father.
You want to be a crown prince?
Why are you scolding me as well?
Everyone say, I don't deserve to be my father's son.
I thought...
My father did such a thing to your family.
I thought at least you'll think I deserve to be his son.
At least your father can save the world.
But you...
You...
Do you really want to kidnap me?
How dare you!
I'll tell Minister Du about it!
How dare you come back to Luoyang?
Since you've found her,
we can't let you leave now.
Sister.
We're relatives.
Let's just sit down and talk.
You need to realize your fault.
Don't do silly things, my friends.
Li Changge!
What are you doing?
You said you like to play.
You can play here as you want.
Four warriors.
Please let my brother play here.
Please let him feel at home.
Okay.
If you do any harm to me,
my father will punish you.
I'm the crown prince, the future emperor!
How dare you do this!
You want to die here?
My brother had a serious fever,
so his brain is not functioning well.
Don't believe what he said.
Sister!
Sister, it's my bad.
Let me go.
We're relatives.
We can sit down and talk.
You know I'm your sister?
Okay.
Since you still call me sister,
I'll teach you a lesson for your dad.
Warriors.
Please take care of my brother.
Don't harm him, or his mother will blame me.
Relax.
We've taught many kids a lesson.
We know it.
Have fun.
Stop!
Don't leave!
Sister.
Sister!
[Sumo Hall]
I've never lost once since I was young.
Naughty boy.
He just received a small punishment.
Feeling happy?
Then go back with me.
Go back to where?
Shiba and Senior Qin are in Luoyang.
They're looking for you.
Shiba and Senior Qin...
Where is Yuan?
Yuan is also here.
And Xu Feng?
People of Yanxing Sect are all here.
Yanxing Sect?
It's the alias of Senior Qin's group.
I really miss them.
What's wrong?
I don't know how to face them when I go back.
Don't think too much.
Just go back.
Let's go.
[Luoyang Office]
Princess.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad