♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad Episode 36
Excuse me.
Are you from the Central Plains?
Could you help me check
whether it's from the Royal Family there?
Layman! Don't talk rot!
Have you ever seen anything from the royal family of Central Plains?
Let me see!
Such a cheap handkerchief.
Not only the royal family
but also I will refuse to use it! It's so rough!
You... How dare you!
You did deceive me!
Let the head judge it! Follow me!
- Go!
- Help me!
How dare you ask us to do so?
Young Master, shall we help her?
According to her behaviors and apparels,
she must be rich or noble.
Someone will go to help her even if we don't.
Young Master.
It feels wrong.
They've even taken over gromwells in black markets.
They're the most covert!
Seems that Khan's Tent wants to destroy us all.
What should we do now?
Where can we find the gromwell?
Let's lodge in the hotel and keep on searching it.
We must find and bring it back!
Okay.
- Follow up!
- Let me off!
- Go!
- I didn't repudiate!
- I just need a few whiles to pay!
- Go!
Why are you so brutal?
- I didn't cheat you!
You know to cheat at such a tender age!
Full of tricks! I won't trust you!
- I'm not!
- Go!
Ask him to pay! He's rich!
No! No pain, no leaving!
Take it!
Thank you...
I've got bellyache...
Stand up.
Uncle...
Are you going to leave me in the lurch?
You tricked me and escaped last time.
I have a headache.
Ouch, it hurts!
The same old trick.
Well, you didn't mention bellyache last time.
Uncle.
Your joke isn't funny.
Enough? Can we leave now?
I can go with you
but I'm hungry and I want to eat noodles.
Haven't you just finished your meal?
Does it matter?
Here you are.
Please enjoy it.
Well, how can I eat...
while you're all staring at me?
Yummy! It's so delicious!
I've got bellyache!
What's wrong?
Something wrong with the noodles!
Boss!
Yes, Sir?
I'm here.
Something wrong with the noodles!
It's impossible... Wait!
- What's going on?
- We've operated for decades!
- We've never met it before!
- I...
- Any mistake?
- Namtso.
Go to check the kitchen!
In case I'm poisoned, you may find the toxic!
Do it! At once!
- You guys, go to check the kitchen!
- Yes.
This way, please.
Uncle, go with them!
I've got a tummy ache...
I have to go to the toilet!
It aches...
She escaped again!
Let's chase!
It's you...
Enemies here!
You played a trick but why did you blame on us?
It's enough. Leave her alone.
- Wait! She's...
- Let's leave.
Step aside!
Get out of the way!
How can they find me so quickly?
- Step aside!
- Soldiers here...
Are they the soldiers of Mobei?
You fear soldiers?
Don't move!
Help me!
- What to do?
- Stun her at once!
Stop it!
Let's leave!
- Find them!
- Yes!
Take care.
Shall we have a meal?
- This way, please.
- Fine.
Who are you?
Why did you tie me up?
So who are you?
Why did you make trouble with us?
Why do I have to answer you?
By the way,
you're quite weird and fear soldiers.
I think you're not normal peddlers!
As you've found it,
then it's time to silence you.
Do you know the result of bringing us trouble?
Do you want to kill me?
Here's the inn, right?
Many people here.
It's not a good place to murder.
Clever girl.
Tell me.
Why are they? Why did they chase you?
My enemies.
I think it's good for me to be tied.
It's better than to be arrested by them!
Little girl! Pack of lies!
I dare not let you leave and bring us trouble.
Stay here quietly.
If you refuse,
I'll leave you in the field to serve as the food of wolves!
Changge, what's up? Who's she?
Still tells me nothing.
Then what should we do to her?
Though her background is unknown,
I don't think she's a hoodlum.
As she's smart,
she's found that we don't want to cope with soldiers.
If we let her off so easily,
she might bring us more trouble.
Guard her first.
Then we'll try to find a solution.
Sounds reasonable.
Then let's do it.
Want to trap me?
Come on... She's here for me?
Mimi, what's wrong?
What are you thinking here?
I'm thinking of my father, mother
and young brother.
My whole family lived in Mobei
when I was young.
Though we were not rich,
we were very happy.
Until Ashile Tribe came.
They brought us battles
and ruined my family.
Many clansmen were homeless.
Fortunately, King of Mobei appeared.
Though Mobei wasn't conquered,
it's still pinned by Ashile Tribe.
Whoever brings others wars
will be punished.
My father said so.
In my childhood,
he taught me to tell right from wrong.
Well, Changge.
I really cannot distinguish
between right and wrong now.
It seems that I should hate Ashile Tribe
but Eagle Division is also a part of it.
I love the guys there.
Am I wrong?
They're not the same.
Shouldn't you be tied?
I... Why didn't you escape?
I didn't want to leave.
I think you're quite right.
Ashile Tribe and its Great Khan
must be punished in the future.
So who are you?
My name is Zhenzhu. I'm from Monan.
But we're in Mobei.
I'm here for Qihan Festival.
Mobei has the liveliest celebration.
So you come here yourself?
Guys who're chasing you...
Fine... It's because my father made me angry.
He asked them to capture me back.
Well, I don't want to be back now.
Oh, come on.
Just a kid who ran away from home.
I'm not a kid!
I'm now 14 years old and can get married.
I think you only enjoy larks.
I can let you leave
but you need to remember it.
If you dare come to bring us trouble,
I'll capture and kill you.
You won't kill me!
Why?
My intuition.
By the way, anything to eat?
I'm hungry.
Don't eat too much...
I'm full!
Then answer my question.
How far is Monan from here?
Are there any gromwells there?
Gromwell?
It's not a rarity.
As there are many in Mobei, why do you ask Monan?
Because we can buy none of it in Mobei.
Though its trade has been banned,
we still can banish God of Plague.
Every Qihan Festival,
everyone will take out gromwells to banish God of Plague.
Banish God of Plague?
Mimi.
Is it as same as what you've told me today?
Its main part is to banish God of Plague...
People will build up a stage in the town
and someone will take the stage and perform.
Then people will throw all their gromwells
to God of Plague.
How couldn't I find such an idea?
Which part of the performance should be fastidious?
Fastidious?
Anyone's here?
Soldiers!
Are you all dead?
Where's Shixin Sili?
He isn't in Khan's Tent now.
Then where's Sher?
Ask him to come!
Young Khan led Wolf Division to inspect.
No one is here...
They're all out!
Why are they not here?
You're sick and should stay in bed.
I'll report to you as they're back.
Sun...
Princess.
Khan is still concerned about Eagle Division.
Can he dispatch them?
Please be at ease.
We have soldiers guarding there
and they cannot fetch any gromwells.
Thanks, Taoist Sun.
He's out of danger temporarily
but the change of his condition
is faster than my imagination.
You mean...
he cannot wait till ten days later?
Since I've told you ten days,
I will let him hold out until that time.
But if they cannot get the gromwells on time,
I'm afraid he'll be in danger.
Are you ready?
Yes. Please be at ease, Senior Qin.
Let's wait and see.
Nice!
Banish God of Plague!
- Banish God of Plague!
- Good job!
- Nice!
- Banish God of Plague!
Good!
Look at that!
Let's go to have a look.
Nice dance!
Awesome!
Small tricks.
It's our turn!
Hit below the belt...
Nice!
Good job!
Awesome!
Perfect!
Amazing!
So nice!
Banish God of Plague!
Good!
Throw the gromwells!
Banish God of Plague!
Awesome!
Nice!
Go to investigate their background.
Yes.
Put it here. Be cautious.
- Be careful!
- Senior Qin, is it enough?
I've counted. Enough for Eagle Division.
Leave some here and wait for their check.
I see.
Wait!
Are you going to leave?
What about me? What should I do?
As you've had enough fun, go back to your home.
Don't let your Father worry about you.
Sir.
What's going on?
Our leader wants to see you.
Your leader?
King of Mobei?
Sir, we're just commoners with no crimes.
Could you tell me why he wants to see us?
Does it need a reason?
Fine.
Well...
I'll go with you.
Please let them set out.
Who are you?
Our leader wants to see you all!
Sir, please take it easy
and let us have a discussion first.
Changge, what should we do now?
It's a crucial juncture for us.
We cannot make any mistakes.
If we conflict with them,
neither gromwells nor we can leave here.
That's it.
But if we follow them, won't we waste time?
Just play it by ear.
If things go wrong... Please be at ease.
I know the map of Mobei well.
If we want to break out of here,
Yanxing Sect can come to our aid at any time.
Okay.
Sir. We'll follow you.
This way.
No shoo-in. Retreat first.
Report to the leader at once.
Is your Highness King of Mobei, Yaoluoge Pusa?
I lead my trade caravan, passing your territory.
Please forgive our offence.
We do beg your pardon.
Forego formalities.
I've never thought you're a pretty lady
after you remove the attire of God of Plague.
King of Mobei lost to a young lady.
Well, you're the other God of Plague.
Shut up.
Who allows you to see my face?
Oh, come on!
It's only because you lost to us.
You're as old as my uncle
and why are you still aggressive?
You not only hate to face your failure but also want to play tricks.
Shame on you!
Who is old?
You!
You're at least 20 years older than me!
I won't argue with you.
My soldiers find plenty of gromwells on your carriages.
Tell me.
Who are you?
And why do you embezzle gromwells at all cost?
Please calm down.
We're non-native businessmen,
knowing nothing about rules here.
As we cannot purchase gromwells,
there's no other way for us.
Why do you want gromwells?
Because trades of gromwells are banned in all tribes here.
Sounds interesting.
Go ahead.
We want profits
so we care nothing about the risk.
Since Ashile Tribe bans the trades,
there must be guys who need it.
As you're subject to Ashile Tribe,
you dare not allow people to sell.
As long as we can get it,
we can find buyers and double to send it.
Huge profits.
By the way, I'm curious about one thing.
Go ahead.
As you've noticed it very early,
why didn't you inquire us when we won?
Why do you ask us now?
What are you waiting for?
You're smart
but you have no chance to know it.
Soldiers.
Put these reckless guys in jail.
- Yes!
- Hold on!
Do it at once!
Don't waste my time!
- Put them in jail!
- Go!
- We can't leave now.
- Loose us!
- Wait a second!
- Yaoluoge Pusa!
King!
- You.
- King!
Come here.
Have you let the soldiers of Monan leave?
Seeing their lord be arrested,
they hurried to leave and report.
It's a smart young lady.
I see. You can leave.
Report to me as King of Monan comes.
Yes.
Anyone's here?
We want to leave!
We want to see King of Mobei!
We need to see your King!
Come on!
Changge, what should we do?
We've stayed in Mobei for a few days
and we need eight or nine days to rush back without rest
while we're now detained here,
knowing nothing about the time to leave.
Let's try to find a way to leave!
What my father has told me is right.
Here's a bad place!
Why do you say so?
Mobei and Monan were good neighbors.
A hundred years ago,
Mobei conquered Monan's ancestral territory.
After that, they've had battles for long because of it.
Afterwards, Ashile Tribe came.
Though they had no fights,
both of them led a hard life
and my Father forbade me from going out to play.
So they're bitter enemies.
Though King of Mobei is the leader,
he's controlled by Ashile Tribe.
According to his expressions,
it seems that he's ashamed of it.
All the people here are ashamed of it!
No one wants to be a slave.
And no one wants to be controlled.
Our trades of herbs even need to obey their rules!
Anyone's here?
- Why are you crying?
- Come over here!
Go to tell your King
that I want to make a deal with him!
- Come back!
- You'll regret!
COME BACK!
Take it easy.
My Father will come to save us.
He's the bravest man in the world.
How can I take it easy?
We need the herbs to save people's lives!
Hang in there, Mu Jin!
Mu Jin...
I need to go out... Come back! Let us leave!
I want to see your King!
Release us!
Hurry!
Anyone's here?
Come on!
Let us go to see your King!
Thanks to you,
there has been no new patients recently.
All the patients we have are in stable condition.
Tegin! Mu Jin seems in a bad condition.
Taoist. How is he?
The plague is always changing.
A mutation will suddenly come during the treatment.
I'm afraid
he's unlucky.
He's suddenly
in the most dangerous condition.
Could you help him?
It's all up to his fate.
What do you mean?
Cold and heat struggles in his body.
We must cool down his heat first.
But all my ways are in vain.
I'm afraid...
he cannot hold out until the appointed time.
Mimi...
Noble Princess.
Do you think I'm old?
No.
You're still as brilliant as my first glimpse of you.
Only you and Alir are sincere to me.
As for Alir...
No one can serve me better than her.
Unfortunately...
she's Ashile Sun's mother.
She has to be killed by me in the end.
Being served by her for years,
I really don't want to do so.
Forget it...
I don't need to make feints before her anymore.
What about finding you some new female slaves?
No thanks.
Do you want to report to me anything?
Report to Your Highness.
I have some news from the Desert.
Ashile Sun didn't go there himself.
He appointed his female slave to go there.
Mimi Guli went with her as well.
And someone from the Central Plains
accompanied them.
Female Slave...
Central Plains...
She's Li Changge.
I think so.
I've never thought
he would let Li Changge
go to complete such a crucial task.
It seems their relationship is unusual.
Li Changge is not a common lady.
Glue to her.
Please be at ease.
They have been arrested by King of Mobei.
Because of the prohibition of gromwells?
Yes. Mobei fears Khan's Tent and dares not to violate it.
Sensible boys.
But don't let down guard.
Ask someone to warn Mimi Guli secretly
not to forget her task.
At your command.
Besides,
call up 10 thousand infantries each from Mobei and Monan.
Step up the practice.
I will.
By the way,
you've told me
to find me some new female slaves?
Then bring me their wives and daughters.
I see.
In addition, ask a new emissary to go to Mobei,
showing him Li Changge's image.
I want to know all the Eagle Division's movements in Mobei.
Yes.
King.
They're clamoring for seeing you again.
Who?
The one who dressed up as God of Plague.
They call her "Changge".
Can she come to see me as she wants?
- Let them alone.
- Yes.
King, King of Monan comes.
He comes quickly this time.
- Bring him in.
- Yes.
You.
Go to the jail and bring his daughter here.
Yes!
We must protect our Young Master.
Play it by ear.
Come on! We waste an entire night!
How is Eagle Division?
Why hasn't no one come yet?
If we can't make a deal with them, then let's break out.
Probability of success?
About 60%.
We can have a try.
Fine.
Let's prepare for it first
and then take action in 30 minutes.
Okay.
Is he willing to see me?
You?
Impossible.
Our King wants to see Princess Tujia.
Princess Tujia?
Is there anyone called that?
Princess Tujia.
Don't bother me!
Tell my father I'll get up later.
Time to get up, Princess Tujia.
You're Princess Tujia?
Our King asked Princess Tujia to go to see him.
Where is she?
Father... My father must come to save me!
I am!
This way, please.
Don't worry!
As I see my father, I'll beg him to save you out!
I thought you would come in the afternoon.
But you come early in the morning.
You're really impatient.
Pusa.
I don't want to argue with you.
Tell me where my daughter is!
Yinan.
Can you be polite?
Your words are ugly.
Your daughter carried soldiers of Monan,
crossing my territory,
and stole gromwells with unidentified spies,
trying to carry them away.
I haven't blamed you for all these things,
yet you're now quarreling with me?
Spies?
What spies?
I thought you ordered them to do that.
After thinking for a while,
you might have known Ashile Tribe's order
about banning trades of gromwells.
I think you dare not violate its order.
Pusa!
How dare you!
I can fight with you
but let my daughter off first!
- Tujia!
- Father!
Pusa!
If you hurt her,
then my troops will be ready to fight!
Yinan.
Haven't we got enough battles already?
If Ashile Tribe knows
she carried gromwells away secretly,
I'm afraid... What do you want?
Do you know that they called up soldiers from us quite often?
Come to the point!
The day before yesterday,
they came to call up again.
I've promised them I'll give them in ten days.
I've heard
you carried a battalion of cavalry elites
to find your daughter.
What about leaving them here
and carrying her back?
How do you think?
You've gone too far.
Think of it.
Father...
Fine. I agree.
Let her go.
Loose her.
- Tujia!
- Father!
Tujia!
My daughter!
Did you get hurt?
Did I make trouble with you again?
My daughter.
Don't be willful later on.
- Let's go back home.
- Father!
I wish you can do me a favor.
I had some new friends
and they've been arrested too.
Could you help them?
What friends?
I know you're not interested in gromwells.
Did they abet you to do so?
No! They're good people.
Your daughter is really simple.
She believes in all others' words.
Beware of deceptions.
Father, don't listen to him!
If you only know them by chance,
then don't raise new issues.
Father, please meet them.
Then you'll know they're all good!
Changge told me they needed gromwells to save people!
Save people?
Pusa.
Bring her here.
More people, more cost.
Can you afford?
It's my business.
Just bring her here.
You.
Go to bring her here.
Yes.
Noble emissary from Khan's Tent is here.
How dare you not go out to welcome me?
Well, can pigs fly now?
You guys stay together?
Fine.
Then I don't need to go to Monan in the hot sun.
The emissary from Khan's Tent?
What's the matter again?
Two things.
First, Great Khan orders Mobei and Monan
to deliver 10 thousand infantries separately.
Set out in 10 days.
Where to go?
Go to enlist in the troop of Dingxiang.
Khan's Tent is forcing them to deliver.
Dingxiang... Second,
Thanks to all you tribes for serving King's Tent.
Khan asked Khatun to invite all your female families
to Khan's Tent and live for a few days.
What female families?
Wife and daughter.
I have no wife and daughter.
I'm afraid you've made a futile run.
I hear your mother is still alive...
I hear there's a cute young princess in Monan.
I won't go!
Well, here you're.
That's all.
I've told you all.
No one can violate Khan's orders.
Behave yourselves.
Do you remember?
Yes.
Don't alert them.
Report to me about her things at any time!
I've never seen him before...
while it seems
he knows me?
That man!
We can't let him leave!
Who are you?
Changge!
She's the one you want.
I won't hold back.
I'm the military counsellor of Eagle Division,
Ashile Sun's trusted follower.
Capture that man at once.
I'll be solely responsible for the consequence!
How to be responsible for it?
If you offend Khan's Tent, no one here can be free!
You cannot be free now!
Stop him at once!
We have no time!
I'm here to find gromwells
for a pestilence is raging in Eagle Division,
but Khan's Tent blockades all purchasing channels.
What does it mean?
It means they have abandoned Eagle Division.
Now, we have to form an alliance!
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad