♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad Episode 33
Can you still move?
Yes.
[Liuyun Taoist Temple]
Minister Du,
archers are all here and waiting for your order.
As for that, I can do it.
[Liuyun Taoist Temple]
Li Yaoshi?
We're specialized in different aspects.
Mr. Du, about what you're not good at,
please let me do it.
What are you staring at me, Mr. Du?
I've been in your place many times to ask for you help,
but I even couldn't meet you.
However, what happened in Liuyun Taoist Temple
could bring you here.
I found a good apprentice,
but I haven't got a chance to teach.
If he dies there,
that would be a huge loss to me.
Today,
you two can die together with me.
That's worthwhile to me.
Ashile Sun,
how dare you betray Khan and secretly help her?
Big circle defeats small one.
It's him.
Who?
Everyone listen!
The 3rd, 6th and 7th soldiers in row 3 step forward!
The 2nd, 3rd, 6th and 7th soldiers in row 4 step backward!
Draw the bow!
Changge, let me take care of everything.
Trust me.
Drop!
Everyone returns to his place!
The 3rd and 4th in row 1 step forward!
The 4th and 5th in row 4 and 5 step backward!
The tortoise doesn't show its head!
Drop!
Don't let her get away.
Ashile Sun,
Don't you think you let down Great Khan
who brought you up since so many years?
No, he didn't let Khan down.
He's also helping Ashile Tribe.
It's not easy that the tension
between Tang and Ashile Tribe got eased.
But you're stirring up again.
Do you really think the lives of soldiers on both sides are nothing?
The achievement of a general cost many lives.
I'm doing a great thing.
I can't care about all the minor details.
If you move aside now,
I can still hide it from Great Khan for you.
Otherwise,
your Eagle Division and you
will definitely get punished by heaven.
Shut up!
Ashile Sun,
are you really gonna help Du Ruhui's side?
Are you really gonna betray Ashile Tribe?
Stop talking nonsense.
I'm only saving a person I care about.
I didn't betray Ashile Tribe.
Contrarily, looking at what you did,
you're trying to get Ashile Tribe and Tang in a war.
And that is putting our Tribe in misery.
Do you think you can hide what you did from Great Khan?
Ashile Sun,
Tang's soldiers won't let you go.
Someone here.
Take her away.
Yes.
We haven't done head counting.
No need to be scared now, Princess.
Where's he?
Who?
The one who cooperated with me, of course.
It was me that cooperated with you just now.
Well.
Don't you believe?
Do you two know each other?
We've mentally known each other for long.
Right, Li?
Yes. We've mentally known for long.
About such kind of fate,
you won't understand, Mr. Du.
Commander Hao. We didn't find them.
Father.
There's no one in the backyard.
It's always been only Master and me here.
Who are you looking for, Minister Du?
Never mind.
I'm sorry for what I did before.
Please forgive me, Master.
To save you,
she almost died.
You should also take care.
Don't get too obsessed.
Master, you should have a good rest since you're injured.
As for the chores here,
I'll send people to handle.
Thanks for your kindness, Minister Du.
Please wait a second, Mr. Du.
Your behavior now
is getting more and more confusing.
Who are you exactly looking for?
And you just let that person go like that.
I'm working for the imperial court.
It has nothing to do with you.
However, about your odd behaviors,
I can't understand.
Fine.
I just helped you eliminate the enemies.
And now you're so mean.
You're only an ordinary person now.
Surely you're not qualified to question that,
unless you can become an officer again
and work for the imperial court.
You're prodding me again.
Well. It's fine that you don't tell me.
I don't really care about it.
Anyway, the things about the imperial court
are too ambiguous and it's hard to make them clear.
You're the one who wanted to catch.
And now you just let that person go.
You can't even decide it yourself.
Stop talking nonsense.
How officious you are.
Now what matters more is to find Crown Prince,
and the rest of our enemies here in the city.
They should know where Crown Prince is.
Father.
I'll let them lock the city gate
and search in the whole city.
Wait.
Though I'm only an ordinary person,
I can't help saying something.
You make it so obvious.
Don't you worry that you'll wake the rest enemies?
What do you mean?
Despair gives courage to a coward.
If they kidnapped Crown Prince,
what will happen?
You've created such a disturbance.
I think they won't stay here for long.
It won't be wrong that you guard the city gate.
There are so many people.
We can't check them one by one.
What's more, you've seen it.
They are all disguised as ordinary people and refugees.
How can you check them?
Mr. Du,
I have an idea free from waking the enemies.
Please tell us, Princess.
I can find the spies disguised as refugees.
But...
I need your token.
Line up!
Thanks.
- You all can have it.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Here.
It's provided by the officer.
Those who want to go out,
get the porridge before leaving.
Next one.
- Thanks.
- Next one.
Thanks a lot.
Thank you.
Next one.
Thanks.
Wait.
I'm sorry.
Next one.
Even if Changge is fine,
I won't forgive you.
Line up, please.
Next one.
Follow that father.
Yes.
Stop eating.
Since we're out of the city,
you're useless.
Don't move!
Take him back.
Yes.
Move!
How is it going?
I've arrested him.
You're wise, Princess.
You figured out such a brilliant idea.
For the people who're really starving,
such little dirt means nothing.
Did you get hurt?
I'm hungry.
I'll get you some food, OK?
I've sent people guarding around here.
Everything goes well as your plan.
It's not safe outside now.
Let me send you home.
Since the business has been settled,
Commander Hao doesn't need to do so.
Go.
Let this big brother get some food for you.
Mr. Wei.
How is it going?
When we counted the dead bodies,
it seemed that something went wrong.
But it also seemed... nothing went wrong.
Did anything go wrong or not exactly?
I heard that a soldier found a corpse moving.
Then Commander Hao checked on his own.
When he went back,
he seriously criticized that soldier,
saying that he had giddiness.
But...
it didn't look like what Commander Hao would do.
He used to would rather wrong a thousand suspects
than let one go.
Commander Hao did everything carefully.
Stop your gossip.
I dare not do that.
Get up.
It's over now.
Keep your mouth shut.
Don't ever mention it again.
Yes.
You can leave now.
Changge.
Good that you can escape safely.
Your companion is indeed capable.
Open the door.
Minister Du.
This evil woman...
It's OK.
Yes.
It seems that you're in the mood, Lady.
I wonder if you'd like to talk with me.
You know,
I was in Luoyang once
with my grandfather when I was little.
And my favorite is the peonies here.
You can found them easily among various kinds of flowers.
At that time, I was thinking
that I also want to be like a peony.
I want to be the outstanding one
among a group of people.
Your wish has come true.
Now everyone in Luoyang knows that
an evil woman ruined Liuyun Taoist Temple
and cruelly killed people.
Tell me,
who are you?
What do you want?
I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm from Family Yang in Hongnong.
Lord Jingwu, Yang Su, is my grandfather.
So you're the leftover villains of Sui.
And you still have evil intentions.
Sui will control Central Plains again one day.
Your Sui is fatuous and cruel.
It's already gone.
You can stop working in vain.
Whether it's gone already,
you can wait and see, Minister Du.
You still have other companions?
Or...
you're just following someone's order?
Since it's a game,
it won't be interesting if I tell you.
Your companions in this city have all been eliminated.
You'd better give in.
If you tell us everything,
you can make amends for your faults.
Then I can still keep you alive.
If I was afraid of death,
I wouldn't have come here.
Good.
Then I'll lock you here
and you'd wish you were dead.
[Dapu Inn]
Don't move.
You finally wake up.
How do you feel?
Much better.
Where are we?
You're in the inn we live in.
Don't worry.
It's very safe here.
The man who ran after us
let us go deliberately.
If Commander Hao insisted arresting me,
we couldn't have run away whatever we did.
Will he continue going after you?
It doesn't matter.
Medicine is ready.
Taoist Sun gave the prescription.
Take it before it gets cold.
Changge is injured,
so it might not be convenient.
I can do it.
The medicine was just...
just boiled.
I can take it myself.
Are you OK?
Are you good?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Let me do it.
Just leave us here.
Shiba.
You often hurt people unintentionally.
Let's leave here.
Let him deal with it.
- I can do it myself.
- Don't move.
Anything funny?
Take the medicine.
That's horrible.
Little by little, when can I finish it?
Slowly. Easy.
So bitter.
Looking at you,
it's still not bitter enough.
Your word is not a comfort at all.
What kind of comfort do you want?
Sun.
Have we forgotten anything?
What's wrong?
- Li Chengqian.
Where's exactly my little brother?
That's worrisome.
God bless the good man.
His Highness will be fine.
Princess. Mr. Wei.
Someone sent a letter.
Give it to me.
[Open it immediately]
Tell Minister Du, that I took the letter.
Yes.
That's Changge's handwriting.
[Crown Prince is in Sumo Hall of Dongshi.]
Sumo Hall of Eastern Market.
Let's go to find my brother.
Wait.
Luoyang is in turmoil now.
It might be a trap.
I can't ignore your safety.
But... Ask Hao Du to come with us.
When did you begin trusting Hao Du so much?
At least you'll be safer.
I can yield,
but I can't put you in danger.
Brother Shuyu will always protect me.
Hao Du.
There's some news about Crown Prince.
[Sumo Hall]
Li Changge.
How dare she lock me at such kind of place?
Chengqian.
Let me check.
What happened?
Hao Du!
Take people to shut up this place!
And arrest all of them!
No one can escape.
Chengqian.
Are you deaf?
Your Highness,
since you're fine,
let's not attract the attention.
No way!
I have to revenge.
Now! Immediately!
Shut it up!
How dare you violate my order?
Sister!
They don't listen to my order.
Say something!
It's fine. Little brother.
You're Crown Prince.
How can you be so unreasonable like a naughty kid?
Go home with me.
And that Li Changge.
I have to catch her.
And make her suffer!
You saw Changge?
It was her that locked me here.
Where's Du Ruhui?
Minister Du is waiting for your Highness at the state office.
Please go back with Princess at first, your Highness.
Good.
She stopped me from having fun
and kept me in such kind a place.
I'll tell Minister Du
and let him arrest the bitch Li Changge!
Changge was right.
If it were me, I'd let you stay in the pigsty.
You're still thinking about having fun at this time.
No.
It was too boring at night.
I wanted to relax outside.
Li Chengqian.
You're the Crown Prince,
but you only care about having fun.
You put the whole Luoyang in a mess. You...
You're completely outrageous.
What's more,
who is bitch?
That's your cousin.
Sister.
You slapped me.
You slapped me for Li Changge!
How can you not cherish your dearest brother?
That hurts, right?
You deserve it.
I...
Leyan.
Li Chengqian Leyan.
Come here.
Why are you hiding?
Li Chengqian, come here.
Li Leyan.
- Come here!
- Let him go.
You're perverted by Li Changge.
I'll tell father about that.
You... come here.
Brother Shuyu. Don't stop me.
I'll give him a lesson.
Come here!
You're misled by Li Changge.
Come here.
Sister, stop.
I'm sorry.
Brother Shuyu. Help me.
Leyan. Forget about it.
Someone is watching.
Li Chengqian.
I'm warning you.
When you're back,
you'd better restrain yourself.
If you dare mention Li Changge to anyone,
I'll break your leg.
I won't mention her. I won't.
I haven't seen her at all.
Brother Shuyu. Let's go.
But Crown Prince...
Hao Du, send Crown Prince home.
Remember,
if he dares say anything,
you can beat him to death.
[Sumo Hall]
Help...
Here comes the trade caravan!
Trade caravan.
You can't catch me.
You can't catch.
Stop running.
Mimi.
Traveling merchants are here.
They brought lots of goods.
Let me take you to have a look.
Mimi. It would be late if you don't go there now.
Where's she?
Never mind.
I'll get some unique things for you.
Lambs.
Hurry. Have your meal.
Come out to have your meal.
Come here.
Come.
Go out. Move.
Let's go.
Come. Move.
Hurry. Let's go.
Little brother.
Wake up, little brother.
Sister.
Help me.
Who are you?
Why are you here?
Wake up.
Where are you from?
It's so hot.
No.
I have to find the doctor to check you.
You're finally awake.
Master asked me to remind you.
What are you saying?
She told you
not to forget your task.
Who are you?
Who sent you here?
Why are you here?
Master ordered you to keep me here.
No way.
I have to send you out.
Let's get out.
Sister, please help me.
Sister.
Please help me.
Otherwise Master will kill me.
You...
Master said that if you don't behave well,
you should know the consequence.
Mimi. Are you there?
Mimi.
I'll come in.
It's early in the morning.
Why are you yelling?
Traveling merchants were here.
I wanted to take you to pick some good things,
but you were not there.
So I went there myself.
Every morning, I feed the lambs.
So you went feeding the lambs.
I have a good stuff for you.
Go, let's check it inside.
Can't we just talk outside of the tent?
Mimi.
Are you blaming me for going there alone without you?
No.
I was afraid if I went there late,
Su Yishe and others would snatch them all.
I said that I don't blame you.
Mimi.
How about having a walk?
The flowers outside our division are blooming.
They're colorful.
Very beautiful.
Let's go.
Go.
It's really very pretty.
You'll know it when you get there.
Go.
That's it.
Why did you bring me here?
Well.
Don't you like here?
Yes, I do like it very much.
By the way,
you said that you had something for me.
What's this?
Open it and have a look.
It's a candy.
Where did you get it?
I traded it with traveling merchants.
Do you like it?
Have a taste.
That's so sweet.
Why do you stop eating?
It's quite a good stuff. How can I eat it?
I should keep it as a treasure.
It's enough only by licking it.
Mu Jin.
Thank you.
No need to say thanks.
As long as you like it,
I'll always buy it for you from now on.
Mimi.
I love you.
Do you know why I brought you here?
Because I heard that
as long as I come here with the one I love,
we'll be together forever.
I want to be with you forever.
What are you talking about?
I mean it.
I really like you very much.
Mu Jin.
You're a good man.
I don't deserve you.
You don't need to belittle yourself.
It's me that don't deserve you.
I'm sorry.
Sister. It hurts.
I made you hurt.
Master ordered you to keep me here.
Mu Jin.
I really don't deserve your love.
Hurry.
Come.
Follow us.
Quickly. Come.
Wait for me.
I always have the feeling
that Sun has been away for long.
When Sun was still little,
though he was afraid of me,
he always begged me to teach him the martial arts.
But now...
Great Khan doesn't feel well these days.
Please don't drink too much wine.
Who asked you to come here?
Leave here.
Please remember to have your medicine, Great Khan.
I haven't been in Eagle Division for long.
And I also haven't seen Sun for a long time.
If I knew what would be like today,
we two shouldn't have doubted each other.
If he'd like to come back now,
I'll definitely award him greatly.
♫ The wicker is broken and the flowers fly away.
♫ I ask the passengers whether he'll come home.
Jinse.
Princess.
Well done.
I want you exactly to torture me in front of Yanli.
When you humiliate me more,
people here would all feel more sorry for me.
When everyone here doesn't think I'm dangerous,
it would be the best time for me to take an action.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Stand up.
Princess.
I'm sorry that you suffered.
That's not a big deal.
You're my capable assistant.
Don't let me down.
Princess.
I'll do whatever I can,
even if I might die for that.
It's...
me that's not capable.
I'm so incapable.
Princess.
Has that child arrived at Eagle Division?
Yes, Princess.
He's arrived.
But...
I underestimated Yanli's feelings towards Ashile Sun.
I didn't expect that he still cares about his son.
When I encouraged Li Changge to save Luo Yi,
and asked Alir to help her,
I was trying to find a chance to kill Ashile Sun.
But Sher was too softhearted.
He kept this bane alive.
You took a risky move, Princess.
Thankfully Alir is dead and can't prove anything.
Otherwise...
Otherwise what?
Luo Yi betrayed Sui.
Of course I'd have an excuse
to get myself free from being doubted.
By the way, is there any news from Luoyang?
No.
No news.
I'm afraid that would be the worst news.
Jinse probably didn't finish her task.
We should move faster.
While Ashile Sun isn't back,
begin whatever we can.
Please be assured, Princess.
For these two months,
I have been arranging our men around Yanli
according to your order.
He won't be Great Khan for long.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad