♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 32
Princess.
- All piss off.
- Yes.
You tailed me.
Did you lie to me and take advantage of me
from the beginning?
- I was under orders--
- Under orders to cheat me.
Take me as a lure for my best friend,
and capture her as a booty to satisfy Minister Du,
so as to get promotion.
Am I right?
- If there's nothing else--
- Answer me.
Crown Prince's missing is a big deal.
It was I who took Changge to Ziwei Palace.
If Changge's involved in Crown Prince's missing,
am I an accomplice?
I used to fear you for your cold-bloodedness,
but later I thought
you were good-natured under your indifference.
But now,
I think you're a puppet
without emotions, thoughts or heart.
Hao Du,
can't you see with your eyes?
Since Changge ran away from Chang'an,
did she do any harm to our people
or Tang Dynasty?
In Youzhou,
to capture Li Yuan and Wang Junkuo,
Changge risked her life and narrowly escaped death.
In Shuozhou,
she was even captured for the people there.
Isn't enough for her
to have escaped death once?
Are your so-called orders so important?
♫ As long as you're happy. ♫
Hao Du,
one lives neither for obeying orders,
nor for credits,
but for what is worthwhile.
I understood it too late,
so I lost Changge.
♫ I can't get rid of what is called love. ♫
♫ I'm not afraid of being exiled alone, ♫
♫ flying in the sky, ♫
♫ as long as you're happy. ♫
[Dapu Inn]
Yuan, what's up?
Are you unhappy?
Didn't you play happily with Sun?
Look who's here.
Young Master!
Sister, it's Brother Li.
Yuan, come here.
You're this tall now.
I can't even hold you.
Where's Senior Qin?
- I'll look for him.
- Okay.
Take care.
Go ahead.
Senior Qin.
Young Master, you're finally back.
When you were not here, we were rather anxious.
So was Senior Qin.
We were all looking for you.
I'm sorry to have let you worry.
Shiba.
Shiba,
thank you for helping me take Sun away.
It's my duty,
but I hope just this once.
I promise.
Young Master.
Senior Qin.
Well.
You're back safely.
I can finally rest assured.
Sorry to make you worried.
Never mind.
I'm quite excited to know you're safe.
Young Master,
what's your next plan?
I don't know.
I don't know I can survive this time.
The officials in Chang'an have arrived in Luoyang.
I'm afraid you can't stay here for long.
Go back to grasslands with me.
They've found you.
The best way is
to leave for someplace they don't know.
Let me think over it.
Changge,
There're three things you promised me left.
Gonna break your promise?
I thought when I was dying, we were quits.
Quits?
You want us to be quits?
Let's leave it later.
Leaving Luoyang is the most urgent thing now.
As for where to go,
you can decide when we get out of here.
Please let us know when you decide.
Yanxing Sect's at your service.
Did you forget your mission
after being slapped by Princess?
I dared not.
Dared not?
The longer Li Changge remains on the loose,
the more dangerous Crown Prince will be.
I just don't understand
why you conclude it's Li Changge who caused Crown Prince's missing?
Are you questioning me?
I dare not.
I just saw in person
in Shuozhou,
Li Changge's sufferings for the people there.
If she wanna harm our country,
- she utterly...
- Shut up.
It's the first time you've questioned me.
I didn't mean it.
I'm bound to capture Li Changge again for you.
Don't bother.
Now that you've been swayed,
seizing Li Changge is not your business anymore.
Father,
you haven't fully recovered.
It's not your business.
Just stay at home and reflect on your mistakes.
Think about your identity.
I will.
Did you lie to me and take advantage of me
from the beginning?
I used to fear you for your cold-bloodedness,
but later I thought
you were good-natured under your indifference.
But now,
I think you're a puppet
without emotions, thoughts or heart.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
If Li Changge's there,
don't kill her for the sake of Crown Prince.
Yes.
[Luoyang Office]
Thanks.
- Have some water.
- Thanks.
[Liuyun Taoist Temple]
You must be the Master.
Yes, I am.
I'm from the Central Plains,
but moved out after marriage.
On knowing my hometown suffered a disaster,
I felt so concerned.
On the way of visiting my relatives,
I heard Liuyun Taoist Temple
had been helping refugees for charity.
I come specially to offer incense
as a pathetic contribution.
You're so kind-hearted.
Please.
Why're you standing here?
Yesterday you told me to leave the issue later.
A night passed.
Can we talk about it?
Well...
You first.
Li Changge,
I don't want us to be quits.
Take back what you said.
Now both of us are alive.
We can't be quits.
How can I take back what I said?
It's a deal between the two of us.
I've never agreed to be quits,
so what you said doesn't count.
Why're you so shameless?
You're unreasonable.
Whatever.
All in all,
I remember what you owe me,
and will never forget it.
So... we can't be quits.
Okay,
I promise you.
Liar, liar, pants on fire.
Then can you let go of me?
Where're you going?
Liuyun Taoist Temple.
To say goodbye to Master.
With plenty of things to do,
I can't leave until I finish what should be done
and the handover.
I'll accompany you.
It's inconvenient for you
to go to a Taoist temple for nuns.
I just wanna say goodbye, and come back soon.
Let me accompany you to the gate.
I won't get in.
Since when have you become a hanger-on?
♫Who can say that one has never been shy♫
♫or missed anything for a while on the way?♫
♫Looking at the color of the blue sky♫
♫Dyeing your eyebrows corner, I'm dazzled♫
I don't want to lose you again.
That feeling.
♫My hair is a mess♫
♫A twinkle in your eyes♫
♫That's the warmness♫
At dusk,
I'll pick you up at the gate.
I'm not a three-year-old kid.
♫I wish you were a lasting song for me♫
Remember, I'll pick you up.
Okay.
♫So I'll hold your hands♫
♫All unknown lights♫
♫Light up the boundless blue sky♫
Master,
- I saw at the gate...
- Take your time.
I saw a group of people.
I didn't know what they are coming for.
It seems they didn't come for a doctor.
It's Minister Du...
Is A'Li back?
It seems A'Li has no chance to be here at our temple again.
Anyway.
I hope she has gone away long ago,
and won't bite the hook here.
What does it have to do with A'Li?
Excuse myself.
Taoist Master blesses you.
Minister Du,
have you fully recovered?
Thanks for your concern.
It's not easy for me to recover.
Today I come to
bother Taoist Sun with a check of my body.
Unfortunately, he went out
with Situ Langlang to see patients at dawn.
I don't know when they'll come back.
So Taoist Jingdan, can you give me a check?
It's my duty as a doctor.
- Minister Du, please.
- Please.
- Await me outside.
- Yes.
- Minister Du, please.
- Please.
- Your pulse condition...
- What?
It seems hard and tight with Qi depression.
You might have been furious and worried a lot
these days.
How can I not be worried about natural and man-made
calamities in Luoyang?
There're natural calamities indeed,
but man-made ones...
Have you heard of
the fire accident in Ziwei Palace?
Yes, I've.
The Palace caught fire and Crown Prince was missing.
You know how serious it is?
You mean it's related to
our Liuyun Taoist Temple?
You know it clearly.
Liuyun Taoist Temple's alienated from
the secular world and royal court,
only engaging in helping others.
Minister Du, you'd better have evidence.
Don't move.
Stop.
Behave yourself.
Don't move.
Evidence?
Minister Du's right.
The arsonist is here indeed.
Behave yourself.
- You're...
- Aren't you looking for me?
[Liuyun Taoist Temple]
Why is it so quiet today?
Brother Li, did you get it right?
I don't remember
you placed these two pieces.
You really leave no loopholes for me.
You're so cunning.
If we don't play fair,
I don't know when can we finish the game.
I'm playing chess.
Don't distract me.
Then...
Be careful.
You're like a spent arrow.
Don't struggle anymore.
You seem upright but crafty indeed.
But it's too early for you to be so excited.
It's unknown who'll win at last.
Don't move.
Behave yourself.
You'd better not fight with us,
or these pathetic beggars will kick the bucket.
Did you set the fire in the Ziwei Palace?
Who're you?
You don't have to know.
In short,
I'm here to kill you.
Did you kidnap the Crown Prince?
He's dead.
She's lying.
What does she want?
How dare you murder Crown Prince?
I'm the enemy of your master.
If it's not him,
who shall I kill?
Do you work for Ashile Tribe?
Now Crown Prince's dead.
You failed to protect him.
How can you report it to Li Shimin?
You'd better kill yourself
with dignity than be thrown into prison.
Full of nonsense,
not enough to sway your mind.
Thank you.
If you succeeded in killing him,
you'd have spread the news
and caused chaos all over Luoyang.
How can you wait till today?
How can you a Taoist
be such a busybody?
Ms. Quan!
Ms. Quan, are you okay?
Mind your own business,
or I'll stab her heart.
I'm the one you wanna kill.
Don't hurt innocent people.
Yeah.
You can't leave alive today.
It's known by all that
quick-witted Mr. Fang and Mr. Du
are Li Shimin's capable assistants.
It's not fruitless for me to kill one of them today.
You're brave enough,
but how do you feel now?
What about this?
You look handsome,
but can't move now.
What a pity!
Quickly, cut the crap.
If you ask for death,
I'll show my mercy, and satisfy you.
Wait!
This female slave looks quite familiar to me.
You're...
Sher's slave?
Lady Jinse, you get a good memory.
Why're you here?
I'm here to take revenge.
What revenge?
I've to take revenge on Du Ruhui.
Lady Jinse, what about leaving him to me?
Don't let his blood stain your clothes.
Unexpectedly,
I'm not the only one who is eager to kill Minister Du.
Did he make you be exiled to the grasslands?
Lady Jinse,
can you do me a favor?
Du Ruhui,
you can't die so easily.
Interesting.
Take aim.
Don't ruin my plan.
You cornered me in a dilemma for an evildoer.
Have you thought about today?
I've a clear conscience.
What a blood debt!
How dare you say so?
I don't know your relationship,
but I advise you not to assist another evildoer.
You're doomed. Cut the crap.
You deserve this!
A'Li,
think twice.
Don't make a great blunder.
If I don't kill Du Ruhui,
I can't feel at ease.
I thought you didn't split hairs,
but you're still unrepentant.
I'm wrong.
I aspire to save all,
but can't save you at last.
I don't need it.
Master, no more words.
Go ahead.
A'Li!
- A'Bi, take them away.
- Yes.
Why don't you cherish your life
after running away from grasslands?
In this case,
die with them!
I've just been out for hours,
but you're having such a fierce battle.
Thank you.
Never mind.
If Mr. Sun hadn't asked me to fetch medicine,
I'd not encounter such an interesting thing.
Master, hurry to help me.
Did I... Did I hear it right?
You called me Master.
Go.
It seems I've to rise to the occasion.
A'Li, take Minister Du and the others away.
Situ and I will cover you.
Hurry to go!
Minister Du.
Hurry.
Ms. Quan, take care. I'll open the gate.
Why can't I open it?
It can't be opened.
It's open. Let's go.
- Hurry.
- Go.
Li Changge!
Hurry.
Hurry!
What do you want at all?
Don't flatter yourself.
The reason why I saved you
is that you're inseparable from the country.
Take Minister Du away!
Minister Du, let's go.
Li Changge,
get out.
A'Bi, take care of them.
I'll save Master.
Minister, let's go.
Father,
I'm sorry.
Hao Du,
you've improved a lot.
Thanks, Father.
Remember, don't be conceited at any time.
You're obliged to guard Hongyi Palace,
and serve Prince Qin.
At the critical moment,
you even have to sacrifice your life.
Are you afraid?
No, I'm not.
I'll serve Prince Qin and Father forever.
Hurry.
Ms. Quan, take care.
Come on.
Minister Du!
It's a signal from Father.
Go.
Bad news from Liuyun Taoist Temple, right?
I wanna go as well.
Now Liuyun Taoist Temple's situation is unknown.
For your safety, you'd better stay at home.
How can I?
I don't know whether Changge's in danger.
- Let me go with you.
- Okay.
Leyan,
- follow me closely.
- Okay.
I have a nice book.
Wanna have a look?
No, thanks.
Just have a look.
[Warcraft of Lord Wei]
Brother Li, what do you mean?
Aren't you gonna leave?
It's a gift.
Don't forget me in the future.
It's not an ordinary thing.
Where did you get it?
Just family heritage.
It's Warcraft of Lord Wei...
Brother Li, are you...
Are you Li Jing, the Lord Wei?
Don't I look like him?
- Nice to meet...
- Sit down.
If you stand up, how can I talk to you?
Do you want, or dare you accept this book?
Why not?
Wait.
You must finish this game with me,
and then I'll give you this book.
Drums.
It's...
The sound of drums is a signal for assembling reinforcements
from the southwest.
It's at Liuyun Taoist Temple.
Liuyun Taoist Temple?
Changge!
It hasn't been finished yet.
I'll keep my words.
If you go now, you'll never get this book.
I have to go.
The book is so precious.
Thanks, Brother Li.
Thanks, General Li.
See you.
Listen,
if you go on like this,
I'll blow your brains out.
Hypocritical.
Go ahead.
Please spare me!
Master!
Master.
Why're you back?
You don't have to.
All this happened because of me.
You shouldn't account for it.
Master, take her away.
I'm on it.
Master, sit.
Wait a second.
Today I won't let you make it.
Don't overestimate yourself.
Attack!
You're awake.
Minister, our men are gathering.
Minister Du, please hold on.
I've asked a man to find Taoist Sun.
You'll be okay.
I'm okay now.
What's going on inside?
Master, A'Li and Mr. Situ are all inside.
Don't worry.
Master and Mr. Situ are skilled in martial arts.
- Father.
- Hao Du.
Sorry I'm late.
Hurry to save Li Changge out.
Sneak in the back.
There are many skilled killers from Ashile Tribe inside.
Kill them all and spare no one.
Yes.
Go.
- Minister.
- Mr. Du.
Princess, why're you here?
I... Wei Shuyu, take Princess back.
There are many skilled killers from Ashile Tribe inside.
It's dangerous.
But...
Where's A'Li?
In order to save us, she's injured,
and she is still inside.
Who the heck are you?
The one who will take your life.
Lady, kill her.
It's not the time.
Whoever you're,
I'll smash you to pieces when I'm out.
Ashile Sun, why're you here?
Jinse, it's you.
You are against me for a woman.
Do you forget your origin?
How dare you betray Khan for Tang Dynasty?
Kill him.
Kill them.
None shall survive.
Can you still move?
Yes, I can.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad