♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 34
The notice wrote that the court will distribute the unclaimed fields to refugees.
And those refugees will be free from rent and forced labor.
Build water conservancy projects and local public welfare barns.
Help disaster areas by creating jobs.
That's all.
The water can float a boat, but also overturn it.
Do you think that he would be a good emperor?
If he dares to keep a slack hand,
I could kill him then.
It is not a bad choice to let him go.
Maybe.
Although I'm not resigned to it,
but I'm clear that he is the best choice for Tang dynasty now.
What's your next plan?
Now they are know I am staying here,
so staying in Luoyang is not a good choice.
The border invasion of Tang dynasty has finished.
I plan to go to the desert.
Then come with me.
It's been a while for me to stay here.
I have no idea how Eagle Division is now.
It's time to go back.
I heard from Senior Qin that we could leave today.
So fast!
The passport I got from the officials is a literati family from the north.
Please call each other brother and sister later,
don't make any mistakes.
Thanks for your arrangement, Senior Qin.
Brother,
let's go!
You are so beautiful, my sister.
Put this on,
don't make bad men covet at you.
Disciple!
Master!
Taoist Sun.
Taoist Sun!
Luoyang is such a small place.
I never thought I would meet you here.
It seems that the destiny brings us together.
Where are you going?
Why not stay here for some more time?
No, no!
I heard that the emperor was asking to see me.
If his Majesty keeps me at the Imperial Medical Academy,
that will be too bad for me.
No!
I...I have to run!
This experience is both a disaster and a blessing for me.
I lost something but also gained a lot.
I finally understand my father's saying,
People's still living a hard life,
how could I look on with folded arms?
As my father's daughter,
how could I fall behind with no progress?
Sister!
Let's go faster!
I'll never come to this hell again!
Changge,
hope you all the best!
Brother Li,
what are you doing here?
I'm here to see you off.
General Li.
Just call me brother Li.
Brother Qin,
you are so bad!
You didn't even tell me that you are leaving.
Your girl is the princess.
What a good taste!
What are you talking about?
So mysterious!
Nothing.
How do you do, princess?
How do you do, Lord Wei?
Hope that you are well, princess.
I never thought that Lord Wei is also a free and unfettered man.
I have no more time to be free.
Several days later,
I will head to Chang'an with Minister Du.
Lord Wei endows with the talent to govern and to serve.
It's a pity to keep you in this countryside.
I envy you, princess.
The vast grassland abundant with rivers and vegetables,
and flocks and herds.
I really want to see it once I have a chance.
Brother Li,
how did you know that?
Don't be nervous.
I am here alone.
I have some words to say to you here.
Please, go ahead.
Actually, no Warcraft of Lord Wei exists.
That book was a lie.
I just wanted to see if you would give up your original aspiration for that warcraft.
But although there is no warcraft in this world,
strategists are.
Strategists can be generals and also swordsmen.
But a real strategist will never be defined by military accomplishments,
but his mind.
A benevolent heart is invincible.
Think about it.
Don't be anxious.
Someone can't figure it out in his whole life,
but I believe you can.
If one day we meet on the battlefield,
I will remember this.
A benevolent heart is invincible.
You are worth teaching.
Fine, it's time for me to go back,
or my wife would be angry.
Goodbye!
Take care.
Lord Wei passed his lifetime experience on you,
No one could ever compare to his generosity!
Come on!
Just a few days passed,
this is the thirteenth one!
Grand Witch, what is happening now?
I've tried all my methods,
but I couldn't help it.
More and more people have been laid up these days.
That couldn't be possible.
The water and food here are all clean.
How could it be?
I made a divination today.
I'm afraid that...this is a curse from the god.
A curse?
No,
we have to notice Sun about it.
This disease is infectious,
I've put them in danger.
No!
It couldn't be like this anymore.
No...
we can't stay here any longer.
We must go!
Sister... Go!
Where are we going?
Master said that if you didn't listen to her,
you should know the consequence.
Buzhen...
Where are we going?
Buzhen, Buzhen...
Help me!
Help!
Your Majesty.
Mr. Du.
You're back.
Your Majesty.
I saw Li Changge in Luoyang.
You saw Changge?
The god blesses me!
It'd be good if she is safe.
After she killed the leftover villains of Chini at Liuyun Taoist Temple,
she escaped with a man from Ashile Tribe.
I failed to catch her.
Please forgive me, your Majesty!
You are saying that she was with a man from Ashile Tribe?
Before she escaped, she saved me at Liuyun Taoist Temple,
as well as people there.
Please stand up, Mr. Du.
Yes...
Her adamant temper would never change no matter where she is,
or with whom she is getting along.
Thanks to that she is still alive,
or I would be guilty all my life.
No worries, your Majesty!
Li Changge not only lives a powerful life,
but also is killing people fiercely.
Mr. Du.
You've been a cautious man,
why did you let her go this time?
It's my fault.
But Li Changge is so cunning.
[Nan'an Courier Hostel]
I'm so tired!
I have to take a good shower first and then have a big meal!
Go!
Yes.
Princess.
It's time for dinner.
This is princess's dinner.
Yes.
Come on, give it to me.
Go out, I don't want to eat.
Brother Shuyu.
Why is it you?
I heard Haodu's voice just now.
Still angry with Haodu?
He lied to me and took advantage of me,
I'd never forgive him.
But you should eat.
Come on.
I'm also a bit hungry.
Let's have it together.
These are all from Haodu.
Then put it away.
I won't eat his food.
Do you feel that Haodu has changed?
I admit,
Haodu is much more kinder and softer than before.
But he lied to me,
and almost harmed Changge.
Whenever I thought this, I feel...
What if Haodu saved Changge?
What do you mean?
I have to tell you something.
That day when we were fighting with Chini at Liuyun Taoist Temple,
Changge was there too.
You know that.
But do you know how she escaped?
Changge is such a clever girl.
There were so many ways for her to escape.
Even if she is the cleverest man in the world,
she was encircled by soldiers at Liuyun Taoist Temple.
How could she escape without being noticed?
Are you saying that it was Haodu who secretly let her go?
I sent someone to ask about it.
When a soldier was counting bodies,
he found that a body was moving.
But Haodu scolded him, and said he was dimmed.
It seemed that it might be Changge.
But hasn't he been catching Changge all the time?
Who knows?
Maybe Changge changed him,
or you might wake him up by slapping.
Brother Shuyu.
Why are you telling me these?
You changed your view on him?
Change?
I still hate him.
But it's the fact.
You have the right to know.
I'm telling you these,
because I want you to accept his protection.
After all, he is quite a good bodyguard.
Thanks, Brother Shuyu.
Have your dinner, or it would be cold.
The grassland is ahead of us.
Young Master.
No matter where you are, I would always be with you.
Senior Qin,
for these years in Shuozhou,
you should hate and fear Ashile Tribe the most.
Senior Qin.
Why not...
I'll only follow masters with wisdom this whole life.
Others never matter to me.
Senior Qin.
I promise you safe when you are at Eagle Division.
A'Zhun.
You underestimated me.
I'm such an old man, what do I fear?
I didn't mean that.
It's quite late now.
Have a rest.
We have to continue our journey tomorrow.
Young Master, you too.
I'll let Xu Feng stay here.
Xu Feng might lull Yuan to sleep.
Don't wake him up.
Senior Qin, go to have rest now.
Okay.
Go.
Stop.
Tegin.
I never thought that you really found our young counsellor back.
Yaro, why are you here?
Mu Jin asked me to look for you in Tang,
but I find you here.
Tegin, come back quickly!
Eagle Division is in trouble.
What?
Grant Witch said that we were cursed.
Cursed?
I...I don't know it.
But many people in Eagle Division got a disease.
Ragged plaque appeared on their body,
and many people died.
Grant Witch had no way to solve it.
Go back and have a look!
Ragged plaque?
A disease?
Yes.
But Taoist Sun just left.
Senior Qin, can I ask you for help?
Go ahead, master.
Could you send people to find Taoist Sun back?
Because they are going on a donkey carriage,
they can't go too far.
No worries.
I'll send someone to find Taoist Sun back.
Thanks, Senior Qin.
Yaro, have some rest now.
We will go back to Eagle Division tomorrow morning.
Yes.
Changge.
Sun.
You can't shake me off.
We've been through so many scary things together.
We agreed to go through all the hardships together.
The same this time.
Okay.
Together.
Buzhen.
Brother,
you're awake.
Sorry...
It's okay.
I'm here.
You'll be okay.
Sister, I'm dying... Don't say that.
You are still young.
You will live to one hundred.
So good.
I can have a sister with me at last...
You'll be okay.
They sent me to transfer message to you.
But I accidentally got infected on my way here.
You'll be okay.
They said that as long as you saw my face, you would bring me back.
It's okay.
You'll be okay.
Buzhen.
Is his name Buzhen?
He's so lucky to have you as his sister.
It's okay.
I'll be with you.
There's no slave in heaven.
I'll get a basin of water for you,
and send you away with a clean body.
Mimi Guli,
are you there?
Mu Jin is with the Grand Witch now.
He asked me to take some spice for you to ward off evil.
You can burn it on the fire.
Are you in there?
I'm coming in.
This boy is the curse.
And she, is the one who brought the curse here.
It's her!
Fine, Mimi Guli.
We Eagle Division kept you here,
but you dared to curse us!
You harmed my son.
He is dying now.
Give him back to me!
Sorry.
Excuse me... What can a sorry do?
- Give my son back!
- Leave her alone!
Make this clear first!
Mimi.
Where did he come from?
You had nothing to do with him, right?
I saved him.
I secretly hid him here in my tent.
I...
I didn't think that he would be...
He...
She was bewitched.
So she could curse everybody!
Or why did she stay with the curse all the time
without getting infected?
Yes... Mu Jin.
You heard what Grand Witch said?
It was all her who made us harmed.
She is already bewitched.
We can't keep her here.
Kill her!
Yes!
Mu Jin.
Mimi Guli can't stay here any longer.
Kill her! Kill her!
Kill her! Kill her! Kill her!
You still want to protect her.
Mu Jin.
You are obsessed with this demon, aren't you?
Mimi Guli is also a member of Eagle Division.
I can't see you burning her to death without doing anything!
Burn her! Burn her! Burn her!
She can't stay.
Burn her! Burn her!
Burn her! Burn her! Burn her!
You hear that?
Stay away.
Get out of the way!
Do you want all the people to die with her?
If you want to burn her, burn me first!
Burn her! Burn her!
Mu Jin!
Burn her! Burn her! Burn her!
Burn her!
Stay away!
Stop!
Tegin! Tegin!
Tegin!
Sun!
You came back just in time!
Mimi Guli brought a curse to us.
We have had so many people ill.
They are dying.
Tegin,
you have to uphold justice for us.
Yes, yes!
Uphold justice for us!
Uphold justice for us! Yes!
We Eagle Division never kill each other!
Nothing will be a reason for us to kill each other!
Yes, he's right!
But Tegin... I will take charge of it.
I'll give everybody an answer.
Everybody,
go back now.
Go, let's go.
Go, go.
Go back.
Let's go.
Forget it.
Untie her.
Mimi...
- Mimi!
- Changge...
You finally come back!
Are you frightened?
It's okay now, it's okay.
Don't be afraid.
I'm back.
Everything would be okay.
Don't cry.
I just checked on those clansmen who got cursed.
How are they?
It may not be a curse.
It's plague.
Plague?
Follow me.
Go, follow me.
Mimi.
Where did you save him?
I herd sheep every morning.
He fainted outside the sheepfold.
I...
Do you know where he came from?
Since he got infected,
he couldn't have gone far.
Maybe he's from a tribe nearby.
It's okay, don't be afraid.
I know you wanted to save him.
But I think it's a little abnormal.
Did he say anything to you before he died?
No, Buzhen...
Buzhen?
Is his name Buzhen?
No...
I don't know his name.
I just call him this.
But if I hadn't taken him back,
he would have died.
I know, I know.
Calm down.
We will be with you all the time.
Stay here.
I'll go find Sun.
I'll be back soon.
I...
Plague is an incurable disease on grasslands.
What's the difference between it and curse?
If we call it a curse,
people would have a glimmer of hope.
The plague can't have no source.
It must be related to the boy brought back by Mimi.
Any information?
She calls him Buzhen.
I feel quite acquainted with this name.
Buzhen...
Did he know Mimi?
Maybe in some other relationship.
I'll go and ask her.
Wait.
Mimi won't say anything she doesn't want to say.
Okay.
I won't ask.
I will accompany her for a while later.
Leave Mimi alone first.
Sun.
What are you going to do about the plague?
Tonight, new tents should be built outside the campsite..
The patients will be treated in new tents.
This should be done as soon as possible.
Mu Jin,
arrange people and horses.
Help them transfer,
and move goods and materials.
Relatives can apply for going together.
We will cure them at any costs.
Yes.
Is this your routine?
Changge.
You know in our grassland,
if we encounter snowstorm during the migration,
what would we do?
Unite in a concerted effort to protect women and children?
No.
The old, weak, sick and disabled would stand outside,
to fend against snowstorm for those strong warriors and women.
And then they would die.
But I don't want this sacrifice.
There's also a convention in our central plains.
Do one's best and leave the rest to God.
But if you didn't exert all energies,
and try your best,
you can't leave it to god.
Maybe...
Maybe we missed some other ways.
What way?
It's been such a long time for Mimi to look after this boy.
And he was the source of plague.
Why didn't Mimi get infected?
You evil!
Give my son back!
Wait!
I'll kill you!
Only you are killed, can we be saved!
And my son would be saved!
Don't run!
How could you be so silly?
Why...
Why were you protecting me?
Why?
It's good that you are okay.
Mu Jin...
Sorry!
These red spots...
It's all my fault.
Mu Jin is infected now.
All these spots are the same with those on the dead.
We can't wait anymore.
I'll stay with Mu Jin outside our campsite.
No.
We have no other choice now.
Mu Jin can't be left behind.
I will treat Mu Jin.
But if you got infected too,
what could Eagle Division do?
Send him to my place,
I'll look after him.
No.
All this was because of me.
And Mu Jin became like this due to my fault.
No, Mimi.
You would die if you go out now.
Even if I die,
I deserve that.
Don't worry.
I'll take good care of him.
Taoist Sun! Master!
Senior Qin was so fast to take you here.
You are clever to ask Senior Qin to find me.
What curse?
Nonsense!
I have seen this situation so many times.
It must be a serious plague.
If I was not here,
how could you two deal with it?
Yes.
Thanks, Taoist Sun!
But you have to be cautious!
Because many people have been infected.
If not,
why would I come?
Taoist Sun, let me lead you.
Please follow me.
Please, Taoist.
You lead the way.
Senior Qin.
How are Shiba and Xu Feng?
Yuan is still too young,
I was afraid of her getting infected.
I asked Shiba and Xu Feng
to wait outside the tent of Eagle Division with Yuan.
That would be good.
Then Senior Qin,
you don't have to come inside either.
Wait for our message.
Okay.
Greetings, father.
Father.
Yan.
It's good for you to come back!
Greetings, father.
Come on.
Yan,
you... you are thinner than before.
It's my fault to worry you, father.
Father, I am thinner too,
I nearly couldn't make my way back.
In Luoyang...I...
Father.
My life was so hard in Luoyang.
Why did I hear that you had a good time in Luoyang?
Even Minister Du couldn't control you.
I know I was not right and made a big trouble.
I regret to do it too.
Sister has already scolded me for father.
Right, sister?
You're welcome, brother.
I didn't scold you.
You asked for it.
Father.
Sister beat me many times for this.
She held a stick like this to beat me.
I offended crown prince.
I accept my punishment.
Yan.
I think you are more and more like Changge now.
Father.
Although I am not Changge,
I got improved a lot after this disaster.
Sorry, father.
I was wrong.
Father, please forgive me for my sister's sake.
Go back to your Eastern Palace and ponder upon your faults!
Okay.
I will not disturb father's conversation with sister.
Yan,
it's been a hard way for you.
Father.
I don't think it's hard for me.
And this experience is worthy of volumes of books,
and I'm so lucky to have it in my life.
My Yan is much different from the one in the past.
Are you hungry?
Have dinner with me,
and chat while eating, okay?
I'll listen to father.
Taoist Sun.
How is it?
What curse?
Nonsense!
Just plague.
Then could it be treated?
Only invalid herb exists in this world,
but no incurable disease.
So you already have had a method to cure them?
Although this is serious,
we still have time.
Give me a pen and paper.
[Gromwell,stemmed, five qian; cicada slough; Angelica sinensis]
These herbs are quite common.
Eagle Division has these,
but we don't have one of them.
What?
Gromwell.
Could it be substituted by others?
No.
Adjuvant could be substitute,
but this could not be changed.
There's something that you don't know.
Plague came from the desert,
but it never came to the grassland.
That's because that the local usually eat and wear lithospermum.
That's it!
No wonder I didn't get infected.
Every time I got fever when I was young,
my father treated me with gromwell.
As far as I know, once you get this plague,
you won't get infected again.
So she was not just lucky,
but have immunity against it.
We can find this gromwell.
But how can we control his state of illness now?
Don't worry,
I can give you a prescription,
and let them drink it.
It can relieve their illness a little,
and save them out of danger.
But they have to have gromwell in ten days,
or even immortals could not save them.
Gromwell is from the north of the desert,
I thought that you would have it.
Khan's Tent must have it.
I'll go and ask for it.
Wait.
Eagle Division is quite unstable now,
if you go now,
I'm afraid that they would find ways to harm Mimi.
It would be a mess again.
Tegin,
I can go.
I'm fast.
Besides, I am just a nobody.
Great Khan won't bewilder me.
Don't worry, Tegin.
I promise that I'll be back with the herb safely.
Okay.
I've written down the moves of Dingxiang in Central Plains.
Give this to Great Khan,
he will understand as soon as he finishes reading.
Yes.
Go.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad