[English subtitles are available.]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 30]
Ms.Ling, Brother La Pu has left.
Where has he gone?
No idea.
I told him not to, but he wouldn't listen.
He said he didn't trust you guys.
Let's split up and look for him.
You found the base of the Black Voodoo Cult?
Yes.
You guys go find La Pu first.
Qianjie and I will check this out.
Let's split up.
Let's work in pairs,
so as to have one another's back.
Shaoyang and I will search over there.
I'm pairing up with you?
Are you unhappy about it?
We can take separate actions.
I didn't say I was unhappy.
Hurry up! Or Brother La Pu would die!
La Pu!
Let's search separately.
I worry that the Black Voodoo Cult would catch them.
Alright, be careful!
Meet me at our usual spot then.
La Pu!
I thought we agreed to gather at the city gate.
What's the deal now?
Guess you and Brother La Pu
planned to meet up here
instead of at the gate,
and then run off together.
Run!
This way.
Help!
Let...let go!
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Help!
Let go of me!
Let go!
So much noise.
It seems you don't intend to kill Ling Yushi,
at least not for now.
What is it that you're up to?
I'm worried that
they would overthink, just like you.
So I asked them to
find Ye Yihao first,
to divert their attention.
Ye Yihao.
You really made it out of the Graveyard of Gods.
Aren't you guys the same?
You wanna cause trouble in my territory?
You will get yourself killed.
Did you manipulate voodoo insects to
bring disturbance to the Dark Jade City?
Who else would be
capable of that?
Where else apart from
the Dark Jade City?
The Dark Jade City is merely a start.
How can you manipulate
the Supreme Voodoo Insect?
Hasn't it been lost for long?
You thought it was lost?
That's why you've always despised me.
For millenniums, the Black Voodoo Cult
hasn't made great achievements.
Manipulation of voodoo insects
is only about turning people into puppets.
I know exactly what you're capable of.
There's no way you can
cultivate the Supreme Voodoo Insect.
Tell me.
Who's behind you?
The Heaven Fighting Race.
Your ancestors were slaughtered by them,
and you're conspiring with them!
So long as I can restore
the Voodoo Cult to its glory,
it doesn't matter who I work with.
What are you after?
Qin Lie and Ling Yushi.
One is Gongmu Lie.
The other is the Mother of Land.
They're obstacles to the Divine Race.
Look,
what if they got poisoned
by the Supreme Voodoo Insect?
So what?
The more powerful they're,
the stronger the Insect's
counterforce will be in their body.
Gongmu Lie and the Mother of Land
would become our slaughtering machines.
And then, we can work with the Divine Race
and eliminate those who despised us.
That would rejuvenate the World of Fantasy.
It's about time. It will happen.
La Pu!
Help!
Help! It's La Pu.
Help! Help!
La Pu, are you alright?
Can you see things?
Let go!
Qin Lie!
What happened, Qin Lie?
It worked.
The Mother of Land has been poisoned
by the Supreme Voodoo Insect.
Why don't you bring people to kill her, Duan?
Any delay would leave us in endless troubles.
Who is that?
Big Brother.
Hurry back to the inn.
Chu Li.
Siqi.
Why are you here?
Look, I think we saw this before.
This belongs to La Er.
I found it on the ground.
Perhaps...
They're caught by the Black Voodoo Cult.
What did you find?
This is my keepsake for you.
Please keep it safe.
In the future, you should comb
my hair with it every day.
Even if I'm no longer with you one day,
upon seeing this,
you would still think of me.
It's okay.
It's my comb.
I might have left it here just now.
And oh, Ling Yushi is in trouble.
Let's hurry back to the inn.
What happened?
Just hurry up!
Can you suppress it on your own?
No wonder it's called the Supreme Voodoo Insect.
I can only contain it temporarily.
What about you?
Are you alright?
I had a severe headache all of a sudden.
But it's gone now.
Who plotted all this behind the curtain?
And why are we the target?
Overthinking wouldn't fix the problem.
Go find Uncle Li
to deal with the situation.
If the poison kicks in,
you probably can't control it on your own.
No,
I can't leave you alone at the inn.
Neither of you can stay.
Let's go!
Duan Qianjie knew you were poisoned.
He brought people to capture you.
Wait outside.
Yes.
Did Qin Lie and Ling Yushi come back?
They did,
but they left again,
in haste.
Mr.Chu and Ms.Tang went with them.
Tang Siqi.
You can settle down here.
I've checked. It's safe here.
Where is this?
A place to hide things.
This is full of Terminator Profound Bombs.
If Duan's people found here,
just bombard them with those.
Also,
his fighters are strong.
These might not suffice. I'll get more.
You have more?
Yeah, loads of them.
If I dig out all the bombs across
the five continent,
they could destroy the whole Land of Chaos.
Qin Lie, I'm worried that Shaoyang and Tingyu...
Go!
I'm fine.
Yushi was poisoned by the Voodoo Insect?
Of course.
Otherwise, why'd she leave?
Tang Siqi must have tipped her off.
Everyone poisoned
by the Voodoo Insect
has been sent to prison.
Give my order. The Dark Jade City
is now on full guard.
Yes.
Brother Duan,
go find Qin Lie and Ling Yushi.
Talk to them nicely,
Don't pick a fight with them.
I'll go in to check
if there're any traces left behind.
Sure.
Where are Qin Lie and Ling Yushi?
I don't know.
What's their plan?
I'm here to help.
I don't believe you.
You fell for it again.
What trick are you playing?
Last time, you've seen
that Shadowless Stone, right?
That...
That's a trick invented by Master Mohai.
He's got a childlike temperament.
In the public eye,
he invented things to kill or save people.
Behind closed doors, he just fiddled with
those boring tricks.
The thing under your feet
is used to deal with his wife.
With this,
his wife could never catch him.
His wife?
That's right.
Stay here. I'll get going.
I'll kill you sooner or later.
Harsh words and deeds
can be a demonstration of love.
Just stay here. Bye-bye.
You...
I made some rice soup.
Hope you didn't ruin the kitchen?
Almost.
How's it?
I used to long for touching your face,
wondering how that would feel.
But I never dared to.
I fear that would scare you away from the Ling Borough.
And now I've touched it.
But I didn't feel a thing.
I've got a rough skin.
It wouldn't feel nice anyway.
When the poison in you is cleared,
you could touch it
whenever you want.
You've lent me a lot of money,
so take that as my repayment.
Then I'd suffer a great loss.
As long as you're with me,
I have nothing else to wish for.
Qin Lie,
pick a flower for me.
Did you think of any cure
for the poison in your body?
I smelled the fragrance of flowers on the way,
and just wanted you to pick a flower for me.
That's it.
Then, as soon as Chu Li is back,
I will go.
He's back.
I'm so concerned about you guys.
So I brought a couple of them back first.
And I'll go again later.
Brother Chu,
please take care of Yu Shi for me.
I'll be out for something.
What is it?
Picking flowers.
Picking flowers?
Now?
They're blooming now.
It only happens once in a few years.
They're more precious than the One Heart Leaf.
Qin Lie,
go pick one for me.
You see these spirit flowers and plants every day.
Is that not enough?
Why bother picking flowers?
It smells so nice!
I'll find a bottle to put them in.
No need for that.
You...
What are you doing?
My power only allows me
to tie down the Supreme Voodoo Insect.
With this,
even if I lose my five senses,
I could still feel you and I won't be
worried about not seeing you
or forgetting you.
Yushi, to me you're
always different
from anyone else.
I've never
doubted the feelings between us.
But I always feel
there is a strange force
that is trying to separate us.
The Soul Suppressing Orb?
Both my memory and family background
have been sealed.
Could my feelings have been sealed too?
Don't worry,
and don't be afraid.
I'll always stand by your side,
anytime and anywhere.
What are you thinking?
The same as what you're thinking.
Who is the mole
amongst us?
I'm not a mole, definitely not.
I...
Excuse me.
I was inside and eavesdropped on you
the whole time.
You were saying a lot of honeyed words,
and it was awkward for me to come out.
I trust you.
Why are you suspicious of a mole?
The Three La's lost their ability to prying,
so it was at the inn that
the Voodoo Insect got them.
Uncle Li has cleared out the inn
and forbidden others to check in.
Duan also deployed a heavy guard around the inn.
Someone who could get in
and place the Insect
is by no means an outsider.
So?
You're suspecting Uncle Li?
It can't be Uncle Li.
I know he treats us well,
but you don't know for sure.
I see. It's related to
the Spirits Artifacts.
He wants to own it.
Right?
Brother Chu,
I've got no time to explain.
But trust me,
it's not Uncle Li.
Then who would it be?
Du Shangyang?
I heard he is quite temperamental, and...
No.
He's not capable of it.
Besides him, there's another person.
What do you think of the mastermind
behind all this?
Don't worry.
I've got a solution.
Are you feeling cold?
Not as much as it would be in the Ling Borough.
What,
are you homesick?
When we've got spare time,
let's go back there.
To me, home is just
where you are.
Yu Shi,
do you still remember my promise
to you at the Qi Sha Valley.
I said I owed you a wedding.
That was not out of guilt or pity,
it was visceral.
Regardless of the prophecy of Chongming
or the seal of the Soul Suppressing Orb,
at this moment,
I just want you to know that
I, Qin Lie,
am going to marry you, Ling Yushi.
Yushi,
please say yes.
Yushi?
I'm alright.
I suddenly couldn't
hear your voice.
I'm seeing it again.
- Qin Lie!
- Big Brother!
What happened?
It's there.
What's the matter?
Master of the Gongmu House
asked you to retrieve Volume Two.
Why are you still here, Father?
Do I have to do as he says?
Gongmu Shan is too cautious about things.
While it's a good quality,
overthinking can lead to loss.
He only wants his grandson to show up
when the situation
has become flawless.
But sometimes, miscalculation is inevitable.
Chongming is a case in point.
[Hua Yuxin]
But you promised him, Father.
Did I?
He left as soon as he finished talking.
Did I make any promise to him?
Go down there, now!
Remember, only watch,
but don't take action.
Yes.
Go then!
Master Li!
Evil beings.
Shaoyang!
Siqi!
I know that you could find me.
How would I forget
our promise?
Where are my earrings?
I forgot them.
And oh,
what happened to the kids?
When I came back, the town was guarded heavily.
I asked around
and found out Qin Lie is in trouble.
Are they alright?
Yushi was poisoned by the Supreme Voodoo Insect.
Qin Lie and Chu Li are hiding together with them.
Tingyu's whereabouts are unknown.
So where are they now?
And how are they?
Whilst looking for the kids,
I found La Er's shoe
and this comb.
If I tell you I lost it,
while looking for them,
and it coincidentally dropped at
the place where La Er was caught,
would you believe me?
At the Scarlet Tide Continent,
Qin Lie turned to the Nether Race.
I helped the Profound Heaven Alliance capture them.
In your eyes,
I betrayed Qin Lie.
But in my eyes,
he betrayed the entire human race.
But you all think I'm the one to blame.
Afterwards,
I've been considered
entirely unworthy of trust.
I've only got one question.
Did you turn to the Black Voodoo Cult for help?
Song Ting Yu was right.
At the Graveyard of Gods,
I should have followed Ye Yihao.
Even if I ended up getting killed,
at least that would be clear-cut.
Did Tingyu really say that?
Siqi,
I had always been alone,
fighting for myself.
Until one day,
I thought I met someone who wouldn't leave me
no matter how much I lose,
someone who genuinely knows who I am.
But now it looks like
everything was but a dream.
Siqi,
although I really cherish
the affection between us,
I'm afraid it has eventually
come to an end.
From now on,
we'll part our ways.
Please take good care of yourself.
Shaoyang.
I'm sorry.
The Eye of Frost.
Master.
We were looking for you.
What is it?
Li killed many people in prison.
Big Brother.
He woke up.
Is the headache still there?
Not anymore.
It's gone all of a sudden.
Uncle Li, Duan Qianjie
or Du Shaoyang.
One of them must be in trouble.
I have to find out.
Sister Buli.
The Master of Frost.
You are the legendary Master of Frost.
Killing was the only thing on Li's mind,
as he slaughtered many in the town.
I had no choice but to freeze him.
Someone did it on purpose.
I think you guys
can already guess who she is.
Not really.
Now we need to lure her out,
but with what?
With his life.
Big Brother.
The Eye of Frost.
He deserves death for the massacre.
Do you want to kill him?
Yes.
Then I'll kill you first.
Help me.
Watch out, Qin Lie!
Gongmu Lie!
You're conspiring against me.
How else can we make you show up?
There's another person besides him.
It's Song Tingyu.
In the Imaginary Beast's illusion,
she wanted to kill you many times,
and called you Wuchun.
It also happened when you
entered her mind.
Afterwards, at the Graveyard of Gods,
The Night Fairy also showed
such hatred when she saw me,
which was so close to
what Song Tingyu showed.
The Night Fairy is Song Tingyu, correct?
Wait,
at the Graveyard of Gods,
they were two different people.
That's not true.
They were the same person.
Stop her.
It's half of the divine sense.
You're ganging up on me.
Our guess is right.
Even if you didn't harm the three kids,
you'd be the only one who could
easily steal the Spirit Pillars from me.
Since the meeting at the inn,
you've never showed up.
You were observing us in secret.
There's one thing I couldn't figure out.
Ten millenniums ago,
half of your Spirit Consciousness
left following Gongmu Lie.
Why did it end up as Song Tingyu?
Half of my consciousness followed you,
watching you suffer for this women,
and sealed to unconsciousness by Gongmu Shan.
I was too weak to save you,
so I just stayed by your side.
After ten millenniums, you finally woke up.
I chose the most powerful place
on the Scarlet Tide Continent,
so that I could still protect you.
Half of my consciousness waited for you
at the Graveyard of Gods for ten millenniums,
The other half protected you
for another ten millenniums.
But still,
all you care about is this woman.
How did you manipulate the Supreme Voodoo Insect?
I have my own ways.
The Night Fairy,
expel the poison for Yushi first.
We can sit down and talk.
I'll do that after she dies.