[English subtitles are available.]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 29]
I thought after you grew up,
your temper would be better.
Answer my question.
So what if you know your father is alive or dead?
Since you can't find it,
you won't be able to get to it.
Why?
'Cause you don't have enough power.
Unless,
you have the Crimson Flame.
I have it.
Volume Two of the Scripture of the Nine Hells.
I didn't expect Chongming to
have such an ace in his hand.
You were forced to use the Soul Suppressing Orb
to seal the divine blood of Gongmu Lie.
Then you ordered the four spirit artifacts to guard the Soul Suppressing Orb.
After he was asleep for 10,000 years,
when the Golden Force dropped their guard,
you secretly awakened
Qin Lie of the Human Race.
You arranged all this
for your grandson.
But how come Chongming was able to foresee
what's happening today 10,000 years ago?
I've got it.
They have people from the Ghost Eye Race
that can see the past and the future.
Damn it.
Say something, please say something.
Chongming knows where my son is.
What do you mean?
Chongming once said
in a time of turmoil,
my son could be dead and also alive
'cause the spirit of the God of War won't die.
Aren't those words only comforting?
When I heard of my son's death,
I was also suspicious.
So I secretly went to
the Deserted Spirits Realm to look for the truth.
Chongming said those words to me.
At that time,
I didn't take them seriously.
But today
she said the same words to my grandson
and kept them in Volume Two of the Scripture of the Nine Hells.
It is definitely not a coincidence.
I've got to find Chongming.
Wait.
She died of serious injuries before she sealed her remaining power in Volume Two.
10,000 years have passed.
Her divine sense might have all gone.
Even if there's only a slight chance,
I will seize it.
Big brother, the way ahead is too dangerous.
If he were your son,
would you be afraid of danger?
Thankfully the Night Fairy stopped it.
They can't see Volume Two again.
The Divine Race is about to come back.
Before he builds his temperament,
he should stop dreaming to be awakened.
You go there
and take back Volume Two.
What if something unexpected happens?
Then play it by ear and wait for me to come back.
What if you won't be able to come back?
Then put this
in his mind.
I was holding two grenades in my hands.
Ms.Ye told me
Big Brother is Gongmu Lie,
and Yushi is Wuchun.
Ms.Ye herself
had also lost half of her divine sense.
We didn't say this before
not because we wanted to conceal it
but because we didn't know how to say it.
Now...
As for the Black Voodoo Cult,
I'll have Duan deal with it.
Now our biggest threat
is the Divine Race.
When the Human Race and
the Divine Race were fighting,
the Gongmu Family also joined the war.
Gongmu Hao was even known as the God of War,
but unfortunately he died in that war.
Once the Divine Race is back,
together with Gongmu Lie and the Mother of Earth,
they will definitely give a hand to the Golden Force.
Nothing is clear yet,
and there are too many mysteries.
Why Yushi and I
were asleep for 10,000 years?
Now we have woken up,
but we don't know who we are.
And just now,
who was it that interrupted Volume Two?
Interrupted?
What interrupted Volume Two
was the Spirit Pillars stolen from me.
I checked Yushi's crystal.
I'm sure my Spirit Pillars were stolen.
Someone used the power of
my Spirit Pillars to interrupt Volume Two.
Is it the Night Fairy?
I think so, too.
So the Night Fairy didn't disappear?
She made it out of the Graveyard of Gods?
What about the guys from the Ghost Eye Race?
Ask for their opinions.
I've asked them,
but they didn't know anything.
They are talking about our race,
but don't allow us to get involved.
They're treating us like children, huh?
Obviously!
Then we should escape from here.
In the last three years,
we've been kidnapped three times.
Eight of us died.
All our spirit stones were stolen.
Another 25 died of hunger.
We had 36 of us.
Now only we three have survived.
Shall we still trust her?
But we have a bed now.
I've never slept on such a soft bed.
I want to sleep on this bed forever.
So you choose a bed over me?
She is the Mother of Earth,
so she's our mother.
Isn't it a good thing to have a mother take care of us?
Where was she when we were in trouble?
Or when we were dying
due to the lack of spirit stones?
Now she wants us to call her mom.
It's too late.
One more thing.
Chongming said,
only when Gongmu Lie, Wu Chun
and the four spirit artifacts gather together
can Volume Two be summoned.
What are the four spirit artifacts?
Volume Two was poised to be summoned in my hand.
When Mr. Li appeared,
it unfolded right away.
I knew you would think this way.
Help yourself to check this sword.
I also wish
it were the spirit artifact Gongmu needs.
My Terminator Profound Bombs
could be one of them.
In terms of power,
they can definitely make it to the top four.
Check them.
If these are not enough, I can give you more.
How about
we all show our weapons?
Start from me.
Anyway,
I would like to know
how you think of these two's new identities.
Especially you.
Whether you're Qin Lie or Gongmu Lie,
whether you like it or not,
I'll call you Big Brother.
So will I.
No, I was wrong.
I should call you brother-in-law.
You should be very clear
about my attitude towards Gongmu Lie.
Brother Duan?
I don't care about who he is.
No matter what,
Shaoyang and I consider him as Qin Lie.
Thanks to you all.
As for the Black Voodoo Cult,
could you ask your men to get rid of them?
When I'm in the mood.
Come here, time for a meal.
What's wrong? You don't like it?
Are you kidding us?
We don't eat food.
What do you eat?
We eat spirit stones.
- Spirit stones?
Why do you think we charge
so many spirit stones
for each question we answer?
No wonder
you've earned so many
yet you don't have a proper shelter.
How many spirit stones do you need to eat?
1,000 for breakfast, 3,000 for lunch
and 5,000 for dinner
each person.
Each...
9,000 per person per day.
27,000 per day for you three!
You'll never have enough
no matter how hard you work.
Some people even bully us,
and don't pay after they get the answers.
Others believe we're rich,
and kidnap us.
We're the last three of the Ghost Eye Race.
'Cause the others have all died of hunger.
How many spirit stones do you have?
Those can barely fill my stomach.
I'll fill your stomach.
I have no other merit
but being super rich.
It won't be a problem
to feed them for a few years.
Brother Chu,
see for yourself.
All gone?
Just a mouthful.
Can you really feed us?
Of...course, I told you just now.
I have no other merit
but being...
Super rich.
It seems we need to work for Uncle Li
to be able to feed them.
Lianrou.
Lian...Lianrou.
What brings you here?
Lianrou.
So it's true.
You don't like me anymore.
I...
Why would you say that?
Did you forget I'm from the Illusory Demon Sect
and can see who is in your mind?
You have someone else on your mind.
I sensed that long ago.
I didn't say it, 'cause I wanted to see
how long you were going to lie to me.
But I couldn't bear it anymore.
I...
Who is Lianrou?
She...
Tell me.
Did you forget the Love Eater we met?
It ate my love for you.
Then I met another girl.
I wouldn't say I don't like you anymore.
But you still have her on your mind.
Not me.
We shouldn't betray our commitment.
That's very bad.
But if I have both of you on my mind,
it's even worse.
But don't worry,
I'll forget her soon.
Tomorrow, I'll forget her tomorrow.
I...I'll let you rest.
This...
This seems to be my room.
So annoying.
Come in.
You're still awake.
I can't fall asleep.
You're also awake.
Are you alright?
Huh...
Are you afraid that I can't accept
Qin Lie is Gongmu Lie
and will force him and Lin Yushi apart?
Let go of him.
You didn't fancy any guy
on the Scarlet Tide Continent.
But here is different.
There's always someone that deserves you.
Such as...
Such as,
Chuli, the guy that bombs everyone he sees.
Actually I think
he is a good match for you.
He is also playful,
much better than Du Shaoyang.
This Du Shaoyang
always wears a sullen look
as if someone owes him a huge debt.
Why did you get me involved?
You used to be so arrogant
and always put on airs.
Ever since you got together with Du,
you don't even dare to talk loudly anymore.
Where is your old self?
Bittersweet, this is what love should be.
Is Du Shaoyang alright?
Knowing his good friend
becomes Gongmu Lie,
he must be suffering.
Of course.
I tried to console him,
but he wouldn't talk to me.
He just wanted to go somewhere alone.
I wanted to stop him
but I didn't want to upset him.
Uncle Li,
Duan Qianjie knows very well
the flaws of the Eye of Frost.
From the very beginning,
you sent him to look out for us secretly,
didn't you?
If he went across the line before,
please forgive him.
He is not a bad person.
He has a poker face,
but he did help us a lot.
Thank you for taking care of us.
Uncle Li, to you.
Uncle Li,
you and him are...
He and I are like brothers.
Why did you beat him?
You deserve it. Go beat him.
Shame on you.
Beat them.
They deserve it. They deserve it.
Go away.
Stop.
You two jinxes.
Don't show up in my face.
I'll beat you every time I see you.
Let's go.
Where are your parents?
I don't remember.
Maybe my bad luck killed them. You?
Same here. I don't remember clearly.
They probably died for the same reason.
My surname is Li, what's yours?
Duan.
I'll call you Brother Duan.
From today, I'm your big brother.
You follow me. I'll look after you.
I'm your big brother.
You follow me. I look after you.
You don't know,
we never knew if we could get our next meal or not.
We were always hungry.
We even had no place to live.
We looked everywhere for shelters.
Summers were bearable,
but winters were the most difficult.
Little brother.
Let's start a fire, ok?
I'm tired, big brother.
You do it.
I'm also tired.
You're the little brother, you do it.
Big brother, come close to the fire.
No. It's better here.
It's in the corner, no wind.
You said you were cold, didn't you?
But now I'm not cold.
Come closer and share the fire.
I need to sit here to think about things.
A lot of things.
Go to sleep if you're tired.
That was a long time ago.
Considering your difficult past,
your friendship now is even more precious.
Brother Duan
is the biggest concern on my mind.
What adventures did you have
that let you have so many skills?
Not necessarily adventures.
But I did understand swordsmanship
better than others.
As for Brother Duan,
his skills developed from a fight after another.
He is talented in martial arts.
With his help,
in my fight at Mount Heavenly Sword,
I unexpectedly inserted the sixth sword in it,
and became a Sword Holder.
Who is stronger, you and him?
I really don't know.
We've never had a real fight.
Even if one were stronger, the gap would be minimal.
But how come you become a sword holder,
but not him?
He made me.
In fact,
in our hearts,
we treat the other as family.
Though he is defiant,
to him,
I'm his only family.
Big brother, drink some water.
Big brother.
Big brother, you have a fever.
Is everything clear?
Drop the act.
You pretended to chat, but you've been plotting.
What's your purpose of poking around our story?
There is one thing
I really don't know how to say.
'Cause it's too weird.
Volume Two has shown up.
You only know about the four spirit artifacts,
but you don't know
they are not common artifacts.
You said we all live in your mind.
Are you nuts?
Calm down.
You trust him?
I believe he won't deceive me.
Duan Qianjie,
I didn't deceive Uncle Li.
If you're not human,
but spirit artifacts...
- You're not human...
- Duan Qianjie.
Big brother,
do you really believe we are spirit artifacts?
Wait.
We're spirit artifacts?
Qianjie, do you remember your parents' faces?
The truth is in Volume Two.
Someone interrupted it
'Cause they didn't want us to know too much.
Volume Two was interrupted by the Spirit Pillars.
It is probably the Night Fairy who did it.
But what's her purpose?
If the person behind this is your old flame,
you'd better think about how to lure her out.
Are you upset?
None of your business.
Your rival is so much better than you.
It must be hard for you, right?
Your rival in love is also much better than you.
How do you feel about that?
I surely don't like that.
But you seem to have forgotten
Xie Jingxuan was poisoned by a voodoo insect.
You have a solution?
If you can't find the master of the insect,
even if you wipe out the Black Voodoo Cult,
it will be useless.
Unless,
you become the new master of the Black Voodoo Cult.
You're asking me to hide in the dark
and become the new master of those vicious insects?
Song Tingyu, what do you want me to do for you now?
Do you know the Voodoo Master?
It's Jiang Yan. He died in the war with the Divine Race.
His body is still in the Graveyard of Gods.
I met him before.
Jiang Yan, the Voodoo Master,
was an ancestor of the Black Voodoo Cult.
The Voodoo Race was the predecessor
of the Black Voodoo Cult.
The race was good at using voodoo insects.
Their skills were diverse and remarkable.
In prehistoric times,
every 100 years, there would a dark period
that lasted for a year.
The whole world was in darkness.
People couldn't survive.
The Master would let out voodoo insects
to lighten up the sky.
After he died in war,
manipulating voodoo insects became a lost art.
In order to survive,
they have become today's Black Voodoo Cult,
vicious and looked down upon by others.
Now all the other voodoo skills have been lost.
Voodoo insects have become a tool to kill.
Though the Voodoo Master died,
his body is in the Graveyard of Gods,
and it still has the smell of voodoo insects.
Even if you only get a little bit of it,
you shall be able to dominate the Land of Chaos,
and be on a par with Qin Lie.
To remove the voodoo insect from Xie
will be a piece of cake.
This is the entry to the Graveyard of Gods.
It's up to you to make a choice.
Is that
the Voodoo Master?
You stole the Spirit Pillars,
and interrupted Volume Two.
I'm not keen to read
their ridiculous romance stories.
I'm Jiang Yan, the Voodoo Master.
I used to be upright and
protect the people of the Spirit Realm.
However, in the war with the Divine Race,
I was set up by the Golden Force
who wanted to exterminate my race.
Our devotion and commitment
only brought us betrayal and slaughter.
If you want to use my power,
you have to swear
that one day
you will take our Voodoo Race
back to the Land of Gold.
I, Du Shaoyang,
I want to beat him.
I don't want to stay weaker than him all my life.
If for my whole life
I'm just useless,
how can I say I love her.
I'd rather cut her out of my life,
let go of her
and myself.
The way ahead is long.
My destination is unknown.
Facing the moon,
I, Du Shaoyang, hereby swear
I will lead the Voodoo Race to regain glory and power.
Congratulations! You've got a new lease of life.
You are the Night Fairy?
It's not hard to steal the Spirit Pillars.
But only the Night Fairy
can use it with ease.
You're not stupid.
Where is Ye Yihao?
Is he dead?
No,
I kept him alive.
He'll be useful one day.
The Supreme Voodoo Insect.
He inherited it from the Voodoo Master.
From today, he'll replace you
and become the new master of the Black Voodoo Cult.
My Master.
Yushi, say something.
Qianqian.
Are you really leaving us?
I'm going back to the Illusory Demon Sect.
Why not go back later?
After we remove the voodoo insect from Siqi,
I'll take you there.
I'm not happy here.
Qianqian, there must be a misunderstanding.
Shut up.
If you don't love me,
don't play with my feelings
and waste my time.
Can I visit you in the future?
You're...always welcome.
Don't worry.
It's all my fault.
I'll be responsible for it.
I'll help you to take her back.
He said he would take me back.
I should have killed him just now.
You didn't eat anything. Nor did you take any food.
It'll take a few days to go back from here.
I'm afraid you'll get hungry.
You're a lady. Be gentle.
Since you fancy gentle ladies,
go back to your Lianrou.
Sorry, I was wrong.
I put my foot in my mouth.
Do you want it or not?
Get lost.
Shall we use teleport or fly?
I don't have a flying vehicle.
Can I use yours?
Get out of my face.
Can you say something else?
Fuck off.
Why are you following me?
Since you don't like me,
why do you come here to see me off?
I don't know.
I'm just worried about you.
I feel bad.
Is it true that you don't know why
but you just want to follow me?
Yes, you know what I'm thinking.
Do you want to say
your symptoms are the same as mine
when I first met you?
You just don't know why.
Is that because
I have you in my heart?
How can that be?
You're such a good actor.
I was almost deceived
by your innocent face again.
You're a playboy.
You already have a girl.
Now you want to hoax another one.
We girls from the Illusory Demon Sect
hate players the most.
We'll kill every last one of them.
Come with me if you have guts.
I promised Yushi
that I would take you back.
Go away.
I'll kill you if you don't go.
Hongyan.
Boss.
What's wrong?
The Supreme Voodoo Insect.
It's recorded that in the prehistoric times
Jiang Yan, the Voodoo Master, was one of the greatest lords.
Under his leadership, the Voodoo Race
were respected and remarkable.
He kept the Supreme Voodoo Insect himself.
It was superb.
It could kill and also save people.
But after he died in the war with the Divine Race,
the Voodoo Race began to decay.
The Supreme Voodoo Insect has been lost.
It'll not only make people lose their five senses
but also control their consciousness.
It is like her,
but more difficult to deal with.
Once scratched by people poisoned by a voodoo insect,
you will be infected.
How many people have been poisoned?
More than 1,000.
The number is increasing.
10,000 years have passed
since prehistoric times.
Those insects must have died of
either hunger or coldness.
Besides,
the Voodoo Master has long been dead.
His body is in the Graveyard of Gods.
We all saw him.
Is it because Ye Yihao is still alive?
I have the same concern.
Where are the three Ghost Eye people?
No way.
How come I've lost all my power?
We've really lost our power.
Why is this the case?
The Supreme Voodoo Insect.
Will I be blind and deaf?
Their target should be us.
They attacked them
'cause they want to stop us
from getting any clues.
I ordered my men last night
to guard them from outside.
I didn't expect
the they would be able to sneak in.
Why will the Black Voodoo Cult target us?
Because of our feud in the Graveyard of Gods?
I don't know.
Something is wrong here.
My men are trying to find out
whether the mutation only occurred
in the Dark Jade City.
We can't rule out they may have also occurred
in other continents and cities.
If they only occurred in the Dark Jade City,
once the news got out,
all sects will send people
to wipe out the Black Voodoo Cult.
It will be a huge trouble then.
By then,
the Dark Jade City may really turn into a Land of Chaos.
Yushi, Big Brother has left.
What did you say?