Amazing!
Seo Jin, you look beautiful.
You truly look like a newlywed!
How much did that dress cost?
The pink looks perfect on you.
Why did she blow
so much money on a dress?
Especially since who knows
how long this marriage will last?
Are you happy?
Extremely.
I hope it last forever.
Thank you for coming, Yoon Hee.
We have
such an unusual relationship.
We worked together,
we're both Hera Club members,
you were classmates
with my wife, whom I love,
and Ro Na was friends with my kids.
Why are you bringing up Ro Na
on a day like this?
My mistake. I apologize.
I'm sure you're still distraught
over losing your precious child.
It's fine.
Congratulations.
(Gangnam Police Station)
Did you really pay him
to give a fake confession?
Are the accusations true?
Why did you do it?
Tell us!
Give us a statement!
Thank you, members of Hera Club,
for coming to bless us
on our marriage.
We will love, respect,
and cherish each other.
Ms. Cheon,
you should say something too.
Why do you look like that?
You look like you're
being dragged into slave labor.
I know. You're as pale as a ghost.
Are you feeling sick?
- Well...
- She was too nervous last night...
to sleep a wink.
She's too sensitive.
Are you okay?
Hang in there, it'll be over soon.
We should make
a toast together though.
Assemblyman Lee.
Would you do the honors?
- You're so cool.
- Shall I?
Actually, every couple for whom
I gave a toast...
ended up going to divorce court...
and became enemies.
Amazingly,
their marriages came to
a crashing halt within a year.
However,
these two will be different.
Let's drink to them.
To a beautiful...
It's my mom.
- Seriously.
- Gosh.
Ms. Mi Ja,
your man Kyu Jin is working.
What? Dr. Ha...
is Bae Ro Na's real killer?
What was that?
The real killer? Who?
He just said Dr. Ha killed Ro Na.
Dr. Ha is a murderer?
That gentle Dr. Ha that we know?
Hey! Turn on the TV.
Hurry!
What's going on?
A new suspect was arrested...
for the murder of Bae Ro Na.
This suspect was disclosed to be...
the victim's stepfather,
and has caused...
an outrage.
Ha, who is the Korean representative
of a famous...
foreign pharmaceutical company,
bribed someone to confess
to the murder...
- to cover up his crime.
- No.
- No!
- Gangnam Police state...
- Why are you so shocked?
- That he named the real killer.
- He has...
- They arrested Ha...
- nothing to do with you anymore.
- As he tried to flee the country.
The motive has yet to be determined.
You...
How do you like my wedding gift?
I wanted to surprise you.
He has not admitted the crime yet,
and has exercised his right
to remain silent.
(Residents Garage)
Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol!
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Take me to the police station. Now.
Where's Mom? Where is she?
She's at her wedding.
It should be over soon.
Wedding? With whom?
Whom else? Seok Kyung's dad.
They really got married?
After kicking me out to the US?
You didn't know?
I shouldn't have said anything.
Eun Byeol. Don't cry.
You have me.
I won't abandon you.
It's Seok Hoon.
Don't let him in.
I don't want to see him.
Don't let him in here again.
Seok Hoon's here.
Get out.
I have nothing to say to you.
What are you doing? Did something
happen between you two?
You got your memory back,
didn't you?
You remember, don't you?
You jerk!
Was it all a lie?
When you asked me out...
and when you said you liked me?
What were you trying to get
out of me that you lied to me?
I want to hear the truth.
What did you do to Ro Na?
Tell me.
Tell me right now!
I don't know. I didn't do anything.
Stop talking about Ro Na!
I'm sick of it!
Ms. Jin. Kick him out! Now!
Get out.
She can't get upset.
Excuse me! Come help!
Eun Byeol. I'll uncover the truth.
I'll find out why Ro Na died!
Eun Byeol!
Why did Ro Na die?
- Eun Byeol.
- Ms. Jin.
What do I do?
I remember everything.
What I did...
during the festival.
How could he kill his stepdaughter?
And then he asks for a divorce
and moves out?
That rotten jerk.
That scum of the earth.
Are you okay, Yoon Hee?
I knew Yoon Chul was a jerk.
Why did he have to
get involved with that jerk?
(Gangnam Police Station)
Yoon Hee. Divorce him right now.
I'll get you
100 million dollars in alimony.
I still can't believe it.
How could he do that
when he has Eun Byeol?
He probably did it for her.
They were rivals, you know that.
Was it to get Eun Byeol
the grand prize?
Is that why he did that to her?
That happened to Ro Na
during the Cheong A Art Festival.
That's what makes him frightening.
But seriously, poor Eun Byeol.
Her dad's a murderer
and her mom's a scammer.
Chairman Joo.
Did you really not know?
Not at all.
I'm in shock as well.
(Gangnam Police Station)
Is it true
that Ha Yoon Chul made you...
give a false confession?
Yes.
In exchange for
500,000 dollars in cash...
and his promise to provide
treatments to my sick child.
You didn't kill her, did you?
Who hired you?
Was it Ha Yoon Chul?
No. No one hired me.
I... I really did kill her.
You refuse to talk.
It was all...
because he made me do it.
He promised me...
money for my family to live on
for the rest of their lives.
I couldn't refuse...
I'm sorry.
Ha Yoon Chul. Do you admit
to murdering Bae Ro Na?
I do.
I killed...
Bae Ro Na.
I can't give you that much time...
since reporters are outside.
I know.
Thank you, chief.
Yoon Chul.
What... What happened to you?
Why did you come here?
People will get suspicious.
Go home.
I think Dan Tae threatened Mr. Park.
I thought he'd bury it
if I married him.
I really didn't know he'd do this.
I was expecting it.
Did Eun Byeol leave?
She came home.
Ms. Jin called and said
she was with her.
Send her to the US.
It's dangerous for her to be here.
Worry about yourself.
Just deny it.
I'll persuade Mr. Park somehow.
I admitted it already.
Are you mad?
Do you plan to live as a murderer?
It's true...
that I tried to kill her.
I decided to harm her...
and visited her in the hospital.
Even though I couldn't
bring myself to do it,
I've been tormented by guilt.
I'm relieved that
things turned out this way.
This is not what I wanted...
when I married Dan Tae.
Don't worry about me.
Pull yourself together.
Dan Tae, that jerk,
wouldn't stop here.
He'll drag Eun Byeol
into this any moment.
I'm going to kill that jerk.
I'll take the fall.
You protect Eun Byeol.
Can you do that?
(Gangnam Police Station)
How do you feel?
Your ex-husband
has turned into a criminal.
I've been curious.
You were having feelings
for Yoon Chul again.
So what made you
still marry Dan Tae?
Who says I was having
feelings for him?
That's not true.
I guess I don't have to get blood
on my hands anymore.
Dan Tae is going to destroy...
your family himself.
What?
Do you think
your daughter can be safe...
if Yoon Chul goes to prison?
It'll only tear you apart.
The truth doesn't change.
What are you talking about?
I have to go and
meet with the detective now.
He is going to hold a briefing
about who really killed Ro Na.
I wonder how many more times
the culprit will change.
No way.
Does she know?
You're back.
I heard that Dr. Ha
is at the police station.
How's Eun Byeol?
She's not coming out of her room.
She's in shock after hearing
about your wedding.
Why did you tell her?
She already had a lot to deal with.
It seems like her memories
have come back.
What did you just say?
She remembers
what happened that day.
The day of Cheong A Art Festival.
She came back home early...
wearing a dress covered in blood.
How do you know that?
There are no secrets
between me and Eun Byeol.
You didn't know?
She feels closer to me than to you.
But don't worry.
I'm on Eyn Byeol's side.
I'll pretend I didn't see anything.
Eun Byeol.
About my wedding...
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you
beforehand. I...
I don't want to hear it.
I need to study. I need to get into
Seoul National University.
That's what you want, right?
Look at me when I talk to you!
Why aren't you asking about Dad?
Don't you want to know?
He killed Ro Na, right?
He should pay for what he did.
What?
Say that again.
I saw everything on the news.
He confessed.
Isn't that what
you and Dad wanted all along?
That's why you erased
all my memories.
Have your memories...
really come back?
Did you think you could
get rid of my memories?
You should have done it
more properly.
You should have erased
everything completely!
Now that Dad is
taking the fall for me,
am I supposed to feel grateful?
Is that all you have to say?
After everything your dad
and I have done for you?
Did I ask you to do that?
I never wanted that!
It was what you wanted,
so why do you hit me?
I'm a lot stronger...
than you think.
Why did you even give me
all these medications?
I would have forgotten everything
if you had just told me to.
- Eun Byeol!
- What?
Didn't you know I was a monster?
The day you abandoned Grandpa
and ran away,
I'm the one who left him
dying alone in the rain.
I'm the one who memorized
English words at his funeral.
So how could I possibly stay sane?
You're the one who did this to me!
Still, I didn't tell anyone.
I hated you for making Grandpa die.
But you're still my mom.
I should protect you.
That's why I've kept my mouth shut.
So how could you go
and marry Seok Hoon's dad?
You didn't know
I have feelings for Seok Hoon?
What are you talking about?
You have feelings for Seok Hoon?
Is there anything you know about me?
Other than my grades
and penalty points,
you know absolutely
nothing about me.
Get out. Get out right now!
Get out!
Eun Byeol! Stop!
Stop! What are you doing?
- Eun Byeol, no! Stop!
- I'm going to kill myself.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- Please don't do this, Eun Byeol.
- Mom.
Honestly, I'm scared.
What if I get arrested?
Is my life over?
No. We'll find a way.
Do you think I can't protect you?
I won't let anything happen
to you and Dad.
Trust me.
I didn't mean to kill her.
I swear.
I remember what happened clearly.
I got upset and swung the trophy.
But then Ro Na fell down the stairs.
That's when I heard a phone ring...
and came to my senses.
You heard a phone ring?
I still hear it in my ear.
It's driving me crazy.
Mi fa sol fa mi mi
Mi re ti re mi
Do you mean...
there was someone else there?
I don't know.
I panicked and ran away.
If Ro Na had been transported
to the hospital immediately,
she wouldn't have died.
I only hurt her shoulder.
I still can't believe that she died.
Her shoulder? Are you sure
it was her shoulder, not her head?
It was definitely her shoulder.
Ro Na died after getting hit
in the head with the trophy.
No. I never hit her in the head.
- I'm sure of it.
- Do you remember it clearly?
I remember it so clearly
that it horrifies me!
Why can't you trust me?
Can you tell me...
everything in detail?
Everything that happened that day,
from beginning to end.
Take your time.
Don't leave anything out.
Na Ae Gyo and Jung Doo Man...
aren't just business partners.
There's more to it.
What key is this?
Have you been waiting long?
What took you so long?
The traffic was terrible.
I heard Oh Yoon Hee
put her property up for sale.
I'm going to start the bid tomorrow.
I have a question for you.
When did you quit smoking?
Did I not tell you?
I quit because I couldn't stop
coughing.
Is that right?
Good for you.
Maybe it's because I haven't
seen you in a while.
You feel...
a little different.
The way you hold your glass.
You always held your glass
with your left hand,
but you're holding it
with your right.
You got angry at me when I asked you
to change yourself...
to be right-handed just so that you
can be like Shim Su Ryeon.
Having had to pretend
I'm Shim Su Ryeon my whole life,
I guess I got used to using
my right hand.
Right.
I see.
Does it make you feel better
if you check?
Sorry. I've just been on edge.
You know how paranoid I get.
I check and double-check.
Your butterfly looks
especially attractive today.
Should I sleep here tonight?
Don't get on Seo Jin's nerves
from the first night.
If you want Cheong A Group
in your hands,
you need to have some self-control.
Spending a night out
on the first night of our marriage?
Don't you think that's too mean?
Isn't the wedding
just a formality?
What do you mean?
I'm ready to live with you
happily ever after.
Don't touch me.
Thanks to your surprise,
Eun Byeol couldn't leave for the US.
I'm going to stay at my home
with Eun Byeol for a while.
That's what I've come to tell you.
"My home"?
That's heartbreaking.
We've signed the papers.
We're legally married.
This is your home.
Where do you think you're going?
I'll give you...
Cheong A Constructions
as you wanted.
I can just think of it like I got
into a marriage fraud.
In return, I want
Eun Byeol's necklace back.
I think you're getting it all wrong.
I'm the upper hand here.
You're not in the place to be
barking like a crazy dog.
You lunatic. Give me the necklace!
This is our marriage manual.
Read it and follow along well.
(Marriage Manual)
I'm going to leave
all the house duties to you.
Of course, I've fired
all the housemaids already.
- What?
- To be a good stepmother...
to Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung,
I figured you'd be better off
without the helpers.
Of course, you can't meet
Eun Byeol without my permission.
Have you gone insane?
Eun Byeol is my daughter.
I'm the only one who can
take care of her right now!
I don't care about any of that!
Why should I be worried
about Ha Yoon Chul's kid?
Don't you remember what happened
to Su Ryeon?
I'm sorry. I guess...
I guess I got a little upset.
See? You should've just listened.
I've given it some thought,
and the Cheong A Medical Center
looks like a solid deal.
Why don't you hand that over too?
Are you a gangster or something?
You'll never have the Medical Center
or the Foundation!
Don't get so mad.
You're scaring me, lady.
What are you?
Was your goal to take
my money from the start?
Maybe you underestimated me,
but I'm Cheon Seo Jin,
Cheong A Group's eldest daughter.
I won't give anything else
other than Cheong A Constructions.
Be thankful and stop dreaming.
Where are your manners?
This is a warning, ma'am.
Let's get a divorce.
I can't live a single day
with a man like you.
Get the papers ready right now.
You idiot, how many times
need I tell you...
that I get to start and end
the relationship?
You're the idiot here!
I'm Cheon Seo Jin.
You think I'll go down by myself?
I'm going to let the world know
that you killed Shim Su Ryeon.
You piece of garbage
and a murderer!
You need a good lesson, ma'am.
Let me go!
You garbage! Let me go!
Let go!
Let go of me!
What?
Are you surprised?
You should've watched
what you were saying.
Shim Su Ryeon also died
because she didn't know her place...
and acted like a lunatic.
But you're going to be
another type of fun than her.
(Golden Real Estate)
(New development-focused)
I'm Hwang Geum Bong.
(Become rich
with Golden Real Estate.)
(Golden Real Estate)
Lot 27 in Cheonsoo District.
I'd like to buy that.
There are a lot of people
eyeing that property.
There are dozens who have paid
provisional deposits.
Why don't I show you something else?
I don't need anything else.
It has to be lot 27.
This is where I'm coming from.
You know my chairman, don't you?
Chairman Joo Dan Tae.
You know that 70 percent
of the properties are ours.
There's a way
where we can both win.
What do you think?
Are you interested in joining me?
(Golden Real Estate)
Go and check what's going on.
Yes, sir.
(Golden Real Estate)
Let me make myself clear.
I don't plan on betraying
Joo Dan Tae,
so stop stalking me.
If I see you one more time,
I'm taking you to Joo Dan Tae.
There's no way you can do that.
If you were going to do that,
you would've exposed me
to Joo Dan Tae already.
Is that what you want?
Should I go and do that?
Be honest with me.
You don't trust Joo Dan Tae
right now either.
He abused your children...
and killed his wife.
Do you want to end up dead
like Shim Su Ryeon?
Mind your own business!
Why do you care if I die or not?
That's none of your business.
Why are you trying to buy
lot 27 of Cheonsoo District?
Whatever the reason is, use me.
There's no way you can
buy that land without me.
I own the land.
I don't plan on teaming up
with someone like you.
I'm putting my life
on the line for money.
I'll get rid of anyone
who gets in the way.
(Golden Real Estate)
I put my life on the line for this.
I'm going to take revenge
for my poor baby, Seol A's death.
And I'll destroy everyone
who gets in my way.
Na Ae Gyo is auctioning
for lot 27 with the highest bid.
An auction?
Yes.
Why an auction?
Let go!
- Come here.
- Let go!
- Come here!
Let go of me!
Let me go!
Let go!
Stop!
This is all you get
in this penthouse.
This is the release
for Cheong A Group's shares.
You won't be stepping out of here
until you sign this. Got it?
Say hello.
Joo Dan Tae! Open the door!
Joo Dan Tae!
How dare you betray me...
and side with that Ha Yoon Chul?
I'll make sure to get revenge...
on everything you've done.
You better get excited.
Open the door, Joo Dan Tae!
Joo Dan Tae!
Shim Su Ryeon,
is this your revenge on me?
Handing me a trashy man
like Joo Dan Tae over?
(Seoul Gangnam Police Station)
(Silence)
I won't take long.
We're married on paper,
so it only makes sense
that I visit once at least.
Did you hate Ro Na that much?
So much that you wanted to kill her?
I have nothing to say.
It was all for Eun Byeol.
There's nothing bad in trying
to protect your own child.
You would've done the same
if you were me.
Yes, I was like that.
I did everything...
if it was for Ro Na.
But later, I learned...
that if you do something bad,
you reap the consequences.
No matter how much you try
to run away, it'll haunt you.
Don't you ever think...
that what you've done for Eun Byeol
was the best you could've done.
What about my Eun Byeol?
She did nothing wrong.
This is the divorce paper.
I'm submitting it today.
It seems...
like we're really over.
Even for a short period of time,
I'd hoped that Ro Na, you, and I
would live a happy life.
I was stupid.
My Ro Na...
was so full of love,
just like you.
What?
I'm going to do my absolute best...
to make sure that you suffer
the worst consequences.
I'll make you regret so much
that your heart will tear apart.
You deserve that.
You killed your own child.
What are you saying?
I'm sorry for not having told you
any earlier.
But...
what a relief.
Thank goodness Ro Na didn't know
any of this before she left.
Had she known that
her birth father killed her,
imagine how heartbroken
she would've been.
Oh Yoon Hee!
What are you saying?
Let me make my final request.
Apologize...
to Ro Na sincerely for just once.
I feel so bad for my daughter,
who never even got...
to be treated like your daughter.
You can do that much, can't you?
Yoon Hee. Tell me right now.
You're lying, right?
You're lying to make me suffer!
Please.
Don't go, Yoon Hee!
What are you saying?
What do you mean?
Yoon Hee! That's not true, is it?
Yoon Hee, tell me right now!
Tell me the truth!
Yoon Hee! Don't go!
Yoon Hee, please!
Don't go!
What are you saying?
What do you mean?
(Silence)
Get the smartest lawyers
at the firm.
Get the press ready.
Be on standby.
You really never know people.
How could Dr. Ha do that?
He killed Yoon Hee's daughter...
and tried to divorce her
because he felt guilty?
I'm getting goosebumps.
There's no way that nerd killed her.
He's a complete chicken.
What made you change your mind?
You were the one who was
most angered by the news.
That's because my Yoon Hee
was there too.
Anyway, he doesn't have the guts
to kill someone.
I'm putting together a team
of lawyers for Yoon Chul...
with the best lawyers
at my father's firm.
Are you insane?
If people hear that
you've helped a murderer,
you'll lose the election for sure!
Did you not see yesterday...
how Seo Jin raced out of the hall
as soon as she heard the news?
What does that mean?
She can give up all of her money
for Ha Yoon Chul.
And my firm needs to take
advantage of that.
You think Ms. Cheon was shot
in her head or something?
Why would she give her everything
for her ex-husband?
I just get a feeling...
that this one case will make me...
a filthy rich man. I just know it.
Such nonsense.
Just drink this.
Our home is the only home
without maids in Hera Palace.
That's why I'm planning
all of this to get money.
Once Cheonsoo District's prices
skyrocket,
we'll move to the penthouse
on the 130th floor.
The penthouse? Really?
If we get about 5 to 6 units,
The rent there alone
would be almost 300,000 dollars.
Kyu Jin.
Cheers.
That's why we need to
put our all into this.
I need money.
The price keeps going up every day,
but I don't have the money.
Why are you so lovable?
Is this a trend?
So this is the furniture company
that Shim Su Ryeon ran?
The famous lot 27
in Cheonsoo District.
It's quite large.
I've wanted to see it myself.
I kind of want it.
I want to run it.
It does well in sales.
There's a reason
everyone wants this lot.
Did something good happen?
Why did you bring me here?
It's to apologize
for being irritable yesterday.
Everything is going perfectly
according to my plan.
Cheong A Constructions is
already mine.
And I should get
Cheong A Medical Center easily too.
The purchase of this lot
going smoothly, right?
I plan to raise the price
a little now.
How?
I played a little game
so that people will smell money...
and gather like bees to honey.
The value of land isn't determined.
It's made.
As we've always done.
You never disappoint, Ae Gyo.
Congrats, babe.
Joo Dan Tae Village,
your lifelong dream,
is finally coming to fruition.
And you won't have to live
in hiding anymore.
You can stand beside me publicly.
I have something for you.
Here.
What is it?
A gift?
Oh my gosh. What is this?
It's Seo Jin's lifeline.
You hold onto it
until the stock matter is finished.
She's searching for it
like a madwoman.
Is this that necklace? The evidence?
Does Cheon Seo Jin know?
What?
That her daughter didn't kill her.
What do you mean?
Don't be so shocked.
You can't fool me.
Cheon Seo Jin is more naive
than I gave her credit for.
Right when you were going after
Cheong A Group,
Cheon Seo Jin's daughter
killed a person.
Was that really a coincidence?
Who gained the most from that?
You did.
Did you kill her?
Ae Gyo!
(Mr. Ma Doo Ki)
Excuse me.
How did it go?
I'm sorry.
The judges were too adamant.
I couldn't influence them.
Skip to the conclusion.
Who wins the grand prize?
The grand prize is going to
Bae Ro Na.
Bae Ro Na?
Why her of all people?
Hey, you. Doo Ki.
Can't you do anything right?
Seok Kyung is getting the gold...
She can get that easily
without your help.
Our deal ends here. Got that?
She's just as annoying as her mom.
Bae Ro Na, you annoying witch.
(Na Ae Gyo)
Ae Gyo?
Seriously.
Eun Byeol?
What is that?
(The 28th Cheong A Arts Festival)
Mr. Joo.
Please call my mom.
I'm...
hurt...
Why...
you?
Why must a loser like you
win the grand prize?
If not for you,
the free pass to Seoul University
would be Seok Kyung's.
What are you saying?
Can't you give in a little
for Seok Kyung?
I really love my daughter...
a lot.
Don't kill me.
It always annoyed me
whenever I saw you.
But...
since you gave it up for her...
Eun Byeol.
Who knew you'd
actually help me like this?
If I play my cards right,
I can get rid of
two annoying witches at once.
I really am...
a lucky guy.
(Cheong A Arts High School)
I got the most similar one
from the car.
Good.
(File cannot be restored
after deletion.)
(CCTV recording deleted.)
Where were you all this time?
The bathroom was packed.
We'll bring our director,
Ms. Cheon Seo Jin,
to the stage to announce the winner.
There's a dead body outside!
Someone is dead!
Ro Na!
- Ro Na!
- Jenny!
There's a person here!
Stop running.
Stop running, kids!
I killed her?
I killed Ro Na?
What gave you that misconception?
Is it really a misconception?
Does anyone know Joo Dan Tae
better than I do?
You can't fool me.
Regardless,
Ro Na was very useful.
Just as much as Seol A.
Thanks to those tragic girls dying
right at the most opportune times,
I was able to swallow up...
Su Ryeon's and Seo Jin's fortunes
very easily.
Hear that,
Yoon Hee?
Joo Dan Tae, it was you?
You killed Ro Na?
Who was it?
What did all of you do
to that young girl?
Welcome to your nightmare.
Now, do you understand
what our dad's like?
That's why I warned you
not to marry that louse.
You should be careful.
You may not get out of here alive.
Like our mom.
I still hear it in my ear.
It's driving me crazy.
Mi fa sol fa mi mi
Mi re ti re mi
(Na Ae Gyo)
Na Ae Gyo?
Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol, get up. Right now.
Get up.
Mom, when did you come?
Can you sing that ringtone
that you heard again?
The one you heard by the stairs.
As much as you can remember.
- Why?
- Just sing it.
Mi fa sol fa mi mi
Mi re ti re mi
What is this about? What happened?
That jerk was there.
It's clearly his ringtone.
You can't come to the 85th floor
without Chairman Joo's permission.
Take her to the penthouse.
It's okay, Eun Byeol.
Let go! I'll walk on my own!
- Mom!
- It's okay, Eun Byeol.
Let go!
Let go! I said, let go!
Show up in front of
my daughter again,
and I'll kill you all
with my own two hands.
You have to wake up
at 5 a.m. tomorrow.
I guess you won't get much sleep.
You can still make some soup
for me, right?
I do hate Ms. Cheon,
but I can't let Dad be happy.
If he lived happily
after killing a person,
it would be unfair.
(Lot 27,
Cheonsoo District, Auction)
(Take a leap
toward the next Gangnam!)
She's making it so obvious.
How much cash did you prepare?
Why should I tell you?
We're all competing
against each other.
Do you know
who this land belongs to?
Chairman Joo, of course.
This is where Su Ryeon's
furniture company used to be.
Oh, my. You didn't get the memo?
It belongs to Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee?
Why did she never tell me?
We're best friends.
There are no best friends
when it comes to land and money.
Rumor has it that
she's very close to Yoon Hee,
but I guess it's not true.
I thought what they have is
the friendship of the century.
Mind your own business.
You two have no friends either.
That's why you stick together.
- That's not true.
- Are you jealous?
Mother, how much do we have?
- This much.
- What? Only 300,000 dollars?
- Add another zero.
- Three million?
Don't you know better?
Why don't you shout it
into a bullhorn?
Is this land really worth
30 million dollars?
Kyu Jin says it'll eventually be
worth 300 million dollars.
I took out loans
against my buildings in Gangnam.
Keep a straight face.
All speculators in Gangnam
with deep pockets are flocking here.
Since Joo Dan Tae raised the stakes,
the property will be sold
at the highest price.
I wonder how much
Joo Dan Tae will bet.
He would never want to lose
that land.
Just you wait, Dan Tae.
I'm going to find out everything,
even if I have to kill you.
His tie and collar look different.
He changed.
Why?
Secretary Do, I need you
to look for a person.
Her name is Na Ae Gyo.
She seems close to Joo Dan Tae.
Find out what
their relationship is. Hurry.
As a result of your enthusiasm
for lot 27, Cheonsoo District,
we've decided to invite
all of you here today.
We'd like to give
our super VIPs here...
a chance to purchase the property.
On behalf of the owner
of the property,
let me start the auction.
The starting price is
10 million dollars.
- 11 million.
- 12 million.
- 13 million.
- 15 million.
Come on.
- 20 million.
21 million.
- 23 million.
- 25 million.
Ms. Kang has earned so much money?
- 30 million.
- Now 30 million.
Why don't you give up now?
Why should I?
33 million.
Is that woman out of her mind?
Mother, we should give up.
We're already over budget.
Don't be greedy, okay?
We're not at 33 million.
Can anyone give me more?
Is it being sold for 33 million?
It's not like me to give up here.
I can sell it to Chairman Joo
for double the price later.
40 million.
- 40 million?
- Honey.
Has he lost his mind?
Sell it to me. I'll pay 40 million.
We're now at 40 million.
Is everyone else giving up?
All right. 40 million, it is.
The property is sold...
50 million.
Now 50 million.
I mean, what about the market price?
The difference is getting
too big now!
It's a superb location,
but this is ridiculous.
You'll lose money
when you sell it later.
Don't be an amateur.
I get to decide
what I do with my money.
Worry about yourselves.
Well?
If no one else is bidding,
why don't we stop here?
I have bills to pay.
Where would I get
50 million dollars?
I give up.
Mom.
(Cheonsoo District
Starting bid: 10 million dollars)
Anyway, who are you?
Are you an individual investor?
I'm with Cheong A Group's
Investment and Development Team.
Cheong A Group?
Chairman Joo sent you?
What? Are you toying with us
with your money?
Here's the five million dollars
for the deposit.
(Bank check for 1,000 dollars)
I'll sign the contract tomorrow
with the owner.
I'll bring the remaining
45 million dollars tomorrow as well.
Sold for 50 million dollars.
Who is that woman?
She's from Cheong A Group.
Chairman Joo is going to get
all the good land again.
This stinks.
I wanted to crush that jerk
Joo Dan Tae...
so that I wouldn't have to put up
with his arrogance anymore.
I'm so angry.
But does that woman seem familiar?
She has a cold air about her.
It's very familiar.
But I can't remember
where I saw her before.
Right?
Yes...
Hey.
Finally, lot 27 is ours.
I think 50 million dollars is
too high.
I feel like Oh Yoon Hee
came out the only winner.
Starting tomorrow, the lands we own
will shoot up in value.
Cheonsoo District will blow up.
I guarantee it.
My car's here. Talk to you later.
Do you still have something to say?
I keep...
I keep getting a feeling
that you're not a bad person.
But seeing how money-crazy you are,
you really are one of
Joo Dan Tae's people.
I won't hope for anything
from you...
or try to talk to you again.
I hope I will never...
see you again.
I feel so sorry for Su Ryeon.
She was too sweet
to be used by someone like you...
until she died.
Live in guilt toward Su Ryeon
for the rest of your life.
What is this?
You said you wanted to see her.
Come with me.
Get it.
Will you be okay?
Father doesn't know
that I know the secret passage.
Don't worry.
I'm helping you because of Ms. Oh.
Get in already.
Get in.
Why did you want to see me?
Yoon Hee. Please save me.
I'm begging you.
Yoon Hee.
What are you talking about?
You're making no sense.
It really was Eun Byeol...
who killed Ro Na.
Eun Byeol did it.
I've done a heinous thing
to you and to Ro Na.
But...
there's a trap here.
Joo Dan Tae was involved.
I need you in order to find...
Ro Na's real murderer.
Help me.
Yoon Hee.
(Accelerated High School Math)
Seok Hoon.
It's me.
These are photos of Na Ae Gyo
from the past few days.
She didn't go anywhere unusual
other than restaurants.
There's no need
to monitor her anymore.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
I feel so sorry for Su Ryeon.
She was too sweet
to be used by someone like you...
until she died.
Thank you...
for remembering me.
What are you doing?
You're Su Ryeon.
I know you're Su Ryeon.
Don't try to run away.
I'm sorry...
it took me so long to recognize you.
(The Penthouse 2)
How beautiful is it to admit defeat?
Shim Su Ryeon's dead.
I couldn't forgive myself
for going to the airport first.
I will never forgive you.
I can't guarantee
Eun Byeol's safety.
Let me kill him myself.
Maybe Shim Su Ryeon knew
before she died.
The game's over.
You can put the penthouse up
as collateral and get a loan.
Did Na Ae Gyo deceive Chairman Joo?
I'll kill you, Ae Gyo.
Na Ae Gyo died last night.