[October 28, 2017, MML Festival]
[SHAX rehearsal, cue.]
[SHAX]
[Episode 1]
♫ Don't make me waver with sweet words ♫
♫ Just let me be ♫
♫ Please stop, don't say another word ♫
♫ You know I'm different,
it won't make a difference ♫
♫ For things to be back as they were ♫
♫ Please stop, no waste,
we're just different ♫
♫ Try walking in my shoes
for even a second ♫
♫ You'll know how venomous you were ♫
♫ Step aside, just get away ♫
♫ It's done now, it's done now ♫
♫ I'll forget about us ♫
[♫ It's done now, it's done now ♫]
[♫ That will be better for us ♫]
[♫ What is meaningless ♫]
Just you wait.
Ma-ha will come your way.
Hand me your phone.
You're done being on it.
You need to be focused now.
It's a war from here on out.
Got it.
[SOS, Life call]
[SHAX, stand by.]
Ryok?
[2017 MML Festival]
We'll give it all we have and have fun.
Let's party up there.
The SHAX way.
-Let's go, SHAX.
-SHAX!
[2017 MML Festival]
[What do you mean
there's no one on the lift?]
[-Eun-jo's missing.
-Find him!]
What's going on?
-Come on.
-What?
Get out here. Wear the wires.
What are you talking about?
Where's Eun-jo?
Will you let this be the end?
You and Eun-jo are nothing without SHAX.
Hurry.
Unless you lead today's performance,
SHAX will be shattered.
We'll think about Eun-jo later.
Block out any other thoughts.
All that matters right now is SHAX.
[2017 MML Festival]
[Is something troubling you?]
[Don't be upset.]
[You're precious as is.]
[1 week before the MML Festival]
[Alarm: 5 a.m.]
Morning.
[Five years,]
[1,825 days, and 43,800 hours.]
[11.4km, 1 hour 14 minutes]
[We're all given the same amount of time.]
[But it's never enough
even though I never waste a second of it.]
[An era of a million K-pop trainees.]
[Music Holic]
[Only 0.1 percent of them
get to make their debut.]
[And to become one of them,]
[I've been devoting all of my time.]
[Music Holic]
Watch your gaze.
Follow the camera and keep
the tension in your bodies. Got it?
-Yes.
-Got it.
Okay, we'll take five.
-Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
[Music Holic]
It's not strong enough.
Only NOG would bother turning on
the AC at full power.
[Music Holic]
It's not like power rates are steep,
you know.
Besides, aren't we their assets?
I've been with a major agency, remember?
They roll on a different level.
And you envy that?
Most are run on debt.
I still wouldn't mind
being a trainee in one.
[NOG Entertainment]
They're perfectionists.
It's best to leave them during practice.
That's Eun-jo.
He may seem like a softy,
but he's relentless.
Go to Jae-u with questions.
He's the mom of the group.
Do-jin grew up abroad,
so he's like a wild gun.
I-hyeon forgets to eat
when working on songs,
-so force him to eat at times.
-Got it.
And he's the sweet but bitter
youngest member of the group.
He's also the shot caller.
You'll be caring for them in proximity,
-so get to know them.
-Got it.
[This may not be as big as NOG,]
but our agency isn't so bad.
It's true we're on the luckier side.
Some agencies
have dance studios that get no sun
and trainees sing in restrooms
since there aren't booths
to feel echos in.
♫ I mean it, hurry hurry, 119 ♫
♫ Yes, you will be my lover ♫
[OMEGA Entertainment]
No matter what happens,
I'm going to make my debut at Music Holic.
-Same here.
-Me too.
-Let's debut!
The debut group hasn't been announced,
so don't get ahead of yourselves.
It'll be announced tomorrow.
I'm already scared.
What if I get kicked out again?
As if you need to worry.
Your dancing is like art,
so you'll make the cut for sure.
I'm the one who should be worried.
Ma-ha, you'll make it too.
You worked harder than anyone here,
so don't worry.
Said like a true friend. Thanks, Yu-jin.
We'll be a success story. I'm sure of it.
You're so full of yourself.
Is there anyone here
who hasn't worked their butts off?
Ma-ha, don't be too disappointed
with the results.
You can always try harder next time.
[OMEGA Entertainment]
Hyun-ji, get a grip on yourself.
How can you still be fumbling
with this choreography?
I'm sorry.
We only got it yesterday.
You make your debut in 14 days.
The chief executive of this agency
got you this far on his connections,
so it's up to you to--
Here we go again.
The darn chief executive.
What has he done for us anyway?
Annie.
-Hey!
-Annie?
[OMEGA Entertainment]
Hey!
[Hanjib]
-You're 23, right?
-Yes.
How long have you been a trainee?
-Seven years.
-That's a lot of hard work.
Your debut is right around the corner,
so why...
What on earth am I actually seeing?
What...
Look at yourselves.
You see,
we're one to listen to our agency.
"Solve any conflicts between members
on the spot."
Still. How did you get this dirty?
As the leader, I tried to break it off,
but our eating styles were too different.
Dip or pour?
I'm sorry to interrupt you,
but a sauce should be poured
for tangsuyuk.
All I want is to enjoy the dish
in the traditional way.
The tradition of any fried dish
is its crispiness.
Maintaining that crunch is key,
don't you agree?
-You're clueless.
-And you don't even eat tangsuyuk.
Quiet. That's enough.
It differs for me,
but I wanted it as a dip today.
Tangsuyuk? But I want burgers.
Sorry, I shouldn't have asked.
Either way is fine by me,
but a man should prefer it being poured.
Great. This is just great, you guys.
Thank you.
So you fought
over a sauce being poured
or being left as a dip.
He poured the sauce
before the discussion was over.
No way. It wasn't me.
-Who else could've done it?
-I did.
Just like right now,
no one asked for my opinion,
so I poured it out of spite.
From now on, respect my opinion too.
-We're a team, aren't we?
-And it's over.
Hyuk's the shot caller, right?
Anyway, Mr. Ji will be here soon.
Before this gets worse...
I'm just going to be informal with you.
Guys, clear this up and take showers.
We have a cafeteria downstairs
that everyone envies,
so must you eat this here?
We'd rather save the time and practice.
Do you always argue like this?
-Annie.
-Annie, are you all right?
Annie!
Annie, are you all right? Annie!
Let's have burgers.
-Burgers.
-Unbelievable.
Guys, cut it out.
Eun-jo. A word, please.
What? Me?
Darn, that was close.
Is he still not done?
[Don't you know
how crucial these moments are?]
[NOG Entertainment]
[The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message after the tone.]
Ryok?
[Music Holic]
[Kim Hyeon-o, NOG Entertainment trainee]
We've made our choices for the boys.
The girls don't stand out to me though.
She's tall and
will have a refreshing presence on stage.
[Song Ji-oh]
Look at her age.
How long will she be good for?
Let get rid of those
whose expiration dates are drawing near.
This is a business, you know.
How many times must I tell you
to only keep those
who can bring in the bucks?
Keep personal feelings out of it.
See this as only a business.
How about her?
Her dancing and singing are above average,
but she's a tough one
to mold into a certain group.
Then she's out.
But you see,
she remembers choreography well
and is persistent. If we wait--
Tae-geun? Tae-geun!
This is a business, darn it.
What if we send her
to OMEGA Entertainment?
-OMEGA?
-A group takes the stage in ten days,
but one of the members dropped out.
I see.
They must be antsy over there.
Give her to them.
And make sure we get enough in return.
This is a business, got it?
[Music Holic]
-Ma-ha.
-Yes?
A word, please.
So if I choose to go,
I'll debut in a group right away.
Don't be too upset about it.
This can be a good opportunity for you.
Fine. I'll go.
[Mom]
[I'm sorry I can't celebrate
your birthday with you tomorrow.]
[I'll send your favorite side dishes
by post though.]
[Eat up and train hard.]
[Lee Ma-ha]
[I'm going to be a star. November, 2013.
Lee Ma-ha, you can do this!]
[I'm going to be a star.]
[November, 2013.
Lee Ma-ha, you can do this!]
[Music Holic, Lee Ma-ha]
Lee Yu-jin.
If you're going to keep following me,
then carry my bag.
It's heavy.
Sure.
That almost killed me.
Are you okay?
I was certain you'd be included
in the next group to debut.
How can they send you to another agency?
I'll just be sold.
-What?
-It was my first time
being chosen.
I don't care
if I'm replacing someone else.
The choice wasn't mine to make,
but the outcome is.
-I know I'll do well.
-Ma-ha.
I'm sad that I can't train
with you guys anymore,
but you never know what will happen.
Some people became a star
after moving to a smaller agency...
from a big one.
I could become like them. Don't you think?
I'm sorry.
I'm of no help.
Why would you be sorry?
I'll call you and pester you
when I'm bored or tired.
Are you going to ignore my calls?
No way. You can call me anytime.
Don't struggle on your own.
Anytime.
Yu-jin, I'll be the first
to debut on a music show.
Just wait and see. I'll prove it to them.
So long.
Why can't you stay in the line?
Darn it!
She's confused because
it's choreography for three.
You still haven't heard from Annie?
Do you think something bad...
You. Don't even bring up her name.
Especially you, Ri-a.
Watch your mouth in front of the CEO.
[OMEGA Entertainment]
You're going to make your debut
no matter what,
so get it together, okay?
-Okay.
From the top.
[OMEGA Entertainment]
Keep going!
Who is she?
I'm sorry. I was only going to watch.
You memorized the moves
by watching them from behind?
You must've sent her the video
of our choreography.
What are you talking about?
It was changed yesterday.
I like dancing a lot,
so I catch on a little fast.
But you did it really fast.
Since the new member is here,
let's turn over a new leaf.
All right! Yes!
I think this is going to work.
What do you think happened to Annie?
I feel bad that she got replaced.
I don't know. I can't even reach her.
I'm not going to worry about
someone who went off the grid.
But still...
By the way, do you think she'll be okay?
What do you mean?
I mean, everyone ran away
after seeing how messed up this place is.
What if she runs away too?
Let's just be nice to her first,
so that she won't think of running.
What if the manager yells
and speaks crudely at us?
He won't since our debut
is around the corner.
What about having no warm water
and cockroaches?
Should I not tell her?
Tell her the boiler is being fixed,
and about cockroaches...
I can catch them all.
She'll definitely want to run away.
I'm not going to run away.
I have nowhere else to go anyway.
I put my everything on this.
[School withdrawal form]
I'm sorry for being a freeloader,
but I really want to debut.
I'm okay with cold showers
and cockroaches.
So
thank you in advance.
Seven people ran away
without a word within this year.
Don't be so sure about it
before even trying it out.
Still, we share the same goal.
So let's work hard.
Thank you in advance too.
Ma-ha!
-SHAX!
[On the day of our comeback stage,]
[Eun-jo disappeared into thin air.]
["SHAX's Comeback Stage.
But Where is Eun-jo?"]
["Eun-jo Was Nowhere to be Seen
on Their Comeback Stage"]
[CEO Park Jin-man]
[Things You're Prohibited to Do]
[No cellphone, do not leave after 10 p.m,
do not drink, do not see anyone...]
Do not steal money?
There's someone who stole everything
from here and ran.
This is the room we're sharing.
You can use this bed.
I know it'll be uncomfortable.
Thank you.
Take your time.
Did it belong to the girl
who used this bed?
[OMEGA Entertainment]
[D-5]
[My heart races]
[D-3]
[OMEGA Entertainment]
-OMEGA-3!
Cut! Okay, that was great. Let's move on.
That's it?
[OMEGA Entertainment]
I'm so hungry.
-Here, have some water.
-Thank you.
I'm hot.
-Come here.
-You do it.
We're hot too.
[D-1]
It's so cool.
Fine, you do it.
What are you doing?
-I couldn't sleep.
-Me neither.
It doesn't feel real.
I lost so much weight,
but it's still tight.
What if it rips
while dancing on stage tomorrow?
Then it'll be recorded on a fan camera
and remain as your worst moment.
What do I do? I'm so nervous.
Please let Hyun-ji
overcome her stage fright
and rip the stage. Amen.
I tend to go overboard
when I get too excited.
Please protect Ma-ha
so that she doesn't fall onstage
when she goes overboard.
-Amen.
-Are we good?
-Yes.
If we don't sleep, our makeup
will get cakey. Let's go sleep.
She's right. We might stay up
the whole night. Let's go.
Hold on.
Even so, this is our historical night,
so let's take a photo.
Shall we?
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
Waiting for tomorrow's sun to rise,
-OMEGA-3!
[According to the results of the autopsy,
there was no sign of murder.]
[The case of a 20-year-old woman
who jumped into the Han River]
[The police have closed the case.]
[closed as a drown case]
[Hyun-ji, Ri-a, Ma-ha]
Hello, we're OMEGA-3.
We'll dominate the music scene!
He's coming.
-2, 3. Hello!
-Hello!
We're OMEGA-3.
We'll dominate the music scene!
Hello, we're OMEGA-3.
Hello, this is Ji-hak.
We'll dominate the music scene!
The police?
[How are you related to Ms. Jang Yu-ri?]
Jang Yu-ri?
-Annie.
-Hello.
-We're OMEGA-3.
["Where is Eun-jo? NOG Does Not Clarify"]
Come in.
The dead body found in the Han River
is a trainee from Mr. Kim's agency.
It seems like he'll get away
as they couldn't find a connection.
I think Mr. Ji will get investigated.
I'm sure he won't say anything,
but if he...
Ji-hak is no longer our man.
He has nothing to do with us.
-You get what I'm saying, right?
-Yes, sir.
So don't let them ever mention NOG.
Yes, sir.
I'll cancel all the scheduled gigs
of SHAX for now.
Are you out of your mind?
Don't you know how much we spent
on their new album?
Do not cancel any gigs.
Call "Fact Check",
and cover the major articles
with that girl's suicide.
Tell the PR team to release an article
saying Eun-jo is taking a break.
Yes, sir.
Also...
["Where is Eun-jo? NOG Does Not Clarify"]
Before we cancel his contract,
add up all the expenses we spent on him
and send a certified mail
to his parents in the States.
-Yes, sir.
-You're dismissed.
[Ri-a, Hyun-ji]
What's that?
I didn't want to come empty-handed.
[Green Room: SHAX]
We're going in there?
Is it okay if we go in?
["Call Me", OMEGA-3]
[Ma-ha]
[-This is not right!
-Keep it down!]
[Let's talk after the show.]
-Hello, we're OMEGA-3.
-Ryok!
We're OMEGA-3.
-Hello.
Right.
["Call Me", OMEGA-3]
[SHAX in my heart,
Shut it and follow SHAX]
[Welcome back, SHAX!]
Haven't you received
the official fan club kit?
I'm a newbie, so...
Fans of SHAX can only use
the official kits and approved placards.
We need to be especially mindful
in concerts and music shows.
You need to study up on these things.
OMEGA-3, your rehearsal starts now.
1, 2, 3.
Hello, we're OMEGA-3.
We'll dominate the music scene!
♫ OMEGA-3 ♫
-Stop. Stop!
-What is it? What's wrong?
-What is it?
-OMEGA-3 can't be on TV today.
All of a sudden? Why?
-The dead body from the Han River.
-What dead body?
She was the trainee for OMEGA-3!
Annie...
Wrap up and leave now.
The trainee committed suicide
after getting abused!
It's the most searched topic right now!
How can we air their performance?
Let's change the set.
OMEGA-3, get off the stage.
Let's get ready for the next team.
I'm sorry. Please leave.
I'm sorry, but please hurry.
-Bring in the next team!
-Hurry.
[SHAX, My soulmate, I-hyeon]
Please get off the stage now. I'm sorry.
Get off the stage. Hurry now.
Bring in the next team!
-SHAX!
It's okay.
Don't cry. It's okay.
[OMEGA-3, Ma-ha]
It's okay. It's probably nothing.
It must be fake news.
Oh, no...
Annie...
["Sinjin Daily", Entertainment News,
Reporter Park]
Darn it!
Why did she have to
jump into the Han River?
Hey, cancel everything related to OMEGA-3.
And make them move out.
Don't leave any traces of them.
What about the girls?
They were meant to be used for petty gigs.
Just cancel their contracts.
We can make a group like that anytime
with money.
This is so frustrating!
After the tragic death of a trainee
from a certain agency,
[Jang Yu-ri rests here.]
[people are questioning whether she was]
[abused by the agency.]
[K-pop has gained a good reputation,]
[but there are parts
that still need to be fixed.]
[There are many agencies]
[that are only after money
without establishing a proper system.]
["Call Me", OMEGA-3]
[Young kids who want to
become idol singers]
[sign a contract
and have their youth hocked.]
[3 years later]
The nominee for the Best New Actor Award
is Kwon Ryok of "The City of the Outlaws".
[Seong Hyuk, Kwon Ryok]
Let me announce the winner.
The 43rd Baekho Film Festival,
the Best New Actor Award
goes to Kwon Ryok of
"The City of the Outlaws".
Congratulations.
[Baekho Film Festival]
Congrats.
Thank you.
Kwon Ryok, congratulations.
[Baekho Film Festival]
He's the best in the music industry,
and now, in dramas and films too.
He's very amazing.
Yes, hello. I'm Kwon Ryok of SHAX.
First off, I'd like to share my gratitude
with Director Lim Jun-bong,
who trusted me without holding prejudice
against me as an idol star,
as well as the production crew
and my seniors and juniors.
And I want to thank the members of SHAX
who gave me their support,
as well as my family, Fins.
I'll continue to do my best and repay you.
Thank you.
And the next performance is
by the best singer Korea has ever seen,
please welcome La Ri-ma!
♫ Frustrated, irritated ♫
♫ The change in our relationship
is frustrating ♫
♫ I'm frustrated ♫
♫ Tell me, give me an answer ♫
♫ The change in our situation
is frustrating ♫
♫ Give me an answer ♫
♫ And there's no time
so just tell me in this place ♫
♫ I hate it this vague love ♫
♫ And there's no time
so just tell me in this place ♫
♫ So bring a change
to your pile of confusion ♫
I'm La Ri-ma's younger sister, La Ri-maha!
[Makgeolli Festival]
Hey!
Just sing a trot song or something
instead of that!
♫ Now tell me that you feel the same way ♫
♫ No more confusion ♫
♫ Be confident, proud ♫
♫ Speak of our love from tomorrow,
friendship is over ♫
♫ And there's no time
so just tell me in this place ♫
No one pays cash these days.
Goodness, I'm sorry.
Things with our company bank account
have been complicated.
But we gave you a really cheap deal.
Of course, the copycat has to be cheap.
Anyway, what will you do
about this dead event?
What? Ma-ha has her game.
She'll make things lively soon,
so don't worry.
Hello.
I'm La Ri-ma's younger sister, La Ri-maha!
They're going to have some fun now.
Goodness, ladies and gentlemen,
your reaction is a little stingy!
I'm home.
-Surprise!
-Actor Kwon!
Enough.
Thanks, really.
Did you see a lot of actresses?
Who was the prettiest? Tell me.
No idea.
I have to shower and go shoot.
Gosh, we need to hear
some stories from you!
Hey, I'm going to start acting too.
-My gosh.
-What is it now?
Boys, take this.
What are these?
-My gosh, Ryok is so lucky.
-I'm so jealous.
Why didn't you let him take a break
on a day like this?
He looked tired.
He volunteered to do this.
No one can stop that workaholic.
[Mr. Hwang of Jongno]
[7 Missed call from Mr. Hwang of Jongno]
-Hey, Yu-jin.
[-Are you all done?]
Are you coming back to Seoul?
No, I suddenly got a movie shooting.
I'm on my way to Mungyeong.
You're very busy. It must be tiring.
What's the film?
A historical one.
I never did anything,
and I finally got to work,
so I'm still doing okay.
Make sure you eat well, though.
Don't worry.
I never skip a meal, remember?
Anyway, why did you call?
You know,
it's your birthday soon...
-We're going to practice now. Come in.
-Okay.
-Hello?
-You should go. Don't get scolded.
[Okay.]
Good luck with your shooting,
and come back safely.
-I'll call you later.
-Okay.
[I'm La Ri-ma's younger sister,
La Ri-maha!]
My gosh, no way. She's the most brazen.
La Ri-maha!
No way.
I can't believe her.
-One, two.
-She's unbelievable.
A copycat?
-A hat?
-Her dance and singing
aren't exactly a good copy.
Copying? Hats?
Hey, forget it.
Guys.
If you have time to look at this,
go write your rap and practice.
Jae-u.
My gosh.
What's so bad about this?
So what's the film about?
What was it again?
I heard about it, but I forgot.
They suddenly said they had a minor role.
You might end up coming back
if it goes well, you know.
-So I'm a fill-in.
-Hey.
It happened rather quickly,
but you aren't a fill-in.
It's okay. It's great to be busy for once.
Yes, let's stay strong
and hold out a little more.
I know you'll get your big break, Ma-ha.
Is it because I had
a glass of makgeolli back there?
What's wrong? Do you feel sick?
It's not that bad.
We still have some time.
Let's stop by a rest area.
Gosh, the air is nice,
no one is around, and it's quiet.
How perfect is this?
There aren't many people,
so go to the restroom.
-I'll get something to drink.
-Okay.
I'll get some medicine.
You can get some rest.
-Okay, thank you.
-Sure.
[Rest Area]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
What are you doing?
I've seen her somewhere.
It's cold. Get in already.
Okay.
The scenes changed around a little.
Yes, could you come a little earlier?
Yes, thank you.
Director, she's here for the kisaeng role.
-Hello.
-What? That's in the afternoon.
You got here way too early.
Did you get here?
Yes. You can get your makeup first.
What? He clearly said
the shooting was in the morning.
It's better than rushing things.
I can get ready and wait.
And who knows? It might begin earlier.
Exactly. I love your attitude.
-Go get your makeup done.
-Okay.
Ma-ha. The mole.
Okay.
[Incoming Call]
Who is this?
Hello?
[Hey, did you really think
I'd have a problem finding you?]
Mr. Hwang, I was about to call you.
Please give us some more time.
Just five more days, no, three.
Hey, man.
Why can't you wait a little longer?
Do you know who I am?
Mr. Hwang, please help me.
[You're in Mungyeong, right?]
[Don't you dare take a step outside.]
I'm not in Mungyeong.
I'm in Busan! In Busan, I said!
You said we could have
all day off tomorrow.
This will push back all of our schedules.
It's an important interview,
so we couldn't put it off.
Please do this for us. Thank you.
Man, this is driving me crazy.
Pick up your outfit over there.
Okay, thank you.
Kwon Ryok messed up all of our schedules.
This is so annoying.
He always does everything as he wants.
So arrogant.
What?
The male lead is Kwon Ryok?
Ryok, run up.
Cut down the right side.
Then the left side.
Slam him with your sword, then kick.
Stab the middle guy.
All the kisaengs can move to the right.
Here we go. Slay him.
Ryok, look to your right.
Then turn around.
Ryok, follow him and slay him.
Let's try again.
-Okay.
-To your spots.
Let me explain this once again.
Once he gets up, this side will move out.
Once he stabs him,
all the kisaengs can move out this way.
Don't walk out too much
and just leave this way.
Do not get this confused.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
Let's take it again.
[Cafe]
Two cups of Americano. Here you go.
Thank you.
Hello.
Okay.
All right.
My lord.
My... Goodness.
This is tough.
The sun is about to set.
How dare you throw a feast
with your people's money?
Not one of you will
leave this place alive.
No, that doesn't sound right.
How dare you throw a feast...
How dare you throw a feast
with your people's money?
Not one of you will
leave this place alive.
What was that?
Did someone just take a picture of me?
Where did Dae-gwon go?
Dae-gwon!
One second, please.
I'm so sorry, but Ryok hasn't had
a lot of sleep lately.
-What?
-He has a really big zit right here.
I didn't see anything.
There is one.
His fans will get mad when they see it.
So once he slays him down,
can you do the close-up
on his left profile?
If you suddenly make this change,
we'll have to change all the sequences.
I'll make sure he doesn't get confused.
Could you please
just talk to the action director?
It might be too hard.
Sir, can we change
the right to the left for this part?
-Let's do that.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Mae-hyang. Pour me a drink.
Give me a drink too.
How dare you throw a feast
with your people's money?
Not one of you will
leave this place alive.
Cut! Are you okay?
-All right.
-Hey!
Whoa, hey.
Are you okay?
Didn't you tell her
about the direction change?
I'm sorry!
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
I forgot to relay that to you. I'm sorry.
It's all right. No, I'm fine.
-I'm okay.
-Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
-Are you sure you're fine?
-Yes, don't mind me. I'm fine.
I'm sorry.
Then let's take it from the top.
Ryok, over here.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Stand-by.
I love that face. Okay!
-Great work.
-Great work today.
Great job. Great work today.
Dae-gwon.
-I got it.
-No, don't.
I'll take this.
Let's go. Great work today.
[Ma-ha]
I'm sorry, Ma-ha. I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault.
It's cold.
Where is he?
[Epilogue]
[November, 2013]
Hello, my name is Lee Ma-ha.
I want to learn how to dance
with the best dance crew, Star Is Born.
We don't let just anybody in, so go home.