[Episode 2]
Excuse me. I'm sorry to ask,
but how can I get to the town center?
It's quite the distance.
Walk straight down that road.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
Good job today.
-Take care.
-You too.
If only you were given a better owner.
Let's get going then.
Here.
Go ahead.
They're always so fast to leave sets.
-Dae-gwon.
-What?
They found out again?
[I love how sexy you are
and how you love me.]
[Why did you change your number?
You should've at least told me.]
It didn't even last six months.
I'm exhausted.
I'll change your number right away.
Let's get going so that
you can rest for the interview tomorrow.
Thanks.
-Hop in.
-Sure.
Don't forget your seat belt.
What on earth?
Dae-gwon, what on earth was that?
People did mention something about ghosts.
What ghosts?
Check it out for me. Go on.
But you're my manager.
You! Well, you earn more than I do.
Go on.
What is it? What do you see?
Nothing. I don't see a thing.
Really?
-What? Why?
-Something's there.
-It's her.
-You're making no sense.
The kisaeng you slashed to death.
I heard a manager left his actor behind.
-Was he hers?
-What do you mean?
One of the managers ran off.
I've seen those fleeing
while leaving their cars behind,
but one leaving in the car is a first.
Hey, back up.
To give her a ride? No way.
-Why not?
-You know the agency's policy.
-No.
-Come on.
Hello.
-Get in.
-Sorry?
No, I'm good.
The town center is right past that hill.
I'll get there in no time.
Which is why you should hop in.
I know well being in the industry myself.
We're not supposed to give people a ride.
I don't want to bother you
with something this trivial.
The offer was more than enough.
Good night.
You'll catch a cold once your sweat cools.
Hold on.
If this is because of earlier,
there's no need to be bothered.
This is me wanting to walk,
so go about your own way.
Copycat.
Wait. He knew?
Darn, it's cold.
[7 years ago]
Do you perhaps know Stevie Wonder?
He sang "I Just Called to Say I Love You"
and is my dad's favorite artist.
I once saw him on TV, you know.
Despite being visually impaired,
he writes songs and even sings.
On that show, he said this.
We were all born with unique talents.
The only difference between us
"is that some make use of it
while some don't."
And this is what my dad said right after.
Ma-ha,
"I hope you live your life
the way he does."
So you came to our dance team
to utilize your talent?
Yes.
I'm thinking about moving to Seoul too.
I doubt he'll approve of that.
You will. Won't you, Dad?
Seoul's too bright even at night
to properly see the stars.
That's the only downside.
I can see a lot of stars today.
When did you figure it out?
When you started to avoid me.
No, I wasn't avoiding you at all.
Only stay at my heel.
Got it.
He'll come running over
if he senses that something's up.
Well, we're here.
It's still cold outside.
Will you be okay from here?
Yes, I can find my own way now.
A friend will pick me up.
We should've just let her get in.
She didn't want to
and there's the agency policy.
You know I never go against
the boss' words.
As if.
I'm such an idiot.
-Dae-gwon, can you slow down?
-Sure.
What's happening?
Ma-ha!
No wonder she refused to get in.
What on earth?
-Yu-jin?
-Are you hurt?
No, I'm good.
How did you know to get here?
I'm glad. What a relief.
Dae-gwon, I'm tired.
-Can we hurry home?
-Sure.
[3:04 a.m.]
How did you know to get here though?
[Hello? Hey, Yu-jin.]
I can't get a hold of Ma-ha.
Maybe she's busy filming.
I can't reach our manager either.
[It just doesn't make any sense.]
-Could something be up?
-Let's hang up for now.
[Ma-ha]
[I suddenly got a movie shooting.
I'm on my way to Mungyeong.]
Were you that worried about me?
Nothing beats a good friend.
-My soulmate.
-It was quite the distance
and was dangerous to walk alone.
I ran the whole length
feeling the cool and refreshing breeze.
The stars kept me company too.
Wasn't there anyone
who offered you a lift?
There was,
but it would've only complicated things.
I wouldn't have been as comfortable
as I am with you.
Whatever. I still can't believe
what your manager did.
How can he leave you stranded?
You should report him.
He shouldn't get away with this.
He'll only do this again to someone else.
Forget it. I'm the one
who didn't want to let go.
Besides, he's not a bad person.
I bet he's overwhelmed
with guilt right now.
Wait. But what if you get caught?
It'll be fine.
You should get some sleep.
I bet you're tired.
Maybe I will.
[SHAX]
SHAX?
What?
When did we get here?
You should've woken me up.
Hyun-ji, you're here too.
I got worried
when you couldn't be reached.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm good.
Yu-jin, you'll be late. Get going.
-Sure. Get some rest.
-Okay.
Thanks for last night
and be safe on the road.
Got it.
-Bye.
-Drive safely.
-Let's go.
-Come on.
-Sure.
Where did you go last night
in the manager's van?
I'm sorry.
Forget the apologies
and tell me where you went!
Were you out with a girl?
Hold on. His silence says it all.
So tell me.
Are you seeking fun
since we have no fans that watch us?
What about the others then?
Do you think we stay locked up
because we have nowhere to go?
This won't happen again.
-I'm sorry.
-Get a grip on yourself.
You know how crucial our next album is.
Who knows what'll happen
if it doesn't stir up any response?
Let's head inside. Come on.
-Hyeon-o, that's enough.
-He gets on my nerves.
So much for the boy scout act.
Where the heck did he go anyway?
Weren't you scared?
What did I tell you?
I knew he was one
to throw people under buses.
You should've left the agency when we did.
I knew I was being used
to cash in on smaller gigs.
But you still went along with it?
Well,
I guess I didn't want to let go.
Because once I do,
I knew it'd be out of my reach.
How one can leave you behind baffles me.
Do you know why I was upset and terrified
while walking down from the woods?
It's because I knew
that my lifeline had been severed.
[I finally saw my place in this world.]
What I've always dreamed of
seemed well within my reach,
but I couldn't quite grab it.
For some reason, I kept looking behind me.
It made me feel worse.
This must be the end for me.
I made up my mind on my way back here.
I'm quitting.
I think I've tried enough.
I'd rather get my GED.
-Ma-ha!
-Hey.
We're only 22.
In the K-pop industry,
we're considered old,
but not out in the rest of the world.
We're young enough
to try whatever we want.
You're right. I'm quitting with you.
You too?
I went to sing at a wedding yesterday
and ended up feeling sorry for myself.
Reality hit me hard.
As a kid, my grandma would take me
to sing for families
hosting parties and events.
It struck me that
nothing had changed for me.
Is this what I get
for working my butt off?
Fine. I'm quitting too.
I grew up hearing I was pretty,
so I thought I really was.
But here,
I'm just another above-average face.
Living in a bubble as a queen
must've been the peak of my life.
I'm not as talented as you two are.
Don't say that.
That's enough. Stop crying.
70,080 hours. 2,920 days.
Eight years.
I'm sick and tired of it now.
As of tomorrow, I'm starting a new life.
Reboot!
-Devil SHAX.
-Hello, we're SHAX.
Ryok,
I hear your new project is a period movie.
I was worried at first
since the genre is foreign to me.
So I've been channeling
the rookie actor I used to be
by practicing my tone and fight scenes.
Well, I'm curious as to
what we can look forward to from you.
I'd appreciate it
if you checked it out in theaters.
Lastly, could you tell us how it feels to
celebrate SHAX's sixth year?
I was the last one to talk,
so why don't I go first?
Individually, we lack in many ways
and have a number of flaws.
I hope we can continue
to complete one another
for ten, maybe 20...
Actually,
until the day we die.
Isn't SHAX originally a six-piece group?
Many are still wondering about
what happened to Eun-jo.
Is there no possibility of him returning?
Please stick to the approved questions.
You were the closest to Eun-jo.
Are you not in touch?
That'll be all for today's interview.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
Good work.
[Jang Yu-ri rests here.]
You should always drink
with someone you're comfortable with.
It tastes sweet.
The group you're managing
is Sparkling, right?
It seems like
they're getting good word of mouth.
Not so much. They're not doing good.
If they can't make a hit song
in their third year,
it'll be the end of them.
Are you coming back?
You must've gotten an awesome song.
-No.
-Or did you get an investor?
What's wrong
with the "Fact Check" reporters?
They've never asked such a thing.
Because SHAX isn't causing any trouble,
they just want a newsmaker.
Those lazy pigs. They never do their job.
I'll look for newsworthy material.
What about Ryok?
He got back home after the shoot.
It's been three years,
and he's been getting treated.
so he must've gotten better.
But keep your eye on him.
He could break down all at once.
He's the only one
who's making big money for us.
Yes, sir.
-SHAX!
[SHAX]
Eun-jo.
Eun-jo!
Eun-jo...
Eun-jo... Eun-jo!
[I'm sorry, Ma-ha. Forgive me.
From Go Ba-wi]
[Jeonghyun-ro 82-gil]
[I'm sorry, Ma-ha. Forgive me.]
[From Go Ba-wi]
See? He's feeling guilty.
[GED Exam]
All right. Thank you. Have a good day!
[GED Exam Academy]
[2020 GED, Korean, English, Math]
[Master the GED Exam!]
Hello?
Oh, right. I see.
I'm sorry. Bye.
Hello?
Yes, I am Lee Ma-ha,
but I'm not interested.
Yes. I'm sorry.
Goodness! Those creative scammers.
[Mahee Hair]
I'm home.
-What about the academy?
-What's with your new hair?
Is it pretty?
I got briefed about the classes for now.
Oh, right. I got a weird call earlier.
JH Entertainment?
The CEO's name is...
-Ji-hak.
-That's right. It's Ji-hak.
-You got his call too?
-Yes.
He's a conman.
I asked him how he got my number,
-and he told me to come for the audition.
-You got his call too?
Those psychos. It's so frustrating.
Maybe it's the new kind of voice phishing.
[Do you want to dream once again?]
[The Renew Audition,
November 1st, 2020, JH Entertainment]
[Music Holic]
[Ma-ha]
[Hey, Yu-jin.]
Hi, Ma-ha. It's been long.
Darn it. Will you focus?
Sorry.
Hello, Tae-geun. Have you been well?
I'm doing okay.
Yu-jin is practicing at the moment.
Then I'll call him again.
That means it's about something
you can't tell me.
Stop calling him if that's what you want.
Sorry? Okay.
Oh, right. Didn't Ji-hak call you?
Okay, thank you.
What is it? Did his manager pick up?
It must be about the last time.
Yes.
About that conman though...
I guess he's not a conman after all.
He used to be a manager at NOG.
NOG?
[The Renew Audition, JH Entertainment]
[JH Entertainment Audition]
[It's open for today.]
The audition is held in a cafe?
I don't care if he was a manager.
I'm sure he's just a conman.
Still, we're here anyway.
Let's go in.
Come on!
I'll go in because I pity myself
for coming all the way here.
Fine. If it's a con,
let's just have some tea.
Let's go.
You came.
The one in the middle is Lee Ma-ha.
You're Yoo Ri-a.
And you're Sim Hyun-ji.
-Yes, that's me.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm the CEO of JH Entertainment
and the owner of this cafe.
I'm Ji-hak.
You're all pros,
so shall we begin when you're ready?
Is it okay if we audition together?
Actually, we didn't come for the audition.
We came to commemorate
the ending of our dream.
Is that so?
-It's a little embarrassing.
-It's our first time.
To perform together as a team.
We were supposed to debut as a team.
Yes.
I know you made your debut
as a three-piece girl group. OMEGA-3.
No, we did not debut.
We were just close to it.
There was an incident
on the day of our debut.
You were dragged out of the stage
during your rehearsal.
I know that too.
[It's really hard to
make idol groups popular these days.]
What are you going to do
with those girls who have nowhere to go?
With your career and discernment...
I'm Ji-hak of NOG.
I'm the manager of SHAX, Ji-hak.
It was those titles.
It wasn't me.
[Sim Hyun-ji]
The trainee
who was kicked out
without getting to debut.
[Ri-a]
The girl who only sang
other singers' songs on their stage.
[Lee Ma-ha]
The girl who only does cheap gigs
and never got to do her own stuff.
They made their debut,
but they fell
to the bottom of their lives.
You need stories to be popular these days.
You know it too.
They're as good as the popular ones.
They don't have those trained smiles.
They'll reveal everything
about themselves.
After that, I'll garner attention on them
with a totally different method
as quickly as I can.
This place is not much of a stage,
but you can go ahead
and commemorate your dream.
-OMEGA-3!
♫ My baby, my heart is beating so fast ♫
♫ Oh, my ♫
♫ My heart goes pit-a-pat,
it's beating fast ♫
♫ I know it boy ♫
♫ You're perfect for me, you're my type ♫
♫ My eyes are filled with love for you ♫
♫ When the long-waited love
whispers to me ♫
♫ I fall for you ♫
♫ I stare at my phone all day ♫
♫ But I can't express
how much I love you ♫
♫ I wait again, like a fool ♫
♫ My boy, I want to hear
your sweet voice ♫
♫ If I hear your voice ♫
♫ My heart just melts, Ring my bell ♫
♫ Always stay right next to me ♫
♫ You're so handsome, I'm so happy ♫
-Good work.
-That was great.
-Thank you.
I'd like to work with you three
if it's all right with you.
-What?
It's giving us a headache, isn't it?
I'm getting scared
because this is all too sudden.
Is it possible
to be the CEO of an agency
and run a cafe at the same time?
I know, right?
Seems like there's no part-timer too.
Exactly. That means he's penniless.
But
when we auditioned,
it seemed like he was sincere.
I agree.
Does that mean you all got convinced?
Nonsense.
I even cut my hair
to show how determined I am.
We won't sign with him anyway,
so why don't we just lay it on?
Like the fantasy of all trainees?
Well, since you wanted
to work with us so much.
Let us tell you our conditions.
Here's the contract I want to suggest.
[Management Exclusive Contract]
[Article 1, Exclusive Management]
[A monthly payment
of 1.82 million won will be given.]
You're going to pay us monthly?
-As soon as we sign with you?
-It doesn't make any sense.
I may be paying you minimum wages,
but if we have more profits,
I'll divide and pay them
according to the contract.
I don't buy it.
Are you a conman, by any chance?
Would I say I am if I were one?
You're not going to make us
do anything weird, are you?
"If the employer asks the employee
to do something extreme,"
"the employee can receive
a penalty for breach of contract."
You're not banning us from
using our phones, going outside,
or dating?
You know well
that those things can't be stopped.
Just remember
that actions come with consequences.
You need to take responsibility
for your own action.
Excuse me.
Hello, welcome!
Come with me.
I was going to drive a hard bargain.
But his was even harder
that I couldn't even suggest anything.
What do you want to do?
I'm all convinced, but...
Even so, this doesn't make any sense.
[Management Contract]
Maybe it's because we've never
had such a contract. It does make sense.
In Japan, celebrities receive
a monthly payment.
We've seen a lot of people who struggled
after signing a wrongful contract.
The duration of the contract is a year.
That's all I can afford, actually.
If it doesn't seem to work out,
we can cancel our contract.
What if we make it big?
Then we'll write up a new contract,
satisfying each party's conditions.
That's only if you want to.
-Excuse me!
-Coming!
[H Cafe]
It's only a year.
Just one more year.
I want to extend my dream
by just a year.
Fine. Let's just take a chance
and extend it by a year.
We have nothing to lose anyway.
Okay, then.
Let's do it.
[Lee Ma-ha]
[Yoo Ri-a]
[Management Contract]
Just like you said,
we have nothing to lose.
So let's trust each other
and work together.
Then what should we do first?
You didn't read
your contract thoroughly, did you?
Your contract starts tomorrow.
You can go home and rest today
since you'll become busy soon.
Thank you for this.
-Thank you for this.
-Sure.
It's another beginning
starting from tomorrow.
Maybe we should come up
with a new group name.
-With a new mindset.
How should we name ourselves?
-Gosh, it's hot!
-Be careful.
Cool it down and drink it slowly.
-Tea Party?
It sounds the same backward.
It sounds the same forward.
Hello, always happy,
we're Tea Party!
[It sounds the same backward.]
[It sounds the same forward.]
Hello, always happy, we're Tea Party!
[Shinjung Bank]
[Loan Agreement, Ji-hak,
1 hundred million won]
[JH Entertainment, Tea Party,
Submit your songs for the group]
[Application deadline, End of November]
[Your email has been sent.]
When did you prepare all this?
It reminds us of the old times,
doesn't it?
Right.
We'll get a new song,
decide on the concept, practice our dance,
and prepare for our debut.
We'll have to practically live here
for about six months.
I'll have you debut as soon as I can.
But
we don't have a song yet.
You got your group name, Tea Party.
Your first show could be within this week.
I might as well just catch a burglar
and be on the news.
That's a good idea too.
Our concept is to go all realistic.
You'll show yourselves as is.
It's in your contract.
Hey, Ji-hak.
It has been ages.
This place hasn't changed at all.
I haven't heard from you for so long
that I thought you moved abroad.
So? Returning to the industry?
I made a humble three-piece girl group.
Hey, I liked how the program you make asks
really tough and good questions.
So you watched
my current affairs program as a friend?
I'm honored.
Let me ask you for a favor.
I make a current affairs program now.
I can't be your connection anymore.
Take just one look at this.
Let's talk then.
[Management Contract]
-What is it?
-Just take a look.
An idol group who gets paid monthly?
But they're an idol group.
Shouldn't they release a song first?
Like I said,
our concept is candid reality.
I need people to pay attention
to Tea Party first.
Then comes their music.
I need you to quietly make
a list of agencies we can take over.
You know that
we need better girl groups, right?
-Yes, sir.
-Good.
I heard Ji-hak came back.
That's his only stock-in-trade.
What else could that man do?
Should I look into it?
Let him be.
It's tough to make a living,
so he probably got some kids
to perform at events.
-You may leave.
-Yes, sir.
Ji-hak, really?
Mr. Ji.
Hey, Mr. Ji.
Why won't you tell us what the program is?
You can't just drag us over
to the TV station.
We really have nothing prepared.
[Absolutely no smoking allowed]
["Current Affairs and People,"
Person of the Week]
Now, this is the first stage
you three will appear
as Tea Party.
["Current Affairs and People,"
Person of the Week]
If you don't want to do it,
don't. I won't force you.
But if you run away now,
[Recording in Progress]
you can never return.
Current Affairs and People,
["Current Affairs and People,"
Person of the Week]
it's time for Live Interview
with our person of the week.
We invited a very special idol group
who's making their debut at a news program
instead of a music show.
Could you introduce yourself?
One, two, three.
-Always happy, Tea Party.
I'm Ri-a, the leader.
-I'm Hyun-ji.
-And I'm Ma-ha.
You three have such cute greetings.
Thanks for joining us.
I should thank you.
Thank you. See you on the set.
[I heard you'll be the first group...]
-Great work.
-Great job.
-What's next?
-We're done for the day.
Let me get the car.
-Wait for me.
-Let's go.
[We get paid monthly
even before we start making a profit.]
[Our agency considers
the practicing hours as labor.]
[Back when I was a trainee,
I had to work lots of part-time jobs.]
["Current Affairs and People,"
Person of the Week]
[I sang at weddings,]
[at a barbecue place, and delivered too.]
["Current Affairs and People,"
Person of the Week]
[It's wonderful
now that I can only focus on my practice.]
[If it's not too rude to ask,]
[may I ask how much you get paid?]
We get 1.82 million won a month.
That's the minimum wage.
Aren't you the first group in Korea
to sign a contract like this?
Yes, people don't bring this up,
[Ri-a, Hyun-ji, Ma-ha]
but many agencies consider
the expenses they spent
on the trainees as their debt
when they make the debut.
My friend owes over 100,000 dollars,
so she hasn't been paid
even though she's in her third year now.
I think this system has
its strengths and weaknesses.
I'm starting to wonder
who your CEO is
to let you sign
this unprecedented contract.
Is he or she rich?
No, not at all.
First off, our CEO is
definitely not a rich man.
I saw his loan papers.
We have to get our big break
before he runs out of money.
We can do it!
You make me want to root for you.
I really hope you do well.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
Then let's switch the gears a little.
Don't idol stars all have
a special talent to show?
Could you show us what you can do?
Yes, I'll go first.
♫ Don't criticize me
and call me a cruel woman ♫
["Current Affairs and People,"
Person of the Week]
I would've almost called you cruel
if you sang a little more.
Thank you.
You have such an impressive voice.
-And next?
-I don't have any special talent to show.
[Ta-da.]
[That was a cute moment
from the visual member.]
[You're so lovely.]
[Lastly, Ma-ha?]
[I'll sing you a song
I sang the most often]
[while I performed at local events.]
[-I need a moment to get prepared.
-Sure.]
What are you watching?
[I'm La Ri-ma's sister, La Ri-maha!]
Is it because she looks like me?
Just look at me. Why look at the copycat?
-What brings you here?
-For the same reason as you.
Idols on Air?
I got you that gig.
If I didn't do that,
I'd never get a chance to see you.
See you on the set.
What? You're leaving like this?
I have a full day.
Bye.
[I'm Ma-ha of Tea Party!]
[Thank you.]
She gets on my nerves.
That little witch.
What did we just do?
[Studio 25]
I don't remember.
I never said anything.
I just sat there smiling.
Hey, Grandma. Did you watch me?
You all got together to watch it?
[Mom, I'll be on TV today!]
[Make sure you watch me!]
Ma-ha.
My mom said,
"You've done so well, Hyun-ji."
I suddenly broke out in tears.
My makeup is all smeared.
I want to break out in tears too.
[Yu-jin]
[Congrats on debuting on network TV.]
[I look forward to more.]
Look forward, my foot.
[Messages]
Hey, what on earth is happening?
-All kinds of people must've watched it.
-Look.
-Tea Party.
Shall we?
-Yes.
[Tea Party]
["A Girl Group on Salary"]
["Tea Party's Ri-a Owns 'Tears'"]
["Tea Party, Hyun-ji"]
["Will Tea Party Make It?"]
Who are they? They seem unique.
Tea Party. They're the hottest issue now.
-Why don't we have them too?
-Aren't they still a nobody?
["Current Affairs and People"]
They got a story to tell,
and the girls seem interesting.
Her impersonation of La Ri-ma
could get her going
for four weeks on our show.
Okay, let's call her when we shoot.
You can't come dressed like this.
You're La Ri-ma's copycat.
I'm Tea Party's...
-We have wigs, right?
-Yes.
["Hometown Report"]
[Hyun-ji: Weathercaster gig]
[KBC]
["Happy Time", 3 p.m.]
Why is the performance fee still the same
as it was three years ago?
But you all have done a lot of hard work.
So how much did we make?
What?
Right, well.
How much?
Your debut, "Current Affairs and People",
paid 187 dollars and 60 cents.
"Hometown Report" was filmed
out of the city,
so they paid 288 dollars and 60 cents.
Dog and Me was also out of the city,
so they gave us 252 dollars.
Can you pay us if we made so little?
We have to perform at events
to make money.
[La Ri-ma's sister]
[Why won't La Ri-ma sue her?]
[Why does she keep copying?]
Why does she keep copying La Ri-ma?
The debut of a copycat idol group
who performs with another artist's song.
Come on.
If you're going to let it get to you,
don't look at it.
It makes me concerned, that's why.
Everyone said it was funny at first.
Hey.
Are you going to speak casually to us now?
People keep criticizing me
as a copycat idol.
I couldn't just look away.
If you can't look away,
then study the malicious comments.
Read them,
then forget the comments
that you can't change with your actions.
But if you can do something to change it,
you can do that.
Then there are scumbags
who just enjoy cussing at you,
whom you can report on.
Okay?
I get everything,
[You don't even have a song.
Why are you on TV?]
but this one thing really kills my pride.
"You don't even have a song.
Why are you on TV?"
I agree.
This is Ji-hak of JH Entertainment.
Idols on Air?
Idols on Air.
Yes, all right. Okay.
Okay. Thank you. Yes. Thank you.
What was that?
Are we going to be on "Idols on Air"?
This is huge.
My gosh, SHAX will be there
for the next shooting.
The guests are so amazing.
That's so awesome!
But I'm sorry.
They only asked for Ma-ha.
Congratulations.
-You can do it!
-Go get them.
[Monthly Plan]
And "Idols on Air" is your last schedule
before you begin recording
your first single album.
-Our single album?
Yes, I asked a publishing company
to find you a song,
so they'll flood in.
This is awesome.
Hello, I'm Lee Ma-ha of Tea Party.
Can you check on the lighting?
Don't be nervous.
It's your first time,
so don't get too ambitious.
It's your chance to learn.
When they make you do stuff,
you just do your best.
I'm here to represent Tea Party,
so I'll do anything to my best.
Yes, Chief Producer. One second, please.
Ma-ha, everyone here is your senior,
so make sure you greet everyone, okay?
One second.
Yes, sir. Yes.
Hello, I'm Lee Ma-ha of Tea Party.
There's La Ri-ma.
She's prettier in real life.
She's so pretty.
That's La Ri-ma.
Hello.
It's you. My copycat.
What? You don't look anything like me.
Is everyone blind?
La Ri-ma, you're here.
Hey, Director.
-Anyway, is she going to be on the show?
-What?
You wanted her here.
Yes.
Well, now that she's here,
we can turn this into a fun episode.
She's my copycat,
and it's her first time
appearing on TV next to me.
Why don't you dress her up
to look exactly like me?
-Hey.
-Yes?
Do you have another outfit?
I do.
Sounds great.
I knew it, La Ri-ma. You're so good on TV.
Is that all right?
You'll have to copy me
to get a few more seconds on TV.
Of course, you'll do it.
What are you doing? We're losing time.
Move it.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey, that's Mr. Ji.
-Mr. Ji?
I heard he made
a girl group named Tea Party.
I guess they'll be on the show.
-Ryok... Hyuk, let's go.
-Okay.
Once I go on TV like this,
people will criticize me a lot once again.
Hello.
Thank you for your help last time.
I always carried around your jacket
in case I run into you.
Is copying La Ri-ma all you can do?
Sorry?
You'll have to copy me
to get a few more seconds on TV.
Is copying La Ri-ma all you can do?
And this is our last guest.
She's a rookie who came to visit
"Idols on Air" for the first time.
I never imagined that she had a sister.
Here's La Ri-ma's sister, Lee Ma-ha.
Please welcome her!
I'm La Ri-ma's sister, La Ri-maha.
I'll do my best
to copy my sister to a T.
Music, please.
Will you give me a hand?
She reached out for help!
Will she take her hand?
[Epilogue]
Hey, she's back.
It has been a month already.
And she doesn't live in Seoul either.
She does seem passionate.
Your number.
What?
Okay.
Here.
[You received a video message.]
Copy that by tomorrow,
then I'll think about it.
Thank you.
Copycat.