♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I’ve never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫  I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I’ll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I’ll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don’t regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Balad
Episode 5
Tegin,
The water is ready.
Su Yishe and Nuer are exploring the way ahead.
and found substitutes for us
to head for the grassland through the pass.
But,
according to our speed now,
it will take us half a month to get Youzhou.
Half a month?
It would be too long.
We have to hurry up.
Yes.
That is...
How could it be a dead body?
Why is it him?
Tegin,
what's wrong?
Yaro,
find a place to stay.
Yes.
Tegin, let me hold him.
No.
When did he change to a stickybeak?
As if that is a piece of gold?
Search carefully!
Dead or alive, we must find her!
Yes...yes...
Wei Shuyu.
Congratulations!
For what?
You intercepted Li Changge yourself.
And then you took the first place to shoot her.
You made great contributions on clearing the leftover traitor.
Of course I should tell his Highness
to publicize your contribution.
Hao Du.
You are so ruthless, aren't you?
Aren't you clear whether Changge is guilty or not?
It's not important what I am thinking.
I just follow Father's order.
What he orders is what I think.
But Wei Shuyu, I also have something to tell you.
We cannot have it both ways.
If you want your family,
follow my order.
Tegin,
This is where hunters take a rest.
Few people would come.
Take the wine bottle and medicine, and a set of clothes.
Yes.
Shameless!
Why did you hit me?
What are you doing?
Can't you see what I am doing?
What did you see?
You are a man,
what can I see?
Then why are you covering your eyes?
I don't like blood.
I don't want to see your wound.
Since you are so marvelous,
then do it yourself.
I didn't ask you for help.
Aliqi.
What does it mean?
Spirit from the west.
Much better.
Thanks!
Are you silly?
Bear it!
You are a real man.
Give her the medicine.
Don't touch me!
Don't cry aloud like a woman!
We don't have to wait till now if we want to hurt you.
Leave her alone.
He's really ungrateful.
Go.
Father,
what's wrong?
Prince Qin was here just now,
and I scolded him out.
I think he will send someone here soon,
and put me to death.
Father,
I'll prepare for the carriage now,
please escape to hometown Quyang first.
I'll find Mr. Du now.
Shuyu,
your father is not a coward.
But, sorry for making you involved.
Father,
it's my fault.
I'm not strong enough to protect my father, nor my family.
Stand up.
What I did has nothing to do with you.
Today, Prince Qin came to our house,
so he is really a broad-minded man.
If you want to work for Prince Qin,
I won't stop you.
Father,
I don't know whether it is a right choice or not.
Mr. Wei.
This is what his Highness asked me to deliver to you.
Father.
No!
I'll plead to his Highness,
and Wr. Du.
Shuyu.
Father!
Take it.
Mr. Wei.
Please enjoy.
Father.
Father, no!
I'll plead to his Highness,
and Mr. Du.
How did I teach you since you were young?
Take off your hands.
Vinegar celery.
Mr. Fang always says that Mr. Wei loves vinegar celery.
Crown Princess Zhangsun
made it with five flavors in person.
Just to show my gratitude.
Today it was my fault.
Please forgive me.
Father...father...
Father!
Father! No!
Fa...
I was too narrow-minded.
But Prince Qin knows when to yield and when not.
Although we are from different sides,
I never say it out but I am clear in mind,
Prince Qin is benevolent and generous,
but also resolute in his decisions.
No one can stop this mishap.
As for my loyalty to my master,
I can decline him for my whole life.
But the lands we are in still belong to Tang.
People here are still people of Tang.
My long-cherished wish is just for repaying Tang.
Father,
I know.
For my whole life, I'm convinced by only a few people.
This vinegar celery...has convinced me!
Thanks.
It's a misunderstanding.
You saved my life, I will...
It's okay.
You don't owe me anything.
There's nothing between us.
That would be good.
Well... Can I have this wine?
Yes,
but I never suffer any loss in business.
Why not make an exchange?
I can give you the wine.
You need to answer my questions.
Okay?
It is impolite not to reciprocate.
Then let's play a game.
Dare you?
Of course.
We ask each other questions in turn.
If one can not answer,
then one should drink as a forfeit.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Where did you get the wound on your shoulder?
Soldiers from the court shot me.
You are so straightforward.
Since it's an exchange,
no one is allowed to lie.
My turn.
What's your name?
Surname, Qin.
Zhun.
You can call me A'Zhun.
A'Zhun...
You?
Surname, Li.
I was the 14th child in the family.
Call me Shisi.
Why did you want my dagger?
I just wanted to embarrass you.
I knew you were a bad guy.
A'Zhun, where are you from?
I'm from central plains,
born beyond the Great Wall.
Then where's your home?
That's another question.
Next,
where would you head to?
For a revenge.
Then what about you?
To the north.
Revenge for what?
What to do in the north?
A huge business.
Since you have answered it,
why did you take a drink?
Because you will ask me about the business,
and I cannot answer.
I will be drunk if I keep drinking.
Then the last question,
are you really called Azhun?
Then Shisi,
are you really Shisi?
Good!
Come on!
Cheers!
Again!
Drink!
What is Tegin talking with him?
I've long been not hearing that laugh from him.
Tegin has been leading Eagle Division for years,
but Great Khan is always suspicious of him.
And he always got impeded by that deadly foe.
Under such a situation,
if it were you, could you laugh?
Yes, you are right.
But never mind that,
don't be upset by that.
But I haven't seen him caring about anyone so much.
Your Highness,
Princess Yongning has nothing to do with the rumor.
It seems that it was done by others.
As for Princess Yongning,
it was my fault to let her escape.
Fine.
These days, massive forces have already yielded surrender.
Even if she has any move,
it won't cause a big trouble.
Just pay more attention to her.
Yes.
Keming.
What's more, your Highness?
What Changge took away with her,
is an important item of the court.
No matter what,
no one can keep it.
Clear.
Wei Zheng was right.
I'm the most ruthless person in this world.
Princess.
Mr. Du.
His Highness is in there.
You can go in.
Tegin.
Let's go.
Where is that boy?
He's gone.
Gone?
Why didn't he tell me?
Just go?
Su Yishe.
Send a scout back to the Eagle Division.
Ask them to prepare these,
and wait for me outside Youzhou.
And, hand this to Great Khan.
Don't worry, Tegin.
Go.
Tegin,
what should we do after we get Youzhou?
I've already asked Su Yishe to prepare the road stone.
Greetings, father.
It's hard for you to see me yourself.
Anything happened?
Nothing.
I just want to come to see you.
That's so kind of you.
If nothing wrong, just go back and have rest.
I'm still very busy now.
I want to ask you about Changge.
Please don't harm her.
Changge just has a bad temper.
- But she...
- Yan.
Yan.
Forget Changge.
It's good for both you and her.
Father!
Your Highness, the court sent someone here.
He is here to see Princess.
His Majesty heard that
Princess harbors great righteousness in mind,
and would love to marry into the grassland.
I am here to send rewards,
and the imperial edict.
Please accept it, Princess.
Crown Prince's daughter,
young and quiet,
as one of the members of the royal family,
all your reward is according to the regime.
Now you are Royal Princess Yongan,
you can get the rewards of 3000 households,
and this is executed at once.
Noble Princess Yongan,
accept it, please!
I accept it with pleasure.
Thanks to your Majesty!
I still have to marry into the grassland, right?
[Du's Mansion]
Father,
you have been upset
since you came back from Hongyi Palace.
Is that because his Highness is still concerned about Li Changge?
If she is still alive,
then she'll be a big trouble.
I can't understand.
Why can Li Changge make Crown Prince, Princess,
and Family Wei protect and defend her?
His Highness is very affectionate towards her.
Princess is her good friend.
As for Mr. Wei,
if Li Changge is alive,
she must go to find Wei Shuyu.
Keep an eye on Wei Shuyu.
Find the Seal of Crown Prince.
And kill her.
Understand.
Hao Du,
remember.
Never mind the trivial things
when doing something important.
Never be tied by any affections.
Yes.
[Chang'an]
From here I will leave Chang'an.
I never thought that I would come here one day.
Hurt! Hurt!
A'Dou?
Master!
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Why are you here?
I asked you...
I've been here waiting for a whole day.
Since I know master will head north,
then you must pass this boundary tablets on your way.
Master, I've been with you for some days.
Am I making any progress?
But if you didn't show up,
I would doubt myself if I was wrong.
A'Dou,
I still have no idea where my future is.
You have a bright future.
Although you can't stay at Pinxiang Store,
you have many other choices.
Why must you follow me?
Master,
you are my future.
I will be with you no matter I'm alive or dead!
I said that,
I won't be wrong.
my master must be a big hero!
Which hero has no general with him?
I am my master's general!
Master!
I'm serious!
A'Dou.
Master!
Let me follow you.
Kowtow.
Since you take me as your master,
we have to obey the ritual.
Master, please take me as your apprentice!
From now on, you are my apprentice.
We will never betray each other.
Okay.
Master,
where are we going now?
Youzhou.
My father's soldiers and horses are there.
Li Yuan, the Governor of Youzhou, is my father's good friend.
Besides,
if we can persuade him to help us,
it will be possible for us to win.
Then I am going to be a general so quickly?
Far from that!
But,
I will never give up.
[Chang'an]
My house is not good enough for you.
I am here to say sorry.
Mr. Wei was right.
I scolded you so much,
which one do you mean?
This is for that plate of vinegar celery.
Mr. Wei is also a father,
when you were risking for Jiancheng,
did you think about Shuyu?
Don't worry,
I have some farmlands at home,
it's enough for my boys.
So a man like Mr. Wei also worries about his sons.
What do you want to say?
Just a chat.
I also have kids and always worry about them.
I have read a lot.
But I have no idea how to protect them as their parents.
I'm a father,
I can feel your love to kids.
I heard about that marriage of Princess Yongan.
If you're worried about it,
then I may give you a suggestion.
Please.
What?
I suffer a strange disease?
Yes.
Remember.
This strange disease can not be cured so quickly,
and you have to go to Luoyang to get medical treatment.
Luoyang?
Yes.
I have already arranged for you.
Start your trip as soon as possible.
Go!
You always cry.
How could you be a princess if you are so weak?
You should learn from Changge!
Yan.
Because you suffer from this,
so you can't marry so far.
Understand?
Stay at Luoyang for the treatment.
I will send someone to take you back as soon as you are recovered.
I know you get on well with Mr. Wei.
I have asked him to escort you to Luoyang.
You don't have to worry about anything with his help.
As ordered.
Brother Shuyu.
I will take you to Luoyang.
Thanks, Brother Shuyu.
You will understand your father someday.
You!
Come!
Okay.
Next.
[Youzhou]
Be careful!
Next.
Go.
Okay, okay, go.
Okay.
Next.
Go.
Thanks.
What's in your carriage?
Food.
- Food?
- Yes.
You. You.
Go and search.
Yes.
No...no need to search.
Just some grains.
It's not up to you.
Any problems?
No.
Okay.
Thanks!
- Go.
- Thanks!
Go, let's go.
Wait!
Sir.
Why are you so nervous?
No, sir.
What's in here?
Officer, just some grains.
Sir...
Open it and search.
Yes, yes.
No...
Take them all.
Yes.
No, no, no...
No, sir!
Go, go.
I'm wronged, sir!
Wronged!
General.
What's that?
We didn't get anything,
and you didn't see anything.
Remember?
Yes!
I was wronged! Officer!
Go quickly.
Thanks.
- Thanks!
- You're welcome.
Master,
you're so clever.
If we didn't get on this carriage,
how could we get here so quickly?
There would be many blisters on our feet.
This is leveraging.
Learn from it.
Their food is quite good!
Slow down, madam!
What will we do next?
Wander around.
Okay, let's go.
Let's stay here.
Please.
Waiter?
Here!
Two gentlemen,
which room do you want?
The cheapest?
The cheapest.
This way.
Go.
Please.
Have a look here.
Although our room is not big,
it is enough for you two.
Besides, it's quiet here.
Are you satisfied, client?
Yes.
Okay, have some rest first.
And I will prepare the hot water for you.
I will explore around the Governor Mansion.
you stay here.
Don't expose yourself.
Yes.
Master, just bear it.
It is good enough for the boss to provide us with the warehouse.
I will clean it up.
And make it a cozy place for you to have a rest.
A'Dou,
don't be too tired.
I'm okay with that.
I'm not tired, master.
Have some rest now!
Nothing,
I will explore here.
Master, I will follow you.
You are just a little boy,
it'd be strange for you to go with me.
Sleep early.
I'll take you some food.
This is the last stop.
Tomorrow we will arrive at the palace in Luoyang.
Brother Shuyu,
am I going to leave tomorrow?
The view of Luoyang palace is very splendid.
Those servants will be your side.
Those days when we could play together are just like a dream.
We three were so good,
but now we have to be separated remotely.
and head to different places.
All good things must come to an end.
No one can stay with each other for the whole life.
Brother Shuyu, I understand.
I have to wake up.
We have grown up.
Brother Shuyu,
could you...could you write to me when you are free?
As soon as you get news about Changge,
tell me.
I promise you.
I will find her.
It's late.
Go back and have rest.
I never thought that you could be so quick.
I can catch up with you until you are almost at Luoyang.
Listen, Wei Shuyu!
Decree from Crown Prince.
Wei Shuyu is assigned as the special envoy of Chang'an.
No need to go back to Chang'an.
Go with Hao Du to Youzhou.
Call Li Yuan, King of Lujiang, to come to the court.
Please tell me,
do you have her message?
You hope it's a yes, or no?
No matter what, you have to go with me.
Besides,
you just need to issue the decree.
As for others,
stay away from it.
Someone saw that Princess Yongning
and a boy appeared on the way to the north,
heading to Youzhou.
Listen.
Keep an eye on Wei Shuyu.
If they meet each other privately,
kill Yongning.
If Wei Shuyu stops you,
the same to him.
Yes.
Boss.
Which is your best ironware?
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There’s always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There’s always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There’s always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There’s always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad