♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I’ve never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫  I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I’ll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I’ll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don’t regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 6
Sir.
Your dishes.
Have a taste.
Here's the wine.
Have a drink.
Sir, what would you like?
A plate of mutton.
OK.
Generals, it's my treat.
It's considerate of you.
Where are you from?
Honestly,
I have a cousin called Niu Awu
who serves in the army in Youzhou.
Do you know him?
There are indeed several bros in the camp with the surname Niu.
But I'm not sure whether he's in the troop.
Considering your filial piety,
I want you to dissuade him from serving in the army here.
Look for another way out.
Why?
You're inexperienced.
If you serve in the army here,
maybe you'll lose your life soon.
Mind your words!
Don't talk nonsense when drunk.
If someone eavesdrops,
you'll be killed.
Thank you for saving me.
But Youzhou is a very important city in our country.
Everything is in order here.
Why do you consider it bad?
Since the incident on 4th day,
Commandant Li hasn't come out yet.
Other commandants are in a hurry to show congratulations
and report on work in the capital.
But our commandant shows respect to no one
and won't go out.
Seven days have passed.
If his Highness blames him,
He doesn't come out.
King of Lujiang will be killed.
We the defending troops in Youzhou will also be killed.
General Wang and King of Lujiang are related by marriage.
They're two grasshoppers on a rope.
Perhaps General Wang will be killed, too.
Just muddle along.
Cheers.
I didn't expect that Li Yuan
is affectionate, righteous and courageous.
So there's nothing hard.
Thank you for enlightening me.
Have a good meal.
See you.
Have the dishes.
Come on!
You and I are in the same position.
I've always been tolerant of you.
But you've always bothered me.
No need to do that.
You are from a famous family in Shandong.
You have a bright future.
I'm just a warrior.
How dare I have a comparable position with you?
I don't want to be your enemy.
You don't have to be sarcastic all the time.
These are the gifts from the imperial court.
Be careful. Don't bump on the road.
Go!
Yes!
Brother Shuyu!
Where did you get the iron ore?
General.
We got this iron ore by accident
from selling goods in the north.
Our master said we can earn a lot
by selling the ore to the blacksmith shop.
If you impound the goods,
I'll lose my life when back.
General.
It's too wasteful to smelt such excellent iron ore
into ordinary farm tools.
Little bro.
Can you get more iron ore?
I...
Smuggling iron ore is a felony.
Kill him!
No!
I can!
Commandant.
How much do you want?
I want as much as you have.
Well...
I have to discuss with my master.
Little bro.
Remember.
I want 2000 dan.
Let me know when the goods are ready tonight.
In front of the thatched cottage outside the city,
no pay no goods.
OK.
Don't play tricks on me.
Or you and your guys will die.
General.
Don't worry.
Go.
Send a team of bowmen
to ambush near the thatched cottage.
Both the guys and goods will be captured.
Yes!
[Governor Mansion]
Why are you here?
Do you love me so much that
you follow me all the way?
You think too much.
Why not tell me you come to Youzhou for business?
You didn't ask me.
What do you want to do here?
Just private matters.
Deal with private matters in Governor Mansion?
It seems that you're rich or a dignitary.
Don't talk nonsense!
I'm new here.
Can't I hang around?
I'm going back to the inn.
Coincidence.
I also want to go back.
Shall we walk together?
Azhun.
Take care.
See you next time.
Please.
It turns out that there's a strong connection between us.
We have to walk together further.
What a coincidence!
Look at the fans.
Have a look.
[Qingxiang Inn]
You live here?
You also live here?
Shisi, why not go back to your room?
You first.
Do you think we live in the same room?
Tegin, you're back!
Tegin, what are you happy with?
Am I?
Yes.
You seldom smile.
How is everything going?
Tegin.
I wouldn't have been angry
if you didn't mention him.
Considering your task,
I didn't beat General Wang.
Guess what?
He asked us for 2000 dan of iron ore.
So greedy!
We don't have that amount.
Tegin, what should we do?
Refuse.
Refuse?
Tegin.
I don't know what you mean.
Tonight,
let's go to see General Wang.
Really?
Master!
Why do you come back so early?
Did Li Yuan agree?
I didn't see him.
But I have some achievements.
A' Dou.
Look for paper and ink.
I want to write a letter for a visit.
OK.
Hope this time my guess is right.
Leyan?
Brother Shuyu.
Princess?
Why hide in the carriage?
Get off right now.
Come on.
Why do you follow us?
Brother Shuyu.
In fact,
I just worry about you.
So I followed you in secret.
You don't have to worry about me.
Don't be willful next time.
I'll arrange for my men to send Princess
back to Luoyang immediately.
No.
I don't want to return Luoyang alone.
Men!
Let Princess mount the horse.
Brother Shuyu!
Hao.
Why rush to send her away?
I'm worrying about her safety.
Brother Shuyu, he's untrustworthy.
Can you send me away?
But I'm busy with my official business.
Or shall I follow you?
I won't make any trouble.
Hao.
Youzhou's affair is urgent. It can't be delayed.
It's OK to go back a few days later.
If there's any trouble with her on the way,
can you take the responsibility?
I will be fully responsible for her safety.
Leyan.
You have to share a horse with me later.
At the next station,
I'll find you a carriage.
Brother Shuyu.
This bad guy said that
he would not only kill Changge but also you.
Put things in order.
Ready to go.
Yes!
Don't worry.
Got it.
General Wang.
Thanks for waiting.
Yes!
Are you the master of those merchants?
How long have you been in business?
For years.
General.
Nothing is on the cart!
How dare you play tricks on me?
Wang Junkuo.
I haven't seen you for years.
Can't you recognize me?
You're...
You're the Tegin of Eagle Division in Ashile Tribe!
Ashile Sun!
How dare you come to Youzhou?
You bite the hook.
If my memory doesn't go wrong,
it's you who invited me to Youzhou.
I've found that there's a trick.
But compared with what I want,
I'd better take your head to Chang'an.
That's more valuable.
If you go to Chang'an,
you'll never return.
I come here to give you a way to survive.
But you refuse.
Master!
Your handwriting is beautiful.
Master.
What are you writing?
A way to survive.
A way to survive?
Secrets of martial arts!
You can understand like that.
I'll see whether Li Yuan accepts it or not.
Master.
What's this?
Seal of Crown Prince.
Seal of Crown Prince?
Quiet!
Master.
You...
From now on,
I'm afraid of nothing.
Have a seat.
Are you afraid?
What do you want to say?
Prince Qin has entered Eastern Palace.
Youzhou is in emergency.
You're more clear about the situation.
Instead of waiting for death,
you might as well use the favorable terrain of Youzhou
to find your own way out.
I am loyal to my country.
Stop talking nonsense!
You say you're loyal to your country.
Why are you secretly searching for iron ore?
You want to forge weapons in case of rebellion.
Are you going to tell me that
you are going to pay tribute to the new crown prince?
Your mind is not perturbed
because the deal is not that worthy.
If Khan wants to help you,
iron ore is a piece of cake.
What do you mean?
Western warhorse!
Calm down.
If you want this deal,
Ashile Tribe will endlessly provide Youzhou
such warhorse and weapons.
What benefits can you get
by providing us with such aid?
You're quite clear about Prince Qin's strength.
Though Youzhou is important,
you can't resist for long after rebellion
even if you win for the time being.
Why not submit to Ashile Tribe
and rely on our support?
You can resist against Prince Qin,
or even fill his shoes.
It's impossible for me to listen to Yanli,
who is quite disgusting.
Stop daydreaming.
Now that you refuse,
bye.
Go.
General, shall we shoot arrows?
Follow them.
Find out where they're stationed.
Yes!
Go back and tell your General
our Tegin doesn't like his behavior.
One more step,
your head will be apart.
If you understand,
tie a white towel outside the cottage.
Then someone will contact you.
Who is it?
I'm Su Yishe, a warrior of Tegin Sun.
There's critical intelligence for Great Khan.
Eagle Tribe.
Go!
Young Khan!
Do what?
Stop!
It's my intelligence for Great Khan.
You shouldn't read it.
Give it back to me!
Why are you alone?
Where is Sun?
Did he die before I take action?
Stop daydreaming!
Nothing wrong with him!
Let me go!
I want to see Great Khan!
Take it easy.
He's quite busy.
Let me read it on his behalf.
No wonder I can't get his information.
He went to Youzhou.
I'll give it to Great Khan.
Go back to Eagle Tribe as soon as possible!
Mom.
Are you OK in the paradise?
I miss you very much.
I'll do something important tomorrow.
I can't predict success or failure.
But I have no other choice.
Even Wei family turns to Li Shimin.
I have no one to rely on.
I can only take risks.
Seal of Crown Prince
belonged to my dad.
I want to contact dad's former troops by it
to revenge for Eastern Palace.
But if you were alive,
you would have blamed me for my impulsion.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of Seal of Crown Prince.
I won't let villains get it.
You look upset.
What are you thinking about?
No.
I'm watching the moon.
Really?
I thought you're upset
because you failed to enter Governor Mansion.
You're joking.
I just passed by.
I'm just a nobody.
I dare not make friends with Governor Mansion.
Nobody?
I remember that when we met for the first time,
you were full of high spirit.
Are you really a nobody?
A'Zhun.
You're used to trusting no one, right?
You'll be tired of suspecting others.
I won't ask where you're from.
And you don't ask where I'm from.
OK?
No.
Then there's nothing to talk.
You're so stubborn.
If you don't want to tell me,
I won't ask you.
Are you getting better?
It's nothing for a man to get hurt.
Man?
Don't you feel strange that we watch the moon together?
The moon itself is a symbol of reunion.
Seeing the moon in a foreign land,
I'll think of my hometown.
That's nothing strange.
I think moonlight in Central Plains
is not better than that of grassland.
Have you been to grassland?
I just passed by in business.
Yes.
Merchants like you
must have been to many places
and seen a lot of beautiful scenery.
No wonder you looks down upon the moonlight in Youzhou.
Hope I can go to grassland
and see whether the night sky there is as beautiful as you said.
You want to see grassland?
Maybe I'll never have such opportunities.
By the way,
what's your business in Youzhou?
Is it hard to do?
It depends on fate.
I don't believe fate.
I only believe human effort.
I didn't expect that a man like you should believe in fate.
Human effort is the decisive factor?
Interesting.
You're right.
I made a slip of the tongue.
But as a merchant,
you're interested in horsemanship and archery
and are strong and vigorous.
Who's your master?
I learned on my own.
I've been bereaved since childhood.
I learn these skills just for survival.
You're quite gifted.
Unlike me, I learn from...
If you're tired,
have a rest.
No!
I can!
♫ One thought leaves a trace, eyes are filled with anger. ♫
Stand straight!
♫ Looking at the past, I want to forget each other. ♫
♫ The long ballad is silent, the long sword is not victorious. ♫
♫ Desires are endless. ♫
♫ I find myself at a loss. ♫
Stand up!
Again!
♫ No hope, no world, no image. ♫
I don't know how to repay you.
Now that the dagger is won by myself,
I should give it to you.
Yongning, you've grown up.
One day,
I'll kill my mom's murderer with this dagger.
♫ Hide the impermanence of the world. Black hair turns gray. ♫
♫ Obsession is like Epiphyllum. It's OK to forget it. ♫
Return it to me.
So mean.
You talk like a woman.
Boring.
You should eat more meat.
You're too slim.
None of your business.
Master, why haven't you...
I saw nothing.
Go on.
Thank you for accompanying me.
Master.
Why is the merchant also here?
None of your business. Go to bed.
Shisi.
In fact, the moonlight on the grassland
is not as beautiful as you think.
Your Highness.
Since you asked me to come at midnight,
What can I do for you?
Do you have any information of Changge?
Someone saw Princess Yongning
on the official road to Youzhou.
It seems that she is determined to fight me to the end.
Your Highness.
The men I sent will be in Youzhou soon.
Don't hurt her.
You treat Princess Yongning as your own daughter.
You've been teaching her carefully these years.
I witness that.
And I understand your kindness.
But Seal of Crown Prince is out of the ordinary.
Tang Dynasty's just been established.
All kinds of forces are covetous.
Princess Yongning is still young.
She's seen little of the world.
Can she really distinguish between the good and the evil
when surrounded by so many forces and deal with them properly?
If one day she is bewitched
and uses the seal to do something harmful to our country,
the consequences would be unimaginable.
Keming.
I'm tired.
You shall leave.
You know the pros and cons clearly.
Things have never been perfect since ancient times.
Hope you can be decisive.
I shall leave.
A' Dou.
This time,
I don't know whether I can come back smoothly.
If I haven't come back at dusk,
take the Seal with you
and ask A'Zhun to take you away.
That merchant?
Why?
I don't know.
I think he's trustworthy.
But...
It's my order.
Hope I won't run into you.
Any information from Chang'an?
Don't worry, Governor.
Anyway, I'll guarantee your safety.
Report!
Governor.
Someone is outside.
He said he's your old friend.
He wants to see you.
And he asked me to give it to you.
[Eastern Palace]
Governor.
Why are you frightened?
He's from Eastern Palace.
What?
As former subordinates of Prince,
this is your hospitality?
A coup happened in the Eastern Palace.
We've long been subordinated to the court.
I won't allow you to act wildly here.
Since you're from Eastern Palace,
you'd better fold your hands for capture.
I'm here to see King of Lujiang.
You have no right to see him.
I'm here to give him a way to survive.
Let me listen first.
Youzhou is abandoned and in danger.
If he doesn't lead the troops to fight against the rebels,
will he await his doom?
Nonsense!
Wait!
Be careful.
He may be a spy of the court.
So my guess is right.
You're so nervous because you're preparing to rebel.
Right?
Since you find that,
I have to kill you.
Since you want to kill me,
Yongning will die with no pity,
Yongning?
You're Yongning?
Brother Shuyu.
You shall leave.
Yes.
We're in Youzhou.
I have an idea.
Shall I first take Princess to the inn
and then meet you in Governor Mansion?
You're the envoy from Chang'an.
It's unsuitable for me to do that.
But I'm afraid that you do that not for protecting her
but keeping away from me so that you can go to see that Princess.
Why do you frame me up with no evidence?
If I don't protect her,
will you?
It doesn't matter.
Since you offer to protect me,
you have to protect me at all times and don't go away any further.
Do you agree, Envoy Wei?
OK.
Since it's the order of Princess,
that's all.
By the way, write a letter to Chang'an
to tell his Highness where Princess is
so as not to make him worried.
At this time tomorrow,
we will meet at the east gate of the city.
Shut up.
Take away all these guards
for the sake of security.
People can easily find that they're in the army.
If I take them,
they'll be noticed.
Let me take you to the inn to have a rest.
But you have to ride the horse on your own.
I must play for time.
Considering your speed, you won't arrive at the inn till night.
I'm Princess.
You must listen to me.
OK.
Just hang around on your own.
Go!
Hao Du!
Why don't you wait for me?
Hold on!
Or if you tumble off, I won't take the responsibility,
Go!
God is fair.
[Governor Mansion]
You escaped this calamity.
It's a pity that I can't resist against the enemy
with Crown Prince in Chang'an.
Now I live on in degradation.
Yongning.
Since you can turn the bad into the good,
Prince can be comforted in Heaven.
Uncle.
Yongning is gone from now on.
Just call me Changge.
I'm very sorry.
Forget it, General Wang.
Stand up.
I heard that General Wang is alert and brave.
It turns out that he's a tiger-like general.
Yongning.
Don't be afraid.
Although Prince died,
I'll protect you.
Tomorrow, I'll ask men
- to take you to...
- Uncle.
I'm here not for shelter
but to help you.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There’s always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There’s always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There’s always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There’s always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad