♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaf clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage
and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 31=
This is what
I've always pictured it in my head.
Aunty and Grandma
are taking a walk in the yard.
And the yard has been filled with
different flowers and plants.
You're here.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at
a helpless face.
That's why I asked you to come help.
Ever since
you said "let's break up" last time,
Yan Yan has been really hard on me.
I can't even
protect myself.
I haven't even said what it is yet
and you've already thought of
a bunch of reasons to put me off.
Tell me, what is it?
Here.
These are all the relevant information
on all the projects of our studio.
I've sorted them out for you
in chronological order
and in order of importance.
You just have to make sure
the project coordinators
finish their projects according to the plans.
What do you mean by this?
You're done with work?
I want to go away for a while.
Where to?
The performance of my mechanical heart
keeps getting
more and more unstable.
I'm really scared
that one day,
I might pass out in the car,
on the streets,
- or in the studio...
- Stop it.
Don't say unlucky things like that.
I don't want to hear it.
But I have to face it.
Don't worry.
I'm not
as extreme as I used to be.
I won't end my life on my own.
I just
want to use the time I have
to help others.
Such as,
helping those I love.
Chuan,
can we
not talk in this way?
It scares me.
You made it sound like a farewell message.
What would you do
if you were me?
I don't know.
You should at least
tell me where you're going.
Xiao Ning has always wanted
to rebuild her family house.
So I want to
help them fulfill this wish.
If Xiao Ning asks me,
what should I tell her?
That I don't know.
I just know that
out of everyone around me,
you're the best at lying.
Entrusting this task to you
is definitely the right choice.
I believe in you.
(Architectural design size)
Chuan.
Chuan, when are you leaving?
Not up yet.
(Take care of the studio.)
Mr. Xu.
Xiao Ning.
Where is Mr. Gu?
I didn't see his car
in the parking lot.
He's not picking up my calls either.
He left.
Where to?
You know that Gu Chuan and I
went to the same university, right?
Yes.
Our university
is holding an alumni works exhibition.
Gu Chuan is an outstanding alumni representative.
He's going to host the exhibition.
When will he be back?
He told me
to temporarily take care of company affairs.
I'm guessing it'll be a while.
One to two months.
Maybe even half a year.
I'm not sure.
It's okay.
He'll be back eventually.
Or, do you not want to be
my assistant?
No, it's all work.
It's the same for me.
Have you had breakfast?
Gu Chuan left me some breakfast
before he left.
Let's have some together.
I'm fine.
Mr. Xu,
I'll be going to the studio now.
Then I'm not having any either.
Wait for me.
Let's go together.
(We've broken up already.)
(I no longer have any hope.)
(Why leave without saying goodbye?)
(Is he trying to avoid me on purpose?)
(Does he)
(hate seeing me)
(that much?)
♪I look at you, my heart feels
as if it has been shocked♪
♪Take my hand and don't let it go♪
♪I'll follow you to the end of the world♪
♪He and she♪
♪Round and round, losing ground♪
♪Wandering Earth♪
♪Fading, wiped out♪
♪Round and round♪
♪Where the heart wants to go♪
♪The body follows♪
♪In my memory♪
♪Who is that♪
♪No, I can't sleep♪
♪Pieces piece together our encounter♪
♪I can admit♪
♪I belonged to you from that moment on♪
♪I still won't quit♪
♪Despite going off-course♪
♪The clips flashback to awake
your silhouette in the shadows♪
♪The light in your eyes shines more
and more clearly, like the light♪
Xiao Ning.
Good morning, Boss.
Morning.
What would you like to drink?
Please get me a glass of water.
Thanks.
What's up with you?
You're disappointed that it's me, right?
No, I'll go get you water.
Chuan,
you're really worrying me.
(I'm fine.)
Have you thought it through?
If we continue like this,
I'll tell Jiang Xiao Ning
everything for sure.
No matter what,
I'm never going to give up on you.
Who are you never going to give up?
Wi… Wifey.
I'm not someone
who looks through a man's phone.
But I can't let you
play me like a fool.
Wifey, what are you talking about?
You're not a fool at all.
Don't try to change the topic.
Who was it? Tell me.
It's really no one.
It's Gu Chuan.
Who are you trying to fool?
What can you two talk about?
It really is Gu Chuan.
Check my phone if you don't believe me.
See if it's his number.
What were you two talking about?
We were
just randomly chatting.
Randomly chatting about what?
I can't tell you.
You just
want to do it the hard way, huh?
Xu Cheng Ran.
Wifey.
I really can't tell you.
I can't tell you even if you beat me to death.
I mean
what kind of shameful deal
did you two make?
If I tell you,
that would make me a terrible bro.
If you don't,
you'd be a terrible husband.
Xu Cheng Ran.
What did you promise me before?
Didn't you say
that you'd never lie to me again?
Wifey. Could you not put me
in a tough spot?
Are you going to tell me?
I...
I can't.
Fine.
No need to tell me.
My wifey is so great.
I'd never do anything
to hurt you.
Pack your stuff and get out of here.
(I was worried that she wouldn't be able to face me.)
(But actually, it's me who can't face her.)
Hello?
(I'm getting married next month.)
Congratulations!
Why did you
break up with Jiang Xiao Ning?
No reason.
Just thought we weren't a good fit.
(Really?)
(Think it through.)
If you turn your back on her now, it'll be for life.
You're always like this.
You decide
everything on your own.
Why can't you face
what's going on together?
It's solely my business.
Don't stick your nose in it.
I know
I'm being nosy.
I just want
you and Jiang Xiao Ning to be happy.
If you let her pass you by like this,
I'll be sad for you.
The person who feels the saddest is me.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
When you weren't here,
we processed the data
for this.
But it hasn't been checked.
Here, check it.
Although I wasn't here these couple of days,
I didn't stop working.
I finished checking it
and made notes of mistakes
on the side.
Please check it.
(Main materials of the project equipment)
Nice. Very thorough.
You've made great progress.
Thanks, Brother Dong.
It's what I should do.
Xiao Ning,
come with me.
What is it?
Did you guys
quarrel or break up?
Was that
too blunt?
But everyone in the company
knows about you and Mr. Gu.
Something between you two
seems off these days.
There's nothing between Mr. Gu and me.
I'm just
a normal employee like you.
My position isn't even as high as yours.
Something must be going on between you two.
Look at you.
It's as if your soul has left your body.
Everyone is talking about
how an iron girl like you taking time off
is either because of a major accident or...
Just think it's because of a major accident then.
Go back to work.
It's really nothing?
Work hard.
Okay.
I'm starting to realize that
those in hiding have it easy,
while those who are left behind are about
to have a mental breakdown.
I couldn't take it and almost
told Yan Yan the truth several times.
What are you doing here?
To see you.
You've made quite a bit of progress already.
If you tell Zhao Yan,
you're seriously dead to me.
I didn't.
A big-shot designer like you
doesn't need to
worry about these tiny details.
I'll ask designers from
our company to come help you.
I can't let anyone
related to our company get involved.
I'm afraid Jiang Xiao Ning will find out.
Alright then.
Take it easy and pace yourself.
Don't rush too much.
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
I'm just scared...
Chuan,
are you okay?
Let me help you go back to rest.
Be careful.
It's too hot.
Do I need to charge you now?
No.
These days, it
occasionally malfunctions.
Hurts a lot.
Go back with me.
What good does going back do?
No difference between being here and going back.
Resting at home
will at least be a little better.
Have you gotten Xiao Ning to sign the will?
Not yet.
Are you sure about this?
Don't let her find out
what those are.
Otherwise, she'd definitely come looking for me.
Everything I've done so far
would be for nothing.
Alright. Go back.
The earlier everything gets settled,
the more at ease I'll be.
Go.
I'll leave then.
Take care of yourself.
Call me if anything happens.
Okay.
Xiao Ning.
I'm downstairs.
Can you come down?
Brother Xu.
Long time no see.
How are things between you and Gu Chuan?
Why are you bringing him up all of a sudden?
Is Gu Chuan really that great?
To you...
I seem pretty useless.
Brother Xu, don't say that.
When we were kids, you always
fought back for me when I got bullied.
When I wanted candy,
you bought me candy.
For my birthday every year,
you'd give me
really pretty presents.
I remember everything.
I've always thought of you as my own big brother.
You're a part of our family too.
So you won't develop feelings for me
and fall in love with me, right?
You're so exceptional.
Given everything about you,
you'll definitely find me
a super perfect sister-in-law.
I'll be waiting,
waiting for the day you have that
silly smile on your face.
Xiao Ning.
To be honest,
it's really nice to still
be able to chat with you like this.
I thought you were
never going to talk to me again.
No way.
You're my big brother.
Have you eaten?
Aunty says we're having dumplings.
Come have some with us.
I'd love to,
but I'm scared that Aunty will kill me.
I'll protect you.
Really?
Let's go.
Do you like it?
Here.
You have some too.
Mom.
Why is this actor showing up again?
Doesn't he know that
he's not welcomed?
Not welcomed, not welcomed.
Both Grandma and I don't like him.
It's okay. Just eat.
I don't like him.
Aunty, you don't have to say that much.
Aunty,
come and have some.
There were only 15 dumplings.
And I made all those for you.
There's nothing left for me.
I'm full. You should have some.
Brother Xu, Aunty is joking.
Aunty, I'm hungry.
Sit. It's okay.
Eat.
I made these this afternoon.
Thank you, Aunty.
I miss the red cooking you make the most.
Look at you talking nonsense.
I thought you
didn't like quail eggs when you were little.
How come you like them now?
I was too young.
I grew up now.
You become a sweet talker now.
Really?
I thought he was already a sweet talker
when he was little.
Who is this?
How come he looks so familiar.
Grandma,
Do you remember Brother Tang Xu?
I do. I do.
He always gets first place in exams.
So you remember that.
You should come to my place to eat.
Ning Ning,
learn from him.
But don't stay for too long.
If you can't finish your homework,
you'll be scolded.
Got it.
Come, Grandma.
Let's watch TV together.
Come on, let's go.
Brother Xu, take your time.
I will.
Nice.
This kid is so good at studying.
The TV show is pretty interesting.
Aunty,
I actually visited here a lot.
I've always wanted to come up,
but I was afraid.
I was afraid that you'll be unhappy to see me.
After all, my father...
Alright. Stop.
I'm warning you once again.
Don't bring
the old things up again.
I understand.
It's between the elders.
You have nothing to do with it.
Grandma and I
are just mad at your father.
We're mad that he embezzled the funds
and got my brother involved.
But he is gone for more than ten years.
Why bring it up?
I know
what you're thinking.
I have everything
that you've given me
written down in a notebook.
Aunty,
you don't have to give anything back.
I'm not asking for anything.
So you want me to give them back?
I'll have to be able to afford it.
But I can't afford it.
But,
to be honest,
we're reasonable people.
We know
who treats us well
and who doesn't.
I don't hold
a grudge against you.
And
I shouldn't.
As long as
you're still treating Xiao Ning well
like you did before.
Treat her as your own sister.
I'll treat you like I did before.
Come up if you ever visit.
Don't stand downstairs by yourself
and make things look weird.
Neighbors are gossiping.
Understood. Thank you, Aunty.
Not enough to eat, right?
Let me make some more.
Eat.
Lao Jiang,
I'm finally here to see you.
Even though
I've been out for days,
I was afraid to visit you.
(Grave of Late Father Jiang Guang Da and Late Mother Shen Si Lan)
I'm ashamed to visit you.
But I can't run away from it any longer.
Even if I avoid visiting you now,
we might see each other
on the other side
after I die.
So I'm here shamelessly
to visit you, my brother and my sister-in-law.
Lao Jiang,
this toast is to you two.
We haven't been
drinking together in decades.
I'm going to drink too.
Uncle Tang.
Xiao Ning,
why are you here?
I meant,
do you not have to work today?
It's the weekend.
What was I thinking?
Come.
Uncle Tang.
Thank you for visiting my parents.
None of my dad's past co-workers
came to visit,
ever.
You're the first one.
Don't thank me.
I should have come
a lot earlier.
What kind of person
do you think my dad was?
Your dad is
the kindest
and the most honest person I've ever met.
Do you think he would be
someone who would embezzle public funds?
You can tell me when you've thought about it.
What's up, Xiao Ning?
Mr. Xu.
I didn't know you were still here.
I thought someone forgot to turn off the lights.
You're just in time.
I have something to talk to you about.
Sit.
I heard from Gu Chuan that
you've been working
as an intern.
But your internship has already ended
a long time ago.
Although your payroll has changed,
the company
has not officially processed it.
Is that right?
Even though Gu Chuan is good at designing,
he's terrible at managing a company.
He has too much on his plate.
Plus, I already got my pay raise.
I didn't care
about the official process.
That's not okay.
We have to be professional when it
comes to managing a company.
Sign these documents.
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
Xiao Ning,
Gu Chuan
didn't attend the open class.
Where did he go?
Did something happen?
Is he okay?
He's fine. He's good.
He went on vacation.
I don't understand
this person.
He said he wanted to find a place
where he can't see you
to find some peace.
He can go anywhere
he wants to go, as long as he's happy.
I don't want him to
get annoyed by seeing me.
Last time we talked over the phone
and he told me something even worse.
What did he say?
He said that
he won't come back
if he finds a girl there.
He really said that?
I think so.
I was a little drunk,
so I can't remember clearly.
This is the last document.
Sign it.
(Successor: Jiang Xiao Ning)
Good. Everything has been signed.
Thank you.
Mr. Xu.
If you have any news of Gu Chuan...
I will let you know immediately.
Thank you, Mr. Xu.
I'll leave then.
Please forgive me, Chuan.
She won't sign
if I don't lie to her like this.
(Am I this annoying to him?)
(Then why should I still stay here?)
(I should resign.)
Check this out.
You'll see a garden
after you enter.
The living room is inside.
We built a balcony
on the second floor.
It follows
the design you gave us.
You can rest assured.
Let me answer this call first.
Cool.
Hello?
Chuan.
I finally made her sign
with the help of a little lie.
When should I bring them to you?
Can you keep them?
I'm afraid that if something happens,
I won't have time to handle everything.
Don't say things like this,
alright?
I'll keep them for you temporarily.
I'll bring them to you
when I go see you.
Thank you.
You don't need to thank me.
Thank you for taking care of me
and tolerating me all these years.
Nonsense.
I'm going to hang up.
I got things to do.
♪The rims of my eyes eventually turned red♪
♪I have so many things to say♪
♪There's no need to say them out loud,
let them be secrets♪
♪Let them become eternity♪
♪The box is full of our past memories♪
♪It's heavy enough to defy the passage of time♪
♪That energetic boy is riding in the car♪
♪With the pinky promises we made♪
♪The person I used to love so much♪
Wifey,
I miss you so much.
I have something to tell you.
♪I'll stay right here and wait for you to come back♪
Didn't you say that you
have something to tell me?
How many cans have you drunk?
Let me drink more.
Otherwise, I don't know
how I should start.
I don't understand.
Is there anything
you can't tell me?
Wifey,
I want to tell you about
Gu Chuan and me.
Do you want to hear it?
Of course.
Gu Chuan and I
were in the same year in university,
but we were in different majors.
However, I had heard of him long before that.
People said that
there's a genius
in our university.
Being just in his second year,
he had already won all the university-level
awards in his field.
I was curious.
I thought
who could be that smart?
Can he really outsmart me?
So I went to check him out.
I wanted to see
what kind of person he is.
He was
even weirder than he is now.
He was so cold
and refused to let other people into his life.
I was so interested in him.
I mean it.
I pestered him
like how I pestered you.
It took me half a semester
to become friends with him.
And then one day when I was chatting with him,
I said to him
"Chuan,
everything is good about you.
Except for that you always pull a long face,
showing no emotions and acting like a dead person.
You can't create any designs
with love being like that.
Then I found out that
the youngest triple
Grand Slam winner
in the field of design,
my best friend, Gu Chuan,
cannot
live like a normal person at all.
He died once.
He was in a car accident
and had to get a mechanical heart.
You're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
What mechanical heart?
Just talk about Gu Chuan.
Don't make it like a sci-fi movie.
It's the truth.
The mechanical heart
is also a global limited edition.
That thing tortures him every day.
It makes a lot of noise when it's working.
It has to be charged every day.
An abnormally high heart rate would
cause electric discharge,
which will hurt the people around him.
That's why
he lives
with no emotion.
Does Xiao Ning know?
Jiang Xiao Ning knew about it.
I'm thankful to her.
Before her, Gu Chuan was afraid
of dating other people.
He was afraid that
he won't be able to make others happy.
He finally lived like a human for the first time
after he met Jiang Xiao Ning.
Why did he still
date Jiang Xiao Ning
if he can't be with anyone?
Wifey.
You know what?
Gu Chuan.
Gu Chuan will die soon.
What do you mean?
The doctor who did research on mechanical hearts
suddenly passed away not long ago.
Gu Chuan's heart
cannot hold on any longer.
And no one can
repair and maintain it.
Isn't that just frustrating?
They say that these things are high-tech,
but they can't even perform automatic upgrades.
So you're saying that
Gu Chuan can die anytime?
He's already preparing for
his funeral arrangements.
He even made a will.
Besides his parents,
he left a part of his inheritance
to Jiang Xiao Ning.
He really loves Jiang Xiao Ning.
His mechanical heart
has been having a lot of problems.
And he won't rest at home.
You know what he's doing?
He's been leaving early and
going home late recently
to fix
Jiang Xiao Ning's family house.
Yan Yan,
Gu Chuan is my best, best,
best friend.
But I can only
watch him die
and I can't do anything about it.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪