♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone,
but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark,
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 35=
Are you sure Hao Tian Soul Master is
behind Cang Hui School?
Shi Nian has always said so.
But in fact, no one has ever seen him.
Who does Shi Nian usually contact?
Who is his superior?
I think I remember an instance
where he was talking
to a lump of black smoke.
I got closer to have a look,
but I wasn't able to see
who he was talking with.
Let's consider our next move
after we arrive in Martial Soul City
and see Hao Tian Soul Master.
If, by any chance,
the person behind Cang Hui School
is indeed your father,
what will you do?
I wish he wouldn't do such things.
However,
if it is really him,
I will stop him from going down the wrong path.
My father has especially prepared
a horse carriage
for us.
This carriage has
great shock absorption performance.
We'll ride in comfort
all the way to Martial Soul City.
We can take a rest and get prepared.
I have sent away the horse carriage
sent by Chief Ning yesterday.
We will go to Martial Soul City on foot.
There is no time left for training
before the final.
Master intends
to use this opportunity
to improve your stamina.
Headmaster has agreed with us.
It can't be.
Where is my master?
He flew there in advance.
He will arrive before us.
He will get in touch in advance
with the people from Martial Soul Hall.
Teacher Liu and I will lead the group.
Let's get going.
We still have a long journey ahead.
Set off!
You learn it fast.
Teacher Liu.
Take a rest.
-Thank you.
Are you tired?
♪The youth rides a horse♪
Where are the others?
They went to the mountain
to gather some wild fruits.
Is there anything that we can help with?
Both of you...
We don't seem to have
enough firewood for the night.
How about this?
Both of you go to the mountain
and take some firewood back.
All right.
No problem.
Let's go.
All right.
Be careful.
Okay!
Got it.
You must come back before nightfall.
Got it!
♪Have the belief to save the day♪
♪Go on a great adventure♪
Give it to me.
Thank you.
Here.
♪Overlook the sky♪
♪The light is so brilliant♪
We went on adventures like this in the past.
♪The dream is burning in my chest♪
A long time ago.
Will you go to see her
when we get to Martial Soul City?
♪Despite all the difficulties♪
She is
the chief of Martial Soul Hall now.
There's no point in meeting her.
You're not the kind of person
who would feel inferiority
because of your status.
It's not about inferiority.
It's about different choices.
How is it different?
It's simple.
When I was with Bi Bi Dong,
she was already a genius in Martial Soul Hall.
As for me...
Well, you know.
The useless guy
who couldn't get past Triple Soul Rings.
So?
Who separated you two?
Afterwards, I suddenly got news of her marriage.
She was not marrying me,
but the former Chief Qian Xun Ji.
Did you not know anything beforehand?
I didn't.
I wanted to see Bi Bi Dong
and talk things through.
But she wouldn't give me
a chance to meet her again.
It's normal.
Martial Soul Hall
offered a bright future for her.
So she chose a better future.
I can understand.
She has succeeded to the position
of the chief of Martial Soul Hall
and become the Greatest Soul Master.
I think that she made
the wrong choice.
♪The wind whizzes past my face♪
♪The rain drenches my shoulders♪
♪Despite all the difficulties♪
♪I have a fire in my heart♪
Hong Jun.
Come and take a look.
There are a lot of wild vegetables.
Go over there and pick some.
There. Over there.
Go on.
I don't see any wild vegetables around.
Rong Rong,
this is for you.
I made it myself.
You fool.
♪Every ordinary moment♪
♪The years leave marks on the face♪
♪Rage not for tomorrow♪
♪Only hold on for friendship♪
♪Get through the sea of clouds♪
♪Get the wind and clouds moving♪
♪Looking light years away♪
♪To seek the memory of the former life♪
♪Keep the smile after the threat♪
♪No one can stop our vow♪
♪Join hands and look at the world♪
♪Overlook the sky♪
♪The light is so brilliant♪
♪The dream is burning in my chest♪
I once kissed you
when I was little.
♪The rain drenches my shoulders♪
But after going through so much,
I think...
I was right to kiss you.
♪The wind and clouds may hide the light♪
♪The youth still goes on his adventure♪
Wu.
What are you planning to do after the final?
After the final...
♪Look at the world♪
I want to travel across Douluo Continent.
I want to see more landscapes,
and find more interesting Soul Masters to fight.
♪The dream is burning in my chest♪
The two of us together?
♪The rain drenches my shoulders♪
Of course, we'll be together.
We won't be separated.
You promised me.
♪I have a fire in my heart♪
They haven't arrived yet?
The other four have all arrived.
Only Shi Lan Ke has yet to arrive.
Martial Soul Hall reception
has a schedule to follow.
The other four can enter the city first.
We'll wait here.
You'll wait?
What about the arrangements
for student registration?
Who will fill up the participant's forms?
You can enter the city first
and deal with the procedures.
I'll wait for Dai Mu Bai and the others.
You'll wait?
Who are you...
The...
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
So who am I?
Pardon me.
The Crown Prince of Tian Dou Empire
also comes to Martial Soul City?
He should have other business here.
The chief has issued an order
to allow him to enter the city.
She issued an order
for the Crown Prince of Tian Dou Empire?
Yes.
It looks like the relationship
between Tian Dou Empire
and Martial Soul Hall
has become closer.
Yes.
How about this?
You enter the city first
and deal with the procedures.
I'll wait
for your students.
All right.
Greetings to the Chief.
Report to the Chief.
I have successfully
completed my mission.
And the results
are better than what I expected.
I'm sure you've known about this.
I have successfully replaced Xue Qing He.
Once the contest is finished,
I can go back to Tian Dou
and inherit the throne.
I know.
Initially,
my plan after leaving Martial Soul Hall
was to go to Shi Lan Ke School
and replace the Prince of Xing Luo, Dai Mu Bai.
But then I found out
that he has a powerful brother
named Dai Wei Shi.
The two brothers
are at odds with each other.
Dai Mu Bai is at a disadvantage.
He won't be able to inherit the throne.
Therefore,
I changed my plan
and chose Xue Qing He.
I know.
Chief.
Given the current situation,
I have another plan in mind.
We can
combine the power
of Martial Soul Hall and Tian Dou
to invade Xing Luo.
We can build up Martial Soul Empire
to dominate the world!
Enough!
I don't need you to tell me
what to do!
For the sake of Martial Soul Hall,
I wandered around
by myself.
I struggled hard and grew up alone.
Yes, I admit
I was willful at first.
I insisted on changing the plan.
But after all this time,
how could you dismiss
all my efforts
just because you don't need them?
Or perhaps,
all the efforts
and sacrifices I have made
for Martial Soul Hall
are worthless in your eyes?
I meant
you don't need to make these efforts.
But why?
Do you know
how many times I almost died
out there?
Had it not been
for Tang San who saved me,
you would have seen
a corpse now!
That Tang San...
I heard that he is gifted.
So, in your eyes,
whether I am dead
or alive
matters less than an outsider.
Is that right?
Do not forget your identity.
Yes. Teacher.
How many Soul Rings does Tang San have?
He is a Soul Sect.
He killed
a Decade Millennium Soul Beast
to get the Fourth Soul Ring.
Decade Millennium Demon Fox?
Go and advance to the Fourth Soul Ring.
This place seems
to be bigger than Tian Dou City.
Why is he the only one here?
Did we arrive early?
Why is the Grand Chrysanthemum Master here?
He is
the tournament host
sent by Martial Soul Hall to Tian Dou?
Right.
He was the one
who knocked out all of us that night.
Should we
do some tricks on him?
It's an eye for an eye.
You fool.
He is a Grand Soul Land Master
with Nine Soul Rings.
We might not be able to defeat him
even with all of our power combined.
A Grand Soul Land Master with Nine Soul Rings?
You've seen the Greatest City.
How is it? Are you thinking
of asking me to be your master?
Were you waiting here just to say that?
Tang San, come with me.
Why should he?
Someone wants to see him.
Who?
I'm afraid I can't tell you.
Then we can't do what you want.
This is Martial Soul City.
Everyone here
knows that Tang San leaves with me.
I will be responsible
if something happens to him.
Can you tell me
who wants to see me now?
The chief.
Why does she want
to see me personally?
Why don't you ask her yourself?
Does he have family members?
His wife, Bi Bi Dong, is the current chief.
And his daughter, Qian Ren Xue.
Why?
You want to take revenge on them?
But they have nothing
to do with your mother's death.
Qian Xun Ji was the mastermind.
When he tried to kill my mother,
did he ever think about her child
and her husband?
One day,
if I really meet
those people from Martial Soul Hall,
I...
I really can't guarantee
that I will act rationally.
Tang San.
Hatred shouldn't be spread.
You shouldn't hate everyone
from Martial Soul Hall because of this.
Your mother would not wish
to see you live in hatred forever, would she?
Telling you the truth
doesn't mean I want you to take revenge.
On the contrary,
I hope that you won't have hatred in your heart.
You have your own mission and your path.
Don't be blinded by hatred
and let it ruin your life.
No way.
I have to remember my mother's words.
I mustn't be rash.
-I mustn't be rash...
-You will see the Chief
as you go up this way.
Are you not going in?
I'll wait for you here.
Hu Lie Na?
Show me your Soul Ring.
Soul Ring?
It really
is the Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
Didn't the chief want to see me?
Why is it only you here?
A Decade Millennium Soul Ring?
How can it be?
This doesn't make sense!
Isn't yours also
the Decade Millennium Soul Ring?
It was an exception
that I could absorb
the Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
What you can do,
Martial Soul Hall can do it as well.
See you in the arena.
Are you a member
of Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team?
In the contest this time,
the champion can only be
Martial Soul Hall.
So, you guys organize the contest
to oppress all Soul Master Schools
in Douluo Continent?
You're leaving like this?
Didn't the Chief want to meet me?
Where is she?
Tang San.
You are the chief of Martial Soul Hall?
You...
What happened?
Why is my Martial Soul out of control?
Blue Silver Plant?
What else?
I don't understand.
Why is the chief
so interested in Tang San?
Because of the Decade Millennium Soul Ring?
It has been proven
that she can do such a miracle too.
The Chief's wisdom is as profound as the sea.
To be honest, I can't
tell what she's thinking either.
If you want to see my Martial Soul,
just tell me.
There's no need to make a move yourself.
There should be more.
Twin Martial Souls. Hao Tian Hammer.
You're Tang Hao's son.
You should know
that your mother's Martial Soul
is Blue Silver Plant.
Therefore,
Twin Martial Souls
are your parents' gift to you.
Did you go after my parents as well?
Are you related to her death?
The former chief
was heavily injured and eventually died
because of your father.
Do you think
I should kill you now?
Hide your Hao Tian Hammer well.
Do not let anyone see it
during the contest.
What do you mean?
Back then,
I was not involved in pursuing your mother.
Who else was involved?
Right now, you don't have the right to know.
If I am able to survive,
I will pursue the matter to the end.
You can leave now.
See you in the arena.
Martial Soul Hall
has arranged the lodging
for every Soul Master.
It's huge.
This way, please.
I think I have an idea
about who wanted to see him.
That's why I'm worried.
Although nothing will happen
in Martial Soul City,
we still can't let our guard down.
How about this?
You take them there.
I'll go back and check it out.
-All right.
-I'm going with you.
Don't worry.
With me here, Tang San will be fine.
Wu.
Martial Soul City is huge.
You have to stay together with everyone.
If you get lost,
Tang San will be worried.
She's right.
Besides, I've also given him
the emergency fireworks.
If there is an emergency,
we'll use Rocketing Kiwi
and fly over there immediately.
All right.
Let's go.
I'll take you to the lodging.
Let me do it instead.
I know him, after all.
You've returned as well.
The school representatives
from Xing Luo have all arrived.
Go and report it.
Let's chat later.
Let's go.
I'll show you around Martial Soul City.
You've returned.
The school representatives
from Xing Luo Empire
have arrived.
So they've all arrived.
This is the schedule for the final.
Who was that person?
He is the Grand Ghost Master.
One of the Grand Soul Land Masters.
Another one with Nine Soul Rings?
He and the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
are very good friends.
He appeared
and disappeared in an instant.
But it didn't seem like Teleport.
His Martial Soul is called the Ghost.
Allegedly, it can
travel through the interspace.
The chief once mentioned
that this type of Martial Soul
is most suited for assassination.
Do you remember...
Remember what?
Can we find a quiet place to talk?
My room is just ahead.
This is my room.
It's safe.
No one else knows about it.
Have a seat.
What did you want to talk about?
Do you remember Su Yun Tao's death?
In the Star Forest?
Master saw the murderer.
I'm sure he has told you
about the person's characteristics, right?
He's dead.
What did you say?
I saw him being killed in the Star Forest
with my own eyes.
Nonsense.
Who killed him?
It was a black shadow.
Didn't you also say
that the murderer was very likely
to be someone from Martial Soul Hall?
Why are you looking at me like that?
You suspect
the Grand Soul Land Master
of Martial Soul Hall
just because of a vague black shadow?
When Master was in the Star Forest,
he saw the murderer
meeting with Azure Bull Python.
The murderer was meeting
with Azure Bull Python in the Star Forest.
The King of Star Forest?
The murderer must have
killed Su Yun Tao
to silence him.
But the question is
that the black shadow's face couldn't be seen.
How could Su Yun Tao expose the secret meeting?
Are you suspecting the Grand Ghost Master?
This is impossible.
Why is it impossible?
Do you remember your speculation?
You mean
the murderer was very likely
to be someone Su Yun Tao was familiar with?
Yes.
It's the only reason to kill Su Yun Tao.
How could Su Yun Tao
have recognized that person's identity
from a black shadow alone?
Unless he's very familiar with the murderer.
Su Yun Tao had no family member.
He has always lived in Martial Soul Hall.
If the murderer was someone he was familiar with,
it's very likely
to be someone from Martial Soul Hall.
Not only that,
but Master also witnessed
how the black smoke turned into a human form.
The time has come.
Have you made up your mind?
The conflicts between humans
have nothing to do with me.
What do you think?
Don't you think it's familiar?
Martial Soul Hall
is not your Shi Lan Ke School.
Don't go around without permission.
I want to see Bi Bi Dong.
You called the Chief by name.
Even the emperors of the two empires
dare not be so rude.
Let him in.
Get back to work.
Judging from the characteristics
of the Martial Soul,
he seems to be the murderer.
I think there is another possibility.
Tell me.
Didn't you always say
that the Grand Soul Land Master behind Cang Hui
had ulterior motives?
Wouldn't it be possible
that he disguised himself
as the Grand Ghost Master
and killed Su Yun Tao?
This idea of yours is groundless.
So is yours.
If you suspect Cang Hui,
why don't you ask them yourself?
Cang Hui is alert against Martial Soul Hall.
But it is open
towards Shi Lan Ke School.
You can observe them secretly.
And tell me
if you find anything odd.
Why should I help Martial Soul Hall?
We can discuss
the payment.
Back then,
I was not involved in pursuing your mother.
Who else was involved?
Right now, you don't have the right to know.
Does Martial Soul Hall
have any yearly activity records
that can be checked?
Yes.
They're usually kept
in Martial Soul City's library.
All right. I promise you.
I'll help you investigate Cang Hui.
In exchange, you let me enter the library
to check the archives from that year.
Which year?
Around ten years ago.
For what?
If you can't give me
a reasonable explanation,
I won't let you check them out.
I want to find out the relationship
between my master and your chief.
My master and your chief
once had a relationship.
You are here.
You called me Bi Bi Dong.
If it weren't for you,
I'd have almost forgotten this name.
Tang San is my pupil.
I have to protect him.
Then, do you know
that he is Tang Hao's son?
You knew it.
But you didn't plan to tell me.
Where is he?
I let him go back.
Did you really let him go?
Am I that narrow-minded
in your heart?
I spoke rashly.
I won't disturb you any longer.
If it weren't for Tang San,
would you have come to see me?
You're the chief of Martial Soul Hall now.
I'm just an ordinary school teacher.
Do I have the right to see you?
I told you before.
Your brain is the most precious treasure.
Sometimes, I wonder...
what if
we didn't miss it.
There are no "what ifs" in this world.
But some regrets
can be mended.
I believe in your capabilities.
You're the best teacher in Douluo Continent.
With your help,
we can let
Martial Soul Hall rise.
I will let everyone
know your name.
Time has changed everything.
It's all in the past.
Do you understand?
Have you ever grieved
over what happened in the past?
The paths that we chose
were going to be different anyway.
You said that you would
let everyone know my name.
I don't need it.
Bi Bi Dong.
The things that we want are different.
Our paths will never cross.
Certain things...
should just stay in memory.
Take this.
With it, you'll be able
to look up the archives from that year.
I'll help you to keep an eye
on Cang Hui School.
Remember to give it back to me once you're done.
Got it.
Xie Yue?
Why are you here?
Who is he?
It's none of your business.
Go.
How dare you?
You gave him
your Martial Soul Token?
I just lent it to him.
What right does he have
to take your Martial Soul Token?
Return it to her.
I'm only borrowing the token temporarily.
And you already intend to hurt me?
Consider yourself lucky that you're not dead.
Don't hide behind a woman if you have guts.
Enough.
You go first.
If you want to stay and fight him,
then return the token to me.
The chief has said
that personal duels are not
allowed before the contest.
Tell me your name and school.
Tang San, Shi Lan Ke School.
Xie Yue,
Captain of Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team.
Remember this name.
If I see you in the arena,
I'll crush you with my own hands.
How could you guys
choose a lunatic to be the captain?
You'll have a miserable death.
Tang San!
Master.
Why are you here?
I was looking for you.
It's good that you're fine.
Let's go back to the lodging.
All right.
-Which way?
-You don't know?
Master, this is my first time coming
to Martial Soul Hall.
I did come here before.
But this place has been expanded.
It's quite different now.
So... we're lost?
Theoretically speaking, yes.
We'll find a way out somehow.
Let's try this way.
What are you doing?
You seem to be in trouble.
Please give us orders.
We are at your service.
The token on your hand
has the authority to mobilize
various resources in Martial Soul Hall.
Can I enter the library with this?
Of course.
Did Hu Lie Na give this to you?
Yes.
I didn't expect
the chief's disciple
to have such an authority.
It can't be.
As far as I know, the hierarchy
in Martial Soul Hall is very strict.
It's impossible
for her to have this authority
by just being the chief's disciple.
This is almost equivalent
to the authority granted
to a Grand Soul Land Master.
But Hu Lie Na only has Quadruple Soul Rings.
This road is way too narrow.
Perhaps...
Martial Soul Hall isn't that rich to fix the roads?
It's hard to walk on this road.
I can fly freely in the air.
How about we just fly there?
Lower your voice, will you?
We have to keep a low profile.
Tang San was immediately
called away when we arrived.
Probably,
someone is plotting against us.
The participating battle teams are not
allowed to engage in personal fights.
He attacked first.
I heard that you
have Quadruple Soul Rings now.
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪