♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 34=
Theatrical club.
The three largest theatrical clubs
in Tian Dou City.
Don't you know?
Never mind.
It's a famous theatrical club anyway.
But why does the Prince
want to buy a theatrical club?
It's for Ou Si Ke.
Does he like theatrical clubs a lot?
That's his biggest dream.
My grandfather asked around
and found that Prince Xue Xing
wants to buy Starry Theatrical Club
in exchange for Ou Si Ke to quit Shi Lan Ke.
Grandfather wants me to tell you
that if you need our help
to control Ou,
just let us know.
It's fine.
This is a good thing.
What do you mean?
How is that a good thing?
Ou Si Ke must be very happy
to take over the theatrical club.
But the condition is
that he has to quit the contest.
He is going to quit anyway.
Why?
So Ou Si Ke got a theatrical club for free.
The Prince is such a nice person.
Isn't such a famous theatrical club
very expensive?
It's not that expensive actually.
The Soul Masters are the most important
in Douluo Continent.
Other forms of entertainment
don't really matter.
No, I mean...
You don't care
about Ou Si Ke taking over the theatrical club?
Why should I care?
Isn't that considered betrayal?
How is that betrayal?
Don't you want to enter the final?
How can he quit now?
What I want to do is my own business.
Ou Si Ke has no obligation
to fight for me at all.
Moreover,
if I stop Ou Si Ke from chasing his dream
and keep him in the arena
for my own goal,
isn't that making him my slave?
Tai Long,
we need to respect our partners.
So I don't have to stalk Ou Si Ke?
No.
I support
his decision.
If you don't believe me,
I can bring you to Starry Theatrical Club.
Everybody is waiting for you there.
How did you know I like arts?
I'm the Prince.
It's not hard for me
to investigate a little school.
In that case, what should I do?
Leave Shi Lan Ke
and revive Starry Theatrical Club.
It's simple.
Prince, you put in a lot of effort
just to make me leave Shi Lan Ke
and quit the contest?
Such a trivial theatrical club
is not a big deal for me.
But seriously,
I never imagined
I would have the chance
to become the owner of Starry Theatrical Club.
I...
Your dream will come true once you sign it.
These are the contents of the tactics
that you guys need to work on.
You don't have to memorize everything now.
Just a brief understanding would do.
Ou Si Ke, you're back.
Did you buy the stuff?
Where's Chief Ning?
My dad has already departed to Martial Soul City.
Has the final not started yet?
He said he wanted to go earlier
and see whether he could find
something fishy in the contest.
What's the matter?
Are you looking for him?
I have something to tell you guys.
You must stay calm
after listening to me.
What's wrong?
Prince Xue Xing came
to see me in person.
What happened then?
That's it.
This is not a big deal.
Why do you want us to stay calm?
No. Don't you get it?
Prince Xue Xing came
to see me in person.
You know...
He always goes against us.
We already know that.
Then,
he gave me an ownership transfer letter.
He said he wanted to give me
an incredible theatrical club.
That's the theatrical club
that I've always wanted.
Maybe...
You guys can never imagine
how great that theatrical club is.
Starry Theatrical Club.
One of the three largest theatrical clubs
in Tian Dou City, right?
How did you know that?
Did you accept it?
Of course...
I did not accept it.
Why?
Can I betray Shi Lan Ke?
How is this betrayal?
Besides, you were supposed to quit in the first place.
The theatrical club is a present
from the Prince.
I want to stay here.
Aren't arts your dream?
That's right.
I'm an orphan.
Headmaster found me
and has raised me since childhood.
Since young, I've always hoped
that I could have a very powerful Martial Soul.
But I became like this
after it had awakened.
The Food Branch Martial Soul is very powerful.
Every time I used my Martial Soul,
I would dress like a chef,
carrying the bucket
and giving out sausages.
Everybody made fun of me back then.
Eventually,
I didn't want
to show my Martial Soul.
I even started to fear
and hate my Martial Soul.
As for arts,
they should be my consolation
after I fell into despair.
But I know very clearly
that I still want to be a Soul Master.
I want to shine bright
as a Soul Master
in the Soul Arena.
You've already done it.
That's right.
It seems
that I've already done it.
But you know?
Every time I take part in a competition
together with you guys,
my heart melts a little!
Every time,
it'll melt a little.
I like
the feeling
of fighting alongside you all.
I...
I think
as long as the seven of us are together,
no matter what hardship we face,
no matter how tough it is,
we can overcome it.
So...
please let me stay
to fight alongside you.
All right?
Have faith in me.
I will never disappoint you.
Good luck.
Good luck!
It's still him alone?
Perhaps,
the other members are insignificant.
He might be the only one in Cang Hui School
who can fight.
We should be prepared,
in case all the members
from Cang Hui School
come in an ambush.
The leader of each team,
please come on stage
to draw the rules.
Finally, you got a mixed battle.
The rules are simple.
Both teams may dispatch
all fighters that can fight,
until one team is completely defeated.
A mixed battle.
Master, is there anything you want to remind us of?
Only the top four can enter the final.
The safest way to get to Martial Soul City
is to win
all the upcoming battles.
Yes.
Let's defeat them all!
-Defeat them all!
-All right.
Defeat them all!
Let's go!
It's a mixed battle.
You stand alone?
It's enough.
How arrogant.
We can start now.
You ate Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum before?
What does it have to do with the battle?
Answer my question.
I ate one.
That's great.
I thought Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum
became extinct.
How about this?
I'll take you as my pupil.
I'm not interested.
My Soul Skill is special.
Only Soul Masters
who consumed Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum
can fully perform the skill.
For all these years,
I've only come across
one such Soul Master, you.
I said I'm not interested.
Are we going to fight the battle?
That's fine.
We can talk
after the competition ends.
Then,
the battle starts now.
Put out your Soul Power.
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
The third variation of the guerrilla tactic,
exploratory contact.
I surrender.
What did he say?
Cang Hui School surrenders.
Shi Lan Ke School wins.
I...
What is going on?
Why did he surrender?
What are they trying to do?
Why do you think
Ye Zhi Qiu chose to surrender?
How is that even a question?
He was fighting against all of us by himself.
He might be afraid.
His Martial Soul is strange.
Even if he was fighting us all by himself,
he would still have a chance.
But we've found out
the truth behind his Martial Soul.
He was bound to lose in this battle.
But he didn't know that we had found out
the truth behind his Martial Soul.
You got a point.
Anyway, he surrendered.
It's a good thing that we won.
He's here.
Let's talk in private.
Be careful, Brother San.
Don't worry.
What are they talking about?
Dai Mu Bai.
Why did you surrender?
Because you guys defeated
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad.
You did well.
What kind of reason is that?
Teacher Shi Nian has expectations for you guys
and has decided to let you enter the final.
In order to enter the final,
you have to be in the top four.
You guys have already lost one battle,
so you can't lose the battle today.
So this battle
was a gift for us?
Work harder from now on,
and fight for the top four.
What's next then?
What do I have to do after we enter the final?
He will look for you
after you arrive in Martial Soul City.
You surrendered.
Don't you fear that Cang Hui School
will not make it to the top four?
I'll see you at the final.
Are you done talking?
What's the matter?
That guy insisted to take me as his pupil.
He said
I might be the only one
in Dou Luo Continent
who had eaten Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum.
Did you agree?
Of course not.
I have my school and teachers.
He's a Grand Soul Land Master.
If it were you, would you agree?
What did you two talk about?
Cang Hui School surrendered on purpose.
He said he wanted us to enter the final.
Why?
We'll know after we arrive in Martial Soul City.
Uncle.
You even want to kill the Crown Prince for fun?
I suspect that your spirit
has been controlled by Martial Soul Hall.
Spirit control?
How is that possible?
Look at me.
Do I look like my spirit is being controlled?
I'm sure that you know
I have been against Shi Lan Ke.
It's just a school.
It's not important.
So what if I know?
You helped them once.
What's wrong with that?
I watched you grow.
Though you're the Crown Prince,
you are pedantic and stubborn.
I know your personality.
You would have stopped
my action against Shi Lan Ke,
but you did nothing.
Uncle,
you're suspecting me
just because of this?
I can see a lot from a small thing.
Focusing on the details makes it easier
to detect anomalies.
I suspect that your behavior
has long been controlled
by Martial Soul Hall.
Perhaps,
the person who is controlling you
is right inside!
Uncle, if you don't believe me,
come in to see for yourself.
Uncle, my house is small.
It can't hold so many people.
All of you stay here.
Go in to arrest him if you hear anything.
Yes!
This is the secret in my house.
Are you satisfied, Uncle?
You're fake!
I wanted to disguise myself perfectly.
I didn't expect that I couldn't pass the first test.
So it's right that I didn't show up.
By the way,
Uncle, you're really hard to deal with.
Guards!
We're surrounded instead.
I can't believe
you really want to harm the Crown Prince.
Fortunately, I was well prepared.
Uncle,
you made a mistake.
He's the fake Crown Prince.
The real Crown Prince is in the house!
Uncle,
don't you think you sound childish
by saying that?
Take him away!
You purposely ignored what I did
and waited for me to confront you.
You've been preparing for this moment!
Take him away and keep him under surveillance.
He is not allowed to contact anyone.
Beware of his collusion
with outsiders to trouble the royal family.
Yes!
Wu.
Why are you standing at the door?
I feel that you got
something on your mind.
Feel?
After the battle,
Ye Zhi Qiu talked to you in private.
You came back and told us
that Cang Hui School
wanted us to enter the final.
That's the truth.
I wasn't lying.
I think
you have something left unsaid.
You can even notice that?
I won't notice it in other people.
But you're different.
Why am I different?
I've been observing you every day.
So I know how you look
when you're happy,
and how you look when you're sad.
I also know how you look
when you have something on your mind.
You'll get to know a person
if you've observed him for a long time.
Didn't we agree
to treat each other as a family member
and be there for each other?
Although we met
a lot of people together,
you are
the most important person to me.
Ye Zhi Qiu gave me this
and asked me to meet him in the town at night.
Let's go together.
All right.
I promise you.
From now on, no matter what happens,
we'll face it together.
Brother San.
Why are you here?
Where's Brother San?
I guess he went back to the dorm.
What are you doing?
What is this?
Earrings.
Earrings?
A prop for the theatre?
You made it for yourself?
Of course it's not for me.
It's a gift for Rong Rong.
For Rong Rong?
Keep it a secret.
We're brothers,
so make sure you keep it a secret.
It's for Rong Rong?
Rong Rong calls you a fool every day,
and you're giving her a present?
You know nothing
about adults' affection.
Adults' affection?
Tell me, then.
Tell me about adults' affection.
Adults' affection?
Adults' affection
is romantic.
It's sweet
and full of love.
What's this?
I've washed your clothes.
I washed the dark ones
and the light ones separately.
Why didn't you tell me?
You've been busy
studying tactics with Tang San
and the rest these days.
You don't have to worry about these things.
I've already
organized the clean clothes
by season
and their types.
By the way,
I still have a robe.
The weather is not so good recently.
The clothes don't get dried properly.
I was worried that you
might want to wear it urgently,
so I dried it with my Martial Soul.
You used your Scarlet Flame Dragon
to dry clothes?
As a result,
one of your clothes was burnt.
I planned
to buy a new one for you tomorrow.
Sorry.
Please don't apologize.
I should thank you.
Between the two of us,
formality is not needed.
I'm just thinking
that you're a Soul Saint,
and your Martial Soul should be put
to better use.
It feels better
to do these things for you
than fighting.
Don't feel stressed.
I am just kidding.
Er Long.
You're here again.
Well...
I'll go out and do some more exercise.
You've been doing that the whole night!
Haven't you had enough?
Well...
Can I go to bed now?
The weather is nice today.
Go out and train for a while.
I'm heading out now.
It's late. You should go to rest.
I think he needs more training.
Should I go out or not?
-Yes!
-No!
A firefly?
No.
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum?
Tang San!
Ou Si Ke, Ma Hong Jun!
Come here. We need to discuss the tactics.
Where are they?
Ou Si Ke?
Tang San?
Ma Hong Jun?
Ou Si Ke?
What's wrong?
Teacher Liu?
Headmaster?
Master?
Zhu Zhu Qing?
Wake up.
So the person you care about most
is this little girl.
It's you?
You're a Grand Soul Land Master.
There must be a reason for you
to attack us!
Your headmaster, teachers, and students
were knocked out by me at once.
They didn't have time to react.
Is it so great to bully the weak?
I let you remain conscious,
so you can see the difference.
The difference between them and me.
The difference between Martial Soul Hall
and Shi Lan Ke School.
I hope you can understand
that if I become your master,
it's way better than the whole school.
What do you think?
No way.
I'm a Grand Soul Land Master
from Martial Soul Hall.
I can help you overcome your elder brother.
I can also help you
become the Emperor
of Xing Luo Empire in the future.
You know who I am?
I checked it out.
It's between my brother and me.
Stay out of it!
Without you,
I can still defeat him.
Is it so important to take me as your pupil?
As a Grand Soul Land Master,
I can't pass down my principle
of Martial Soul.
It's always been my regret.
There are many Soul Masters.
Feel free to teach anyone!
But only you've consumed
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum.
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum
has special compatibility.
My principle of Martial Soul
needs someone who is talented like you
for its continuity.
Among the Soul Masters in Douluo Continent,
only you are qualified to be my pupil.
I can find time to ask for your guidance.
My pupil
must be a member of Martial Soul Hall.
Then the deal is off.
How about this?
I can help you cheat your way
through the upcoming battles.
Did you acquire your Soul Power
by cheating?
You are suitable to be my pupil.
Wake them up!
Are you all right? How do you feel?
I saw a light drifting in.
Wasn't I in the house?
How did I get here?
I'm glad that you're fine.
I thought you would come alone.
I won't keep anything from her.
Betrayal comes from trust.
So you asked me to come
in order to show me
your pessimism?
I need your help.
What can I help you with?
Poison again?
No, it's an antidote.
I prepared this for Du Gu Bo.
It can delay the poisoning.
Take this as a down payment.
If you and Du Gu Bo help me,
I'll figure out a way
to get the rest of the antidote.
Aren't you going to confront
Shi Nian on your own?
I tried.
You failed?
I got something from it.
What is it?
Follow me.
Where is it?
Five students from Cang Hui School
signed up for the contest.
The other four
are over there.
What does that have to do
with the thing you mentioned?
After regaining my memory,
I remembered something.
The people over there
came to Cang Hui School
at about the same time as I did.
We all have Mutant Souls.
When we first arrived
at Cang Hui School,
we had the same excitement and hope.
We thought
Cang Hui School could change our lives.
During that period,
we became best friends.
What happened then?
In the end,
like me,
they were controlled by Shi Nian.
No.
They had it worse.
Stay away!
Soul Skill?
It's an illusion.
Dodge it!
Watch out!
It's fine.
This is interesting.
Let me fight it.
It changed its state from illusory to real?
Mutant Soul, Spear of Void.
What is it this time?
It's Returning Mirror.
Stop fighting.
Try again.
That's all?
If she doesn't back down,
she will die.
Teleport?
Enough.
It's me.
Go in.
Stay behind me.
Sure.
Stop thinking about fighting.
Flee when there's danger, okay?
Okay.
This is...
His Martial Soul is Spear of Void.
The other guy has Returning Mirror.
They can coordinate their attacks.
You saw it.
What happened to them?
Shi Nian made them like this.
Spirit control?
It's not that simple.
Shi Nian's Martial Soul is Broken Dream.
It can cause hallucinations.
There is no way to escape.
The four of them
were under Shi Nian's control,
and were forced to go into their dreams
that they can never communicate with others.
They lost their consciousness.
They are like puppets pulled by strings.
Had it not been for the rules of the contest
that the captain must speak to the opponents,
as the captain of Cang Hui School,
I would have suffered
the same fate as theirs.
Shi Nian only sealed my memory,
so I could
communicate with others during the contest.
So I got to meet Venom Soul Master.
With his help,
I broke
Shi Nian's spirit control over me.
And I regained my memory.
This is the reason
why I want to work with you.
I don't want to be like them.
Also,
I still hope to save them.
Let's go.
We can't stay here for long.
I showed you my secret.
Without outside help,
I can't escape from Cang Hui School.
You can fight against Shi Nian now.
Cang Hui is backed by a Grand Soul Land Master.
Taking down Shi Nian
won't make a difference.
When we arrive in Martial Soul City,
and deal with Hao Tian Soul Master
behind Cang Hui School,
we may have a chance
to break free from Cang Hui School's control.
Are you sure Hao Tian Soul Master is
behind Cang Hui School?
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪