(Last Episode)
I've committed a sin against you
that cannot be cleansed.
No words or actions
can bring me forgiveness.
I've missed you so much.
I loved you,
and that's why I resented you...
and felt bad for you all the more.
I'll take my punishment.
Here's my last act...
of atonement for you.
Gangnam Police Station.
I'll walk on my own.
- Get in here!
- Let go!
Let go of me!
Move it already!
I didn't do it.
- Save it.
- Listen to me.
Excuse me.
Yes? How may I help you?
I came to turn myself in.
I...
killed a person.
Power.
Ares.
Sunrise.
Zeus...
Zeus Palace.
What do you think?
For the new apartment.
I absolutely love it.
It sounds luxurious and rich.
Since I've become the president
of the residents association,
should we just buy the penthouse?
Forget it. Why would we move into
a place where people die...
and come back to life?
We'll move to Cheonsoo
in a few years anyway.
But you should dress nicer...
than the previous
association president.
Hey. Don't compare me
to that stupid jerk...
Joo Dan Tae.
They could bring me
a truck full of Joo Dan Taes.
I wouldn't trade you for them.
While we're here, let's get you
a suit in each color...
made of the best Italian fabric...
No, 2 or 3 in each color.
You have a cute face,
so you look good in bright colors.
If you must define it,
I have a handsome face.
Let's buy them all.
We have way too much money.
I don't think
that's a good color for him.
He's a member of
the National Assembly after all.
Something respectful and refined.
And his face totally screams,
"petty weasel."
Hey.
Kyu Jin looks like a prince
no matter what he wears...
because of his face.
I ask because I'm really curious.
Are you my stalker fan?
Are you?
Why are you following me
when I'm shopping?
Come on. You're hurting my feelings.
Didn't we strike it rich
with Cheonsoo District?
We're on a different level now.
We're all nobles.
We should have at least one bestie
on the same level.
I came to get a suit too.
A men's suit?
Didn't you know?
My husband is coming to Korea soon.
Mr. Yoo's coming?
Has it been five years already?
Did he close out the business
in Dubai?
I'm coming into a lot of money soon.
There's no reason to make him suffer
alone in that faraway land.
I'll tell you my husband's size.
I want the best...
The most expensive suit.
I'll take about 10 of them.
Did you say 10?
Come this way, ma'am.
Hey. Guys?
Hey. You.
Assemblyman Lee! Assemblyman Lee!
Assemblyman Lee!
Why aren't you answering your phone?
What?
Chairman Joo called.
Will he pay the 30 million dollars?
That's not it. Cheonsoo District...
- What? What?
- What about Cheonsoo District?
Cheonsoo District has been
flipped upside down!
Did it go up even more?
- Yes! We did it!
- Breaking news.
Cheonsoo District, which has been
the talk of the town...
for being named the location
of the new town development,
is now wrapped in a scandal related
to bribery of a government official.
Jung Doo Man, the party leader
of the Happy Future Party,
has resigned as party leader...
and submitted himself voluntarily
to the prosecutors.
Jung colluded with Joo Dan Tae,
the chairman of Cheong A Group,
who is being investigated
for the murder of his previous wife.
He changed the district
for the development...
and manipulated an over-inflation
of property value in Cheonsoo.
Focus is also turning to
the cause of death of Na,
to whom Joo Dan Tae had entrusted
to lead the development investments.
As per sources in the Ministry of
Land Infrastructure and Transport,
Cheonsoo was going to be announced
to be a landfill for garbage,
but it was suddenly named...
- the location of the new town.
- Let me in, Mr. Hwang!
Mr. Hwang!
A landfill? What?
Did you scam us?
Let us in, you scamming scumbag!
Mr. Hwang! Please return my money!
I can't even get married
without that!
Mr. Hwang! Let us in
before we get angry!
Are you trying to kill us?
Are you stupid?
How could you buy everything up...
without looking into it?
I even sold all of my buildings
in Gangnam and put it into this.
Why did you do that?
And why is this my fault?
You were happier than I was!
Kyu Jin. If your dad divorces me,
you have to let me
live with you, okay?
Okay.
Give me my money!
Mother.
Just tell me to kill myself.
That scares me more
than going bankrupt!
What are you talking about?
You can't do this to me!
Oh no.
- How do you feel?
- Why are you asking me?
Assemblyman Lee Kyu Jin is here!
- Assemblyman Lee!
- What do you think about this?
- Let's go.
- Assemblyman Lee!
- Please give us a statement.
- Please say a few words.
I came to look at some land
for farming, that's all!
Out of my way!
No! This is defamation!
Get out of my way, jerks!
What? Can't assemblymen buy land?
Move!
- Assemblyman Lee!
- Wait!
- Honey!
- Assemblyman Lee!
Kyu Jin!
It's not true.
I'm not in the car! Honey!
Kyu Jin!
It has been confirmed...
that Assemblyman Lee was involved
in the war for Cheonsoo District.
He used the names of his parents,
son, and cousins...
to purchase
30 million dollars worth of land.
Yes. Hello? Madam?
Cheonsoo District... Hello?
What's wrong with my phone?
Lee Kyu Jin, Ko Sang A, Kang Ma Ri.
You need to come with us.
Oh no, I'm done for.
Already?
Hey, you.
Don't you know that Assemblymen
have immunity?
Plus, we're victims
of the Cheonsoo District scam.
This is about the murder of
Min Seol A.
What did you just say?
Min Seol A...
That case was closed years ago.
We were victimized by Shim Su Ryeon
more than we care to mention...
The murderer confessed,
which reopened the case.
The murderer confessed?
Who was it?
Wait.
- Honey. Honey!
- No.
Wait!
I simply did what I had to.
I brought someone
who wanted to see you.
Will you meet with her?
Ro Na.
That's Ro Na, right?
I guess the police
didn't tell you...
in case it would influence
your statement.
Ro Na was alive.
What happened?
Su Ryeon saved her.
She assumed the killer
would go after her again,
so she had been watching closely.
If she hadn't bribed a doctor
in advance,
something horrific
would've occurred.
Ro Na had to stay alive...
to prove Joo Dan Tae was
her assailant,
so she faked her death...
and transferred her
to another hospital.
(Funeral Parlor)
(Bae Ro Na, Murder)
Ro Na.
She's still not breathing.
Maybe it's too late.
No. Please don't give up.
We must save her. Let me take over.
Please don't die, Ro Na.
Open your eyes.
You must live for your mom.
She's breathing again.
Ro Na.
Do you recognize me?
Ms. Shim.
Good.
That's my girl.
Su Ryeon risked her life...
to save Ro Na.
Ro Na is waiting.
She's feeling a lot better now.
I'll bring her to you.
No.
She's alive. That's enough.
I'll meet her...
when I can face her...
without feeling ashamed.
Seeing her alive like this...
is more than I deserve for now.
I'm so grateful.
(Gangnam Police Station)
You could call it speculation...
if you're politically biased.
But in terms of
collective responsibility,
it's not speculation at all.
Also, I became an assemblyman
to bring about social justice.
Do you think I disposed of a corpse?
That's complete nonsense.
Assemblyman Lee, show some respect.
Who gives you
the right to yell at me?
Me? Did I yell at him?
No way.
Detective, just think about it.
We have such a high social position.
We have both fame and fortune.
How could we possibly
dispose of the dead body...
of a poor orphan
who had nowhere to go...
and destroy the evidence?
That's a crime, isn't it?
We're people of integrity.
Integrity, my foot.
Anyway, how long are you going
to talk about this kid, Min Seol A?
Who is it this time?
Who cooked up this story
and dragged us in it?
Who is it? Answer me!
I told you not to yell at me,
you punk!
Ms. Kang.
Who said that?
I cleaned the fountain that day?
I may scrub people's backs,
but I never do much cleaning.
There was emergency waterproofing
work at Hera Palace that day.
That's what the other residents
testified.
Is that when you transported
the dead body of Min Seol A?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
There's a witness.
She saw all of you.
Who is she?
It's already been two years.
Who is this crazy woman
claiming that she saw us?
I'd love to see her face.
It's Ms. Oh Yoon Hee.
Ms. Oh already testified
that she saw you that day.
She really did?
That crazy witch.
How dare she turn her back on me?
- Ms. Kang.
- Why do you keep calling me?
Was it you? Did you frame us?
That day, I saw everything
with my own eyes.
The horrible things
that you did at the fountain.
As you know,
I was at Hera Palace that day.
But you were drunk
and couldn't remember anything.
That's not true.
I remember everything.
I remember everything
that happened that day...
very clearly.
Are you trying to frame me...
for something that
didn't even happen?
So what did you see?
Min Seol A killed herself.
She was devastated after being
abandoned by her own mom.
Seol A...
didn't kill herself.
I killed her.
Seol A was killed at Hera Palace...
by me.
What did you just say?
You killed Min Seol A?
Is that really true?
Does Su Ryeon know?
She does.
(Gangnam Police Station)
Sorry to interrupt your meal.
How does it feel to have killed
Na Ae Gyo with your own hands?
Shim Su Ryeon!
Are you really...
Shim Su Ryeon?
Are you?
You must have hoped...
that I'd never find out
about Na Ae Gyo.
Too bad.
I did, already two years ago.
That's when I realized
why you always forced me to wear...
only the clothes you bought me.
You had Na Ae Gyo
dress just like me...
and pretend to be your wife...
to use her for lobbying.
I was too busy
taking care of Hye In...
to meet any people, anyway.
You probably thought
no one would ever find out.
By using the daughter
of the Simoon Construction chairman,
it would've been no problem
manipulating big shots.
How come I didn't recognize you?
How could you possibly
fool me so completely?
Luckily for me,
I could find a ton of information
about Na Ae Gyo in Thailand.
For two years,
I lived more like Na Ae Gyo
than Na Ae Gyo herself.
I risked my life
to be able to get back...
and finally kill you.
How dare you fool me?
It creeps me out to think that you
were the beginning of all my misery.
You killed Seol A's dad,
pushed Seol A to the edge,
and even killed Ae Gyo.
On top of that,
you tried to kill Ro Na
when she was innocent.
I imagined ripping you to pieces
every single day.
How can a scumbag like you
still be alive?
I'm baffled
by the unfairness of it all.
Then shut your mouth
and keep complaining.
Let me tell you what.
Na Ae Gyo betrayed you long ago.
She was in love with Mr. Jung.
That's why she wanted to leave you.
That's complete nonsense.
What do you even know about her?
I'm the only man
she loved in her life.
She was ready to do anything for me.
Then why did you kill her?
Joo Dan Tae!
Mr. Jung!
What happened?
What have you told the police?
Do you have any idea
what I'm going through here?
Get me out of here right now.
Why should I?
If that's how you're going to be,
this isn't going to be fun.
Aren't you going to run
for the presidential election?
Does this mean that you're okay...
with me exposing...
your relationship with Na Ae Gyo?
Na Ae Gyo and I...
aren't in a disgusting relationship
like you think we are.
But how would a despicable man
like you know that?
You're garbage...
that's never been loved, after all.
Are you saying...
that you really loved my woman,
you dog?
Even after having everything
you've done,
I can't believe you have
the audacity...
to eat to live on.
Despite everything,
Na Ae Gyo was the only one...
who felt bad...
for someone as disgusting
as you are.
Killing that woman...
will be the biggest curse...
in your life.
There's nothing you can do now.
All of your money,
Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung,
and the penthouse are all mines now.
Until you die, I hope...
that you'll rot
a pathetic death in jail,
Joo Dan Tae.
I'm going to do whatever I can...
until your misfortunes reach
their heights.
That's my loyalty...
to Na Ae Gyo.
Get ready,
Joo Dan Tae.
Jung Doo Man!
Shim Su Ryeon!
Mr. Baek!
What jerk is it this time?
Na Ae Gyo was right.
I heard you have a real name.
That's Mr. Baek?
Get out of there.
Bring it on, you jerk!
Talk to me face-to-face!
I don't have time for that.
I'm leaving for the US today.
The police are investigating
my parents there.
So, don't you get false hope.
I won't be cutting
any deals with you.
I'm going to make sure to expose
every last bit of you.
I'll show you that this isn't
the end, Joo Dan Tae,
no,
Mr. Baek.
Doesn't it hurt?
(25 years ago)
It's bearable.
I need to leave a mark on myself...
so that you don't confuse me
with Shim Su Ryeon.
And why would that even happen?
I could find you
with my eyes closed. You're mine.
But why a butterfly, of all things?
You could've just gotten a mole.
To be reborn...
as a beautiful butterfly.
What do you think?
Beautiful, right?
It's stunning.
I'll make sure that you live
like Shim Su Ryeon.
As the happiest woman in the world.
You can hold on a little longer
until then, right?
For how much longer
do I have to wait?
It won't be long.
If I use Shim Su Ryeon's name right,
we'll become so rich that we could
suffocate under our piles of money.
I'll buy a house in Gangnam,
build a building,
and build a Joo Dan Tae Village...
on the land where my mother has
passed away on,
and make the whole world kneel
before me.
And we'll have children?
Of course.
We'll have a son and a daughter.
Our kids will live
in the most expensive home...
located on the highest level
in Korea.
The home that will be the closest
to the sky.
The penthouse.
Just thinking about it makes me
so happy.
So, Na Ae Gyo...
is really dead?
I...
killed...
Na Ae Gyo?
Mom would never do that.
How can she not want to see me?
She's my mom!
I must ask Mom myself.
Ha Eun Byeol!
Why? You look like you're looking
at a ghost.
What happened?
Why are you here?
You must've been hoping that I died.
I'm sorry I'm back alive like this.
Why did you do that to me,
Ha Eun Byeol?
Why did you try to kill me?
Did you hate me that much?
No, I didn't do anything.
I didn't do it!
I didn't think you'd admit it.
I feel bad for your dad...
for taking the blame
for someone like you.
But that won't make you innocent.
You'll be punished too.
Go away!
You're dead.
There's no place for you now.
Get out of my sight!
Are you okay?
You still have to be careful.
Let's get back to the hospital.
Ha Eun Byeol!
Where have you been
without telling me?
I told you to not go anywhere.
It's dangerous outside!
Ms. Jin!
I hate it here. I'm scared.
I'm scared to death.
Take me somewhere, anywhere.
I don't care where it is.
Just far away.
Take me somewhere
where nobody will find me.
Please, Ms. Jin!
You're really fine with anywhere?
Yes.
Wherever I don't see Bae Ro Na.
You poor thing.
Let's leave everything here and go.
Call me Mom from now on.
Call me Mom.
It's been a while, Shim Su Ryeon.
We meet, at last.
Could you give us a moment?
Are you sure?
That suits you so well.
Shut your mouth.
What have I ever done you so wrong?
The one who killed Min Seol A is...
Oh Yoon Hee, your favorite.
Compared to the disgusting thing
Oh Yoon Hee has done,
I've barely even shown my teeth yet.
You think...
Seol A is the only one
you've ever done wrong?
What, taking your husband from you?
You can have him back right now.
I will forever regret the fact
that I loved him for a moment!
How can you be so unapologetic
even at a time like this?
I've had my share of being punished.
Do you know what Joo Dan Tae did
to my family?
Do you want more?
What, you think I'll get on my knees
and beg you for forgiveness?
No, don't do anything.
I'm going to take over now.
I'll make sure that you regret
everything you've done so far.
You can just quietly sit around
and reap what you've sown.
Who do you think you are?
You think you rule the world?
You think you're the judge?
What right do you have to say that?
The only wrong I've done is
to live my life to the fullest.
All I've done is the best
for my daughter.
What's wrong with a mother
loving her daughter?
I'm innocent!
I won't let you be, Shim Su Ryeon.
I'll make sure to pay back for this.
(Ma Ri Sauna)
(Two months later)
(Urgent, on sale!)
(On sale for 2.1 million dollars)
(Director's Office,
Principal's Office)
- That's gold.
- That's spot-on.
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
You're just like her.
What are you guys doing there?
Why are you going
into the Director's Office?
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
(CEO Joo Dan Tae)
(Lee Kyu Jin, you idiot!)
There he comes!
Do you admit to killing
Ms. Na Ae Gyo?
No, I'm innocent.
Do you admit to kidnapping,
locking up, and beating...
Ms. Shim Su Ryeon and Bae Ro Na?
I've never done such a thing.
Do you admit to having lobbied
illegally...
for Cheonsoo District?
You supposedly have a list
of politicians who received bribes.
Are you thinking of turning that in?
People may have taken money from me,
but I've never bribed anyone.
Why would I bribe people like them?
Do you plan on claiming innocence...
for today's trial
on Ms. Min Seol A's death as well?
I've done nothing wrong.
I'm innocent!
- Please answer us!
- Is it true...
- Over here!
- Will you admit...
I'm innocent. I'm clean.
I've done nothing wrong.
(Courtroom)
I'm not going to run away!
Seriously!
Let go! That hurts!
I can walk on my own.
Mom!
My goodness!
Mom is okay. Don't worry.
Min Hyuk! Have you eaten?
Don't worry about Mom.
I'll be just fine.
He's lost so much weight.
Attorney Kim, what class
is the judge from?
Eun Byeol...
(Defendants)
Everyone, stand up!
(Judge)
You may take a seat.
Your Honor, I'd like to bring
Ms. Shim Su Ryeon as a witness.
(Seoul Central District Court)
- That witch!
- How dare you?
- Su Ryeon!
What have we ever done wrong?
You're crazy!
Everyone, quiet.
(Defendants)
Please proceed.
(Witness)
On the day of the incident,
on your way down in the elevator,
you witnessed someone pushing
Min Seol A off, right?
And that person is...
Oh Yoon Hee. Is that correct?
(Gangnam Police Station)
Yoon Hee wanted me to pass this
onto you.
Su Ryeon, I have a favor to ask you.
Please come to the court
as the witness...
who saw Seol A die,
so that I may receive the punishment
that I deserve.
That's the only way for me...
to get justice on the rest.
Please.
Please testify.
Yes, that is correct.
- I knew it!
- Ridiculous!
How could that be?
How could she?
Oh Yoon Hee...
pushed my daughter Seol A
from the 47th floor.
I saw it clearly.
My gosh.
You really did it?
This is insane.
It is not insane.
It totally makes sense.
I knew it.
It's unfair to treat this murderer
the same as us.
You shouldn't compare us
to this evil villain...
who killed someone
so young as her daughter.
Your... Your Honor.
If you want to stone someone,
you should stone her.
What did we do wrong? Tell me!
I was about to sit down.
She killed a person...
and got her daughter into the school
in her place.
She even moved into
the apartment...
where the victim Min Seol A lived...
She even started a war
for her property...
several times its value.
She should get
an increased sentence.
If you have any shame,
say something, Oh Yoon Hee.
You acted like you were best friends
with Min Seol A's birth mom.
Do you have an honest bone
in your body?
Keep it down, will you?
If you cause a scene again,
I'll kick you out of the courtroom.
Prosecution.
Joo Dan Tae.
Do you admit the charges?
I did not move the victim's body...
or set her home on fire.
You shouldn't take
a murderer's word for it...
and treat us like criminals...
Do you have proof?
Proof that we were involved
in Min Seol A's murder.
Korea's legal system is based on
evidence and trials.
This is in the Constitution.
I never did that either.
It was definitely the murderer
Oh Yoon Hee acting on her own.
I agree.
I swear on my daughter's name.
Me too. I'm innocent too.
Your Honor.
I'd like to submit into evidence
a video of the defendants...
confessing to the crime.
It was not submitted in advance.
Please keep it out.
I'll accept it.
What?
Hey, you!
Do you know how much I pay you?
Do your job, punk!
I'm going to...
Silence in the court!
This is my final warning.
No! No.
Me. I'll go first.
That night...
All I did was wipe the blood off
the fountain.
That goes for me too.
Jenny's mom told me
to wipe the blood,
and that's all I did!
Stop it! This is a trap.
They're putting on a show
to get evidence!
Hey. Keep your mouth shut.
You can die for this alone!
I can't die.
That guy, Joo Dan Tae said...
we should dispose of the body.
I honestly...
only followed
what Joo Dan Tae said.
What a joke.
Lee Kyu Jin, you stupid scumbag!
The bag.
You brought the golf club bag
to put her body in!
That golf club bag.
We moved that in your car!
- And your ex-wife, this witch.
- What?
- She faked the girl's suicide note!
You two couples! You made it
look like it was suicide!
Those are false confessions
that we said under duress...
in order to survive,
thinking there was a bomb.
Shim Su Ryeon threatened us
at gunpoint.
That's correct.
If anyone moved the body,
it would've been Oh Yoon Hee,
who killed her!
We really didn't do anything.
This is unfair.
It's so unfair,
that it's killing me.
All we did that night was
enjoy the party.
They weren't fake confessions.
All of it is true.
What are you saying?
Hey. Don't do it. Hey.
Think about Eun Byeol.
Do you want both of us
to go to jail?
(Defendant)
That night, we took
Min Seol A's body to Bosuk Village,
and faked her cause of death.
We were afraid that she would
tell people that our children...
were assaulting other children.
We knew she was locked
in the mechanical room,
but we did nothing to help her.
We were all...
crazy.
You're the one who's crazy!
You're insane!
This is all gibberish.
Don't believe him!
- Sit down.
- The evidence is fake!
I didn't do it.
That jerk is lying!
- Let go! Stop it!
- Wait!
- Guards!
- It's a lie.
I did no such thing.
Stop lying, you jerk!
You jerk!
Let go of me!
Do you plan to push me off a cliff
and kill me?
Yoon Chul. So your heart
belongs to Yoon Hee, doesn't it?
You wanted to take her side even if
you fell into the pit with her?
You don't care what happens to me,
is that it?
You're dead, you punk!
- You...
- I'll get you!
Ms. Cheon. Why are you so slow?
Can't you do it like this?
I've never done anything like this
before.
Sang A, you're good.
You pass.
Defendant Kang Ma Ri.
Desecration of a corpse.
Tampering with evidence.
(Tampering with evidence,
desecration of a corpse)
Violation of the Housing Act.
You are sentenced to
1 year and 6 months in prison.
It's easy once you use your head.
Defendant Ko Sang A.
Tampering with evidence.
(Tampering with evidence)
Is this big enough?
Desecration of a corpse.
Violation of the Housing Act.
You are sentenced to
1 year and 6 months in prison.
Defendant Cheon Seo Jin.
I know all about
the admissions fraud...
by Cheong A Arts High School.
Kidnapping of a minor.
False imprisonment.
(False imprisonment,
kidnapping of a minor)
Tampering with evidence,
desecration of a corpse.
It's Min Seol A's bag.
I wrote a suicide note.
Set that up too.
You are sentenced to
seven years in prison.
If she fell from there...
Make her fall forward...
Defendant Ha Yoon Chul.
Tampering with evidence,
desecration of a corpse.
Harboring a fugitive.
You are sentenced to
two years in prison.
Defendant Lee Kyu Jin.
Lift it higher. Seriously.
Darn it.
Tampering with evidence,
desecration of a corpse.
Trespassing.
Violation of the Housing Act.
You are sentenced to
two years in prison.
I'm of feeble mind
and I've repented!
Defendant Joo Dan Tae.
Violation of the Housing Act.
Violation of the Enforcement Decree
to the Real Estate Registration Act.
Offer of bribe.
Kidnapping of a minor.
False imprisonment.
Desecration of a corpse.
Defiling a corpse.
Trespassing.
Tampering with evidence.
Setting fire
to a present living building.
Attempted murder.
Murder.
You are sentenced to life in prison.
(Life in prison)
Why am I getting life in prison?
If it were me,
I'd sentence you to death.
Keep it down.
(Defendant)
And Joo Dan Tae, Cheon Seo Jin,
Lee Kyu Jin, Ko Sang A,
and Kang Ma Ri,
you are also found guilty
of contempt of court.
(Contempt of court)
All rise.
You may take a seat.
I never should've gotten involved
with a low life like you.
Why did you have to drag us down
with you? Why?
Hey, Seo Jin.
You couldn't shut up
this little coward?
He was your hotshot husband!
Shut it, Dan Tae.
- This is all your fault.
- What?
You said you'd take responsibility
for it all.
Why should I take responsibility?
Joo Dan Tae!
I heard you were the one
who tried to kill Ro Na too!
You're a demon!
Get off of me!
You crazy jerk.
You jerk. Let go!
- You jerk!
- You scumbag!
Tell them to kill him.
- Let go!
- Oh my gosh!
- You demon!
- Let go of me!
- Joo Dan Tae!
- You little... Let go!
- Hey, you!
- Darn it.
- Get back here!
- I'll get you.
You jerk.
Get over here.
- Get over here.
- You punk.
- You demon!
- I'm here. So what?
- Get off!
- How could you do that?
You demon!
- You demon!
- Darn it.
Shut it.
My son! Min Hyuk!
Mom.
Jenny. Madam. Please help me.
I can't go to jail
and leave Jenny by herself.
Please help me.
Mom.
Why can't you go?
If you were afraid of prison,
you shouldn't have broken the law!
Even if you are one of my people,
I can't forgive you for doing that
to a child.
We'd readily spend
10 million dollars...
to get you out on bail,
but the Three Queens won't spend
a penny on something like this.
Don't use your child as an excuse.
It's sickening.
I'll look after Jenny.
No. Madam. Madam Chairman.
- Please don't leave! Jenny!
- Mom!
How dare you sentence me to prison?
Show some respect
for a former lawyer!
This is an attack...
on the rule of law in this country!
Let go of me!
Do you know who my father is?
Min Hyuk! My boy!
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
This is humiliating.
Stop calling my name.
Where's Eun Byeol? How is she doing?
How should I know that?
Shame on you.
You've brought disgrace
upon your father.
How shameless of you
to ask about Eun Byeol.
I'm sure she doesn't need
a mom like you.
Mom. Seo Young.
Please bring Eun Byeol to me.
Tell her I miss her.
Tell her I miss her so much.
Please...
Mom.
Joo Dan Tae, you were the worst man
I've met in my life.
What did you just say?
I wish I could gouge my eyes out
for not seeing how evil you are.
I wish I could curse my own heart
for falling for you.
You shouldn't be the one to talk.
Who was the one who jumped
into my arms, saying you're in love?
It was you!
I was never in love with you,
not even for a second.
From the start, you were nothing
but prey for me, Cheon Seo Jin.
Don't you dare to say my name
with that trashy mouth of yours.
- Cheon Seo Jin.
- Shut it!
- What are you going to do?
You two are truly meant to be.
- What?
I'm so sad that I won't get
to watch this anymore.
You brats!
What took you so long to visit
your father?
Is this how I raised you?
I gave you everything!
This is the best you can do?
You aren't our father anymore.
You're the man who killed...
both the woman who birthed us
and the woman who raised us.
We can't forgive you.
So, don't you speak to us
like we're your kids ever again.
When did my son grow so big?
You think you can stay
on your high horse...
and deny the blood
that flows in you?
Even if the sky were to split
into two, you're my kids.
If I'm evil, you're a son
of an evil man.
If I'm a snake, you're a baby snake.
Give up on your paternal rights.
What? Give up on paternal rights?
From now on, our mother will be
our only guardian.
We're here to apply for a usurpation
of your paternal rights.
You can talk to our lawyer
about the rest of the process.
Who says you can do that?
You think anyone will take you
seriously without me?
I'm not giving a single penny
to either of you!
Do you even have money?
You have no money now.
I hear the penthouse is
already Mom's now.
Did you not know?
How dare you treat me like this?
You ungrateful brats!
Joo Seok Hoon! Joo Seok Kyung!
Is this how I raised you to be?
Do you know how much I've done
for you two?
You don't deserve to be called
humans if you don't know!
I don't think you should be
so happy either.
You've been fired
from your Director position.
That's fine.
You and I are nothing now.
Get out of my face.
I guess I won't have to keep
the secret now, right?
Eun Byeol is the only one
who knows, right?
That Eun Byeol's grandfather died
because of you?
It's too big of a secret
for someone young like me to handle.
I'll need to share it,
so I'm thinking of uploading it
on National Petition.
Seok Kyung,
Joo Seok Kyung,
no.
Do you see where you are now?
Seok Kyung, no.
We need to talk, Seok Kyung.
Seok Kyung! No!
- Please look here!
- Over here!
What do you have to say
about the murder?
Why did you admit everything?
I admit that I'm guilty
of having done all of it.
I may not ever be forgiven,
but I will live
the rest of my life...
asking Seol A for forgiveness.
Your Honor, before you announce
the verdict,
I'd like to say something.
Please speak.
Oh Yoon Hee has done
something unforgivable.
But she's the only one...
who has been there for my daughter,
who had nobody to rely on.
No, sir. I need money.
You didn't even pay me last month.
Are you crazy?
Hey. Do you know how many plates
you broke?
Clean this up.
Clean everything now!
What do you think you're doing?
Don't you think it's wrong...
to have a young girl carry
those heavy grills?
This is child abuse.
I'm going to report you.
- Who are you?
- I'm her mom. Why?
Get up.
You can make money elsewhere.
Hey, lady. Are you crazy?
Hey! Get lost
before I call the police.
I'm sorry you lost your job
because of me.
I'll find another one.
Get something good with this.
It's okay, I have money.
It's because I feel so bad.
Take it, it's okay.
My daughter remembers her...
as a woman who was so kind
for nothing in return.
Not only so,
but she was also accused of murder
and served time in jail,
and has experienced what it's like
to lose her own daughter.
The law must judge her,
but I...
have already forgiven Oh Yoon Hee.
Seol A, you feel the same, right?
Everyone, please stand up.
I pronounce the verdict.
Since Defendant Oh Yoon Hee...
has admitted her wrong
and came clean on it,
was feeble-minded at the time...
but is now apologetic
of her wrong action,
and the family of the victim would
like favorable arrangements,
will serve three years in jail.
- Three years?
- Mom!
- Please tell us how you're feeling!
- Do you admit to everything?
Why did you admit to it all?
This is all a plot to bring me down!
It's a conspiracy!
My party won't stand this!
Hold on!
Jenny. Where's Chairman Song?
Where is she?
Please don't leave me.
Min Hyuk! My son!
My boy!
Let me talk to her.
My dear citizens!
I will be back!
Mom!
I will overcome this tribulation...
and I shall be back!
The legal system of Korea
has fallen!
- Eun Byeol.
- Let go!
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! I didn't do it!
Eun Byeol!
I love you, son.
Make sure to eat regularly, okay?
Eun Byeol. I didn't do it.
Eun Byeol. My Eun Byeol...
Don't glare at me.
I can't stand this twerp.
Mom!
(Prisoner Transport)
(Joo Dan Tae Village)
I can do it alone.
No, you can't.
You haven't been here in a while.
I'm sure there's a lot
that needs fixing.
Seok Kyung volunteered to help too.
I did not.
Did you hear about Eun Byeol?
She disappeared into thin air.
She got scared and took off
since you came back.
I hope she never comes back.
That shameless brat
gives me the chills.
Hey! Ro Na! Get out here!
What do you think you're doing?
What are you two doing?
How childish are you?
Are you two losers back together?
You two need to snap out of it.
This isn't the time to serve Ro Na.
She's the reason our moms and dad
ended up in jail!
- Jenny.
- Stay away from me.
If your mom hadn't killed Seol A,
my mom wouldn't have been locked up.
I had no idea,
and liked your mom so much.
Do you know how heartbroken I was
when I thought you had died?
How could you do this?
You say you're my friend,
so why do you always hurt me?
Why do you make it impossible for me
to be happy you're alive?
I won't let this go, Ro Na.
Do you know who our family is?
My grandpa said he'd get you back...
for getting my dad fired.
Fine. My mom did something terrible.
I won't defend her.
But you need to take responsibility
at least once for what you did.
I'm ready to be punished...
for hurting you.
I won't forgive the jerks
who made my poor mom...
miserable.
You know how important she is to me.
Just you wait.
My dad won't stand for it.
She's right.
Her dad is a very scary man.
You're dead, Ro Na.
You loser.
Worry about your own life.
If Jenny's dad comes back,
he'll kill you and me first.
Don't mind them.
Let's finish unpacking.
What are you looking at?
I can't be a good person
because of you jerks.
Let's go, Seok Hoon.
We're supposed to see Mom.
Our Mom must be waiting.
She gave birth to you.
Have you...
ever met her?
Yes.
What was she like?
(Na Ae Gyo)
She was really cool.
She never hesitated...
and was loyal.
She cherished and loved you guys
a great deal.
Liar.
But she never once came to see us?
She had her reasons.
I'll tell you later
after some time has passed.
Where is Seol A?
I want to visit her.
(Min Seol A)
This trophy...
is yours.
Congratulations on winning
the grand prize, Seol A.
(May you be a beautiful song in
paradise where there is no sadness.)
(Seoul Dongbu Detention Center)
Mr. Chairman. Take it easy.
Here, have this.
There's a fun article in the paper.
He who smiles...
during hardship is
the most superior.
Quote from Shakespeare.
(Logan Lee)
(Out! D-day. 9)
Inmate number 1521, discharged.
(My Princess)
Dad!
My princess, how have you been?
I'm back in Korea.
Are you really back in Korea?
Come home quickly!
My princess.
I'll be home soon. See you.
Bye.
Hello, sir.
(Reformation, Order)
Where's the punk now?
Ladies and gentlemen, our flight,
which departed from JFK Airport,
will land at Incheon International
Airport shortly.
Please remain seated...
- Are you going to propose?
- With seat belts fastened...
- and raise the window shades.
- The rings.
- The flight attendants...
- Oh, yes.
Will make sure your trip
will be safe and comfortable...
You made a great choice.
They look gorgeous.
You think so?
Thank you.
I guess Korea has changed a lot.
It sure has.
I'm excited
because it's been so long.
I finally get to meet
my old friend again.
I'm glad I lived...
to meet him again.
Mr. Baek.
Su Ryeon, where are you?
I just got back.
Already?
I was getting impatient,
so I couldn't wait any longer.
I'm back in the penthouse too.
I'm busy organizing all the stuff.
The kids must be excited.
Well... I'd love to see you.
Can we meet soon?
I have something to tell you too.
I'm going to my store soon.
Should we meet there?
Sure, let's do that.
(Logan Lee)
Hi. I'm here.
Me too. I just arrived.
I'm in the parking lot.
Can you come out for a second?
I'll be right there.
Can I go have a smoke first?
- I'm a little nervous.
- Sure, go ahead.
Goodness. My bad.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
I'll save her. I'll set her free.
We'll take Seol A's revenge
together.
Do you think I deserve a new life?
I can't forgive myself
for leaving for the airport first.
I don't know you.
I know it's you!
I'm sorry it took me
so long to recognize you.
Why are you here?
You could get caught.
The last promise I made to Seol A...
I want you to be happy.
I'll make you happy.
(The Penthouse 2)
The highlight of the 28th
Cheong A Art Festival.
The recipient of the Grand Prize...
Bae Ro Na? Can't you give in
a little for Seok Kyung?
I really love my daughter a lot.
You don't love Mr. Joo!
I'll do whatever you say,
So please leave Eun Byeol alone.
Don't you remember what happened
to Su Ryeon?
Is this how you train your help?
Who dares to insult Ms. Jincheon?
I'm sorry. Ro Na, please don't die.
I need you in order to find
Ro Na's real murderer.
I have a great plan
to finish off Dan Tae.
Na Ae Gyo died last night.
No way! That's impossible!
She wasn't Na Ae Gyo.
She was Shim Su Ryeon.
Su Ryeon saved Ro Na.
I'm here to turn myself in.
Looking over here and over there
Whoever dares to betray me will die.
So that I could kill you.
(The Penthouse 3
will premiere soon.)