Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 10
Miss, you are back so early?
Early?
If I’m a little late,
I can’t see this.
Miss, don’t get mad.
I didn’t mean to hide it from you.
It’s just you boarded
the ship hurriedly,
mistaking me as the ship owner.
And later,
there were so many accidents.
I didn’t find a chance
to explain this to you.
So you decided to
use these to please me in Pingting
before telling me the whole thing?
Well...
Is it useful?
You’re as noble as a fairy.
I’m afraid you mind I’m a businessman,
old and ugly.
Don’t pretend to be modest anymore.
Since I agreed to your proposal,
I will do everything I can
to help you,
including your Chamber of Commerce.
Of course.
as your wife,
I will get what I want,
right?
Of course.
But
before making a deal with me,
you’d better think it through.
You started from scratch and
became the richest person in Suchuan.
Everyone knows your story.
As you said,
to make a deal with you,
of course I’ve thought it thoroughly.
What do you mean?
I will be your good wife,
but you have to help my brother
revive the Yins.
Since it’s a business,
the more you pay,
the more your brother
will get.
Here is all I have.
you can see it clearly.
You can get anything
as you want.
Then I have to think it over.
How about making babies?
It’s perfectly justified.
It’s not one, two, or three,
but nine in total.
It depends on your ability.
Good.
Out of home,
you’re Mrs. Weisheng,
Yins’ daughter.
I’ll pretend to respect you like guests,
and treat you with courtesy.
What you eat, wear and use
will be the best.
But you should know,
I offer you the most expensive clothes
is to allow you to act as
a noble lady.
When at home,
you’re my wife.
You have to do
what I ask you to.
Okay.
What are you waiting for?
Take off.
I mean,
take off your clothes.
Continue.
Enough, enough.
I can’t pretend anymore.
I’m so sorry.
I just want to have a try.
I’ve never ordered
a noble lady before.
I’m a little slaphappy.
Sorry.
But
Miss Yin Zhuang,
you are a little different
from what I expected.
But you are exactly what
I thought you were.
Anyway, I don’t care.
I just need you to fulfill
your promise to the Yins.
Besides,
I want you to promise me
another condition.
What’s it?
In front of my brother,
you should care about me, protect me,
and take good care of me.
Okay.
I promise.
Miss, where are you going?
Continue to go shopping.
I won’t save money for you.
I will never break
my promise to the Yins.
How do you know my size?
Eye survey.
Continue! Continue! Continue!
Who are you?
Take me to him.
He is not here.
Wanted?
Wanted
This Wanted...
I saw many robbers acting like a cop.
Say.
Where is he?
He’s rescued by someone.
No one knows where he is now.
Rescued?
By whom?
I don’t know.
I really don’t know.
The shift on duty that day
were killed by the Marquis.
Please spare my life.
I really don’t know.
It has nothing to do with me.
What a spacious house!
Come here!
You sleep here tonight.
Tidy it now.
It’s clean.
Why do you shake it?
So... Sorry.
Are you alright?
Do you need a physician?
No need.
Come on, tidy it and have a rest.
Tomorrow,
we’ll continue the work.
Sir,
I... I tell you,
I...
I really have something urgent to do.
I can’t help you work.
None of my business.
Sir,
I... I am a wanted criminal.
If the soldiers find that
I’m here with you,
it’s bad for you.
It’s none of your business.
Sir, I really can’t persuade you.
What about this?
I’ll help you work for more days,
and deliver the goods for you.
It’s my reward to you.
But
can you do me a favor?
I’d like to ask you something.
Seventeen years ago,
in Pingting,
a girl named Jin’er got lost.
Do you know?
There are so many girls
named Jin’er.
How do I know?
Well, wait for a moment.
What a trouble!
Wait for a moment.
Not long, not long.
I’ll finish soon.
Sir,
you’re a blacksmith.
Have you seen
such a tattoo?
What did you draw?
I don’t understand.
Look... Look carefully.
Have you seen it?
How can you make a deal with me?
If you don’t want to work here,
just go back
to Zhu Xi’s prison.
Go.
If I really want to leave,
you can’t stop me.
You can have a try!
I...
Boss, bill.
Sir.
You needn’t pay the bill.
You have my portrait, too?
Who are you?
Starlight Sword.
Surely you’re Mr. Yin Xiao.
You’re from Moon Tribe.
I have a letter from Zhaodu.
Please
send my apologies
to His Majesty and Linglong.
I will find Huotu Xin
and protect him.
No news is good news.
Both Zhu Xi and Weisheng Yan
are looking for him.
It means
he’s safe now.
Is Linglong
really the Goddess?
She needs to prove it
by the Ritual of Eternity.
Will she be put to death
if she fails?
You’re moving
under the monitor of Zhu Xi.
You must be careful.
Lord.
Go,
send this letter to Zhaodu.
Everything goes well in Pingting.
Aye.
Well,
the messenger from Moon Tribe...
You still need my instruction?
No.
Linglong,
why are you having a meal here?
What are you reading?
Nothing.
If I eat in my room,
a lot of maids would stand there,
offering dishes
or passing towel for me.
I’m not used to it.
No one dares to enter your study.
You can ask them to leave.
Then they will stand at the door,
looking at me,
waiting for me to finish.
Don’t you think it’s suffering?
Even so, you can’t sit on the bookshelf.
There are so many reports on your desk.
I dare not sit there.
Alright.
I’ll ask them
to send my dishes here.
Let’s eat together.
If so, a lot of people will come here
to serve you.
I’m leaving now.
What’s wrong?
Am I annoying you?
If you don’t like others to serve you,
how did you get this bowl of food?
It looks good and tasty.
I got it in the kitchen.
Linglong,
you are the Goddess.
How can you steal food from the kitchen
just because you don’t want trouble?
It’s not the first day you know me.
Or
do you think I’m
not dignified and good-mannered?
It’s against the rule?
Rule?
Even I dare not set a rule for you.
Who dares
in Suchuan?
I’ll get another bowl for you next time.
Where is Weisheng Yan?
Mr. Yin Xiao.
Master is at Miss Yin’s room.
I didn’t ask
anything about this necklace.
I just had a glance at it.
How do you know I like it?
If I’d like to,
I would know it.
If so,
I dare not go shopping in the future.
If only you like it.
I know you want to please me.
But it’s not good
to our Yins’ reputation.
If it causes rumors,
how could my brother
build prestige in Pingting?
That’s right.
It’s my fault.
I just want to please you.
I didn’t think so much.
I’ll put it on.
Speaking of your brother,
I have to think about
how to make him forgive me.
Don’t worry.
As long as I like it,
my brother will understand.
That’s good.
Do you like it?
Of course I do.
This is the life I dreamed of.
Yin Zhuang,
I will let you live
a life you never imagined before.
I believe you.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
My brother has already left.
I know.
So you have to listen to me.
It’s really beautiful.
Your handkerchief
is beautiful.
You mean this?
This fire
is the pattern of our Fire Tribe.
Looks good, right?
This is made by my father.
If you like it,
I can ask my father to make one for you.
I don’t need
a handkerchief
made by your father.
What?
Nothing.
You have finished reading
so many books?
What are you looking for?
Nothing.
Well...
Did you read this book?
Yes.
I’ve read the name list
of the ladies to be your wife, too.
No wonder you behave so strangely today.
Is it that you heard I chose some ladies
and you are jealous?
Whether you have a wife or not
has nothing to do with me.
You remind me of that.
In a few months,
Chief Priest will start to
choose ladies for me again.
In fact,
all of these ladies are
dignified, good-mannered,
sweet and elegant.
Even a duke’s daughter
put a handkerchief
in her name card.
You want this?
Give me.
Get it!
How come you hit me?
What’s wrong?
Didn’t you ask what I’m reading?
This is
the name list of Tianqi’s followers.
What’s wrong?
Are you
looking for this?
There must be a problem.
Sixteen years ago,
Zhaodu got the news that
Pillar of Eternity was lit
at Fire Tribe,
and sent some people to check it,
but nothing was found.
Yes.
So I checked the record.
A total of nine followers
were sent to Fire Tribe back then.
But these nine people
died in ten years
because of illness
or accident.
No one is alive now.
You mean
Chief Priest is hiding something?
It’s only him who knows it.
Goddess,
I can’t answer
your question.
You don’t know
how the Goddess comes from, either?
If you don’t know,
how can you be sure I’m the Goddess?
Goddess
is linked by blood
with the royals of the Yuans.
His Majesty found you.
It’ll never be wrong.
But His Majesty found me
under your instruction,
didn’t he?
No, no, no.
In the unseen world,
it’s the Goddess
who guided His Majesty.
But isn’t it you who
told His Majesty that
sixteen years ago,
Pillar of Eternity was lit
at Fire Tribe?
Yes.
If so,
the Goddess is so important to Suchuan.
Did you send anyone
to check it at the Fire Tribe?
Of course.
But
we had found nothing.
If we had the news
of the Goddess that year,
Tianqi
needn’t wait for so long
before you arrive here.
Found nothing?
It’s an important matter that
Pillar of Eternity was lit.
Back then,
the followers sent to Fire Tribe
were grouped by three people.
They monitored each other.
After returning to Zhaodu,
they were separated
and described the situations
in Fire Tribe.
I’ve checked
those records,
but there is nothing unusual.
Goddess,
do you want to check them?
No need.
I’ve checked them.
You’re brilliant.
But
since I was born,
I’ve never left Fire Tribe.
Why didn’t I hear
someone went there
and looked for the Goddess?
Well,
I’m afraid only the then Chief Priest,
my master,
knew the answer.
Your master?
Where is he?
My master
is buried
below Fozhuan’s tomb.
Linglong,
do you have the answer?
Nine people
died successively in ten years.
It’s definitely not a coincidence.
What on earth did they find?
Do you still think
Chief Priest is hiding something?
My intuition tells me that
Chief Priest surely knows something.
Intuition?
Why are you laughing?
My intuition is really...
Accurate?
Anyway,
it’s my intuition to follow you.
Do you think it’s accurate or not?
Yes.
Father,
I’ve sworn that
I can revive the Yins
by myself.
But you still decided to
marry Yin Zhuang to Weisheng Yan.
When you were alive,
I couldn’t stop you from doing so.
Now you’re not here,
I still can’t stop it.
You said,
I don’t know
what Yin Zhuang’s felicity is.
Yes.
I don’t know.
But do you really know?
It’s too cold.
Too hot!
The members of Fire Tribe
are born to resist heat.
Even you ask me to
put my hands in boiling water,
I won’t feel hot.
Take it.
What...
What’s it?
Measure the temperature with it.
It’s too hot when it turns dark.
It’s good if it doesn’t change.
What does this mean?
That’s killing hot!
Are you going to scald me to death?
Come on! Be quick!
Don’t waste time.
Unsatisfied.
Thinking I’m slow.
Why not ask your granddaughter
to look after you?
These are city guards.
Curfew time.
Don’t run about.
They come at the right time.
Sir,
I won’t stay here anymore.
I’m leaving now.
If you want to shout,
please be louder.
Are you mad?
Come back.
Are you crazy?
Sir.
Shout!
Send me out!
You can get ten coins.
I... I don’t want it.
You... Come back.
If you don’t shout,
I’ll do it.
What will you shout?
Help!
Catch the criminal!
Here’s the criminal!
Here.
Help!
Here’s the criminal!
Don’t shout!
My silly son is drunk.
Mistake!
-It’s not a mistake!
-Mistake!
I’m the criminal!
Catch me!
Please leave now!
Follow us!
You bastard!
Didn’t your mother teach you
to respect the seniors?!
He’s my man.
Get lost!
Yes!
Wu Yuan.
It’s really you.
Sir.
Your granddaughter is back.
You know it?
Of course I do.
I’m not stupid.
I tell you!
If you dare to put my grandfather
in danger again,
I’ll kill you!
You think I’m dangerous.
If you think so, you should ask
your grandfather to stay away from me.
How do you know it?
This drug can cure your wound.
You’ll be recovered
as well as before.
I didn’t think this drug bag
is yours long ago.
Say it.
Tell me everything
you know.
I won’t escape anymore.
You were caught at Zhu Xi’s prison.
You’re still keeping my drug bag.
Do you really
have feelings for me?
Do you think any man
can be induced by you?
Do you only know this trick?
Your grandfather is watching.
As a woman,
do you know what shame is?
Shut up your dirty mouth!
You...
Grandpa!
Look.
Your grandfather can’t watch it anymore.
Leave here now.
I won’t help you anymore.
Help me?
Aren’t you ashamed?
Since the first day I met you,
I was wanted
by various people.
Only you are helping me, right?
I think,
you’re the most vicious one.
I said shut up your dirty mouth!
Get lost now!
Showed your true colors?
Let your grandpa see
what kind of person you are!
You... You...
You...
Grandpa!
Are you alright? Grandpa!
Are you alright?
-Sir, are you alright?
-Grandpa.
Go!
Grandpa.
Go.
Take a deep breath.
Grandpa.
Come on.
Take a deep breath.
Here I come.
Here.
Inhale.
Breathe in.
What are you doing?
I... I’m saving him.
What’s this?
Breathe in. Inhale.
Cattle sand.
Cattle sand?
Cattle sand is poisonous.
He’ll be fine.
Don’t do it!
Get off him!
Grandpa.
Are you alright?
He’s fine.
What... What’s wrong?
From now on,
don’t speak with
my granddaughter like this!
What do you know?
You know nothing.
Grandpa, calm down.
Calm down.
One, two, three, four...
ten coins, no more, no less.
Do you have a heart?
Why did you sell our daughter?
Return this money to them.
Get away!
Return to them! Return to them!
Come. Go!
Mother!
Let’s go!
No!
Don’t catch her! Let me go!
I’ve never paid ten coins
for such a small girl.
-Don’t catch her!
-Mother!
Be content!
-She’ll have good clothes.
-Let me go!
She’ll live a better life than you.
Mother!
-Mother!
-Give me my daughter!
Mother!
You cried.
No. Just a nightmare.
You lied.
You dreamed sad things?
What are you doing here?
Is it related to your parents?
I’m quite familiar with the way
you behaved in your dream and the voice.
Linglong is like you in her childhood.
But
she never admitted
she dreamed of her mother,
but she called her mother in her dream.
Listen,
I only have my grandpa.
No parents.
Sorry.
I shouldn’t have said that
to you
in front of your grandpa.
After all,
you saved me many times.
It’s nothing.
After all,
what you said is right.
Yesterday...
Were you going to thank me
for saving your grandpa?
I wanted to ask you
why cattle sand can save my grandpa?
I don’t know.
We all use this in Fire Tribe.
It seems your grandpa
is seriously ill.
You said
you want to make a deal with me.
Is it you want to ask Linglong
to save your grandpa?
If you want help, just tell me.
Why do you make such a detour?
If I told you directly,
would you help me?
Of course.
You won’t
get anything from me.
Would you help me?
How could you think this way?
In this world,
no one will help others for nothing,
except my grandpa.
The people in Pingting
are quite different
from those in Fire Tribe.
A letter from Zhaodu.
This is a copy.
The original is kept by Yin Xiao.
Yin Xiao?
By the way,
how’s Yin Xiao’s sister?
She’s at Weisheng Yan’s mansion,
busy preparing for her wedding.
Weisheng Yan is not a good guy.
I boarded on his ship accidentally
and ends like this.
And it’s him who sent me to Zhu Xi.
How could Yin Zhuang marry him?
How do you know
what kind of people the Yins are?
How much do you know about them?
In Yin Xiao’s letter to Zhaodu,
he didn’t mention
you’re wanted by Zhu Xi.
Didn’t he?
Yes.
Really?
That...
That’s good. That’s good.
If he said that,
Linglong will worry about me.
It’s good he didn’t.
Stupid.
Speaking of Zhu Xi,
you should be his subordinate.
Why?
You are afraid of him?
You are useless to him.
What he wants is your daughter.
After I visited his Pingting city,
I know better what kind of person he is.
So it seems
Linglong had better stay in Zhaodu.
It’s much safer than here.
Right?
If
your daughter is the Goddess,
there is
no safe place for her
in Suchuan.
What on earth is the Goddess?
Goddess
is a tool to help others realize
desires and ambitions.
Why should it be Linglong?
You’re her father.
You should find the answer by yourself.
No.
I have to go to Zhaodu.
You must help me.
It’s bad to send you to Zhaodu.
I’ll go out for a while.
Help me look after my grandpa.
Look,
it’s good
you behave like this.
What?
Ask me for help.
It’s good you say it directly.
It’s what you should do.
I...
Last evening,
who made my grandpa so angry?
When my grandpa wakes up,
just do whatever you can
to please him.
If you can’t make him happy,
you’ll be dead.
Where are you going?
You made a trouble yesterday.
I have to deal with it.
If you believe me,
don’t go to Zhaodu,
because you and your daughter
are the biggest weaknesses
of each other.
Our plan
is to send Huotu Xin to Zhaodu,
not hiding him.
If I don’t do something
to make him believe me,
your plan can’t be finished.
He looks stupid.
Actually,
he’s very clever.
Zhu Xi will go to Zhaodu soon.
What to do?
You have to ask him.
I mean
what do you want me to do in Zhaodu?
I really like talking with you.
Greet your grandpa for me.
My grandpa is getting worse.
It seems this medicine doesn’t work.
So you have to hurry.
Don’t think falsely that
you did something for him,
and he’ll ask his daughter
to cure your grandpa.
The Goddess won’t act
according to the will
of ordinary people.
You let Linglong go,
and then Huotu Xin,
making them gather at Zhaodu.
What do you want to do?
You needn’t know.
Just remember,
it’s only me who can cure your grandpa.
your grandpa.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪