Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 9
Fozhuan
was buried on top of Tianqi Cemetery,
way above
the deceased Chief Priests.
He once told me
that place was the closest to God.
Thank you.
Did Fozhuan
teach you those tricks?
You...
You knew already?
Of course.
You’re like a younger version of him.
Yuan Yi is right.
No one can fool you.
I thought
I did a flawless job.
Even Chief Priest held that bead,
and called it
Master Fozhuan’s core.
He kept yelling
that’s the holy treasure of Tianqi Sect.
Let him be if he insists on
enshrining Fozhuan’s thingy.
Fozhuan would be glad
that his trick fooled those old farts
even after his death.
Inside is
his ashes.
Did you mean to tell me the truth?
Tricks, however good they seem,
can’t be used on the one he loved.
You still have my feather.
I once heard from seniors
that nothing
could separate those in love,
not even death.
He’d turn into the spring breeze,
the summer rain
and find you again.
Do you also believe in that?
That’s a way
to make one feel better, isn’t it?
Yes.
At least, breeze and rain
sound much comforting
than ashes.
Thanks.
But
he is dead.
His life ends in this urn.
He wouldn’t return in any form.
Minister Fei,
words had gotten out
that the Ritual of Eternity
would be held in Zhaodu.
What?
Every fiefdom has announced it.
Those old dogs!
You may leave.
All their eyes are on you.
Do you know what that means?
I...
Over the past 500 years,
Suchuan has been under the Yuans’ rule
as they’re the royals of Immortal Blood.
Despite fierce wars among others,
the Yuans are unaffected
in Zhaodu.
The chosen one by God
is the last force
to maintain Suchuan’s balance.
I can be of help to Yuan Yi, right?
Why are people in awe of God?
Because in this world,
there is no God.
Out of sight, out of doubt.
God is merely a symbol,
a deterrent.
Others dare not to dethrone Yuan Yi
for fear of God.
Once the Ritual of Eternity completes,
won’t it enhance God’s influence
and make him more powerful
than a mere symbol?
No, you aren’t a symbol.
You’re flesh and blood
and visible.
Once you lose,
then
hundreds of years of reverence
towards the Yuans
will collapse.
By that time,
enemies all over Suchuan
will flood in.
That’s the direst consequence
of the Fall of God.
Those things
have never...
They’ve never occurred to you, right?
Then
why did you agree to hold that ritual?
I was
trying to stop Yuan Yi
from looking for God.
I once assumed
you were hired by Chief Priest
or Zhu Xi.
But...
I want to see the one Yuan Yi chose.
I won’t fail.
Thank you.
Don’t get me wrong.
I’m not helping you.
If you can’t prove yourself
at the Ritual
or fail to overwhelm everyone
with a miracle,
I’ll have to
execute you for deception
for the sake of
the Yuans and Suchuan.
Thank you for telling me all that.
It’s
totally different
from what Yuan Yi said
or what I imagined.
I’ve been burned by the Earth Fire
and hunted by Zhu Xi,
but never have I
been this scared.
My father is right.
But that’s fine.
Because
I’m Goddess.
Ah!
Goddess.
She touched my hand.
Let me touch it!
Let me!
Please!
No.
Come on
Linglong.
You’ve started to get the hang of it.
You’re right.
The world that accepts me
is indeed different.
I wish my father
could see this, too.
Put these on.
They’re for me?
Just my size.
There are
good people in Pingting after all.
Sir,
thank you
for your kindness.
I’ll
repay you for it someday.
Sure.
Keep that in mind.
By the way,
may I ask you a question?
Do you know Zhaodu?
Are you going there?
It’s far from here.
Could you tell me the direction?
Good.
What are you doing?
Isn’t this how people
greet each other here?
Knock it off!
But
weren’t you...
You said you’d repay me, didn’t you?
There’s no such thing as a free meal.
You mean
I have to pay,
right?
I don’t have...
Sir,
in the Fire Tribe, we call it a...
Blood Stone.
It’s not worth a bun in Pingting.
No one wants it.
Then...
What do you want?
Come on! Hurry!
Yes. Throw it in!
Go on!
Good.
Now, add some water.
Yes, water.
I mean water. Over there.
Sir,
what’s all this for?
I’m forging a weapon.
They’ve lost
their courage.
Such a battle had never been seen
that Kunwu’s cavalrymen swept
the West Border
like the sandstorm.
Sand raised by hoofs
pierced Suchuan troops’ hearts
like sharp arrows.
Despite blood gushing out of
Emperor Yuan Qian’s wounds,
he stood still with his sword.
He knew
what behind him
was Suchuan.
God lifted the Nu River,
and made it fall
over Kunwu troops’ heads.
Soon, sand turned into mud.
The ferocious cavalrymen
were waist-deep in the mudbath.
Emperor Yuan Qian’s Sword of Kings,
blessed by God’s power,
was shining radiantly.
Thus, warriors of Suchuan
regained their courage.
That
was God
and his supreme power.
Sir,
what are those in your ears?
I mean your ears...
Look!
You were saying?
Never mind.
No wonder
you were the best blacksmith
in Pingting.
Load one stone
into it,
it can shoot 50 times.
Incredible!
I wish
I could have more of it.
You want more?
No problem.
I can make you 50.
50!
Really?
Will your granddaughter agree to that?
Even this one
is made behind her back, right?
Don’t worry. I can handle it,
young man.
Forget it.
I wouldn’t dare tick her off.
Others begged me to make it,
but I said no.
It must be fate
that brought us to meet.
Make up your mind.
Do you want more or not?
Are you messing with me?
No, no, no.
I wouldn’t dare.
Aside from your granddaughter,
given
your condition,
I’m concerned...
Don’t be.
I have help.
Is he your apprentice?
Be careful with it.
Not exactly.
Just a handyman.
What say you?
Alright.
I’ll pay
two gold coins
per piece you make.
Is that fair?
Two gold coins?
I’m not that expensive.
Excuse me?
It’s a deal.
100 gold coins
for 50 pieces.
I need a deposit, though.
Pay me
30...
No, 50 percent first.
Deal.
Are you drained?
No.
Jade
can be found in the Fire Tribe, too.
It’s beautiful
but too fragile.
Can I turn this sword
into the unbreakable Sword of Kings?
Not now,
I’m afraid.
It’s not even dark
and you already
dozed off.
Ritual of Eternity isn’t a game.
Your tricks
won’t work there.
If you fail,
even I can’t help you.
Are you reprimanding me
as an emperor?
It’s not my fault.
Your story is too boring.
Story?
Is that what you think?
Am I wrong?
These…
These,
all of them
and books over there
tell nothing but stories, right?
About those things you said,
such as battling with the emperor,
helping him beat back enemies,
treating his wounds,
blessing Sword of Kings with power,
aren’t all those stories
between God
and the emperor?
They’re a whole,
safeguarding Suchuan together.
Honestly,
they can’t help me in any way.
Back in the Fire Tribe,
if you ask a senior,
he can go on and on
for a whole night about how warriors
battled the Earth Fire.
But nothing
explains
the origin of the Earth Fire
or why it’s been on for 500 years.
Yours are just the same.
None of them answers
where God is from.
Sometimes,
answers can’t solve problems.
Sir,
so you’re a blacksmith,
quite a skilled one, actually.
Are you also familiar with those skills?
I’m not,
but my tribesmen are.
Now, they can only
patch things up.
Techniques ancestors created
are long lost.
I know.
Ancient Fire Tribesmen developed tons of
excellent quenching and forging skills.
At that time, Jinshi City
was our shrine.
Most techniques are gone
but weapons ancestors forged
have been passed down.
My Fire Spear
is one of them.
Once I find my daughter,
you’re welcome
to go to our tribe
and have a look
at our ancestors’ legacies.
You’re going to love them.
I’d better stay away
from that sinful land.
How...? How is it sinful?
You don’t understand.
It’s none of your business.
Here.
No, no, no.
Sir,
that’s too generous of you.
I can’t thank you enough
for saving my life
and I’m obligated to help you.
I can’t take your money.
Sorry, I can’t take it.
That’s not for you.
Go to the store across the street.
Pick up two jars of liquor
and a roasted chicken.
Ask them for the change.
Put the hat on
to cover yourself.
Don’t you dare escape.
One step to the side
and I’ll shout.
You’re
worth ten gold coins.
You can’t get out of Pingting.
You know who I am?
Of course.
Or would I’ve brought you back?
Where else could I
get free help?
Go ahead.
I’ve...
I’ve learned about
the Fire Demon in your tribe.
It’s said she set the Earth Fire.
My father said
seniors made that up.
It’s not true.
Are you always afraid
it is true?
You’re hell-bent on
putting out the Earth Fire
to prove
your mother isn’t the Fire Demon, right?
No!
How could a Fire Demon
give birth to Goddess?
I said
it’s a cooked-up story.
Fine.
Let’s say it is.
What do you want to know?
I’ll tell you everything.
I have tons of questions.
What is God?
Why is it me?
Where is God from?
Did another God give birth to him?
If my mother was a God,
what about my grandmother?
My father is an ordinary person.
So
could a God and a person
create another God?
I’ve...
Never considered their reproduction.
I’m serious.
Why are you blushing?
It’s...
It’s never crossed my mind
that Goddess would discuss that with me.
Propagation is of great significance.
The Fire Tribe is sparsely populated
and fighting fire is dangerous.
We need enough populations
to guard the Flame Chilling Wall.
Unlike my father
who only has one daughter,
most families have more than one kid.
But
that doesn’t
concern you royals,
does it?
No wonder Gods are almost extinct
and you’re the sole heir to the Yuans.
I... I’m sorry.
I... I crossed the line.
What’s up?
Nothing.
You seem spirited
when you’re on that subject.
Not true.
But I guess
you’re right.
This morning,
when I helped a maid up
by touching her slightly,
she became excited and yelled
she was blessed by Goddess.
Others around were eager to touch her
to share my blessing.
God can’t be touched
by ordinary people easily.
Of course, they were grateful.
When I was young,
people in my tribe
forbade their children
from playing with me.
They were avoiding me
and calling me an evil demon.
Because of that,
my father had tons of fights with them.
He called that
exercise.
Soon,
people of Suchuan will know the new you.
Then
we can visit your mother together.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Master,
news came from Zhaodu.
Chief Priest has notified
every branch of Tianqi Sect
that Ritual of Eternity
will soon be held
to announce
God’s reappearance in Suchuan.
That’s fast.
Linglong
is as good
as I expected.
Do you also believe in that?
It’s been over 500 years
since the last Ritual of Eternity.
How come people still buy that?
That’s why
we should support
our young Goddess.
Moon Guards tried to intercept letters
Chief Priest sent to all fiefdoms
but some still got out.
They’ve already known
we’re going to hold Ritual of Eternity
and they’ll use that as an excuse
to come to Zhaodu
and see
if Goddess is real.
I’m not afraid of them.
They refused to come
even if I summoned them.
This time, I can
use this chance
to show them how powerful Zhaodu is.
Fei Tian,
isn’t that
what we need Goddess for?
So, to you,
she represents Zhaodu’s power?
Fei Tian,
I appreciate all that you’ve done
for my family.
But we both know
however hard we try,
it doesn’t change the fact
that Zhaodu is isolated
and the Yuans are declining.
Linglong is our hope
to turn things around.
Trust me.
We’ll prove it to you.
Suchuan is yours, Your Majesty.
You don’t need to prove anything
to anyone.
As per the late emperor’s will,
I’ve found teachers for you
to study history, the art of war,
and politics.
I’ve rectified the court
and eliminated the corrupted.
Whatever happens in Zhaodu
and whatever decision
you make,
I’ll support you
as always.
But
I fear that I’ll disappoint you.
I’m
a member of the Moon Tribe.
You know,
we don’t worship God
but the emperor only.
If you do care about her,
make sure of her safety first.
If she fails at the Ritual of Eternity,
you’ll
have her killed.
Fei Tian!
Zhaodu is my city.
Linglong is my girl.
No one can hurt her.
Go get prepared.
Those of the Chamber of Commerce
will come and make a scene again.
They’re really
giving me a headache.
Ritual of Eternity is a huge event.
Marquis Pingjiang will
take advantage of it
to rake in money.
Those merchants’ pockets
have almost been emptied
by all sorts of taxes he concocted
over the years.
They can’t wait for you
to marry Miss Yin
and gain her family’s support
to back the Chamber of Commerce
and battle Marquis Pingjiang.
Where are the two siblings?
Touring around the city
as you asked.
I want to eat this.
Lanterns!
All new lanterns!
Miss, would you like a lantern?
It’s of the latest style.
Round lanterns!
It tastes so good!
This place was the size of tofu
from Weisheng Yan’s place.
I didn’t know it’d be
so crowded and bustling
until we came here ourselves.
Back on the Bright Moon Island,
I heard Pingting was big
but it’s actually bigger than I thought.
How could we find Huotu Xin
in such a large city?
Just wait and see
if Weisheng Yan is a man of his word.
Weisheng Yan?
Yin Zhuang,
do you know
what kind of person he is?
He’s rich.
We’ve stayed
at his house for days
without seeing him once.
Don’t you find that strange?
I’m too busy
getting used to new things here
to think about him.
I still think
it’s a hasty decision
for you two to get married.
Xiao, you’re thinking too much.
Father’s decision
can’t be wrong.
But he has...
Left us.
Alright.
I know
you hate to see me leave,
don’t you?
I knew it.
But
I can’t stay with you forever.
Soon, I’ll become
too old
to get married.
No, you won’t!
Yes, I will.
I know that for a fact.
Girls should
have a grand wedding
in the most beautiful gown
when they’re the prettiest.
Look.
We’re in Pingting,
the richest city in Suchuan,
and the place you need to conquer.
Xiao,
I’m just a girl.
All I need
is to live a well-off life
and not to bring shame on our family.
But you’re different.
You’re the eldest son.
It’s your responsibility
to revitalize the Yin family.
Do you remember
what Juan said on the fishing boat?
This is Pingting,
not Bright Moon Island.
So
you should learn
to let me go.
How do I look?
You look great.
Let’s go.
He’s handsome!
Look how adorable
the local girls are.
You should
look around
and meet new people.
I know.
Come.
Let’s go shopping.
Look,
these are
the finest fabrics.
This one is good.
I like it.
Take a look.
Are there other fabrics?
What about those in this color?
The pattern is nice.
That’s not to my taste.
There’s more over there.
Xiao,
these fabrics are beautiful!
I can’t imagine how gorgeous
the dresses made of these will look.
Choose any fabric you like.
I’ll bag it for you.
Thanks.
Let me see those in different colors.
Look at these.
Sure.
Miss,
are you into this fabric?
You have good taste.
There’s only one piece
in town
and it’s been made into a dress.
Miss,
you can try it on.
Can I?
Someone must’ve
ordered that dress.
Don’t worry.
Feel free to try it on.
If you don’t like it,
we have other styles for you to choose.
Go put it on if you like.
Bring me the dress.
Yes.
Do I look good?
Xiao,
you don’t need to buy it for me.
It’s on the house.
This dress
is made for you.
What do you mean?
Is it you in the drawing?
That’s...
We have dresses your size
made of all kinds of fabrics
in our store.
Not just us.
A few days ago,
every store in town
received your portrait.
Wherever you go
and whatever you like,
we’ve had everything ready for you.
No wonder it fits me perfectly.
Is all that Weisheng Yan’s arrangement?
Yes.
He’s
surprisingly considerate.
Miss,
would you like matching headwear?
It’ll make you look
even better.
Why not?
That dress
is yours.
The fabric left will be destroyed.
That’s unnecessary.
Don’t waste it.
Weisheng Yan
doesn’t allow others
to wear the same dresses as yours.
Weisheng Yan,
when will it be?
Soon.
Marquis Pingjiang
is one step away
from emptying my vault himself.
Yes, Weisheng Yan.
Over the past year,
he’s taken money
from my business
in all kinds of names.
Now,
Zhaodu is suddenly
holding some
Ritual of Eternity.
Who knows
how much more he needs
to present Goddess in Zhaodu?
Just wait for it!
Goddess is Suchuan’s guardian.
No disrespect is allowed.
Guardian my foot!
If Goddess could keep me
from being robbed,
I’d fall prostrate in worship.
I don’t buy those corny tales.
The Yuans
must be cornered by the nobility
and they’re desperate
to assert their dominance.
Back to business.
Don’t go off-topic.
I’m asking you.
Tell me,
when are you
going to marry Miss Yin?
Aren’t you going to
other stores?
No.
They all have my portraits.
If I go,
more things will go to waste.
However rich Weisheng Yan is,
it’s wrong to squander money like this.
I’ll talk to him.
Ritual of Eternity.
What is that?
It’s to announce God’s reappearance.
Bullcrap!
There’s no God
in the world.
There is.
According to my grandfather,
our ancestors
used to be God’s servants.
Notice
Back in the day,
God could control the weather.
God or no God,
it has nothing to do with us.
That’s wrong.
It’s said
God’s reappearance is a warning.
Those bad people
will get punished.
Let’s go.
Linglong did it.
She was accepted by Zhaodu.
Yes.
But she still has to
go through the Ritual of Eternity.
With God’s reappearance,
the Yuans’ rejuvenation
and our family’s resurgence,
restoring Suchuan to its former glory
can be expected.
Look around.
Does anyone care about that?
We still
have a long way ahead.
It must be tough for Linglong
to be in Zhaodu alone.
We must find Huotu Xin quickly.
Look.
Wanted Reward: Ten coins.
Zhu Xi has made Huotu Xin a wanted man.
Isn’t he in danger?
Yin Zhuang,
go back first.
I’ll go ask around.
Xiao,
are you letting me
go back alone?
Aren’t you worried about my safety?
See those two?
They’re Weisheng Yan’s men.
They’ve been following us all day.
You’re safe with them.
Be careful.
Weisheng Yan,
you’ve promised us
that you’ll hook on to the Yins
to battle Marquis Pingjiang.
That’s why we invested
in your chamber.
It’s been days
since Miss Yin arrived.
Nothing has happened.
What’s going on?
Has she
turned you down,
Weisheng Yan?
Did you use the Yins
to coax us into investing in you?
The Yins are going downhill
but they’re still the oldest
and most prestigious family in Suchuan.
What’s that saying?
A lean camel is bigger than a horse.
As lean as it is,
it doesn’t eat dog food.
Shut up.
Don’t show off your ignorance.
Anyone else is better than you.
You’re simply jealous because
he’s getting married with Miss Yin.
You... You stay out of it.
It’s for everyone’s sake.
We all have concerns,
right?
It’s the heiress to the Yins.
A Yin, you know?
She isn’t like those harlots
you can buy in brothels.
Her family is renowned.
You know what?
That chick at Fuyan House
is as good as Miss Yin
if not better.
Her pretty face
and dainty hands...
Master! Master!
Weisheng Yan,
are they all your friends
in the Chamber?
It’s dry lately.
Make some tea
with the green tea I brought from home
for everyone
to taste.
Yes.
Miss... Miss Yin Zhuang.
Greetings, Miss Yin.
I apologize
for barging in like this.
My brother and I are new here.
I appreciate your hospitality these days
and I should’ve
visited you long ago.
That’s too kind of you.
We owe you an apology.
In this case,
should I leave
so that
you can continue
discussing your business
or may I stay
so that we can discuss
our marriage together?
I’ll
see you around.
Good day.
Miss Yin.
-Let’s go.
-How gorgeous!
Come on.
Take your eyes off her.
She’ll never be yours.
What a beauty!
-She’s incredible!
-Enough!
She’s prettier
than those in the drawings.
Go date your chick in the brothel.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪