Shoot first.
Vincenzo Cassano.
We're from the Interpol.
We came here to arrest you
and repatriate you.
Drop your gun, Vincenzo Cassano.
Stay away! Stay away from me.
Put your guns down.
KIM IN-YONG
Officer Kim In-yong.
Officer Baek Gyeong-su.
Yes.
Go tell your superior
that the Interpol had no evidence
and went back.
Also, take care of these bodies.
Understood?
Do as I say,
or you'll be dead within two days.
Got it, Officer Baek?
Yes.
You go back and tell your boss
to stop acting up and wait for his death.
Yes, I will.
I'll get going.
Wait. I can't let you go like this.
Here's your preview.
For a moment there,
I thought I was going to die.
Didn't you say
you were just going to lure Vincenzo
for the Interpol to catch him?
Yes, I did.
Where did you get a gun?
Well…
I bought one to kill Vincenzo.
The Chief Prosecutor
brought in the Interpol.
Why did you try to kill him yourself?
Ms. Choi, are you stupid?
Vincenzo is a Mafia.
Unless he gets a death sentence in Italy,
he'll come back to kill us.
How can you not know that?
So there were Vincenzo's men
at the ice rink?
Yes.
He hid five of his men there.
That sly bastard.
Then it means
he fooled us completely, doesn't it?
As frustrating as it is…
it seems so.
Was he aware
that the Interpol was coming to get him?
Seeing he hid his men there.
About that…
I'm not so sure.
Did he hire more men
like they do in the Mafia?
Yes, you're probably right.
That must be it.
Stay away from guns
if you value your life.
Let's go, Ms. Choi.
Bye, Ms. Choi.
I know you're all busy.
Don't bother coming to see me.
You're hiding something.
Of course not. Can't you see I got shot?
I need you to be honest with me.
Come on. You don't trust me?
Just hold my hand. I'm in pain.
It hurts so much.
-I'll call you.
-Where are you going?
EPISODE 18
So this is your first task
as the Chief Prosecutor?
You win some, you lose some.
That's how it is, right?
Now that you've done this yourself,
what do you think?
After one more try,
I might be able to master it.
Do you know what the biggest problem is
right now?
VIP WARD
What could it be?
I'm afraid
you might also just have made it
on Vincenzo's hit list.
If you had sat back,
you could have spared your life.
He won't kill me
just because I brought in the Interpol.
Stop making things worse
by meddling in affairs you're not good at.
Focus on keeping your position
and staying alive. All right?
You look awful.
Who gives her the right
to talk to me like that?
Yes. Chief Prosecutor speaking.
I'm not interested.
-Cheers.
Goodness.
If things had gone wrong, Mr. Cassano
would be on a plane right now.
That would have been horrible.
We almost said goodbye to you today.
We need to talk. It's urgent.
Han Seung-hyuk brought in the Interpol
to take you to Italy.
They'll be landing shortly.
What? Are you scared?
Of course.
We'll be surrounded by guns.
Just have one of them come close to me.
And leave the rest to me.
It's done.
-Great.
-Thanks.
Are you saying Paolo framed you?
-Yes.
-How can we trust you?
If my priority had been to escape,
I would have killed you all.
Leave me here. In return…
I have a present for you.
The list of bribes that Paolo gave
to politicians and ministers
and the recordings to prove that.
There's more.
Fly out to Malta tomorrow and look
for a paper company named Jason Fund.
Look into their accounting records
in that flash drive.
All of you will receive
a special promotion.
-Is it heavy?
-No, not at all.
-Give me some.
-I'm fine.
-It's okay.
-I'm really fine.
-You must be tired. Let me help.
-I'm not tired.
Why did you not betray me
when he said he'd make you the chairman?
He won't make me the real chairman.
I'll just be his puppet.
So I said no.
You did well today. Bye, then.
Wait a second.
They'll be suspicious.
Can you shoot me somewhere fleshy
so that the bullet just grazes me?
-In the arm?
-Yes.
-Get me the gun.
-Is it in the bag?
-Silencer.
-Quickly.
It might…
hurt more than you think. You might faint.
Don't worry. I can handle this much.
I didn't shoot yet.
-On three.
-One.
-Two.
It's not as bad as I thought,
Grandma. Why are you here, Grandma?
Hey.
Lovely morning.
-Can we have a word?
-Do you want a beating?
Gosh. Come on.
Please.
BYEBYE BALLOON TRAVEL
Jasmine tea? Coffee? Solomon's seal tea?
Don't bother.
Is there something you want to tell me?
The thing is…
a new hot-air balloon
arrived in Busan recently.
It's the latest model
and is very powerful.
It can fly extremely long distances.
Why are you telling me this?
ONE-TIME FREE TICKET
When you're in this line of work,
you might need to flee in a hurry one day.
You won't have time to book flights.
They might even bar you
from leaving the country.
Are you telling me
to escape using this?
We already helped 47 people
leave the country safely.
Sadly, two of them didn't make it.
I'd say it's a worthwhile bet.
Why are you trying to help me
after all I've done to you?
How should I put it?
It's kind of a wish fulfillment.
There was a man who dreamed of living
like Michael Corleone from The Godfather.
Then he met a real Corleone.
How could he not respect him?
Anyway, I'll hold on to it for now.
Yes?
Can you…
call me bro just once?
Bro…
my ass. I ought to beat you up.
All right. Fine.
Gosh, I've got goosebumps
all over my body.
My goodness.
Number one.
We need to remove the rest of
Jang Han-seok's pieces from the board.
All his pieces in Sangcheon-gu are gone.
So only the bigger pieces are left.
Then let's take care of them today.
It's going to be a long, hard day
for them.
Mr. Nam, what about the lawsuit
against Babel Tower?
It's ready.
All you have to do now is
submit it to the court.
-Gosh.
-I shouldn't do that.
-Oh, my.
-Look at that.
Come to Glory Sound Cafe by 3 p.m.,
or you'll be held responsible.
Chairman Jang Han-seok.
Why did he tell us to come
to a place like this?
I have no idea.
What are we going to do
in a public space like this?
His text startled me.
How dare he send us a message like that?
Are you sure you'll be able to
build Babel Tower?
-What?
-I heard
that they are reexamining it now.
-From my experience…
-Why is this being played here?
What are you doing? Turn that off.
Quick!
Where's the manager?
-The media are already
-Is something wrong?
-starting to suspect…
-Turn that off.
-Hurry up.
-Quick.
-Okay.
-It's a minor error with the document.
No big deal.
-It's even louder now!
-Wusang will
-Move.
-take care of it in a few days.
-I'll pull the plug.
-Don't you worry.
My goodness.
-Damn it.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Jang,
is this how you're going to play it?
It had nothing to do with me.
It was your house.
Your very own house!
It could have been a bug--
This is completely different
from when Mr. Seo died.
I'm not in this alone.
If you keep this up, I won't sit back.
Do you understand?
Mr. Hwang. Hello?
Damn it.
This time,
we're determined to root out
all corruption related to the Babel Tower.
You're all about to witness
the shocking truth.
Would you like to add anything, gentleman?
In the Bible, the Tower of Babel falls
because of human greed.
And that's exactly what's going to happen
in court soon.
The Babel Tower will fall
before it's even built.
Any message for them?
These are going to be
our last words for Babel.
"You can see yourself out."
Goodbye.
-Anything else?
-What's your plan?
-What will happen next?
-Wait!
Please add something!
NANYAK TEMPLE
Have some fruit.
Sorry. We're going out to beg for alms.
You're begging for alms
quite often these days.
You've been doing it every day
lately, right?
Are you struggling?
No. We're okay.
Please leave the fruit inside.
I appreciate it.
-Sure.
-Goodbye, then.
See you.
The temple can't make ends meet
without any visitors.
I feel sorry for them.
My goodness.
If they're begging for alms every day,
their situation must be pretty bad.
They're monks, so they won't have
any money saved.
Who would want to visit the temple
when this whole building is a mess?
I would go, but I'm a Christian.
Then why don't we all chip in
and help them out?
Right. We should help each other
during hard times.
I'll go and talk
to the laundromat owner, too.
-Okay.
-All right. Let's do that.
Since we handed in the files, should
we start leveling the playing field?
Yes. We should do this fiercely
as my father wanted.
Take it easy.
I should say the same to you.
I'll see you later.
All right.
They checked, but there were no bugs.
How on earth was it recorded, then?
There were a lot of people.
It's likely that it was one of them.
No. This is Vincenzo's doing.
A humiliation worse than death.
To give you that, I'm playing a game
of chess with you starting today.
And I'll get rid of your pieces
one by one.
They're all gone.
If it really is Vincenzo's doing,
it's a pretty big blow this time.
My gosh. Those spineless idiots.
We should've gotten rid of them as I said.
This happened
because you didn't listen to me.
JIPURAGI FILED A CLAIM
FOR DAMAGES AGAINST BABEL
Did something else happen?
Hong Cha-young filed a claim for damages
against the Babel Group.
That claim must be the checkmate.
CLAIM FOR DAMAGES
AGAINST ILLEGAL ACTS
FILED BY: CHO YEONG-UN AND 10 OTHERS
AGAINST: THE BABEL GROUP
PLAINTIFF'S DEMAND
CHIEF PROSECUTOR HAN SEUNG-HYUK
BABEL HAS HIRED ANT COMPANY
TO THREATEN THE TENANTS
VINCENZO
Yes, this is Chief Prosecutor
Han Seung-hyuk.
I saw off the Interpol agents you sent.
I just did what's legally appropriate.
You shouldn't have done that.
Why does "legally appropriate" sound
so awkward
when it's coming from a Chief Prosecutor.
Let's make a deal tonight.
Well…
why would I make a deal with you?
You should if you want to live.
I'm hanging up on the count of three.
One, two.
Wait… He hung up.
Damn it. He has the upper hand.
What kind of a deal does he want to make?
Bring some wet towels.
Let me join you.
How do you always find me?
Are you my stalker or what?
You may not know when,
but you look pretty calm
for someone who's going to die.
Didn't it occur to you
that we could kill you first?
No, not at all.
But if you win the lawsuit
regarding the Babel Tower,
we'll let you live a bit longer.
There's no need.
I'll fulfill my dream of living longer
at a convenience store
by drinking some yogurt.
But it won't be a life worth living,
because we'll come after you again.
VOICE RECORDING
Pyo Hyeok-pil and I
were ordered by Choi Myung-hee
to kill Hong Yu-chan
and disguise it as a car accident.
Oh, my poor Crystal Balls.
Recordings like that are useless.
On Choi Myung-hee's orders,
we've gotten rid of the following people.
Congressman Baek Min-u,
Park Dong-cheon of Gudam Police Station,
Deputy Minister Jung Jin-taek,
the Good Politics Committee
Chairman Lee Seon-u,
Reporter Lee Yang-su,
TQ Logistics'
labor union leader Kim Min-hyeok…
What do you want with those useless names?
I'll use this
to give you a Christmas present this year.
About 30 years in jail.
Don't you think the pot
is calling the kettle black?
Who's the pot?
Oh, I know. You're the pot.
-And I'm the kettle.
-You and Vincenzo…
Do you think you'll look clean
if you expose us?
We're not trying to look clean.
We just want to have the upper hand.
Yes. That's the spirit.
Good point.
Let's see who wins in the end.
All right.
I get that I upset you,
but people are bound to get hurt
during a war.
You know, like a collateral damage.
Anyway…
what deal did you mean?
A deal regarding your life.
What?
I was going to let you live,
but I decided to kill you after that stunt
you pulled with the Interpol.
Seriously?
That's not something to make a deal about.
Life is the most precious gift
that was given to us.
Hey!
I'm a Chief Prosecutor
at the Namdongbu Office.
How dare you be so disrespectful
to your elder, you little brat?
Don't talk about age.
All age does is
give you a lot of responsibilities.
Don't take that tone with me!
You little brat!
Show some respect!
But, hey!
I'm signaling for you to come in!
I told you to come in
once I hit the table!
Why are you all so clueless?
Darn it.
Gosh, my hand hurts.
You're pretty old-fashioned and childish.
It's quite disappointing.
Fights are always
old-fashioned and childish.
I'm sure you know that.
Don't worry.
The bullets went through your legs.
What are you waiting for?
Come on! Do something!
Don't you have any guns?
-Get out, all of you.
-Get out.
Get out!
Come on, get out.
Take those guys on the floor.
I've never seen a sly person
who's not a coward.
You're right. I'm pretty sly.
I'm sorry.
Please don't kill me.
Who are you?
This is what you get
for disrespecting your elders.
Those darn geezers!
How dare they do this to him?
They're full of energy, aren't they?
They're provoking us.
Look at his foot.
Should we just get rid of them all?
They still have quite a lot of power
in this country.
It could just backfire on us.
It may not be now,
but we'll deal with them eventually.
They're useless to us now.
A devil tantalizes
another devil…
Stop!
-Get him!
-Damn it!
Get him.
Let's go.
There was no need
to beat him up like that.
You know who I am, don't you?
Mr. Kim.
Prosecutor Jung In-kuk and I
have been close for a long time.
He told me
to find you if I wanted to open
the secret room
in Geumga Plaza.
I can't open it.
The iris recognition device is
inside the room.
Then we should find another way.
Who designed the security system?
I don't know.
Mr. Wang hired that person himself.
When installing security systems
in another country, you use local people
because security structures and methods
are different for each country.
Here.
You'll have to do some work
with my men starting today.
Look into all the security experts
and hackers
who were working in Korea
during that time.
How would I do that?
You're an intelligence agent.
You'd better pull it off
if you don't want to die with your family.
What is this?
Hey! Go!
Come on!
CHIEF PROSECUTOR HAN SEUNG-HYUK
We can't just sit back and watch anymore.
Mr. Jang could really end up dying.
Terrorism, shooting…
Just arrest them and Vincenzo.
You should know better.
Arrest them?
That's only possible
when we have the upper hand.
If anything goes wrong,
all our bribes and the Guillotine file
could be revealed.
You're the Chief Prosecutor,
and you can't catch one lousy Mafia?
You were an ace prosecutor
of the Namdongbu office.
Can't you do anything right?
Hey!
You're in the Chief Prosecutor's office
right now!
Lower your voice.
All right, fine.
You know…
I've been thinking hard about it.
Let's use one of the Mafia's tactics.
The safest place to be right now
is jail.
You know what I mean?
Stop talking nonsense.
It does make sense.
Even for Vincenzo Cassano,
breaking into a jail cell won't be easy.
What do you mean?
Are you telling me to go to jail?
Just for a week or two. I'll make sure
you feel at home there.
Ms. Choi, you know how much I hate jail.
I've been hiding my identity
because I didn't want to go to jail.
I know that.
I'm not telling you to stay there.
It's just for your protection.
Protection or not,
I don't want to go to jail.
You must admit it now.
Vincenzo…
We're no match for him.
Darn it!
I really mean it.
I don't want to go to jail!
Don't be afraid.
I'll make sure your cell
is like a hotel room.
Darn it.
BABEL GROUP
Mr. Jang Han-seok?
We're from the Namdongbu
Prosecution Service.
We are arresting you
on charges of tax evasion.
Me?
You have the right to consult an attorney,
to explain yourself,
and to a writ of habeas corpus.
You're always arresting innocent people.
Just be quiet. There are people watching.
Let me talk to my brother for a minute.
Launch Babel Bio while I'm away.
I postponed it.
What?
There are a lot of rumors
about Babel Bio right now.
They're saying it's a front for inflating
stocks and manipulating accounts.
Who are you to decide that?
No, it wasn't all me.
The board and the Planning Division
advised me.
-Hey.
-And sir…
you told me to become a businessman
like Elizabeth Holmes.
But she's a fraud…
and she's in prison.
So what you were saying
was for me to become a fraud.
But I can't do that.
I don't want to cause any trouble for you.
Do you…
really have a death wish?
This is exhausting.
Why would I die?
This is all for your sake.
Take him.
Anyone hungry?
All right. Get out.
You must've had a tough time, sir.
-It's been a while, Mr. Jung.
-Hello, sir.
It's been a while for me too, sir.
Vincenzo won't stand still.
Are you sure you can return?
Did he not threaten you?
He did once.
But a prosecutor should never give in
to a Mafia.
Next week, he's going to become
an assistant chief.
He'll have more power then.
I see.
I'll look forward to it.
Thank you, sir.
Me too, sir.
You have good drinking etiquette.
I may lack knowledge,
but I'm confident about my etiquettes.
It's hot.
-By the way…
-Yes?
You won't kill me, right?
Yes.
Because it kind of looks like
you're repenting.
How can you tell if I'm repenting, though?
I could be putting up a front.
You don't repent with words.
You do it by showing
how much you've changed.
I don't know how long it'll last,
but you're keeping it up pretty well.
My gosh.
How are you so eloquent?
That was a compliment.
You're just amazing.
By the way, why are you helping me
despite the chairman position?
Why am I helping you?
Because you just feel
like a brother to me.
It's strange.
You curse at me, and it's fine.
We play hockey, and I feel at ease.
And it just feels like
I'm drinking with a friend.
That's how I feel.
I'm only asking because I'm tipsy.
Can I treat you like a brother
when we're alone?
No.
I understand, Mr. Cassano.
Fine, but you better mind your manners.
Okay, bro.
The food got cold.
It smells weird.
There's some left.
-Hey.
-Yes?
It's a bit salty.
Maybe there's too much salt.
-Is that it?
-Yes.
Every time I invest, it's a flop.
He gave me some tips.
Share some tips with me.
I'm so jealous.
INTERNATIONAL SECURITY
INTELLIGENCE SERVICE
Jang Han-seo, you bastard.
Inmate 6723, you have a visitor.
I'm glad. I was bored.
What do you think?
Don't I look good in these clothes?
You do.
You look relaxed like you're in Cancún.
It's nice in here.
And people are nice too.
Do you think you're safe in there?
You must have people looking after you.
The head of the jail
must treat you well too.
I'm sure you did this in Italy too,
so you must know.
I'm sorry for being a party pooper,
but do you think everything is going
according to your plan?
Don't you think I'd know
that your car was bulletproof?
Do you really think
those men failed to kill you that night?
Persuade Jang Han-seok to go to jail
without him knowing.
I can make that happen,
but wouldn't he be suspicious
if I came up with a charge?
You'll find a reason
to arrest him tomorrow morning.
Okay.
I'm the one…
who put you in there.
Nothing's more entertaining
than an enemy who doesn't know
why they're losing.
Just kill me, you Mafia bastard.
Stop bothering me.
Tell me the truth.
Why are you keeping me alive?
You're afraid, aren't you?
You're afraid of the aftermath.
Right?
I thought you were smart,
but you still haven't caught up.
Let me tell you something new.
Guess what the Mafia used to call me.
It means "a cat that's full."
A cat that's full
toys with a mouse all day
before eating it.
When I was little,
a robber murdered my foster parents.
I joined the Mafia and tormented him
for two years.
Then he attempted suicide.
I had him receive treatment
in the best hospital.
The day he was discharged,
I treated him to the best meal
and killed him.
The real reason I've let you live so far
is because you're my mouse.
That's who I really am.
This is my last time toying with you
before gobbling you up.
You're going to witness
the Babel Tower falling from your cell.
I can get out of here tomorrow if I want.
This is the information on your
paper company I got from Ragusang Gallery.
Did you think I gave Mr. Jung
the original copy?
Idiot.
You little…
With this, you'll be in there
for another whole month…
no matter how hard they rack their brains
to get you out.
I hope you enjoy…
seeing the Babel Tower fall
from your cell.
Inmate 6723, let's go back.
Let me go!
About the information
on the paper company.
Did he say there were no copies?
Yes, that's what he said.
How could you blindly believe him?
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
It'll take some time
since it's a criminal charge.
Yes.
Chairman Jang won't be released
anytime soon.
At this rate,
he might as well live behind bars.
Isn't that what many people want?
Hey…
You're right.
Chairman Jang Han-seo can retrieve
the Guillotine file.
Let's keep him behind bars a bit longer
with that information.
Should we?
All right, then.
I'm more concerned
about the Babel Tower lawsuit.
Who knows what Vincenzo
and Hong Cha-young may do?
Sir, could you postpone my promotion
for a while?
I'll take care of the lawsuit
and Chairman Jang's case myself.
Hey, Luca.
Mr. Consigliere, I've arrived
at Incheon Airport.
"Incheon"?
What's wrong?
I had no idea that this was all his plan.
I'm sorry, sir.
In any case, I'm safe here, right?
Yes, sir.
Mr. Jung and I will take care
of the paper company
as well as the Babel Tower.
I can't leave for now, right?
No, sir.
I refuse to watch Babel Tower fall
from behind bars.
Get me out of here as soon as possible.
Got it?
Yes, sir.
And Han-seo…
Keep an eye on him.
He seems to have awfully matured lately.
I'm looking for Vincenzo Cassano.
-Consigliere?
-Yes.
Follow me.
-How have you been, Luca?
-Excuse me.
Luca!
Are these your friends?
Everyone likes you.
Luca!
Consigliere.
Dario and Sebastian have been killed
by the Luciano family.
There's no telling who's next.
What the hell is Paolo doing?
Paolo was indifferent from the get-go.
There's intel that the police are planning
to catch him,
so he's packing up to leave.
That heartless bastard!
Their conversation seems quite serious.
I think a few people lost their lives,
and Vincenzo just swore.
Consigliere.
Come back to Italy and save our family.
If you don't,
it will be over for our family.
I've narrowed it down to
four security experts and hackers.
Look at the last page.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
Her current home address is Geumga Plaza.
That's right.
So the locksmith has been living
right next to the vault.
What is this?
Don't go…
Come on, now.
It's not like he's going to fight
in a war.
-Stop it.
-But he is going to fight in a war.
He might be fighting a battle
to the death--
-Enough.
-Okay.
But I can't.
Mr. Nam
I'll only be away for two weeks.
Don't worry.
But what if two weeks become four,
and four weeks become…
Please!
I didn't know you could be so troublesome.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
We'll be okay for the time being.
Chairman Jang is in jail after all.
Come on. Don't look at us like that.
Geumga Plaza is like a fortress.
Mr. Nam.
Please, don't cry.
Wipe your tears before you see him off.
Hey, come on out!
Coming!
This is red pepper paste
and seasoned dried radish.
Have them while you're there, okay?
-Thank you.
-I'll put it inside.
There.
This is pickled lettuce that my mom made.
I'll put it in your suitcase.
This will bring you good luck.
Keep it with you at all times.
It's true. They say it has magical powers.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
We'll protect this place
for the next two weeks.
You will come back for sure, right?
Of course, he will. Don't be absurd.
He'll take care of everything
and return right away.
Buddha will be by your side at all times.
Help us, merciful Buddha.
Thank you.
Be careful.
Thanks, bro.
Have a safe trip.
You should go.
Your passport?
Have a safe trip.
Make sure to eat on time.
Don't take too long.
Bye.
Don't cry.
-Why are you crying?
-He'll be back soon.
It's only for two weeks.
Are you sure?
You cried.
-I didn't.
-You did, didn't you?
You should go.
I'll see you off.
It's okay.
I'll be back.
Prepare for the lawsuit while I'm away.
Okay.
And you don't need to buy me
a perfume or scarf on your way back.
Never.
Go inside and have a cup of coffee.
If something happens,
call me right away.
Don't you worry.
I'll get going then.
Luca.
Mr. Cassano!
Friends are…
like two souls
in one body.
Don't get hurt…
since it'll hurt me too.
I promise.
Would you like some wine?
No, thank you.
HOW TO BEFRIEND A BIRD
Nice to meet you, Ms. Seo.
We won't become friends,
so I'll skip the introduction.
Open it right now.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know how.
Say that one more time,
and I'll kill you.
Did you see him off?
Of course.
He'll take care of everything and return
like he's been doing here.
Of course.
But this place does feel so empty
without him.
Two weeks?
We'll be busy preparing for the trial,
and time will fly.
You're right. Let's focus on that.
We can do it.
It's open.
Where's the gold and the Guillotine file?
I have no idea.
Damn it. Where did you hide them?
I'm telling you the truth. I have no idea.
You little…
Tell me the truth.
Where is it?
Damn it.
Go get her.
Mr. Tak!
Mr. Lee!
Mr. Park!
What's wrong?
Some thugs barged into Nanyak Temple.
Who?
Mr. Nam, hurry upstairs
and call the others.
I can't! Then you'll be in danger.
Now!
Ms. Seo.
Come here while I'm asking you nicely.
Who are you?
This has nothing to do with you.
Stay out of it. It's dangerous.
It does have something to do with me.
I'm her lawyer.
I see.
Jipuragi Law Firm.
You're Lawyer Hong Yu-chan's daughter.
How do you know my dad?
How could I not? He was an incredible man.
Whatever.
-Just get lost.
-I guess
he didn't teach you
how to respect your elders.
He taught me to show absolutely no respect
to people like you.
Bring her over.
Get your hands off of her!
You can't take her.
No!
Stop right there.
Mr. Cassano.
Are you two all right?
Why didn't you go?
I took care of it in another way.
And…
I forgot to feed Inzaghi as well.
Anyway, stand back.
Do you happen to be Vincenzo Cassano?
That's none of your business.
I'll make you pay
in less than five minutes.