(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
- Yes. - Yes.
- Director, the last shot. - Okay, then.
Thank you so much, sir.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- Cheers. - I love you, sir.
Don't worry and just do your jobs.
- Yes. - We trust in you.
Get in the back, sir. I'll drive.
No, Director. Tonight, I'll drive you.
I didn't have that much to drink. It's fine.
- Get in. - Yes, sir.
- Get the door for him. - Oh, right.
Gosh.
I can't believe I'm hitching a ride in your car, Director.
It's my lucky day.
You could let me drive.
(Ms. Na Se Na)
What's the problem, Ms. Na?
I'm calling to see if you got back safely.
I'm on my way home right now.
I'm sorry for leaving first, sir.
My mother suddenly said she doesn't feel well.
If your mother isn't well, you should rush to her.
I'm not that stuffed-up an old man.
What was that? Did we just hit a man?
I... I must call for help.
What should I dial? What's the number?
- Put that down! - What?
He's already dead.
Do you want to lose everything?
Yes.
If you all keep your mouths shut,
I'll prevent your companies from going bankrupt.
Your lives from now on,
I will pay for everything, okay?
Okay?
Okay.
(Ms. Na Se Na)
Ms. Na, do you get what I'm saying?
If you stay by my side,
I will make you...
a full-time regular teacher.
I can even make you my school's principal, okay?
(My daughter)
(Dark Hole)
My dad told me that...
human beings are the scariest.
I'm scared of the mutants,
but even more so of people like Jin Seok.
In a situation like this, he tried to save his own skin.
However much the world may change,
bad people will eventually pay for what they did.
Do you really think so?
My dad died in a hit-and-run accident.
But no one suffered the consequences.
In this world,
it's the victims who pay the price.
(Order, justice, love)
"Order, justice, love".
It's all a lie.
Isn't it?
Why? What is it?
What are you going to check now?
Let's move on.
The punk just never listens.
What about your mom?
My mom died when I was in elementary school.
I have no family.
I saw the serial killer who murdered my husband.
She put a white cover over his head...
and injected him in the neck.
I still can't believe that she did such a terrible thing.
Detective. Are you all right?
(Muji Hospital)
Where did he get to? Why can't I find him?
I knew this would happen.
I posted a complaint that...
we shouldn't accept any more useless immigrants.
- A petition. - It's not "complaint"?
You're so ignorant.
Why do you think Madam Kim wants us to find him?
He's a lowlife.
She says he got dirty blood on his hands.
Dirty blood?
Are you saying he killed someone?
I don't know that much,
but Madam Kim said he's a lowlife who did something very bad.
We must catch him and offer him as a sacrifice if we're to live.
- Shine the light in every corner. - Okay, let's look.
- Oh, come on. - You idiot.
- It's too dark. - Let's keep looking.
I want to go home, Mom.
Why don't you have anything? What did you do, you fool?
You moron!
I want to go home.
Who did this?
My goodness.
Darn it.
I want to go home!
I don't want to die.
You managed to get everyone to stand on your side.
I'm impressed by your charisma.
What's wrong?
Do you also want to live?
Why do you ask? Are you going to help me live?
Not me. Him.
I won't fall for that crazy nonsense.
Should I...
just stab you or not?
You tell me.
Do you think you can kill me?
What do you think you're doing?
You won't ever be able to kill me.
You'll be the one seeing blood, not me.
(Authorized personnel only)
I know you're in here.
It's okay. You can relax.
I'm the security guard here.
I'm trying to protect you.
The guy who came with you...
asked me to fetch you.
Really?
Are you really a good person?
Yes.
I'm a good person.
You can relax.
My gosh, there he is.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Bring him to me.
If you want to live,
just do as he tells you.
I saw everything.
I know that your hands were once covered in blood.
No... No! He tried to kill me first.
Don't be scared.
I'm only here to give you joy.
(Master key)
Nice.
I bet there's nothing here.
Our ancestors were right.
A crisis comes with opportunities.
Excuse me.
Can I go to the bathroom?
I'm sorry I made you wait.
What was that?
Is he not a mutant?
Hey, you...
What... Why...
What was he doing here?
Who is he?
He's just...
Here you go. Eat up.
Ma'am, thank you for cooking.
Are you sure this is okay?
We just need to make sure Director Choi doesn't find out.
You're right. It's not like he'll kill us.
Don't get too greedy and end up with an upset stomach.
I won't be able to help you then. You got that?
Eat up before it gets cold.
It won't taste good if it gets cold.
Hey, it's darn good.
What? Did you just say "darn"?
Did you just cuss at me?
Grandma, it means it's really delicious.
Oh, really?
Chan and Do Yoon, you should try some too.
Here you go.
What do you think? Is it darn good?
Yes, it's darn good.
What's wrong?
I think I just heard something.
Is it that darn old man again?
You mean Director Choi?
Yes. I don't care if he's a director or a nobody.
That little jerk just can't shut his mouth.
You sure have the mouth of a sailor.
You'd better eat up before I swear at you.
Ma'am, you should start a pancake restaurant someday.
I'll invest.
Me too.
You're still wet behind the ears. You can't have any money.
I'll get a job.
I'm an amazing waitress.
Do Yoon, you don't like the pancakes?
- I do. - Then why aren't you eating?
I'm saving them for the detective.
Don't worry.
I've put some aside...
for those who went to get the medicine.
Hey, why are you crying?
My mom used to love pancakes. Especially kimchi pancakes.
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
Why are you crying too?
Don't worry, guys.
I'm sure they're all doing fine.
Stay strong and eat well...
so you can meet your parents again. Do you understand?
It looks like you're all having fun.
Where's everyone else? Why did you come back alone?
What? Do you want to die too?
Hey. Watch your mouth.
Mind your own business.
- Where's the medicine bag? - You're still alive?
The janitor might die because of you.
He's going to die anyway. What's the use of medicine?
He must've stolen the medicine bag.
You little rat. You're dead meat.
Come here.
Are you okay?
Put that down. I said, put that down!
He's acting like a mutant.
Shut it! I'm not a mutant. I'm not!
Go away. Don't come near me.
I said, don't come near me!
What's with that punk? Has he lost his mind?
My goodness.
(Searching for Creativity)
Darn it.
You want to kill them all, don't you?
What?
Who are you?
What on earth are you?
Didn't you see the disdain in their eyes?
What are you trying to do?
They're just a bunch of vermin anyway.
Kill them all.
Who are you?
Come out. Come out, you bastard!
Don't you want to make people fear you?
What?
Make them scared of you.
Isn't that what you want?
I can help you.
Let them know how intimidating you can be.
Kill everyone who has ever looked down on you.
Fine. It's all over now anyway.
They should all just die.
What happened to the detective and the girl then?
We parted near the pedestrian overpass.
Well...
I'm sure they'll get back soon.
Goodness.
Look what happened because of that lunatic.
I'll be right back.
Look over there. Is that the smoke?
The mutants are here!
Run! The mutants are coming! Run away!
- What? - The mutants are coming!
- Hurry up! - We must stop them!
- Come on! - Hurry up!
Run! The mutants are coming!
The mutants are coming! Hurry up and run!
- Grandma! - You have to run.
- Grandma. - Go on, Chan.
- Grandma! - Chan!
- We have to run. Hurry! - I can't.
- What about my grandma? - Hurry!
Grandma...
Run faster!
We have to run. Come on.
- Chan! - Chan is here.
- Run! - Let's go!
- Hurry up! - Come on!
Who is it? Who's crying?
Let me see, punk.
No! Stop!
Come in.
Come on. Hurry.
- Let me in. - Oh, no.
- You can't. - Open the door.
- Let her inside! - No.
Save me! Let me in!
(New Wing Lobby)
What are you doing?
Why aren't you stopping the mutants?
They got through the barricade.
We have to get out of here.
You useless fool.
No one's running away!
Do you still not get it?
Father.
Why are you here?
You didn't show yourself even when your mother died.
Let's talk.
What nonsense do you want to say now?
The physics teacher.
I fired her because she took a bribe from a parent.
Don't lie. I heard from everyone else.
You made up some excuse to fire her.
Why?
You can't fire people like that just because you don't like them.
You naive fool.
Do you think a full-time high school teacher position...
is easy to get?
- What? - Do you think you got...
a full-time position...
as soon as you graduated because you're so competent?
You're able to keep your position...
because someone before you left.
Of all the things you accomplished,
what do you think you did on your own?
Did you do that for me?
Because of you,
I was causing harm to others without even knowing about it.
Don't be so weak.
That's how the world is.
No.
The world isn't like that.
It's you that's like that.
Do you still not get it?
This place is done for!
Shut your mouth!
I am this school!
For as long as I live,
this place never disappears.
[VIU Ver] OCN E06 'Dark Hole'
"Breach at Muji High School"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Where were you all this while?
Pull yourself together! What's wrong with you?
Why did you do that to me today?
- What? - Why did you do that to me?
- I've had enough. - No! Save me!
What are you doing?
I can't breathe!
I will make you pay for what you did to me!
(Security Office)
Well? Isn't this fun?
The people see you...
with fear in their eyes as they tremble.
(No service)
Get out.
Mister! Help me!
Mister!
Help me! Don't leave me!
(Muji High School)
Open the door! Let us in!
Get in, quick.
Hurry up. Sit down.
Darn it.
Get out.
Do you think you can run from me?
We have to leave.
(Muji High School)
- Over here! - Over here!
Over here!
Dong Rim.
Detective! The bus stopped.
Go.
Go, now!
Dong Rim, climb down slowly. I'll catch you.
I'll catch you. Take your time.
That's it. Slowly.
Take your time.
I got you.
Detective. Are you okay?
Get on the bus.
Get on, quick.
- Come on. - Thanks.
What's that?
Isn't that a mutant?
A mutant? Where?
It's coming this way.
Why on earth would it come here?
If it tries to come in, you go outside and kill it, okay?
- Why us? - What?
Then must I?
Wait.
Open the door.
It's not a mutant. It's a pregnant woman.
- Open the door, quick. - Help me!
(Muji Hospital)
Ma'am, are you all right?
You can't pass out.
Take her to the ER.
Bring a bed now!
- Get a bed! - Stay with me.
She isn't well. Put her on saline.
Okay.
You're awake.
It's okay, ma'am. You're safe.
What? Speak slowly.
Pock... Pock...
I think she's saying "pocket".
(Prisoner record)
That ward was closed.
(Help! There are survivors here.)
(Prisoner record)
Doctor, what's wrong?
(Emergency Medical Center)
(Fire door)
Everyone, they're back. They're finally back.
Please help.
Let me treat your wound.
Thank goodness.
(Emergency Center)
Officer Park.
He's not a prison guard. He's a murder.
(Prisoner record)
- Oh, my gosh. - My goodness.
Step back.
I said step back.
Hey, put down your guns.
I said put down your guns.
Put your guns down!
- Please don't do this. - Walk away from your weapons.
Take a step back.
Keep going. Good. Stay there.
(Muji Hospital)
I want you to drive.
What? Where are we going?
Just be quiet and get inside.
(Ministry of Justice)
We could die if we leave this place.
If we don't leave this place, we'll die anyway.
Head to the highway.
Whose call are you waiting for?
It's not like that.
- A woman? - What do you take me for?
- Is it another weird woman? - She's not weird.
- Name? - Yoon Saet Byeol.
He'll be safe too, won't he?
Hey, have you lost your mind?
- You don't need to go. - So we just let him take her?
Wait. Here's the ambulance key.
Please save Ms. Yoon.
Tae Han! Tae Han!
It's beautiful how he's willing to sacrifice his life.
What happened to the main building?
Jin Seok got rid of the barricade.
What about the kid?
I'm not sure.
When I got there,
the place was a mess due to the black smoke and mutants.
Hwa Sun.
My name is Do Yoon. I'm eight years old.
You're coming back, right?
- Stop the bus. - What?
They're alive.
Look over there. They're still alive.
That's the broadcasting studio.
The studio is soundproof, so I guess it's safe there.
Detective, there are way too many mutants.
We can't save them on our own.
Plus, we can't even guarantee that they're okay.
Mutants only attack people who are fine.
The fact that they're all together means they're alive.
Stop being crazy. Let's just get out of here.
We don't have time for this.
We can't leave without them.
Stop being so frustrating!
Listen.
What if your parents or children were in there?
Would you still want to leave?
The detective is right.
Yes, she's right. Let's save them too.
My gosh.
We can't abandon them when they're still alive.
What do you want?
This is completely crazy.
Why are you trying to save someone you don't even know?
The girl who got kidnapped was Young Sik's crush.
I owe him.
I need to save her for his sake.
You need this to arrest him.
I'm not a cop anymore.
I would rather take your gun.
But do you even know where he went to?
He'll try to leave the city.
Soon Il, you know the murderer who killed the nurse?
Can you find him for me?
What? All by myself?
Well, obviously.
You can do it, right?
You know I always got calls from the homicide department.
- They wanted to scout... - Yes, I know.
They said you had a good hunch for finding criminals.
I have faith in you.
Tae Han.
If you come back as a mutant,
I'll kill you myself. Do you understand?
Are you shooting a movie or what? Stop being so corny.
Now leave. I need to go.
Careful.
(911 Emergency)
You be careful too.
(Muji Hospital)
Officer Park.
Darn serpent.
Were you talking to me?
What? I didn't say anything.
Whatever. Can we talk for a minute?
Sure.
His eyes look like a serpent's.
What did you just say?
Nothing. I'm going.
- Where are we going? - Just follow me.
Hey.
Stop going up. It's dangerous.
Why are you so scared? You're a police officer.
You get scared too easily.
What is this place?
Officer Park, I thought of something.
You know your debt, right?
How about I write off your debt if you do something for me?
What? What is it?
Let me just borrow that for a moment.
What do you need the gun for?
Didn't you see earlier?
I never let anyone look down on me.
Especially not Yoo Tae Han and that shaman.
Give me the gun and leave while I'm being nice.
I can't do that.
If I lend my gun to anyone, I'll lose my job.
Tae Han doesn't know, right?
That he got dismissed from the force because of you.
Welcome, Officer Park.
Officer Park, why are you so surprised?
Is there a problem?
What are you talking about? I'm not surprised.
Aren't you feeling well? Why are you sweating so much?
I'm wearing thermals.
You know, those extra warm ones.
Come have a drink with us.
We have some food too.
Hey, chop up some intestines for Officer Park.
Yes, sir.
- Come here. - No, thanks.
No, I'm really fine. I just ate.
I had intestine soup.
Gosh.
How can you be joking around...
when you still owe me?
You see, can you wait for just another month?
Goodness. You shouldn't have been so greedy.
Why did you have to gamble with borrowed money?
Look at all the trouble you've caused.
Should I just report you right now?
Is the number 112 or 114?
It's 112, sir.
Oh, I see.
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
Please let this slide.
Officer Park, your showmanship is impressive.
Officer Park.
Are you sure you'll do whatever I tell you to?
Hey.
I need you to take care of Yoo Tae Han.
He's an officer too.
How can I take care of him?
Just make a report...
that he took bribes.
I'll take care of the rest.
"Hey, your man, Soon Il, sold you out..."
"to pay off his gambling debts."
It's going to be really interesting,
don't you think?
You can't do this!
No! Please!
Give me the gun!
No!
Hey, stay with me.
Stay with me.
Please.
Come on.
This is bad.
Let's go. Come on.
Her condition is getting worse.
Her vitals are unstable, and the baby isn't doing well.
Doctor, please save Ji Hye.
- Put an oxygen mask on her. - Yes, Doctor.
Let me have a look.
I'll do it.
We must hurry up.
Get me some oxytocin.
Hurry!
Ji Hye.
Hang in there.
Ma'am, look at me.
It's okay. Stay with me.
It's okay.
Nurse!
(Medication Protocols)
(Propofol)
Ji Hye, stay with me. Hang in there.
Ji Hye.
The uterine contraction is causing the baby's heart rate to drop.
Doctor, please save Ji Hye and our baby.
Doctor.
Get as much equipment as you can.
Thank you, Doctor.
Ji Hye, hang in there.
(Emergency escort)
(Ministry of Justice)
(Jingan Supermarket)
Detective.
I'll try to do as you said.
Please be careful.
Okay.
(Muji High School)
(Restricted Area)
It's Hwa Sun. She's back!
Do Yoon, are you all right? Will you open the door?
Put on your masks.
Leave through the east exit.
You'll see a school bus.
- Hwa Sun. - Go.
Are you both okay?
- Yes. - And the grandma?
- Take good care of her for me. - I will.
Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
Did my mom become like them too?
It's okay. Let's get out of here.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
Do Yoon. Get away from me!
What about the detective?
She's still inside with Do Yoon.
Dong Rim. Dong Rim!
Dong Rim. Han Dong Rim.
Hwa Sun.
Lee Soo Yeon?
(All child actors underwent psychological therapy.)
(Special thanks to Lee Cheol Min.)
(Dark Hole)
This is what the monster wants.
For everyone to tremble in fear.
He will protect us from this confusion.
We believe!
To end this,
I must find out what the monster is.
The murderer called Lee Soo Yeon that you're looking for.
She's with me now.
It's not dangerous, is it?
Don't worry.
It's all over now.