(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
(Director's Office)
Don't stand there...
like a thief and just come in.
Mr. Choi. Take a seat.
Do you know what this is, Mr. Choi?
It's a pistol.
It's not just a pistol.
It's a badge of honor.
It was a gift from the President himself...
for serving my country for my whole life.
Do you know how many people suffered because of that pistol?
They suffered?
If I hadn't captured those traitors,
the great world we live in right now wouldn't exist.
Don't justify what you did.
The age of using power to suppress others is over.
Listen carefully to what I say.
As long as I have this badge of honor,
on this campus, my word is law and justice.
(Dark Hole)
It's Lee Soo Yeon. She's back.
I need to check for myself if Soo Yeon's really back.
Even my husband died. How do you expect me to ignore this?
What could this be? A meteorite?
- What's wrong with your eyes? - Stay away!
I'll gouge your eyes out.
What did you see in the hole?
My friend's eyes turned black like yours and he went weird.
You must know something.
Why did you do it?
I see things out of the blue.
Lee Soo Yeon.
I saw the serial killer who murdered my husband.
Hey, Han Dong Rim!
Do you know what a sinkhole is?
What are you doing?
What's that?
Is there something going on outside?
I'll gouge your eyes out.
Please help me.
I think something happened to my daughter.
That woman also had black eyes just like him.
Do Yoon. Do Yoon! Jung Do Yoon!
- Mom! - Go! Now!
Mom!
- Young Sik. - Are you going to beat me again?
If you hear this, come to Muji High School.
We have a shelter.
Let's hurry up and go inside.
What could the sound that only you heard be?
I don't know anything for sure yet,
but considering how the mutants suddenly stopped attacking,
I think they're being controlled by something.
Hello? Please open the door!
Where's the woman? That woman inhaled black smoke too.
What if they're all infected?
Stop pretending to be tough.
I can see how terrified you are.
- Wait. - Isn't that your wife?
How do we get up there?
That ward was closed.
It's surrounded by mutants. It's too dangerous.
I'll lead the way.
You guys protect the lady.
Do we have first-aid supplies?
To treat this wound, we need to get supplies from the nurse's office.
I have a plan.
You can reach the nurse's office and avoid the mutants.
(Episode 5)
Hey.
Can you hear me?
What was that? Where did that come from?
It's not mine.
Hey, Detective.
You might not believe me,
but I saw something amid the smoke.
There might be more to this than just the black smoke.
What do you mean there might be more?
I think there's something else inside the black smoke.
Be careful.
Detective. Detective.
Who's the detective? Who are you talking to?
She's a detective from Seoul.
She thinks there's something else inside the black smoke.
What does that mean?
It's all ready.
I'll be right back. Wait here.
Hwa Sun.
My name is Do Yoon. I'm eight years old.
I'm in class 1-4 at Gaehwa Elementary School.
You're coming back, right?
Yes.
I promise I'll be back, so wait here, okay?
Okay.
You really shouldn't have done so many demonstrations...
back when you were young.
You know The Pledge of Allegiance to the Flag, right?
If you're able to recite that without getting anything wrong,
I'll set you free.
What do you say?
I guess you really are a spy.
Listen.
"I pledge allegiance to the national flag of Korea..."
"and wish eternal honor to both my country and its people."
"And I solemnly swear..."
"to dedicate my all to stay loyal to my country."
Here.
There you go.
This is what you call a patriot.
I guess fate brought us back together.
Doctor.
Are you Kim Ok Boon's guardian?
How's my mother doing?
I'm keeping an eye on her, so don't worry too much.
Doctor, can you let me see her just this once?
Well, the thing is,
if we keep opening the doors to the isolation room,
the equal pressure will change,
and that could cause malfunctions with her treatment.
Right now, it's best for the patient to avoid coming in contact...
with people from outside.
You understand that, right?
Yes.
Then I'll trust that you'll take good care of her.
Of course.
Bye.
Detective.
It's okay now.
The black smoke isn't attacking us.
It's just watching us.
The black smoke might not be...
the only thing we need to be careful of.
Is there something more?
When the security guard got attacked,
I saw something.
It looked like it had tentacles. It was a different creature.
- What? - You're all very brave.
But we have no time to waste. We need to get going.
What do you want?
Ma'am, you remember me right?
I'm Bong Ju's mother. I work at Daebak Real Estate Office.
Just go back. It's useless.
What?
That person's already dead.
Oh, my goodness.
Goodness, my mom.
My poor mom.
Mom.
I meant your husband's dead.
What?
Why are you so startled?
He deserved to die.
What...
What are you talking about?
You already knew...
he was cheating on you.
That darn punk.
He put me through so much.
I bought him a foreign brand car...
and brand new golf clubs.
I got him everything he wanted.
But he cheated on me?
That's why it's useless to trust humans.
You just need to trust in him.
Who are you talking about?
Look in there.
He's inside.
Gosh.
Is that shaman really that good?
- Wait a second. - Who is she?
He's in there.
- Hello, Doctor. - Hello.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Which department are you in?
You're not in the emergency department, are you?
Well, I'd been working in Seoul until recently.
Now I work in the internal medicine department here.
Thank you.
You must've been scared,
but you still decided to stay here.
Sure.
The patients here need us.
- Get some rest. - Okay.
(Police)
Hey, what's wrong?
It feels like someone is following us.
Don't be ridiculous. We're the only ones here.
Come along.
- Officer Park, look up there. - Where? Is it the darn mutants?
I just saw the black smoke go into that vent.
- Really? - Are you sure?
- Hurry up and put on your gas mask. - I'm sure.
I saw it clearly.
I'll take a look.
Are you out of your mind? It's too dangerous.
If it really is the black smoke,
it must be following us.
- Soon Il. - Yes?
Can you get down on the floor?
- Me? Why? - So I can step on your back.
- I have a bad back. - Then you go up and look.
No. I think you should go up and look.
Come on.
Here we go. Gosh.
Down!
What's going on?
The smoke...
went back into the vents.
What? How can it possibly move on its own?
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
What we heard over the radio earlier must be true.
It could've come in here but probably stopped on purpose.
You're not going out there, are you?
I don't think it was trying to attack us.
Then what? Did it just want to scare us?
Exactly.
It's trying to scare us. Like in hunting.
This is driving me crazy.
Are you saying the smoke is alive or something?
Let's get something straight.
I'm the leader here.
I'll lead the way. You guys follow me.
(Have you been vaccinated for pneumonia?)
(Administration)
Ma'am.
What?
Can you give me a talisman?
You knew my husband was having an affair,
and you predicted that...
the man in the cap would die if he went out, and you were right.
From now on, I'm going to rely on you.
- Please help me too. - Hey, wait.
- Stop it. - Be quiet.
- We got here first. - Hold on.
Why are you standing up? It's bad luck.
Pardon?
Kneel.
- Yes, ma'am. - Come on.
Ma'am.
Ma'am, thank you. Thank you very much.
This is a sign that you have been chosen.
Never wash it off.
Of course. I understand.
Thank you.
My goodness.
In the name of the Father, and of the Son, and...
Lord, I believe in you.
Forgive our sins and cleanse us.
Hold on. Wait.
There you go again. I said, don't order me around.
Stop it. Are you a kid?
You should stop, Officer Park.
Go ahead.
And watch out for the mutants.
(Close the door behind you to maintain the temperature.)
There are mutants!
- Where? - At the end of the corridor.
Let's go in quietly.
Have you lost your mind?
We have no choice.
They turned an abandoned school into this shelter.
I'm glad that the kids like it.
What if they'd grown with the love and care of parents?
Then they wouldn't have gotten involved in crime,
and they wouldn't have to live here.
There you go again.
Just look at yourself.
You've turned out so well even without those things.
That's only because I had you by my side.
Like we did for each other,
if we trust and love those kids,
don't you think they can change?
Do you believe that people can change?
Yes, I believe so.
I changed after I met you.
Soo Yeon said that...
you and I are her only family now.
I still can't believe that she did such a terrible thing.
I wish that she weren't a murder suspect.
Are you all right?
I'm fine. It's nothing.
(Muji Hospital, 5th floor)
Hey.
She's not here.
Ji Hye's not here.
Security office. Security office.
Come in. Do you not hear me?
Darn it. They should be by the monitors.
Where did they go?
I think they ran off to escape the mutants.
The negative pressure room?
That's a better place to escape the smoke.
It's connected to the emergency exit.
Hyun Ho.
Calm down.
Let's go.
Wait.
Officer Park?
Officer Park, do you hear me?
Darn it.
Let us in, mister!
(There are survivors. Rescue us.)
Will you please get a signal? My back's hurting.
Darn it.
What do you think you're doing?
No, Director Choi.
I have a slipped disc.
A slipped disc?
I have a doctor's note.
Send him outside.
Pardon?
Send away these freeloaders!
Are you out of your mind?
Don't talk like that. You're scaring the kids.
If you're the director, shouldn't you act like one?
- My goodness. - It's a gun.
Do you want to leave as well?
Answer me!
Will you leave with these freeloaders...
or will you shut your mouth and do as I say?
No, well... What I meant was...
Is that it?
I'm sorry. I apologize.
I must've lost my mind in the heat of the moment.
I will do everything you say.
This is why, in an emergency situation,
order and control are paramount!
Stay with Dong Rim in a safe place.
Once the path to the nurse's office is clear,
I'll come and get you.
I'm over here!
What are you doing? Open the door!
Dong Rim.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Well...
The mutants might appear. Are you scared?
No.
I'm more scared of people than the mutants.
Why have you been like this lately?
You didn't talk to me like this.
Do you really not know why?
Why...
Dong Rim, I...
Why are you alone? Where's the detective?
Can't you tell?
I'm alone because the mutants got to her.
Tell the truth. What did you do?
Why? Do you think I killed her?
How could you?
Just hit me. Hit me if you can.
Shoot. You really did hit me.
I shouldn't have listened to someone like you.
What do you mean by that?
I think you and I are just the same.
Are we not?
Han Dong Rim.
What are you doing?
We can't go back emptyhanded if the detective sacrificed herself.
She has lost her mind.
Why aren't you going after her?
[VIU Ver] OCN E05 'Dark Hole'
"A Convict on Loose"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
We're almost there. Hang in there.
Come on. Let's go.
Nurse! Nurse!
She is so darn heavy.
Why did she have to die?
You're alive.
Good.
Where's the card key?
Hey, where's the card key?
Lady, have you seen the card key?
Don't just sit there and look for the card key.
I need the card key to get on the elevator.
- What... What do you mean? - The card key.
Find it if you don't want to die.
You said your baby's nickname is Wriggly, right?
If you want to stay alive to see your baby,
you'd better find the card key.
I... I don't know where it is.
Where did she put it?
Darn it.
Gosh. My gosh, wait.
Wait.
Look.
He's alive.
Hey, where did the others go?
Tell me. Where did they go?
Where are the others?
They're all dead.
What do you mean?
Tell me what happened.
Officer Cho, calm down.
Calm down.
I can't believe this.
Ji Hye... Ji Hye was just about to give birth.
She's alive.
The pregnant lady. She's alive.
She got on the elevator and went down.
She did it. She's alive. Officer Cho, she's okay.
She's alive. She's okay.
(For staff only)
(Ministry of Justice)
(Regional Correctional Service)
Please... Please save my baby.
(Prisoner record)
(Noh Jin Su)
(Rape, murder)
Aren't there any more card keys?
Are you okay?
It was my idea to come here.
They all died because of me.
You should stay strong.
Stay strong...
and help those who are still alive.
Let's go.
Do you know...
how long it takes to the nearest highway?
Around 10 minutes by car.
Why?
Rather than hiding in the hospital like this,
wouldn't it be safer to get out of Muji completely?
Considering we haven't heard anything yet,
I doubt the other places are any different from here.
Let's get out of here first.
Soon Il, let's go.
Officer Cho, let's go.
Do you think Ji Hye is alive?
What if she met mutants down there?
I'm sure she's safe.
She managed to take an elevator down even in this situation.
She's a strong person. Don't worry.
I really hope...
you're right.
Who on earth did this?
He showed me everything.
Darn it.
(On)
Tell me what you saw.
What are you talking about?
Did you order them to break the security cameras?
Tell me what you saw,
and you'll live.
What am I supposed to tell you?
Why are staring at me like that?
Do you think you can run away from them?
(Muji Hospital)
Do you still think you can hide it from me?
I know everything.
He showed me everything.
Gosh. Stay away from me.
(Muji Hospital)
Sir!
Sir, please open the door!
Please open the door!
Sir!
- Open up! - Please, sir!
- Hurry up! - Open the door!
- Please open the door! - Open up!
Hurry up!
Hurry up and open up!
(Muji Hospital)
If you want to live,
just do as he tells you.
Help!
Sir, please save me!
No.
I didn't do that on purpose.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing's wrong.
Why are you just standing still?
Go away!
Dong Rim, let's run.
Let's go.
(Nurse's office)
Are you okay? Let me see.
I'm fine. I can walk.
Let's go.
Go in.
(Haeoreum Building)
Run.
Keep running. Dong Rim.
Are you okay?
Detective!
Are you hurt?
I can't walk.
Where's the medicine?
Jin Seok ran away with it.
Get the medicine back and go to the main building.
I'll bring Dong Rim there.
- Still... - Hurry up.
Okay.
Can you stand?
I'll try.
Go, Detective. You'll end up in danger too.
Don't give up. It's not over yet.
We have to jump.
From up here?
There's no time to wait. Hurry!
What building is that?
The gymnasium.
The main building's too far for you.
Let's go to the gymnasium.
I'm sorry. I got you in a mess.
Don't say that.
- Drink this. - Thanks.
Darn it!
It's just an emergency measure, but it should help.
Aren't you afraid?
People usually get scared and run off to save themselves.
Why wouldn't I be afraid?
How is it?
Thanks. It feels much better now.
I know it's hard but hang in there.
Our janitor. Will he be okay?
The medicine bag...
Your teacher will get it back.
So don't worry.
My dad told me that...
human beings are the scariest.
I'm scared of the mutants,
but even more so of people like Jin Seok.
In a situation like this, he tried to save his own skin.
However much the world may change,
bad people will eventually pay for what they did.
Do you really think so?
My dad died in a hit-and-run accident.
But no one suffered the consequences.
In this world,
it's the victims who pay the price.
Why? What is it?
What are you going to check now?
Let's move on.
The punk just never listens.
I saw the serial killer who murdered my husband.
She put a white cover over his head...
and injected him in the neck.
I still can't believe that she did such a terrible thing.
(Isolated Ward)
(Restricted Area)
What are you doing here?
We need more saline in the ER.
I see.
Did you try the large drawer by the ER desk?
No, I didn't.
Look in there. There should be a lot.
Okay.
And also...
From now on, without my permission,
do not enter this room.
Of course, doctor.
(Isolated Ward)
(Restricted Area)
(All child actors underwent psychological therapy.)
(Dark Hole)
Why are you doing this to save strangers?
Pretend your parents or kid were among them.
Would you still turn away?
I can't leave when they're still alive.
Hey. Are you insane?
Yoo Tae Han doesn't know, does he?
That you're the one who got him fired.
Get out! The mutants are here!
They got in! This place is overrun!
- Hwa Sun. - Lee Soo Yeon?