♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 30=
You're not going to save her?
No, I won't!
I... I'm no match for you.
She treats me badly
and she'll always yell at me anyway.
You're surrendering.
But why should I accept it?
I... I...
I'm obedient.
I'm also very likable.
I'll perform something for you.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Rocketing Kiwi!
Are you surprised?
It's edible.
Isn't it impressive?
It's really sweet.
What a brat.
That hurts.
If it hurts,
why did you step forward?
I was the only one at that time.
Who would save you if I didn't?
But actually,
it doesn't hurt that much.
It will be fine soon.
You don't have to worry about me.
Idiot. No one is worried about you.
I'm really smart, you know?
Didn't you see
how I tricked the old man?
Or we couldn't have escaped.
Idiot.
Stop calling me an idiot.
I did exceptionally well today.
Okay?
Thank you.
This is bad.
What's wrong?
Fifteen minutes!
Rong Rong, don't be mad.
I was in a rush,
so I forgot the time.
It's okay. I'm not mad.
Come on. Let's head back to the school.
This is not right.
You must be really mad now.
You're going to get back at me later.
I'm really not mad.
I think you are.
If you are mad now,
just vent it out already.
Or I would constantly be on edge.
Idiot.
Enough. Get up.
Let's head back.
What...
What did you say when we were up in the sky?
Rong Rong, Rong Rong!
Here is the voucher for 2,500 Gold Soul Coins.
It should be correct.
Thank you.
There's no problem with the plaque, either.
But
you still have to pay
five percent of the handling fee.
This...
I will pay
for his handling fee.
If that is so, we are done here.
Thank you.
Uncle Ning, thank you.
You gave Rong Rong the Silk Woven Tulip
to help with her Martial Soul's mutation
and completed Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
These 2,500 Gold Soul Coins
will be my gift for you.
Uncle Ning, Rong Rong has been missing.
We are still looking for her.
Since I've given you the money,
she is not going back
to Shi Lan Ke School.
Of course,
she won't take part in the contest, either.
So Rong Rong was taken away by you.
Please stop finding her from now on.
Oh, right.
Let me remind you.
The registration is closing soon.
Let's find Headmaster and register.
Hurry up.
That way.
Quick, quick!
Excuse me!
Excuse me.
There are 2,500 Gold Soul Coins.
We'd like to pay for Lanba School's debt.
Payment received.
You are in.
This is great!
I'd like to change the name of
Lanba School
to Shi Lan Ke.
Please fill it in here.
Here.
Wu, what are you looking for?
I'm worried that Prince Xue Xing
might cause trouble again.
Right now,
he has no reason to stop us.
His Highness is here.
The contest is about to start.
I will win this.
I have arranged the opening match for you.
They will be your opponents.
Shi Lan Ke School.
The information on all Shi Lan Ke students
is written here.
Basically, they are Triple Soul Rings
and a useless Martial Soul
with Blue Silver Plant.
A weakling like him
is no match for me.
It's the school led by Xue Qing He.
Tai Long.
I saved your tribe.
Yes.
We'll always remember your kindness.
Finish them
in the first battle then.
Headmaster.
In the auction,
it was Ning Feng Zhi
who bought the herbs.
He is Rong Rong's father.
He said he would not let her come back.
He's probably the one who took her away.
This is not entirely bad news.
At least we now know,
Rong Rong is safe.
Are we not going to get Rong Rong back?
We are a school.
It's completely reasonable
for parents to bring back their children.
They should at least
let us know beforehand.
They probably have their reasons.
Dad.
Tang San.
I saved Rong Rong.
A brat from Shi Lan Ke
took Rong Rong away?
From you?
That brat is pretty interesting.
He's of Support Branch too.
And he could fly.
But you are the Grand Soul Land Master
with Nine Soul Rings.
Even if he could fly,
you are capable of stopping him.
Rong Rong wanted to go anyway.
You let them go deliberately, right?
I guessed it right away.
Well, this old man
must be trying to lay hold of Rong Rong
to threaten her father.
I fought real hard
to rescue her out.
It's not a big deal.
I made it in no time.
That's not right, Ou Si Ke.
Wu and I saw Rong Rong's father
in the auction.
He said he took Rong Rong away.
That... That old man is not a bad guy?
That's Grandpa Sword.
His name is Chen Xin.
He's the elder in our clan.
Then, he's pretty strong.
He's not only strong,
but also a Nine Soul Rings Soul Master.
Grand Soul Land Master.
His sword skills are phenomenal.
He's the Sword Master.
I saved Rong Rong
from a Grand Soul Land Master.
At that time, the lad
had the sword pointing at his heart.
But he didn't care about his life.
He still went forward.
Saving Rong Rong was the only thought
in his mind.
This contest is dangerous.
Do you know that?
All right...
Come on.
Have a seat.
Don't be mad.
Do you remember when you were young?
You fought together with your good friends.
Strong opponents could never intimidate you.
Back then,
if you were to back down from difficulties,
you wouldn't have been
the chief of Qibao Amber Clan.
Young people
have their own journeys to go through.
You have to let go of their hands
so they could shine their own light.
Give me your hand.
Your hand.
Headmaster said it.
Grandpa Sword intended to lose.
Or both of us
couldn't have escaped.
Will...
Will your dad want you back again?
I don't know.
But
if he wanted to do that,
he would have caught up with us.
You're right.
Why are you laughing?
You almost died.
Right.
It's terrifying now that I think of it.
Stop being so reckless next time.
If I didn't get reckless,
what if they were real bad guys?
How could I save you if I was not reckless?
Thank you.
What? You...
You just thanked me.
Before we fell,
you said that too.
Shut up.
Sit tight.
I won't go.
Didn't you ask
whether my dad would come for me?
If he really does,
I won't go.
That's a given.
We are the Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke!
We need each of us.
Idiot.
We just received the news.
For Soul Master School Contest,
our first opponent has been decided.
It's Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad.
What a coincidence.
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad
was trained by Prince Xue Xing.
So they want us to lose.
But there's one thing they don't know.
It's that Tang San and the rest
have full Soul Power.
They can advance their Soul Rings.
Advancing before the contest
is against the clock.
We won't reach Star Forest in time.
Sunset Forest.
Soul Beasts in Sunset Forest
are relatively lesser.
So we can't hunt together.
We'll be in groups from now on.
Dai Mu Bai, Zhu Zhu Qing, Ma Hong Jun.
You three will follow Headmaster.
Ou Si Ke, Ning Rong Rong.
Both of you are of Support Branch.
You two will be a team
along with Ms. Liu Er Long.
Tang San and Wu.
You two are with me.
I oppose.
I don't know the way.
I can't lead the team alone.
Back then, your sense of direction
was much better than Luo San Pao.
Do you have a problem?
I don't.
How about this?
I'll leave Luo San Pao with you
to lead the way.
There's no need for that.
Both of us can be a team.
Rong Rong, Ou Si Ke.
Both of you will be with Headmaster.
He's the strongest
in Golden Iron Triangle.
There won't be a problem.
Okay.
It'll be fine.
Yes, it'll be fine.
All right. We have decided.
Let's get going.
Be careful.
Beware.
San, be careful.
Let's go.
Come on.
Follow me.
Let's go.
Slowly.
Be careful.
This is their training.
We should try not to interfere.
What kind of Soul Beasts should we get
for Tang San's Fourth Soul Ring?
You'll decide.
Does Master owe Ms. Liu money?
Why does Ms. Liu
keep looking at him like that?
I think it's because of their relationship.
What does that mean?
I think Ms. Liu likes him very much.
Ms. Liu is so pretty.
They are a good match.
Look for Soul Beasts
instead of talking nonsense.
How is that nonsense?
Wu, well said.
She has better taste than you.
In Sunset Forest,
there are Phantom Tiger
and Starlight Tiger.
They are suitable for Dai Mu Bai
and Zhu Zhu Qing to advance.
A huge spider.
It's a Human Faced Demon Spider.
It's the kind
that Tang San killed in Star Forest.
It ran away.
It probably went to Tang San.
Why?
Human Faced Demon Spider
is highly sensitive
to the Qi of its same kind.
Tang San killed one before.
Once it finds out about that,
it will see him as the main target.
Should we go and assist Brother San?
It's not necessary.
Ms. Liu Er Long is there.
A spider like that is nothing.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Sister Qing, be careful.
I'll help her.
No.
Just watch.
Ms. Liu is amazing.
Her Martial Soul is Scarlet Flame Dragon.
It inflicts high damage.
Gang, bring me the pouch.
Wu, you go instead.
But she asked for you.
It's not right for me to go.
Come with me.
Ms. Liu.
Thank you.
Do you have to change
every time you fight?
I have gotten used to it.
Ma Hong Jun belongs to the Flame Branch.
But his clothes never get burn off.
My Martial Soul is kind of different.
It causes an unusual amount of damage.
So it's less controllable.
So it's not very convenient in battles.
If there are people around after the fight,
I will maintain my Martial Soul
and get changed in somewhere convenient.
Over the years,
besides Gang and other girls,
no one has seen it.
Did Master saw it before?
It was an accident.
We just formed our group,
the Golden Iron Triangle
and was traveling the world.
We would get into fights sometimes.
When the opponent was defeated and fled,
Ms. Liu collapsed.
It was then I realized she had no clothes on.
So Headmaster saw it too?
Lander was chasing the opponent.
There were just me and her.
What happened then?
She fainted, so I had no choice.
I had to find her some clothes
and put them on for her.
You put it on for her?
She passed out. What can I do?
He had seen it all at that time.
I was in a dilemma after I woke up.
It's either that I beat him up
or get married to him.
Beating him up doesn't sound right.
Since he was helping me.
So...
you decided to marry him?
Unfortunately,
he chose Bi Bi Dong in the end.
Master, you are at fault here.
You put on clothes for her.
It was an emergency.
You could have covered her with something.
She could put it on herself
after she woke up.
That sounds right.
I was flustered at that time.
I didn't think of that, OK?
It's Human Faced Demon Spider.
Tang San, capture it.
That's the Soul Beast that suits you the best.
It's strange.
You killed its kind before.
It should be attacking you.
Master, should we go after it?
Let's wait for Er Long and Wu.
Why?
There's a Human Faced Demon Spider.
Where?
That way.
Be alert, everyone.
It's unusual for it to keep running away.
It's probably scared.
Do we lose it?
How strange.
It was running in this direction.
This is bad.
Retreat quickly! Back to the forest!
It's Pit Demon Spider.
I'll deal with it. Run.
Tang San and Wu, hurry up and run!
Run!
Let's go.
Spider Web Cage.
It's poisonless but extremely sturdy.
I'll help you.
Wu!
Don't move. Be careful of your wound.
It hurts a little but I think I'm okay.
Impossible.
It pierced through this.
It's Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
A flower that could withstand
the Human Faced Demon Spider.
Tang San! Wu is fine.
The flower protected me.
Absorb the Soul Ring
and you'll be able to advance.
Ms. Liu.
Can I have the Pit Demon Spider?
Of course.
Do you want to use the Pit Demon Spider
to advance?
You can't.
Judging from its size,
it's more than ten thousand years old.
Its Soul Power is
too strong for you.
You want to absorb such a powerful beast
for your fourth Soul Ring.
It's too risky
and dangerous.
You said that
the contest gathers
many talented Soul Masters.
If I am to enter the final,
I have to take risks.
Only then can I be strong.
But you can't absorb
the Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
This is Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
It can help absorb
Soul Beasts that are beyond your power.
In the Interspace,
I have the Ice Fire Mouth Spring
that my mother left for me.
It might give me some help.
Headmaster.
Rong Rong and the rest are back.
You guys are back.
What... What happened to them?
They are being greedy.
They chose the Soul Beasts
that are closest to their limit
in order to advance.
As to when they will wake up,
it'll have to depend on their luck.
We both advanced.
The premium herbs
are indeed powerful.
When Zhu Zhu Qing
and Ma Hong Jun advanced
to Triple Soul Rings,
their Soul Power was still full.
So they all ended up
advancing to Quadruple Soul Rings.
In other words,
we have reached Quadruple Soul Rings.
Everyone.
The Soul Master School Contest
of Douluo Continent
for Tian Dou Empire zone
will begin officially today.
We are in big trouble.
The opening match has begun.
Brother Dai and Ma Hong Jun
are still not awake.
The first fight for the opening match.
The opponents
are the newly joined Shi Lan Ke School
and
the famous
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad.
We don't know if Brother San and Wu
can make it in time.
Master.
Gang.
Where is Tang San?
And Wu?
Tang San and Wu are still
absorbing Soul Rings.
They can't make it here for now.
You guys will go for the first round.
Us?
Here are the rules for the preliminary.
A one-on-one tag match.
Losers exit the arena while winners stay
until all their opponents are defeated.
The last winner will then be determined.
Let's have Shi Lan Ke
and Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad
to send out their contestants.
Headmaster.
Let me do it.
I will try to fight all the way through.
I'll go.
Support Branch is strong too.
I will help exhaust some of the opponents.
The rest will be on you guys.
I have the responsibility
to uphold the honor of Shi Lan Ke.
He actually looks cool.
Do you two have anything to say?
You... Are you a human or a flower?
Are you a human or a flower?
Isn't that Ou Si Ke's voice?
Why is it so clear?
He's amplifying his voice
through a flower.
That is not an ordinary ability.
I am the host of the contest
and also the referee.
How do we determine the winner?
You lose when you fall off the stage.
You lose when you lose your mind.
You lose when you can't fight back.
What if I killed him
accidentally?
Don't worry. With me here,
it won't happen in the arena.
Do you all understand?
The contest starts now.
It starts already?
Support Branch Soul Master.
Yes.
I will let you attack first.
Thank you.
Where's your Martial Soul?
Soon. It's ready soon.
It's almost done.
Rocketing Kiwi!
Are you done?
Referee!
Did he sneak off the arena?
He's still within the arena.
Scorpion Tail Sting!
Why isn't there any blood?
Is it an illusion or an ice doll?
He didn't make any sound after falling.
Shi Lan Ke School
wins the first match.
The weapon and items used
are acceptable for Soul Masters.
His flying ability
is his own Soul Skill.
He did not violate any rules.
He used his weapon and items
and won the match.
Not bad.
He's a capable young man.
How promising.
Let's see if we have the chance
to invite him into our clan
and give him proper training.
I will take over.
I give up.
A student has abstained.
Shi Lan Ke School has one person down.
Well done.
Why is he holding Rong Rong's hand?
She is just supporting him to walk.
That's normal.
He can't!
Rong Rong is looking at him differently.
Her eyes are sparkling.
About him joining our clan...
I oppose!
Ou Si Ke, well done!
How did you do that?
My Rocketing Kiwi
can only last for 15 minutes.
So I didn't fall,
I stopped while facing the floor.
I'm not asking that.
Of course I knew that.
I want to know
how did you trick him
into seeing you as an illusion?
I added an immediate cooling feature
to this staff,
so that it could create a layer of ice
over my body.
Even if I'm wounded,
I wouldn't...
I wouldn't bleed immediately.
It looks like
the Ice Puppet
from Ice Branch Martial Soul.
That's right.
It is an item used
to act as
an Ice Branch Martial Soul on stage.
It can turn clouds into rain while cooling.
It's killing two birds with one stone.
Yes.
Turning clouds into rain?
What's the use of it?
The opponents are all Triple Soul Rings.
Relying on the electric current
from the staff
might be insufficient to defeat him.
But it's a different story if the body is wet.
What's the difference?
I realized it when I was testing
the electric shock.
When your body is dry
or when it's wet,
the damage inflicted is completely different.
If your body is dry,
your injury will start from your skin.
Some even look like a burn injury.
But if it's wet,
your external wound will be reduced.
But your internal wound
will be significant.
I didn't know it.
You are quite impressive.
Of course.
I realized it...
after being electrocuted so many times.
Are you guys still competing?
Admit defeat if you are scared.
Stop wasting our time.
We can't interfere.
Besides the rules,
even though we can't see the referee,
he is very powerful
in terms of his ability.
Get ready.
The next contestant.
For this round,
Rong Rong can be the next.
Okay.
Their Support Branch Soul Masters
can fight too.
What an interesting school.
Tang San seems to be missing.
After Tang San came to Cang Hui,
I haven't paid much attention to him.
Do you know why?
It's because you have him under control.
I'm waiting for today's match.
I would like to know
if Tang San's team
is strong enough to be my pawns.
Investigate
the identity of the new referee.
Yes.
Get him
to favor our side.
We'll accept any price he suggests.
What if he refuses?
Threaten him.
How do you plan to do that?
Your Highness.
Give us a moment.
Are you thinking of fighting
the Grand Soul Land Master?
I never thought
that as the Grand Chrysanthemum Master,
you would lower yourself to be the referee.
The chief takes this contest very seriously.
Your Highness,
didn't you say you planned to threaten me?
Since it's the Grand Soul Land Master,
I would say it's winning you over.
If you want my help in the contest,
it's not impossible.
On what conditions?
I heard that
you are an enemy of Crown Prince Xue Qing He.
We will help you to deal with him
and seize the ruling right of the empire for you.
What then?
I will be the puppet for Martial Soul Hall.
The conflicts in Tian Dou Imperial
don't require Martial Soul Hall
to interfere.
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪