♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 31=
The war between the royal families
in Tian Dou Empire
is none of Martial Soul Hall's business.
In this case,
let's watch the match.
Next,
Shi Lan Ke School.
Jiubao Boosts!
First, Strength! Second, Speed!
Third, Soul! Fourth, Defense!
The match hasn't even started.
I didn't hit you.
Is this allowed?
As long as she doesn't hit you,
she can prep however she wants.
Is it time to start now?
Why hasn't the match begun?
The girl's Amber Pagoda
doesn't have seven layers.
The Martial Soul of Qibao Amber Clan.
If it's not seven layers, how many layers then?
Perhaps the rumor of nine layers is true?
This school is interesting.
The match starts now.
Is that your trump card?
Don't dodge if you can.
What's that?
That should be what Ou Si Ke left behind
from the previous match.
I left all the gunpowder
in the arena.
It will explode if the temperature is right.
It can stagger
but it won't be powerful enough to kill.
If you can't knock him out of the arena,
surrender immediately.
You almost scared me.
Surrender, Rong Rong!
Don't hit her!
Rong Rong!
He touched the ground first.
The order doesn't matter.
Both of you are out.
I disagree!
You lost. Just admit defeat.
If you hit her again,
your team will be disqualified.
Let's go.
They didn't notice us, right?
No, not at all.
That's good.
What are you staring at?
Grandpa Sword and my dad
came to my match.
Where are they?
Up there.
The two hooded men.
You noticed them through the disguise?
They don't want to distract me,
so they covered themselves up.
But their disguise
is so poor.
After all,
I'm the princess of
Qibao Amber Clan.
I'm smart.
You won.
I'll forgive you for your tantrum.
This is cheating.
No, it isn't.
This is the trap left by the previous guy.
Let me give you an example, Your Highness.
If a hole is left from the previous match
and someone in the next match
fell down
and twisted his ankle,
is this cheating?
This is different.
I don't see a problem here.
I disagree.
Your Highness,
this is a competition
organized by Martial Soul Hall.
If you disagree with the rules,
go organize your own competition.
So this is personal then?
It's a fair competition.
Two Support Branch Soul Masters
can create such a result.
It's impressive.
These two matches
are not about strength
but strategy.
But if you have no power,
your brain can only do so much.
I hope the next Soul Master
can bring me some excitement.
Or else,
I'll be very disappointed with
Shi Lan Ke's battle team.
Here, Rong Rong.
Replenish your stamina.
I'm fine.
I told you to surrender.
You took out one opponent.
I didn't want to be the useless one.
Hold on.
Stamina is crucial.
Take one.
Here, take it.
Good luck!
Don't worry.
Sister Qing has Quadruple Soul Rings.
But our opponent is
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad.
Don't worry.
I left notes in the house.
Whoever wakes up first
can come over
straight away.
I hope they can wake up on time.
The match starts now!
She fainted.
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad,
one contestant is out.
Start!
Quadruple Soul Rings again?
Zhu Zhu Qing should be able to win.
What?
The Support Branch Soul Master just now
worries me.
Zhu Zhu Qing is getting slower.
I knew it.
It's the ability
of the Support Branch Soul Masters.
My eyes can't keep up
with your speed.
Let me tell you,
the Soul Skill that the Support Branch
Soul Master used just now
is called Heavy Armour.
It has a simple effect.
The last person who touches her
will be protected by the Armour
and will have to shoulder its weight.
But the weight
might not affect you much.
Heavy Amour might look like
a Supportive Soul Skill,
but for me,
it has another use.
You can sense my movement.
No, I can sense
the Heavy Armour.
As long as the Armour is on you,
you can't have any secrets
in front of me.
Surrender.
Nether Slash.
Impressive,
but not enough.
The Armour from the Support Branch
is sturdy,
but it has a limit, right?
You fought me
so that you can wear the Armour down?
Nether Claws.
Fainted.
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad,
another one out.
Another Quadruple Soul Rings?
Surrender.
Start!
It's okay. Surrender.
Your teacher is right.
You're fast.
My Martial Soul is King Kong.
I have no Soul Skill.
Usually,
Speed Type Soul Master
is my worst nightmare.
If your legs were not injured,
perhaps I wouldn't be able to win.
Why don't you announce the result?
This fight is not over yet.
Sister Qing!
Stop fighting! Just surrender.
Stop fighting!
You can try,
but you only prolong the inevitable.
Ghost Shadow Doppelganger.
Shi Lan Ke School, one contestant out.
Shi Lan Ke School,
who's the next one?
Brother Dai, you woke up?
Ma Hong Jun,
did you see this?
Yes.
Then why didn't you go?
I'm...
illiterate.
Hurry up!
We can make it.
Our rival is
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad.
We might have to fight till late night.
I'll count to three.
If Shi Lan Ke School presents no one,
it'll be disqualified.
One.
Two.
Tang San from Shi Lan Ke School
will join.
Wu.
Start!
Black Soul Ring.
Decade Millennium Soul Ring.
How is it possible?
Are you the last one
from Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad?
Your teammates put up a great fight.
I'm glad.
I'm worried about their injury.
Guess I'll have to win
as soon as possible.
Intertwine!
Constraint of Spider Web.
Blue Silver Cage.
What happened?
How did I get down here?
The last contestant from
Tian Dou Imperial School's
Second Squad is out.
Shi Lan Ke School won
the first round, the first match
of the competition.
Master. Headmaster.
How's the injury?
You look terribly wounded.
Why aren't you guys speaking?
What happened?
You won just like that?
According to the rules,
you lose if you're out of the arena.
What?
Isn't it?
Yes,
I just didn't expect
a swift match.
Exactly.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I don't understand.
Tang San's Soul Skills
are not that powerful.
How can he win so quickly?
Tang San has already found out
his own combat rhythm.
It's a piece of cake.
Let's go.
We'll visit Shi Lan Ke at night.
This team
has what it takes
to be my pawn.
Headmaster.
We made it.
You guys came.
Master.
The match is over. We won.
You won? Hooray!
Why are you so late, Captain?
The match is already over.
How's the wound?
It's fine.
What fine?
Sister Qing has the worst injury.
Especially her legs.
Can you still walk?
Yes.
I'll bring her back for healing.
Okay, just go.
Put me down!
People are watching.
Stop gawking.
Let's go back.
Yes, let's go.
Brother San.
Let's go.
Let me help you, Rong Rong.
This is unusual.
What's so unusual?
I think it's normal.
Usually, Brother Dai only cares about
the outcome of the match.
He always mulls over
the strategy after each match.
Why is he not
interested
in our strategy today?
He only cares about Sister Qing.
I didn't expect
that he knows how to take care of a girl.
He only takes care of Sister Qing.
But that's odd.
That Brother Dai that I know of
is someone
strong and manly.
He would never speak
more than one line
to a girl.
Now he's carrying Sister Qing
with such gentleness and care.
Wait.
His Martial Soul mutated.
This is not normal, Brother Dai.
-The Martial Soul advanced and mutated.
-Idiot!
Rong Rong!
Your Highness.
Sorry for letting you down.
Your Tai tribe
were cornered
by Martial Soul Hall
before I saved you guys.
Yes.
My grandpa told me.
We will never forget
your help.
Is this how you pay your gratitude then?
I'm willing to accept all punishment.
Don't let Tang San
live to see another day.
Understood?
I will challenge him.
They have a master and a headmaster.
How are you going to challenge him?
Find you grandpa.
Ask him to kill Tang San.
I can't.
Tell him that
he owes me one.
I'll cash in here.
But Your Highness...
Go and tell him now.
I...
Yes.
Brother San.
Wu?
Come in.
What's up?
Teacher Liu said that
the wounds of Rong Rong and Sister Qing
were not serious.
They just need to have a bit of rest.
That's good.
I see you hiding in your room
after the match.
Is something troubling you?
Do you remember
what I told you about the Xuan Tian Records?
You told me
that your dad let you learn
different techniques from it.
Wu.
Can you promise
not to tell anyone about
what I'm going to say next?
I promise.
In the domain,
my mum told me that
Xuan Tian Records
might be able to create
another kind of power that's different
from Soul Master's.
Different from Soul Master's...
Is it a new way of fighting?
Then perhaps
we don't need Martial Soul anymore.
Humans don't have to hunt
Soul Beasts down.
I don't think so.
Why?
It seems that my Martial Soul
has combined with Xuan Tian Strike.
That man wants to kill Tang San.
Let them be.
Won't he ruin our plan?
If I'm not mistaken,
that man is the leader of Tai tribe.
Another fallen tribe.
The leader of Tai tribe
is allegedly a strong one
with Eight Soul Rings.
More importantly,
he's under Prince Xue Xing's order.
Have Tang San and the others
become the targets of Prince Xue Xing?
Don't meddle.
Don't draw the attention of the royal family.
What if Shi Lan Ke
gets destroyed?
We'll find another pawn
to manipulate.
I'm going back to the school.
You go and visit Venom Soul Master.
Du Gu Bo.
He's been poisoned for so long.
We owe him an explanation.
Tell him about my request.
But...
He's a Grand Soul Land Master.
Are you afraid of death?
I...
I'll visit Venom Soul Master now.
Don't worry.
He's still poisoned.
He won't hit you.
Go.
Wu,
try tearing it.
Wow.
Is it because of
the decade Millennium Soul Ring?
It's because of Xuan Tian Strike.
They are some basic techniques that I learnt
from Xuan Tian Strike.
What does this have
to do with Blue Silver Plant?
After the advancement,
I realized that Xuan Tian Strike
could be combined with Soul Power.
And this Blue Silver Plant
became more tenacious.
Isn't that good?
But this also means that
Xuan Tian Strike is a Supportive Soul Skill.
It cannot replace the Martial Soul.
Perhaps my parents
are mistaken?
Perhaps the Xuan Tian Records
is not that miraculous?
Be patient.
Once you become stronger,
you might find out
other possibilities.
If only I could see my dad now.
Let go of her.
Eight Soul Rings. A Great Soul Land Master.
If we fight here,
your teachers and schoolmates
will be affected.
She's just asleep.
I did not hurt her.
Follow me,
so I won't hurt anyone else.
You did obey us so nicely.
I don't want others to get hurt
because of me.
Such integrity.
The fact that my grandson lost to you
is not unacceptable.
So is this a revenge
after you lost to me?
I'm not someone like this.
The Tai tribe
owes someone a favour.
We came here
because we were forced to.
What did they ask you to do?
To kill you.
So just me alone?
No one else?
Knowing that a Great Soul Land Master
is going to kill you,
you still remain level-headed.
As long as you don't drag others in.
So you'll submit to your fate?
Do you think you can win?
You have Eight Soul Rings.
I don't stand a chance.
Then why do you fight?
I'd rather die in a battle
than surrender.
Fine.
I'll give you a chance.
If you can get past me
and enter the door,
consider yourself safe.
I'll leave.
What if I can't?
I'll kill you.
Okay.
Bring it on.
Kiddo.
Your Blue Silver Plant is tenacious.
What is this Soul Skill?
The Martial Souls of our tribe
have no Soul Skill.
What's that then?
Harnessing strength to its fullest.
I can create an updraft
just by snapping my finger.
It can be used to hurt someone.
Blue Silver Cage.
Hao Tian Hammer.
What's Hao Tian Hammer?
My Martial Soul is Blue Silver Plant.
What's your name?
His name is Tang San, grandpa.
Is your surname Tang?
What's your father's name?
Tang San, it's me.
Your Blue Silver Plant is stronger now.
Let's test
its Soul Power data.
Tang San.
Wu.
You said your dad was a blacksmith?
Yes.
What kind of blacksmith?
Other than a normal blacksmith,
what else could a blacksmith be?
How is he a blacksmith?
What's your father's name?
Why should I tell you?
Tell me
and I'll let you in.
Such power.
Spill it!
What's your father's name?
Sir, if you have any problem,
you can come to me.
No need to trouble the youth.
Spill it!
I won't.
Titan?
Who are you?
Lander, Er Long.
Go back first.
Trust me, Tang San will be fine.
Tang San.
Your father's name.
You can tell him.
My dad is Tang Hao.
Grandpa!
Grandpa, are you all right?
I entered,
so you lost.
What are you doing?
So that's why you have Hao Tian Hammer
and Blue Silver Plant.
You have Twin Martial Souls.
What's Hao Tian Hammer?
My Martial Soul is Blue Silver Plant.
Young Master!
Wait.
Grandpa.
I've finally found you, Young Master.
Stand up first.
Okay. Okay.
I'll stand up.
Calm down, Young Master.
You should calm down instead.
Actually,
Master Tang Hao is my master.
M... master?
I'll tell you everything.
Elder?
He's a sore loser.
That's why he came for revenge, right?
Look how timely my arrival was.
I stopped everything on time.
No, it's...
You want me to wake them up?
Aren't they our enemies?
Yes, enemies.
They even
put me to sleep.
See?
Elder, hear me out.
They were our enemies at first,
but then
they knelt down in front of me.
Did they hit you on the head?
Elder, they did kneel down before me.
Elder, I'm the eye-witness.
Both of them
are not our enemies.
Your public relation is so complicated.
Let's save him first.
All right.
The poison is so powerful.
Run for your life, Young Master!
We're all friends here. Don't fight.
So you were saying...?
It would be better
if we speak in private.
All right. I'll get out.
Elder, rest in my room, please.
Sure.
I'll wait for you outside.
I have something for you.
Slowly, Elder.
What is happening?
Okay.
Now you can speak.
Do I have to go out too?
I won't keep anything
from Wu.
So she's Young Master's wife.
No, no.
She's my sister.
What?
Master Tang has a son and a daughter?
Not blood-related.
Continue, please.
Back then,
my bad temper
caused huge trouble.
I provoked someone I shouldn't have.
The Tai tribe was almost wiped out.
If Master Tang hadn't intervened,
my tribe
would have long disappeared.
My life belongs to Master Tang.
Then do you know
what happened between him
and Martial Soul Hall back then?
Why are you kneeling again?
Grandpa.
Here.
Sit down.
Young Master.
This is something
that I can never let go of.
I failed Master Tang
when he was hunted down
by Martial Soul Hall.
Did you take part in the siege?
Of course not!
If I did that,
then I'd be no different than a lowly swine!
Then what do you mean by failed?
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪