He's okay.
Rocket.
Very good job!
That's how...
That's how... we'll get away.
Go find your mother.
For the radio?
Might help us boost the signal.
For you.
Thank you.
It'll be dark soon.
Listen to me...
Too loud.
S.
S.O.
S.O.S.
S.
S.O.
S.O.S.
Dinner.
1, 2, 3,
4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
I'm sorry.
Beautiful.
I didn't say anything.
You cannot go down there!
Why not?
You know why.
I'm not a child! I won't make a sound!
Just don't.
Please.
This time, I took small
amplifiers from the stereo.
It.
It. Won't.
It. Won't. Work.
No, this should increase
the frequency to...
It.
It. Never.
It. Never. Works!
But...
we'll keep trying
until it does.
Stop.
Just
Remember, you need to divide.
Carry the three.
Amazing!
Time to go.
...please don't make me go...
You'll be fine.
Your father will always protect you.
Always.
Listen to me...
It's important that you learn these things.
He just wants you to be able
to take care of yourself.
...to take care of me.
...when I'm old...
...and grey...
...and I have no teeth...
Don't worry.
I don't want to go.
There's nothing to be scared of.
...of course there is.
I'll go.
I need you to stay and help your mother.
I want to go.
Just stay here.
You'll be safe.
...next time.
They'll hear you.
Look at me.
Listen.
The river...
The river... is loud.
Small sounds...
Small sounds... safe.
Big sounds...
Big sounds... not safe.
Unless...
there's another sound nearby...
that's louder.
You're safe.
I wanna show you something.
Hey,
you're all right.
You're all right.
I promise.
Why didn't you let her come?
Do you blame her
for what happened?
No.
Because she blames herself.
It was no one's fault.
You still love her, right?
Of course I do.
You should tell her.
Rocket.
I need you...
I need you... to make a sound...
that's louder.
Your mother...
Your mother... needs your help.
You.
You. Can.
You. Can. Do this.
Shh...
It's okay. It's okay.
You're safe.
They can't hear us.
It worked.
You just need to rest now.
Where are they?
I'll find them.
No, she was with me.
She was with me, and...
then I had to go and do laundry, and...
He was with you. How did he...
Rockets.
So he'd still be there.
- I'm sure he is.
- He knows to wait for you.
And she is...
She's smart. She'll have found a place.
They know what to do.
It's a boy.
I could've carried him.
He was so heavy, wasn't he?
I can still...
I can still feel the weight in my arms.
Small, but
so heavy.
And my hands were free.
I was carrying the bag,
but my hands were free.
You have to stop.
So, I could've carried him.
I should've carried him.
Who are we
if we can't protect them?
Who are we?
You have to protect them.
Promise me
you will protect them.
Don't worry...
Don't worry... he'll come for us.
We can't stay here.
We need to go.
He'll come for us.
He will come for us.
He'll come for you!
No, you're wrong.
He told me!
Don't move.
Stop.
Are you okay?
You okay?
Let's get to the truck.
Dad!
I
I love
I love you.
I
I have
I have always
I have always loved
I have always loved you.