SHIN HAE SUN, KIM JUNG HYUN
BAE JONG OK, KIM TAE WOO
SEOL IN AH, NA IN WOO
WRITTEN BY CHOI AH IL
DIRECTED BY JANG YANG HO
MR. QUEEN: THE SECRET
THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.
I, Court Lady Choi,
has been living in the palace for 30 years.
I know everything that
goes on in this palace.
Not only the secrets of
everyone in the palace...
but also the other side of every
incident unfolding without a break.
Let me tell you.
There is nothing I do not
know about in this palace.
I want to go back!
But I have no idea...
why Her Highness is acting like that.
Your Highness.
In the palace, everyone has secrets.
Let us unveil...
the secrets that seem
too trivial to reveal...
but provoke too much curiosity to ignore.
THE SECRET OF THE GUY FRIEND
CCTV
TEST, AUTHENTIC MASTERPIECE, PERVERT
There are so many words I still
do not know the meaning of.
I have no other choice.
I should ask the Queen in person.
Your Majesty.
Why are you coming out from here?
I came to keep Her Highness company.
Do you have nothing better to do?
What is your job?
I am an envoy.
- Leave immediately.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Run.
Today, I will make sure...
What are you doing here?
What are you doing here, Your Majesty?
Does a husband need a reason...
to visit his wife?
I also just came...
to see if Her Highness is doing well.
Then please excuse me.
The Queen is doing well.
Poor fellow.
They say the early bird catches the worm.
Today, I will make sure...
Your, Your Majesty.
Even you, Royal Chef?
Yes, Your Majesty.
What brings you here in
the morning, Your Majesty?
Do you not sleep at all?
As I got older, I wake
up early in the morning.
Prepare the meal.
Already?
I will have a big breakfast.
A big meal in the morning?
Give it to me quickly!
Yes, Your Highness.
- His Majesty has come.
- Fine!
Let's do it again! Let's
do it again, Your Highness.
Yes, do it again.
- 2 syllables, about relationships.
Romance.
Romance. A good choice.
- Friendship.
- I had not thought of that.
Passion.
You lose. Come here.
Urine.
- Urine!
- Don't try to get away with it.
Indian Rice!
Why does it not count?
It could be like "You're in"
my heart, can it not? It hurts!
Wait... Urine!
- Indian Rice!
- It hurts!
- Urine!
- Oh, my goodness.
You are here.
- You're here.
- Have you arrived, Your Majesty?
I was going to Seonjeongjeon
Hall. I took a wrong turn.
Loving.
- Come here.
- Standing.
How are you guys so strong?
The Queen is always surrounded by men.
- Special Director Hong.
- I am not doing it!
- Let me go!
- No!
Not there!
- Oh, my.
- Not there!
We do not even know each other, do we?
Books for your hormones are the best kind.
I cannot believe I am reading an
erotic fiction fit for teenagers.
Your Highness.
You cannot read such books, Your Highness.
I have to read it because I have
to learn the Korean alphabet.
I am not finished... Oh, yes.
Hold on, hold on.
Let me read it one more time.
Your Highness, His Majesty has come to visit.
What are you reading so intently?
Do you want to read it too?
- My goodness.
- A rat!
A rat.
A rat as big as a calf was passing by.
Forgive me for surprising you, Your Majesty.
If it's as big as a calf, it
must be a calf, not a rat!
Where is the book I was reading?
Your Highness.
It is time to go to Daejojeon Hall.
Right. Everyone must be there, right?
"Everyone"?
- I guess you have plans.
- Yes.
- With whom?
- Someone.
Of course, it is someone.
I am asking if it is more than one person.
What are you trying to ask?
Just ask me what you really want to ask.
I'm not one to put much effort...
into figuring out your real intention.
There is no "real intention".
- But there is.
- I said there is not.
Are you sulking?
What do you mean I am sulking?
The king never sulks.
I just came to find a book I need.
Do not disturb.
Oh, it is right here.
The book I was looking for.
"As Eunuch Kim untied the
string of his jacket,"
"my heart also..." What?
What is this?
I finally found something we have in common.
We share the same interests.
"We"?
I'll leave you alone so that you can
enjoy the book for your hormones.
I'm off.
Wait.
I have something I want to ask you, My Queen.
What is it?
It is nothing big.
Who is the one...
you cherish the most?
Hong Yeon.
Oh, Court Lady Choi as well.
That is not what I mean.
Leave us alone. Go.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
- Quickly.
Do not walk backwards. Turn
around and walk out quickly.
Hurry up.
What is it that you are taking so long?
Please be honest with me.
It depends on the question.
I will not say it if you
are not going to be honest.
Forget it, then.
Among men!
Among men, who do you cherish the most?
Jang Bong Hwan.
And who might that be?
He is...
the only man in the world who is perfect.
He's the coolest guy I know.
He's got everything.
He's got looks, a great personality,
incredible skills with a blade,
and a mastery of all theories,
which makes him the ultimate man.
He's the best.
He always feels new. He makes me thrilled!
Why are you not with him
if you value him so much?
I know, right?
Because we can't be together,
I long for him and miss him more.
I'm crazy for him.
Are you sighing because of this
fellow called Jang Bong Hwan?
Do you miss him so much...
that you cannot even sleep
and even feel depressed?
No way.
Are you jealous?
That's cute.
Cute?
What? What are you doing?
Yes. I am jealous.
You are not public property.
So do not say "we" carelessly.
That is an order.
I do not want anyone else...
to call you "my dear
Queen" or even "my sister".
Also...
Do you still find me cute?
Yes. You're cute.
But not as much as I am.
What on earth...
is this overused, conventional
heart-throbbing scene...
from a romance cartoon?
I would never fall for something like this.
Or would I?
- Jindo Dog One is issued.
- Pardon?
- This won't do. I must check.
- Check?
If this heart belongs to the body...
or to the soul.
I must check...
Go ahead and check.
Why does it feel good? It's upsetting.
No. Stop it, Kim So Yong.
Stop it. Stop it already.
Does this upset you that much?
I shouldn't be like this.
My gosh.
I should not be like this either.
There are many interesting
books in the library.
But nothing is more interesting...
than the true character of the
gentle elders in the palace.
In the palace, everyone has secrets.
Let us unveil...
the secrets that seem
too trivial to reveal...
but provoke too much curiosity to ignore.
THE SECRET OF THE REAL SIBLINGS
QUEEN SUNWON
KIM JWA GEUN
KIM MUN GEUN
It would be perfect if
I get a tiger card now.
By the way, a tiger attacked a town...
in the Yeongnam region.
It caused quite the ruckus.
I see. She needs the tiger card.
What is worse...
is the rumor that says...
there is strange energy
of the dragon in the sky.
He needs the dragon card.
Whichever it is, I am doomed.
What are you doing? Play your hand.
Where did the tujeon player go?
Actually,
because the game is so interesting,
my heart is throbbing.
Actually, if I do not play the right hand,
I am worried...
that you will chew me up.
"My heart is throbbing."
"You will chew me up."
Court Lady Chun.
Is this so funny?
I apologize, Your Highness.
Hurry up and play your hand.
Her Highness is waiting.
There. Oh, my goodness.
My hands were sweaty. I
accidentally put down two cards.
This round does not count. Let us start over.
- We cannot do that.
- I agree.
As the younger brother, you should give up.
As the elder sister, you should give up.
I made concessions to you
throughout my whole life...
for being born a woman.
Have you forgotten that you had
all the honors to yourself...
since you became Queen?
Is that what I get in return for raising you?
I do not know about that.
All I remember is serving you.
Calm down. Please do not fight.
Blood is thicker than these mere cards.
Ever since we were young,
every time we played,
we would always growl at each other.
We are very competitive.
That is right.
No matter how old we get,
I am just a child before you.
I will make a concession. You should take it.
No, you should take this first.
- Brother.
- Sister.
My goodness. Look at you.
You are both competitive...
and yet you both make
concessions so generously.
Anyone can tell that you are
siblings. You are so alike.
- That is not true!
Then, for the sake of your relationship,
let us say that I won this round.
- What are you talking about?
I want to go home.
From the southeastern sky,
there is a red energy
shooting towards the palace.
It is as strong as fire.
The river flows backwards.
Frogs rain down from the sky.
A series of strange events are occurring.
Everyone is confused and worried...
about such inauspicious signs.
Word among the people is that...
it is a sign of the end
of the world drawing near.
I am worried.
Is...
the world really coming to an end?
THE SECRET OF DESTRUCTION
Tonight,
the sky will fall.
Fire will fall from the sky,
and everything will burn.
It will turn into a blazing inferno.
Maybe the world...
has always been ready to be destroyed.
It is not strange even if the world
comes to an end at any moment.
If you had that so, you should have told us.
If I had known, I would
not have worked so hard.
I would have enjoyed my life at ease.
This darned world.
I do not think...
the world will come to an end so easily.
Even small creatures like us...
struggle to survive.
The world would not be that weak.
So let us stop thinking about it,
and focus on finishing the book on tactics.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Bring the brush and ink.
You are going to squeeze me out to the end?
I am not doing this.
Special Director Hong.
What if this really is
the last day of my life?
I do not want to die working to the end.
You should consider today as your last day,
and do what you want.
That is why I want to
finish creating this book.
It is something I want
to finish before I die.
You are a fool who is obsessed with work.
You need to watch your mouth.
What do you care?
It all ends once the world comes to an end.
Did you just talk informally to me?
Yes. Yes, I did.
We are all about to die.
I cannot afford to be polite.
Calm down, Special Director Hong.
Won Beom, you punk. You are the worst.
You are a corrupt employer
pretending to be my friend.
Your Majesty. I too must do
something on my last day of life.
Even if this day is my last,
I will fix your manners for you before I die.
Gosh. You are so authoritative
just because you are a bit older.
Plus, did you have to be that tall?
Did you eat all the
potatoes on Ganghwa Island?
That is cold.
I finally came to my senses.
I will stop right there.
It is 5pm.
It will soon be nightfall.
Is today really the last day?
Where are you going?
I have changed my mind.
If the world ends tonight,
where I should be...
and with whom I should be
not to have any regrets.
It's fine. Don't worry.
I said it's fine. Nothing's going to happen.
Still, there are rumors.
Don't trust the rumors.
It's fine. It's all right.
It's okay. My goodness. I said it's fine.
Don't trust those rumors.
His Majesty is here.
Are you also unable to sleep...
in fear of the world coming to an end?
Come to an end, my foot.
I was comforting them
because they were so worried.
I can't ignore the woes of women.
How kind of you.
Hey. Royal Chef.
What are you still doing here at this hour?
Your Highness.
What?
Is something good going on?
Are you that scared of dying, Man Bok?
I was scared. What?
My eyes were just tearing
up from chopping scallions.
Is that so? Sure, sure.
My goodness.
I have always been in on
such important rumors.
How come I was not aware
of the end of the world?
Anyway, it is getting late.
Gosh, it's cold.
See? I told you. Nothing's happening.
You all had me scared. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- The Queen is right.
You should stop worrying and go to bed.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Hurry up.
Your Highness. Is that...
A meteor shower.
Is that rain?
How is it that the end of
the world is so beautiful?
Please let me go back to my healthy body.
While I'm lying in bed in a coma,
please don't let me lose muscle mass.
My Queen.
If you see a shooting star,
make a wish and it'll come true.
Make a wish. Hurry.
Make a wish.
A wish?
Let Cheoljong live longer than
what the history books say...
and live happily ever after...
like a prince in a fairy tale.
Please let me be born as a stone...
in my next life.
Why do you want to be a stone?
So I will not have to do
anything and live comfortably.
Then in my next life,
I will kick that stone.
In my next life,
let me be born as Her Highness' mother.
Please let me succeed...
in rehabilitating Her
Majesty in my next life.
In my next life, let me be born
as Her Highness' elder sister.
So she would not be lonely.
It was a good life.
I hope my next life is as good as this life.
If...
I am ever reborn in my next life...
I told you to make a wish,
but it seems you're all
wishing to be born again.
What did you wish to be born as?
No matter how much I think about it,
I do not want to be born again.
No wonder.
If you pour so much into this life,
you wouldn't want to be born again.
It's okay even if it's hard.
I know you're trying hard.
I know you're trying so hard not to crumble.
Still, I want you to be reborn.
I've learned something
from living a second life.
Trivial things that I
would probably regret...
if I hadn't known about them.
Right. I would have regretted it so much...
if my life ended without meeting...
such a strange person like you.
Who knows?
I might show up before you in an
unexpected and strange form...
once again.
So you have to be reborn.
You are already unexpected enough even now.
My family died on the same day.
I hope to meet them again in the afterlife.
Are you okay?
Did you make a wish?
There is one more wish.
I know it cannot happen now,
but one day,
I want to...
watch the sun setting in the distance...
with the person I long for.
How nice it would have been
for her to be here as well.
What's with this mood?
No in-house romance.
You cannot date your family.
That is not what I meant.
I am a man of much guilt.
I am a woman of much guilt.
I said, no in-house romance.
When I am born again, I
hope to meet My Queen again.
Even if we misunderstand,
hate each other and fight,
I hope we recognize each other in the end.
I hope we meet again not as King and Queen,
but as So Yong and Won Beom.
Everyone. Dismissed.
Dismissed.
Your Highness. The flames
are falling this way.
Your Highness. Maybe
there is a fire somewhere.
We are doomed.
- We are totally doomed.
- Fire.
We're not doomed.
Wish for it a million
times. It will never happen.
Look. It may be a mess,
but it's running fine.
Seriously.
This darned world is darn strong.
It is a darned world, but it never ends.
Oh, dear.
MR. QUEEN: THE SECRET
THIS DRAMA IS FICTIONAL AND
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS ARE UNRELATED
TO HISTORICAL EVENTS.