(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 39)
Ashina Sun.
I guess the effect of the medicine isn't enough.
Starting today, increase his dosage.
Yes.
Tell those heading to Northern Desert...
to investigate more carefully.
They must see...
Ashina Sun's body.
Mimi Guli didn't even destroy the purple gromwell.
I don't believe that she'll kill Ashina Sun.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I'll surely handle this well.
Right.
I heard that Bu Zhen and King of Sui...
are very close.
They're playmates who are in the same age group.
The King of Sui really likes him.
As long as we still have him,
then he would still...
be useful.
Young Khan.
We've already confirmed that aside from Mu Jin,
no survivors came back from the Bear and Eagle Armies.
Why?
Ashina Sun has fought in many battles.
He is very experienced.
How can this happen?
Ashina Sun.
I haven't had a good drink with you yet.
I thought that if you were dead, I'd be very happy.
Why am I not happy at all now?
You were the opponent I have the most faith in.
I haven't proven to you yet that I won't lose to you.
Ashina Sun, you brat!
Do you want me to lose to you forever?
When you were alive,
I couldn't stand you.
You're making me suffer even after you're dead.
Do you believe that Ashina Sun is dead?
He's the God of War of the grasslands.
How can he die?
She Er.
You're drunk.
Uncle.
It must be Uncle.
If he hadn't agreed,
how would Tu Ka She dare...
to kill him?
Who would dare to lay a finger on Ashina Sun?
I can even imagine...
that on the battlefield in the Great Desert,
on the front were troops from Great Desert...
and Tu Ka She was on the back.
They all wanted Ashina Sun dead.
We all have our own destinies.
Don't jump to your own conclusions.
If people with ulterior motives...
hear what you're saying,
your uncle will get angry.
It will be bad for the Wolf Army too.
Angry?
Ashina Sun is dead...
and I can't even speak my mind?
In the past,
I've always tried to beat Ashina Sun.
The Eagle Army is gone now.
Even if...
I become king of the grasslands,
what's the point?
Of course there's a point.
You're the true king of the Ashina Tribe.
You should rule the grasslands.
Ashina Sun is dead.
You should be pleased.
You can't let me down.
She Er.
Ashina Sun.
I can't believe...
that you even managed to win my son over.
I underestimated you.
Where is he? Did you catch him?
He's dead.
Who shot the arrow?
We've got him surrounded.
He knew he couldn't get away so he killed himself.
Where is his corpse?
It's outside.
We searched him.
He didn't have anything of value.
Ashina Tribe is the one...
who wanted him dead.
One of their own...
wanted to kill Ashina Sun.
It's the capital.
If they ever try to hurt Ashina Sun again,
I'll surely avenge him tenfold.
I have one more favor to ask.
Tell me.
Since they sent a spy,
they must want to see the corpse.
Can you burn down the battlefield and destroy the corpse?
Under such grief, you can even think so meticulously.
Incredible.
Don't worry. Leave that to me.
How is he?
I did everything I could.
But...
whether he last until tomorrow...
Anyway,
you'd better be prepared.
Thank you.
I want to take good care of him.
Come on.
Ashina Sun.
You can hear me, right?
I've already asked Bodhisattva...
to make arrangements for the Eagle Army.
When you wake up,
we'll leave together.
Let's go to a place...
where people never go into battles.
The water and grass would be abundant there.
There would be herds of cows and sheep.
I heard that if we go a little further north,
there's a very beautiful snow-covered mountain.
Come and see it with me, all right?
I suddenly remembered when we first met.
Back then,
I've lost all my family.
But I became friends with Qin Zhun,
an unexpected guest.
My surname is Qin.
My name is Zhun.
You can call me Qin Zhun.
Be it rain, storm, or thunder,
be it blades or arrows,
let me block them for you.
That was the darkest moment of my life.
But you were there.
This is also your darkest moment.
I'll never leave you.
We've been through so much.
We surpassed them all.
We can still surpass more things in the future.
Am I right?
Actually, I really hate you.
You're arrogant, egotistical,
and you can't take care of yourself.
But I can't live without you.
Didn't you always tell me...
to use the rest of my life to repay you?
I promise you.
I'll never ever leave you in this lifetime.
But you have to give me a chance.
Wake up.
Ashina Sun.
Can you please wake up?
I'll stay here with you.
Wake up.
There are so many things that we haven't done yet.
There are so many places that we haven't seen.
Don't abandon me.
I didn't expect things to turn out this way.
In the Northern Desert,
that was what happened with Ashina Sun and Chang Ge.
Go and meet up with them first.
The Eagle Army doesn't exist anymore.
I'm afraid it's not safe for you to stay here.
What about you?
Why are you staying here?
Great Khan is sick.
The capital will be moved.
I've already looked into it.
The capital will be relocating to Dingxiang.
I have to go with them.
I still have some unfinished business.
What is it?
Since we're all in the same boat now,
the Yanxing Sect...
won't desert you.
It won't be convenient if you follow me.
Please relay this information to Ashina Sun.
Also,
Ya Luo is dead.
I went to the prison in the capital secretly.
Ya Luo was nowhere to be found.
The guard at the prison told me...
that when Ya Luo arrived at the capital that night,
he was already killed.
The capital...
isn't what it used to be anymore.
You said the capital is moving to Dingxiang.
So there is someone...
from the Sui Dynasty in Ashina Tribe?
It's Khatun.
That's really interesting.
I can't interfere with Ashina Tribe's affairs.
I only follow orders...
from Young Master.
Thank you, Elder Qin.
In the future, you must be extra careful.
Also,
if you see Mimi,
tell her...
to live well.
Young man,
I think...
she'll wish to hear that from you yourself.
Xu Feng, tell our men...
that we'll stay here...
and await the orders of the Young Master.
Also,
send a letter to Northern Desert first.
Yes.
Young man,
take good care of yourself.
Farewell.
Ashina Sun, you're awake?
You're really awake.
I knew you wouldn't abandon me.
Are you really...
won't ever leave me again in this lifetime?
Did you hear me?
Since I was able to hear your true feelings,
even getting shot with 10 more arrows would be worth it.
What are you talking about?
Don't you know how worried I was last night?
I was scared...
that you'll really die.
I thought I was going to die too.
But I heard you call out my name,
so I came back from where the Heavenly Wolf God was.
I even heard...
that you'd avenge me.
I'm really happy.
Chang Ge.
The moment I got hit by the arrow,
I didn't think about anything.
I just wanted to take you home.
Chang Ge, I...
Prince Sun, you're awake.
There is no Prince Sun anymore.
Just call me Ashina Sun.
All right.
I'll inform them first.
Everyone was worried all night.
Hurry up.
Be careful. Don't break it.
- Keep up. - Here's another box.
- Keep up. - Slowly.
- Give me a hand. Place it here. - Don't break it.
Those at the back, keep up.
That's good. Here.
Here, give me a hand.
Be careful.
- Slowly. Put it here. - You're so noisy. Shut up!
Young Khan.
What is going on?
Great Khan gave orders...
that the royal court will be moved to Dingxiang.
We're starting on it today.
The Great Khan is terminally ill.
His Majesty must not tire himself out.
From now on, perhaps the stamp, the capital,
and the entire grassland...
will be in your hands one day.
You're the true king of Ashina Tribe.
You should rule the grasslands.
It's my mother.
Uncle is sick.
Ashina Sun and Tu Ka She are dead.
I'm the only one left in the royal court.
Is this a coincidence...
or my mother's plan?
Tu Lu Ke, what do you think?
You're reunited with your mother now.
It's a good thing.
What's the matter?
The spy we sent to Northern Desert...
- is dead. - He's dead?
I think the Northern Desert Army found out.
You're all useless.
That means...
no one actually saw Ashina Sun dead.
Yes.
One more thing.
Tu Ka She's body hasn't been found either.
The Northern Desert Army...
defeated Ashina Tribe for the first time.
They burned down the battlefield...
to boost their morale,
so...
I got it.
You may go.
Yes.
What did I say?
A wolf on the grasslands has nine lives.
He won't die that easily.
Let's get down to business.
Ashina Sun.
I know you're a tough guy.
I won't beat around the bush with you.
The one who tried to kill you...
was sent by the Ashina Tribe.
There is no reason to hesitate anymore.
As long as you surrender with the Eagle Army,
I guarantee...
that I'll treat you well.
Thank you for your kindness, King of Northern Desert.
But I led the Eagle Army in pretending to be dead.
I didn't do it to let my men work for someone else.
Aside from Northern Desert,
where else can you go?
Anywhere is fine.
Even being in exile...
is better than spending our days...
in battles and bloodshed.
Your talent for leading troops would be wasted.
- Why not come to Southern Desert... - The Eagle Army...
won't become anyone's weapon.
Now that we've talked things out,
I want to say something too.
Go ahead.
I think no matter how wary...
Yan Li Khan is of the Eagle Army,
he wouldn't kill Ashina Sun.
Behind this...
Dingxiang.
It must have something to do with Dingxiang.
So you thought of that too.
Yes.
No matter how much my father hates me,
he wouldn't just throw away this weapon of his.
But if it's that person...
She knows better than anyone...
that there's no way the Eagle Army will work for her.
Now, all of Great Desert's tribes have rebelled.
Princess Yicheng's plan has failed.
But I don't think she would just let it go.
I'm just afraid...
that more people in the Ashina Tribe will be manipulated by her...
and blindly participate in battles.
For now, if we want a peaceful life,
there's only one option.
Form an alliance with Tang.
Form an alliance with Tang?
If we form an alliance with Tang...
and let a third party get involved,
when the time comes...
that Yicheng wants to start another war,
she'll also think twice.
What if she doesn't stop?
I can't just sit and watch Tang attack the Ashina Tribe.
I don't want such a thing to happen too.
But we have to do our best.
Only in getting all three sides involved...
can this war not begin.
Chang Ge,
you're oversimplifying things.
This isn't a simple matter in the first place.
But if we don't do our best,
there would be no hope at all.
This is the letter Elder Qin sent me this morning.
There is some news...
from Mu Jin.
Ya Luo is dead.
My father is also very sick.
The capital...
I can't believe the capital is moving to Dingxiang.
Yes.
If my guess is right,
Yicheng...
is slowly controlling the royal court.
The capital is moving to Dingxiang.
Once Yicheng is in complete control of the whole Ashina Tribe,
her next move...
would be against Tang.
Does that mean...
you came to us for Tang's sake?
No.
I'm doing this for all the innocent citizens...
who would suffer from war.
Regardless if it's Great Desert,
Ashina Tribe, or Tang,
these innocent citizens...
shouldn't be used and sacrificed...
by these people's plots and desires.
None of us can stay out of this.
And I thought you had a great plan.
Form an alliance with Tang?
Don't forget.
We were all Tang's enemies once.
That's right.
In getting Tang involved,
who can guarantee...
that it won't be like the Ashina Tribe?
It won't.
This crisis...
can only be solved by Tang.
Based on what I know about Li Shi Min,
Tang will never become like the Ashina Tribe.
If we let Tang keep Ashina Tribe in check,
when the time comes,
the entire Great Desert...
can get through this without suffering any losses.
There is nothing more convenient than this.
Besides,
all of you want to seek alliances...
to resist the Ashina Tribe.
How can you let go of such a powerful ally?
Wait.
We've been discussing here for so long.
Here's the thing.
Why would Tang join forces with us?
In a few days,
I'm sure we'll hear some news.
Ashina Sun.
Ya Luo...
Ya Luo died for the Eagle Army.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Chang Ge.
Father wouldn't kill Ya Luo.
I know.
Father was as strong as an ox.
It's impossible for him to get sick so easily.
Ashina Sun.
I know that.
If not for the greater good...
If not for the greater good,
you'd lead the entire Eagle Army and charge to the capital...
to avenge Ya Luo then save your father.
Yes.
As Eagle Army's commander,
I couldn't protect Ya Luo.
As a son,
I shouldn't let Yicheng continue to harm Father all the more.
I know we're all waiting for the right time.
But don't worry.
Yicheng would never kill Great Khan.
After all, she needs him to lead Ashina Tribe's troops.
I'm so confused right now.
Don't.
I'm here.
Ashina Sun.
I'll go with you to save your father.
We'll seek justice for Ya Luo...
and the entire Eagle Army.
Chief, the envoy of Tang wishes to see you.
- All right, you may go. - Yes.
Tang?
That was fast.
Li Chang Ge is not an ordinary person.
I'll meet the envoy.
Will you stay here...
or stay on the side?
I don't want to hear your crap.
Summon the envoy of the Tang.
King of Northern Desert.
I'm the envoy of Tang, Wei Shu Yu.
Recently, our imperial court found out...
that the Ashina Tribe was drafting soldiers in Great Desert.
His Majesty sent me...
to invite all the leaders of Great Desert...
to head over to Chang'an...
and discuss our alliance.
Thank you, Envoy Wei, for coming such a long way.
Let's discuss this slowly...
and carefully.
Chang Ge?
Wei Shu Yu?
Why are you here?
Chang Ge, why did you come to Northern Desert?
Ever since we parted in Liuyun Abbey,
Le Yan and I have been worried about you.
What about Le Yan? How is she?
Her Highness is doing well.
She personally inspected the farmers...
to get close to the citizens.
She is so different from before.
After all, she suffered...
a lot of hardships.
But that's a good thing too.
After all, the princess of Tang needs to become mature.
You're also a princess of Tang.
You've matured too.
Shu Yu.
Tell me how Li Shi Min...
Tell me your motive in coming here this time.
A secret report came to His Majesty.
After reading the secret report,
he told me to come here to discuss the alliance.
That secret letter...
was from Shuozhou.
Was that from you, Chang Ge?
Yes.
I didn't expect...
that you'd still care about Tang.
After all,
Tang is my hometown.
Is he your friend?
Yes, he's my friend, Ashina Sun.
Ashina Sun, come here quickly.
Let me introduce you to my friend from Tang, Wei Shu Yu.
I don't think...
your friend likes me very much.
That's just how he is.
Don't mind him.
It's fine.
Ashina Sun...
Ashina Sun.
He is Ashina Sun from the Ashina Tribe.
Yes.
He is Ashina Sun of the Eagle Army.
I received a secret report.
The Eagle and Bear Armies fought in Northern Desert...
and they're all dead.
How can he still be alive?
It's a long story.
Please hide the news...
that Ashina Sun is still alive.
The alliance meeting is coming up.
We don't want to cause more trouble.
I can promise you that.
But Chang Ge,
if you consider me as a friend, listen to me.
He's not a good person.
You should stay away from him.
Wei Shu Yu.
I know you mean well.
But I know what I'm doing.
Don't worry.
In that case,
there is no point in discussing this further.
Chang Ge, I still have work to do.
I have to go.
Today,
my meeting with Envoy Wei...
might have raised a lot of questions in your mind.
Then go ahead and tell us yourself.
I used to belong in Tang's East Palace.
The current emperor killed my entire family.
While I was on the run,
I met Ashina Sun...
and became friends with him.
So...
Envoy Wei and I are old friends...
and I'm also the military strategist of the Eagle Army.
Interesting.
Won't Tang kill you now?
If not,
how am I able to meet you now?
I'll believe you for now.
Great Desert cannot afford to lose a strong ally.
However,
who should we send to Chang'an?
I want to hear your opinion.
If you two trust me,
I'm willing to be an envoy of Northern Desert...
and attend the alliance meeting in Chang'an.
You?
I was the one who talked to other tribes about the alliance before.
So they must trust me somehow.
Don't worry, Chief.
I'll surely do my best for Great Desert.
You're not from the Great Desert.
Why are you working so hard for the alliance?
I want to end the wars as soon as possible.
Be it the Central Plains, grasslands, or the Great Desert,
people won't suffer from starvation and separation anymore.
Is that all?
Aren't those enough reasons?
What kind of identity do you want to go as?
Is it up to me?
Let me hear it.
I want to go as princess of Northern Desert.
As your sister.
What do you think?
That's fine.
Thank you, Chief.
Since you made a deal with me for the purple gromwell...
until now,
it seems like every step is going according to your expectations.
It's a good thing that you're a friend,
not a foe.
Father.
I want to go to Chang'an too.
Even a fake princess like Chang Ge can go.
Why can't a real princess like me go?
You're eavesdropping on us by the door again.
I was just passing by.
Then I heard Chang Ge mention...
that she's going as a princess.
Father.
- You can't go. - You know this.
I've always wanted to go to Chang'an.
No.
Father, this is a rare opportunity.
If I have such a troublesome daughter,
I would have sent her away as far as I could.
You...
Since Her Highness is a very active girl,
if you won't let her go,
she'll surely find every possible way to go.
She should just come with me.
That's easy for you to say.
What if something happens to my precious daughter?
I have Chang Ge and Ashina Sun.
If anything happens to me,
you can hold Chang Ge accountable.
Father.
I'm telling you.
Tu Jia is my one and only precious daughter.
All right.
Chang Ge will keep me safe, right?
For this trip to Chang'an,
please proceed with caution...
and form the alliance successfully.
I surely won't let you down.
I'll see you off here.
Have a safe trip.
Ashina Sun, have you been to Chang'an?
This is my first trip to Chang'an.
From what I heard, Chang'an is huge and beautiful,
and there's plenty of delicious food.
You'll never know what will happen in our trip to Chang'an.
Are you ready?
Back then in Liuyun Abbey,
Abbess told me to do what my heart tells me,
then just suffer the consequences.
If I just want to seek safety and avoid calamity...
and back out in the face of difficulty,
I wouldn't be who I am today.
No matter what happens, I'll have no fear or regrets.
Also, I have you, right?
You're right.
Come on.
I'll go and get a few people to come and help.
All right.
- Come on. - Here.
Check everyone coming and going.
Do not miss anyone.
Do you understand?
- Yes. - Yes.
Is Great Khan's meal ready?
Yes, it is ready.
Did you add enough ingredients?
I did.
Khatun provided instructions.
She's afraid that Great Khan won't feel full.
Please ask Khatun not to worry.
Great Khan surely won't be disappointed.
(May blessings abound)
You may go.
Yes.
Your Highness.
Northern and Southern Deserts already sent envoys...
to head to Chang'an and discuss the alliance.
The leader is no other...
than Li Chang Ge.
No matter where Li Chang Ge goes,
she can establish herself.
We have quite a few men in Chang'an.
We'll just await your instructions.
Do you plan to kill her?
Tang and Great Desert's alliance will happen for sure.
Killing Li Chang Ge...
won't be useful.
Your Highness, you mean...
Since Great Desert is going to form an alliance with Tang,
I should also...
show my sincerity in cooperating with them.
Your Highness, you can't.
I know what you're worried about.
But now,
I'm not that girl in the carriage...
who couldn't do anything but cry anymore.
I'm very looking forward...
to going to Chang'an.
Since you're going,
I'll go with you.
No.
I still need you to guard Dingxiang for me.
When did you...
start following me?
Was it at Daxing Palace...
or when I got married?
In the 18th year of the Kaihuang Era,
I became a guard in Daxing Palace.
On your second year, you came to the grasslands with me.
I have married four husbands.
But in the end,
you're the one who has always been by my side.
In other words,
I'm also the one who's always with you.
In these huge grasslands,
you're the only one...
I can trust.
On behalf of Your Highness,
I'll surely guard Dingxiang well.
There you are.
I personally made some food for you.
Mother.
What's the matter?
You can't sleep?
Do you miss the grasslands?
It's late.
Mother, get some rest too.
Wait.
I want to talk to you.
Try it.
I know...
that you have a lot of questions in your mind.
And you feel like...
some things happened too suddenly.
I only want to ask you.
All these years,
have you ever thought of breaking away...
from your uncle's shackles...
and being able to see me every day?
Yes.
When I was young, whenever I got hurt...
or punished,
I wanted to go to you the most and seek solace.
But I wouldn't dare and I couldn't.
I can only nurse my wounds myself.
Mother.
I'm not quite used to this.
I understand.
All these years,
you grew up all by yourself.
You're already used...
to life without me.
No.
Now, we've reunited...
at last.
Are you happy?
Yes.
Dingxiang is my hometown.
Here,
I have too many memories...
as well as regrets.
I hope that while I'm alive,
I can make up for some things as much as I can.
Are you willing to stay beside me?
Everything I do...
is for you.
I know.
All right.
You should get some rest too.
I should go.
I still have to go to Chang'an.
Chang'an?
Why would you go to Chang'an?
To finish what I started.
Mother.
I'll go with you to Chang'an.
Stop.
I didn't know that Chang'an would be so lively.
This is so much more fun than Southern and Northern Deserts.
Ashina Sun, Chang Ge.
I'll go and buy something.
Miss, look at this candy figure.
It's two pennies each.
I still came back here.
The place remained the same, but everything else has changed.
The past can only remain in my memory.
Mother, how are you?
You've returned to your sad place.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm fine.
I just feel a bit nostalgic.
As soon as this matter is over,
I'll take you out of here.
Coming back this time,
it feels like everything happened ages ago.
Life...
is really unpredictable.
I tried so hard to run away back then.
Now, I threw caution to the wind and came back again.
Ashina Sun.
Don't you think people are very fickle?
You ran away back then in order to live.
Now, you came back,
so that more people can live.
Chang Ge.
You didn't do anything wrong.
If everyone is living in misery and suffering from the conflicts of war,
how can I live an ignoble existence?
Saving others is also the same as saving myself.
Don't worry.
I'll surely keep you safe.
I'm the princess of Northern Desert now.
Who would dare to harm me?
That makes sense.
With a guard like me here,
I'm afraid the one who tries to offend you...
would be doomed.
(The Long Ballad)