(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 40)
(Quadrangular Courtyard)
- It has been a while. - Yes.
This way, please.
Let's go.
It's a nice place.
Please.
- Here you are. - Come on.
Is it nice?
Look at that.
You can't find it in the desert.
The yard is reserved for you guys...
so that you'll be more comfortable.
In that case, you don't have to fight for a case.
That's nice of you. Thank you.
We're so close,
you don't have to thank me.
If you're not used to it,
you can let me know anytime.
You must be tired from sending us off.
Since the arrangement has been made,
why don't you get back to work?
Get some rest.
Chang Ge, we have so many rooms.
Where do you live?
Your Highness, you may choose first.
That's great.
I want one over there.
You two, come with me.
- Yes. - Yes.
Come on.
Which house do you live in?
I'll clean it up for you.
I'm not in a hurry.
I need to go somewhere...
to meet someone important.
I'll go with you.
Go.
Stop.
Mr. Wei.
It is time to report to the palace.
Get some rest.
I can go by myself.
Yes.
Go.
Go!
Shu Yu looks tired.
He didn't even see us.
Mr. Wei just came back.
He didn't even enter the house.
(Wei Residence)
Greetings, Princess Yong'an.
- Please get up. - Thank you, Your Highness.
Why is Mr. Wei in such a hurry?
Where did he go?
Your Highness.
Mr. Wei just came back from Quadrangular Courtyard.
He's just done settling down the envoy from the Northern Desert.
Now, he's going to the palace to report for work.
Mr. Wei works so hard.
Did your trip to the west go well?
It's all good.
However, it seems that...
in the Northern Desert, Mr. Wei met someone he used to know.
(Speak and act cautiously)
Your Highness.
This is the room of the princess of Northern Desert.
All right.
Yes.
It's you.
I was too rash in the past.
This is Princess Yong'an of the Tang Dynasty.
- Don't be rude. - An Rou.
I didn't know that you're a princess.
So she is Chang Ge's friend.
But isn't Chang Ge...
hold a grudge against the palace?
Should I let her know...
that Chang Ge is in Chang'an?
I didn't expect you to be the princess of the Northern Desert.
What happened in Yunzhou was a misunderstanding after all.
I've been meaning to ask you.
How did you know...
there's a word "bunny" in my pouch?
It's because the same character...
was embroidered in my pouch too.
Maybe it's a coincidence.
I think we're meant to meet each other.
My pouch was given by my best friend.
I thought you two knew each other.
In that case,
since you've traveled a long way,
get some rest.
If you need anything,
just let the servant in the Quadrangular Courtyard know.
I won't disturb you further.
(Quadrangular Courtyard)
What should I do?
She's alive.
If Her Highness knows about it,
she'll be over the moon.
Your Highness.
Since you came back from Quadrangular Courtyard,
you've been spacing out.
The princess of Northern Desert...
reminded me of Chang Ge.
I wonder...
how is she doing?
What pouch was that?
What Yunzhou?
I don't understand.
It's all in the past.
It doesn't matter.
Perhaps Mr. Wei is still in the palace.
Do you want to see him, Your Highness?
Shu Yu has been rushing around for a few days.
I'll go in a few days.
This is...
(Salvation through charity to others)
This is where my mother rests in peace.
I want you to meet her.
What are you doing?
This is the first time your mother meets me.
I have to leave a good impression.
If my mother sees you with her own eyes,
she'll like you a lot.
Chang Ge.
Thank you for bringing me here to see your mother.
Let's go.
(Salvation through charity to others)
(Memorial tablet of Madam Jin)
Someone still remembers your mother.
That's why they clean the place regularly.
These offerings are very fresh as well.
Yes.
I'm surprised that someone in Chang'an...
would still remember my mother.
I don't know if it's Le Yan or Yu Shu...
who ordered someone to do it.
In the past,
when I left Chang'an,
what worried me the most was the people in Chang'an...
would forget her, the neglectable sacrifice.
(Memorial tablet of Madam Jin)
But now,
I'm relieved.
(Memorial tablet of Madam Jin)
Mother, I am back.
I came back to see you.
This is Ashina Sun.
I'd like him to meet you.
I'm Ashina Sun and I pay my respects to you.
Chang Ge.
I'd like to propose a toast to your mother.
Madam.
It's our first meeting.
I wasn't prepared.
Please take this cup of wine...
as a token of my apology and respect.
All this time,
I put Chang Ge through so much trouble.
Please forgive me.
Now, Chang Ge and I are in love.
Let me take care of her from now on.
(Memorial tablet of Madam Jin)
Madam, don't worry.
From now on, I'll look after her...
and take care of her...
to make it up to her.
What nonsense are you talking in front of my mother?
It's not nonsense, it's the truth.
Have you forgotten what did you say when we're in the Northern Desert?
Are you going back on your own words...
in front of your mother?
When men on the grasslands fall in love with someone,
they'll love her, protect her,
and take care of her for the rest of her life.
Ashina Sun.
Thank you.
We're so close.
You don't have to thank me.
Mother.
I'll visit you often from now on.
Ashina Sun and I...
will visit you together.
Chang Ge?
Chang Ge.
You left in a rush at Wei River.
Now that I know...
you're safe,
I can finally be at ease.
I haven't killed the murderer.
I would still be alive of course.
Stop right there.
Stay away from her resting place.
God is above our head.
Aren't you afraid of karma?
(Memorial tablet of Madam Jin)
Drop the act.
You don't deserve to be here.
I will kill you one day.
Chang Ge.
If you really want to kill me,
you would have killed me with the arrow...
when we met each other at Wei River.
If I may guess,
you shot the arrow...
when we were at Wei River, right?
I wasn't going to save you.
I wanted to save the people of Tang Dynasty.
You put the Tang Dynasty first.
You always put people first.
You've never dishonored the country because of your personal agenda.
That's great.
Princess Yongning...
has finally grown up.
About what you did in Luoyang,
Minister Du...
has told me everything.
So what?
I won't forgive you.
I won't ask you to forgive me.
(Memorial tablet of Madam Jin)
I won't ask Jin to forgive me.
Shut up.
Don't call my mother's name.
Fang Yi, stand down.
Don't worry.
Her Highness prioritizes the nation.
She won't harm His Majesty.
I raised you.
I know what kind of person...
is my child.
You look good together.
Since you're being protected,
I'm sure...
Jin will feel...
relieved.
(Memorial tablet of Madam Jin)
It's him.
He has been praying for my mother.
Mother.
I won't be able to avenge you.
This is a household registration deed prepared for you.
You can use a new identity...
to live in the Tang Dynasty.
You don't have to hide anymore.
Is this an idea from that person?
It doesn't matter whose idea it was.
We want you to start over...
and live the life you want.
Change my name...
and bury all of my past.
That's what you want.
I used to be your teacher in the past.
I know a little about you.
Since you're not obsessed with revenge,
what's the point of trapping yourself in the past?
I still have some unfinished duties.
I knew that...
the secret letter came from you.
Are you determined...
to be the envoy for the desert?
I became the ambassador for the Northern Desert...
to seek help...
and to make peace.
If the Tang Dynasty...
is willing to be the shield to the Northern Desert,
the Northern Desert...
will naturally become the spear to the Tang Dynasty.
In that case,
if Ashina Tribe wants to colonize the desert...
or if they intend to invade the Tang Dynasty...
they will at least stop and think.
Do you know...
if both parties decided to form an alliance...
due to the fear of the situation,
but not to sincerely make peace,
the alliance...
is just an agreement...
that can't withstand any blow.
- It's worth a shot. - It's worth a shot.
Sir.
You're now...
next to the stronger master.
Could it be due to the fear of the situation?
Chang Ge, have you ever thought about it before?
Prince of Qi and your father...
decided to make things difficult for His Majesty.
How did His Majesty...
know about the details...
of such a well-hidden affair?
His Majesty was informed...
by the spies in the East Palace.
The crown prince had meticulous planning.
No matter how long His Majesty's arms and legs are,
he couldn't get into the crown prince's study.
Who could it be?
How about I tell you a story?
That year,
Emperor Sui Yang traveled to the north to the Great Wall.
When His Majesty arrived at Yanmen Pass,
he was besieged by Ashina Tribe.
While saving His Majesty,
a young general...
saved a pretty, young woman...
by accident.
Later on,
the young general was ordered to go on the battlefield.
He told that young lady to stay back with the other women.
He was...
my mother's lifesaver.
No way.
Then...
Mother was...
My mother wouldn't hurt my father.
They're husband and wife.
That's not all.
That young general made a great contribution...
in his first fight.
Hence, he was entrusted with important tasks.
Later, he was sent to battlefields...
more and more frequently.
However, he didn't know that...
when he was fighting battles,
his elder brother...
mistaken that young lady...
as his mistress.
after getting drunk.
When he returned from war,
that lady was already pregnant.
She was pregnant with me.
After you were born,
that general adored you.
Maybe it's fate.
When you were young,
you didn't even smile when you saw your father.
Only when your eyes met the general,
you would smile nonstop.
Slowly, you grew up.
And then you guys got along...
like a father and a daughter.
I don't have to go into that.
Chang Ge.
In this world,
only he truly cares...
about you and your mother.
Why didn't my mother tell me anything about him?
Was that the reason why she couldn't get along with my father?
My father was never pleased with me.
I thought it was because I was not good enough.
I couldn't read my mother's mind.
What kind of daughter am I?
Chang Ge.
You brought your mother a lot of joy.
Because of you,
she's not lonely.
Since...
Since my mother was a spy,
why did he kill my mother?
Sometimes what you see...
is not always the truth.
Not always the truth?
(Chang'an)
Ashina Sun, do you think...
Mr. Wei is speaking the truth?
The grudges...
that I've been holding are all in my head.
Is that so?
Chang Ge.
It's not your fault.
It's a complicated world.
It can't be explained with simple language.
(Chang'an)
Every person who wants to leave Chang'an...
will have to pass by this path.
In the past,
I left this place in the name of the treacherous princess.
I thought when I came back again,
I would be leading an army...
to avenge my late father.
I didn't expect...
I would be so confused.
I hesitated even when facing my enemy.
But I have to admit,
he was a good emperor.
I should hate him.
But he has always doted on me.
He was the one who taught me both the pen and the sword.
I'm closer to him than to my father.
I know how you feel.
My mother was killed by She Er.
I hoped I could kill She Er on the stop...
to avenge my mother.
But when I actually had to do it,
I hesitated too.
If I had killed She Er,
I would bring trouble to the Eagle Army.
It'll affect the peacefulness on the grasslands.
That's not what I want.
And it's not what my mother wanted.
When personal vengeance conflicts with the great cause,
we can't help but get flustered.
Furthermore,
you're dealing with the leader of the Tang Dynasty...
and the millions of people behind him.
You hesitated...
because you care about the happiness of other people.
I think...
your parents won't blame you.
It's over.
It doesn't matter whether your mother informed him.
This tragedy...
was probably inevitable.
Your mother was sandwiched between the siblings.
I'm sure she had a hard time.
I know.
I just feel sorry for my mother.
She couldn't share it with anyone.
That's why...
my mother told me to kneel before the Buddha.
She wanted me to make a vow to live with no grudges.
She knew it.
Your mother is an amazing woman.
She's a great mother.
Therefore, Chang Ge,
you should pull yourself together...
and live a better life.
Ashina Sun.
When everything is over,
the Tang Dynasty, the desert,
and the grasslands...
will be at peace for a long time.
When the time comes,
let's go live in the countryside, all right?
No matter where you go,
I will follow.
(Chang'an)
(Quadrangular Courtyard)
Chang Ge.
What's wrong?
You look tired.
I'm fine.
It's just that I'm so stubborn.
I enlarged the family feuds.
I almost...
I almost killed someone who has been nice to me.
It's over.
Have you...
forgiven the man who killed your father?
I don't know.
Some things...
are hard to explain...
whether it's right or wrong.
I would have told her if I knew.
What?
The princess of the Tang Dynasty was here yesterday.
She's the princess you gave the pouch to.
Le Yan?
Did she say anything?
She thought I was the princess of the Northern Desert.
She also asked...
how did I know about the pouch.
But I didn't tell her the truth.
I didn't want you to feel bad about it.
She's my best friend in Chang'an.
That's right.
I should see her since I'm here.
Your Highness,
didn't we just go to Quadrangular Courtyard yesterday?
Why are you going there again today?
Furthermore, you opted not to take a carriage.
You're so secretive.
That lady we saw yesterday...
wasn't the princess of the Northern Desert.
From how she dressed,
I could tell that she's not from a noble family.
I guess...
she's just a servant.
Your Highness, you...
Did you make a conclusion based on those aspects?
Yesterday, when I asked her about the pouch,
she was stuttering and she was also delirious.
She was so condescending when she was in Yunzhou.
She has completely changed.
Hence, I'm sure that...
she knows Chang Ge.
What?
Is Princess Yongning here too?
For the sake of Chang Ge's safety,
we need to keep a low profile.
I just want...
I just want to verify my speculation.
I don't want to alert anyone.
And I hope Chang Ge is really there.
Come on.
Hao Du.
I saw Your Highness leaving the palace...
without taking the carriage.
I was worried about your safety.
So are you...
following me in secret again?
I'm just worried about Your Highness.
This is Chang'an.
I'm safe.
You're right, Your Highness.
However, all the ambassadors from different tribes are here.
You should be careful, Your Highness.
Hao Du.
You once said that...
you'd only capture those who harmed the Tang Dynasty.
Yes.
If Your Highness is worried,
I'll just follow you from afar.
As long as it's not dangerous,
I'll never come between you and...
your friend.
All right.
I didn't want to draw any attention anyway.
Got it.
I will keep it a secret.
Chang Ge.
Let me go with you.
Don't worry, Mimi.
I'll be fine.
But this is Chang'an.
And you've been hurt before.
I'm really worried.
If you don't promise me,
I'll tell Ashina Sun.
- Well... - Are you going out?
(Quadrangular Courtyard)
I want to see Le Yan.
Are you going to the palace?
But before I go see Le Yan,
I'm going to meet with Shu Yu first.
You don't have to go there.
Chang Ge.
Le Yan.
I knew you'd be here.
I didn't get to see you yesterday,
but I have a hunch that you're here.
It's my bad.
I didn't go to see you after coming back to Chang'an.
It's not too late to see you now.
I met her on the grasslands.
Her name is Mimi Guli.
I think you've met each other.
This is...
I know him.
When I was in Luoyang,
he saved you.
His name is Ashina Sun.
Ashina Sun, this is my sister.
All right.
Stop chatting, everyone. Let's go inside.
I had fun today.
All my best friends are here.
I didn't have the guts to dream of a reunion like this.
Chang Ge.
Are you still going to leave Chang'an?
You're right.
Chang'an won't be able to hold you back.
But...
how did you become the princess of the Northern Desert?
It's a long story.
This is a feasting song.
Feasting?
The ritual of feasting is only for the guests.
The ritual is used to welcome the newly joined convoy.
However,
all the convoys are already here.
Why are there newly joined convoys?
I don't know.
How about this, Mimi?
Wait here.
Let Le Yan and I find out what's going on.
All right, come back soon.
Sure.
Why are you in a panic?
What should we do?
We have to do something.
We can't just wait here to die.
That's right.
Am I right?
Chang Ge.
Who is she?
If I may ask,
does Your Highness know that convoy of Ashina Tribe is here?
Your Highness,
did the Tang Dynasty invite them here?
The Tang Dynasty didn't intend to invite them.
You...
You're from the Tang Dynasty.
The princess of the Northern Desert met with a Tang person in private.
That's not true.
Ashina Tribe coming to Tang...
means they know about the alliance.
I don't care if you collude with each other.
We have to leave now.
Zhi Xi.
What if Ashina Tribe found out our alliance with Tang...
and decided to attack us at this juncture?
All of us will be wiped out.
- Yes. - All of us will be wiped out.
We have to go back quickly.
Don't worry.
The Tang Dynasty will never abandon all the tribes.
I can promise you.
I'm Princess Yong'an of the Tang Dynasty.
- Princess. - She's a princess.
No.
We still need to leave.
The Emperor of Tang is far away.
It's easy for you to say that at the moment.
When the dog is beaten, the lion is tamed.
They will leave us hanging for sure.
- Yes. - Let's go.
Listen to me, everyone.
- Don't make noise. Hold on. - Move.
Calm down.
Listen to me, everyone.
Listen to me, guys.
Now, listen to me.
Are you done?
Since Ashina Tribe...
has the guts to come to Quadrangular Courtyard,
they must have passed through customs.
They are here for a diplomatic mission.
However, if anything happens,
do you think the Tang Dynasty will turn a blind eye?
What are you afraid of?
We can't take it lightly.
Why are you all standing there?
Are you welcoming Ashina Tribe?
- Your Highness. - Your Highness.
It's you.
Ashina Tribe is here.
Yes.
I heard that Young Khan is here.
The lady that he's escorting...
is someone from Ashina Tribe...
known as Khatun.
Are you serious?
I think it's real. That's what I heard anyway.
Khatun?
The time has come.
The old Mimi is dead.
Right now,
you can be bold and brave.
You can be yourself, Mimi.
Look.
The moment Ashina Tribe is here,
these guys behave...
as if they are rabbits that run into an eagle.
All they do is run.
No one is running away.
The Southern Desert isn't afraid of you.
Zhen Zhu.
You're dressed inappropriately.
What role are you playing...
in the Quadrangular Courtyard?
If I expose your true identity,
will you...
She Er.
You...
You're alive.
Why did you lie to me?
You're a jerk.
I thought you were dead.
I can't believe you pretended to be dead.
Coward. Liar.
I overestimated you.
I engraved your name on the warrior tombstone.
You don't deserve it.
Don't play innocent here.
You two colluded to stab me in the back.
Don't tell me you know nothing.
I don't want to be your enemy.
From now on,
we're not brothers anymore.
Yicheng came to Chang'an.
This is...
It has been a while,
Li Chang Ge.
Today, the Great Khan is relaxed.
He kept making noise when he was first moved to the room.
Tell me about it.
Maybe the decoction is working.
He has stopped making noise now.
Great Khan was so cool all his life.
It's a pity that he fell sick.
What are you talking about?
I told you before.
Don't ever...
talk about anything that happens here.
- Forgive us, Commander Lei. - Forgive us, Commander Lei.
- We are sorry. - We are sorry.
There is no next time.
I'm showing mercy by letting you live.
It's also a lesson for everyone else.
This is what happens when you gossip.
The Great Khan's illness...
is strange.
(May blessings abound)
(Imperial Kitchen)
- Why did Khatun come to Chang'an? - Yes.
Chang Ge.
This is...
She is She Er's mother.
I'm Khatun from Ashina Tribe.
Great Khan has caught an illness.
My son and I had to come...
on his behalf...
to sincerely express our gratitude...
to the Tang and other tribes.
Of course.
It's also for the betrothal...
between the Tang Dynasty and Ashina Tribe.
I shouldn't have come.
But we're discussing our children's marriage.
At least, one of the parents...
has to be here.
The Tang Dynasty always honors its words.
I believe that...
they will keep their promise.
I think everyone was here in Chang'an...
because you believe the same.
So they're here for the betrothal.
- They're here for the betrothal. - Yes.
I'd like to propose a toast...
to everyone.
Chang Ge, she means...
the Emperor of Tang had a betrothal with Ashina Tribe.
If His Majesty goes back to his own words,
does that mean...
he will overturn the alliance with the desert anytime?
I can't believe that she said that.
Could it be that she is certain that...
the Emperor of Tang won't marry the princess as promised?
Hao Du, take her away first.
I'll handle things here.
Khatun and Young Khan have just arrived today.
On behalf of the Northern Desert,
I propose a toast to Khatun and Young Khan.
Wait.
Why don't we let your guard...
drink for you?
The tour guard is so obedient, Your Highness.
It looks like you taught him well.
Since Your Highness can come to Chang'an...
on behalf of the Ashina Tribe,
it seems that you've taken well care...
of the capital.
Well,
a guard of the Northern Desert...
has no say in it.
(The Long Ballad)