Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 9)
Sir, are you all right?
Water.
- Water.
- Water?
It's done.
Stop.
You killed Prince of Lujiang.
Prince of Lujiang, Li Yuan,
is rebellious and disobedient.
I've already killed him.
You killed your master to save yourself?
I serve Prince of Lujiang.
He instructed me to do evil things.
I had no choice.
Now, I've killed him.
I hope...
I hope I could redeem myself.
Where is Shu Yu?
Envoy Wei...
was wounded by Prince of Lujiang's men.
- I've instructed men to treat him.
- You...
He is recuperating in the room.
Envoy Wei?
General Shen.
I have a piece of important information for the royal court.
Do you know the identity of the person who just left?
She is the traitor, Li Jian Cheng's daughter.
- Arrest him!
- Yes.
Shen Gu. You...
Prince of Lujiang has rebelled.
Arrest all of his men for investigation.
Shen Gu.
I did this for you out of kindness.
I can't believe you're this ungrateful.
Shut him up.
I won't let you be.
Chang Ge.
Why are you here?
I'm just glad you're fine.
Le Yan is waiting for you at the stage station.
Somehow...
Wang Jun Kuo suddenly let me go.
He even got me a physician.
Hao Du lit the signal fire.
I impersonated you...
and summoned our generals outside the town.
Wang Jun Kuo knew that he is at a disadvantage,
so he killed his master to save himself.
What?
I've done all that I could.
Take good care of Le Yan.
Make sure she gets home safely.
Chang Ge.
As long as you're holding the Crown Prince's seal,
Hao Du would...
It doesn't belong to Li Shi Min anyway.
I just took what belongs to me.
Master, how was it?
Let's go.
- Keep a close eye on her.
- Yes.
(Governor's Manor)
Under the orders of Crown Prince Zuo,
I have come to arrest the rebels.
I'm Shen Gu, a general stationed at Youzhou.
Envoy Wei has informed us.
We're dealing with the funeral now.
Envoy Wei?
If Envoy Wei didn't arrive in time,
I can't even imagine the consequences.
What a shame.
Prince of Lujiang has been killed by Wang Jun Kuo.
We can't get the first statement.
(Governor's Manor)
Master, the person who kidnapped you is here again.
Come here.
Hold on.
What are you planning to do to Wang Jun Kuo?
Once I've informed the court,
we will proceed from there.
For security purposes,
I've had him locked up in my camp.
Wang Jun Kuo is very cunning.
And he has many subordinates.
He might get away.
Thank you.
Who are you?
Why are you arresting me?
It's a kid?
Who are you?
Why did you push me?
I've contributed a lot.
I brought help from the camp during the night.
Don't forget to tell this to the court.
I'm waiting for my reward.
I led the rest of the rebels and eliminated...
- the rebellion in Youzhou!
- Search the place.
- Yes!
Go!
Where is Chang Ge?
You're asking me?
It can't be like this.
I have to get her back.
- It's still with her.
- I'm glad you know.
If we don't find it,
you and I can never go back to Chang'an.
Get up now.
Go and get her back.
Your partner is still in town.
Will he be all right?
We made a promise.
I'll leave hints along the path.
He'll come and see me when he gets out.
Thank you for saving my life.
I dare not accept a bow from Your Highness.
How do you know?
You have a courtly temperament.
Other people won't be able to learn it.
Rumors have it that Princess Yongning is still missing.
I was once the Crown Prince's subordinate.
How could I not recognize you?
Wang Jun Kuo even offered to hand you in to the imperial court.
This proves even more that I was right.
In that case,
why don't you join me and leave together?
Now, the whole Youzhou is in Li Shi Min's hands.
He surely won't let my father's former subordinates go.
Instead of being submissive,
why don't you leave with me?
We can work together.
I am a general.
I only follow orders.
General Shen.
The whole Youzhou is under Du Ru Hui's control.
We can never get Youzhou back.
We'll only be waiting for death here.
Besides,
I still have the Crown Prince's seal.
Do you really think a lifeless object...
can mobilize thousands of troops?
I'm helping you because I want to repay the Crown Price's kindness.
It's a selfish action.
I'm the Crown Prince's former subordinate,
but first, I am a general of Tang.
Now, the Ashina Tribe is planning an attack in the north.
Youzhou is an important town in the north.
There are millions of people.
My job is to protect...
the land of Youzhou.
If I can't even perform my duties,
no matter what you have,
it'll be pointless, Your Highness.
Although I don't agree entirely,
I respect your decisions.
I learned something today.
Your Highness, you should leave.
When the chasers arrive,
I will have no choice but to do my job.
I can no longer stay in Youzhou.
The world is huge.
Yet, I have nowhere to go.
Go northwest.
Go to Shuozhou.
It's an isolated place.
It's a piece of land between Tang and the plains.
The royal court won't be able to reach you.
Thank you, General Shen.
Take care, Your Highness.
I shall bid you farewell.
Go!
- Go!
Stop.
Your Highness, that's enough.
If we continue, we'll be exhausted.
Didn't you say that jerk has left already?
Why did he come back?
I can't let this go.
I already observed the surroundings.
There's no trace of an army passing by.
That jerk must have come back alone.
Your Highness.
- What do you want to do?
- He plotted against me.
Why can't I do the same?
You should report back to Great Khan in this instance.
If we delay any longer,
Great Khan will get suspicious of us.
Stop telling me what to do and what not to do.
Do you really think that you're my elder brother?
So what if Great Khan is suspicious?
Am I supposed to just let this go?
Great Khan is leading his men to Shuozhou.
The astringer should be in the north of Shuozhou by now.
Go this way.
If we can guess which route he's taking,
so can Ashina Sun.
Yes.
Could they have taken the south route?
Don't you think he would have thought of that already?
That jerk is always full of tricks.
He has been after me.
He knew I would guess that he went this way.
But Great Khan gave him an order.
If he goes this way,
the military line will be delayed.
He would do whatever it takes to complete Great Khan's orders.
That's why he'll definitely take the north road.
And I have a feeling that...
he will take the main road on purpose.
We'll cut him off at the main road.
We need to be fast.
Pick him up on the side road.
Why?
Because I think he'll take the main road.
I'm sure he expected me to think that.
This time, I bet...
he could have guessed it too.
- Go!
General Shen.
Are you trying to harbor a criminal?
A criminal?
What are you talking about?
The rebel, Wang Jun Kuo, has been imprisoned.
And you two are barging in...
with a piece of one-off charm.
I can't believe everything you say.
Now that the rebellion has begun,
we can't have any scouts...
get out of the town.
It seems today,
you're not letting us pass no matter what.
So what?
With General Shen's ability,
there's no way we can get away from him.
One of us has to sacrifice.
My martial arts skills are better than yours.
You should leave first.
Be very careful.
Go!
Attack!
I knew they wouldn't be able to find you.
But when you think you've dodged it,
you will definitely show up.
Nice try, right?
That's right.
You're not defeated by failures.
Not bad.
Go!
Who told you to attack him?
My job is to protect you.
I'm not here to see you get beaten up.
I...
Ambush is about hitting the target immediately.
Now that you've alerted him,
it'll be hard to catch up with him.
Come on.
We must go back and report this.
Go!
Stop.
You guys continue to chase after him.
I can't let him get away with this.
- Go!
Go!
Chang Ge.
Stop it.
Haven't you gotten into enough trouble in Youzhou?
When are you going to stop running away?
Chang Ge.
I, Wei Shu Yu, swear to the heavens.
I'll do whatever it takes to protect you.
Even if I can't undo anything,
I'm willing to die with you.
Whether it's the world of the living or the dead,
I'll be with you until the end.
I won't trust anyone anymore.
I won't stay for anyone.
But you still have the Crown Prince's seal.
They won't spare you until they get it back.
You make it sound good.
You just want to retrieve the Crown Prince's seal.
So that you can get your job done.
Chang Ge.
Wei Shu Yu.
Listen carefully.
From now on,
we're no longer related.
This is the last time I'm doing this.
I'll give you another merit.
Take it back and report to your higher-up.
This is nothing but a lifeless object.
You can't move people's hearts.
From now on,
I won't rely on anyone else but myself.
Shen Gu.
You're hiding a criminal of the imperial court.
When I return to Chang'an,
I'll report this to the Crown Prince and get you punished!
Please don't be angry.
General Shen said you've been proven to be innocent.
He asked me to apologize on his behalf.
By the way, Envoy Wei is here.
Sir, this way, please.
Please.
Did you lose Li Chang Ge again?
I have found the Crown Prince's seal.
We can return to Chang'an now.
I do not only want the Crown Prince's seal.
I want Li Chang Ge too.
Wei Shu Yu.
Where are you going?
The Princess is waiting at the stage station.
Good girl.
What's your name?
Who exactly are you?
If my partner doesn't see me when he gets back,
he'll definitely come looking for me.
By then, you'll be in trouble.
So let them come to me.
Good girl.
You have to be grateful.
Or you might get yourself killed.
Let me ask you again.
What's your name?
Tell him.
I'm Le Yan.
That's good.
Just call me Hai Lao.
Be good from now on.
I'll find a good family...
and sell you at a good price.
If you don't,
I'll cut off all your limbs.
I was kidnapped too.
These two are human traffickers.
Human traffickers?
They would kidnap women and children for human trafficking.
Human trafficking?
Where to?
What does he mean when he said he will cut off my limbs?
It means he'll cut off your arms and legs...
and made you a beggar.
Le Yan.
We have no other choice but to help each other out.
Do you understand?
Go!
Le Yan.
Where's the Princess?
Where did the guest of this room go?
I don't know.
I didn't hear anything from this room.
All of her valuables are gone.
There are no signs of struggles in the room.
The Princess couldn't have left by herself.
There's only one possibility.
She was knocked out and taken away.
Wei Shu Yu.
Clean up the mess.
Return to Chang'an immediately.
Report about Youzhou...
and that the Princess has gone missing.
No.
I'm going to find her.
I'll say this one last time.
Your mission now...
is to report back to Chang'an.
Le Yan has disappeared.
That's not important right now.
She doesn't know the area well.
It's a war zone further north.
Le Yan is a noble woman.
She's innocent and weak.
She's all alone now.
Our first priority is to bring her back.
Shut up, Wei Shu Yu.
Let me ask you, whose fault is it that the Princess is missing?
Who told her to come along?
Who's the one who guaranteed to take full responsibility...
for the Princess' safety?
I said I'd bear it.
And I will take full responsibility.
You can report to the higher-up.
No matter what it takes,
I will find the Princess.
If anything happens to her,
I'll pay for it with my life.
Wei Shu Yu.
Don't forget why you come to Youzhou.
Also,
you won't find the Princess alone.
We need the Crown Prince's help.
It's a mark left by my master.
Your Highness.
The smoke signal has been extinguished.
Youzhou has been conquered.
Envoy Wei is on his way back to the capital.
That's good.
Your Highness.
All Li Jian Cheng's former subordinates...
are around Shandong, Hebei.
If we let them continue to guard the city,
it'll be nursing a viper in our bosom.
The same thing that happened in Youzhou will happen again.
What are you trying to say?
All Hebei townsfolk are guarding the perimeter...
to prevent invasion of the bandits from the plains.
Are you trying to take away...
all their military power?
If you have a better solution,
I'm all ears.
Don't forget.
It was your son who went to Youzhou.
Not only Prince of Lujiang didn't follow him back to the capital,
but he also started a rebellion.
Your son...
is such a genius.
Your Highness, I didn't teach my son well.
I have committed a grave sin.
When he comes back,
aside from the punishment from the royal court,
I will punish him personally.
But the Youzhou incident...
is related to our great nation.
I beg you, Your Highness.
Please don't suppress the military officers.
So that the people wouldn't panic.
I once assisted Jian Cheng in managing Hebei.
I'm willing to go to Hebei...
to appease Li Jian Cheng...
and Li Yuan Ji's former subordinates.
Mr. Wei.
If Your Highness trusts me,
I'll set off tomorrow morning.
I hope Your Highness could make them yield...
and submit to you by making peace.
All right.
I'll leave it to you, sir.
It's a long journey.
You may dress casually...
and act without permission.
Thank you, Your Highness.
If he doesn't return,
no matter where he is,
I will get rid of him...
on behalf of the royal court.
You don't mean it.
In fact, you purposely talk about...
punishing the generals and his son...
to incite him to volunteer to go to Hebei.
So what?
Poor Wei Zheng.
He's such a straightforward person.
He thought...
if he didn't take care of it himself,
you will really request His Highness to punish the generals.
It's not easy for us to get him on our side,
of course we have to put him to good use.
Otherwise, it would be a waste of his talent.
That makes sense.
Every time I see you,
you're either living in a woodshed or a shabby house.
Why are you here?
I should be the one asking you that.
Not everyone is as wealthy as you.
Why are you hurt?
What are you doing?
Treat your wound, of course.
Come on.
Ask me anything you want.
Don't hold it in.
How did you get hurt?
What's with the horses?
There's no need to beat around the bush.
You have questions for me, don't you?
Yes.
I am from the Ashina Tribe.
I won't deny that.
You and Great Khan's son of the Ashina Tribe know each other.
He colluded with Wang Jun Kuo.
He even stole from Youzhou's treasury.
Are you involved?
I can only tell you this.
I was indeed wounded by his men.
As for the treasury's carriage you stopped,
it was also me who flawed it.
It really is you.
Who are you?
Qin Zhun.
Since you don't want to tell me,
then I won't ask.
I'll think of you as a profiteer.
But it's not my style to not help those in need.
After leaving Youzhou,
where will you be heading?
I can't tell you.
Go down this road.
There are only two choices.
It's either heading to Shuozhou...
or the plains.
I don't think...
you're heading to the plains.
Don't go to Shuozhou.
Why not?
That's the border.
It's next to the plains and far away from Tang.
Also,
over the years,
it has always been a war zone.
You should just mind your own business.
I'm serious.
You should leave.
It's not safe here.
If anyone asks,
just say you've never seen me before.
Will you be all right...
by yourself?
Don't worry.
I won't die that easily.
Hold on.
Next time,
don't live in this hellhole anymore.
Sympathy is not my thing.
I'm lending it to you.
Remember to pay me back.
Thank you.
Until we meet again,
Shi Si Lang.
No.
Princess Yongning.
I'm glad we got it back.
Reward Envoy Hao and Envoy Wei.
Thank you, Your Highness.
The Chang Ge I know...
won't give this up that easily.
Is Chang Ge all right?
After Princess Yongning handed this over to me,
she escaped.
Forget it.
Don't cause any more trouble.
Put an end to this.
I have something else to tell you, Your Highness.
Is it about Chang Ge?
It's about Princess Yong'an.
What's wrong with Le Yan?
Princess Yong'an...
followed the troop to Youzhou.
But unpredicted changes happened in Youzhou.
Wei Shu Yu was captured by Wang Jun Kuo.
Hao Du went to rescue him.
And Princess Yong'an waited at the stage station.
But...
When they returned to the stage station...
after signal smoke is cleared,
Princess Yong'an disappeared.
Your Highness.
I've asked the surrounding counties...
to secretly find out where Princess Yong'an is.
Wei Shu Yu has requested to go look for Princess Yong'an...
to make up for his mistakes.
Should we summon...
Wei Shu Yu back for punishment first, Your Highness?
Forget it.
I believe that...
he'll do his best to find Yan Er.
Convey my orders.
Say that Princess Yong'an is ill.
And she's still recuperating at Luoyang Palace.
You can't tell anyone about this.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
I'll surely make arrangements.
Ke Ming.
You may leave now.
I want to be alone.
I'll take my leave.
Le Yan.
You dropped your food.
Pick it up.
If you're not going to eat it, I will.
Slow down.
It's all yours.
You're so good to me.
We'll be sisters from now on.
We'll share the good and the bad.
Le Yan, I'm a bit thirsty.
I'll drink your water.
Hai Lao.
Can I have some more water?
I've given you all the food and drinks for today.
You gave them up yourself.
Whose fault is it?
Fang Yi.
Your Highness.
Any news from Le Yan?
I've sent out more men to search for Princess Yong'an in every county.
But...
there's no news yet.
Yan Er.
A weak girl like you...
wandering among the common folks.
I'm really worried about you.
Water.
Le Yan.
Shu Yu.
Shu Yu, you came to save me.
Don't die here.
Don't get my carriage dirty.
Who is Shu Yu?
Do you want me to bring Shu Yu...
to keep you company?
No.
Please don't hurt Shu Yu.
You've been missing for days.
I didn't see anyone named Shu Yu come looking for you.
Could he have forgotten about you already?
How much money do you want?
How much do you want?
I'll give it to you.
Just let me go.
So you're from a rich family.
Then all the more reason I shouldn't let you go.
Your family will kill me if I set you free.
No, they won't.
They won't. I promise.
They won't.
Hai Lao, please.
Please let me go.
I need to rest.
Shut up.
Or I'll cut off your tongue.
Shu...
Good job.
You've learned your lesson.
Stop.
Le Yan.
Where are you?
(Shuozhou)
Sachets.
Sachets. Have a look.
They're playing ball.
Buy one for your child.
Catch.
Shuozhou is far beyond the borders of the state.
This place is isolated.
It has been at war for years.
Why is it so busy and crowded?
I'm Gongsun Heng of the state.
Surrender now, you thieves.
Gongsun Heng?
- No.
- Give me something to eat.
- Have a drink.
- Thank you.
- Take it.
- Even in the Chang'an,
- Thank you.
it's not as busy and harmonious as this place.
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)