Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 12)
Army Chief has commanded me...
to come and collect...
Gongsun Heng's command token.
Where's the command token?
Give it to me now.
The thieves sure got here fast.
Come on.
Madam, please be sensible.
Move out of the way.
Don't make our men use force.
This is the Gongsun family's private residence,
not the Shuozhou Office.
I can't make the decision...
on what my husband...
wants to keep or hand over.
I must wait for my husband's return...
before giving you an answer.
Madan, you better cooperate.
If you give it to us sooner,
it will also clear...
Governor Gongsun's name sooner.
Your family can also reunite sooner.
Governor Gongsun is currently detained and awaiting trial.
The result will all depend...
on Chief's decision.
At a time like this, I suggest...
you don't offend us.
What a coincidence.
Gongsun Heng fought in wars all his life...
and guarded this city for half of his life.
While with him,
I'm used to seeing weapons.
These empty words...
can't scare me.
Then don't blame me...
for being rude.
Who is it?
Who did it?
Speak if you must.
But don't you dare to act imprudently...
in front of my master.
Governor Gongsun is not here.
Madam can't make a decision.
If you need anything,
just come to me.
Can you make the decision?
My master has fallen into your hands.
I have to make the decision even if I can't.
Madam, if you trust me,
let me handle this.
Please go inside and take care of Yuan Niang.
- Thank you.
- This way, please.
Everyone.
Come with me.
Bad news!
Something bad happened! We got robbed.
Nonsense.
How can the Governor's Manor get robbed?
Are you kidding me?
We haven't thoroughly checked the money and items we lost.
But Governor Gongsun's study...
and the accounting room experienced very serious losses.
In order to minimize the loss,
we need to go after the thief right away.
All right, that's enough. Where are your manners?
This is Imperial Guard Wang, who works for Chief Sima.
Greet him immediately.
Imperial Guard Wang, you came just in time.
Please help us go after the thief now.
What a joke.
How is a robbery at Governor's Manor my business?
Give me the command token now.
Command token?
The command token is in Governor Gongsun's study.
This is bad.
Where's the study?
Right there.
Come on.
Elder Qin.
We really got robbed.
Search the place!
What should we do?
My goodness. This...
Imperial Guard Wang, we didn't find the command token.
Don't try to trick me.
I don't care if the command token was really stolen or not.
Within three days,
if you can't hand over the command token,
there won't be peace in Governor's Manor.
Come on!
How did you know that they would come?
Sima Tu keeps pressuring Governor Gongsun...
to give him the command token.
This time, he detained Governor Gongsun...
just to get the command token.
This is...
just a delaying tactic.
Then what should we do now?
Are we really going to hand over the command token?
Do you think Sima Tu can mobilize Shuozhou's troops...
once he has the command token?
You can try...
to take the command token to the camp.
See if those soldiers...
will listen to you.
What do you mean?
Could it be that the soldiers of Shuozhou...
disobey the command token?
Forget the command token,
even the Emperor's seal...
won't be able to control...
the soldiers of Shuozhou.
The only thing that can make them obey willingly...
isn't an object.
Only Gongsun Heng can do that.
Elder Qin!
- Elder Qin.
- You have news?
Sima Tu sent people to open our vault.
They want to take all the money and everything valuable...
to reconcile with the Ashina Tribe army.
This won't do. We can't show weakness.
This way, we'd only be digging our own graves.
Governor Gongsun is locked up in prison now.
He can't command the army.
What should we do?
The worst-case scenario is we fight them head-on.
Let's just charge in.
Let's break into the prison to save Governor Gongsun.
You want to bring troops to charge into prison?
That would be exactly what Sima Tu wants.
Not only would you fail to save Governor Gongsun,
but you'd also be endangering Shuozhou.
Governor Gongsun hired you to be the chief registrar.
I hope he was not wrong about you.
I didn't expect Elder Qin to be quite smart.
Even if he walks shakily...
and seems unable to walk well,
he's quite clever.
Am I right, Master?
Master?
Master.
What are you thinking about?
I am thinking of a way to save Governor Gongsun.
Select thousands of elite soldiers...
and surround Chief Commander's Manor.
I'll personally go there.
- I'll surely...
- You're very annoying.
We just came to Shuozhou.
We don't know much about the situation here.
Even Elder Qin doesn't know what to do.
Gongsun Heng trusts me so much.
How can I not save him?
Aside from hijacking the prison wagon, what else can we do?
Can you kill Sima Tu?
Why are you looking at me?
- I know what to do now.
- Master, where are you going?
I'll go and meet Elder Qin.
I've been waiting for you for a long time.
You knew that I'd come?
You must have come up with a plan.
We don't have much time.
Tell me.
I do have an idea that requires mobilizing troops.
Tell me about it.
I need some reinforcement soldiers under Governor Gongsun's command.
When the time comes...
This plan is too risky.
If we make any mistakes, we'll lose beyond redemption.
But right now,
we have no other choice.
Governor Gongsun...
was right about you.
Before Governor Gongsun went to Chief Commander's Manor,
he knew that he might be trapped.
He ordered me to wait for the right time...
to give this to you.
(Listen to orders carefully.)
I definitely...
won't let Governor Gongsun down.
All right.
What do you want me to do? Tell me.
Elder Qin.
I would like...
very reliable assistant generals working for Governor Gongsun...
to meet me here.
All right.
But let me tell you something.
I'm not helping you.
I'm helping Governor Gongsun.
Master.
Didn't you want to talk to Elder Qin?
Why is he leaving?
We know what to do now.
What will you do?
Governor Gongsun left a note for me.
What note?
One's heart.
I finally understand what Shen Gu said back then means.
- I'm Guo Ning.
- I'm Zhang Hui.
- Greetings, Chief Registrar.
Greetings, generals. Please rise.
I think the two of you...
already know that Governor Gongsun is in trouble.
Sima Tu intends to open the prefecture vault to negotiate peace.
I asked the two of you to come here today...
to seek your help...
to resolve this matter together.
Just tell me what to do.
As long as we can stop them from opening the city wall...
and get Governor Gongsun back,
we'll surely do everything we can.
In that case, I won't be shy then.
How many light cavalrymen are there?
There are 6,000.
General Zhang Hui and I have 3,000 each.
Then get 1,000 troops...
under General Guo's command.
Split them up in half.
At midnight daily,
ambush Ashina's camp outside the city.
Once they retaliate,
retreat right away.
Don't lose any troops or horses.
Yes.
What about me? What should I do?
I need you to secretly mobilize a part of the troops...
to go outside the city.
Station in the mountains in the northwest and northeast...
to form a triangular formation with the city's troops.
We only have 30,000 troops in the city.
Guarding the city is already pushing it.
Why do you want to send troops out of the city?
If something unexpected happens on the day of the peace negotiation,
General Zhang Hui's troops...
can pretend to be reinforcements.
When that time comes, we can overwhelm them for a while.
I understand now.
Don't worry, Chief Registrar.
I'll surely make proper arrangements before we open the city's gate.
Thank you, generals.
(Broad-minded and knowledgeable)
Master, is a note really powerful enough...
to mobilize thousands of troops?
What mobilized the thousands of troops isn't the note,
but one's heart.
If something goes wrong with this plan,
I'm afraid that even Governor's Manor...
would be doomed.
Without a hitch, there was no egg.
This is the only drastic measure...
I can think of...
to address the situation.
By the way, Elder Qin,
can you help me find a hidden place?
Except for you and Xu Feng, no one can find out about it.
All right.
I'm willing to gamble on Governor Gongsun's judgment.
I hope he's right.
Follow me.
There's a secret room in the manor.
What is your name?
We only ran into each other by chance.
We won't meet again.
Do you think we'll become friends?
Aren't we friends now?
The grasslands?
I don't know anyone there.
I'd rather not.
You know me.
What's the matter?
Ashina Sun.
Since you came back from Tang,
you turned into a different person.
You're even smiling for no reason.
And you're smiling...
so creepily.
Are you hiding something from me?
It's nothing.
Ashina Sun.
Could it be that you've fallen...
for some lady in Tang?
Thank you, Heavenly Fox God.
Ashina Sun...
finally gets it now.
Don't you have anything better to do?
Don't talk to me about that.
Just tell me if I'm right or wrong.
You're right.
How boring.
Hurry! Put out the fire!
Water! Hurry! Help put out the fire!
Put out the fire!
What's going on?
- Your Highness.
- Didn't you say...
that Gongsun Heng was captured?
- I...
- Why are we being ambushed?
I...
Reporting!
Your Highness, the Tang army burned our provisions.
Did you save them?
Put out the fire if they're burning!
- Why are you reporting this to me?
- Yes.
What's the use of reporting it to me?
Go!
You better get the facts straight.
Otherwise, I'll kill you first,
then I'll massacre Shuozhou City!
Yes.
I'll go and meet Sima Tu now. I'm going now.
(Shuozhou)
What did you find out?
The Bear Army's provisions are burning.
They're trying to save them now.
On our side, only a few tents have been burned.
Everyone is fine.
Those who attacked us are like flies.
They're so annoying,
but we can't catch them.
It's funny though.
The Bear Army was the one that was hit badly each time...
but they're not being more cautious.
What are you thinking about?
Gongsun Heng had led the army for decades.
He only defends and doesn't attack.
This is really unusual.
It seems like...
there's another expert in Shuozhou City.
Expert?
This is the legendary passageway?
I can't believe that Governor's Manor has such a thing.
This should be a secret room left...
from the Sui Dynasty period.
Not bad.
Dou.
Remember everything that I'll be saying now.
Starting now,
you can't disclose...
everything you hear...
or see here.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Even if I don't quite understand it,
since you're someone destined for great things,
I'll do as you say.
Little Chief.
What happened? Are there any casualties?
Not a single soldier was injured.
According to the plan, we ambushed them after lights out, then ran.
These repeated ambushes...
caused them great turmoil and made them unable to sleep.
At this rate,
we'll annoy the hell out of them.
We've achieved our objective.
We need a new approach.
What is it?
It's just that this approach...
will be hard on you, Xu Feng.
Chief.
Didn't I tell you not to come?
Why are you...
Tu Ka She sent me here to ask you something.
What exactly are you planning to do?
If you've changed your mind,
and you won't open the city and surrender anymore,
I can tell His Highness.
Then please bear...
the consequences yourself.
We're still making an inventory of the Shuozhou vault.
Within two days, we'll provide the Declaration of Surrender.
Why would His Highness say that?
Our camp is being ambushed...
by Shuozhou's garrison each night.
The entire camp can't sleep peacefully...
and are in a terrible fix.
Is this the sincerity...
of your peace negotiation?
How did that happen?
You're in charge of the four prefecture's troops.
Gongsun Heng is in your hands now.
If you say that you don't know anything about it,
why would I believe you?
Gongsun Heng is in my prison.
He can't escape.
It's definitely...
It's definitely impossible for him to instruct them.
My brother.
A few days ago,
I heard that Gongsun Heng's command token...
was stolen.
Now, it seems like the thief...
is the one pulling tricks secretly.
In the past few days,
my men have been guarding...
those in Governor's Manor very closely.
The whole family is there.
I'll send Wang Li now...
to perform a city-wide search.
Even if they have to dig three feet under the ground,
we'll find him.
In that case,
I have one more favor to ask of you.
I already know where that thief is.
It seems like someone has been watching...
Chief Commander's Manor all along.
Didn't you notice, my brother?
Did Gongsun Heng ask you to do this?
I knew that Gongsun Heng...
has always had evil intentions.
He's up to no good.
Come.
Take him away.
Sima Tu.
Leave him to me.
I'll make sure...
that he'll be in utter misery.
To the torture chamber.
All right.
You can't die.
But if you want to live,
it's not that easy.
You...
You traitor.
You won't tell me then.
Are you sure...
that you'll only bring that many people for tomorrow?
The eastern side of Shuozhou's mountains is dangerously steep...
and it's full of swamps.
No ambush has ever occurred there.
Because of this geographical advantage,
Gongsun Heng never guarded it much.
Those people...
are enough.
The scout reported earlier...
that the Eagle Army's Central Plains military strategist...
went to Shuozhou again tonight.
I'm afraid...
that tomorrow's acceptance of surrender is fake,
and they'd attack the city instead.
If that's what Tu Ka She is planning,
he could work well with us.
But Chief Registrar Li in Shuozhou...
will surely not just sit and await doom.
I don't know if Tu Ka She...
can handle him.
Chief Registrar Li?
I've already checked.
He's the new chief registrar in Shuozhou.
He came from another province.
He has only been in the position for a short time.
Xu Feng.
I'm incompetent.
You were exposed?
They noticed me.
I fought with them for so long before I was finally able to escape.
I circled around for many hours.
I'm sure no one followed me.
Forget it.
Go and treat your wounds.
Don't show yourself for a while.
I'll tell you!
That's right.
I know where Chief Registrar Li is.
I can take you to him.
I know...
where they're hiding.
I won't run away.
All right.
If you capture Chief Registrar Li,
I'll reward you greatly.
If you run away,
you should know the consequences.
This is Chief Registrar Li?
That's right.
A wise man submits to the circumstances.
Kill him.
I didn't expect you...
to be so ruthless.
Good.
I like it.
Bury him.
Congratulations, Yi Bu Khan.
I've already ordered someone to kill that chief registrar.
It's my emeritus certificate. It's all ready.
The entire Shuozhou is ours.
Do you need these?
I'll decide for His Highness.
You can have these.
Thank you, Minister.
Thank you to His Highness.
Come on.
The military strategist said...
that they already had killed Chief Registrar Li.
The gift list in the Declaration of Surrender...
is prepared as well.
What's the actual name of Chief Registrar Li?
I'm not sure what his actual name is.
Isn't Shi Si Lang's surname Li too?
In this world, there are so many people with the same last names.
I don't think it's Shi Si Lang.
Command a team to follow Tu Ka She tomorrow.
Don't let him die directly.
Yes.
(Shuozhou)
Army Chief Sima Tu...
opens the city and offers the Declaration of Surrender...
on behalf of Governor Gongsun Heng.
We hope that the Ashina Tribe's prince...
can spare the lives of our citizens...
based on your merciful nature.
The citizens...
thank you for your kindness.
Bring it forward.
These are the offerings of money, valuables, and provisions...
for your army.
Please take a look.
All right.
How can this happen?
I can't believe he didn't die.
Will you surrender or not?
What does this mean?
Did you set me up?
Let me explain.
You don't know what's good for you.
No!
If you move,
I'll kill you.
This is bad.
There's a coup d'état in the city.
Warriors!
The Tang army wronged us first. You can't blame us!
Come on.
Attack!
- Kill!
Kill!
Release the arrows!
Signal using the flag.
Send 5,000 troops...
to make them retreat to the riverbank.
Your Highness.
Gongsun Heng's Chief Registrar is commanding the battle.
They've set up an ambush.
We don't have enough people.
Why don't we retreat to the riverbank first...
and assemble with the army?
Didn't you say that Gongsun Heng has been captured...
and his military strategist is dead?
I...
Cease the attack!
Retreat!
If you don't know the strategic plans of other states,
you can't get their recognition and be their friend.
If you're not familiar with the dangers of the forest...
and its terrain,
you can't march your troops properly.
Next,
it's up to you, General Guo.
Yes.
Army Chief died in battle.
The army can't be without a general.
The highest official...
in Shuozhou should replace him.
Yes.
I'll go get Master.
Sima Jian was right.
The shallow water in July is perfect for us to march on.
My brothers, stay close.
When we get into Shuozhou City,
that place is ours!
You can do whatever you want!
- Charge!
- Go!
Stop.
Minister, help! The Tang army set up an ambush.
They're pursuing us!
Your Highness.
Remind me.
Take Shuozhou City...
leave Chief Registrar Li to me.
I'll kill him with my own hands!
Your Highness.
They stopped attacking.
Why did you stop chasing us?
Come here!
- Come here!
- Come on!
Retreat!
Retreat quickly!
(Prefectural Governor's Manor)
This is all thanks to Chief Registrar Li.
If it weren't for him,
I'm afraid that Shuozhou would be in danger.
Chief Registrar Li is a clever man.
He used the Bear Army to kill Sima Tu.
But I have a question.
How did you know...
that the Bear Army will attack the city?
Sima Tu is a coward.
This time, in negotiating peace with the Ashina Tribe,
he was opening the door to a dangerous foe...
and asking someone to act against his own interests.
Ashina Tribe doesn't only want...
to plunder resources.
They want to use this peace negotiation...
to attack the city...
to fulfill their ambition.
I just went with the flow...
and used them to kill him.
I see.
Xu Feng deserves a lot of credit...
for our success this time too.
If Xu Feng didn't work with me...
to put on an act,
I'm afraid that we couldn't have fooled Sima Tu so easily.
It's just a bit of physical torture.
Even if it means risking my life for Master,
I would do it.
We've been following Master for so many years.
We should be loyal.
Yet you just came to Shuozhou for a short time,
and you've disregarded your own safety.
I really admire you.
However, I still have one question.
If I stab you a little deeper,
I'm afraid it will go through the blood pack and into your heart.
Why do you trust me so much?
I trust...
your loyalty to Governor Gongsun.
Well said.
I'm so lucky...
to have loyal people like you guys...
around me.
Commandant Li, I must thank you too.
Elder Qin, what did you call me?
Commandant of Light Chariots, Li Shi Si.
You filled up the dam upstream,
then released it to flood the enemy.
Commandant Li.
Your plan was great.
Shuozhou City was safe...
from being handed over...
because of your great contribution.
Please accept...
my bow on behalf of the people in the city.
Governor Gongsun.
Governor Gongsun, I can't accept this.
I still let you down.
They were able to save Tu Ka She.
Come on, rise.
Rise, all of you.
This time, I think the Bear Army was fully dispatched.
But I don't know if...
You're afraid that the Eagle Army will come too?
Eagle Army?
The Eagle Army is Ashina Tribe's strongest military force.
They're not as incompetent as Tu Ka She's men.
If the enemy...
still has enough strength to attack,
and the river is flooded so they can't cross it.
The southeastern side is filled with mountains.
Besides, swamps are everywhere outside the east gate.
Even the citizens of Shuozhou go around them.
In that case,
the garrison outside the east gate...
should be transferred west of the city.
All right.
Listen carefully, everyone.
Let's do as Commandant Li said.
- Yes.
Your Highness.
The Tang army is very cunning.
They set a trap...
and even used you to kill my brother.
Because of this,
Gongsun Heng's Chief Register and I...
are absolutely irreconcilable!
What's the matter?
Do you feel bad that I killed Sima Tu?
No.
My brother was ineffective.
As the army chief,
he couldn't even control a governor.
He deserved to die.
I'm loyal to you.
Heaven and earth can attest to that.
Even though Sima Tu is dead,
I can still provide...
Shuozhou's information to you.
Please give me...
one more chance.
Remember.
I can take your life anytime.
Yes.
I will never...
let Chief Registrar Li get away again.
Reporting!
Your Highness. Earlier, Ashina Sun gathered...
the Eagle Army and left all of a sudden.
I don't know where he went.
Come.
Everyone.
Today,
let me tell you a story.
I saw it with my own eyes back then.
Chief Registrar Li...
did a somersault...
and shot that heavy arrow...
weighing 100kg.
He accurately avoided our warriors.
Without veering...
to the left or right,
he hit that peace agreement...
held by that man from the Ashina Tribe.
- Great!
- Amazing!
You can't call him Chief Registrar Li anymore.
Governor Gongsun has already posted an announcement.
He has already been promoted...
- to Commandant of Light Chariots.
- Yes.
- You're right.
Commandant Li is so young and capable.
He became Governor Gongsun's assistant.
- Shuozhou is so fortunate.
- Yes.
(Prefectural Governor's Manor)
I didn't expect that in just a few days,
you can already share my husband's burdens...
and defeat the enemy.
I'm so lucky.
Using tea instead of wine, I'll make a toast to you.
You're exaggerating, Madam.
I'm the lucky one...
because I'm able to be stationed in Shuozhou...
with Governor Gongsun.
Look at how skinny you are.
The north is cold. You need to dress warmly.
Later, I'll look for suitable fabrics...
and make more clothes for you.
Madam, you're so good to me.
I'm very touched.
That's a token of my wife's gratitude.
I think you should stop being so shy.
If you don't mind,
this will be your home from now on.
Thank you, Governor Gongsun.
Thank you, Madam.
Ever since...
my mother passed away,
this is the first time that I've felt such kindness.
Madam, I want one too.
Fine, I'll make them for you both.
Make him more clothes.
Let's eat.
- The food's getting cold.
- Yes.
Governor Gongsun!
The food storage is on fire.
It's already reduced to ashes.
What?
It's the Eagle Army.
Any casualties?
The fire is spreading fast.
Imperial Guard Xu already led us in putting out the fire.
The citizens nearby weren't affected.
Xu Feng did well.
- You may go.
- Yes.
Governor Gongsun.
Is the Eagle Army...
the elite force you've been worried about before?
They're finally here.
I just didn't expect them to come so soon.
Master.
In the swamp by the east gate,
we found these Paulownia wooden boards.
The Eagle Army's cavalry is very fast.
Together with the Paulownia tree's buoyancy,
I'm afraid that they've already crossed the marsh.
Governor Gongsun.
This is all because of my negligence.
Because of our geographical advantage,
I moved the men from the east to the west.
I'm willing to redeem myself.
Please send me to the east to face the enemy.
That's enough.
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)