Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 8)
A decree's authenticity...
can be verified right away.
Chang'an uses top-quality ink cake.
The low-quality ink cake you used...
bled once met with water.
Also, the silk you used...
is of inferior quality.
Don't talk.
What's going on?
Don't worry.
As long as you don't show up,
your master won't be in danger.
All this proves...
This proves the item is in Youzhou.
It's in your hands.
Arrest her.
- Yes.
Take her away.
Search the place.
Yesterday, my master even told me...
Li Yuan is the only person she can trust now.
I can't believe he's actually a scoundrel.
No, I must save my master.
If you go out now,
it will only make your master die faster.
Your master's life depends on the thing you have on you.
Make sure you hide it well.
I'm sure your master can definitely escape.
Don't you believe so?
I do.
- My master has nine lives.
- Good.
Then do as I say.
Go to the city gate right now and wait for your master there.
What about you?
Will you save my master?
Just worry about yourself.
Go.
Mr. Peddler.
I believe you.
There's nothing.
Let me ask you.
Where is it?
Don't assume I won't dare to strangle you to death...
just because you're Princess Yongning.
So she's Li Jian Cheng's daughter, Princess Yongning.
No wonder she could steal the Crown Prince's seal.
Shi Si Lang wants to take revenge on Li Shi Min.
Jun Kuo.
If you kill her,
who will know where the item is?
Take her back for now.
(Peace and harmony)
Keep watch on this place.
If anyone comes, seize them all.
Yes.
(Governor's Manor)
Is Your Highness still unwilling to reveal where it is?
Your Highness's face is considered a pretty one.
But it may no longer be intact later.
I advise Your Highness to just obey and tell us.
I don't want you to suffer in vain.
I've already witnessed how great your acting skills are.
If I tell you now,
I'll just die even faster.
Your Highness is indeed a true princess.
You'd rather die...
than hand over that object.
But since you don't care about your own life,
I wonder if you care about other people's lives then?
I'm afraid that envoy, Mr. Wei,
won't live past today.
Kill him if you want.
He has nothing to do with me.
"Nothing"?
I saw how Your Highness...
protected Mr. Wei with my own eyes.
How about this?
I'll send someone to bring him here.
You and your old friend can have a nice reunion.
Maybe you'll recall something then.
- Yes.
It looks like Your Highness is really determined...
to cut ties with your old friend from Chang'an.
All right.
I'll kill him now then.
If you kill him,
you'll never get the thing you want.
I knew it.
It seems Your Highness is still reluctant to see him die.
Then I'll give you more time.
Look at him and recall your memories.
If you still don't recall anything,
both he and you...
will have to die.
Wei Shu Yu.
If I work with Wang Jun Kuo,
Youzhou will fall in the Ashina Tribe's hands.
But maybe I can use the forces of these rebels...
to attack Chang'an.
What are you thinking, Li Chang Ge?
It's the Ashina Tribe you're talking about.
If you help Wang Jun Kuo because of this,
you'll be the greatest sinner of the Tang Dynasty.
Come in.
Your Highness.
Are we departing today?
Yes.
Wei Shu Yu's work is almost done.
We are meeting up with him today.
I'll take you to the east gate of the city later...
to meet Wei Shu Yu.
Are you not leaving?
I'm not leaving.
Hao Du.
If you run into Chang Ge,
can you spare her life?
Hao Du.
It's getting late.
Please hurry and pack your things, Your Highness.
Why are you locked up here too?
I know.
You're still mad at me.
Why are you in Youzhou?
Was sending me off a cliff not enough?
You won't give it a rest until you personally see me die.
Chang Ge.
I...
Stop talking.
Get some rest.
Whether you believe me or not,
I never betrayed you.
Hao Du set me up that day...
to mess with your emotions.
So what even if that's true?
You still chose to succumb to him.
I'm sorry.
I don't want you...
to be locked up in prison because of me.
You're thinking too much.
I'm here because I tried to get blood from a stone...
but hurt myself instead.
What?
Wang Jun Kuo...
Wang Jun Kuo wants to hand Youzhou over...
to Yan Li Khan.
That jerk is too ambitious.
He's a traitor.
Is Prince of Lujiang not going to do anything about this?
Prince of Lujiang is the mastermind.
What?
What are you going to do?
What should I do?
Isn't this the ending...
you and your new master want to see?
Chang Ge.
His Highness has always doted on you.
- He never thought of...
- Stop it.
Even if I shatter to pieces,
I won't succumb to Li Shi Min as you did.
Did you come to Youzhou alone?
No.
Hao Du and I are to meet at the city's east gate...
at 3:45pm today.
But trust me.
I won't tell him I saw you.
Do you think you'll still get out alive to see Hao Du?
If you want to make it out alive,
you'll need his help.
Guards! I want to see Li Yuan!
- Guards!
- Chang Ge, what are you doing?
It's none of your business.
Guards!
You're not going to hand over the Crown Prince's seal, are you?
What else should I do?
Give it to you?
What's the problem with your chefs here?
There's not a single dish that's edible.
I advise you not to overdo it.
There's a limit to the governor's patience.
I'm a princess.
Show some respect.
Thanks to you,
I can't even eat anything now.
I don't have an appetite.
You want to die, don't you?
Uncle Li Yuan.
Is this how you teach your men?
Yongning.
There's no use stalling us like this.
You're right.
My subordinate and I agreed to meet at a set time.
Even if I go early,
I won't see him.
If I don't get there safe and sound,
he'll carry out the orders I gave him in advance.
When that happens,
no one can get their hands on the Crown Prince's seal.
I have to hand it to you, Yongning.
I underestimated you.
But we're a family.
There's no need for us to fight.
I'm glad you think that way, Uncle Li Yuan.
It's getting late.
- We can go now.
- All right.
I look forward to hearing good news from you.
Uncle Li Yuan.
Wei Shu Yu is one of my people.
Even if he dies, he has to die by my hand.
If anything happens to him,
I won't hold back.
Please.
Princess Yongning managed to safely escape from Chang'an.
Someone like that wouldn't fall into the hands of Wang Jun Kuo.
What benefits did the Ashina Tribe give you?
Instead of earning merit of punishing the rebels,
you'd rather serve as Yan Li's slave.
Your Highness.
Do you really think...
people will risk their lives for you...
based on a few baseless words?
Besides, what you said about punishing the rebels...
is all utter nonsense.
Only that Crown Prince's seal you have is valuable.
Perhaps you could earn a good amount out of it.
If news gets out...
that you've defected to the Ashina Tribe,
aren't you afraid the morale in the Youzhou's army will falter?
Then, the surrounding provinces will attack together.
You'll all be doomed.
Your Highness doesn't have to worry about that.
You should worry about yourself.
Hao Du.
Don't disappoint me.
Why is Shu Yu...
Chang...
Don't shout.
If you call her, she's dead.
Look at that guy.
Li Chang Ge is being watched.
Who are they?
I don't know.
But since Li Chang Ge is here,
something bad must have happened to Wei Shu Yu.
Shu Yu.
If you don't want anything to happen to Wei Shu Yu,
stay here.
Stay still.
It's an ambush.
Move.
Your Highness, do you still want to run?
Who are you?
I advise you to hand the item over.
Or else, I'll behead your master.
Go ahead.
But...
you have to give me her head.
I need to take it back to report the completion of my task.
You're not one of her people.
Who exactly are you?
Who are you to ask me all these questions?
Wei Shu Yu is in trouble.
I figured.
Hao Du.
Chang Ge?
Chang Ge.
Let her go.
You first.
A life for a life.
That's fair.
Le Yan.
Why are you here?
Chang Ge, I...
What are you waiting for?
The one in my hands is a Tang princess.
Then do you know who I have in my hands?
I don't care who she is.
Let her go.
I'll count to three.
If you don't let her go,
this woman is dead.
Qin Zhun.
Don't do anything reckless.
Hao Du.
Don't hurt Chang Ge.
Let her go.
Hao Du.
One.
If we don't leave now, Wang Jun Kuo will bring his men.
None of us will be able to leave then.
Two.
Who are you?
Three.
- Chang Ge.
- Let's go.
Chang Ge, hurry and go.
- Chang Ge!
- Your Highness.
Your Highness.
- Chang Ge, hurry and leave!
- I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Didn't you already leave long ago?
I...
I came back to take care of something.
Take care of something?
Do you want your horse back from Wang Jun Kuo...
or are you helping Wang Jun Kuo collude with the Ashina Tribe...
as their middleman?
Qin Zhun.
Don't force me to become your enemy.
I was just trying to save you.
Thank you for saving me.
I won't ask about the past anymore.
But from now on,
stay out of my business and leave Youzhou.
I think I should be the one to say that.
Those people won't let you off.
If you go back now, you're going to die.
Come with me.
I don't need you to tell me what to do.
I definitely won't let Youzhou fall into the Ashina Tribe's hands.
If you keep following me,
I'll report you.
The imperial court is trying to kill you.
Why are you still working for them?
I just hate the people who destroyed my family.
But I'm still a citizen of Tang.
Didn't you always want it?
Take it for self-defense.
Let go. You're hurting me.
Hao Du, let go of me.
Let go.
Didn't you hear Chang Ge say...
that Shu Yu is in trouble just now?
I only care about where Li Chang Ge is.
But...
- Shu Yu...
- I'll say it again.
I only care about Li Chang Ge.
I'm here.
Chang Ge.
Chang Ge, why did you come back?
If you move again, I'll kill her right now.
Li Chang Ge.
Are you not running anymore?
If you don't listen to me,
none of us are going anywhere.
Listen to you?
Do you still think you're a princess?
Li Yuan and Wang Jun Kuo...
colluded with the Ashina Tribe's Young Khan.
They're planning to give Youzhou to the Ashina Tribe.
A vicious army is currently coming to Youzhou.
Do you think we can still run?
Don't doubt it.
Wei Shu Yu...
is locked up in the dungeon of the governor's manor now.
If it weren't for the sake of Youzhou,
I wouldn't be standing in front of you right now.
Hao Du.
Let's go and save Shu Yu...
Why should I trust you?
Based on the fact that I'm the one standing here now,
not Wei Shu Yu.
Wei Shu Yu has the entire Wei family behind him.
Do you think he would risk his whole family's life...
to put on an act with me?
There's no need to look around.
I'm alone.
Why are you unscathed?
Because the Crown Prince's seal is in my hands.
Hand it over.
Youzhou is about to fall into the enemy's hands,
yet you're still concerned about that?
Youzhou has nothing to do with me.
My priority...
is to bring you and the Crown Prince's seal back.
Nothing to do with you?
How could a general of the court say that the fall of Youzhou...
has nothing to do with him?
If Du Ru Hui were to hear...
how you have no regard for the bigger picture,
he'd kill you.
Don't talk about my godfather.
Why is a thief who stole the Crown Prince's seal...
talking to me about the bigger picture?
Li Chang Ge.
Even if what you said is true,
I won't let you run away again.
You're ignoring urgent priorities.
You only care about your personal gain.
How will you accomplish great things with such a mindset?
Regardless of what I accomplish, I don't need you to teach me.
Bringing back the Crown Prince's seal is the most important thing.
If Wang Jun Kuo gets his way,
it'll be too late even if we ask the court to send an army in.
Li Chang Ge.
I don't care whether this is all true or not.
My priority right now...
is to safely get the princess out of Youzhou.
If you still think of the princess as your friend,
then cooperate.
Useless!
There are so many of you,
yet you lost her.
I'm sorry.
I've ordered people to search the city for Li Chang Ge.
I've also given orders to close off the city gates.
I don't care what method you use.
I must get it by tomorrow.
Otherwise, when we face Young Khan,
you and I will be in big trouble.
Governor.
I have something else to report.
I've discovered that there's another group...
tracking down Li Chang Ge as well.
That man is skilled in martial arts. He's even better than me.
He's definitely not a martial artist.
Could he be from the imperial court?
Then our plans...
Governor, you don't have to worry.
That person doesn't care...
whether Li Chang Ge is dead or alive at all.
He just wants to capture her.
So I suspect that person...
may also be after the Crown Prince's seal.
At this point,
there's no turning back.
I want both Li Chang Ge and the people...
- from the imperial court.
- I got it.
As long as she's alive,
she won't be able to leave Youzhou City.
Has Young Khan made any moves?
Yan Li Khan's army is heading south soon.
All we have to do is prevent any news of Youzhou City...
or other places from getting out.
Once Young Khan's big army arrives,
we won't have to worry about anything.
Both our glory...
depends on this.
Yes, Governor.
Hurry! Close the gate!
No one may enter or leave.
Close the gate? Why the rush?
This is General Wang's order. Hurry and follow through.
If the criminal escapes, it's on you.
Yes.
(Youzhou)
Chang Ge.
I've always liked to lean on your shoulder...
ever since we were young.
I feel reassured whenever you're around.
I don't care if you're anxious.
I don't know...
how long it'll be until the next time...
I can lean on your shoulder.
Untie me.
My hands hurt.
Li Chang Ge.
You're underestimating me.
(Rest stop)
Is capturing Chang Ge really that important?
Is it more important than our lives,
the entire Youzhou City,
and the lives of the civilians?
Youzhou has been sealed off.
I can't save the people of Youzhou.
I can't save Wei Shu Yu either.
So you're just going to watch Shu Yu die?
We'll send a smoke signal outside the city...
and inform the court.
This is the only way.
You mean...
Shu Yu can be saved?
We can only leave it up to fate.
It's you?
Hurry in.
Why are you here?
The peddler told me to wait for you at the city gate.
I stayed there the whole time.
I didn't even blink.
Then,
I saw soldiers sealing the gates.
Only one carriage left the city at the last minute.
I guessed that would probably be the last chance...
for you to escape.
So I followed the carriage.
That peddler was indeed right.
What did he say?
He said he believes that you'll definitely escape.
- Where is it?
- It's here.
It's here with me.
By the way, Master,
who kidnapped you?
They're from Chang'an.
They've even made it all the way to Youzhou?
The situation is very urgent now.
I'm going to need reinforcements.
Dou, wait for me here.
Master.
Don't leave me again.
What I'm facing now is a major army from Youzhou.
If I don't go over there now...
and Wang Jun Kuo gets his way,
there really won't be any way to escape then.
Then why are you still going?
Because I don't have any choice.
Besides,
I don't believe the Youzhou army...
will become stooges like Wang Jun Kuo.
Master.
Don't leave me again.
Fighting on the battlefield is my dream.
I want to see a real army.
I won't let you go on your own no matter what you say this time.
All right.
I'll take you.
I'll let you see...
what a real army looks like.
All right.
Before I go, I need to meet someone.
Wait for me outside.
Chang Ge.
Tell Hao Du to take you back to Chang'an.
It's not safe to stay here.
Chang Ge.
I can't go back to Chang'an.
Grandfather wants to marry me off to the prairies...
and intermarry with the Ashina Tribe.
What?
But my father said I'm very sick...
and told me to recuperate in Luoyang.
Listen to your father.
Be good and stay in Luoyang.
Chang Ge.
But I don't want to go anywhere.
I really want things to go back to the way they were.
That can't happen.
Then...
Then can we still see each other again?
It's best that we don't.
Chang Ge.
Hao Du said that...
sending a smoke signal is our only chance.
Do you think Shu Yu can be saved?
I'll definitely save him.
Don't worry.
Youngsters these days are always in such a scurry.
By the way, Youzhou has been sealed off.
They have given orders not to let anyone in or out.
It's getting late.
There's a rest stop up ahead.
We can take a break there.
Just go with the flow.
Life is full of surprises.
Isn't that right?
Su Su.
Let's go.
Stop right there.
What are you doing?
Here's my seal.
I'm an envoy from Chang'an, Wei Shu Yu.
Let him in.
(Share weal and woe)
You're saying Governor Li and General Wang...
have defected to the enemy?
What proof do you have?
The envoys and subordinates that came with me...
are all locked up in the dungeon of the governor's manor.
If you and your soldiers come along with me,
you'll see for yourself.
Soldiers from outside the city...
are not allowed to enter without a military order.
If you don't have any other evidence,
I'm afraid I cannot comply.
But the city is being controlled by Wang Jun Kuo's followers.
As soon as the Ashina Tribe's army arrives,
Li Yuan will hand Youzhou over to them.
The north of Tang will be defenseless.
Everything I'm saying is true.
Please dispatch your troops.
What if I refuse?
Then...
please forgive me for being rude.
You're not an envoy from Chang'an.
Speak.
Who are you?
Captain.
There's a smoke signal.
Smoke signal?
It's a smoke signal.
Captain, please send out your troops immediately.
Convey my orders.
- Assemble the entire army.
- Yes.
Your Highness.
How is it?
The word got out.
The Tang soldiers are on alert now.
We have to leave now.
Wang Jun Kuo, that piece of trash.
Has the Youzhou vault been emptied out?
Good thing Your Highness had taken precautions.
The maps, family registries, silk, and money in the vault...
have all been transported out.
The carriage is hiding in the woods outside the city.
Good.
We didn't come here for nothing.
Let's leave the city with Wang Jun Kuo's command token.
Yes.
Stop.
Let's hide. We need to avoid them first.
Ashina Sun.
Don't go, Young Khan.
They have a lot of soldiers with them.
If you expose yourself now, it'll be hard to escape.
Your Highness, you're someone of special status.
We can't let anything go wrong.
Let's go.
Come on.
It seems like someone is hiding over there.
- Go and take a look.
- Yes.
This is from the Youzhou vault.
It seems like there must be trouble in the city.
Convey my orders. We must speed up.
We must get to Youzhou City before dawn.
- Yes.
(Gumeng Inn)
Don't even think about calling for help.
Why don't you try it?
Let's see if you can shout faster than my blade moves.
She's still a kid.
Don't scare her.
Su Su.
Don't be afraid. It's all right.
Why hasn't anyone come back yet?
Can Chang Ge really save Shu Yu?
Su Su.
Let me find you a friend.
Would you like that?
Shu Yu.
Sir, are you all right?
Water.
- Water?
- Water.
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)