Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 7)
I didn't come here to seek protection.
I'm here to help you.
You mean...
Li Shi Min is currently surrounded by enemies.
He'll definitely split up the troops...
and station them everywhere to be sure.
Youzhou's army...
can also split up into two groups...
and take them by surprise...
in the south of Linpu Town and Jiangzhou,
then go west into Tongguan County.
When the time comes, the two armies can collaborate.
In a short time, we will win.
You mean...
You're extraordinary indeed.
There are indeed no cowards in the Li family.
Your Highness.
You came from the capital.
Do you know His Majesty's condition?
And what were Crown Prince's instructions?
That's the reason why I came here.
Before my father died, he gave me a decree.
Li Yuan, Prince of Lujiang, receive your orders.
This is the decree.
"Prince of Qin, Li Shi Min..."
"has committed treason and rose up in rebellion,"
"terrorizing the capital and endangering the nation."
"Youzhou's governor, Prince of Lujiang, Li Yuan,"
"must lead troops, go to the capital,"
"and kill the traitor..."
"to help the nation and make things right."
"Carry out this decree upon receipt."
I, Li Yuan, shall obey the decree.
This decree has resolved Youzhou's emergency indeed.
In rushing to prepare supplies for the troops,
we were afraid that after mobilizing them,
we couldn't sustain them.
With this decree,
Crown Prince's former subordinates will surely help out.
Governor, Chang'an's envoy has arrived.
He's waiting in the front hall.
Li Shi Min's envoy arrived so quickly.
Uncle Li Yuan, in my opinion,
it's better not to meet the envoy.
Your Highness, don't worry.
We've already come up with a plan,
and we have the decree.
We surely won't fail Crown Prince's orders.
Since the traitor's envoy came here himself,
why don't we take this opportunity to capture him...
and show our desire to fight him?
(In good times and in bad)
By Crown Prince Jian Cheng's decree,
capture the traitor.
Wang Jun Kuo, you're passing on a fake decree.
How should you be punished?
Kill him on the spot. Kill him!
Wait.
Wei Shu Yu.
Chang Ge.
Why are you here?
Are you not even embarrassed to ask me that?
Let me explain.
What can you explain?
If you surrender now,
I can let you live.
Chang Ge, you're crazy.
Do you know what you're doing?
You're aiding and abetting a rebellion.
That's because I'm not as lucky as you...
who has a choice...
and can follow another master.
Right now,
I'm a slice meat on the chopping block.
Do you expect me...
to just watch Youzhou experience what happened in the East Palace?
Chang Ge, listen to me.
Crown Prince is kind.
He sent me to Youzhou this time...
to let Prince of Lujiang feel at ease.
We have a misunderstanding.
A misunderstanding?
Cut the crap.
- Capture him.
- Yes!
Put down your sword.
I'll say it again.
Put down your sword and you'll be spared.
Your Highness.
What we discussed today...
requires human sacrifice.
General Wang.
Do you know Crown Prince's assistant, Wei Zheng?
Wei Zheng is a great assistant of East Palace.
He is the son of Wei Zheng.
If we kill him,
I'm afraid that the East Palace officials would feel disappointed.
I've long heard that Assistant Wei...
is very loyal to Crown Prince.
I can't believe that his son is such a coward.
You traitor.
Who are you to talk about my father?
You...
Envoy, you're mistaken in believing Prince of Qin.
Heaven and earth can attest to my loyalty to Tang.
Crown Prince Jian Cheng left a decree before he died.
We're just obeying his decree to kill the traitor.
- Chang Ge.
- Guards.
Take him into the dungeon and keep a close eye on him.
Chang Ge, you...
Come on.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Yongning.
The envoy may have been captured,
but after a while,
those in Chang'an can't help but be suspicious.
Besides, if news of you being in Youzhou leaks out,
it'll be very unfavorable to our future plans.
In my opinion,
why don't you stay at my place and recuperate for a few days?
There's no need, Uncle Li Yuan.
I have a place to stay.
I'll see you first thing tomorrow morning.
You're new to Youzhou.
You're not familiar with the place.
Moreover,
if Youzhou's spies follow you,
it'll be very troublesome.
Here's what we'll do.
I'll send a team to protect you secretly, all right?
Uncle Li Yuan.
Since I can come here all the way from Chang'an,
I can take care of myself.
I'll get going.
Jun Kuo.
I saw Chang'an's envoy go inside.
I can't believe that Shi Si Lang wasn't captured.
She's wounded.
It's a bit fishy for her to be wounded now.
Come on.
Over there.
Why are the staff from governor's manor following Shi Si Lang?
This is getting more interesting.
Shi Si Lang.
Who exactly are you?
(Crown Prince's seal)
Governor.
Is there a problem...
with this decree?
(Crown Prince's seal)
You two, go out of the city now.
Go to the thatched hut outside the city and put on a white cloth.
Remember.
Don't let anyone find out.
Wait for the important guest from the north to contact you.
- Yes.
Master, you're back.
Master, why are you wounded?
Master.
Why are you wounded so badly?
I'm fine.
Dou.
I was being followed just now.
Master, who was following you?
I don't know.
I think it's my uncle's men.
But I can't do things according to my instincts now.
Because the only one I can count on now...
is my uncle.
Master, you have me.
She knows military strategy.
She's good at coming up with a plan.
If I don't need to fill out my name, I won't come out.
How about this?
Caravans have a lot of carriages and goods.
They won't search everything.
Just give me a place to hide.
She's not afraid of dying.
I can't believe such an amazing woman exists in this world.
Wei Shu Yu.
You're indeed the princess's good friend.
You guessed that she'd pass by this place so easily.
Who is it?
What is it?
Did you cry?
No.
Men can cry too.
Don't be embarrassed.
I was never a crybaby since I was little.
I bleed, but I don't cry.
Stop acting tough.
Everyone gets upset.
If there's nothing else,
I'm going back to sleep.
I'm feeling down.
I wonder if you...
can take a walk with me.
Now?
There's a curfew.
That's strange.
So someone like you...
is afraid of curfews.
Where are we going?
What's the matter?
Are you afraid that I'll sell you off?
I'm afraid you don't have that capability.
Why did you bring me there?
This place is far from worrisome things...
and closer to the moon.
Instead of getting close to the moon,
I think I'm closer to a troublesome man like you.
Is that a bad thing?
It's getting colder.
What's the matter?
Do you want me to give you my robe?
Do you feel better?
I feel much better.
So...
what exactly happened?
Let me think.
If it makes a man like you so sad,
it must be because...
your marriage proposal got turned down...
and the girl you love ran off with someone.
What a bunch of nonsense.
I just met an old friend.
No.
We're not friends anymore.
A friend?
What kind of friend?
Why aren't you friends anymore?
We grew up together.
We studied and practiced martial arts together.
I thought that we'd be the same our whole lives.
But later on...
Later on,
perhaps you'll reconcile.
That's impossible.
In the future,
I don't think I'll have a friend like that again.
That's natural.
"Natural"?
Someone told me that...
some people are soft like water.
They tolerate everything.
And some people are like fire.
They'll only burn more and more.
Those who go near him will get burned.
If we force ourselves to be with them,
we'll only turn into ashes.
Who told you that?
Your friend?
My...
My foster father.
After he told me that,
my best friend and I parted ways...
and became enemies.
I'm probably the fire type of person too.
Do you think we'll become friends?
Aren't we friends now?
Qin Zhun.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
You brought me here in the middle of the night.
You even tried to advise me.
I should thank you indeed.
Shi Si Lang.
You can't stay in Youzhou for long.
Leave as soon as possible.
Why are you suddenly saying that?
Did you hear any news?
There's some movement in Youzhou's army.
Chang'an wasn't peaceful before either.
There are a lot of checkpoints here.
I'm afraid we'll get dragged by the disturbance here.
Qin Zhun.
You don't believe that I can protect myself?
I...
You should mind your own business.
Since you know that it's dangerous in Youzhou now,
after you're done with your business,
leave this place.
All right.
You should go.
It's almost dawn.
I miss my father.
When can we go back to Chang'an?
Please rest, Your Highness.
- I'll get going.
- Don't go.
I don't want to rest.
Just...
stay here.
Hey.
Why are you so quiet?
Your Highness told me to stay,
so I'm staying put here.
You look so serious.
It's quite funny.
It's getting late. We're alone here.
It's really inconvenient for me to stay here.
- I'll get going.
- Don't go.
Are you not following my orders anymore?
Look.
I embroidered this bunny.
Other bunny embroideries...
have red eyes.
Mine has green eyes.
Because the grass is all a bunny sees.
That is a place with freedom.
I also want to be free.
Why are you so rude?
Are you always this cold?
Are you also the same as your godfather?
I don't think I've ever seen you smile.
Do you know how to smile?
Hao Du.
I'm talking to you.
Are you deaf?
I feel so bad for myself.
Chang Ge is still missing.
And my father...
is sending me to the prairies for intermarriage.
And now,
you ridiculously brought me here.
I have no one to talk to.
I've never spent the night outside alone.
I miss my father.
I want to go home.
What are you doing?
Let...
Let go of me!
Put me down!
Hao Du!
Good night, Your Highness.
I'll just sit here.
I won't leave.
Shi Si Lang, get some rest.
You too.
Your Highness.
Why are you here?
I've been waiting for you all night.
Since you're not back yet, I came out to take a look.
What's the matter?
Did you have a date with that East Palace guy?
Get down to business.
Wang Jun Kuo sent someone today to give this submission letter.
Go back first.
I have something to take care of.
Wait. He already went back to his room. You...
How long are you going to hide?
Come out.
When did you arrive?
Today.
Is he here?
Lead the way.
(Outstanding beauty)
Sir.
It has been a while since you came here.
Come here, pretty girl.
Come on. Let's drink more in your room.
- Give me a kiss.
- You're so bad.
Your Highness.
He's here.
Sir, does this feel good?
Why are you here?
What do you think I came here for?
Do you want to try it?
I've never seen you with any girl all these years.
If you don't like it,
did you come here to watch us?
Hey!
Since I was little, I've hated your arrogance.
Leave.
Why exactly did you come here?
The reason why you're here is the reason why I'm here.
How did you know where I'm staying?
As usual,
you won't stay too close or too far from the governor's manor.
And you won't stay in a fancy and high-profile place.
That only leaves...
a few options.
You're finally using your brain.
I can also make you leave.
(To my son Ashina Sun, I hope you settle matters in Youzhou...)
(and go to Shuozhou.)
My father is transferring me to Shuozhou?
My father is mobilizing troops?
Just be a good dog.
Don't ask questions you shouldn't be asking.
Remember.
You go, but the horses stay.
You know a lot of things.
We grew up together.
Can you hide things from me?
Those warhorses are mine.
But you agreed to the condition.
Then I should complete it.
You don't have that right anymore.
Eagle Army's special assistant, Ashina Sun,
shall obey Great Khan's orders.
This is Youzhou's submission letter.
It's for my father.
I can't believe you haven't opened it yet.
It's just a dog wagging its tail.
There's nothing to see.
It looks good when you do it.
All these years,
you're still the ugliest dog.
All you do is steal bones that others are already chewing.
You don't understand.
It's more fun to steal someone else's.
Stealing yours...
is even more fun.
Wang Jun Kuo...
is becoming more interesting.
I want to see...
if he's really that capable.
Master.
You've been pacing around since morning.
Do you feel uneasy about your uncle?
I don't know.
Since the people I trusted the most betrayed me,
I became guarded against people.
But we have no other choice now.
Other than using my uncle's power...
and moving to the governor's manor,
there's no better way.
But no one can find out about this.
Otherwise,
if something goes wrong on my uncle's side,
the consequences would be unimaginable.
Master.
Let's not move into the governor's manor first.
The wooden shed is nice too.
Even if we don't move to the governor's manor,
my uncle will find out that we're staying here sooner or later.
It's just no one...
can find out about this.
Master.
Why don't you give it to me first?
Let's live separately first.
Once you fully trust your uncle,
I'll return it to you.
Master, you trust me, don't you?
Of course I trust you.
However,
I feel anxious and suspicious about everything.
I think it's right...
to be cautious at a time like this.
Don't place the eggs in one basket.
You've become smart.
All right.
I'll leave it with you then.
Remember.
Nothing can happen to it.
As long as you're alive, you must have it.
Don't worry, Master.
This is considered a part of me.
I can bleed, but I can't lose it.
I must go to the governor's manor.
Stay here.
Sir, these are our guest's horses.
What should I say if you take it away?
Do you have a death wish?
Sir, these are our guest's horses.
Sir, you can't take it.
If you take it, what am I going to tell my customer?
Sir.
What's going on? What happened?
I don't know either.
The horses belong to our guest.
The guest left early in the morning.
When he comes back later...
Wait.
These aren't your horses.
They belong to us now.
Why should I believe that they belong to you now?
Why should I make you believe it?
These are our horses.
Otherwise,
how can they run away like that?
Don't delay us. Scram.
What exactly happened to Qin Zhun?
Forget it. I won't interfere.
I'll go to my uncle first.
Be ready to receive orders at any time.
I've already made arrangements there.
Remember.
Once we get the goods,
I'll release the flare,
then take action immediately.
- Yes.
Go.
- Your Highness.
- Tell me.
She Er and Wang Jun Kuo will be...
transacting the warhorses at the thatched hut today.
Also, they say that She Er is pressuring Wang Jun Kuo...
to give him the Crown Prince's seal in two days.
Crown Prince's seal?
What's going on?
This is Youzhou's submission letter.
It's for my father.
I can't believe you haven't opened it yet.
- Ya Luo.
- Yes.
Did you read Wang Jun Kuo's submission letter?
How would I dare to read it?
I was careless.
It seems like I've underestimated Wang Jun Kuo.
Crown Prince's seal?
No wonder she was on the run all along.
Your Highness, where are you going?
I'm going back.
There are some things that I don't understand.
But Youzhou's affairs have nothing to do with us now.
There's someone who has something to do with me there.
Go ahead. There's no need to wait for me.
General Wang, you're so punctual.
Young Khan, why is it you?
Those from the Ashina Tribe are so interesting.
I meet different people each time.
I'm afraid not many people...
do business this way.
You only need to know...
that I have the final say starting today.
After all, I am Ashina Tribe's Young Khan...
and the one Yan Li Khan trusts the most.
Working with me...
is the best option for you.
I don't care what happened to Ashina Tribe internally.
I also don't care who I make the deal with.
I only care about the goods.
You came empty-handed.
How should I believe you?
Precious cargo must of course be kept safe.
If we just show it randomly, people might find out about us.
General Wang.
You can check the goods first.
Once the alliance is completed,
we'll give you the warhorse as agreed.
Wasn't that the person...
who took Qin Zhun's horses at the inn earlier?
Why is Qin Zhun...
involved with the Ashina Tribe?
This is what I want.
He's here to make a deal with Wang Jun Kuo.
Can you deliver the goods today?
General Wang, you're so impatient.
These warhorses...
will double my might.
Within the day, I'll be able to kill Li Yuan.
Youzhou City will also be mine.
General Wang.
I can give you the goods that you want anytime.
You haven't given me what I want yet.
I should have collateral.
I'll give you what you want soon.
Tell me.
I want the key to Youzhou vault,
so you won't cast me aside after I'm no longer needed.
Also, your command token,
so it will be easier for me to work.
All right.
Then Yan Li Khan and I...
will be waiting for your good news.
Wang Jun Kuo wants to sell Youzhou to Yan Li Khan.
This won't do.
I have to save my uncle.
Yongning.
- Why are you coming here rushing?
- Uncle Li Yuan.
Wang Jun Kuo has betrayed you.
He's working for the Ashina Tribe.
And he wants to take over Youzou...
and kill you.
Yongning, you're not aware.
Jun Kuo has been promoted in the military...
through his accomplishments in resisting the Ashina Tribe.
If you say that he wants to kill me, that's even more absurd.
We've been friends for many years and we're in-laws.
Are you thinking too much?
That's impossible.
I heard it myself.
Uncle Li Yuan. Come with me right now.
If he comes here in advance,
we won't be able to leave anymore.
- Come on.
- You...
You can't escape now.
Princess Yongning.
I've underestimated you.
Wang Jun Kuo.
This is the governor's manor.
How can you act so impudently here?
Retreat!
How can you give orders to Youzhou's troops?
You two will reunite again in the afterlife.
- Kill them!
- Yes!
Come on.
Go after them.
Yongning.
What should we do now?
Wang Jun Kuo has already taken over the governor's manor.
I have nowhere else to go.
It will be fine, Uncle Li Yuan.
As long as they don't catch us,
we can still overturn the situation.
Why don't you come with me first?
- All right.
(Qingxiang Inn)
Yongning, what is this place?
It's where I'm staying.
Where is he?
"He"?
Who?
Did you leave something...
with your friend?
I didn't say that I'm looking for something.
Yongning.
Since we're running away,
of course we should take some valuable items with us.
Think about it carefully.
Where is your friend now?
Dou.
Please don't come back here.
Yongning, we're running out of time.
If Wang Jun Kuo comes here, we'll be in trouble.
We came out from the back alley.
It's impossible for Wang Jun Kuo to follow us.
Could it be...
that you had an agreement in advance?
It's so uncomfortable to eat a lot of field rations.
My legs are numb already.
Master is back.
Your master fell for a trick.
I'm here to help you.
Yongning.
If I don't pull this trick,
how will you come to save me?
To be honest,
what you've been doing in the past few days...
moved me.
Why?
Young Khan wants me to give him Crown Prince's seal within two days.
If I wasn't forced by the circumstances,
I wouldn't have done this.
Those from the prairies want Crown Prince's seal too?
And they want us to give it to them within two days.
It seems like they want to use that to create trouble.
But Governor,
I think Yongning isn't easy to deal with either.
It seems like we must put on an act.
Please give your instructions, Governor.
Once we get the goods,
I'll release the flare,
then take action immediately.
- Yes.
These warhorses...
will double my might.
Within the day, I'll be able to kill Li Yuan.
Youzhou City will also be mine.
Yongning, if you didn't trust me,
how would I know where Crown Prince's seal is?
How do you know that it's in my possession?
A decree's authenticity...
can be verified right away.
Chang'an uses top-quality ink cake.
The low-quality ink cake you used...
bled once met with water.
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)