Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 10)
Sir, this way, please.
Sir,
you look worn out.
You're not a local, are you?
Yes.
You should try our famous smoked jade chicken.
I haven't ordered yet.
Our shopkeeper told me...
to serve all out-of-town visitors our famous smoked jade chicken.
It's a welcome gift from us.
Waiter.
Let me ask you something.
Shuozhou is a border state...
far away from the capital.
It was supposed to be an isolated place.
Why is this place so peaceful and prosperous?
People here even care for the beggars on the street.
Sir, you don't know.
This place is a war zone.
Our people are having peace here...
all thanks to our prefectural governor,
the great Gongsun Heng.
Waiter.
Give us more wine.
- And two side dishes, please.
- All right.
Gongsun Heng.
That's why even kids are mimicking him.
He seems to be well-liked.
Sir, please enjoy.
Waiter.
Tell me more about Gongsun Heng.
He's the prefectural governor of Shuozhou.
He has been here since the Sui dynasty.
All these years,
he has enhanced the military power and the security of Shuozhou.
For every fight that northern barbarians make,
they won't gain a thing.
Governor Gongsun even gives our people farming lands.
It has attracted numerous visitors.
We're the busiest prefecture compared to our neighboring states.
Our shopkeeper told me...
to serve all visitors from other states...
our famous smoked jade chicken.
One chicken does not worth much.
We can't make Governor Gongsun lose his face.
Am I right?
Waiter.
I'll get busy.
Call me if you need anything.
Sir, this way, please.
- Do you have any more seats?
- A former general...
of Sui actually cares so much for his people.
People like him must hate war a lot.
How can I convince him...
to start a revolt against Prince of Qin?
Dou.
Master.
It's really you.
I saw someone that looks like you from afar.
So I followed you here.
That means we're destined to be master and disciple.
Are you hungry?
Let's go. I'll buy you something delicious.
All right.
I always know that you're my savior.
With you, everything will be fine.
By the way, Master.
Should we go to the magistrate now?
Like how we did in Youzhou.
We'll tell him the truth.
And ask him to start a revolt.
Youzhou is an important land to my father.
Even his own men are eyeing this piece of land.
Gongsun Heng was a general from the previous empire.
Why should he help us?
In this world,
I can't trust anyone anymore.
Master, what about me?
Do you trust me?
Yes.
Dou.
I think I've grown up a lot recently.
Not having trust in anyone feels worse than being cheated on.
Master.
I don't understand.
You better not.
Let's go. I'll buy you something delicious.
After meals, I'll take you to the poorest place in Shuozhou.
I'll teach you your first lesson,
which is how to gather information.
His Highness is back.
- Your Highness!
- Ashina Sun.
- Your Highness.
Ashina Sun.
You're back.
You're hurt.
It's a long story.
She Er, that brat.
He even dares to kill you now.
If I die in Tang,
he could walk away from it completely.
If I were him,
I would seize this opportunity as well.
This is a bit too risky.
But what if he reports this to Great Khan?
He won't.
I know him well enough.
There's no way he would tell on me...
and admit defeat.
If I'm going to fight,
I will bear the consequences.
Who bandaged this?
What a mess.
If it were someone else,
he'll be seriously injured.
Why are you laughing?
It's nothing.
Are you hiding something from me?
Keep your distance.
Did a lady from Tang bandage you?
Your Highness, Tu Ka She is here.
He's outside the barracks.
What is he doing here?
The time has come.
I haven't informed him yet.
Ashina Sun.
You're still alive.
I'm glad.
You hurt your eye.
Just say what you want.
Don't give me that attitude.
Do you think I wanted to come?
Great Khan has asked us to come here...
and go to Shuozhou with you guys.
He's afraid you'll lose the battle.
What else?
There's more.
This is Great Khan's orders.
Great Khan has put me in charge of this mission.
And I will take full control this time.
So...
every move you astringers make,
you have to report to me.
Cooperation is all about give and take.
What about the Bear Army?
Are you guys going to report to us as well?
It's not on the order.
You can go now.
Where was I?
You were saying that Ba Lu can finally hold a bow now.
He wants to take part in next year's hunt.
And Ge Sang wants to learn archery and horseback riding.
But her mother says no.
She's right.
Why should a girl learn archery and horseback riding?
I'll go see her mother later.
I'll tell them I said yes.
You agreed?
That's enough.
I'm leaving.
Just you wait.
It seems like someone is defaming us in front of Great Khan again.
Tu Ka She never likes you.
He said he's here to help.
He's obviously here to take all the credit.
It's obvious who's behind all this.
If he chickens out because of one failure,
then that's not the She Er we know.
Right.
Did you just say...
you agreed to let the girl learn archery and horseback riding?
Yes.
I said yes.
(Prefectural Governor's Manor)
Elder Qin.
Ashina's army has come to attack us.
They look well-prepared.
I will send the troops...
to guard the northwest and northeast corner...
to form a horn shape around the city.
What do you think?
You are great in military tactics.
This time, Ashina Tribe...
will be defeated.
(Gongsun Heng)
Even though we're impregnable,
we need the reinforcements from Daizhou and Bingzhou...
to defend the entire frontier.
Without them,
I'm afraid there's nothing I can do.
Governor, there is a big trouble.
Tell me.
Madam and Yuan Niang ran into some bandits...
on their way to the temple.
What?
We found the damaged carriage...
and the body of the coachman on the driveway.
This...
Get up.
Where are my wife and daughter?
We couldn't find them.
You couldn't find them?
Those bandits.
This is outrageous.
Convey my orders.
Get all our men...
and come with me to annihilate the bandits in the mountains.
We must save my wife and daughter.
Yes.
My dear.
Are you all right?
Yuan Niang and I are fine.
Thanks to two young lads.
That's how we managed to survive.
"Two young lads"?
Yuan Niang.
Are you all right?
Good girl.
How are you feeling?
Father, I'm fine now.
You're feeling all right now?
- Good girl.
- My dear.
They are my saviors.
I have to thank both of you for saving my wife and daughter.
I'll do my best to repay you.
My name is Shi Si Lang.
This is my brother, Dou.
It was urgent.
So I had no choice but to lie to Madam.
Lie to me?
In that case,
please come in and have a chat with me.
My brother and I have been wandering from Longxi all the way here.
The two of us...
were taking a break in a forest.
Dou was exhausted, so he fell asleep.
Just as I was about to wake him up to continue with our journey，
I heard a few bandits around.
They're plotting something secretly.
Dou.
Wake up. Let's go.
Come on.
Someone is here.
I've found out something.
Gongsun Heng's daughter is sick.
His wife will pass by here tomorrow to go to the temple on the mountain.
We must seize the chance to rob all the valuables.
That jerk, Gongsun Heng.
He cut off our escape route.
We have nowhere to go now.
I'm merciful enough not to kill his wife.
Let's go and get ready.
So how did you save my wife and daughter?
Actually, my brother and I were trying to figure out a plan.
We can't confront the bandits.
And we can't inform you in time.
So...
we decided to lie.
Hurry, they're here.
We're good.
Come on.
Go!
Move.
- Step aside.
- Stop.
Stop.
Do you guys want a ride?
Thank you, ma'am.
My brother is sick for half a month and couldn't recover.
According to the monks at the temple,
we have to walk to the temple...
to show our sincerity.
I can't bear to see him in so much pain.
But we have no choice.
Really?
Of course, it's true.
Wait for me at the temple.
These two lads and I...
will walk to the temple together.
Madam, but...
I've seen every doctor in town.
But Yuan Niang's cough...
is not getting better.
This trip is to pray to Buddha.
This young man is absolutely right.
I have to walk step by step to the temple to show my sincerity.
You should go.
Yes, Madam.
Madam.
Why don't you let me hold your daughter for you?
How can I trouble you?
No worries. I'm strong.
Here.
Come on.
- Let's walk together.
- Thank you, Madam.
I used Yuan Niang to make you walk with us.
Because...
in this world,
every mother is willing to sacrifice herself for her children.
Thank you for saving my life.
I can never repay you.
You're being too courteous, Madam.
Because my mother...
was just like you.
She would do anything for me.
That's true.
If you had used another reason,
I don't think I'll get off the carriage.
But I didn't expect that...
it will cost the coachman's life.
I've wronged the coachman.
Actually, I didn't expect...
the coachman...
to be killed too.
It's those bandits' fault.
They're too brutal.
It's all right.
You're already doing a good job.
Elder Qin.
Convey my orders.
Make sure to take care of the coachman's funeral.
And from now on,
look after his family.
Yes.
You're indeed a young hero.
It's just that...
is it really just a coincidence?
Governor.
My younger brother and I depended on each other since we were little.
We don't have parents.
After experiencing life and death,
we're already as good as dead.
If I could save your wife's life,
it'll be my utmost honor.
Besides, I've long heard that you are highly respected.
You're strict in rewards and punishments.
You'll surely reward both of us handsomely.
So...
You saved my wife and daughter...
all because you want me to reward you?
Yes.
I did have an ulterior motive.
But all I want is to follow a wise leader.
You think I would keep the two of you by my side...
just because you saved my wife and daughter?
Governor.
My father...
was a former Sui general.
He did nothing great his whole life.
Before he passed away, he asked me to go to the border state...
and do something great.
Besides, I was able to save your wife and daughter.
It wasn't just a coincidence.
Isn't this the fate between you and I?
You have a way with words, young man.
Please get up.
My dear.
Shi Si Lang is the daughter of a former Sui general.
He also saved Yuan Er and I.
He's somehow related to the Gongsun family.
The two lads have nowhere to go.
- How about...
- Thank you for taking us in, Madam.
You two have saved...
my wife and daughter's life.
How can I say no?
Since you're willing to stay,
you may have the room in the backyard.
What happens in the future,
we'll discuss it later.
Thank you, Governor.
It has been so long since I slept on such a comfortable bed.
Master.
So we've succeeded.
Gongsun Heng loves his wife and daughter dearly.
Naturally, we'll be treated well.
But to get him to trust me,
it won't be easy.
Then why did he ask us to stay?
It's all because of his wife.
That means he still has doubts about us.
At least he doesn't trust us.
It's hard to trust someone.
He knows that as well.
No matter what,
we've succeeded in the first step of our plan.
Next, we need to obtain Gongsun Heng's trust.
Then we'll take control of the military...
and start a revolt.
Keep the secret to yourself.
What do you think?
Those two lads...
saved Madam and Yuan Niang.
That alone...
They've gotten your weakness right away.
These two boys are smart.
They're also very brave.
But...
they're also witty and cunning.
Don't worry, Master.
I'll pay special attention to them.
The nation is in turmoil.
War is imminent.
We need people to help us too.
If they're being honest...
about earning some recognition,
then they are at the right place.
But...
We still have to be careful.
Since we don't know what will happen,
then let's leave it to fate.
As for the peace in the manor,
worry not, Master.
I'll protect them with all my might.
Isn't this Prince Sun?
What is it?
I have a question for Prince Sun.
Shuozhou is right in front of us.
When do you plan to take it down?
To attack or not?
When to attack?
It's all up to me.
It's just a small town.
How long do you need to consider?
Are you scared?
It's just a small border state.
But back then, even Shu Le Khan can't take it down.
Try to take it down if you can.
That's because back then,
Shu Le Khan didn't have any valiant warriors.
I'm right here.
I've taken down countless cities that are tougher than this.
What if we fail?
Will the Bear Army take full responsibility?
How could we fail?
You haven't even attacked yet.
Why should we take responsibility?
My army will be leading this attack.
All you need to do is cooperate with us.
That way, we will not fail.
I'm counting on the Bear Army then.
All right.
Get two sets of Central Plain’s clothes ready.
Are you going to Shuozhou?
Know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be in danger.
(Prefectural Governor's Manor)
Good girl.
Give me a hug.
Yuan Niang.
Let's go back.
I want Shi Si Lang.
- Shi Si Lang.
- Madam has made you...
some delicious rice cakes.
- Shi Si Lang.
- What's going on?
They're obviously watching out for us.
There's nothing wrong with being defensive.
Let's go out.
Maybe we'll make a new discovery.
Are you going to get information from bandits again?
Some things should not be mentioned again.
Governor, there's an uneven distribution...
of reclaimed wasteland in Chengdong.
There are arguments.
They're begging to see you.
It's not a big deal.
You can just get anyone to handle it for you.
It's not a small matter.
We can divide and register the land into even sizes.
And distribute based on the number of adult men in one family.
Any undistributed lands will be managed by the government.
They can claim their share of land when younger boys reach adolescence.
What do you think?
Do as he says.
Yes.
Good morning, Governor.
You know politics.
A little.
When did you learn it?
My father is a low-ranking official.
I was influenced by him.
All right. Let me ask you.
There has been a back-channeler dealing with the Hu merchant.
What do you think?
Dealing with foreign merchants is inevitable.
Both parties are only getting what they need.
That's how you make a living.
Actually, you shouldn't eliminate them all at once.
But we have to control the type of item sold and their amount.
Basically, have a general control over the transactions made.
Decisions can be made accordingly if the circumstances allow.
If I didn't hear it myself,
I can't believe this is coming from you.
You've flattered me, Governor.
I'm nothing compared to you.
Where are you two going?
My brother and I are new in town.
We are planning to take a spin around...
and see out what's interesting.
We'd also like to learn about the customs of this place.
All right, you guys go ahead.
Yes.
- You heard him.
- Yes.
What do you think?
You always value talents.
I think you're very tempted this time.
Yes.
If my subordinates had been as talented as him,
then I would have much lesser things to worry about each day.
Elder Qin.
- Follow them.
- Yes.
Your Highness.
You can't let this slide.
Mr. Du.
The Crown Princess just made this plum cake.
Try one.
Wei Zheng just arrived in Cizhou.
And he met up with Li Jian Cheng's former subordinate,
Li Zhi An right away.
Li Yuan Ji's guards, Li Si Xing who was previously imprisoned...
was also released on the spot.
And these two men disappeared in an instant.
They've got some nerve.
Please summon Wei back immediately and punish him, Your Highness.
That's not right, Mr. Du.
I remember you were the one...
who incited him to take this job.
I wanted him to calm down Hebei.
I didn't tell him to release the prisoners along the way.
What's more, it's a military officer who can lead the army.
It's fine.
Your Highness.
Mr. Wei's action reminds me of someone.
There's someone more eccentric than Wei Zheng?
Your Highness, please tell us.
A Qi man from the Warring States period, Feng Xuan.
Yes.
The man who won the people's hearts by burning bonds, Feng Xuan.
He's indeed an extraordinary person.
Feng Xuan had only burned bonds.
But the man whom Wei Zheng released...
was a warrior who can fight.
Get the Central Secretariat to convey my orders.
Inform the East Palace and Prince of Qi before June 4...
and Li Yuan before June 17...
that no one should punish Wei Zheng.
Any offenders will be punished.
Please reconsider, Your Highness.
If even reporting is forbidden,
then Wei's gang will be even more brazen.
Wei Zheng might find this encouraging.
He might even release Wang Jun Kuo.
Have a look.
"I can't be selfish."
"I have to think of the nation."
"It's a great honor to work for Your Highness."
"I have to repay your kindness and contribute to this country."
How cheesy.
As for Wang Jun Kuo,
send in a team of strong men and take him to the capital...
so that no one finds him suspicious.
Don't mention anything about him going to jail or repent.
Just say he has been ordered to enter the capital.
I'll do it right away.
Mr. Fang.
Do you have any news about Le Yan?
Do you think...
the heaven is punishing me?
I've lost Chang Ge.
Do you want me to lose Yan Er too?
Your Highness.
Don't overthink it.
Princess Yong'an and Princess Yongning...
will come back safely.
I will send more men to look for them.
Girl.
You're pretty smart.
Hai Lao.
Look, Hai Lao.
I even brought wine.
Great.
This roast chicken is especially delicious.
Smell it. It smells good, right?
- Good.
- Let me pour you some wine.
It's very aromatic.
All right.
Mr. Ma Zi, please have a drink.
Cheers.
- One more glass.
- Fill it.
Here.
One more.
Fill it up.
Cheers.
Le Yan.
You want to run away?
If they find out,
they'll kill you.
It was so hard to get them drunk.
It's now or never.
Perhaps tomorrow I'll be sold off as a limbless beggar.
If you don't want to,
don't blame me for not bringing you.
But...
I'll go with you.
That's what sisters are for.
Be careful.
Su Su!
They locked the doors.
How can we get out of here?
Here.
Look, Le Yan.
There's a hole there.
But it's too high up.
We can't reach it.
Yes, we can, Su Su.
There are two of us.
Right, Le Yan.
I'll go first.
Help me get out of here first.
Then I'll save you, all right?
Le Yan.
Be quiet.
Ma Zi is still sleeping outside.
Stay put for a while.
I'll be right back.
But you...
Su Su.
The two of them have been wandering around in town aimlessly.
They didn't do anything strange.
They bought a lot of snacks...
and gave to the beggars at the temple.
They said it's Governor Gongsun's order.
There's nothing suspicious.
The people are grateful to the Governor.
Forget it.
Stop tailing them.
You've been exposed.
You may leave.
You don't have to follow them anymore.
Understood.
- Elder Qin.
You're back.
How's your stay in Shuozhou?
It's great.
We walked around the town today.
There's good food in town.
It's fun too.
That's good.
There's news from the capital.
I should report it to the Governor.
I should go now.
Call me if you need anything.
We won't stall you, Elder Qin.
Is it about Chang'an?
I think so.
Then let's...
Let's go inside first.
If Li Shi Min is publicly searching for us,
he would've already informed all the states.
He doesn't have to wait until now.
I'm afraid something worse is about to happen.
To eliminate the Gu Tribe,
cooperate with the Luo Tribe to besiege Wu City.
Cheng Zhi Jie and Li Shi Ji have been at war for months.
Yan Li actually has so much control over Tang's army.
Is he trying to...
What a big ambition.
With your martial arts skills,
you must have an extraordinary background.
You're well hidden in the Prefectural Governor's Manor.
A butler is actually an expert.
Did the Governor send you?
You're wrong.
My master never keeps someone he doesn't trust.
But I had to act careless.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be so fearless.
You're not from Longxi, are you?
I've been away from the Central Plain for too long.
I know the Longxi accent very well.
Although you copied it very well,
there's still a difference.
Who exactly are you?
I let it slip on purpose.
You tailed me here after I told you there's news from the capital.
A spy from the north?
The Military Governor's department?
Or are you from Chang'an?
You're the imperial court's man.
Are you here to take back the Governor's military power?
The imperial court has always been worried...
about Governor Gongsun's military power.
But you should understand.
Shuozhou can stand strong until today...
wasn't because of the imperial court.
You can check out Shuozhou.
How are the people living here?
And compare it with the people of the other states.
It's not an easy task to make such a mundane land a prosperous town.
You're overthinking it.
I'm not from the imperial court.
I'm here to find a place to live.
I lied about my Longxi background...
so that the Governor would take us in.
Forgive me for lying.
I'm not interested in looking into your past.
And I don't care what you want.
Leave the Gongsun family alone.
And I will leave you alone.
You're a smart guy.
You better behave yourself.
This is bad.
They knew that Su Su had escaped.
Don't be afraid.
You're better than her.
You won't end up like her.
I came to see you today.
I want to discuss something with you.
Please tell me.
I thought about it over the past few days.
If you don't mind,
can you stay and be my registrar?
Your brother, Dou,
can be your assistant.
What's wrong?
Are you feeling inferior?
No.
I...
I thank you for taking us in, Governor Gongsun.
Great.
This is my personal guard, Xu Feng.
- Mr. Xu.
- Mr. Li.
All right.
The Military Governor has invited me over to his place.
I'll get going then.
The Governor admired your talent.
And we need manpower right now.
So we can't care about anything else.
But I'll repeat what I said.
Leave the Gongsun family alone.
And I will leave you alone.
You have misunderstood us.
From now on, I'll devote my heart and soul to the Governor.
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)