Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 11)
(Prefectural Governor's Manor)
Governor Gongsun.
Chief Registrar Li.
As the new chief registrar of the Governor's Manor,
I'm not familiar with the affairs in Shuozhou yet.
I should go with you.
There's no need for you to come this time.
Xu Feng will go with me.
Chief Registrar Li.
You two can have a good rest.
Yes.
(Prefectural Governor's Manor)
I originally thought...
that if Gongsun Heng could take me to see Sima Tu,
I could use my wits to find out...
about the battle formation at the northern border.
From the looks of it,
this will require some more effort.
Should we follow them then?
Forget it.
Since he turned me down,
it'll seem like we have ulterior motives...
if we follow along now.
Master, where are you going?
To rest.
Your Highness.
Our spy has reported that Ashina Sun headed...
in the direction of Shuozhou last night.
The Eagle Army hasn't made any moves yet.
Ashina Sun only took Mu Jin with him.
- Guard.
- Your Highness.
Assemble the Bear Army.
Yes.
Since they're giving us a chance,
we need to show them who's boss.
You're brilliant, Your Highness.
This is nice.
How's the situation?
I wouldn't have believed it if I didn't see it with my own eyes.
There are merely less than a thousand soldiers...
stationed in the east and the south.
I knew it.
With the advantage of impregnable terrain...
in the east and the south,
the prefectural governor of Shuozhou...
mainly stationed troops in the north and west.
But I just scouted the areas.
There are only less than 20,000 soldiers.
How did Shuozhou City get its reputation...
of being a secure and resilient city?
Tu Ka She said these people are all useless.
Could this be true?
When we entered the city just now,
did you notice the city wall?
(Shuozhou)
It's a lot thicker compared to other cities...
in the Central Plain.
Also, the rammed earth looks fairly new.
It must be regularly reinforced.
Usually, all sorts of people freely go in and out of the city.
But when a war starts,
no one is able to get in once the city gate is closed.
As long as there are sufficient provisions in the city,
it wouldn't be difficult to survive for several years.
Interesting.
Do you have a plan?
Come on.
We need to buy some Paulownia wood.
Would it kill you to stop being mysterious for one second?
If you can help Gongsun Heng...
analyze the good and bad of the bureaucracy...
and guarantee his career prospects,
a Sui Dynasty official like him who submitted to the Tang empire...
would surely be tempted.
I'm just afraid this isn't what Gongsun Heng is after.
Why are you still such a kid?
You even choke when you eat noodles.
Master.
I think we're out of money.
We used up all our money...
after giving food to the beggars last time.
Did you not keep even a bit for ourselves?
Didn't you say it yourself?
People must be grateful.
If the beggars hadn't told us where the bandits were,
how would we have made our way into the Governor's Manor?
Since we have food and shelter at the Prefectural Governor's Manor,
what do we still need money for?
Master, those were your exact words.
I'll count to three.
Let's run together.
Sirs.
How was the food?
It's a total of 10 coins for 2 bowls of noodles.
No, we haven't finished eating.
We'll pay later.
Sorry, sir.
The two of us came out in a hurry...
and forgot our coin pouch.
How about this?
I'll tell my brother to go home and get it.
I'll wait here.
All right. I'll go and get the money now.
Don't run!
I see.
One runs off first, then the other finds a chance to escape too.
I've seen tricks like this a lot.
Let's go. Come with me to the magistrate.
No, sir. Listen to me.
My brother went to get the money. He'll be back soon.
How do I know whether you're telling the truth or not?
Come on.
- Sir, let go...
- How much is it?
I'll give it to you.
Why are you here?
Here's 10 coins.
Consider the extra money as a reward from this young man.
Thank you, sir.
Sorry for offending you earlier.
Break it up.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
Zhun.
We meet again,
Shi Si Lang.
Who is this?
I told you not to come to Shuozhou.
Yet, look at you.
You didn't listen to a word I said.
What about you?
You're here yourself.
By the way, how is your injury?
You even know about his injury?
I was the one who bandaged him up.
Of course, I know.
So, you're that quack?
His wound would've recovered without getting bandaged,
but thanks to you...
I'm fine now.
Just ignore him, Shi Si Lang.
He...
I'm glad you're fine.
By the way,
Shuozhou has consolidated the border trade situation.
Profiteers like you...
will lose money no matter what business you do.
Shi Si Lang.
How long are you going to be in Shuozhou?
Forget it.
Let's not pry into each other's business.
Master.
You got out.
Mr. Peddler.
Who is this guy?
Dou.
Zhun paid for our meal.
The two of us are on our way out of the city.
Shi Si Lang,
can you take us?
Of course.
We have to part ways eventually,
so I'll leave you guys here.
Zhun.
I wish you all the best with your business.
Shi Si Lang.
Just like last time,
if there's nothing that you must stay in Shuozhou for,
you should leave as soon as possible.
Where else could I go?
Have you ever thought about going to the grasslands?
The grasslands?
I don't know anyone there.
I'd rather not.
You know me.
Thank you.
But I'll pass.
Who are these people?
They're the outpost of the Ashina army.
They're about to attack the city.
Shi Si Lang.
Some of my men are still in the north.
I have to head back to look after them.
You...
You better get as far away from Shuozhou City as possible.
- Goodbye.
- Take care.
Master.
What should we do now?
Let's go back.
I can't believe Tu Ka She is trying...
to earn credit for himself while you're gone.
Are we sure we don't need to do something?
If you want to see Tu Ka She ends up in a mess,
then you can stay.
I'm not interested in watching losers.
Are you that certain he'll lose?
Tu Ka She is an idiot.
Besides, she's still there.
She?
Stop right there.
How dare you trespass our city's defense area?
Release the smoke signal and hit the drum!
The Ashina army is attacking!
Get out of the way.
If we miss the timing to warn them,
will you be able to bear the responsibility?
- Quick!
- No.
Chief Registrar Li.
Let him come up.
- Yes.
Chief Registrar Li.
- Why are you here?
- Governor Gongsun.
The Ashina Tribe's army is attacking.
Hurry and strike the drum.
There's no rush yet.
No rush?
So, you mean...
you still won't strike the drum and warn the people yet.
It's not time yet.
It's all right even if they come closer.
Governor Gongsun.
Think about it carefully.
Once the Ashina Tribe enters the city,
it'll be a catastrophe for Shuozhou.
It will also be...
- an impending danger for Tang!
- Stop it!
- How dare you to attack our master?
- Enough, Xu Feng.
He's just acting out of desperation.
We have to urgently deal with the enemy now.
I don't have time to explain everything to you.
Guards.
- Yes.
Take them back to the manor and watch them closely.
- Gongsun Heng.
- Come on.
You don't know how to make use of your soldiers.
- You're too willful.
- Come.
Gongsun Heng.
(Prefectural Governor's Manor)
Hey.
I won't go to the gate tower.
Am I not even allowed to walk around the manor?
The governor has given orders.
You two are not to go anywhere.
Do you believe him that much?
What if his decision is wrong?
The governor has his own plans.
That Gongsun Heng is just a phony.
I really don't know what he did...
to fool everyone in the city into supporting him.
Did you hear the war drum just now?
They only sent out a warning after such a long time.
I'm afraid...
this battle is a dangerous one.
Dou.
Do you think...
it was wrong for us to come here?
He doesn't even know the most basic military strategies.
I can't believe I was hoping...
to ask for his help in starting a revolt.
Exactly.
Even I know...
we must send out a warning in time when enemies are in sight.
How could he not understand this...
as the prefectural governor of Shuozhou?
He might've done it on purpose.
If he dares...
to give Shuozhou up to the Ashina Tribe,
I won't let him off.
I'll teach him a lesson too.
Governor Gongsun.
Chief Registrar Li.
- I...
- Why didn't you sound the drum?
The Ashina soldiers suddenly struck the city.
Our soldiers didn't respond in one time.
It's only normal that we'd suffer tragically.
Tell me.
How many casualties are there?
Ten thousand?
Twenty thousand?
Or is it more?
Chief Registrar Li, we...
If you don't know anything about military tactics,
why didn't you listen to my advice?
Why did you insist on doing things your own way?
Did you do it on purpose?
You guys...
Do you have any regard for the lives of all the people in the city?
Chief Registrar Li.
This battle was a triumph.
We won.
We won?
How did we win?
Yes, Governor Gongsun.
Hurry and tell us.
How did we win?
Calm down, both of you.
Let me explain.
Our master had his reasons for not sounding the drum...
to send out a warning.
At the time, 3,000 archers were hiding...
inside the city's gate tower.
The Ashina Tribe's soldiers rushed here on their horses.
Very soon, they were within range for us to shoot.
Once our master gave the order,
10,000 arrows were released at once.
The Ashina Tribe's soldiers could not turn around in time...
and they immediately panicked.
Then, our master gave another order.
Convey my orders.
Open the gate and bring out the chevaux-de-frise.
Our warriors got into position...
and attacked the enemy.
The Crescent Moon Array.
Chief Registrar Li, do you understand military strategies?
I've learned a thing or two before.
Come.
Sit down.
Then, tell me.
If you were to lead the soldiers and create a battle formation,
what would you do next?
Next...
The Crescent Moon shall transition to the Serpent Battle Array.
If the body of the serpent is attacked,
the head and tail can come together as reinforcement.
And then?
Mr. Xu, continue.
And then,
after taking such heavy blows,
the Ashina Tribe's soldiers were already utterly destroyed.
But their commander, Tu Ka She, just wouldn't admit defeat.
They tried to attack us again.
Sound the war drum.
Light the smoke signal.
At that moment,
our warriors lying in wait sounded the war drums...
and sent out smoke signals...
in the northeast and northwest corners...
across the gate tower.
The battle cries of our soldiers echoed in their ears endlessly.
Tu Ka She was afraid they'd be surrounded on all four sides...
and was scared out of his wits.
They turned around and helplessly retreated.
Governor Gongsun, you're indeed impressive.
But...
Since there were soldiers lying in ambushes...
in the northeast and west,
why didn't you secretly send them in...
and take them by surprise?
Why did you have to create such a stir?
Could it be that you...
What?
You were bluffing.
You're indeed a very talented young man.
You saw right through me.
You're right.
Only 2,000 warriors were lying in wait.
Your military tactics are indeed incredible.
So...
You no longer think I don't know how to make use of my troops...
and only insist on doing things my own way?
I was the ignorant one.
Just because I learned a bit about military tactics,
I spoke arrogantly to you.
I'm ashamed.
All right.
I won't take such trivial matters to heart.
But seeing how you risked your life...
to deliver the news to us,
I appreciate your kindness towards the civilians in Shuozhou.
Here, I'd like to thank you on behalf...
of all the citizens in the city.
Governor Gongsun.
I really admire your generosity.
After this battle,
I finally understand...
why you're undefeated...
and how Shuozhou City built its secure walls...
and brought joy and peace to its citizens.
If you don't mind,
I want to...
Do you want to join us in fighting the enemies...
and guarding Shuozhou City?
I'm willing to share this responsibility with you.
You're a talented young man...
and you know military tactics.
I'm very gratified.
Get up.
I'm also willing to learn the art of war from you, Governor.
Okay.
Defend Shuozhou City with us too.
Get up.
Congratulations to the Bear Army for making a safe return.
All of you came to see me this time.
Of course, we had to.
Your Highness wanted to be the one to bring home a win first.
Without a word, you led your soldiers...
in a surprise attack on the city.
Although it didn't end well,
at least you didn't get completely wiped out.
I'm not in a good mood.
You better shut that mouth of yours.
The Bear Army's attack this time has alerted the enemy.
If we end up getting backed into a corner in this war,
it's all because of your mistake today.
What's wrong?
I just took my Bear Army out for a bit of training.
How could you hold me accountable for something so serious?
I know what I'm doing.
It's none of your business.
We don't want to get involved with your business either.
We'll be reporting everything about today's battle...
to the Great Khan.
You don't have to do it.
I'll report to him myself.
Send this letter...
to the Chief Commander's Manor.
(Only to be opened by Chief Commander Sima Tu.)
This time, the Ashina Tribe came with ill intentions.
If my guess is correct,
they'll definitely attack again.
We need backup.
I'm on it.
(Broad-minded and knowledgeable)
Governor Gongsun.
- Chief Registrar Li.
- Governor Gongsun,
this is a newly drawn map.
Please take a look.
Why do you look so troubled?
After all, we won the battle.
Why aren't you happy over our victory?
It's just a small victory.
What is there to be happy about?
I've already asked Xu Feng to ask the chief commander...
for backup.
Backup?
Shuozhou's terrain is impenetrable yet,
we still need reinforcements?
The truly powerful enemies of the Ashina Tribe...
haven't shown up yet.
Look at this.
The Wuding River is wide and deep.
It was supposed to be the natural defense line...
between Shuozhou and the Ashina Tribe.
But now,
we don't have enough soldiers,
so we can't dispatch troops to guard the riverbank.
That's why the enemies can freely come and go...
and approach the city.
Since they'll pass this river as they come and go,
why don't we turn this river...
into a war tunnel?
A war tunnel?
As the Ashina Tribe army isn't good in the water,
they probably prefer the dry season.
Of course.
If the river is dry,
there will be nothing obstructing them.
They'll be able to travel twice as fast as usual.
In that case,
we'll give them a dry season.
Give them a dry season?
What do you mean?
From what I heard, the dry season is always in July.
However, it just so happens that we have a lot of rain this summer.
The dry season...
will probably be coming at least half a month late.
Coincidentally,
there's a dense forest at the head of this river.
If we send our elite soldiers...
to block the river current with rocks and wood,
it'll be done in just a few days.
Governor Gongsun,
what do you think?
You...
You're good, Chief Registrar Li.
How did you come up with such a strategy?
Please forgive my nonsense.
You are very clever.
I'm impressed.
However,
the Ashina Tribe's Bear Army was just defeated.
They fled in a hurry.
I don't think they'll dare...
to dispatch any troops for a while.
Even if they do,
they'll be very cautious.
It seems we'll need to carefully think...
about how we can get them to let their guard down.
If it weren't for the fact that the Ashina Tribe's soldiers...
are too strong,
there's actually a more reliable way to fight them.
A more reliable way to fight?
Tell me about it.
The military strategist, Sun Tzu, once said,
"In a battle,"
"one must use unconventional methods to win."
We could send out our troops as bait...
to lure the enemy's main forces.
And then, we can have our soldiers take a detour...
and attack the enemy's flank from behind,
destroying the enemy's territory.
Then, we'll crush them one by one.
Isn't that even better?
Okay.
You're so young,
yet, you're so bold.
That's very impressive.
You remind me...
of someone else.
Who?
The Prince of Qin,
the current Crown Prince.
There were countless heroes near the end of the Sui Dynasty.
He was a young boy back then.
He led an army of men...
and attacked the enemy's territory.
He used the same strategy.
He was invincible.
I can't believe...
I heard you describe the same strategy today.
Chief Registrar Li.
It seems you were just being modest...
when you said you only learned a thing or two.
The Crown Prince's great feats are well-known to the world.
I merely copied his strategy.
I don't deserve any praise.
Chief Registrar Li.
Don't be so modest.
Shuozhou is incredibly lucky to have you.
Right.
One more thing.
Chief Registrar Li.
This is a report for the imperial court.
You must have a messenger travel day and night...
to get it to Chang'an immediately.
Governor Gongsun,
do you not trust the chief commander?
This isn't about trust.
It's just that...
this concerns the safety of the people.
We must do what we can to ensure that nothing goes wrong.
Yes. I'll get right on it.
Li Shi Min.
Will I never be able to step out of your shadow?
I remember now.
You're from Shuozhou.
You know Shuozhou inside and out.
You knew we were going to lose today.
Are you conspiring with the enemy?
I'm innocent!
I've always been loyal to you, Your Highness.
I have a plan.
If Your Highness still wants to kill me after hearing me out,
I'm willing to accept it.
Tell me.
How confident are you about this?
If this works,
Shuozhou will self-destruct.
Your Highness will get all the credit.
Is that so?
Master,
Commander Sima has invited you to his place.
Sima Tu?
Did he say anything else?
No.
Perhaps he agrees to send reinforcements...
and wants to discuss it with you.
After the Ashina Tribe's invasion,
he hasn't made any moves at all.
He has always guarded against me.
It can't be that simple.
All right, you may go.
Yes.
Elder Qin.
This invitation from Sima Tu...
must be a trap.
But he's the chief commander.
I can't disrespect him either.
- I have to go.
- Master.
I'll go with you.
It's okay.
I think it's more useful for you to stay here.
Elder Qin.
If I do not return this time,
hand this to Chief Registrar Li.
Master, are you sure?
The backgrounds of the two young men...
are quite suspicious.
I've never chosen people I suspect.
If I decide to choose them, I trust them.
You can be the one to decide...
when to give this to them.
Master.
Elder Qin.
I know what you're worried about.
I trust him.
But...
- And I trust you even more.
- Master.
This...
Aside from hearing his words, you must also observe his actions.
Then you'll know where his heart lies.
I know.
He may be hiding something.
But I don't believe...
he's someone who will harm Tang and the civilians.
All these years,
I've defended against enemies with my troops...
and fought them countless times.
The enemies may have already seen through my tactics.
But he's different.
He's very clever with making use of troops.
He's versatile.
Moreover, the enemies are not familiar with his tactics.
We may gain victory by giving them a surprise.
However,
he's still inexperienced.
He needs your help.
Even if I don't come back this time,
I believe...
as long as you work together,
you'll surely find a way...
to save the civilians of Shuozhou from danger.
Let me thank you in advance.
Master, please don't be like this.
I will do as you say.
(Broad-minded and knowledgeable)
(Chief Commander's Manor)
- Governor Gongsun.
Stop right there.
What?
Xu Feng.
Wait for me here.
Yes.
Come on.
(Chief Commander's Manor)
Greetings, Army Chief.
So, you still remember I'm the chief commander?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Please explain.
Let me ask you.
Did you deploy the troops for the battle today?
Yes.
It was an urgent matter.
When we discovered the enemy,
the Ashina Tribe was already approaching the city.
We were in an emergency situation.
That's why I couldn't send any men to report to you.
In the face of urgency, I did what I had to.
Please forgive me.
I govern...
the armies of four provinces on His Majesty's behalf.
All the troops...
must follow my orders.
No one is allowed to dispatch our troops on their own.
I do understand the need...
to accommodate urgent circumstances.
But the battle today went on for four hours.
In those four hours,
were you so busy that you couldn't send one person...
to come and inform me?
I was careless.
Everyone knows how meticulous you are.
Why would you be careless?
Ultimately, this is all because...
you've just never had any respect for me at all.
I suppose you've worked too long for the Sui Dynasty,
so you've forgotten we're in a new dynasty now.
I'm serving the Tang Dynasty with utmost sincerity.
I hope you can understand.
I am absolutely loyal.
So you're saying I'm falsely accusing you?
I wouldn't dare.
Knowing that the soldiers only listen to your orders,
you've been a tyrant in Shuozhou for decades.
You've gotten used to throwing your weight around.
What is there you wouldn't dare to do?
Today, you deployed troops without permission.
If I don't do anything,
the other three provinces will follow suit...
and have no regard for me.
Guards.
Army Chief.
We're in a critical battle situation now.
Please allow me to fight off the enemies first.
I'll surely visit you again to accept punishment.
So you want to come back for punishment when you're not busy?
You really are something.
Do you have any respect for His Majesty?
Army Chief.
The war should be our priority now.
Please put the civilians first.
Take him away.
Keep a close eye on him!
Governor Gongsun said...
he will stay at the Chief's Manor tonight.
You can go back first.
Army Chief.
Has the war report that the Governor's Manor...
sent off to Chang'an been intercepted?
Yes.
Any news of Shuozhou will never reach Chang'an.
Immediately send someone...
to guard the post road in the south.
Before the Ashina Tribe army retreats,
any news of the four provinces in the north...
must not get out.
Yes.
Come out.
It's done.
Hurry and leave.
You're not welcome here.
If I hadn't told you...
and we let Gongsun Heng anger the Ashina army,
the four provinces in the north would be in deep trouble...
if we drew the attention of their main forces.
I'm afraid you wouldn't be able to keep your position...
as the chief commander.
I did you such a huge favor.
It's not very appropriate...
for you to send me off like this, is it?
My Sima family...
no longer has anything to do with you.
You chose to defect to the enemy,
but don't drag me down with you.
You're wrongfully accusing me.
I'm doing this for your sake.
I also don't want to see civilians living in misery.
Gongsun Heng wants to risk the lives of everyone in the city...
so he can claim he cares about the people's livelihood.
Never mind locking him up.
You could even kill him.
It's none of your business...
how I'll deal with Gongsun Heng.
Fine.
It's only a matter of time...
until Shuozhou City collapses.
When the time comes,
you should fear for your life.
I'm currently serving the Ashina Tribe...
and I'm highly valued.
You've also seen what the circumstances are.
We're family.
Of course, I'll always keep your benefits in mind.
You and your people have become enemies...
with Gongsun Heng.
If he gets back on his feet one day,
do you think you'd be able to get a foothold in Shuozhou City?
I can only give you a piece of advice.
Give up the wrong path you're on and turn in the right direction.
It's still not too late.
It's almost dawn.
Get lost.
Chief Registrar.
It's late. Aren't you going to bed?
I'll sleep after I organize these documents for the governor.
What about you, Elder Qin?
You're getting old.
Why don't you let someone else...
be on night patrol?
Saying this...
makes it sound like you've done something guilty.
Elder Qin.
I'll just say one thing.
I have a clear conscience.
All right.
- Elder Qin.
- Xu Feng.
You came back so late.
Where's our master?
Sima Tu's subordinate told me...
that Master is staying...
at the Chief Commander's Manor tonight.
I think something's wrong,
so I hurried back here.
I knew it.
They've detained him.
Why?
I'm afraid it's because...
he deployed troops to fight the enemy without permission today.
Sima Tu has always thought...
of the governor as a thorn in his side.
He didn't respond...
to the governor's request for reinforcements.
Today, Master had no choice...
but to deploy troops to face the enemy.
I'm afraid they have a hold on him now.
That makes sense.
From the Sui Dynasty to the Tang Dynasty,
Governor Gongsun has held military power in Shuozhou.
The imperial court assigned the chief commander...
to govern the four provinces...
in order to limit the governor's power.
They fear he'll defy the court's orders.
After today's battle,
even though they didn't exactly get their way,
it'll be their excuse to rise in revolt later on.
Yes.
That dirty official.
How could he be so unreasonable?
I'll send people to charge into his manor...
- and save our master now.
- Stop right there.
- You can't go.
- Why not?
Come to your senses.
They've detained our master,
but they're keeping quiet.
That's because...
they still don't have anything on him yet.
If we fight against the chief commander now,
we'd be giving them proof...
that Master has ulterior motives...
and is conspiring to stage a rebellion,
just like their accusations.
Then what can we do now to save Master?
Master is the prefectural governor.
Although they've detained him,
his life is not in danger for now.
But this must stay between the three of us.
Madam must not find out.
I don't want her to worry for nothing.
Yes.
Xu Feng.
You used to be a scout.
Investigating is your expertise.
Keep an eye on the chief commander.
Do not let him out of your sight for even a second.
Report every single detail to me by a carrier pigeon.
Tomorrow,
I'll meet with Sima Tu myself to ascertain the situation.
Yes.
Elder Qin.
I'll go with you tomorrow.
Chief Registrar Li.
Staying here in the manor...
would already be a great help to us.
What's the background of Tu Ka She's advisor?
This man's surname is Sima.
He's an official of the Central Plain...
whom Tu Ka She captured...
when he went on an expedition with the Great Khan.
Seeing that he is quite clever,
Tu Ka She let him live.
He became the advisor for the Bear Army.
As they would say in the Central Plain,
he's "a villain who got into power".
Who knows what ideas...
that villain has given Tu Ka She this time?
Just now, our scout reported...
that the Chief Commander has detained Gongsun Heng.
Gongsun Hang has been detained?
So what if the city has a strong defense?
Gongsun Heng has been protecting Shuozhou for so many years,
but he got locked up by one of his own in the end.
They're pretty much just handing Shuozhou to us on a plate.
That's too bad.
A great soldier has been ruined by a wicked villain.
Keep an eye on Sima Jian.
Don't let him play with fire and end up burning us.
Yes.
Let me congratulate Your Highness in advance.
My brother has already imprisoned Gongsun Heng.
Once I persuade him some more,
he'll surely surrender soon.
Good.
If that day comes,
not only will I be flying high,
it will also mark the day you get rich.
I want to see how that scumbag...
will still compete with me.
(Prefectural Governor's Manor)
What is the meaning of this?
Just tell us if you want to kick us out.
What are you doing?
There is a thief in the manor.
Chief Li.
This morning, Sima Tu refused to let me in.
But my scout reported that...
Sima Tu claims Governor Gongsun colluded with the Ashina Tribe...
and disregarded military orders.
He is suspected of treason,
so he has been locked up to await trial.
Isn't that nonsense?
Where is the justice?
Justice?
If that existed,
the world would be a peaceful place.
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
(The Long Ballad)