(Episode 3)
Die, die.
Hong Ji A.
It's dangerous to stab everywhere like that.
You have to stab it in the heart, in one go.
Let's try again.
Great job, my daughter.
Come on. That's too boring.
Mom, I don't want to become an exorcist.
Then who'll send away the unrested spirits?
No one will.
A dead person's soul wandering...
in this world without a body...
is the same as...
being in the middle of a blizzard in just your underwear.
Why won't they leave when it's that freezing? What fools.
They can't leave because they're holding...
onto an extremely resentful and hurtful grudge.
That's why we need to help them leave.
We need to help them get over their grudges...
so that they can go somewhere warm and live happily ever after.
Help me.
How did she pass away?
Because of me.
Just go now. I'm tired.
You said I was special earlier.
Why don't you team up with this special psychic?
Why would I?
I refuse to work with a fraud.
You asked me to join hands before.
And we did.
Secretary Joo, please wire Oh In Bum 20,000 dollars.
Tell her your bank account number.
Stop!
20,000 dollars.
Do you think that's chump change?
I'm not going to wire that.
Just do it. You didn't have to come all the way here.
Mr. Oh, we pay our psychics...
2,000 dollars per gig.
She must've been out of her mind and added another zero.
She mentioned 20,000 dollars at least three times,
and I almost died after being dragged upstairs.
- You went upstairs? - Dragged?
You went there willingly.
And don't whine about passing out for a few minutes.
He went there willingly? Into the room?
Like I said.
It may be difficult to wire all that money at once,
so I'm willing to work with you until I get all the money.
I said I would never work with a fraud.
Okay.
I understand your opinions.
I'll look at this favorably and call you back.
You should leave for today.
I hope you make a reasonable decision.
- You know my number, right? - I deleted it.
Then I'll call you. I didn't erase yours.
- Hire him as your psychic. - Are you insane?
He commits scams with spirits.
But he even went upstairs.
Look. Don't you see how the salt has changed color?
Have you ever seen this glow so blue?
This is a first for me.
So what? I still can't send my mom away.
You said he gave you warmth...
and absorbed unrested spirits' memory.
It's not easy to find a psychic who can supplement your flaws.
- I have no flaws. - You have too many.
I've been doing well singlehandedly until now.
I never said it out loud,
but do you know how anxious I get...
whenever you suffer from hypothermia?
Nevertheless, I was fine.
Have you already forgotten about Gonjiam?
You almost died there.
I almost died.
I didn't actually die.
Tell me the truth. Is it me or that realty?
Hey, are you going to abandon me for that realty?
I'm not abandoning you.
I just need to look into something personal.
Aren't I your only personal matter?
You have neither parents nor siblings.
Personal what?
- This. - What?
How did you fix this?
- Did you glue it back? - That one's not mine.
Ms. Hong gave that to me.
Why does she have something that looks exactly like yours?
I thought your uncle gave it to you.
That's what I'm trying to find out.
What the relationship between Daebak Realty...
and my uncle was.
I thought it'd work this time.
You must've been startled.
I'm really sorry.
Next time, I'll find a decent psychic.
Not a fraud.
You trust me, right?
(Daebak Realty)
If he had that much power,
why couldn't he possess your mother's spirit?
- Maybe he isn't a virgin. - He is.
He was possessed back at Dream Officetel.
He could've found a woman after that incident.
That quickly?
- We should look into that first. - Yes.
Who is he?
He's the driver.
Make me the co-CEO.
And him, the chief.
Is he a plus one or what?
That won't give you a higher salary.
- Deal. - Secretary Joo,
please write the contract.
Okay.
You wanted a joint contract, right?
Yes. My name is Heo Ji Chul...
I'm a plus one.
What?
What is this?
I must maintain my purity until this contract ends?
Did you sleep with anyone after the Dream Officetel incident?
- What? - She's no joke.
Why must I answer that?
This is an invasion of privacy.
I'm not interested in your personal life.
I can only hire you as a psychic once I confirm that.
What nonsense is this?
The harmony between yin and yang is of the utmost importance.
If the psychic's yang is tainted,
they can't possess...
an unrested spirit with strong yin energy.
In the worst-case scenario, they could die.
He didn't sleep with anyone.
I've been by his side ever since that incident,
so I can confirm that.
But I wasn't there when he was with you, Ms. Hong.
- Did you two... - Have you gone insane?
Calm down.
So...
In any case, okay.
Since we've confirmed that you're a virgin,
stamp the contract.
A virgin?
- I'm not. - You are.
No, I'm not.
Don't say anything.
What? I didn't.
- Don't. - What?
I said, don't.
Accommodation. I found accommodations for us.
You virgin.
That little...
(We serve breakfast at 6:30am.)
(Changhwa Restaurant)
(Lodging available)
(50 years of tradition)
(New chef's selection every day)
Don't tell me this is it.
Go inside first.
The realty is right there, so it's easy to keep an eye on them.
And the chef cooks anything you want.
Hey, this is the room. Look.
It's an ondol room.
Nice. Hey, come take a look.
Ta-da!
Well, this looks nice.
But this is so not my style.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
(Daebak Realty)
Thank you for the food.
Okay.
Wait.
This is for our next month's meals.
We're always grateful.
And please let us know...
if your new tenants are doing something shady.
And still let us know even when they aren't doing anything shady.
Don't worry.
Bye.
Did you inhale that?
How can you inhale ribs?
Okay. Now.
Yes?
Now?
Okay.
Darn it.
Gosh. That was so close. She was almost there.
- Yes. - How did it go?
She didn't get to see it.
Should we scare the secretary one more time?
We tried that last time, but it didn't work.
Lee Eun Hye needs to see it herself for her to make a move.
Then, where are you now?
We're checking if a building is haunted or not.
I can't believe I'm doing something as ridiculous as this.
Why don't you just perform an exorcism?
Why do you have to check?
Hey, partner.
Ms. Hong.
I asked you a question. Why won't you answer it?
I told you earlier.
To perform an exorcism, I need the name of the unrested spirit.
Listen.
If you need the name, check the name on the lease.
Why go through this trouble?
It's a reasonable question to ask.
The tenant lived here without writing a lease...
and paid the rent upfront in cash for a year.
This tenant doesn't exist on paper.
A man who lived like a ghost died and became a spirit.
Didn't what I just said sound like a line from a poem?
Oh In Bum.
- I'm a CEO. - What?
Don't call me by my full name. Call me Mr. Oh.
We're partners. Let's show each other some respect.
Hey, Oh In Bum.
Unless you're going to keep quiet, just go home.
Gosh. The way you talk to me is quite hostile.
No partners start off on the right foot.
Don't you remember what Ms. Joo said?
You need me.
You need a special psychic.
A special psychic, my foot.
That's a load of nonsense.
What did she mean by I'm like your heating pack?
Why am I your heating pack?
I'd rather strap a heating pack on me instead.
By the way, why do you keep looking around?
Whenever spirits move around, they leave traces...
like footprints.
Gosh. To find out who that guy was,
you should go through his garbage. Goodness.
He had instant rice.
And he also drank.
It looks like he drank alone without any friends.
Goodness.
He had a lonely life.
Why are you looking at me?
Well,
you should be careful.
You might end up dying alone too.
Look who's talking. You're a virgin who doesn't even have a house.
It's you who might die on the streets.
Gosh. No, I've been with...
What was that?
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E05 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"Team Daebak"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
She must've gone crazy. What is she doing?
Turn around.
Show me your face.
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
Let me hold your hand for a bit.
What's that look on your face?
What?
What look?
It looks weird as if you have an ulterior motive.
You're unbelievable. You held my hand first.
I have my reasons.
Gosh.
- Of course, you do. - It's not what you think.
Whatever you have in mind, I assure you that's not it.
I can understand.
You held my hand,
but you don't want to admit your feelings.
It's not what you think.
When I hold your hand, my body temperature goes up.
So when you hold my hand, your body gets hot?
My goodness.
That was so bold I'm not even shy about it.
Let me explain this again.
My body temperature drops...
when I get close to an unrested spirit.
When I first started this job, I almost died from hypothermia.
That's why when I perform an exorcism,
I must bundle up as much as I can and finish as fast as I can.
But strangely, when I touch you...
When my body comes in contact with yours,
my low body temperature comes back up pretty quickly.
Does that only happen with me? Not with other psychics?
- Why is that? - I don't know that either.
Anyway, to me, you are...
A special psychic.
Okay. Let's say I believe that.
Forget it. Let's go.
I'm exhausted today.
Yes, Ms. Joo.
I saw his face.
- Eat a lot. - Thank you.
What about the art museum? Any progress?
I couldn't show the spirit of Chairman Kwon...
because Lee Eun Hye didn't show up.
I need to try again today.
Oh, right.
When I was waiting for her, I hacked into Britium's server.
Recently, someone turned off the security system...
and entered the exhibition hall.
- Who? - Lee Eun Hye.
- Lee Eun Hye? - Yes.
Something didn't feel right. So I looked into this.
There was a special clause in the insurance policy.
Even if the exhibition gets delayed, she makes profit, not a loss.
Do you think this whole thing could be staged?
No.
It makes no sense...
to damage the museum's reputation for some insurance money.
For now,
find all the recent CCTV footage.
If we search everywhere, I'm sure we'll find something.
What?
We ordered hangover soup.
We're out...
of cabbage leaves.
Then you should've told us when we ordered.
Whatever.
- Just eat it. - That's not nice.
What is this?
It's super delicious.
It really is delicious.
Good shot.
Nice shot, Director.
I haven't heard from you, so I thought you were very busy.
I guess you don't skip your morning exercise.
Was there a reason for me to contact you, Chairman Do?
I see.
I did receive a report about the Britium proposal.
I will go over it carefully and contact you.
I'm just worried,
especially now that Chairman Kwon is no longer around.
There's a time for everything.
Thank you for your concern.
Did you find out anything about Ms. Hong's mother?
I heard she died during a ritual.
- A ritual? - Yes.
How did she manage to kill himself?
Isn't it usually the possessed one who dies from getting beaten?
- Incense. - What?
Ms. Hong burned an incense first...
when she was preparing to do the exorcism.
Right, the incense in the expensive-looking bowl.
There must be something in it that causes hallucinations.
That's why I lost consciousness twice.
An exorcist who suddenly became aggravated...
while in a hallucinatory state died of a heart attack.
The client also died of side effects due to the hallucinations.
Ji Chul, we need to make a plan.
A plan?
(From sunset to sunrise)
From the outside, it looks like an ordinary realty office.
I know looks are important in this industry,
but these are really top quality for no good reason.
(Hanok Chicken Soup)
Next group, please come in.
Thank you. Next.
This helmet...
What?
She's going back home now?
Why aren't you picking up?
What's wrong with this?
I definitely charged it earlier.
Darn it.
(Who benefits from redevelopment? Wake up! Wake up!)
The phone is turned off.
- What? Why is your phone off? - Leave a message after...
I was scared for no reason.
Why is it so chilly whenever I come here, though?
What is that?
She should be more organized.
She has so many pairs of the same shoes.
Who is that?
What are you doing?
It's a problem if you do this while I'm not home.
You can't make a mess just because you're unhappy with it Mom!
- Mom? - You just hide after doing this?
My goodness.
Why did she take everything out?
I know you don't like these, Mom.
But each one has its own distinctive detail.
Why did you mix up the pairs?
My gosh.
Ms. Hong!
Are you in? Ms. Hong!
What is it?
Mr. Oh... In Bum has gone missing.
So?
I was wondering if he was here.
He's not. Look elsewhere.
I love you.
It was love at first sight.
It's so sexy how cold you are.
Your violent personality is just my type.
Please have me.
- Are you insane? - I am, right?
I must've gone insane.
Gosh, I even have a girlfriend.
Please forget that, Ji A.
I mean, Ms. Hong.
Then...
Goodbye.
Being beautiful is so tiring.
Darn it!
You startled me.
You should've called and let me know that she was home.
I did.
Anyway, where's the incense?
Don't you know who I am?
What is he talking about?
Take it.
Don't joke around. I'm not in a good mood.
What is that?
I swear I checked it before taking it.
It was definitely the incense.
Are you okay?
Maybe there really is a spirit.
- I couldn't even reach you. - There is no such thing.
What could it be?
(Daebak Realty)
Couldn't we have met somewhere else?
Welcome, Deputy Director Kwon.
- Isn't the view breathtaking? - I guess.
Has Eun Hye given you...
an answer yet?
It's only natural for her to hesitate...
since I offered her half the original amount.
Isn't half a bit too harsh?
Thirty percent,
and she would've resigned for sure.
You're more of a coward...
than I thought you were.
- What did you say? - In a redeveloping neighborhood,
you'll see houses...
that have red flags outside.
Do you know what they are?
They're people who are refusing the redevelopment.
I see.
Until now,
every single one of them eventually put down their flags.
Director Lee has also put up a flag at the moment.
However,
that won't work against me.
You should relax for the time being.
He's the one we saw in Mullae-dong.
The autopsy result said that the cause of death was...
a cerebral concussion.
However, he was already in the final stage of lung cancer.
The approximated time of death is a month ago.
What's his name.
They can't identify him...
because his fingerprints have worn away.
According to the landlord, he was an artist.
- None of his paintings are... - Where did they get that file?
Even I couldn't hack into the NFS.
- Just in case... - I bet someone's on the take.
There's not much.
You two.
If you have something to say, come here and say it.
Should we?
If you give me that file, I could look into him.
Really?
Do it then.
Nice catch.
- What should I look into first? - His name.
Okay.
But how can you find something that even the police couldn't?
Just leave it to me.
Using just a shadow caught in a photo online,
I was the first person to find out...
that world stars Jung Jae Hoon and Kim Sae Hee were dating.
Why is he so enthusiastic about this?
It's the power of love.
What do you mean?
Beats me. What does she mean?
This is all because of you.
Let's end it here.
I'll go to Britium myself and identify him.
Goodbye.
Britium?
(Cho Hyun Seo's Private Exhibition)
Weren't we talking about Mullae-dong?
So why are we here?
Because it's the same unrested spirit.
I doubt that's true.
Why? Because you two made up the one here at Britium?
Come on. That's a bit harsh.
You know our plan fell apart because of you.
Where did I see this?
Where was it again?
That's Mullae-dong.
Judging by the accuracy,
the artist must've painted it there.
Did this artist know Cho Hyun Seo?
Or could it be...
How great are they to call me over at this late hour?
I'm sorry. This is important.
He must be the living legend of Korean art.
Mr. Cho Hyun Seo, it's an honor.
Thank you.
Gosh, you have smooth hands.
I guess you took great care of them since you're so famous.
Ma'am, who are they?
She's Ms. Hong Ji A, a realtor.
And as you both know, this is Cho Hyun Seo.
Please ask him.
What's the model's name in that painting of yours?
I know you're a realtor,
but don't you know what self-portraits are?
Cho Hyun Seo. That's me.
I'm talking about the real model.
What do you mean? A real model?
Do you want to get sued for defamation?
Don't get mad. I'll talk to him.
Ms. Hong!
Is she crazy? That's a priceless painting!
Why can't she be gentler?
You...
How dare you ruin my work?
- Do you know how much it costs? - I don't care.
Just tell me his name.
Tell me who the real painter is.
I paint my own work.
I'm Cho Hyun Seo!
Ask me that question one more time,
and I'll...
Twenty years of finger-painting will wear away your fingerprints.
Yet you claim to have painted all those paintings...
with these fine hands?
It hurts. Let me go first.
Tell me...
who this man is.
I don't know.
You saw an unrested spirit in that painting, didn't you?
No.
Do you want to be tormented by the unrested spirit...
for the rest of your life?
Or do you want to tell me his name so that I can exorcise him?
Kim Byung Ho.
Well, you see...
He was a temporary assistant of mine.
I didn't know that scumbag had drawn...
under my painting like that.
I believe your assistant's painting is the best one you've had.
- Director Lee. - But then again,
that painting won't be shown to anyone.
Right.
I'll take full responsibility and take care of it.
Of course, you will.
And as for all of my paintings in my studio,
I'll hand all of them to your museum.
Of course, you're required to do so as per contract.
You must retire.
Pardon?
What do you mean?
When people find out that you had a ghost artist,
the prestige of my museum will be destroyed...
as we've been sponsoring your art.
You are the fraud.
Why must my museum suffer the loss?
I'm Cho Hyun Seo.
How could you cut ties with me because of a mere...
You deceived me. This isn't a mere incident.
Just focus on your special exhibition for now.
Afterward,
you will retire...
quietly with your honor intact.
(Director Lee Eun Hye)
Who does she think she is? How dare she tell me to retire?
She doesn't even know what good art is.
She's no more than a lowly businesswoman. Darn her.
Darn it. Why isn't this working?
What's this? What's happening?
Oh, no. What's this?
How did you know that...
there was another painting behind the painting?
Don't tell me you could see through it.
- What? - Whatever I find out on the job...
is strictly confidential. That's my rule.
I see.
Just like how doctors and clients keep confidential information?
I see. So you're a professional like those people.
If you exploit the information you found out today,
you might die.
Why do you keep making death threats?
Fine.
Okay. I won't.
Gosh.
The name of the ghost artist is Kim Byung Ho.
Cho Hyun Seo said so himself.
Gather any evidence you can find.
I think we hit the jackpot.
Are you coming?
I'm coming.
- Did you look into it? - Yes. I did.
Cho Hyun Seo has two cell phones under his name.
- Two? - Yes.
So I tracked his phones.
He carries one with him.
And the other stays in only one location.
Yes! Hello.
- Take the food already. - Okay.
What? We ordered soft tofu.
Do you know how heavy the pots for soft tofu are?
You are only a few steps away from the restaurant.
Why did you make me deliver the food? What a hassle.
Wait. But...
She didn't say anything when we ordered our food.
But seriously? This smells awesome.
- All right. Let's eat. - Let's eat.
- Here. - Okay.
Yes.
All right.
So Cho Hyun Seo has two phones under his name?
One of the phones...
never left Mullae-dong.
That must be it.
That was the phone the ghost artist was using.
Videos were...
automatically backed up on the cloud from that phone.
(Videos)
There are over a hundred videos.
I don't think Cho Hyun Seo has any idea about these videos.
If he did, he would've deleted them. This exposes him as a fake.
He wouldn't have kept them.
Goodness. The ghost artist...
must have taken the videos to blackmail Cho Hyun Seo.
But he ended up dead before he could do that.
Then, I ought to fulfill the desire of the late painter.
This place is grand.
- Oh, no. - What is it?
I'm good. Let's go inside.
Darn it.
That darned jerk.
Is that it?
You will get the remaining 113 videos...
once you pay us.
This is odd. It seems less than I was expecting.
Is it just me?
I'll give you...
the rest of the money...
once you get rid of all the spirits here.
I heard that you guys get rid of spirits. Right?
I see.
That's why this place became a melting pot of religions.
But that's too bad.
The lady you saw the other day, Ms. Hong, handles the exorcisms.
Then, get her here now.
Call her now.
Call Ms. Hong now.
Seeing how you're changing your stance,
I guess you're okay with the videos going viral.
Let's go, Chief Heo.
He's back. He's back again.
Don't go. Don't leave me.
Do something before you leave!
I'll give you all of my money.
I'll give you all the money. Please don't leave.
Really? I should sit down, then.
What are you doing? Sit down.
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E06 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"The Artist"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Mine.
All of it!
They're all mine.
In Bum.
Hey, In Bum.
He's coming.
How did you know...
I told you if you exploit this, you'd die.
What?
Gosh. What was that?
Gosh. What just happened?
(Yongin Police Station)
So when you arrived, the incident already happened.
But how did you find that place?
A client asked me to go there.
What's your client's name?
Director Lee Eun Hye of Britium.
Lee Eun Hye.
Britium?
- Just let her go. - What?
You can go.
I spoke with Britium's legal representative already.
Wrap it up.
Wait, Ms. Hong, what about us?
Ms. Hong, Ms. Hong!
Don't call after her.
We didn't do anything wrong, so we'll be released soon.
I doubt that.
Why did you hit Cho Hyun Seo?
Come on. That wasn't hitting.
We were negotiating well and the mood was nice.
Are you really going to insist when we have evidence?
Evidence?
What is this?
What? When did he grab that?
The woman who works there...
even gave eyewitness testimony.
Chief Heo,
say something.
But I passed out, so I don't remember much.
Why are you trembling?
Ji Chul.
Earlier, when I...
I'm sorry.
But you were really scary earlier.
It was like you were someone else.
Oh, no.
Hey, are you all right?
He's bleeding. What if it's serious?
- What am I doing here? - Are you crazy, kid?
Did you do this?
- No, it wasn't me. - If it wasn't you, then who was it?
- Look at him. - How dare you lie to us.
Where are your parents?
Why, this little...
Grandma.
You were a psychic?
If you were born a psychic, this must've happened often.
You're special.
Am I really a psychic?
I was really possessed by spirits?
That's absurd.
My goodness.
Oh In Bum. I don't care how greedy he is for money.
But how can he rush in like that without even thinking twice?
Once a fraud, always a fraud.
Heat or no heat, I'll kick him out as soon as this exorcism is over.
What will you do about the exorcism anyhow?
Did you find a way to do it?
I'll have to lure the spirit in with his work.
He is obsessed with his artworks, after all.
Then we'll have to do it in Cho's studio or at Britium.
Britium appears to have taken every single piece of art...
in Cho Hyun Seo's studio.
Lee Eun Hye moves fast.
So that just leaves Britium.
I'm sure Director Lee...
will never allow us to do exorcism in the same place as the artworks.
I don't need her permission.
The exorcism will be performed at the Mullae-dong studio.
If the spirit has been unable to leave this place,
it means there is another painting hidden here somewhere.
Ms. Joo, I found the painting.
Okay, then I'll take care of the rest.
This is Dongfang meiren.
It's excellent quality.
When I became Director of Britium, I received it as a gift.
To this day, it remains my favorite tea.
I thought it would suit you perfectly,
and I was right.
How long has it been? Ten years?
I do hear news from Chairman Han once in a while.
Chairman Han, of the Masan investment firm?
Not only is he a VVIP of Daebak Realty,
but he's also our secret salesperson.
He appeared to have great faith in Ms. Hong's skills.
Yes, as you'll soon see for yourself, Director Lee.
Does that mean you will take on...
the sale of Britium?
It is the sale of Korea's finest art museum.
Of course, we accept.
However,
would you be willing to grant us just one small favor?
Out. You're being released with a warning.
Get in.
- I don't want to. - Thank you.
Wait, what about me?
I'm not in the car yet.
What are you doing? Chief Heo didn't get in.
It's dangerous for ordinary people to be around when we're working.
Work?
Are we going to do an exorcism right now?
I absolutely refuse.
Then stuff yourself on jail food for attempted murder.
Are you blackmailing me?
Turn the car around.
I'd rather eat jail food then.
You believe it now, right?
That you're a psychic.
Please, of course not.
When we first signed our contract, you did not believe...
that you were a psychic, nor that unrested spirits exist.
That's how you were able to sign the contract so freely.
Isn't that right?
That's right. I still don't believe it.
There's no such thing as ghosts.
Then why are you saying you don't want to work?
If there are no spirits...
and all my exorcisms are fake,
why are you suddenly so scared to join me on an exorcism?
What are you doing?
Hostage negotiations to lure the unrested spirit out.
Blackmail, in a way.
You just stand there...
and when I say so, take your necklace off.
If I...
take this off...
I'll take care of the rest.
He came quickly.
Now. Take off the necklace.
Hurry!
Why are you trembling?
- Where are your parents? - Where are they?
I can't do it.
I don't want a spirit...
- to take over my body again. - Hey.
We don't have much time.
You were right.
I've experienced this many times in the past.
I've finally realized...
that I was possessed.
Do you know how many times I woke up with bloody hands?
I don't want that to happen...
anymore.
(Sell Your Haunted House)
This is what you made your psychics do to make money?
That's assault!
That's exactly why you should've taken it off.
Due to that artist's memory, I become teary-eyed all the time.
Ask Director Lee to return one of his paintings.
He's already dead.
What are you doing? You're scaring me.
No way! I just painted...
one of Cho Hyun Seo's pictures. The greatest painter of all time.
Oh In Bum is here to sell the painting.
Oh In Bum, that little...
Are all your clients' requests stored here?
Why do you ask?
We're dealing with spirits here.
Does that mean neither the client nor the exorcist is safe?
Mom... Mom, I'm sorry.