Now. Take off the necklace.
I can't do it. I won't.
You can do it. You have to.
I don't want to do this, Mom.
Ji A, are you awake?
Auntie.
What happened to Mom?
Call me if you need any help. Anytime, okay?
Mom died because of me, didn't she?
No, that's not true.
Mom told me to stab the ghost,
but I was too scared to do it.
You were right.
I've experienced this many times in the past.
I always thought I was sleepwalking.
I've finally realized that I was possessed.
Do you know how many times I woke up with bloody hands?
I don't want that to happen...
anymore.
You'll never wake up...
with bloody hands again.
I won't let that happen.
Trust me and take the necklace off.
Ji Won,
once the surgery succeeds,
we can go home.
I'll organize everything.
Ji Won,
how can I leave you...
all alone?
I have to go home.
Home?
Why would someone who died at home become a wandering spirit?
What was it...
that just entered my body?
The memories that the spirit could not let go of, even in death.
Please come again.
Why did you tear it off when I was going to take it off?
I was getting emotionally prepared.
That's assault!
That's exactly why you should've taken it off when I told you to.
I was going to.
Even if you hadn't done that, I would've taken it off.
What is this?
What an embarrassing sight, crying like a baby.
What's there to cry about?
Hey, mister, it's not like that.
This isn't me crying.
I know.
That's a side effect.
A side effect?
Once the unrested spirit's memory enters your body,
even after the exorcism is over,
those memories and habits remain in you for a while.
You should stay home for a week instead of going out.
You should've told me that!
It's in the contract.
The contract...
How long did you say it lasts?
A week? It's not forever, is it?
The emotions gradually wear away.
But the memories stay.
So this painful memory will last forever?
This memory of a stranger's?
This is what you made your psychics do to make money?
Gosh, you're really cruel.
You don't even pay us that much.
The unrested spirit's memory...
shouldn't be absorbed by the psychic.
What are you talking about?
Usually, the exorcist is the one who absorbs it.
But whenever I perform exorcisms with you,
you absorb their memory.
I told you this the day we first met.
I see. So is that why you asked to work together?
You coldhearted woman.
You're the one who mentioned it first.
Do you not remember that either?
Like I said, it's best to stay home.
Oh In Bum.
What is it this time?
Eat your favorite dishes, watch your favorite shows,
and buy whatever you like.
Try to take your mind off of it.
Good work today.
(Daebak Realty)
How long...
have you been doing this?
Ten years.
Why?
It must've been tough.
I've only done it once, and it's already unbearable.
But you've been doing this singlehandedly for that long.
You did great today as well, Ms. Hong.
(Daebak Realty)
(Great work today. I ordered your favorite.)
Great work today.
I ordered your favorite.
Eat up and have a good rest.
Oh, gosh.
Check out my reflexes. I saved the chicken.
You want me to carry them one by one safely?
Making several trips is a hassle.
Move aside, so I can pass.
Forget it.
I'll walk around you, my gosh.
Darn it.
It's...
Gosh, you could've moved.
Gosh.
Let's eat.
This looks delicious.
- So this was why. - What?
What do you mean?
Kids from my neighborhood never played with me.
Some of them threw stones at me...
while others ran away crying.
The look on their faces...
was the same one as yours.
It's okay.
Even my grandma said...
that I was possessed...
and that it was my fate.
She'd curse at me.
I thought it was ridiculous.
But she was right.
I'm sorry.
You know that I'm a scaredy-cat.
Do understand. Please?
I'll never be afraid of you ever again. I promise.
Are you still...
scared of me?
No.
What do you want to do?
Do you want to quit here?
No.
I still don't know why my uncle had this.
I must find out.
Having chicken and beer after work is the best.
It must've been tough.
I've only done it once, and it's already unbearable.
But you've been doing it singlehandedly for that long.
I guess he's not that bad of a guy after all.
Don't you think so?
What's your problem? Is this fun for you?
You keep startling me.
I finished all of them.
Got it.
I've been possessed.
No matter what you hear, do not come downstairs.
Understood?
No.
Don't go.
No!
Come to your senses, Hong Ji A!
Snap out of it.
Hurry.
Wake up, Hong Ji A.
This isn't real.
Wake up.
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E07 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"Side Effect"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Mom...
Mom... I'm sorry...
Sorry, Mom.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Sorry. I'm sorry, Mom.
Ms. Hong!
Open up.
(Daebak Realty)
Ms. Hong!
I know you're inside. Come on.
Ms. Hong.
Hey, Hong Ji A!
"Hey, Hong Ji A"?
Why did you pretend you weren't in?
- What is it? - Don't treat me like a stranger.
Open up.
Unless it's urgent, let's talk later tonight.
Wait.
This is urgent.
My heart is breaking because of the painter's memories.
Gosh. I can neither eat nor sleep.
And I'm crying all the time.
Gosh. I'm about to cry again.
Just give it a week.
I explained everything to you yesterday.
You said you would take care of it.
Take responsibility for what you said!
What? You look awful.
- Shouldn't you go see a doctor? - Be quiet. Just come in.
Go ahead.
Pardon?
You wanted a solution.
Punching the sandbag until I forget the deceased's memories is...
my solution.
Is there another solution that's non-violent?
I'm a delicate guy.
Then, punch it delicately.
You can't just leave like that.
Sorry. It was urgent.
Sorry. It was urgent for me as well.
Urgent? What do you mean?
I told you. When I touch you...
When my body comes in contact with yours,
my body temperature comes back to normal.
Oh, that? Then, you must be grateful to me.
You must do something to help the psychic you are grateful to.
What do you want me to do?
I don't know. Do something!
Do you know what happened to me last night?
(Administration, Prescription Pickup Counter)
Excuse me.
Who are you?
- Pardon? - Pardon?
Gosh. How did I end up here?
I came here to see her, but I'm leaving now.
- Wait. - Yes?
Can you give this to Choi Ji Won's guardian?
He has a wife?
They didn't register their marriage, but they were practically married.
And his wife is very sick now.
She needs to get the surgery,
but the money...
I've given this some thought.
Let's ask Director Lee to give back one of his paintings.
Returning a painting means...
that she's acknowledging that there was a ghost painter.
There's no reason she would take that big of a risk.
- Come on! - Hey.
When you punched it, you pretended it was my face, right?
Given the circumstance, we should get the media involved.
If we disclose Kim Byung Ho's videos online,
Britium will be an accomplice in this grand fraud case...
and face a huge monetary loss.
And I'm sure you will be in a tight spot since you signed...
an NDA with her.
The grand fraud case.
You don't have the videos, do you?
You didn't even watch the videos, did you?
The videos? I deleted all of them.
Every single one of them.
Ms. Hong told us to erase all of them...
when she got us out.
Gosh. No way.
Do you think I'd bluff without the videos?
Gosh. Come on.
Didn't you see a yellow ginkgo tree in his painting?
He drew that in because his wife likes that.
But...
Just pretend that you watched a very sad movie.
As you can't change the plot of a movie,
there's nothing we can do.
He's already dead, anyway.
But Choi Ji Won is alive!
Performing an exorcism isn't just for the unrested spirit.
It's also for the people who are left behind.
They must go on their lives.
Say something.
Gosh.
He was incredibly talented,
but he only led a life of suffering.
You offered me a good deal.
I am happy to do business with you.
It's an honor that both of you are satisfied.
All right. I'll get going now.
Ms. Hong. I'll count on you again next time.
I'll say goodbye here.
Good luck with your business.
I made sure the backed-up videos were deleted.
It's up to you to decide if you want to delete...
these videos as well.
So you are telling me...
that the unrested spirit will no longer show up here.
That's right.
I took care of it for good.
My husband wanted to be a painter at first.
As he couldn't fulfill his dream,
Britium had a special place in his heart.
Expanding the museum was his last wish as well.
In the end,
he left too soon to see that.
Was your husband happy?
I know that you were hoping...
that the unrested spirit here would be him.
I wanted to see him one last time...
even if it was just his spirit.
But he didn't show up.
How cold.
People who led happy lives don't remain as unrested spirits.
The fact that you can't see his spirit proves...
that he led a happy life with you.
They didn't register their marriage, but they were practically married.
And his wife is very sick now.
Those paintings belong to Kim Byung Ho.
Of course, his wife deserves to have one.
Mr. Kim had a wife.
Mr. Kim often painted yellow gingko trees...
because that was his wife's favorite tree.
As for the self-portrait,
he painted it for himself.
Can you at least give it back to his wife?
That is all you have to say to me, right?
That was embarrassing.
I never ask for favors. This is all Oh In Bum's fault.
Why did I embarrass myself like that?
At that price, we could have totally matched it.
You should have told me.
I thought...
you were waiting for the price to fall further.
I assumed you had missed your chance, Chairman Do.
Perhaps it just wasn't meant to be.
Please have your tea before it cools.
If you don't drink it at the right moment,
you can no longer appreciate the full effect of the taste.
It's bitter.
What is this?
In Bum, what are you doing? You're scaring me.
Hey, don't come near me. Go away.
What's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
- Blood. - Blood?
- What did you do? - Blood, it's blood!
What is all this?
It's a side effect of being possessed.
How can you live like this?
- Wait a minute. - What is it?
Just now, I've created a Kim Byung Ho,
no, a painting by Cho Hyun Seo.
The greatest painter of all time.
- Right? - Right.
If it's a Cho Hyun Seo piece...
That's amazing.
These side effects aren't just a bad thing.
With this, we can take care of Choi Ji Won's surgery.
Are you kidding me? Choi Ji Won?
Why would we take care of a stranger's surgery fee?
Because I feel like I have to take care...
of that stranger in order for me to live on.
Whenever I picture that face,
my heart...
Here it comes again.
The tears are streaming down.
Anyway,
this is how I'll survive.
And as for the painting,
I can just make another one.
That's true.
If you can create more paintings with these hands,
you're a goose that lays golden eggs!
Find out who has a ton of cash at hand...
in this industry.
Okay, just wait a moment.
Are you really not going?
Secretary Joo, you go instead.
So many spirits gather in places with crowds.
Okay.
You're here.
You've come.
Yes.
Thank you.
Is Oh In Bum doing well?
No.
He went to the museum to sell a painting.
He went to sell what?
The mood is so classy here.
That's great.
- Look at that one. - This is from Germany.
The color is exquisite.
- I'll see you later. - See you soon.
- All right. - Goodbye.
- Long time no see, Hwa Jung. - Oh, hello.
Are you still working at that shabby shop?
- Any desire to come back? - What?
Work here is just so fun.
How did they manage to captivate you so much?
I thought you said you weren't coming.
- Have you seen Oh In Bum? - No.
What?
Who was that beauty?
The CEO of our shabby shop.
Ms. Hong, fancy seeing you here.
I heard you took care of Director Lee's business well.
Good work.
(Special Exhibit of Kim Byung Ho, the Tragic Genius)
The painter Kim Byung Ho had no education and no connections.
He had to live for twenty years as the ghost painter...
of the well-educated and well-connected artist,
Cho Hyun Seo.
What is that?
- What? - Isn't that?
She's saying they weren't real?
- What? - What is this?
She said she couldn't do this so cut and dry,
but she convinced Director Lee in the end.
The truth...
was only revealed...
- after the painter passed away. - I spent a lot of time...
working on my art,
and today, with this prize,
I feel I have been rewarded for the time and effort...
I have poured into my work.
This piece won Cho Hyun Seo the Grand Prize at this art exhibit.
But before that,
when it was submitted under Kim Byung Ho's name,
it did not even qualify in the preliminary rounds.
Here at Britium,
even if we must reveal our own flaws,
we believe that revealing the truth...
would be to pay our final respects to the deceased.
We sincerely apologize...
to everyone here, as well as to artist Kim Byung Ho.
- That was shocking. - This is insane.
- I can't believe it. - Really?
Cho Hyun Seo fled.
It doesn't matter what country.
Just get one that leaves the soonest.
Fancy meeting you here,
Artist Cho.
Darn it.
Are you insane, you jerk?
Do you want to die? You want to die?
Mr. Cho Hyun Seo.
You're under arrest for the murder of Kim Byung Ho.
- Murder? - What?
Not fraud?
Do you have proof?
Yes, we have video footage of you killing Mr. Kim.
- A video? - That's impossible.
I deleted everything.
What?
You want 200,000 dollars? You must be insane.
You're not in your right mind.
Did you start gambling behind my back?
That's how much they're worth.
My pieces.
My pieces?
You think that's the value of your work?
It's the value of my reputation, the reputation of Cho Hyun Seo.
If you try to sell your work without my name attached,
you won't even get 200 dollars for them.
But I...
They said I'm in the final stages of lung cancer.
I'm dying.
For the sake of our relationship,
could you please buy just one of my pieces...
at the proper value?
I really need that money.
- The final stages of lung cancer? - With the time I have left,
I want to return to my hometown...
and spend it with my wife.
Hold on.
Lung cancer?
What will happen to me if you die?
What about me?
- What are you doing? - Move aside. These are all mine.
Move. They're mine.
Hold on.
No, not this one.
Move aside.
No! Please! Not this one!
Move! It's mine! Move!
I said, move!
Hey.
Hey. What's wrong with you?
Darn it!
No. Wait.
That's not what happened. Wait.
I'd like to sincerely thank all of you for coming.
She turned the worst case into something favorable.
She's indeed amazing.
Hello.
I didn't think you'd tell the truth.
I wasn't going to.
But...
Please.
What you said...
reminded me of what my husband said.
Every time he saw Kim Byung Ho's work,
he said it felt like a love letter...
even if the painting...
only showed scenery.
I didn't think too much of it since he was an emotional person.
But after speaking with you,
I thought it was only right...
to send those letters to the original recipient.
It seemed like the last favor I could do for my husband.
The reporters are waiting.
I hope you enjoy the party.
Did you know beforehand?
- Had you agreed on it? - No.
- Oh In Bum. - What?
He came here to sell the work...
he had painted while being possessed.
Have you seen him?
Oh, my gosh.
He's gone totally insane. How could he think of such a thing?
I might as well just kill him.
Where could he be?
Right.
I saw that Chairman Han from the Masan investment firm...
had come with an appraiser.
Among the videos we had found, one of them had recorded the murder.
How did you miss that?
There were 113 videos.
How could I have checked all of them?
We have decided to give...
- Kim Byung Ho's wife, - Hold on.
- What is it? - Choi Ji Won,
all of her late husband's work without anything in return.
Hey, Britium just announced that they'll give Choi Ji Won...
all of her husband's work.
- What? - She'll be filthy rich now!
That means she'll finally be able to receive surgery.
The money I got for this painting...
is all ours.
You better not back out and say that your heart is breaking.
Don't you worry.
Check out the townhouse you wanted. The biggest one at that.
Oh, yes!
Living a righteous life has paid off.
It's authentic, sir.
You wanted me to pay in cash, right?
Correct.
Here you go.
(To my beloved wife, Ji Won)
Here.
- What are you doing? - Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
When did I write that?
Let go of it.
This is your only chance to sell this.
What should I do?
- Ms. Hong. - I'm sorry to tell you this, sir.
But the painting you just purchased is fake.
What are you talking about?
Didn't you purchase one of Kim Byung Ho's paintings?
That lunatic refused to sell it and left.
You're...
finally home.
I'm sorry, Ji Won,
for taking so long.
(2021 Mullae-dong 55)
Is this it?
What's wrong with me?
It was so easy to paint last time.
You said it was easy to paint another one.
You said it was a cakewalk.
So what...
What is this?
Do something, will you?
Gosh. This can't be happening.
Short padded jackets are in trend these days.
That's perfect in length. Just what I needed.
(Oh In Bum)
We won't be having another deal.
- What is it? - Why is the habit already gone?
You said it'd at least last a week.
You're complaining about that?
If you're done talking, hang up. I'm busy.
Wait!
Is there no way to retrieve the habit?
Perhaps, a spell or...
What is this lunatic rambling about?
- It's all sold out. - It's all sold out.
Great job. Congratulations to all.
I hope you wear them well.
Now that we've sold them all, we're going to go now.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Oh In Bum, that little...
What? What did she say?
She hung up.
Let's go and ask Ms. Choi to give back the painting.
I'm sure she will once she hears our story.
She must be rich now.
How could I tell her that?
That her husband's posthumous painting was...
a fake painting that I drew?
Gosh. I can't tell her that.
Then, what are we going to do?
Without that, we won't be able to buy a townhouse!
(Daebak Realty)
Hello, Ms. Joo!
Don't act like a thug.
You checked that I wired the fee.
You look beautiful today as always.
You guys make a lot of money. Why don't you install a smart lock?
Hey.
Gosh. Is this where you keep all of your case files?
Why do you ask?
Just because.
They are important only to me. They aren't worth a penny.
Why would you say something like that?
I might be a fraud, but I don't steal from people.
Frauds and thieves are the same.
They are totally different.
- How are they different? - Look them up online.
Both of you, stop.
- You're being childish. - I agree.
That's enough.
Let's have a get-together. We just closed a big case.
- I won't be attending. - No.
Let's go.
This is some good food!
I should send a photo to my darling.
"Darling"?
I didn't know you had a girlfriend.
- What? - "What"?
Everybody, raise your glasses.
Ms. Hong.
This is our first get-together. Please make a toast.
Is she a principal or what?
No need to make a big speech in front of three people.
When we die, let's hope we don't become unrested spirits.
Cheers.
Ms. Hong. I have a question.
The previous part-time psychic got injured.
Could something bad happen to me...
- even after an exorcism? - Yes.
Really? Are you sure?
Some even die.
Ms. Hong, stop joking.
He'll believe you. You'll scare him away.
Gosh. Why would you lie about that?
I don't lie.
This job requires us to handle spirits.
Anyone can get hurt anytime...
because of a variable we didn't see coming.
Anyone?
Does that mean neither the client nor the exorcist is safe?
- I mean... - What's up with so many questions?
I need to know these things. We are partners.
We are not partners. The contract is over.
Over?
You wanted to work only until you saved 20,000 dollars.
Don't you remember that?
Today's dinner was a farewell party, not a welcome party.
What are you doing? Don't be so rash.
We made a good team.
Do you want to perform an exorcism,
shivering in cold without this special psychic?
What are you talking about?
I've been doing fine without you.
What about Chief Heo?
What?
You know what?
He was so happy that he was making money with an honest job.
Do you want him to scam people again?
This is the first job I never had to lie about to my girlfriend.
I'll work really hard, Ms. Hong.
Don't cry.
They sound really desperate.
Let's work with them for just one more month.
Not you too, Ms. Joo.
Ms. Hong, you're not the one who has to hire a new psychic.
Hyung Sik's leg fracture will heal in a month.
Let's work with them until then.
Just one more month.
- That's perfect. - That's perfect.
Let's celebrate our extension and solemnly raise our glasses.
Let's not be unrested spirits after death.
- Cheers! - Cheers!
[VIU Ver] KBS2 E08 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"The Truth Unraveled"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Excuse me.
I want to put my house on the market.
I'm sorry. We don't handle regular listings.
Someone referred your services to me.
I heard that you guys help sell haunted houses.
Please take a seat.
Please tell us in detail.
Did someone recently die in your house...
or did you kill someone recently?
- Pardon? - Given the nature of our job,
we must ask this question.
I'm sure you'll understand.
I see.
From what I know, nothing of the sort happened.
But we keep seeing the spirit.
My wife has been having a hard time, so we want to sell it.
Nice.
One day,
all the cabinet doors under the sink and drawers were open.
That scared the wits out of me.
This house is new. It's nice.
If you sell the house not long after buying it,
you'll end up paying taxes twice. It'd be a loss.
We're in our 60s and this is the first house we bought.
It's so upsetting.
Oh, right. Where are my manners? I should serve you some drinks.
- Let's go. - Already?
Are you leaving already?
Why don't you have some drinks before you go? Please?
That's so cold.
Your hand is freezing. What's going on?
- Is there an unrested spirit? - Why do you think I held your hand?
Sometimes,
some spirits don't even know they're dead.
Green Villas completed sales of its apartments three months ago.
Before that, it was a mulberry field for a long time.
I saw an advertisement for that place.
Dohak Construction?
Aren't they the ones redeveloping this whole area?
No one around the client has died recently.
That's why I looked more into the building.
There were some messy businesses.
I thought our client was the first one to move in,
but some people lived there before he did.
Because the apartment was vacant for so long,
they bought it at 30 percent off from a secondary agency.
But Dohak Construction, which was the original owner,
said this was illegal and forcibly evicted the residents.
So if any of the victims died,
there's a good chance they became unrested spirits.
Logically, if we just look at which of the residents...
received money in their accounts,
can't we figure it out right away?
It's not as easy as you think.
Mirae Design says they sent money to Dohak Construction,
and Dohak Construction says they never received the money.
But President Hwang of Mirae Design disappeared,
and the trial has been suspended.
So President Hwang lied.
What about the victims who have to wait for the trial's verdict?
What a scumbag.
What about the list of victims?
There are 12 households and 50 individuals.
We'll have to find out if any of them have died.
That will only take a day, right?
- Me? - Why?
Didn't you have the skill to find an all-star couple by their shadows?
Of course. I can do it.
(Dohak Construction)
Head to the redevelopment area.
It doesn't matter how I die.
The Chairman is coming today,
so let's try our best!
Yes, boss!
(Daebak Realty)
Let's get the restaurant first.
All right.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
I'm sorry.
Ji Chul!
Who are you?
Who else? It's me.
So you've been hiding in my area all along.
I'm not sure if that's bold or fearless.
Being bold is being fearless.
You're right.
You're laughing?
Why do you keep nitpicking instead of apologizing?
I'm sorry.
What are we sorry for?
You should be sorry.
You scammed me so fearlessly.
What do you mean, scammed you?
I got rid of that ghost for you. Nice and clean.
That ghost?
You're the ones who made up that ghost.
You should pay people more.
The one who played the ghost told me everything.
I told you we shouldn't use a part-timer to play the ghosts.
I really didn't think she was that kind of person.
Yes, sure you didn't.
- I knew it as soon as I saw her. - Hey!
If you play around in front of me from now on,
I'll kill you.
Okay.
I'll return the 50,000 dollars we got for that job.
- What's your account number? - What about interest?
How much is the interest?
Let me see.
300,000 dollars. Plus the original amount.
- That's robbery! - Robbery?
Some people never can accept interest terms without a beating.
Hey, help them accept it.
No, no.
Ms. Hong, Ms. Hong!
Get out of the way.
How dare you block my way to eat?
Hey.
What?
Those two.
We still have something left to discuss.
- Ma'am! - Go ahead.
We don't have anything left to talk about. Sir.
That punk.
It's the chairman.
Attention, greetings.
- Hello, Chairman. - Hello, Chairman.
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be at the realty office.
It's just...
She is CEO Hong of Daebak Realty.
Please help me.
Sometimes...
some spirits don't even know they're dead.
(Sell Your Haunted House)
You want me to investigate your mother's final client?
Are you sure that's him?
How did you do this work for ten years?
If it were me, I'd already have killed a few people.
You should finish what you've started.
What's this sudden change in attitude?
Are you the same Ms. Hong who told me to do nothing?
I'm just preparing for the unexpected.
I did suffer a bit because of some exorcist frauds lately.
You're not talking about me, are you?
Being a psychic is such an extreme job.
More than that, you know we can't get caught by Ms. Hong.
I don't want to die either.
- Here it is. - What are you doing here?