♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 16=
My dad told me
that Support Branch Soul Masters
aren't strong fighters,
so what we need to do
is to find a partner
whom we can entrust our life.
Only then can we
make full use
of our power.
I've been thinking
where I can
find a partner like this.
By hiring them?
By entering into contracts?
Neither is the answer.
If you were to entrust with life,
that's impossible to do so.
But when I came all the way here,
I've figured it all out.
Like Ou Si Ke,
he entrusted his life to his partners.
In exchange, they now shared
a common destiny.
If you don't abandon them
in desperation,
they will never give up on you.
So what?
In the end, they will all die.
But...
But if you are
unwilling to give,
how could you expect them
to treat you with sincerity?
They're dead.
What's the point of saying these?
Stop!
Sir, you're here.
Human Faced Demon Spider's legs
grow as the years go by.
Judging from its legs,
it had lived for 2,000 years.
Great.
No, it's not.
According to my calculation,
the limit of your Third Soul Ring
is around 1,700 years.
It has
exceeded your limit.
If you forcibly absorb it,
you'll die for sure.
Sir, I have no choice.
Tomorrow, Du Gu Yan, a Soul Master
will go to Star Forest.
She plans to kill a Soul Beast,
and level up to Triple Soul Rings.
[Your mission is
to find a way to meet her]
and break this bottle
in front of her.
What does she look like?
She'll wear a cherry
blossom petal on her head.
You will recognize her immediately.
It's you.
Do you know me?
Kid,
you heard what he said.
You can't withstand this Soul Ring.
Let's negotiate.
Give the Human Faced Demon Spider to me.
But I'm the one who killed it.
No one can absorb it
other than me.
I know.
All I want is its corpse.
Its blood contains notorious poison,
and is able to attract
poisonous Soul Beasts,
for which it's perfect for this young lady.
However,
if you absorb its Soul Ring,
the corpse would disappear.
Of course,
I'm not taking advantage of you.
If you leave it here,
I promise
to capture another
Soul Beast that suits you,
and I assure you that
you will level up to Triple Soul Rings.
How is it?
The people who were with him
snatched my
Phoenix Tail Crest Serpent just now.
After all, we are the elders,
don't take advantage of the kids.
There's nothing to lose in this deal.
Take it.
I can give it to you,
under one condition.
Shoot.
One of my friends is captured
by a Soul Beast.
Save her,
and I'll give it to you.
What kind of Soul Beast?
Titan Giant Ape.
It went that way.
Kid.
I'm afraid
your friend is dead.
Titan Giant Ape is fierce and violent.
Humans can never fight it.
It's meaningless even if I catch it.
Is that a no then?
If you want to level up
to Triple Soul Rings,
we'll exchange for a Soul Beast.
How long does it take?
First, I have to use
Human Faced Demon Spider
to attract poisonous Soul Beasts,
then this young lady
has the priority to choose.
Then I'll find another one for you.
I guess it will take some time.
No way.
I'm running out of time.
Don't act rashly.
You might die.
Sir.
The one who got caught is Wu.
Tang San!
Wu.
I'm running out of time.
Tang San!
What's wrong?
It exceeded his limit,
his body definitely couldn't take it in.
Can we help?
He is on his own.
Tang San!
What is it?
What's wrong?
I saw a plume of green smoke
coming out of his body
and got into her arm.
How do you feel?
Nothing.
Did you really see it?
Ask him when he's awake.
No!
What is it?
You hit him too hard!
What if you hurt Tang San?
Er Ming.
You seem taller now.
What is happening?
Is he turning into a butterfly?
Human Faced Demon Spider's strength
is too strong for him.
It is affecting his body.
Has he failed in
absorbing the Soul Ring?
Not yet.
We'll only know after the cocoon breaks.
It's a one-in-a-million chance
to survive
this kind of ordeal.
Let's go.
We'll get you another Soul Beast.
But I want to wait for the result.
Stand further away then.
He might blow himself up anytime.
Er Ming, it's done!
Thank you, Er Ming!
No need.
It's enough.
Now their highest rank is
Triple Soul Rings.
It would be inappropriate
if I leveled up too fast.
Okay, okay.
I understand.
I didn't tell anyone
that I can absorb Soul Ring.
It's a secret to keep.
Okay.
I have to leave.
Say hello to Da Ming for me.
I don't want to go, either.
But
I will visit you
whenever I have the chance.
Okay?
Come on.
I really have to leave,
otherwise, Tang San would be worried.
Bye.
Please stop.
Okay, fine.
I give in.
Hide yourself
when I'm safe.
Don't let them see you.
Why hasn't he come out yet?
He either blows up,
or
he has turned into a corpse.
No way.
He will never die here.
How many of those are alive
after a backfire from the Soul Power?
There is always a miracle.
It's a miracle
because it's doesn't happen easily.
He is responding.
He is alive.
There is a miracle.
Take your time, no rush.
Tang San!
What happened to him?
The Soul Power is too strong,
it changes his temperament.
The power of Human Faced Demon Spider
has overridden him.
A monster like this
can never be left alive.
He cannot be saved.
Kill him.
Don't!
There's a way!
Move.
Tang San!
Move!
He is my student.
The Soul Power has backfired,
and he has lost his mind.
He is now a monster.
There's a way to save him.
There was no precedent of revival
among those overridden by the Soul Power.
I believe in him.
Even if there's a way,
he has run away.
Brother Dai.
This...
Tang...
What happened to Tang San?
Bring him under control first.
Ou Si Ke, help us.
Ou Si Ke, what are you doing?
Ou Si Ke!
He's strong.
Come on!
Hold it down.
Qibao Amber Pagoda.
Strength Boost!
I feel like I'm much stronger.
Me too.
Of course.
My Qibao Amber Pagoda
can double your strength.
Why are you back?
The Support Branch Soul Masters of Ning Family
will never abandon their partners.
What's wrong with him?
Why are you holding him down?
Why are there legs
growing out of his back?
It's the backfire of Soul Power.
He killed Human Faced Demon Spider
and absorbed its Soul Ring.
But its power
has exceeded his limit.
His temperament
is controlled by the beast nature.
In fact, the spider legs
are the Soul Bones.
What is a Soul Bone?
When a strong Soul Beast is killed,
there is a small chance that
the Soul Bones would be left behind
and attach to the Soul Master.
Tang San's current situation
is caused by the overflowing power
within and outside his body.
If we take the Soul Bones away,
most of the Soul Power can be removed.
He might regain consciousness.
But the Soul Bones are attached to him,
so they share the Soul Master's body.
If we remove them forcefully,
Tang San would stay at
Triple Soul Rings forever.
There's no chance of leveling up.
He would be ruined.
Exactly.
Brother San.
Wake up.
You'll be fine
if you regain consciousness.
Tang San.
He's just a bloodthirsty beast now.
He can't hear you.
Let me remove the Soul Bones.
You're his teacher.
He trusts you.
But if what you said is true,
and if he can never level up again,
do you think he can accept it?
I don't want that too.
But there's hope as long as he's alive.
It's better to stay at
Triple Soul Rings for life,
than being disoriented like this.
A Soul Master who can
never become stronger
has no dignity of life.
I know this better than you.
I'm a Soul Master
who will never advance.
But the dignity of a Soul Master
is not about
leveling up and fighting only.
Save him first.
We can talk later.
Great.
The Soul Bones just appeared,
and they have yet to grow into his body,
otherwise we can't remove them.
If you can't do it,
I can do it for you.
He is my student.
I'll do it myself.
Wu.
Can you hear that?
Brother San is awake. He is talking.
Wu.
I heard him.
He is calling Wu.
Great.
He'll be fine if he wakes up.
Quick, let go.
Brother San is awake.
Is he awake?
Tang San.
Can you hear me?
Regaining consciousness
even after the backfire of Soul Power.
You have created a miracle.
Wu.
Okay.
Wake up.
We will go to save Wu later.
Wu.
Gang, Tang San...
He is not awake.
He is controlled by the beast nature,
but his strong wish still exists.
He has always wanted to save Wu.
This wish has suppressed
the nature of killing.
You stay here. Let's go.
Okay.
If Titan Giant Ape is ahead,
we're seeking for death
if we follow them.
If saving Sister Wu
is Brother San's wish,
I'd like to help him with that.
Wait for me.
Hey.
Stay here.
A Support Branch Soul Master
can never abandon her partners,
even if they are lunatic.
Slow down.
Why are you running so fast?
What if a Soul Beast
comes out of nowhere attacks me?
You should leave now.
We'll be in trouble if they see us.
Right.
Also,
if you run into my friends,
don't hurt them.
They are good people.
Go back, Er Ming.
Remember me to Da Ming.
I'm fine.
Don't hurt him.
Wu.
Headmaster.
Master.
You escaped.
The Titan Giant Ape didn't hurt me.
What happened to Tang San?
Wu.
It's the backfire of Soul Power.
Backfire?
Wu.
Let me save him.
No.
He is not Tang San anymore.
But he is calling my name.
His last wish is to save you.
But sadly,
he can't recognize you anymore.
That's weird.
Why didn't Titan Giant Ape fight back?
What can we do to save him?
Remove the Soul Bones.
Let me try.
If I die in the hand of Titan Giant Ape,
promise me
to take them home safely.
Headmaster!
Stop.
Great one.
Soul Honour of Quadruple Soul Rings?
Among all
Soul Honours of Triple Soul Rings,
he can be considered as a great one.
Sister.
Why are you here?
Of course I'm here for you.
The Star Forest is so big,
how did you find me?
I'm worried about you.
Fragrance Seeking Worm.
Did you put it on me?
You traveled far alone.
As your elder sister,
I have to keep an eye on you.
Has anything happened in the family?
Nothing happened.
Why are you here then?
Aren't you here
to break off the engagement?
Have you told him?
Yes.
Let's go then.
He's dying.
What do you mean?
The honored King of Forest,
I'm here to bring my student home.
I have no intention of
fighting with you.
The Soul Bones
are going to attach to his bone.
They must be removed now,
otherwise it will be too late.
Is the removal dangerous?
He can never level up
and he will stay at
Triple Soul Rings for life.
No way!
The Soul Power in him is overflowing.
The Soul Bones must be removed.
Wu, we are saving him.
Overflowing of Soul Power.
Then we can just transfer it out.
How can you transfer
a Soul Master's Soul Power?
I know the way.
Wu.
I know you're upset,
but this is
the only way to keep him alive.
Hurry up.
Titan Giant Ape.
Darn it!
The King of Forest is at the outskirts.
Who is fighting it?
You said Dai Mu Bai is dying.
What do you mean?
It's none of your business.
Come with me.
Let's get this straight first.
I'll tell you on our way home.
I'm not leaving.
Don't throw a tantrum here.
I'm doing this for your own good.
Let's go.
Let her go.
Oh, you're awake.
I said, let her go.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Don't you know who I am?
This woman is strong.
You should leave first.
What is going on here?
Have you broken off your engagement?
Mind your own business.
Do you know her?
Where is Tang San?
What's with all these people?
How troublesome.
Leave him as soon as you can.
The roar of Titan Giant Ape
came from that side.
Let's go check it out.
Let's go.
Wu.
I'm here.
I'll remove the excessive Soul Power.
It'll be fine.
He doesn't remember anything now.
He won't know about our secret.
Keep an eye out for me.
Don't let anyone come near us.
The process of transferring
can't be interrupted.
You'll be fine in a minute.
No!
It can't be interrupted.
You have to wake up.
Tang San.
The process can't be interrupted.
You must make it through.
Tang San.
Leave them alone!
Fight with us if you dare.
You counted me in?
You can leave first.
Rocketing Kiwi!
Leave them alone!
You can eat my kiwi.
It's delicious.
Do you hear me?
I will fight with you.
Do you want a sausage?
[Do you want a sausage?]
Er Ming, go.
He ran away.
I chased it away.
Wu.
Tang San.
You...
Wake up.
What happened?
Where is Titan Giant Ape?
I chased it away with my kiwi.
Miss,
can you lend me a hand?
Here.
Can you help to treat Wu's wound?
Both of you are girls,
it would be more convenient.
Is she Wu?
Are the wounds
caused by the spider's legs?
I don't know.
She's already injured when I got here.
Didn't he come to save Wu?
Why would he hurt her?
He was deluded by the beast nature,
how could he remember his old friend?
Both of them fainted.
It's not a life-threatening situation.
Let me remove the Soul Bones for him.
It disappeared.
The Soul Bones have
integrated into his body.
What does it mean?
Unless he's dead,
otherwise it can never be extracted.
We're late.
What should we do?
Kill him.
Ma Hong Jun.
Brother Dai.
Wu.
What happened?
The Soul Bones
have completely integrated into him.
He can never be saved.
Killing him
is setting him free.
I won't let you kill Brother San.
Tang San is a student of Shi Lan Ke School.
We will decide what to do
when Headmaster is awake.
He almost got away just now.
If I kill him,
it's better than letting
your Headmaster suffer.
Do you really want to kill him?
He is a monster now.
Wait.
My father is Ning Feng Zhi.
Is your father the chief of
Qibao Amber Clan?
Yes.
Why would the young daughter
of the three elders
hang out with these people?
Sir.
For the sake of my father,
please don't kill him now.
Even if your father is here,
he would kill him too.
Let me repeat myself.
He's no longer a human now.
He...
Wu.
He's awake.
Where is Titan Giant Ape?
Sir.
Can you recognize me?
It's just a Human Faced Demon Spider.
You're the Great Soul Land Master
with Eight Soul Rings.
You don't have to kill me for that.
What's wrong with you?
Why aren't you talking?
Wait, don't you remember what happened?
Wu.
She's not dead.
It's just a minor injury.
We have stopped the bleeding.
Did Titan Giant Ape hurt her?
As I know, you're the one who hurt her.
Let her get some rest.
She's not awake yet.
She will be fine later.
Kid, come here.
I can't believe that
you're totally fine.
How did you revive?
I can't remember.
My last memory is that
I absorbed the Soul Ring.
Then when I opened my eyes,
you wanted to kill me.
No one has ever healed by themselves
after the backfire of Martial Soul.
Kid,
show me your Martial Soul.
You've leveled up to Triple Soul Rings.
He is truly recovered.
This...
This doesn't make sense at all.
Kid,
what's with the green smoke
that came out of your body?
Green smoke? What is it?
Could it be that I made a mistake?
That's it.
Let's go.
What green smoke was she talking about?
The Serpent said
when Du Gu Yan touched you,
there was a plume of
green smoke coming out of your body.
She touched me?
You were unconscious at that time.
Oh, no!
They walked too fast.
I was thinking about Wu,
and I forgot about the bottle.
Didn't I give it to Lander?
When he was fighting
with Titan Giant Ape,
the bottle dropped,
so I picked it up.
And then?
Then when I was fighting
the Human Faced Demon Spider,
the bottle was broken.
The green smoke in it
drifted onto my hand.
But nothing happened to me.
How is that possible?
Sir,
is it possible that it's not a kind of poison?
No way.
There's strong poison in the bottle.
If that's the case,
why hasn't
anything happened to me?
Perhaps
there's also poison
in Human Faced Demon Spider.
When you absorbed its Soul Ring,
it affected you as well.
I'll check the books at school later,
and I'll try to figure it out.
Sir, how about you?
Headmaster said
you went to see Su Yun Tao.
He's dead.
He's dead?
Who killed him?
I don't know.
That's a human figure like the black smoke..
I've never met a Soul Master like that.
But there's one thing for sure,
he is very strong.
He could even
talk to the King of Star Forest.
Did he talk to Titan Giant Ape?
No.
It's Azure Bull Python.
He had a conversation
with Azure Bull Python.
And then?
I headed out of the forest.
Then I saw you
getting ready to absorb the Soul Ring.
After I advanced,
I lost my control.
It's because of
the backfire of Soul Power.
So,
I was the one who hurt Wu.
You were unconscious back then.
It's not your fault.
You're not to blame for Wu's injury.
But I almost killed her.
Both of you are lucky.
Wu is fine.
You're awake.
Sir,
where is Headmaster and Brother Dai?
They went to the town
to find herbs that
can speed up Wu's recovery.
I'll go too.
They went in a group. It's enough.
I have to do something for her.
What kind of herbs does she need?
Why do you ask me to come?
You seem to be treating me coldly.
Regarding today's battle,
even Ning Rong Rong was there,
you're the only one who left.
We are talking about
Titan Giant Ape.
The smartest move is to leave.
Aren't you going to accept me
as your partner anymore?
You're right.
Then I'll do
what I have to do.
Relax, don't be nervous.
That's right.
Tell me everything
about your family.
What happened to me?
She is using the spiritual ability on you.
I just want
to know a little more about Brother Dai.
Okay, I get it.
He's yours.
I won't talk to him anymore.
Don't talk nonsense.
It's not because of this.
What are you trying to do?
I just want to know
a little more about you.
I want to know about your past,
but you always reject me.
This is my only way.
If you do it again,
I'll kill you.
Why are you here?
I just passed by and
I coincidentally saw you.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Snow Return.
True Soul Flower.
You're not dead.
It's you.
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪