♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 17=
Snow Return.
True Soul Flower.
So you didn't die.
It's you?
I have verified it.
You did
smear the contents of the bottle on the target.
Not bad.
What was in the bottle?
Lethal poison.
My plan was
to let you die along with her.
Then why didn't anything happen to her?
You don't have to know.
You only need to know
that since Bu Le sent you here,
you are not expected to return alive.
He intended to kill you
with my hands.
But since you're still alive,
it proves that you still have potential.
Then can you cure Wu's poison now?
Hold on.
Since you have potential,
I'm willing to give you a chance.
Do you want to join us?
Not interested.
We are a colossal force
hidden in Douluo Continent.
The future is limitless with us.
I am really not interested.
The one supporting us
is a Grand Soul Land Master with Nine Soul Rings.
He is even a legend
among the Grand Soul Land Masters.
Have you heard of
the one who fought against Martial Soul Hall,
Hao Tian Soul Master,
Tang Hao?
Tang Hao.
Seems like you've heard of him.
Hao Tian Soul Master.
What is his Martial Soul?
Naturally, it's the Hao Tian Hammer.
Remember my word.
Do not let anyone discover
the Martial Soul on your left hand.
I have many things to do.
You won't be able to keep up with me.
You're saying
that all of this,
including the Martial Soul mutation
in the Nightfire Village,
was supported by Hao Tian Soul Master?
Not just the Nightfire Village.
There are many Soul Masters
in Douluo Continent
who are undergoing
Martial Soul mutation experiments.
Why?
Are you scared
after hearing the name
of a Grand Soul Land Master?
How can I meet him?
It's not that easy
to join us.
You have to pass a test.
What test?
Xi Si City Soul Arena.
Accept the Fiend Battle Team's challenge.
Once you overcome the challenge,
you're qualified to go to Cang Hui School
in Tian Dou City and see me.
Will Tang Hao be there too?
Don't mention his name casually.
Martial Soul Hall has been chasing after him.
Alright.
Once I've saved Wu,
I will go to Xi Si City.
Your capabilities now
are not enough.
Get stronger.
You can only challenge
the Fiend Battle Team
when you are strong enough.
(One day,)
(when your heart and Martial Soul)
(become powerful beyond comparison,)
(I will come to you.)
Tang San?
Why are you here?
What happened?
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
I got the antidote.
You got the antidote?
Let's go.
Master, I'll try it first.
I'm concerned about the antidote
Ye Zhi Qiu gave me.
Since he wants you to join him,
I don't think you have to worry.
Wu cannot get hurt again.
Seems like nothing is happening.
Master,
we've already cured her.
Why isn't she waking up?
I guess,
it might have something to do with you.
Me?
Your Blue Silver Plant Martial Soul
can hold the power from other Martial Souls.
Right now, three of your Soul Rings,
Thorn Apple Snake, Haunted Vine,
and Human Faced Demon Spider,
are poisonous.
Especially those with unique poison,
Thorn Apple Snake
and Human Faced Demon Spider.
The poison in the bottle
didn't take effect on you
because your Thorn Apple Snake Soul Ring
suppressed it.
You also absorbed
the Human Faced Demon Spider's Soul Ring.
Both kinds of poison
were synthesized in your body.
So I suppose
you are now immune to poison.
But how does that affect Wu?
I didn't see what happened,
but the kids said
that when they arrived,
Wu was covered in blood.
You attacked her.
You mean
I am now poisonous?
You have already fully absorbed the Soul Bone,
so you aren't carrying the poison anymore.
However, when the Soul Bone first came out,
the poison was still there.
So, when you attacked Wu,
you poisoned her.
So I harmed her.
But,
only you can save her.
What should I do?
Your Blue Silver Plant
can absorb everything.
Naturally, it can also absorb toxins.
What you can do now
is to place your Blue Silver Plant
near her wounds,
to help her get rid of the toxins.
Alright!
Her clothes will get in the way.
It must be in direct contact with the wound.
But Wu...
Isn't she your sister?
(Her life comes first.)
Master,
I've already done what you said.
I absorbed the toxin from Wu
using the Blue Silver Plant.
Let her rest.
When Headmaster is back,
we'll wake her up
and return to Shi Lan Ke immediately.
Master,
I want to know my dad's past.
I promised your dad that I would not say a word.
You can ask him yourself
when you see him.
Ye Zhi Qiu said
the Nightfire Village incident
and the Martial Soul mutation
were actually controlled by my dad.
I don't know why he did that.
I feel
that I don't understand him at all.
I only know things about him
because people tell me.
Tang San,
I can only tell you
that your dad is indeed Hao Tian Soul Master.
As for the one behind the Martial Soul mutation,
it may not be him.
Don't believe so easily anything others tell you.
When my dad left, he told me
that our family had many secrets.
He'd tell me when I become stronger.
But how do I know when I am strong enough?
I think
I should go to Xi Si City
and challenge the Fiend Battle Team.
I'll join Ye Zhi Qiu!
That's the fastest way for me to meet him.
You're wrong!
Maybe, in Shi Lan Ke,
you're considered strong.
But your power is nothing
in the entire Douluo Continent!
If you go to Xi Si City now,
you won't succeed!
But if I go back to school,
I will see Ma Hong Jun.
How can I face him?
The way things has progressed
is not your fault.
You have a long way ahead.
Thank you, Master.
I will definitely do my best.
Brother!
Watch your step.
You haven't fully recovered.
Brother.
In the Star Forest,
when you didn't recognize me,
I was terrified.
You are my dear sister.
I promise
I will never hurt you again.
Great.
You have my word.
Let's go.
Alright.
Everyone, let's take a rest here.
Gang, you seem to be out of breath.
Not in good shape.
I'm not like you.
You're healthy, old yet strong.
You're saying I'm old?
Be careful of your words.
I'll get some fruit there.
Hong Jun!
Brother San?
Hong Jun.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong?
I know who the mastermind
behind the Martial Soul mutation is.
Who is it?
The Grand Soul Land Master, Tang Hao.
The Grand Soul Land Master?
He is also my father.
Your father?
Why would your father
be involved in the mutation incident?
Ye Zhi Qiu told me about it.
Who is he?
He is Bu Le's boss.
Regardless of whether it's true or not,
I need to tell you about it.
You are one of the victims, after all.
If I hide this from you,
I really don't know how to face you.
Hong Jun,
if you want to take revenge, do it.
I won't fight back.
Did Ye Zhi Qiu tell you this
before the Nightfire Village incident?
No.
I only knew it
after we got out of the Star Forest.
There's no evidence
that Ye Zhi Qiu was telling the truth.
Brother San,
I trust you.
Even if the truth
may not be what we want to face,
I won't blame you.
After all,
you're you.
He's he.
Thank you, Hong Jun.
I will definitely find out
who the real culprit is.
Even if it is truly my father,
I will definitely stop him.
I'm with you.
We're finally back!
I'm so tired.
You must be exhausted.
So tired.
Everyone.
Take a seat.
Go back to your room and take a rest.
Tomorrow morning,
assemble here.
Assemble in the morning?
We just came back!
All of you need to start
your training course tomorrow.
Isn't it too hasty?
You have no right to bargain.
All of you have no problem with it?
I...
I agree with
Headmaster's and Master's arrangement.
Alright, make sure you get enough rest.
There will be even harder trials
waiting for you tomorrow.
Go!
Let's go.
Come on, Wu.
Go back and rest.
Have a good rest.
Gang.
Have you told Hu Lie Na
about Su Yun Tao's death?
I will find the right time to talk to her.
This could be an issue.
What if they blame
his death on you?
I only stumbled upon it by chance.
Also, I don't have the power
to kill an officer from Martial Soul Hall.
But you saw the killer,
and you chased after him.
Wouldn't you be curious too?
That's true.
But there seems to be
a connection between the killer
and the Azure Bull Python.
Do you know how serious this is?
I know.
This is definitely a big scheme,
and it's likely
that it's also related to Martial Soul Hall.
No matter how big the scheme is,
it's none of your business.
Gang.
I know very well
your relationship
with the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
You said it yourself.
It was all in the past.
You'd never think of it again.
Right now,
your students are the most important.
Your disciple.
Leave the big things
to the big shots.
The people around you
should be more important to you,
don't you think so?
I didn't say that I'm planning to leave.
Why didn't you say that earlier?
I wouldn't have wasted my time.
You are right.
My students
are the most important.
Why isn't Brother Dai in the dorm?
He probably went somewhere to train.
Then I hope we won't bump into him.
You...
Both of you...
We...
We couldn't sleep,
so we're out to have a walk.
Me too.
I'm going that way.
We're going that way.
Didn't you want to fight?
What's this?
You wouldn't have come if I hadn't said that.
Come on, then.
I'm ready.
You should enter first, and force the worm out.
The process will be slightly painful.
But I have already added enough herbs
to offset the pain.
You just need to retain your Soul Power.
If you get hurt,
there is medicine.
Have you made up your mind?
Bu Le gave us the medicine.
My dad was harmed by him.
I must avenge my dad.
We'll go together.
Don't worry, Brother San.
Your company is good enough.
You don't have to do anything.
I want to take revenge
on him too.
Is it for Sister Wu?
I'm young,
but I can tell.
Sister Wu
didn't look good before our trip
to the Star Forest.
So you've already known about it.
To be precise,
all of us knew it.
So all of you have actually known it.
Brother San.
I know
that you were worried about our safety.
So you went to Star Town in advance.
I kept it from you.
I am sorry.
Brother Dai has said it.
We are the Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke.
Don't
leave us alone.
Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke forever.
Let's go.
Retain your Soul Power.
Otherwise, you might die.
It's coming out.
What are you doing?
Do you still have the strength?
Do me a favor.
When I force the worm out later,
kill it for me.
It's out.
Are you alright?
I'm fine.
You intended to send me to death.
Right?
I really didn't lie to you.
Only people from the headquarters
can cure that poison.
Spare me! Spare me!
Spare me!
You weren't poisoned.
As a brother
who didn't protect his sister,
I'm here to avenge my sister.
Spare me.
Spare me, please.
What do you want, Ma Hong Jun?
Remember.
Had it not been for me,
you wouldn't have got the Phoenix Soul.
Don't.
I don't want the Phoenix Soul.
Had it not been for you,
my dad wouldn't have been tortured.
He wouldn't have died.
But you have already become stronger.
It's not what I want.
I can compensate you.
Compensate me?
Can your compensation bring my dad back to life?
I...
I can compensate you with money.
I can buy a big house for you.
Alright?
Home is about the people,
not the house.
He can't return.
This boy is going berserk.
Release me!
Hurry and release me!
He's going berserk!
Someone like you
will not come to a good end.
Brother San.
I almost killed him.
I don't want to become someone like him.
Hong Jun.
You did well.
We will have hatred and anger
towards people who hurt us.
We will even want revenge.
This is human nature.
But you did well
in the hut.
You weren't blinded by your hatred,
and did not act recklessly.
Brother San.
What should I do next?
From today on,
you need to work even harder
in your studies and training.
Never give up.
Be stronger from inside out
and create a world that belongs to you.
Alright.
From now on,
I will train harder.
Good.
Let's go back to school.
Master Ye!
Why are you here?
You did well
in Suo Tuo City.
I was just
doing my job.
I dare not be greedy for praises.
I dare not.
Do you know
what our main objective is now?
It is to keep a low profile.
Yet, at present,
how many people
have already known about your existence?
Even Martial Soul Hall
has started investigating us.
It must be Shi Lan Ke School's fault.
No worries.
We can kill them.
We can destroy the school.
Kill everyone in the school?
Actually, I just need to kill you.
Of course, I've thought about it.
Perhaps one day,
I'll share the same fate as yours.
One person is missing.
Well...
Brother Dai is...
I'm here.
I can't believe Brother Dai
is here for Master's class.
As Headmaster requested,
from today on,
I will be giving you Strength Up training.
If anyone thinks I'm unqualified,
and does not want to attend my class,
he can quit.
I won't stop you.
I'm the same.
Alright then.
Since none of you
are quitting now,
no one can ever quit later.
Dai Mu Bai, you're the captain.
Everyone's attendance and discipline.
Your responsibility.
Alright.
The following training
will definitely let all of you become stronger.
As long as you are able to persevere.
Master.
Will the training be very difficult?
Our first lesson is coming up.
Let me warn you.
This may be extremely difficult
for some of you.
What's this for?
Are you going to cook us?
I think this is too difficult.
Have a look.
It smells great.
This is our first lesson?
How is this difficult?
I can eat five bowls in a row.
Master.
Can we eat as much as we want?
Each person gets a bowl. Fill it up yourself.
Pour the soup until it reaches the rim of the bowl.
No fewer than three pieces of meat.
No fewer than four pieces of vegetable.
Finish everything.
This is the first lesson.
Come on.
Have breakfast.
I'll go first.
I'll fill it up for everyone.
Headmaster is usually stingy.
We don't get meat often.
We can only have it once a week.
I must eat as much as I can today.
Come, Hong Jun.
Eat as much as you can.
Just don't eat less than the amount I mentioned.
Hurry, hurry.
Was anyone left out?
Here, Rong Rong.
Wu.
Wu, take the bowl.
It's hot.
Hurry, hurry.
Hurry.
Be careful, it's hot.
Master.
I'll vomit if I eat meat.
You?
I'm on diet.
I won't be eating.
If you don't eat,
you can drop out now.
Is it hard to understand my words?
I'll speak to Headmaster!
It's pointless to speak to him!
If you let him know
that you wasted all the money on the meat,
I don't think he will
show his respect to Chief Ning.
He will kick you out immediately.
What kind of lesson is this?
Eating meat and drinking soup.
How does it help to increase Soul Power?
It does help.
This smells so good.
This soup is based
on the secret recipe
of the royal family of Xing Lou.
It helps the Soul Power grow,
and also strengthens it.
That's amazing.
Have some.
How do you know?
I am from Xing Luo.
I can prove it.
The secret recipe
of the royal family of Xing Lou?
From tomorrow on,
you will have this for breakfast every day.
Master.
I will really vomit if I eat meat.
Lift up the bowl.
Eat it now.
Wu.
Continue to eat it after you finish vomiting.
A Soul Master's journey is full of danger.
If you can't even take this,
you don't have to stay here.
I can do it.
The Strength Up training is right ahead.
Keep up, everyone.
-How far is it?
-Where is it?
Just follow Master.
Wu.
Come with me.
What is it?
Adapt to breakfast slowly.
Here.
I wrapped this radish up with my grass net.
No one knows it.
Hurry and eat.
You're the best, Tang Sang.
I'm starving.
Slowly.
This grass net is so special!
Give it back to me.
Why are you here?
This is my Third Soul Skill.
Constraint of Spider Web.
Spider web?
Then it's related to the Human Faced Demon Spider.
You used your Soul Skill to help her hide a radish?
So wasteful.
We can make a deal.
Give one to me.
This...
Give one to me, please.
Give one to me.
Then this time I hid the radish for Wu,
keep it a secret.
Don't worry. I'm good at keeping secrets.
Don't you know me?
Come on, let me see.
Enough. Give me your hand.
My hand.
The grass net has great adhesiveness.
This means your control is good.
So Constraint of Spider Web can give a net form
to Blue Silver Plant.
You can use it
to entrap your opponent in the arena.
Ou Si Ke.
You've been paying attention
to combat these days.
You want to give up your dream, and become
a Soul Master?
I'm in the Support Branch.
Even if I train hard,
I won't be able to participate in combat.
But Wu,
you really have to work hard.
Among the seven of us,
you're the only one with one Soul Ring.
I already have Triple Soul Rings.
When did you advance?
In the Star Forest.
Weren't you captured by the Titan Giant Ape?
He released me afterwards.
You wouldn't have time to kill Soul Beasts!
Titan Giant Ape
stepped on a Soul Beast.
It was dying,
so I just finished it off.
Then I advanced.
No way, Wu.
You only had one Soul Ring.
Now you have three.
Actually, Titan Giant Ape
stepped on two Soul Beasts!
Impossible.
I've never heard
about advancing two Soul Rings consecutively.
It's totally impossible!
I have no idea.
What are your two Soul Skills?
Second Soul Skill.
Look here.
Long eyelashes, beautiful eyes.
Well...
That's not the point now, you...
Your eyes turned pink.
Ou Si Ke, I think I felt dizzy.
Me too.
Was that a spiritual attack?
Primary Charm that causes short-term dizziness.
Surprise attack.
It's a really useful Soul Skill.
Next, my Third Soul Skill.
I'm here!
Don't yell.
You went really fast.
How did you come over?
No way.
It was not just speed.
Was it Teleport?
Teleport?
Your Soul Skill is unbelievable.
Wu, are you done eating?
We should go.
I'm done.
This is incredible.
Let's go.
Get ready for class!
Time for class.
Each of you, carry one.
Then continue running ahead.
You can only turn around when you see the sign.
Make a round trip before lunch.
Do I have to run too?
Yes.
Each basket is labelled with one of our names.
Brother Dai's, Tang San's,
and Ma Hong Jun's basket are the heaviest.
Mine, Zhu Zhu Qing's, and Wu's weigh the same.
Yours is the lightest.
I'd look ugly carrying this.
If you don't return by lunchtime,
you won't get lunch.
No lunch?
Qibao Amber Pagoda.
Strength Boost.
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪