ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
I don't want to do it.
Do what?
Being disappointed.
It's not your fault anyway.
I don't want to bad-mouth your family.
I just…
What's wrong with me?
I've lived well until now.
So what do I lack?
I value myself
more than anyone else.
So I want to give up.
You said I could
make a mistake.
I hoped
that we'd just have problems of our own.
Because that kind of stuff
is something we can work on.
It's within our control.
But when it comes to external problems,
I have to endure them.
And I don't like doing that.
Whenever I was faced with
relationship issues,
all I had to do was
just end the relationship.
It was my instinct to run away.
Because I hated letting myself get hurt.
This is why I didn't want to meet you.
I knew I'd end up saying this
considering how I felt.
Do you want to break up?
I'm a coward, aren't I?
The fact that I made you say that first.
So you want to break up.
Where's the courtesy?
Even if you're a coward,
how could you make me say it first?
The only mistake you made today
was making me say it first.
You could've slept on it.
Let's give each other some time.
It's the least you can do for me.
I think I deserve that much.
Don't I?
You deserve it. You do.
Okay.
Okay then.
That's good enough. I'll be off now.
EPISODE 13
I think my dad knows
that you guys go around holding hands.
I got scared that he might have
a separate file for me too,
so I started looking for it.
But there wasn't one.
You're his daughter.
Seon-gyeom is his son.
There is this guy I love.
My dad put him through a lot as well
behind my back.
How did he handle it?
He always ran away,
and I always went after him.
I stopped counting
once it reached the fifth time.
I'd go anywhere to find him
no matter where he runs off to.
I wonder how Seon-gyeom will react
if you ever run away from him.
Haven't you ever thought
that he might run away?
Seon-gyeom never runs away.
Do you think
I don't deserve to be with Seon-gyeom?
Are you treating me like a mean
sister-in-law already?
Don't think of me like that.
I sometimes feel like I don't deserve him.
When I'm with him,
I sometimes end up
being faced with my flaws.
And I lose focus on my work.
I'm able to focus better on work
if my love life is stable.
Love is great.
But I never want to lose focus on my work
no matter what happens.
It's kind of like losing myself.
I'll try to help Seon-gyeom
the best I can.
But I'm also quite a mess these days.
I figured it was only right
to tell you first
before telling Seon-gyeom about it.
I hope he never finds out.
I just want us to concentrate
on each other for now.
By the way, why do you go after him
every time he runs away?
Because I know how much he loves me.
That's why he runs away.
Will you turn off the alarm?
My class begins in the afternoon.
Turn off the alarm.
Have fun running.
You don't always have
to overcome everything.
You can rest on the weekends.
SEO DAN-AH
Her grandfather, father,
and older brother…
Wait. They all have "myeong"
in their names
except for Ms. Seo.
Is it because she's pretty?
And I don't see Seo Tae-woong.
Is he really a competitor?
Ms. Seo is way too attractive.
It's Ms. Seo's birthday soon.
I see. Okay.
First, let's apply for the charity run.
I'm done applying.
Gosh, I was hoping you'd respond,
but I didn't get anything out of you.
Is something wrong?
You didn't even go running today.
My goodness.
Tell me what's on your mind.
Don't take it out on the laundry.
These are our clothes.
Does she
really want to break up?
Did I give her a hard time
while we were together?
I thought I tried my best,
but was that not enough?
Did that pile up
and eventually make her explode
because of my dad?
Now I totally get why you weren't
folding the laundry properly.
Is there anything I can do to help?
If you're done with that milk,
wash the carton and recycle it.
You got it.
Then can I ask you for a favor as well?
It's nothing big.
Sure. Go ahead.
I thought you never wanted
to eat japchae again.
I need to use the ingredients I bought.
That's not what I meant.
You can find recipes online.
So why ask me for help?
What if I know the recipe?
It needs to taste good.
How could everything taste so bad
when you chop so well?
-Maybe your mouth is the problem.
-My mouth is always the problem.
Is there anything else I need to chop?
May, I kind of get why you cook.
While I was cooking,
I only thought of how dull the knife was
and if I had to chop the garlic
or mince them.
"I should send resumes tomorrow
so I can keep myself busy with work."
I didn't think of that kind of stuff.
It was kind of like running.
It's a different form of meditation.
That's why I always ask you
to be my cooking assistant.
Do you see the big picture?
That's what makes you a great CEO.
You need to rest like it's an obligation
in order to last in this business.
Working is resting.
You're always busy with work yourself.
After I started my own firm,
I realized that CEOs also love
receiving monthly paychecks.
My dream was to live off monthly salaries.
Why did I have to start my own business?
The movie you worked on
is going to hold a preview,
so come watch it with him.
You should watch your subtitles
on the big screen.
Oh, that.
It's like you.
That's how I feel about that movie.
Don't disappear.
Be with me forever.
I won't.
I said that only to run away myself.
Maybe I'm a piece of trash.
I really need to watch what I say.
What are you thinking?
It's the weekend, and I'm overcoming it.
Today's a weekday.
I'm so quick to lecture others.
FAMOUS RICE BURGERS
Where's the valet?
Why are you suddenly
asking about the ballet?
"Ballet"?
The valet…
Who's going to park my car?
People do that for you?
I've never heard of that before.
Who told you to park here?
-Then where should we park?
-You can't park here.
Why aren't you using honorifics?
I'm sorry. Just a second.
My school is nearby,
so let's just park the car there.
We'll leave. Sorry.
It better be worth all this trouble.
You told me you want to know
what's inside me.
I'll show you before I put it inside me.
Did you think I might kiss you?
I'd be lying if I say no.
I thought I hurt you.
Do you know how rude it is to say that?
You tend to hold a grudge.
And it lasts quite a while.
What exactly did I do to hurt you?
It's better to tell me than to sue me.
Sue you? Why?
Do you think you'd win
if you file a lawsuit against me?
-It's for your own sake.
-Why would I sue you?
Why must we fight at all?
-You have no friends, do you?
-Why would I need friends?
You don't make friends out of need.
You just naturally make them.
Then do you want to be my friend?
You just hurt me by saying that.
I hurt you again? What hurt you?
How did I hurt you?
You didn't tell me
it's your birthday soon.
Do you have any plans then?
No, I don't. And I never will.
Then can we have a party and go on a date?
No.
Are they harvesting the rice?
What's taking so long?
Are you sure you're free that day?
-When?
-On your birthday.
I'm free.
Then let's meet.
Don't bring that up again.
What's the big deal about my birthday?
It's the day you were born.
Being born is a miracle in itself,
but you're also healthy and dating me.
What do you get out of
celebrating birthdays?
Their heart.
That stuff disappears.
It lasts longer because it's invisible.
Some feelings
even grow stronger with time.
You'll regret wasting your time.
I don't even know what will happen
in an hour.
Will you please meet me that day?
I'll tell you what happens in an hour.
-You're being bossy again.
-Let's just meet
another day to eat
and go for a drive like today.
-No.
-Stop saying no.
-I forbid you.
-You forbid a lot of things.
-No.
-You always say no to me too.
Your rice burgers are ready.
Let's stop.
Stop what?
We shouldn't argue
in front of the burgers.
Then what should we say?
"It's delicious."
It's delicious.
Why can't we meet on your birthday?
-So it's okay when you do it.
-Of course, yes.
-Couples spend time…
-Who says we're a couple?
Now that really hurts me.
I hurt you again?
Among all the stuff you said,
this hurt me the most.
What am I to you?
A vending machine.
If you cry again,
I might have to fix my vending machine.
After you bought me coffee,
I looked up all the vending machine menus.
I noticed that they sell hot chocolate.
I'm done eating.
Don't take it out on the food.
I wanted to catch Yeong-il's match,
but it wasn't broadcasted.
Articles flew out though.
He came in second place
at the National Sports Festival.
He only came to Seoul
to prepare for the event.
What if my presence made him lose focus?
He wouldn't have been a champion
if he was fazed by that.
Without you, I'm all alone.
Then you'll keep winning first place.
Maybe it was your presence
that motivated me.
I think he's just in a slump.
Would he come to help me train
-when he's devastated?
-Here he comes.
On your mark.
Get set.
Take it easy, will you?
You won't be competing soon
and the season is over.
Yeong-il, will you continue
to ride your motorcycle?
I came here by car today.
Then what's with the helmet?
It's like a prop.
So it's your schtick?
Who taught you that word?
How can I give it up
when I enjoy being fast?
Seeing anyone go past me
makes my blood boil.
You know I came in second
at the National Sports Festival.
Never have I seen
anyone's back on the tracks,
but I did yesterday.
How did it feel?
Seeing the back of his head?
It wasn't all that bad.
But you just said that seeing the back
of one's head makes your blood boil.
It's not like I can look away though.
-I'll get some more beverages.
-No, I'll go.
-I won't be comfortable.
-But your leg…
It's fine.
The one who beat me said in an interview
that his goal was to break my record.
If I had come in at 10.00 seconds,
his record might've been under that.
If I run faster, those trying to beat me
will run faster too.
Our juniors running faster isn't so bad.
Exactly, and that's a pity.
That's what I think about that,
although others may think I'd be annoyed
that they're faster than I am.
-What was that for?
-I was comforting you.
-Don't do that again.
-Then win the race.
Stop it, will you?
Ms. Seo, let's say you have a kid
and that kid's all grown up.
How on earth
am I supposed to imagine that?
You hate that your son's dating a peasant.
You gave them a bribe
so that they'd go away
and threw a fit at their house.
But what if they didn't break up?
That parent must have a lot of free time.
Mr. Jeong, be careful what you let in!
Can I get you a drink? Tea or coffee?
I'd like a glass of cold water, please.
Mr. Jeong!
Why would you ask me that?
Because you're on the same level
as Assemblyman Ki.
Hold on.
Did you just say we're on the same level?
No, you did. You called me a peasant.
He'll be too busy soon
to keep caring anyway,
-so just stay put.
-Busy with what?
I see you don't watch the news.
This afternoon, the preparatory committee
of Happiness and Freedom Party
confirmed its own election guidelines.
After failing to unify
the opposing parties,
Assemblyman Ki and Assemblyman No
-look to run…
-I wonder who'll run for president.
The two are known to be the front-runners.
-As if I care.
-Assemblyman Ki has maintained
a high approval rating during
his four terms.
Meanwhile, Assemblyman No
is right on his tail.
He might win the in-house election,
but will never become a president.
I guess some would vote for him.
-Like whom?
-People like you.
Never.
You're still in the lead among
the assemblymen and women,
but party members seem to be
leaning toward Assemblyman No.
I see he'll be somewhat of a nuisance.
The opinion poll isn't
in your favor either.
It shows that the people want a new face.
Have my contingency plan ready
so that I can ruin him when I need to.
Yes, sir.
Should I continue to keep tabs
on your son?
What's the use? Leave him be.
I'll deal with the girl once and for all.
My gosh, this is exhausting!
Ji-woo, can you not be the first lady?
I'll lose my job if you stop acting.
As if anyone would let me be one.
I always consider
how your future will unfold
since it's directly linked to mine.
I chose my career over motherhood
to build an impressive filmography,
so why would I sacrifice it
for his career?
I wish to be known as Yook Ji-woo
and not someone's wife
until my coffin is shut and nailed.
This is my life we're talking about.
You know, Director Lee
has been giving us the eye.
This won't do.
Let's go and slice the rest up.
Ms. Oh, I have a question to ask too.
Why do people meet on birthdays?
Because it's a birthday.
He seems to be planning an event,
but my birthday isn't worth that.
I might be willing
to celebrate his though.
You're allowed but he's not?
That's always been the story for me.
I see you made up
after he ruined the painting.
This is the first time
someone's asked me out.
Is everything new for you?
Sorry about the sarcasm.
Well, you came to me first today.
Are you heading home?
I'll give you a ride on my way.
I haven't had my coffee yet.
No.
I forbid you from saying no to me.
-I'll get going.
-Sure.
-Take care.
-You too.
I shouldn't have worked here.
Welcome.
One Americano to go, please.
It's a thief.
The thief is washing the dishes
to make a clean getaway.
What? Hey, it's you. Wait, are you drunk?
Look. It's a thief.
A thief?
I'm not a thief. My name is Ki Seon-gyeom.
Seriously?
Although he does often steal things.
-What do I steal?
-People's hearts.
He's my roommate.
You saw him asleep before.
Anyway, over here is my BF.
You know what that is, right? Best friend.
Well, I'm…
I mean… I'm Lee Yeong-hwa's friend.
-I'll be in the bathroom.
-Sure.
Are you all right? Want some honey water?
Do you like him?
The kid who painted that.
Is it fun for you to mess with him?
Is that what he says?
It's pretty obvious.
Obvious?
Obvious how? Like the size of my drink?
You must pick your toys randomly.
I can't tell who's messing with who.
The daughter of a CEO
dating a regular college student?
You seemed clueless,
so I made it obvious for you.
I see you size up people
in a subjective way.
Likewise.
Your attitude is backing up my suspicion.
It means I need another trump card.
Despite having everything in this world,
you'll have the advantage
since you're his friend.
If friendship is used
as a bargaining chip,
he'll choose you over me.
Why would I do that to him?
Here's the coffee you ordered.
Is not answering questions
a trend these days?
The answer you wanted isn't on the menu.
What should I do?
I don't feel good.
Do you feel queasy? Have some water.
Do you want to throw up?
What's up? Is something wrong?
You…
Have you been studying for the TOEIC exam?
-It's right around the corner.
-What?
I'm worried we won't get
to go to the States together.
What? Why would you worry about that?
I've been studying, okay? So don't worry.
Right.
Are you leaving?
Can you make it home yourself?
Let me take you.
No, I should manage on my own.
An order for Yook Ji-woo's movie came in.
It's for a film festival.
You didn't leave your number
on your resume,
so they contacted you through us.
You must be out of it.
The one she's currently filming?
Killing Day?
It'll take a while to wrap up.
No, the one she filmed before that one.
Code Name Candy.
No way.
She played a drug dealer
by the name of Candy.
I can't believe it.
Are you going to be all right?
She's his mom.
And the wife of that assemblyman.
To me, she's just an actress.
I can't pass up
on the once-in-a-lifetime chance.
You saw how he is with his son.
I'm worried he'll do that with his wife.
This is just a job, all right?
Don't make it out to be a personal matter.
Hey, Mi-joo.
Seriously?
I'm sorry, May.
My frustration got the best of me.
You've been harsher before.
Right. I was once a menace.
Do you apologize to him this easily too?
-You're not the same.
-Why are we different?
To keep seeing you,
I should apologize
as soon as I realize my wrongdoing.
You overlooked so many
of my mistakes in the past.
At times like this,
you prove you're quite stable.
You acknowledge when you're at fault
and apologize quickly.
But what?
I avoid matters
when my love life's involved?
I blame my shitty dating experience.
Whenever issues surface,
I try to solve it right away,
but they just wanted to break up.
You and your shitty ex-boyfriends.
"History will repeat itself,
so I should dump him first."
How could I not think that way?
You would.
It's like I was born to be abandoned,
-so who would like that?
-No one would.
So what references can I turn to
-when he asks for a break?
-None.
You do realize he's not like
your shitty ex-boyfriends though, right?
I do.
Do you know how far
my thought process has reached?
"I didn't like him enough
to muster up the courage
and face the conflicts.
I don't love him enough
to put myself
through the wringer for him."
-Don't ever do that.
-Of course.
Being in love means
you should protect one another.
That's right.
Damn! Stop thinking so far ahead.
This isn't what the break is for.
I know. This is me avoiding
the situation too.
-Right eye.
-The right.
-Where are you going all dressed up?
-What? Dressed up?
I have to look reliable.
-Blink.
-What?
Do that when someone says
you're not reliable.
-Like this?
-Yes.
Your eyes are… You know.
So make use of your talent.
All right.
"Hello."
Hello, I'm here to represent
the athlete, Kim Woo-sik.
SEJEONG CITY HALL
TRACK TEAM
I'm sorry to tell you this
when you've waited so long.
The coach is off at a training camp.
Well, that's fine.
Here.
These are Kim Woo-sik's stats.
Could you make sure that he takes a look?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
Hello, I'm here to represent
the athlete, Kim Woo-sik.
Sure. Come on in.
Hello.
Mr. Ki. So this is how we meet.
I'm the manager
of the Jieum Construction Track Team.
-Have a seat.
-Right.
Thank you for agreeing to see me.
I heard the rumor about
you being Kim Woo-sik's manager.
Right.
I hope your father's well.
Yes, he's good.
Anyway, I'm here on behalf of Kim Woo-sik,
-not as my father's son.
-I'm just making small talk.
So how is Kim Woo-sik doing?
He's been working hard on his recovery.
Here. These are Kim Woo-sik's stats.
Also attached are the results
of his recent physical examination.
The rumor must be true.
You're representing him.
You see, people have been saying
that you're a nobody now.
Why are you supporting a whistleblower
with the resources you have?
I'm frustrated, that's all.
You're not going to be able
to help him like this.
I don't quite follow.
These stats would be enough
if it were yours.
We'd even be glad to sign Kim Woo-sik
as a two-for-one deal.
I didn't mean to offend you.
-I hope you weren't offended.
-Of course not. I'm fine.
-Thank you for your time then.
-No worries.
I miss her.
Wasn't it nice to spend
some time together?
It's about time we cut this out.
Ms. Kim says we're like a couple
in our sixties.
Why don't we end the date
with a movie and a GB?
What's a GB? Ginger beer?
Gruesome beer?
You're being absurd.
GB means a glass of beer.
As if a glass is ever enough.
-Seriously?
-It never ends with one glass.
-How about 12 bottles?
-Come on.
I guess she's fine.
I'm glad.
I'm glad. I really am.
Don't you feel safe
when you're sitting in a dark theater?
That's why I like theaters.
TRANSLATION: OH MI-JOO
TRANSLATION: JANG BYEONG-UK
If I timed myself today,
it might have been
a little over nine seconds.
Nine seconds? Is that good?
Gosh, of course. Totally.
You came to watch a movie with me,
didn't you?
Is it because I played
video games yesterday?
Did I play for too long?
How long has it been?
What do you mean?
Do you have the yips?
YIPS, SUDDEN LOSS OF SKILLS
IN EXPERIENCED ATHLETES
I don't know.
Have you stopped wasting your time
on other people?
Yes, thanks to a tattler.
You've been the best all this time.
Why the yips now that you're with me?
Maybe it's because I was the best…
It's my duty to report.
Is it the company's motto to tattle?
Were you really on a diet?
I know you'd ask me to lose weight
if I was modeling your clothes.
You know we don't have a double standard.
You're an athlete, not a model.
It's a problem
if it affects your main job.
How do you know that that's the cause?
Because it's our job to locate the cause.
We're considering everything.
Does it hurt to look nice
for a commercial?
The shoot is global.
You're known for your skills,
not your body.
Then what do you expect me to do?
Why is everyone bitching at me?
What do you want me to do?
What should I do?
Are things tough these days?
We just
wanted you to train more comfortably.
Why do people keep crying in front of me?
My life's been shitty these days.
Don't provoke me.
-She's sick. Let's go to a hospital.
-Ms. Seo, please.
Watch what you say.
Why should I?
The core problem will remain the same.
She needs to get well if she's sick.
Eun-bi, don't you worry, okay?
Don't take it to heart.
I was worried…
Just tell me if you don't know.
You've been at it for 15 minutes.
You should be done before Ye-jun comes.
I'm not killing time.
I just need a bit more time.
Then at least jot something down.
Is it all in your head or something?
I've confirmed the sketch.
You may begin coloring.
She texted me.
-I should…
-No useless replies.
She told me not to reply.
I've never felt happy
to be told not to do something.
-What's with that face?
-Why? Am I handsome?
Goodness, you look like a handsome idiot.
I'm an idiot in love. Jealous much?
-I guess it's good being an idiot.
-No, it isn't.
-I'm not jealous at all.
-Liar.
-No.
What are these balloons for?
Now you're asking
after blowing all of them?
To throw Ms. Seo a party.
I even bought a gift.
So you've made it up the tower.
What tower?
You mean Rapunzel?
Do you know what happens in the end?
The prince tries to climb the tower
and becomes blind
because he approached her.
I guess he saw the witch, not Rapunzel.
That's not it. The witch made him go blind
because he saw Rapunzel.
Don't you know cause and effect?
This wasn't what I wanted to get at.
I guess I'm weak when with you.
Move.
I ordered a cake from your cafe.
It's going to look pretty.
So what if it is? It should be tasty.
And I borrowed my roommate's car.
I'm going to make the balloons float
out of the trunk.
You get it, right?
They need helium to float.
You should've told me sooner.
You just told me now.
Right. I should buy some helium.
Hey, they will shrivel up by then
if you do it today.
I told you in advance.
Why did you tell him that?
We could've ruined it!
What? Ruin what?
Quit your nonsense.
You're not ruining anything!
-I will!
-Don't!
I will!
You should focus on your love life,
not his.
Are you an idiot?
Me?
Is this a WWJD thing?
And you say you've quit church.
What a man of virtue.
That's Confucianism.
Good for you.
You should change your name to Jesus.
Why are you so sensitive?
Being a senior must be a free pass.
Ye-chan.
Why have you been so edgy today?
It's because I'm a senior. So what?
I'm studying all day
to get into a university.
I'm already irked
that you're college students.
Do you like Yeong-hwa?
Over my dead body.
I have high standards. No, thank you.
Go buy some hotteok for me.
Sure.
Hello.
-It's nothing much.
-Thank you.
What brings you here, ma'am?
I haven't been attentive
to Ye-chan lately.
I'm worried she might be
bottling things up
and will explode soon.
I heard school violence is severe
these days.
Ye-chan wouldn't do such a thing.
I'm not talking about her being the bully.
I'm afraid she's the victim.
I found some bruises on her.
That's probably from boxing.
Ye-chan gets along very well
with her friends.
Sorry?
From what again?
They keep making us do things together.
I guess we're really going to debut.
That's the trend these days.
Tae-woong.
Explain these comments
on your social media.
What?
We were done ages ago,
so why are you still following me, babe?
Stop thinking about me, babe.
That little…
What a psycho!
"Babe"? Has he gone insane?
Delete them before the fans go berserk.
Thank god that happened
after our radio show.
Damn it.
Are you glad our fans didn't
bombard the live comments?
What a great leader you are.
That's my job.
Damn it.
I'll keep the car running, so come out.
He's unbelievable.
-Our fans are going to get hurt.
-You call cannot be reached…
This bastard isn't picking up.
I deleted, unfollowed, and blocked you.
You better not leave any more comments.
Who told you that you could call me?
Do you want a beating?
No, thanks.
That was a rhetorical question.
I'm busy preparing for a birthday party.
I hope this is
our last time talking, babe.
Who cares if you're preparing
for a birthday party?
Mr. Jeong, it's me.
What's Dan-ah's schedule today?
Okay. Got it.
Where are you going?
Somewhere.
-The company would want to talk with us.
-None of it is true, so why?
It's not my fault.
It's not mine either,
but I should still go
because I'm the leader.
Damn it.
Hey, babe! Over here!
I mean, I'm glad
we don't have class today,
but you look pathetic right now.
-So does your face.
-Talk to the hand.
No! Have you gone insane?
A birthday party for my sister?
-Seo Tae-woong?
-Why are you here?
Wait. What did you just say?
Have you gone insane?
Don't ruin her day. Call it quits.
No, before that.
What?
Your sister?
Don't act so friendly.
Even I've never called her that.
Then what else should I call my sister?
She's my sister!
What?
You were siblings?
We still are, you asshole.
Who are you to plan my sister's birthday?
Me?
I'm her vending machine! So what?
What are you rambling on about?
Hey, what are you doing?
Oh, god. What are you doing?
My gosh, do you even know who he is?
-You're damn crazy.
-Who is he?
Ye-jun! How dare you push my friend?
-You little…
-Ye-jun!
-Come here!
-You pretty boy!
-You asshole!
-Stop!
Who the hell are you?
-Gosh.
-Let's talk this out.
-Hold on.
-Who are you?
-Oh, no.
-Come here!
Why were you so late? I'm outnumbered.
I was parking. Yeong-hwa, wait.
Don't do that! No!
-Hold on!
-Oh, dear!
-You little…
-Guys!
-Come here!
-Oh, come on!
My hair! Time out!
-Hey, you!
-Fight outside!
-Get out!
Let go of me!
Mi-joo. Seon-gyeom. You're here.
Hey.
-Have you been well?
-As always.
-Let me go.
-You let go first.
Goh Ye-chan!
-Mom?
-Ms. Dong.
Hello, ma'am.
-Who is she?
-She's her mom.
What? Boxing?
Seriously, boxing?
-Were you aware of this?
-No, ma'am.
-Were you in on it too?
Mr. Jeong, don't tell me you knew as well.
Well…
What's going on?
Is this a gathering?
-Ms. Seo!
-Dan-ah!
-What's going on?
-Let me explain.
Hey, Mi-joo!
You, brat. Let's talk at home. Follow me.
-Wait.
-Ms. Seo, I'm taking a half-day.
-Let me go.
-Follow me!
-Ye-jun, don't forget my bag!
-Is this the only cafe in Seoul?
Why are you causing a scene at my cafe?
Why?
What happened to your hand?
I'm going to get it checked out today.
I think it's due to work.
The fireworks I bought were too big.
There's so much to clean up.
Why are you here?
I was invited.
And I owe Ms. Seo so…
Would you have still come
if you knew I'd be here?
Damn it. I told you not to do it.
This is all because of you.
Both of you, quiet.
I wasn't loud.
You have a loud voice to begin with.
I feel like an outcast.
You guys are too harsh.
Make sure you clean everything up.
And stop causing a mess
at someone else's workplace.
By the way,
how are you two related?
Your name wasn't on the family tree.
I'm a bastard.
A bastard?
This is a secret,
so keep it on the down-low.
What?
Okay.
And
today isn't her birthday.
It's fake. She wasn't born today.
She was born before Myeong-min,
but Dad only registered her birthday
after he was born.
I really didn't want to tell you this,
but I did so you wouldn't ruin
her day again.
It won't take long.
Goodness. When will you clean that up?
-It's okay. You can go first.
-Okay.
Hello?
-Right now?
-Yes.
I can't seem to reach Ms. Bang.
She probably has bad reception.
Okay.
Why are you doing such a poor job?
How are we to trust her with our kids?
I'm truly sorry.
What's going on?
Sir, Su-bin got in a fight
with another student.
-He's here instead of her--
-Are you educating them properly?
Where are her parents?
He's that athlete.
Are you him?
You were in charge of them
before the scandal.
We've filed in our complaints.
I refuse to let you train my son.
He has no right to train anyone.
Forget it. Where's the coach?
I want to see her right now.
I'm struggling to manage everything.
I'm sorry.
It's all because I'm a lousy adviser.
Don't say that.
Is Su-bin in class?
She's not here.
She's been suspended starting today.
The victim's mother demands
an apology from her parents.
But Su-bin… You know her story.
We shouldn't be apologetic
after only hearing one side of the story.
If she's still at fault
after hearing her side of the story,
then I'll apologize to them.
You shouldn't drink
while taking these antibiotics.
Do you mean I can't drink for a week?
They gave me a week's worth.
Don't forget to keep your hand
bandaged when showering.
Are you sure I can't even have one sip?
You know my answer.
Hello. Here's the prescription.
Okay. One minute.
Okay.
Mi-joo.
-What?
-Hello.
I can't believe I ran into you here.
I love your fingernails.
Did you do them yourself?
Yes, it's my hobby.
Mi-joo, you can talk casually.
-Should I?
-Yes.
Did you go to that hospital?
I have inflammation in my fingers.
I fell down some stairs.
I'm usually good at avoiding them
but I couldn't that day.
Are you being bullied at school?
That student ridiculed me and said
I couldn't learn anything
from someone who committed assault.
Does Mr. Ki know about this?
I don't think I can lie to his face,
so I've been dodging him.
I don't want to hurt him.
They said the track and field team
could break up because of me.
How is that your fault?
Are you a big shot?
I shouldn't be laughing,
but that was hilarious.
I tend to be funny.
If I tell them the truth and reconcile,
do you think everything
will turn out well?
Should I tag along with you?
I have a lot of free time.
This is my problem.
If I run away…
-No, if I do--
-Then let's have some tteokbokki.
I know a tasty place.
Ms. Oh Mi-joo, Ms. Lee Su-bin.
Your medication is ready.
-Okay.
Hello.
I'm Lee Su-bin.
I have something to tell you.
So you're the girl.
Bring your parents, not you.
I live with my aunt.
And she's very busy.
I want to apologize.
And I don't deserve to be suspended.
You really are ignorant, aren't you?
Chang-seop grabbed me first,
so I tried to stop him--
Hey. How dare you blame my son?
Bring your aunt then.
I have no business with you.
This is the problem with ignorant kids.
Hey! Who are you?
Who are you? Are you crazy?
A bit?
Hey!
Are you nuts?
-I am.
-What?
I'm totally nuts,
and I don't know what I'm capable of.
Treat her like you just did again
if you're curious to find out.
Then I'll really throw this.
Who are you to meddle in our affair?
Me? I'm her sister.
What's the big deal about having parents?
Let's go eat some tteokbokki.
Su-bin!
Did you cry? She did this, didn't she?
-Let me go!
-Hey!
Why are you doing this?
Did you make her cry?
So?
Why do you want to join track and field?
Why would you?
You bad-mouthed Mr. Ki.
Let me go!
I did that out of jealousy
since you liked him so much.
Why would you be jealous?
Because I like you!
That's why.
What?
You idiot! You fool!
I told you to study.
Now you want to join the track team?
Don't be cruel to her.
I'm going to protect her.
Who are you to protect her? Come here.
Goodness, kids these days
are so passionate.
-Su-bin!
-Stop calling her name!
Let's go.
What do you think about him?
-Well…
-That hurts.
Su-bin.
What took you so long? Did you eat?
-Hello.
Who is she?
She's a friend. I like her.
-I see.
-Hello.
I wanted to buy her dinner.
Were you waiting?
It's okay.
Your track and field teacher came today
as well.
He waited for a long time.
I think he's left.
I guess he came again. It's cold today.
You can talk to him later.
It's a happy ending after all.
Thank you for today.
-Don't mention it. Go.
-Goodbye.
Let's go.
Are you okay?
-Seon-gyeom--
-Don't go.
I won't, so let go of this.
I know you will.
Let me go, and we'll talk.
Wait. Let's just stay like this
for a minute.
I've…
never been stubborn about anything.
So I don't know how to do it.
But could you not teach me?
Not teach you what?
How to break up.
You can teach me everything else,
but could you not teach me that?
Can you just…
like me?
Please.
Please, Ms. Oh.
Catch me if you can.
Do I still look like a kid to you?
Yes, and that's exactly why
I should keep you close at all times.
You didn't come home last night.
-Yes.
-Are you not coming home again?
I'm so frustrated that I can't sleep.
It wouldn't be that hard
to figure out where he is.
What about you?
-How dare you run away?
-What? Me?
I knew she was crazy,
but not to this extent.
Where should I sleep tonight?
I'll pounce on you.
-I miss you.
-Why don't you join our agency?
I'd like us to work together.
You did a good job.
Then why don't you come over
for some ramyeon?
We'll have the house to ourselves.
Subtitle translation by: Ja-won Lee