My goal is
to tear down this building.
72 HOURS AGO, ROME, ITALY
CONSIGLIERE OF THE CASSANO FAMILY
VINCENZO CASSANO
CONSIGLIERE
A LEGAL ADVISER OR COUNSELOR
OF AN ITALIAN MAFIA'S BOSS
To Emilio's house.
Yes, Mr. Consigliere.
EPISODE 1
Why did you come here?
GRECCO VINEYARD
How can you do business
even on the day of your boss' funeral?
This is the last offer from my boss,
Fabio.
An offer from his grave? Not interested.
You can take it and leave.
Killing Union President Carlo
to take over the vineyard and the union
was a mistake on your part.
He was like
a brother to Fabio.
Whatever the offer is,
I won't be accepting it.
Does it sound like an offer to you?
This is Fabio's last act of mercy to a man
who killed his dear friend.
Are you here to make a deal…
or to threaten me?
If you sign this now,
there won't be any problems.
Get lost.
Go back to your country,
you arrogant yellow.
I fought fair and square to take over.
The Cassano family has no shares
in this place.
Get out of here.
You sure you won't regret it?
Regret?
The Lucino family is backing me up.
I'm not scared to go to war.
Regret is the most painful thing
you can experience in life.
Emilio.
I am here to give you a chance
to redeem yourself,
not to start a war.
Sure. Whatever.
Arigatou.
You uncivilized yellow.
Emilio.
You will pay
for disrespecting my people.
You neanderthal.
Vincenzo, did you curse at me?
What did you say to me?
Why are they spraying
the pesticides today?
We sprayed them last week.
Damn it! What…
Shit.
They're not spraying pesticides.
Oh, no! It's all burning!
Everything is burning!
Don't just stand there!
Move it! Now!
Hurry!
That asshole, Vincenzo!
I'll get my revenge!
I'll get back at everyone!
You and the Cassano family!
Hurry!
Father.
You could have done that
after the funeral.
It was his last order.
He told me to take care of it
as soon as possible.
Even so,
burning down the entire vineyard
was stupid.
He said I could use any means necessary
to get it done.
Right. My father always trusted
your decisions,
but never trusted mine.
Because you were always careless
when you took care of things.
You went against his word
that no matter what happens,
we do not harm women or children.
Vincenzo.
My friend.
My brother.
Now that I'm your boss,
I'd like to see you be more loyal.
Paolo.
My brother.
I am always ready
to show my loyalty to you…
as long as you deserve it.
Looking for me?
Did you enjoy the party?
Vincenzo.
I can hear Payan barking.
You must be heading towards the door.
How did you…
Oh, right. Let me apologize in advance.
I know that it's your favorite car.
I didn't kill you
out of respect for Fabio.
And this will be the last time.
I'm leaving Italy
and will never come back.
Do not look for me.
The next time you try to find me,
the car will explode before you get off.
Paolo.
I knew you didn't deserve to be the boss.
LIST OF BUSINESSES IN GEUMGA PLAZA
GEUMGA PLAZA TO BE DEMOLISHED
DUE TO CONGLOMERATE'S TYRANNY
GEUMGA PLAZA
Ta-da!
Get your blood sugar up with this.
YOU ONLY LIVE ONCE
I bought this from the most popular bakery
in Yeonnam-dong.
I'm good. Please go.
Eating this tasty snack
in the middle of a long day
is a form of happiness.
I'm happy enough already.
You're happy?
Didn't you sign up as a test subject
at a pharmaceutical
to pay back your student loan?
You didn't have any side effects,
but you were the only one
who blew the whistle.
-How can you be happy right now?
-I can.
I believe my action meant something.
You are fearless.
But…
will you still be happy
when Babel Pharmaceuticals sues you?
What?
They're livid right now.
They just ordered us
to destroy your life, Seon-ho.
No one really cares
about what happens to you.
Why? Because your sob story
won't make anyone sad.
It's not sad at all.
I'm the only one who actually
cares about your life, Seon-ho.
It's just me, Hong Cha-young.
Pull the cake topper.
YOU ONLY LIVE ONCE
How much is that?
My goodness. What a mess.
-Sorry, Cha-young.
-Where are you manners?
If you were late,
you should've taken a taxi.
That's faster than a taxi.
Besides, that's the city's trend.
Just tell me why you're late.
Lawyer Yoon In-seo told me
to make 1,200 copies out of the blue.
Intern Jang Joon-woo.
Tell me the kind of person
I hate the most.
Robotic people.
Right.
People who work their ass off like robots,
but always fall short in the end.
I might be lacking,
but aren't I a good intern?
A lovely intern at that?
If you start wearing different ties,
I'll think about
whether to like you or not.
But Steve Jobs wore the same turtlenecks.
I prefer sophisticated men
to stubborn men.
COURTHOUSE
DAY 1 OF THE HEARING
FOR BABEL PHARMCEAUTICAL'S LAWSUIT
Claiming the victims died
from the side effects of the drug
is still preposterous.
The plaintiff is provoking the press
with unproven evidence.
The victims all passed away
from cardiac infarction
and had no prior conditions.
One of them had arrhythmia.
Another had pulmonary edema.
And another had low blood pressure.
She extracted these conditions
from the victims' old medical histories.
The paramedics on the scene
stated that they showed typical signs
of an overdose.
Paramedics aren't licensed doctors.
They only stated the external symptoms.
Your Honor, I have the recording-based
statement from one of the test subjects.
Babel coerced him
to make a false statement
to silence the others.
-This statement clearly states--
-Your Honor.
The test subject who made the statement
turned himself in for perjury an hour ago.
I submit the interrogation report
as evidence.
After perjuring himself,
the witness planned
to extort money from Babel Pharm
through the plaintiff's counsel.
But as he was conscience-stricken,
-he decided to turn himself in.
-Your Honor.
It's a one-sided statement. His perjury
charge hasn't been established.
The recording should
be admissible in court.
We will rule
once the witness' perjury charge
has been established.
The next hearing will be held
a week from today in this courtroom.
That is all.
Give me a cigarette.
-I quit two years ago.
-Just leave, then.
At least wash your hair
when you come to court.
I don't need that from you. Just go.
We could have just settled out of court.
How could you start this mess
when you weren't even sure you could win?
Start this mess?
-That's no way to talk to your father.
-I thought you disowned me.
Right.
No daughter of mine would
buy off a witness like that.
Do you find peace
when you criticize your daughter?
You and Babel deserve it.
You guys are like mafias.
How could you be so proud
of destroying the powerless?
Dad.
Can't you stop?
Even if you don't treat me
like your daughter,
I still worry so much about you.
I worry that this might be
taking a toll on you
physically and emotionally.
Dad.
If you stop, I'll help you.
I'm embarrassed to say this now,
but now that I'm older,
I realized that family comes first.
-Cha-young.
-Yes, Dad.
Why don't you quit being a lawyer
and start anew as an actor?
That way, you won't ruin
other people's lives.
You'll never beat me!
We'll find out when it ends.
Also, I've made up my mind.
I am really going to disown you.
How will you do that?
I'm sure I'll find a way.
Bye.
Excuse me.
I need to do an inspection.
WANTED
NAME: PARK JEONG-GUK
May I see your identification?
REPUBLICA ITALIANA
VINCENZO CASSANO
Gosh. You're Korean Italian.
I'm so sorry. Gosh, my bad.
The wanted man is Korean, you see.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
Oh, my. You have such a cool name.
"Vincen Zo"?
Which Zo clan are you from?
-Give me back my passport.
-Okay.
Yes. Mr. Cho. I got here safely.
I see.
See you there, then.
It will take about an hour and a half.
Okay.
Come on. How can they cancel
when I just got here?
Excuse me. Are you looking for a taxi?
Yes.
I drive a limousine.
My appointment just got canceled,
so I am available.
Where are you headed?
Geumga-dong, Seoul.
Really? Then, I promise to
give you a comfortable ride.
-I'm good.
-I'm good, too.
Please get in. All right.
Gosh, you're so handsome.
Did you enjoy your trip?
Where did you go?
I'd prefer not to talk.
Okay. I apologize.
Turn on the news instead.
Okay.
…was apprehended by the police.
In several fishing villages,
Korea Coast Guard…
I must finish everything in a month.
Then I'll leave for Malta right away.
There have been many reports of crimes
against foreigners at our airport.
According to the police, they pretend
to be taxi drivers at the airport,
offer drinks after spiking them
with sleeping pills,
-and steal their valuables. Especially…
-Gosh, these assholes.
How could they when Bong Joon-ho
and BTS worked so hard for our image?
Scumbags like them
are ruining our reputation.
Don't you agree?
Based on the victim's statement
about the stolen valuables,
-A month from now, I'll be…
-the police are investigating if there are
any accomplices.
…drinking a cold beer
on Xlendi Bay.
The in-flight meal must've been salty.
He chugged the whole bottle.
Mr. An.
They caught Agent Wang when he was tailing
them in Incheon and cut his arm off.
What? Where is he now?
Can they reattach it?
Damn it.
Ma'am, ten minutes ago, Masato of
the Kawaguchi Gang stabbed himself
with a bread knife at a bakery in Busan
when our agents surrounded him.
What? With a bread knife?
Gosh, that's really long.
-Call for a helicopter and move out.
-Okay.
So what? Do you have the details?
How the hell did he get here?
He's…
He's a consigliere to the mafia.
He's in Korea?
When he came to Korea five years ago,
he was just an ordinary lawyer.
But now, he's no longer a small fry.
He's the key member of the mafia.
He came back to Korea as a consigliere.
Hey, Mr. An.
Why would they come all the way to Korea?
To achieve what?
There's a lot here in Korea.
We're a global target now.
Then, perhaps,
he just came here on a holiday
to have bulgogi, dongdongju,
makgeolli, and pajeon.
We should welcome him.
Sir, this isn't something
you should take lightly.
-The consigliere is a mafia's--
-What about it?
What the heck is that supposed to be?
It's like you're trying to get scolded.
We have to track him, sir!
The Italian mafia are a heinous bunch.
Just let him be.
Don't you dare launch some operation.
-But he's the consigliere--
-Why you…
Ms. Hong, I heard
you scored a big one today.
Congratulations, Ms. Hong.
You are indeed my role model.
Yes, I did it again today
Go, Hong Cha-young
You're so cool, Cha-young
I am so cool
Yes, yes, yes
Hong Cha-young, Hong Cha,
Hong Cha, Hong Cha-young
I should install blinds here.
Everyone can see through.
Come on, you should've gone easy on him.
He's your dad.
He's not my dad.
He's the counsel for the plaintiff.
Your dad still goes by his nickname
the Tosa among the alumni.
That's why he always takes things too far,
not knowing when to stop.
I'll end this at the next hearing.
Yes. That's it.
A competent lawyer can end things
before things get out of hand.
I should've quashed this
when he filed the petition. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
You should get off work early today
and have some fun.
Oh, right.
Check your bank account.
It's a bonus.
You don't have to give me a bonus.
You are already treating me so well here.
Hold on.
Gosh, I'm so touched.
It's fine. Just take it
and spend it all today.
Gosh, Cha-young.
Cha-young, Cha-young, Hong Cha-young
I'm so moved. I'm serious.
Did he deduct taxes again?
Come on.
His meals must've been salty.
I didn't even ask him to drink it.
He just drank it on his own.
Hey, didn't I tell you?
When I saw him at the airport,
I knew he was loaded.
Gosh, this is a designer bag, too.
Wait. What's this?
This must be over 4,000 dollars.
-Holy shit.
-Hey.
Look at his watch.
If this is authentic,
it'll cost over 100 million won.
Hey. It can't be a knockoff, right?
-Gosh, no way.
-Right? Right.
Look at his style.
He'd never wear a fake watch.
-Hey.
-Look at this.
-He even smells good, too.
-Really?
Find his cologne, too.
You're up.
Who are you guys?
Us?
We are what you think we are.
Seriously?
Gosh, that sounded so cool.
-I told you you were talented.
-Drop the beat.
50,000 WON
I swear I'm going to catch
you assholes and kill you!
I swear to God I will!
Stupid Korea.
Stupid Korea!
Be quiet!
I told you to be quiet!
Shit.
Damn it.
Shut up!
Damn it!
50,000 WON
Damn Korea! Damn it! Damn you, Korea!
You're dead!
Damn it!
Look over there.
He seems like a nice person
now that I get a closer look.
-He's so handsome.
-He is.
-He seems nice.
-Yes.
She only likes handsome guys.
-Seriously.
-Gosh.
Here.
Like this. Go ahead.
-It looks like he was beat up.
-Really?
-He's sure is handsome.
-That's all you care about.
GEUMGA PLAZA
CONGRATULATIONS ON PASSING
THE ARCHITECTURAL REVIEW
My goal is
tearing down this building.
What do you need advice with?
5 YEARS AGO, MILAN
CASSANO FAMILY'S STUDY
My friend, Fabio, told me
that you knew a safe way to hide my gold.
He said his old friend, Fabio, told him
that you would tell him
how to safely hide his gold.
I want to hide my gold in Korea,
not China.
And it must be kept safe to the point
that no one can steal it.
He wants to hide it in Korea.
And he wants it to be safe to the point
that no one can steal it.
There is this method our family uses
which has been passed down for 50 years.
Buy an old building in Korea.
Buy the building under my friend,
Mr. Cho's name
so you don't raise any suspicions.
And then, make one of the lots
look like either a shop or a company.
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
And hire technicians
to create a secret room in the basement
to store your gold.
To avoid getting caught,
transport the gold little by little.
To open the secret room,
the biometric system that recognizes
only you should be utilized.
It must only recognize you.
Not even your family or friends.
But there's more.
That secret room
comes with a special feature.
Sir.
-Mr. Cho, have you been well?
-Yes.
What on earth happened to you?
It's nothing.
What about my residence?
I heard you were coming,
so I had it cleaned.
And I also put away your items
and clothes from Italy.
-Let's get going now.
-Okay.
How are things going?
As you read it in the file,
the Development Opposition Committee
has been formed.
I already told them that
I wouldn't sell off the building.
But they won't believe me.
Oh, right.
Babel E&amp;C bought
all the shops around the plaza.
Any other pressure from Babel E&amp;C?
Nothing, other than the team leader
of Investment and Development
coming here daily to make an offer.
Sir.
The bathroom…
Damn it.
I already set up the bed
and blankets for you.
And I will schedule a meeting
with the tenants tomorrow.
Okay. Sure.
Once this project is done,
are you interested in staying in Korea?
No.
I see.
I put your new cell phone, cash,
and the things you asked for
in the bedroom.
Okay.
What's that?
Oh, the previous tenants put them up.
Should I get them off?
That's fine. I won't be here long.
Gosh, that's a lot.
-Really?
-Yes.
JIPURAGI LAW FIRM
I definitely saw a man with
the building owner at the entrance.
So I followed them.
But it looks like he even rented out
a housing unit upstairs from us.
-A housing unit?
-Yes.
When you saw him,
what's the vibe you got from him?
He kind of gave off an eerie vibe.
What was that movie called?
He looked like a handsome movie villain.
Did you know?
Handsome villains are
scarier and more brutal.
That must be why people
are scared of me. Goodness.
People aren't scared of you, Mr. Lee.
Should I go scare him
and get some information?
Like who he is and why he's here.
Mr. Nam, come closer. Come.
I'll grab his throat and twist it to
the side. Then, he'll start talking.
-Name?
-Nam Ju-sung.
-Where are you from?
-Wangsimni.
-Favorite food?
-Tteokbokki.
-Let go of his throat now.
-Okay.
Okay. You're good.
Tell the rest of the tenants.
-Hurry.
-Okay.
Most of the existing tenants moved out.
We have some tenants left
on the third floor.
Why is that?
The lawyer in the Opposition Committee
is on the third floor.
So that must have played a part in this.
The tenants in this building
are very cautious of me.
This is interesting.
DRY CLEANING
-Well…
-Gosh.
-It's an Italian restaurant.
-Yes.
Well, this is the usual routine.
This is a dancing studio.
What's wrong with him? Is he sick?
He's definitely sick.
Don't eat it, then.
Give me that.
You're basically telling me
my food is awful!
It's just fishy.
Your good looks can't save your ass.
I'm dirt-poor and have no connections!
That's everything I've got!
Stop it!
-I tap out.
-What are you looking at?
I like fishy food!
YEONGHO SNACK BAR
Save me!
-My goodness.
-You brat!
How could you only get 18 points
on your Korean test? Seriously?
Why you…
-I did my best.
-Are you a foreigner?
Are you not from here?
Are you from the States?
Get your guard up. Do it, you brat.
Keep your guard up, you punk.
Please save me. She's going to kill me.
You don't deserve to be saved.
Mom, it really hurts.
-Mom.
-You're a disgrace to this town.
I didn't give birth to an idiot.
They must be insane.
-Yes. This is supposed to hurt!
-What?
-You punk.
-Mom, come on!
You brat.
JIPURAGI LAW FIRM
Well…
Let's go to the basement
where the secret room is.
The business that used to be there
went under,
so I picked a more stable tenant.
Are you sure about that?
They are well-mannered.
NANYAK TEMPLE
So, the tenants…
It's a temple.
NANYAK TEMPLE
That monk is sitting on
15 tons of gold.
You are the owner of the building.
-Yes. Hello, sir.
-Hello.
I have joined
the Development Opposition Committee.
I plan to protect our temple.
All right. He felt a strong presence
of Buddha from beneath the temple.
-He's been fasting.
-"From beneath"?
-No.
-What about it?
-He's fasting.
-Yes.
He's just fasting. He's not eating.
I don't know who you are,
but you should clean your outfit
before you clean out your mind.
Gosh.
I want to get these dry cleaned.
BEST LAUNDROMAT
This is a very rare suit
you can't find in Korea.
The material is different, too.
It's a vintage brand label.
No, you're not getting it.
It's custom tailored in Italy
-by Booralro--
-As in "Testicles"?
Stop lying. Everyone says their suit
is expensive when they come here.
I'm serious. This was a limited edition
of Booralro's fall line.
What nasty name is "Testicles"?
I can tell this is cheap.
I'm from unit 606.
I want them by tomorrow.
You should've come yesterday then.
I can't finish them by tomorrow.
I heard that you came
with the building owner.
-Yes.
-Nice to meet you.
I'm the CEO and the senior lawyer
of Jipuragi Law Firm
and the chairman of
the Development Opposition Committee.
I'm Lawyer Hong Yu-chan.
LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
I see.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Lawyer Vincenzo Cassano.
-What?
-Is "Vin" his last name?
-Right.
-Is he Chinese?
-He might be.
-What did he say?
I don't know. What was that?
Just treat my name as an English name.
Vincenzo Cassano.
-It was Casanova. Casanova.
-That was English.
-Vincenzo Casanova?
-Right.
You must not be licensed
to practice law here.
No. I'm from Italy.
Mr. Baek, you've been to Italy.
-Yes, that's right.
-Right?
He studied to be a chef in Milan, Italy.
Then, you two must have
a lot to talk about.
We'll talk when an occasion
organically arises. We'll talk then.
Where in Milan did you stay?
Well, I was in Milan, Italy.
I stayed in the heart of Milan.
Uffizi?
Uffizi.
Nice to meet you.
I'll stop by later.
Okay.
I guess he understood it. What did he say?
If you're licensed in Italy,
you can't practice law here
other than give advice.
That's correct. I'm not here
to practice law here, anyway.
-I simply came to offer some advice.
-Is that so?
The owner told us
he wouldn't sell the building.
But we don't trust him.
We're different, Mr. Hong.
Don't say stuff like that.
Who would turn down a big payout
from a conglomerate?
We will tell you the details
at the meeting tomorrow afternoon.
Vincenzo Cassano.
What's wrong with the water?
Damn it.
Good.
There's no hot water?
Damn it.
There it is.
It's hot!
Are you kidding me?
What's wrong with the hot water?
Look at me.
It's so hot.
So hot!
Hot!
Come on.
Gosh.
MINISTRY OF JUSTICE
CHEONGJU WOMEN'S CORRECTIONAL INSTITUTION
Defense, make your argument.
The defense rests.
Prosecution, question the defendant.
Defendant Oh Gyeong-ja
was often criticized
by Chairman Hwang Deok-bae
and his family for her improper behaviors
as a housekeeper.
On the day of the incident, when
he said she didn't do her job properly,
she was livid and assaulted him
which led to his death.
The defense rests.
Your Honor,
Defendant Oh Gyeong-ja
had abandoned her own child in the past.
I'm submitting her affidavit
of voluntary relinquishment
of parental rights
to an orphanage in Incheon.
As she is a coldblooded mother
who even abandoned her own child,
it's highly likely that she does not value
other people's lives.
This proves the validity--
That's irrelevant to this case.
You're my lawyer. Say something.
I was sexually harassed.
His whole family is lying!
Don't say anything.
This will work against you.
Chairman Hwang sexually harassed
his previous housekeepers.
He harassed every woman
that came to work for him.
Defendant.
If you speak without permission again,
you will be escorted out.
Suit yourselves.
You've already made your ruling.
HONG YU-CHAN OF JIPURAGI LAW FIRM
APPOINTED AS THE NEW LAWYER
RETRIAL REFUSED BY THE INMATE
LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
…APPOINTED AS THE NEW LAWYER
The statement given by the test subject
who blew the whistle
on the risks
of Babel Pharm's clinical trials,
turned out to be false
which deeply impacted the lawsuit.
Lee had been a participant
in the clinical trial for RDU-90,
a new drug developed
by Babel Pharmaceuticals.
-Hey, look at that lady.
-He planned to extort…
-money from the company.
-Is she mad?
-His intention
-Does she think she's Jun Ji-hyun?
was exposed at the hearing.
Goodness, look at her swinging her hip.
-Their new drug, RDU-90, shows…
-Does she not have a washing machine?
Why is she dancing here?
This is a therapeutic place for me.
So what?
…the market is expected to face some heat.
I heard everything, you punks.
How dare you sexually harass a woman
in a public place?
Do you want the Ministry of Justice
to lock you up? You rascals.
Give me that.
Give me your phone now.
My gosh. Look at this. What…
I should smack you.
Should I send you to prison for this?
What's wrong
with a little dancing, you punks?
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry.
You stay here.
Sit down.
I'm not done with you yet.
I have one more bag of blankets to wash.
TI DIAMO IL
You're my sun
How beautiful you are
You are beautiful.
You're so handsome.
I love
Welcome.
What's your best dish?
Well, that would be my porcini dish.
It's truffle porcini spaghetti.
Everything on your menu sounds delicious.
I'll have that.
What?
Yes.
It tastes like you took this out
from a trash can.
But I'm glad…
that you removed the maggots.
So you studied in Uffizi, Milan?
Yes, in Uffizi.
I see.
But Uffizi is in Florence, not Milan.
What?
I…
A con artist.
-He learned to cook at Uffizi Gallery?
-Excuse me.
I…
Come again.
CHEONGJU WOMEN'S CORRECTIONAL INSTITUTION
You're out.
The look on your face tells me
you're losing again.
Did you become a psychic?
How can you tell?
It's been five years
since I first met you.
I can tell just by looking at you.
Has it been that long?
You're being treated, right?
Thanks to you.
To be less of a burden to you,
I should die soon.
Gosh. Come on. Don't say stuff like that.
Hearing that drains my energy.
You don't have to visit me
every month now.
People might think
that you're my secret husband.
You can tell them that I am.
It will be nice for Cha-young
to have a mom.
Gosh. Goodness.
Anyway, Ms. Oh,
-for one last time--
-Don't even bring up the retrial.
I really don't need it.
Just leave me be.
I've done a lot of bad things in life.
Did you have a nice trip?
Yes.
The team leader from Babel's Investment
and Development is on his way.
I'll go and meet him.
Where should we meet?
There's a cafe across the street.
How about my office?
It concerns our plaza.
Wouldn't it be better to do it
in my office?
How many times must I repeat myself?
My client will demolish the building
and build a new one.
And the previous tenants
will have their lots back.
All right.
This is our last offer.
It's a much better offer
from two days ago.
It's the best we can do.
Do you not understand me?
I hear you just fine.
You know what?
I wanted to wrap things up nicely.
If you keep this up, things will get ugly.
I'm here on behalf of Babel E&amp;C.
If you keep rejecting our offer,
you'll regret it later.
-Are you threatening me?
-Just a little?
Don't ever threaten me again.
It's my first and last advice to you.
What?
-No one is here yet?
-No.
Did you eat?
-Hey.
-Gosh.
-Hey, do you have more? What is it?
-Gosh, what?
Mr. Tak, take off your shoes
when you come in.
Sorry about that. Are you upset?
-You always forget that.
-Sorry.
Mr. Lee, do you have
a wet rag attached to your feet?
Either wash your feet
or put on some socks.
Sorry.
My sweat glands are clustered
on the bottoms of my feet.
-It's an illness.
-Come on.
Everyone, please don't touch the glass
when you open the door.
Do you know how hard it is to wipe this?
There's a handle here.
Gosh, my mirror.
Sorry.
I closed the curtains for a reason.
All right. So is everyone here?
As tenants, we want your promise.
That's why we plan to draw up
an agreement by tomorrow.
And you can sign it
by the end of this week.
I know what you said yesterday,
but are you really a lawyer in Italy?
Yes.
Then how will you handle it
when you don't know our law?
I don't think
my legal qualification matters here.
Our promise to you and your signatures do.
I will guarantee that you will have
your lots back once I rebuild this place.
You promise, right?
We never lie.
What do you think?
Well, they seem very genuine.
Why don't we trust them?
I'm also going to trust you,
Mr. Vincenzo Casanova.
Yes. Me, too, Mr. Casanova.
Let me inform you in advance.
I know martial arts.
If you are deceiving us,
I'm going to put you in a guillotine choke
for six days straight.
Don't do stuff like that. No one cares.
You're embarrassing and so tacky.
Let's sum it up.
Who agrees to trust them?
My gosh. That annoying Vincenzo.
This doesn't feel right.
We have no choice.
Right. Damn it.
This is driving me crazy. Darn it.
Let's give him the benefit of the doubt
and go with the flow.
Merciful Buddha.
Mr. Hong.
The tenants have nothing
but your word to go on.
But I find this unfortunate
because it looks like
you're toying with us.
Is it that hard for you to trust me?
I pretended to trust you earlier
to assure the other tenants,
but I never trust people like you.
I am a lawyer,
and so are you.
But we clearly have different jobs.
You represent money,
but I represent people.
I also represent people.
Oh, yes.
Rich people.
I know Babel E&amp;C will buy this building
so I prepared myself for everything.
So don't pretend
to be a mediator in front of me.
Just proceed with your plan.
Where's everyone?
Honey.
Ju-yeong.
My goodness!
Honey!
Ju-yeong!
-Who are you people?
-We don't have time to chitchat.
Ju-yeong.
GEUMGA PLAZA CONTRACT OF SALES
-All right.
-You…
Stamp your seal on it.
I have a show to catch on TV.
ATTORNEY HONG CHA-YOUNG
JIPURAGI LAW FIRM, LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
RECIPIENT HONG CHA-YOUNG
What is it this time? Come on.
RELINQUISHMENT OF PARENTAL RIGHTS
RECIPIENT HONG CHA-YOUNG
DUE TO ETHICS VIOLATIONS
My goodness. Jeez.
I'm good.
What do you mean?
I'm not interested.
I'm so sick of him.
GEUMGA PLAZA CONTRACT OF SALES
Don't you think I'd be a better actor?
Of course, sir.
-Gosh, that's a no-brainer.
-Come over here.
Yes.
Okay. I got it.
Check your bank account. It's over.
Hey, let's go.
-Yes, sir.
Gosh, let's go.
It says that by nature of clinical trials…
Hello, Ms. Hong.
Who are you to barge into my office?
That's some nasty manner you have.
What's this?
Oh, that?
I mailed that to remove you
from my family registry.
You can't do that anymore.
The family registration system
was abolished ages ago.
You're a lawyer.
I can still try, can't I?
-Hey.
-Yes.
This one, too.
And look at this. This is ridiculous.
"The petitioner rejects
the following words
and any similar words from the recipient.
The following words are,
appa, abuji, papa, daddy,
otosang, bàba, and père."
This is just outright ridiculous.
It's so immature.
-Mr. Nam.
-Yes?
I'm talking here.
Go ahead.
LAUNDRY MASTER TAK HONG-SIK
Damn it. How is this even possible?
You Korean. Damn you. Get out of my sight!
Damn it.
Yes.
What happened to my suit?
It's because your suit
was made from cheap fabric.
-It doesn't happen to good fabric.
-Cheap?
-Do you know how much this is?
-How much?
This is a limited edition
from Booralro's line…
There's no point in talking to him.
By the way, you have a nice build.
You know? You still look cool
with that tight suit.
This might catch on.
Did you do this on purpose?
What are you talking about?
I'm the laundry master.
Then you shouldn't have messed up!
You will have to pay
for what you did to my suit.
You will.
Tenants of Geumga Plaza,
come out of the building now.
Someone's looking for me.
Pay before you go.
Damn it.
Yes, Mr. Cho.
My wife and daughter were
taken hostage. I had no choice.
I'm sorry.
I'll fix this no matter what.
Yes. I will…
Mr. Cho.
Mr. Cho. Mr. Cho? Mr. Cho!
Fine. I can overlook everything
you wrote here. I can live with that.
But this one. Look.
"All the photos that the recipient
took with the petitioner as a minor and
photos that remind the recipient
of the petitioner as the parent
will be donated for the exhibition,
Geumga-dong's History,
held at the Sangcheon District Office
for public interest."
Who are you to donate my photos?
They're the epitome
of my embarrassing past!
It's up to me.
I raised you.
And does that give you the right
to abandon me? This is embarrassing!
"Embarrassing"?
It's because what you do
is less than human!
You're a lawyer. How could you not
have a sense of duty or justice?
Your sense of duty just makes you
the nosiest lawyer in the world!
And your sense of justice is just
groundless hostility against the rich!
This is called mechanical justice!
"Mechanical justice"?
Then is following money
"rational justice"?
Yes. Money is justice in Korea.
And power means justice.
Then, keep living your life like that!
But do not show your face around me. Okay?
Okay. Let's cut off all ties!
-Yes. Let's do that.
-Don't.
Let's never call each other.
-I won't.
-Don't you dare call me!
-Mr. Hong!
Never call me!
Mr. Hong.
You have to come outside now.
GEUMGA PLAZA
Hello.
My gosh. You're a bunch of lazy bums.
Why haven't you put up the signs?
Do it now.
Aren't you cold?
Let's go.
-Yes, sir!
NOTICE
SELLER: CHO YEONG-UN,
BUYER: BABEL E&amp;C
-What happened?
-What?
-But he promised.
-What happened?
What do we do, then?
-Put it up. Just do it.
-Okay.
Cover up the sign.
Hello, sir.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Park Seok-do, the CEO of Ant Company
and the chairman of the Development
Committee for Babel Tower.
What kind of company is that?
It's a shady company
that performs dirty jobs
like high interest loans
and beating people up.
I see.
Oh, right. As of today,
this building belongs to Babel E&amp;C.
Starting today,
the Compensation Team will visit you.
Let's handle this peacefully.
I knew it. Damn it.
This was their plan. But what?
They'll let us move back in?
That lousy Vincenzo or whatever.
I should've shrunk his suit even more.
-Where is he?
-Right.
If any of the tenants give us a hard time,
one of these uncompromising men
will tire you out physically and mentally.
Hey.
Are you crazy? What are you doing?
-Why?
-Who are you?
-You can't do this.
-Why not?
-Are you okay?
-You startled me.
I thought I hit you.
You can't block the path to the restroom.
-What about the people who need to go?
-You got me excited for a second.
Goodness.
-Guys, step aside. Gosh. It's urgent.
-Okay.
I don't want him to do his business here.
Hurry.
-Go. Go ahead.
-Thank you.
My goodness, that idiot.
He's so embarrassing.
Leave now.
You're violating the law
by threatening us like this.
Why don't you stop already?
We will compensate you handsomely.
You say you'll compensate us,
but you'll just beat us up
and kick us out.
This is a good occasion.
Why are you ruining the mood?
-Gosh.
-Hey.
Who are you?
I'm his only daughter.
And I'm Lawyer Hong Cha-young
of Law Firm Wusang.
-You're not my daughter.
-Come on. Be quiet.
-What is a lawyer from Wusang doing here?
-It's none of your business.
This isn't the way
to go about your business.
Don't you know the era we live in?
It's not like we're in
some '90s gangster movie!
Hey, miss.
Do you want to get beaten up
like the movies from the '90s?
-My goodness.
-Hey!
If you touch me again,
I'll make you pay for what you did!
Sure. Okay. Let's see how much money
I have to pay to settle with you!
Stop!
What did he say?
Where's my tape measure?
Do you also need to use the bathroom?
Is it urgent?
Go ahead. Go on.
-Go.
-Let's talk.
Who the heck are you?
Vincenzo Cassano.
I represent the owner of Geumga Plaza,
Cho Yeong-un.
"Vinchenzo Quassano"?
This is ridiculous.
There's no talking your way out of this.
Hey, hold on.
Goodness.
I'm not that curious, but I'll listen.
So what is it?
-Sir!
-My nose is bleeding!
-A nosebleed?
Gosh. Come on. Seriously.
You jerk.
-Oh, no!
-Boss!
If you take one more step…
-your boss will fall.
-Don't move, you dimwits.
Just stay still.
Everyone, stay still.
Given the height of the building,
you won't die.
You'll just break your leg.
But if you're unlucky and fall head-first,
I will be the last person
you see from this world.
Right?
Shouldn't we stop him?
He said he won't die. Leave him.
Pull me up now, you asshole. Pull me up!
Babel E&amp;C bought this building
through illegal means.
And I will not forgive their atrocity.
Unless you want to die, pull me up.
Now!
I'll get this building back
no matter what.
And I will make all of you
pay for what you did.
This building belongs to me.
That was Italian, right? What did he say?
-What?
-What did he say?
He said…
È mio!
SPECIAL THANKS TO JIN SUN-KYU,
LEE HEE-JUN, JEONG SOON-WON
I don't expect you to believe me.
"Threatened"?
Are you still pulling that stunt of yours?
I will blow both you and the tenants away
with this stunt.
My experience tells me
that there's more to this.
A reason enough to make them act this way.
He could have secretly stashed
a fortune in Korea.
Aren't we the best in the country
when it comes to playing dirty?
I don't like things dragging on,
so cut it short.
-Assholes like them should be made to pay.
-"Assholes"?
Cha-young! Tomorrow at 11 p.m.
Legal or not, we'll get the job done.
We have to stop them no matter what.
Hey!
I thought I'd do the same as you did.