ALL PLACES, CHARACTERS, FIRMS AND EVENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTITIOUS.
Where is he?
Where is Lee Jae-shin?
I think you've got the wrong person.
What?
You know where he is.
Where is he? Tell me quickly.
I don't know.
Where is your phone?
Call him.
Call Lee Jae-shin right now.
We're done here.
I said call him!
Move.
Move!
Lee Hyo-joo!
Are you okay?
Why were you talking to Yoon Song-ah?
Why would you ask her about Jae-shin?
What happened between you and him?
What's going on?
There's nothing going on.
Not with me.
I can only help if you're honest with me!
Does it have something to do
with Yoon Song-ah?
I said nothing's going on!
Just find Jae-shin.
He's your friend.
Why don't you know where he is?
What exactly do you know?
What kind of friend are you?
I kept going back and forth
about calling you,
EPISODE 12
and I thought it'd be better
to ask you directly.
I don't understand why Hyo-joo
said that to you yesterday.
Can you tell me why?
I think there was a misunderstanding.
What could there be to misunderstand?
Director Lee Jae-shin and I...
We were in a relationship.
Of course, that's over now.
So you two dated.
May I know when the relationship ended?
It was
quite recent.
Then, when my sister was dating him...
That was why we broke up.
Anyway, he and I are done.
I don't know why she came to me yesterday.
I see. You can leave now.
Yoon Song-ah,
by any chance, do you know
where Jae-shin might be?
He's turned in a letter of resignation
and I can't get in touch with him.
Two hot americanos with
two shots of espresso
and two pumps of vanilla syrup, please.
Here you go.
We'll call your name when they're ready.
Thank you.
Two hot americanos, please.
I'm jealous.
He's got a fiancée and a mistress.
This is why you need to be a big shot.
Who? Oh, Director Lee Jae-shin?
He's probably going to get fired though.
The chairman won't take this lightly.
That female employee's career is over too.
She'd be too ashamed to show her face.
Did you look her up?
She's pretty.
That's probably why he was seeing her.
Right.
Should we go take a look?
Excuse me.
You should be more careful
about what you say.
Who are you?
I'm Chae Hyun-seung from KLAR.
If you want to see what she looks like,
do that when you're sued for slander.
-That's okay.
-No, it's okay.
Thank you.
What's Yoon Song-ah's relationship
with Director Lee?
I don't know.
I heard Chairman's
granddaughter went berserk.
She was shouting and acting crazy.
-Maybe they're having an affair.
-An affair?
She's got some nerve.
He's engaged to Chairman's granddaughter.
She's shameless.
That's why she's messing around like that.
-No self-respect at all.
-Song-ah.
Do you want something to drink?
Yes, I want to get some coffee.
Excuse me.
I'm not as brazen as you think I am.
Nothing's going on
between Director Lee and me.
You seem curious.
No, we aren't.
Come on.
Let's go.
Watch your mouth!
You did great.
This kind of chatter dies down soon.
I know it's hard now but just ignore it.
Okay.
You don't have to stay in the office.
Do you want to go out?
Why avoid them? She's done nothing wrong.
That's not what I meant.
The weather is nice today.
She could let off some steam.
It's fine.
I have a meeting later.
I'll just stay in the office.
If that doesn't bother you.
What are you talking about?
Stop that nonsense.
Let's have something nice for lunch.
I'm sure Manager Kwon will gladly pay.
Okay.
CHAE HYUN-SEUNG
Pay for the coffee
by thinking of nothing
but me today.
Jae-shin?
-Come out.
-No.
I'm going to wait for him here.
You knew Jae-shin was seeing someone.
How long have you known?
That's not a problem.
I won't allow this.
Let's go.
You don't get any say in this.
That's my business.
How could this be your own business?
Do you have no self-respect?
Why are you giving yourself up for him?
You deserve more than this!
Because I love him.
I can't live without Jae-shin.
I can't.
Walk straight. You might trip.
I'll just trip then.
I don't care about falling.
I don't care about crashing
or getting lost.
I'd welcome it all if I can be with you.
What I'm saying is,
you can tell people about us.
It's okay to tell people we're dating.
It'd make things easier for you at work.
But it'd complicate things for you.
Thank you.
I prefer a hug over a thank you.
I'll always be by your side
anytime, anywhere.
You can lean on me at any time.
I'm here for you.
Okay.
I took notes of today's recipe.
You can go over them at home.
-Okay.
-Good job, everyone.
Thank you.
We had a great time today, Chef.
So did I.
I have something to tell you.
Today's the last day of cooking class.
Oh.
Why so sudden?
Is everything okay?
It's just taking more
out of me than I thought.
I want to focus on the restaurant.
I'm sorry.
I guess this is it then.
It sure is a bummer.
-It really is.
-That's too bad.
-We do thank you though.
-Thank you.
You can go. I'll do the cleanup.
Let me help. It's a lot to do by yourself.
No. It's more convenient for me
to do it by myself.
Is everything okay with you?
Yes, everything's fine.
That's good.
You know we are friends, right?
I'm here if something's troubling you.
Okay.
Did I call you out at a bad time?
No, I have some downtime.
What brings you here by the way?
I was having lunch
with a former team member
and I thought of you.
I'll just cut to the chase.
Have you thought about
working somewhere else?
Working somewhere else?
You know I'm working at a foreign company.
Yes.
My team needs
an assistant-manager-level ABM.
I think you'd be perfect for it.
We haven't found the right person yet.
I'd like to work with you.
Your salary would be
much higher there too.
Thank you for thinking of me,
but I haven't considered
changing jobs yet.
Not even once?
It's about time to consider.
Why don't you chew it over?
It won't hurt you.
I'll email you the details.
Okay.
One more thing.
I heard you're in trouble at work.
I know it's just a rumor, so don't worry.
I just want to tell you that
this could be an option for you.
I know.
I'll contact you.
Oh, this?
Senior Yoon asked me to buy it.
You don't have to lie.
We all know.
Of course, we know.
How could we not?
Finally. It was hard
pretending not to know.
What? What's with the look?
Why do you all look so surprised?
I've been working here for so long.
Anyway, take good care of her.
You're the only one she can rely on now.
I will.
Thank you.
They said that?
I guess we really are terrible actors.
No wonder they were acting weird.
Even though we're in the same team,
I didn't expect their trust when
there's a rumor going around about me.
I'm so grateful to them.
Come on.
It's because you get along with them well.
Even if they didn't know about us,
they'd definitely believe you too.
Whose girlfriend is this great person?
I'm sorry.
Whose girlfriend am I? Of course
I'm Chae Hyun-seung's girlfriend.
I have something to tell.
I met a former colleague earlier.
When you went out for a while just now?
She asked if I wanted to work with her.
I see. And then?
I told her I'll think about it.
What's your thought, Hyun-seung?
I get a say in this?
Of course.
This affects us too.
Us.
If I were being selfish,
I'd say I want you in the same office.
But this is about your career.
If this job offer is better for you,
you should take it.
What I want is for you to do
what you want to do.
How many days has it been?
He quit this company.
Why aren't you accepting his resignation?
You're too soft.
That's how you get stabbed in the back!
-I'm sorry.
-Stop saying it and show me some action!
With the Europe project and everything,
we have too many things to care about.
There is no time to waste on that goon.
Are you that incompetent?
You can't work without him by your side?
About that...
I'll make sure the project goes smoothly.
That worthless hoodlum.
How dare he embarrass me like this?
You better make it clear with Hyo-joo too.
If she makes another scene because of him,
I'll disown her just like
what I did to your parents.
If you don't cut ties with him,
I'll take away your position too!
Manager Kwon!
URGENT NOTICE: PERSONNEL APPOINTMENTS
KLAR SENIOR MANAGER KWON -
KLAR ACTING BM
DATE OF APPOINTMENT:
EFFECTIVE AS OF TODAY
What in the world?
Manager Kwon Sung-yeon.
Did you see the notice?
I just saw it.
You'll be the acting BM
before we find a new BM.
What about Director Lee Jae-shin?
You won't be seeing him here anymore.
Report to me about
the projected sales for this month.
What in the world is happening?
Is BM Lee really not coming back?
Let's just...
I'll find out more about it later.
Let's see.
Let's get the projected sales
for this month.
Let me ask around a bit.
Thank you. Please come again.
Thank you.
Hello.
I want a refund.
Sure. Just one second.
Do you have the receipt?
I'll get a refund for you right away.
May I know why you want to return it?
I watched a scrub review video
and it said the product is bad.
It doesn't exfoliate
and it'll damage your skin.
Our products?
That's not possible.
Can you show me that video?
What's worse than KLAR's mascara?
BEAUTY FUN FUN
It's their cream shadow.
The creasing effect is just too much.
Do you see this?
It gets on the small creases,
making them stand out.
And it hardens so fast.
Look at this.
It's very hard.
Who would buy this?
People are returning our products
because of this video?
Yes.
Three people came in for a refund today.
She might be sabotaging
our brand on purpose.
She's bashing our basic skincare
and color makeup.
It's not just a simple low-star review.
I agree.
But we don't have any concrete evidence.
If we provoke her without evidence,
it'll backfire on us.
In the worst-case scenario,
it'll damage our brand image.
I think she has a routine.
Why?
She targets certain brands
and leaves bad reviews.
This kind of content gets higher hits.
She got a few hundred thousand views.
So she gets more subscribers this way.
And we're her unlucky victim this time.
What do we do?
We can't just let this happen.
Of course, but we can't do
anything right now.
We need concrete evidence.
Are you really going to spend
the whole night watching all her videos?
Yes.
I'm not sure if I'll find something,
but I want to do everything I can.
I can't sit by while our products
get slandered.
I'll watch the videos with you then.
You will?
It's our job. And it's my brand too.
It feels very smooth.
Let me test if it lasts long.
I'm going to apply it around my eye.
It applies very well. The more layers...
I have to tell you this.
I'm so angry at the poor quality
of this product.
I just had to post a video.
I don't want these for my subscribers.
Don't waste your money on
this garbage cosmetics.
Oh, my.
The design is cute and lovely.
The quantity is smaller
than other brands.
The texture is moist
and glossy, not matte.
You can see how clean
the shading effect is.
You get moist lips
and it doesn't come off easily.
So it looks natural.
The mirror is big,
so you can see very well.
This puff...
Huh?
What is it?
Senior Yoon.
I got the purchase history
from the CRM Team.
Really?
She's been buying our products and yet
she said it was her first time using them.
She's been a VIP customer for years.
You found her reviews on our online mall?
Right here.
She said the scrub is a holy grail item.
And she said our cream shadow is good,
so she bought all the colors.
This will definitely get her to back off.
She'll have to.
If not, we'll take legal measures.
You're meeting her today, right?
I won't remove the video.
That's why you contacted me, right?
No.
No?
Everyone has their own preferences
for makeup products.
We understand if you are not satisfied.
We're here to confirm
some information with you.
Confirm what?
I watched your video.
You said you'd never used our products.
That's right.
I only use imported products.
But when we were
looking through your videos,
we found something familiar.
What's this?
This was our VIP gift two years ago.
I got this from a friend.
I didn't even know I had this.
Take a look at this then.
We searched the portal
and found your name.
We compared that with our CRM data.
You've been our VIP customer
for three years straight.
Those were all gifts for others.
Even if I did use them,
are you saying that I can't give
bad reviews if they suck?
Of course not.
But, a week ago,
you said the same product
was a holy grail item.
We can only suspect that
you exploited KLAR
for your personal gain.
For example, you wanted to cause a stir
and boost the number of your subscribers.
That's funny.
I already have so many subscribers.
I'm going to post
what you're doing right now.
Go ahead with it.
The law will be the judge.
We're going to hold you responsible
for the damage of our brand image
and the drop in sales.
That's why we asked to see you today.
So what now?
What do you want me to do?
The decision is yours.
Just as your subscribers
are important to you,
every one of our customers
is important to us too.
We do our very best
when we create a product,
so that we won't disappoint them.
We hope the same for you.
Don't disappoint your subscribers.
Oh, my!
I made that in the cooking class.
I want you to try them too.
Thank you so much.
How is the class? Still having fun?
It's over now.
Isn't it an on-going project?
The chef wanted to focus
on the restaurant
and so he ended it.
That's too bad.
I know you were enjoying it.
There's nothing I can do.
It's his class anyway.
By the way, I prepared two servings.
Hmm?
It's for you and
your mysterious boyfriend.
Okay.
I ended the cooking class.
Your wife knows it.
I heard.
She seems like a good person.
She seems genuine.
Unlike you.
How much longer will you deceive her?
What do you mean?
Can I tell her the truth then?
About how we got close and grew apart?
You already told her.
You wanted to befriend me
and so we got close,
then we grew apart as we didn't get along.
You're the one who ran away.
Like a coward.
What are you trying to say?
You disgust me.
It's the same now as it was back then.
You draw a line because you're scared.
And you leave me
to deal with the aftermath.
Do you really see me as a friend?
Have you ever thought of me as a friend?
If I haven't, it's your fault.
You project your feelings onto me
and cross the line.
-Don't come around anymore.
-That's right.
I still like you.
That's why I can see clearly.
You're afraid to accept yourself.
And I pity you for that.
I don't have to accept anything.
This is me.
What happened in college?
That was a one-time thing. A mistake.
I'm not the same as you.
I like men?
Are you crazy?
I thought we could go home together.
I didn't know you have a guest.
He's here because of his wrist.
I'm done. We can leave now.
No. I forgot to pick up Ha-eun.
She must be waiting for me.
I'll get going now.
Man.
This looks wonderful.
I didn't make this,
but I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you.
Is it good?
It's really delicious.
I love watching you eat.
I love shrimp.
There's a lot of shrimp. Eat more.
This is peppermint tea.
It's good for relieving tension.
Something's going on, right?
You sounded tired on the phone.
And you look very tired too.
Does it show that much?
Is it something you can't share?
If it is, you don't have to tell me.
I'm just worried about you.
It's about my best friend.
He's severed all contact
and disappeared.
Actually, he's my sister's fiancée.
I guess it was just me
who thought we were friends.
I knew he didn't really
consider me as one.
But having that thrown in my face,
it's...
It hurts a lot.
I feel betrayed too.
I'm more worried
about my sister right now.
I don't know if Hyo-joo
will let Jae-shin go.
Hyo-joo?
Are you talking about Lee Jae-shin?
Then Lee Hyo-joo...
You know my sister?
She was my customer.
I mean, she used to be.
What a small world!
I love that I have a shoulder to lean on.
It's nice.
Here's a cold glass of beer.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Great work, Senior Yoon.
You too.
Do you think she'll remove the video?
We'll have to wait and see.
We've done our part.
The rest is up to the legal team.
Have you decided what to do
about the job offer?
Why?
Looking at you today,
I don't think you'll leave.
Even if you do, I think you'll come back.
You can tell, right?
I noticed this from the beginning.
Do you like KLAR that much?
Yes.
Why?
I don't know.
I just love being a KLAR marketer.
I love being able to say KLAR is my brand.
I feel especially good
when I see someone using our product.
My first product is lipstick.
I was on a bus
and saw someone taking it out of her bag.
I wanted to ask her how she likes it,
and tell her that
I'm the one who developed it.
It was so hard trying to stay still.
Really?
Yes.
What?
What's with you?
Screw this wretched world.
Wretched?
The world is beautiful. Right?
I'd like to apologize for
my recent post.
The KLAR product review was misinformed.
I wanted to make it more interesting,
and so I exaggerated
some things in my video.
I'd like to apologize to all my viewers.
Okay.
With this apology, things will smooth out.
The return requests died down too.
Did you ask the PR team
to release an article?
Yes, they'll print that
we won't press charges.
I heard you two worked hard on this.
Well done.
Thank you.
Let's have an office dinner soon.
Sounds great.
You're dismissed.
Okay.
Thank you.
Give me a moment, ABM Yoon Song-ah.
Did you hear from Jae-shin by any chance?
I don't think he'll be contacting me.
If he does, could you let me know?
I won't take it the wrong way.
Okay, sir.
Now onto another topic.
Did you receive a job offer recently?
Things might be uncomfortable right now,
but I hope you're not going to leave us.
You're very much needed at our company.
Thank you.
You need to eat.
It's been days.
I don't feel like eating. Go away.
Your brother told me to make sure you eat.
Just a little bit.
I'll leave this here then.
Please eat some.
Did you find him?
His phone has been turned off,
and he's not using his credit card.
It's not easy to track him.
If it were easy,
I wouldn't have hired you.
I'll pay you more. Just find him!
That's it for the weekly meeting.
Right,
we're getting an intern today.
Already?
I know, right.
Wasn't it yesterday Hyun-seung joined us?
You were so fresh-faced back then.
It's only a year,
but I can hardly recognize you already.
Should I break down in tears
right about now?
I was joking.
Don't cry.
Right, sir.
I was wondering.
The intern's desk.
Where should we put it?
It's best if it's next to you.
But this is the only empty desk we have.
Set it up here.
Yes, sir.
You want some help?
It's okay. I can do it by myself.
Can I have a moment, everyone?
This is Ko Myung-jin.
He'll be our intern for a month.
Hello, I'm Ko Myung-jin.
It's nice to meet you.
You can greet him later.
Your desk is here.
You'll learn the basics
from ABM Chae Hyun-seung.
Yes, sir.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
Yes.
Myung-jin.
You can sit.
Yes, sir.
Did you learn how to access the intranet?
I can show you.
It's okay. I'll figure it out.
If you need anything, let me know.
I'll explain our brand
in the meeting room later.
Okay.
I think that covers the brand description.
Now about the job assignments
within the team.
There are basic skincare and call sales.
We have color makeup
and department store sales too.
At the same time, we manage PR,
inventory management
and visual merchandising.
To put it plainly,
our task is to manage all the processes
from product manufacturing to sales.
I see.
Is there anything else
you'd like to know more about?
Feel free to ask.
I had many questions when I was an intern.
I don't have any though.
Okay then.
I think we're done here.
Okay.
It's close to lunchtime now.
Do you want to join us for lunch?
How about the cafeteria?
I'll eat by myself.
I can do that, right?
Sure, if that's what you want.
Thank you.
Okay.
Oh, my god.
You've been turned down?
This is our colleague,
ABM Chae Hyun-seung.
Our interns.
Hello.
Looking sharp, right?
Let's go. I'll save you from eating alone.
Let's go.
We're meeting the sales team today.
They asked for our input
about their sales promotion.
Marketing usually gives them policies,
but sometimes they do their own thing.
I see.
Sir.
Yes?
I'll be honest with you.
I'll soon be joining another company.
This is just for the experience.
So you don't need to train me.
I know.
Our team's intern said
your intern is going to another company.
Really?
Yes. So don't waste your time on him.
I'm still going to
do my best to train you.
That won't make me stay here.
That's not what I'm trying to achieve.
But I learned this from my trainer.
A brand marketer must think that
he is the brand.
When you hear KLAR's name in the future,
I'm sure I will cross your mind.
I don't want to be remembered
as an insincere and irresponsible person.
Let's get on.
Ahem.
Chef Ryu isn't seeing anyone, right?
No. But I don't think he'd be interested.
Marriage isn't his thing.
It'd be nice. But…
You can't always get what you want.
What were you two like in college?
I liked him.
Honey.
Are you happy when you are with me?
I'm suddenly curious.
I'm happy, are you?
I'm grateful.
Thank you for being my wife.
Do you have something
to say to Hyun-seung?
Gosh.
It's about the brand description.
Can I get the original file?
Okay. Sure.
Thank you.
Also,
can you buy me lunch tomorrow?
At the cafeteria.
Okay.
Sure.
Let's have lunch together tomorrow.
Thank you, Senior Chae!
Bye!
Take that home.
Bye.
Mommy!
Ha-eun!
Oh? Uncle!
Where's Mommy?
Something came up,
so she asked me to get you.
Is she on a date with Daddy again?
Maybe. What will you do then?
You want to go on a date with me?
Let's go on a date.
-Let's do that.
-Sounds good.
Awesome.
How did you grow so tall?
Excuse me?
I'm going to grow as tall as you.
Ha-eun said she'll marry me
if I become as tall as you.
One moment, please.
Marry him?
I was feeling generous.
Just like that?
Why are we standing here?
Just one moment.
Senior Yoon!
Hello, Ha-eun!
Meet my girlfriend.
You finally did it!
Now you know I'm good.
I found it!
You found it!
Should we get the bigger one?
Where are the potatoes? Potatoes.
Here they are!
Let's give it to him.
What do you think will be better?
-This one.
-That one?
But that one has a bug in it. A bug!
Which one looks good?
-It's good.
-Is it good?
You're giving me one?
It's very delicious.
Should we ask your uncle to get this?
My uncle buys me many toys.
Really?
Let's dry your hands.
My uncle plays tennis very well.
Oh, I see. That's great.
My uncle listens very well too.
So you did well, Auntie.
Okay.
How is it?
It's so good!
It's delicious. Isn't it, Ha-eun?
I love it.
Is it good?
Eat as much as you want, Ha-eun.
Do you want mussels?
Here.
My hands are tied.
Seriously.
Here.
Thank you.
It's so delicious.
I can sell this.
Who is prettier? Auntie Song-ah or me?
You're asking me?
Of course you're prettier, Ha-eun!
You should've said
your girlfriend is prettier.
I'm sorry, Auntie.
My uncle still has a long way to go.
This is my girlfriend.
It's very nice to meet you.
Now I see why Hyun-seung looked all happy.
Open the door for me.
Okay.
Be careful.
Her backpack.
Thank you.
Let's grab dinner
when both of you are free.
It'll be my treat.
That sounds great.
Why is Ha-eun sleeping at your place?
Yeon-seung went to
a funeral with Wu-hyun.
They are out of town.
Drive safely.
See you another time.
Sure. Drive safely.
Bye.
She said you buy her toys,
play tennis well
and listen to her well.
Then, she complimented me on my choice.
Ha-eun is very wise for her age.
I'm worried if I set
her standards too high.
But she left out the most important thing.
What I do best is loving Yoon Song-ah.
More like you say
corny things really well.
Action speaks louder than words.
Want me to show you?
Stop it. You're too much.
I'm sorry to show up like this.
I really need to tell you something.
Can we talk?
If you must say something,
just say it here.
It's not something
you have to worry about.
Please.
I'll head home.
Call me afterward.
Okay.
You said you wanted to talk.
I was thinking...
I never properly apologized to you.
This may sound like an excuse,
but I didn't mean to keep lying to you.
I wanted to tell you.
But when I was with you,
I could be myself.
I didn't have to be scared that
you'll see the real me.
I could be myself in front of you.
I wanted to hold on to you
just one more day.
I thought maybe you'll be understanding.
I was selfish
and let things unravel like that.
Because I was afraid that you'd leave me.
I'm not asking you to forgive me.
I just...
It was real for me.
I'm sorry that it ended the way it did.
I just wanted to tell you this in person.
I heard you resigned.
What will you do from now on?
I haven't thought that far ahead.
I'm going to start over
with what I truly have.
If I've fallen to the bottom,
then that's where I'll start.
By the way,
Jae-woon might find out about our past.
I'll make sure you
won't be treated unfairly.
He already knows.
I hope that didn't cause you trouble.
It didn't.
And also,
don't worry about me.
Not anymore.
Okay.
I understand.
Can I come in?
Come in.
Is everything okay?
Why are you here?
I wanted to see you.
You should've called me.
I didn't want to waste time.
Why are you still unchanged?
Were you staring at
your phone all this time?
I was just doing this and that.
He came to apologize.
Said he was sorry.
I thought this wouldn't bother you.
I never said it doesn't bother me.
How can it not bother me?
You're my girlfriend.
I think about you all the time.
It's crazy.
I'll leave now.
Get some rest.
Already?
I saw the face I wanted to see.
I should go.
Night.
That wasn't enough for me.
Stay for a while.
It's late. How long is a while?
I don't know.
SHE WOULD NEVER KNOW
Just let go.
He said he's already moved on.
We shouldn't let things get further.
I'll die then.
Ma'am,
I'm the fruit basket guy.
I'll take you to somewhere you like.
Is Song-ah dating someone?
You know, that young man?
What do his parents do?
Did BM Choi suggest you join the TF team?
Do I just have to accept
whatever you decide?
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you sooner.
We're not breaking up.