You're letting your guard down!
Yuzuha!
Father.
I will survive!
What?
How was it?
No good. I can't find any leads.
In any case,
let's gather anything that we can use.
FURNITURE AND INTERIOR GOODS FLOOR
I knew it. It's no good.
All the IC chips have been destroyed.
Video cameras, digital clocks.
Anything that operates
via an electronic circuit board
won't function at all.
But things like this still work, huh?
Since they don't have IC chips installed.
What does that mean?
Maybe...
-Hurry up!
-Look, fireworks!
It might have been
an electromagnetic pulse attack.
I've read about this on the Internet.
When fired into the stratosphere,
it's a weapon capable of destroying
the electronics in an entire city.
Seriously?
So why is this still operating?
I have no idea.
VISA
RYOHEI ARISU
REMAINING DAYS: 3
What?
It's useless if we can't charge it, huh?
This area looks safe.
All right.
This will serve as a decent weapon.
What are you going to fight against?
Zombies?
You can't use electricity
and gas either, right?
But I can still use the portable stove.
Batteries work.
So we can use flashlights, too.
Don't you feel like eating something warm?
I feel alive again!
Nice and hot!
We haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
What were the three of you doing?
When everyone disappeared, I mean.
We were in a restroom.
We were talking in the same cubicle.
I don't really understand what's going on.
What about you?
Saori...
Work.
I was inside the meeting room
organizing the work materials.
And then everyone disappeared
from the office.
Did you see or hear anything?
Chief?
I don't remember.
I arrived at this place three days ago,
and I was made to join the game
out of nowhere, like everyone else.
Everyone died, except for me.
You used them all as bait?
Say whatever you want.
I just...
I just wanted to survive.
Well...
What game was it?
I was at a subway station.
It was a game where they used poison gas.
Everyone was vomiting blood.
Blood was even flowing out of their eyes.
Isn't it strange?
When everyone disappeared
from this world.
It was yesterday
for the three of us, right?
Yes.
But it was three days ago for Shibuki.
Why at different times?
You're right.
And even the vegetables were rotten.
It was only a few days
since everyone disappeared.
What could be the reason?
Maybe the way time passes
is different from normal?
What?
I don't really know,
but even among us,
the time when people disappeared
is different, right?
Did we time travel
while we were in the restroom?
That's impossible.
But it's also impossible
for people to disappear.
Time traveling does not exist.
How do you explain the game
and people disappearing?
Don't ask me that.
In any case,
One thing we know for sure about this game
is that there's a game master.
Game master?
Someone came up with this game.
That I'm sure of.
While we were in the restroom,
they moved the people in Tokyo away
and prepared for this game?
Then they ascertained our movements
and fired lasers
on people's heads when it was time.
Can a human really do all that?
I'm sure it's possible if they inserted
a highly accurate
GPS microchip into our bodies.
Now you're talking like an IT technician!
But who could be behind that?
Could it be the federal
or state government or something?
I've heard some rumors in my company.
An IT corporation from Europe
wants to conduct an experiment,
where within a VR space,
they attempt to create a world
completely identical to the real world.
But we should be able to distinguish
VR from the real world.
It hurts.
I don't think
VR can cause burns like that.
It must be God.
This must be the work of God.
Otherwise, it's impossible
to explain what's happening.
Don't be stupid.
So God really exists.
Hey, is your injury getting worse?
It's all right.
It's going to be fine.
I think Chota needs to see a doctor.
Given his personality,
he must be enduring the pain.
But he's at his limit.
Arisu.
Let's join the game tomorrow night,
just the two of us.
What?
We still have three days
left on our visas.
It's better to get used to the game
while we still have time to spare.
We'll probably have to
beat the next game
with Chota's injured leg.
Are you all right?
Thank you very much.
If we don't learn how to clear the games
with just the two of us,
we won't be able to protect Chota.
You're right, but...
And we can search for a doctor too.
It's easier to meet people in games.
Do we have to do that again?
There might be a hint
as to what the game is about!
Well, I guess.
If we join the game,
we might be able
to find out their signature.
Signature?
If someone actually made this game,
we will definitely be able to find out
their characteristics through the games.
If we can discover that,
we might be able to figure out
a strategy for the game.
TOEI SENDAGAYA APARTMENT
ONE PER PERSON
FACIAL RECOGNITION IN PROGRESS
PLEASE WAIT A MOMENT
THERE ARE CURRENTLY TEN PARTICIPANTS.
Please wait until the game commences.
One minute until registration closes.
Excuse me.
Where did all the people in Tokyo go?
This thing--
-There are so many people.
-I wonder if there's a doctor here.
ONE PER PERSON
Registration has closed.
There are a total of 13 participants.
The game will now commence.
Excuse me.
Just what is this?
I ended up here.
I have no idea what's going on.
-It's a game.
-Stop it.
Beginners will only get in our way.
It doesn't feel great,
but it might be a good idea
to act like Shibuki did.
Difficulty, Five of Spades.
Five of Spades?
It's a physical game.
Strength is everything here.
I'm Nitobe. Nice to meet you.
-Each mark has a different meaning?
-Exactly!
The mark on a trump card
signifies the game's genre.
Club refers to a team battle,
and Diamond refers to a battle of wits.
As for Heart...
It's the most troublesome one.
"Troublesome"?
It's a game of betrayal
where you play with people's hearts.
What about the numbers?
The difficulty level.
The larger the number,
the harder it is to clear.
Game, "A Game of Tag."
Rule. Run away from the tagger.
What?
A Game of Tag?
-Who's the tagger?
-How should I know?
Clear condition.
Discover the safezone
hidden in one of the building rooms
within the time limit.
You clear the game
when this objective is fulfilled.
Time limit, 20 minutes.
After 20 minutes has passed,
the time bomb hidden
in the building will explode.
TOEI SENDAGAYA APARTMENT
O Holy Mother.
Please save us from our tainted souls.
Our smiles are the light of hope.
The Holy Mother will appear when we smile.
O Holy Mother.
Please save us from our tainted souls.
Our smiles are the light of hope.
The Holy Mother will appear when we smile.
So you believe in God.
Here you go.
I've also been doing nothing
but praying recently.
I don't believe in God.
But my mom
has always been super religious.
Because of that, I was bullied in school.
But Arisu and Karube saved me.
They are good friends.
Karube is good at fighting
and is popular with the girls,
while Arisu is clever
and comes from a reputable family.
Someone like me,
I come from a poor family,
and I don't have anything I'm good at.
And now that I'm injured,
I have to rely on everyone else again.
Humans like it
when someone weaker follows them
because it makes them feel at ease.
But not them.
Do you think you'll be able to
join the next game with them?
Your leg is injured, you know?
They are different.
Then will you die for your friends' sake?
Two minutes until the game starts.
Stop following us.
I'm trying to gauge you guys.
Maybe both of you are suitable
to be my allies.
What a joke.
-Are you a doctor?
-No, I'm a real estate agent.
How many times have you played the game?
Let's see, maybe five times?
And you've always won?
Well, I guess.
Where should I go?
I don't know!
You can only rely on yourself.
If you can choose
your starting position,
this is the perfect location.
What?
That's nasty.
Let's see...
Everyone looks like
they're about to die, as usual.
I guess you've always been
betrayed by people, Shibuki.
You've never met anyone decent.
That's right.
The same goes for you, right, Chota?
O Holy Mother...
Please save us
from our tainted souls.
You're wrong.
It must have been tough for you.
The game will now commence.
The time limit is 20 minutes.
Game start.
The tagger is on the move.
Anyway, let's just search
for an unlocked door.
We won't make it if we dawdle like this!
Three minutes have passed.
What was that sound?
He's dead.
Arisu!
-Run!
-Go!
-Arisu!
-Run!
-Down!
-Hurry up!
Hurry up!
-Move aside!
-What's with you?
Hey!
-Arisu, hurry!
-Karube, wait!
Chota,
I can trust you, right?
When it happened,
I was actually having sex
with my superior.
I hated him.
Didn't you say you were working?
They are not even my allies.
Why do I need to tell them the truth?
Since we're both the same,
we should get along.
In order to live...
This is impossible.
This is crazy. I can't do this!
Hurry up, Mai!
Mai!
Aya.
I'll fucking kill you!
Don't come closer!
I told you the truth
because it's you, Chota.
O Holy Mother...
Holy Mother...
The Holy Mother will appear when we smile.
O Holy Mother...
Wait for me, okay?
...from our tainted souls.
Our smiles are the light of hope.
The Holy Mother will appear when we smile.
O Holy Mother,
Please save us from our tainted souls.
Please accept this.
Our smiles are the light of hope.
The Holy Mother will appear when we smile.
Very well, this way.
O Holy Mother.
-Let's go over there.
-Let's pray together.
O Holy Mother.
Please save us
from our tainted souls.
...from our tainted souls.
O Holy Mother.
Please.
Save them.
What should we do, Arisu?
Can you come up with any solution?
We can't clear this game
with something like that!
-Just think, Arisu!
-Then you think of one!
The tagger didn't see us.
His field of vision
is narrowed due to the mask!
It's his weak point!
That could be the key!
-Everyone!
-Hey!
The tagger is currently
at the second level of the central area!
Stop it. You'll get killed!
The tagger has bad vision
because of his mask!
Let's inform each other
of the tagger's location
and search for the safezone together!
It's a good idea,
but no one will respond.
The tagger is moving
from the fourth level of the central area!
Anyone nearby, run!
Really?
-Quick, run away!
-What?
I'm sorry.
A climber?
She's pretty good.
Eight minutes until the game ends.
There are currently seven survivors.
Hey!
Over here! Hey!
Hey Arisu!
We don't have the time
to help someone else!
Don't just sit there, move!
Hey, move it!
Shall we begin?
Arisu!
You go first!
Damn it.
Let's take the tagger out.
We're going up against a machine gun here!
No, that's a human.
The tagger is 190cm tall and weighs 90kg.
Their dominant hand is their right hand.
His shooting is rudimentary.
Most likely
an ex-SDF officer or policeman.
I got it.
Take this.
Let's go hunt down the tagger.
Go search for the safezone.
What?
Hey!
-Don't command us!
-I got it.
I'll search from the top.
Arisu!
-Don't do that.
-We don't have any other choice.
I checked the 5th floor on the south block
and the 6th floor on
the east and south blocks.
Let's split up
and search for the safezone.
I haven't checked
the 1st and 2nd floors.
Understood. I'll go check it out.
-Hey!
It's time to get rid of the tagger.
Five minutes remaining.
See you later.
Okay.
Just where is the safezone?
Calm down. Relax and think.
Come on, follow me.
He wields a MAC-10
and finishes shooting his 32-round ammo
in 1,5 seconds.
We'll go for him when he's reloading.
I'm over here!
Just come at me. I dare you!
Aguni?
Aguni!
You just let him die?
Think.
Why did he shoot
from such a long distance?
So you realized that too?
Yes. The safezone is in this apartment.
Aren't you going to open it?
Why did the tagger chase us?
They could have just waited here.
Seems like there's something else
we don't know.
However,
if you don't open it...
Three minutes until the game concludes.
Look out!
It never hurts to be prepared--
PUSH BOTH BUTTONS
AT ONCE TO CLEAR GAME
Damn it.
Someone, please come over!
The safezone is in Apartment 406!
It's impossible to clear the game alone!
We need two people to do this!
Seriously?
Arisu!
This is getting interesting, huh?
Time remaining, one minute.
Someone!
Please come!
Time remaining, thirty seconds.
Twenty seconds.
You called?
Ten seconds.
Hey!
Five.
-Four.
-The buttons!
Three.
Two. One.
Game clear.
Congratulations.
Excuse me.
This person...
Were they also made
to participate in the game?
Answer...
...in our hands now.
"Answer"?
Hey, can you hear me?
Hey, what's this "answer"
you're talking about?
Return.
The answer is in our hands now.
Return to the Beach.
"The Beach"?
Return.
Return to the Beach.
Subtitle translation by: Qianni Lu