Someone has been calling you.
What? Who?
RDU-90.
Isn't that the researcher?
Dad.
Dad!
No…
Dad…
Hong, a civil rights lawyer,
passed away due to an accident
in Geumga-dong, Sangcheon-gu.
He was revealed to have violated
the attorneys-at-law act
and of committing subornation of perjury,
shocking the public.
Hong was a civil rights lawyer
who had defended
the Babel Pharmaceuticals' victims
and had given voice to the weak.
Due to this accident, however,
his true face was revealed.
While undergoing the recent trial,
Hong demanded money and bribed
those who were involved.
He also convinced Lee,
a deliveryman, to commit perjury.
He had been under investigation
after violating the attorneys-at-law act.
This news has shocked the victims
and many others who revered him
as a civil rights activist.
LAW FIRM JIPURAGI
LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
Mr. Hong, I forgot…
I forgot my keys.
LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
TO LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COUNSEL
THANK YOU FOR BEING THE LAST STRAW
I COULD GRAB ONTO 10 YEARS AGO
DECEASED HONG YU-CHAN
WE WILL CHERISH YOUR MEMORIES
I'M SORRY
I LOVE YOU
I COULD PROTECT MY FAMILY
THANKS TO YOU
I WILL NEVER FORGET YOU
YOU'VE TAUGHT ME WHAT HOPE IS
This is the medical report.
Babel Pharmaceuticals' new drug,
RDU-90, has been approved
and will be released soon.
RDU-90 is considered
the perfect painkiller
due to its lack of side effects
and lasting effects.
A lawsuit regarding the death
of one of its test subjects
had been filed,
but it has been confirmed that it wasn't
directly related to the drug.
THANK YOU
I WON'T FORGET ABOUT YOU
I DON'T BELIEVE WHAT THEY'RE SAYING
ABOUT YOU
THE RICE SOUP YOU BOUGHT ME
WAS THE BEST MEAL I HAD
REST IN PEACE
YOU WERE MY ONE AND ONLY
FAMILY AND FRIEND
THANK YOU FOR HELPING ME
YOUR DEATH WILL NOT BE IN VAIN
I COULD GET OUT OF THAT LONG DARK TUNNEL
THANKS TO YOU
EPISODE 4
LAW FIRM JIPURAGI
Cha-young's first time fishing.
She was good but never wanted
to do it again.
High school graduation.
She didn't want flowers.
Had four servings of ribs by herself.
February 20, 2008.
45TH JUDICIAL TRAINEES'
GRADUATION CEREMONY
January 12, 2014.
Graduated from the training institute.
My dear beloved daughter, Cha-young.
I hope you won't become
an awful lawyer like me.
I love you, Cha-young.
Pungho.
Maru.
Sijin. Eunseom.
This is my first time watering you.
I'll be your new dad from today on.
Let's go to my…
Water has been leaking
from an apartment in Mapo-gu
although it had been built
less than a year ago.
Poor construction has been suspected
as the cause.
You're really closing down
this law firm, right?
There had been issues…
Yes.
The residents are preparing
to file a lawsuit against the constructor
and the company due to the water leakage,
cracks on the walls, and the frequent
malfunctioning of the elevator.
There has been an increasing number
of complaints regarding apartments,
and people have asked the government
to come up with an effective solution.
Next news.
This morning,
an unidentified male body was found
in the coastal waters of Gijang, Busan.
The police are currently trying
to identify the man…
They've decided
to close the law firm.
You seem quite despondent.
Damn it. I haven't done anything for him.
What could you have done?
Were you going to beat up those bastards?
Why not? I could have if I wanted.
Then who will take care
of our plaza's issue?
Didn't Mr. Cassano say he'd buy a building
and let us move there?
Do you actually believe him?
I wonder how he's doing.
They said he'd wake up in a week.
He has been unconscious
for 9 days and 13 hours.
Mr. An.
Why would you count the days
he's been hospitalized?
I just enjoy counting time.
One hour, two hours…
I also don't believe
that he'll move us to another building.
-I think he was just bluffing.
-Bluffing?
He's not the type to bluff.
You're wrong. He bluffs quite a bit.
He criticizes my dishes
as if he was a connoisseur.
He's been in a huge accident.
He must hate this country now.
So he'll probably return to Italy.
You're right.
He has no time to think
about other people like us.
Did you know?
Mr. Cassano installed electric pads
at the temple for the monks.
He also taught some boys
who were smoking around here a lesson.
Goodness. Really?
I believe you're making him out to be
more selfish than he actually is.
That's how I feel.
It's been ten days
since Dad passed away.
The media has painted him
as a crooked lawyer.
I've closed down Law Firm Jipuragi today.
But I have yet to find closure.
I don't believe
that it was a mere freak accident.
So I want to do something about this.
But I have no evidence.
I don't know where to start…
I must be crazy.
I said I wouldn't cry.
Don't be an idiot.
Get up and say something already.
I'm so frustrated.
I'm paying for this private room
and your hospital bills
just to hear your story.
Do you even know how much it costs?
-Then let's go to the bank first.
-Just wire it to me.
You woke up so randomly.
What is going on?
Let's go.
Where do you think you're going?
We need to see if you're all right.
Let's check for any numbness
or cognitive disorder.
The numbness subsided last night.
You woke up last night?
I remember everything.
And I recognize you,
so I'm fine, aren't I?
Then did you hear me cry just now?
You didn't sound like an idiot at all,
so don't worry.
Hey.
Why didn't he tell me that he was awake?
What are you looking at?
I sent this to my daughter recently
as a wake-up call.
RELINQUISHMENT OF PARENTAL RIGHTS
She'd become an incredible lawyer
if only she could think straight.
Times have changed.
Earnest, upright,
and old-fashioned lawyers like me
can never beat the people who are corrupt.
You need someone
who's strong and brazen.
Cha-young fits that criteria perfectly.
Then you should've told her so yourself.
She would never listen to me.
Maybe later. When the time's right.
If I don't get the chance to tell her,
you should do it for me.
Why do you carry around that lighter
when you don't smoke?
Because the sound helps me
focus and calm down.
What's your plan?
Something smells fishy.
I'm going to look into the accident
and the driver himself again.
It's all over.
I'm aware of that.
I just want to double-check.
Why?
Is this your way
of paying your father back?
That's not it.
I may discover something new.
Until two weeks ago, you were his enemy.
But not anymore?
You should've done that sooner.
Are head injuries known
to make people rude?
Anyway, don't do anything.
Nothing will change.
How can you say that
to a bereaved family member?
I've always wanted to tell you this.
Goodbye.
I'm so dumbfounded.
How dare he make me out to be
a horrible daughter?
…a countermeasure is said
to be in the works.
Next news. The unidentified body
found in Gijang this morning
turned out to be a researcher
from a pharmaceutical company.
The police have notified
the family members of his death and…
Yu, a researcher, sent his will
to his company through a scheduled email.
The police believe it was suicide.
The company had been interrogating him
for siphoning pharmaceutical ingredients,
putting the victim under stress.
The police believe he committed suicide
due to the pressure.
The police will hand over his will
to his family
and investigate the incident
more thoroughly.
I'm Choi Yu-bin from YSN News.
Detective Gu.
There's a pressing matter
you must look into right now.
Mr. Nam.
I'll be your bodyguard
and do chores around the office for you.
Please don't close it down.
We can't keep the place for long.
Our registration will expire soon.
If this is about money,
sell anything you have to my pawnshop.
I'll give you a good price.
Don't be ridiculous.
We have no money.
-Well…
-Gosh.
Sir!
-What?
-Sir!
You're back!
-Mr. Cassano.
-Sir.
I was worried.
Thank you.
You look better than I thought you'd be.
-Well, then.
-Wait.
About what you said about helping us
move to another building…
Let's talk about it next time.
-I need some rest.
-But…
By "talk about it next time,"
do you mean you'll reconsider it?
I mean we should talk about it again
next time.
Did you change your mind?
Aren't Italians known for being punctual
and keeping their promises?
Aren't they?
You can't do that.
We've put our trust in you.
We have nothing.
You shouldn't confuse people like us.
-You're right.
-Right.
-Come on, now.
-Let's go in.
We need food on our table!
-I told you, didn't I?
-This can't be.
-This is unfair.
-I knew it.
-Why won't he tell us?
-He can't do that.
Listen!
Don't you think you're being rude?
You're receiving free help from me,
and all you can do is suspect me
and complain?
Is it because we didn't pay him?
What I mean is,
you should at least
have an ounce of faith!
Since we've been betrayed so many times,
it's not easy for us to trust anyone.
You should walk in our shoes for once.
Keep this up,
and I'll have no desire
to keep my promise.
So you're going back on your words.
That's not what he meant!
Damn it! I'm so frustrated!
If you keep being wishy-washy,
we won't be able to trust you.
Fine.
If you can't trust me,
you should look for another lawyer.
But…
What a wonderful sight.
It is, isn't it?
Goodness.
I came here thinking you could be making
Molotov cocktails together.
I love how you've fallen apart.
This was exactly what I was hoping to see.
Let's see.
That geezer of a lawyer is dead now.
And they've ousted the Italian lawyer.
All right, then.
Let's talk compensation, shall we?
I'll be generous.
Generous, my foot.
He's not running a charity.
I can hear you.
Isn't it too hot for a beanie?
Your face is like a heat wave.
Your face suffocates me.
Then is your face the rainy season?
It's so dark and gloomy.
What? What did you just say?
Cut the nonsense and leave.
How obnoxious. This doesn't involve you.
Stop trying to act cool.
How do we negotiate with you?
-Larry?
-We should at least discuss it.
Come to my office with your seal,
and we'll get it all sorted out at once.
Hey, Mr. Italian Lawyer.
What did you do to Mr. Na
that he's acting all scared?
What's it to you?
You little bastard!
Your bluffing is on another level!
Shut up. Adults are trying to talk here.
He was being way obnoxious.
I couldn't help it.
I'm sorry.
Listen carefully.
The day we demolish this place
and pour our first cement,
you will be under it.
Then you'll be there with me,
since I enjoy people's company.
Why you…
-He hit him.
-He got hit.
-He slapped his face.
I swear he has a few screws loose.
He's not scared of anything.
It's all over now.
I'm not this generous usually.
-Hurry up and go.
-Let's go.
All right. You first, Larry.
You can use your thumbprint as well.
-Well…
-Let's go right away.
-What about an unofficial seal?
-That's fine too.
Your guess was correct.
It was Yu Min-chul,
the researcher for Babel, who died.
Cha-young.
Hey, Cha-young.
Weren't you coming back tomorrow?
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Why?
Mr. Yu Min-chul, the researcher,
and my father passed away.
-Was it a coincidence?
-What do you mean?
Did Babel Pharmaceuticals scheme this
along with Wusang?
Without my knowing.
I know you're not really yourself
right now,
but such a conjecture is inexcusable.
-Come back first.
-Please process my resignation.
Come on, Cha-young. What's with you?
Let her do what she wants. Let her resign.
There's no use keeping a hound
that bites the hand that feeds.
There are no bad dogs to begin with.
-It's mostly their owners' fault.
-Be honest.
You planned to double-cross us,
but things went awry, right?
That's such a lousy story you have.
I was going easy on you until now
since we were a family.
But not anymore.
Thank you for the encouragement.
Cha-young!
Are you seriously leaving?
You have to return everything.
Your car keys,
and what about your studio apartment?
Here are my car keys.
I'll give you my house key
after I move out.
Cha-young.
Know your place.
I don't even have to lift a finger
to snap your neck like a twig.
Thank you for motivating me.
ATTORNEY HONG CHA-YOUNG
Hey, you're overreacting.
This isn't right.
You're being awfully casual today.
That's not the issue here.
Cha-young.
No, I won't let you go.
Tell the boss
that you made a mistake
because you were grieving.
And beg.
Koreans forgive you when you beg, right?
If you're too out of line,
even begging doesn't work.
No. Still, don't go.
I'll help you with everything.
I…
I can be your spy. Like James Bond.
Joon-woo.
Cha-young.
You're like glue.
Move. I need to move out of my house.
No.
Cha-young. If you leave like this,
I'll never see you again. Never.
Make your choice.
Cha-young!
It's over for us. Over!
The public has shown great interest
in Babel Pharmaceuticals' new drug,
RDU-90.
Thanks to its lasting effects
and the lack of side effects,
it was known to be an innovative drug
since it was under clinical trial.
After learning about its upcoming release,
many countries such as Vietnam
and Mongolia have shown interest.
Babel Pharmaceuticals is willing
to do anything with open arms
if it's pertaining to the people's health.
During the testing period,
the company was involved in a lawsuit.
However, after the illegal activities
of a righteous civil rights lawyer
were exposed,
the manufacturing of RDU-90
was resumed once again.
Through this incident, we were able
to see clearly who was in the wrong.
NAMDO AUNTIE'S RESTAURANT
DO NOT CROSS
How dare you?
How…
I need to ask you a favor.
I keep asking you for favors.
Goodness, don't say that.
If it wasn't for you, I would have been
compost in a vineyard in Milano.
Tell me what you need.
Damn it! What the hell is that?
Who the hell could've done that?
What is certain is that
it wasn't the work of some small fry.
I agree.
It's Chairman Jang's house
for Pete's sake.
It's not easy to break into his room
with the security system and the guards.
I really don't know any opponents of ours
who'd hire such experts.
What are you doing there?
-What?
-Sorry?
REP. ATTORNEY
Oh, I'm formatting and reinstalling.
The computer was damaged by a virus.
-Why not call the tech team?
-He's not good at his job,
-but quite tech-savvy.
-Right.
Get it done and leave already.
My goodness.
We need to give Chairman Jang something
if we want to placate him.
How about her for the time being?
-Who?
-Someone who has a motive.
Her?
Come on, that's not right. How could you?
God, you're really evil.
We believe Ms. Hong Cha-young
is the most ideal suspect.
I knew it was that lawyer!
She's blaming my company
for her father's death!
Whatever. Put her behind bars
this instant.
All right.
Keep smiling.
Pretty soon, you'll be shedding
tears of blood.
NOTHING'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR BABEL
Dad.
I don't think I can be a wonderful lawyer
like you.
But, instead,
I'll be one hell of a tenacious lawyer.
I hope we get along.
Sir, I hope we get along.
You're so beautiful.
-I hope we get along.
-Okay.
You're also beautiful.
Law Firm Jipuragi has come back to life!
Feel free to ask me for help.
Does this mean we'll resume
what we've been working on?
Yes. I will continue my dad's work
regarding the lawsuit
related to this building's tenants.
Then what about Mr. Cassano?
Forget about him.
He can do whatever he likes.
We have her now.
I hope we get along.
Congratulations.
In any case,
I'll help you guys from now on.
Word has it that you were working
in opposition to your father.
That's all in the past.
I've been born again.
I will fight against corruption
and injustice while obeying the law.
With warmth and benevolence,
-I will embrace you--
-Ms. Hong Cha-young.
Hello, sir. How may I help you?
You're under arrest
for trespassing and blackmail.
-Let's make this easy.
-What do you mean?
Stay still.
-Ms. Hong.
-What are you doing?
-Come on.
-Don't cause a scene.
-No!
-Stop.
Come on!
I've been home since 7 p.m. last night.
For now, we can't verify
that you went home and stayed there.
Then check my phone's location
during the time of the incident.
Then you'll be able to verify that.
You could've left your phone at home
and gone out.
Are you saying I singlehandedly penetrated
Chairman Jang's security,
broke into his bedroom,
and put 50 syringes in his pillow?
Do you think I'm Black Widow?
-She was arrested?
-Yes.
They suddenly came and took her.
Did she break into someone's house
and threaten them?
She did.
How did you know that?
I didn't. I was just guessing.
I can't get her out.
-So if you could help--
-She's competent enough
to get out of there before evening.
Don't worry.
Wait, sir.
We'd appreciate a bit of help.
Please?
I…
I have an opera to watch.
What? An opera?
I don't need to worry about her.
She'll get out on her own.
AM I EVIL?
"If I am indeed evil,
it's because…
of you."
I called the police station,
and things aren't looking good.
Why can't she get out of there?
Jeez.
Come on!
Can you please be quiet? Please?
Her records are clean,
and her alibi checks out.
Her second-floor neighbor confirmed
seeing her through the window.
This is driving me crazy.
Wusang already paid us.
First, let's order some breakfast for her.
Okay.
-Cha-young.
-What? Hey.
You should've called sooner.
Wasn't I your only hope?
No, you were the 57th person I called.
What?
Who are you?
I'm from Law Firm Wusang.
I'm Lawyer Jang Joon-woo.
Why did you come here, sir?
I'll sue if you've broken any rules
-while investigating.
-Stop embarrassing me.
Do you have proof?
You don't, right? Right?
That's enough.
So why is she still here?
I want to see your commanding officer.
This instant.
You should know better
than to throw a tantrum like this!
"A tantrum"?
Did he just curse at me?
Yes, he did.
He pretty much said, "You son of a…"
-How dare you?
-Here's your proof.
This is CCTV footage taken from
a convenience store in front of her house.
It shows that she came home from work
at 6:27 p.m. two nights ago
and stayed home until 8:12 a.m.
yesterday morning.
And who are you?
I'm a lawyer and her legal representative.
What's gotten into him?
Now, show me a irrefutable proof
that she had an accomplice.
If you don't have anything,
she has every right to be released.
I was going to get you out of here. Right?
Do you have proof?
Do you?
Gosh, I knew it.
I'm hungry now that I feel better.
Order me some food before I go.
Who ordered the cheeseburgers
from BurgerJura?
Here!
Please calm down
and have some food.
You should've ordered some seolleongtang.
Did you only bring one ketchup?
Enjoy your meal.
I was going to have that.
Never mind. Go ahead.
Order some more burgers.
-Isn't it too greasy?
-No.
I just can't have fries without ketchup.
It's so greasy.
Why didn't I think
of that convenience store?
POLICE
Yes, we're done here.
Okay. I'll leave as soon as I'm done here.
It's fine. Yes.
I'll see you later. All right.
Tell me the truth. It was you, wasn't it?
You only came out of guilt
because they arrested me. Right?
You felt guilty.
What are you talking about?
Lawyer Vincenzo Cassano?
You're the first Korean
to pronounce my name correctly.
I used to be her assistant back in Wusang.
I'm Jang Joon-woo.
How do you know me?
Because I did a background check
on you for Cha-young.
I was relieved to see
that you had no priors.
I should get going.
-Go. I'm leaving too.
-What?
Wait up!
But I just got here.
You can't just leave.
Gosh, it hurts.
I should get to work.
Welcome.
A double shot of espresso to have here.
Just have a cool, iced Americano.
In Italy, Americano is no better
than sewage waste.
One iced sewage waste for me.
I'm the most sharp-witted person in Asia,
so come clean already.
You must be the best
at feigning ignorance.
Don't you think this is a bit harsh
after what you put me through?
I thought you'd find your way out.
I apologize.
-I'm sorry for the inconvenience.
-Are you really?
It's as if you're apologizing
for canceling my song at a karaoke.
I get pretty upset
when someone does that to me.
Why the hell did you do it?
Because I was furious.
-What?
-That's how I operate.
"An eye for an eye."
Who do you think you are? Hammurabi?
"An eye for an eye," my foot.
I had to suffer because of you.
I'll be careful from now on.
There's more?
Close down your law firm.
Who are you to tell me to do that?
Don't involve yourself with Wusang
or the Babel Group.
I refuse to accept such stupid advice.
Do you know who called your father
before he died?
The caller ID was RDU.
It was Mr. Yu Min-chul.
That's when I knew
that he and your father were connected.
Why didn't you tell me this sooner?
That's such important information.
-I could've brought down Babel and--
-Nothing will change.
You may be able to prove
that Mr. Hong and Mr. Yu were connected.
But the fact that someone intentionally
killed them off?
You can't prove that.
It will take time, but it's possible
if I gather the evidence.
You should know best…
that Wusang and Babel are invincible.
Giving up on a hopeless war will give you
a new opportunity.
Yes.
If I can't do this alone,
I'm sure someone will help me.
I've helped out so many people.
What's this? Gosh, I'm sorry.
Put your faith in God.
He will show you the way.
The person you have called is unavailable,
so please leave a voicemail.
Your call will be charged after the beep.
Cha-young.
A rumor's been going around
that you were on Ms. Choi's blacklist.
Who do you think is going to help you?
I don't want to cut my career short.
Gosh!
What is this about?
LAW FIRM JIPURAGI
They're all similar lawsuits
that I've won.
Real estate redemption
for small businesses
that have lost their ownership
due to large companies.
I did it without Wusang's knowledge.
I got a hefty sum for them.
I'll help you get back Geumga Plaza.
I don't care why you want it,
but I just know
that you need it desperately.
No, you need it at all costs.
You're the real owner, right?
Why are you giving me this offer?
Let me in on whatever you're scheming.
Why should I?
Shouldn't I be the one
who's upset the most?
It was my dad who died wrongfully.
Even still,
I can't let you.
It's not something a lawyer should do.
Right now, I'm not speaking to you
as a lawyer,
but as Hong Yu-chan's undutiful daughter.
Promise me you'll quit
if you cause a hindrance.
Deal.
Grab one.
-Why?
-We'll clink these instead of glasses.
-No, thanks.
-Hurry up.
Don't you want Geumga Plaza back?
Are you ready to turn the tables on them?
Gosh, had those brakes not malfunctioned,
he wouldn't have died,
and you wouldn't have gotten injured.
They should do a better job
assembling cars.
You're just as insincere as you were
when you were interrogated.
I'm here to serve my time, aren't I?
Isn't that because
you made and circulated videos
that sexually exploited minors?
Why would you bring that up right now?
Did they promise to reduce your sentence
if you killed him
-and disguised it as an accident?
-What?
That's ridiculous.
But then again,
Wusang could give you a sentence
of two years or less
thanks to Korea's lousy
and ludicrous sentencing guidelines.
I have no idea what you're on about.
I'm going to stand trial for what I did.
Shut up and listen carefully.
Tell me the truth from now on.
If you don't, you'll die tonight
just by brushing shoulders with someone.
What?
Did you think I'd be intimidated?
Who ordered you
to kill him with the truck?
This is your last chance.
Who ordered you?
Spill it, you asshole.
Let's go.
Wait.
Mr. Pyo.
I don't know his full name.
Mr. Pyo?
Just him?
There was someone who looked like
his boss,
but I only know his number.
What does he do?
I don't know.
He came to the police station
where I was at and promised me
that Wusang would reduce my sentence
if I did as told.
-I'm going to kill you all.
-I'm sorry.
I'm truly sorry.
-What's the number?
-Sorry?
That's enough. Let's go.
He's the one who did it.
But I can't do anything to him.
I can't leave here empty-handed.
Mr. Lee!
Thank you so much for your cooperation.
I'm very relieved to hear
that you'll side with us!
What are you doing?
We'll re-investigate the incident
according to your testimony
and get to the bottom of this.
Why are you doing this?
That's not true. He's lying.
Mr. Lee!
Your sense of justice will prevail.
Thank you so much!
-What?
-Let's go.
-Wait.
-Thank you.
Wait! Hey!
Damn it!
Is this how lawyers in Italy
get their jobs done?
There are more heinous criminals there
than here.
I'm very satisfied right now.
I think we have great teamwork as well.
You didn't chip in at all.
What do you mean?
I stayed emotional
and maintained the tension.
I said all the lines.
Talking is important,
but setting the mood is also important.
How could you not know that?
Anyway, I loved the noir vibe as well.
That wasn't even the tip of the iceberg.
Don't tell me
you'll shoot someone.
You can't own guns in Korea.
That won't happen.
Good. We're not filming a movie.
Let's go find Mr. Pyo.
What do you mean? An unexpected situation?
Yes.
It looks like the truck driver
is going to jump ship.
Elaborate.
Hong Cha-young and that Italian lawyer
stopped by.
It seemed like they were colluding.
Damn it.
I'm sorry.
Sorry doesn't cut it.
You've dislocated my shoulder.
You'll die tonight
just by brushing shoulders with someone.
How dare you ignore me when I'm talking?
-Get him!
-Come here!
-Run!
-Run! Hurry!
Damn it!
Okay. I see.
Thank you for telling me.
Lee Chung-il
got himself into a fight
and was stabbed to death.
Are you glad?
It's annoying, and I feel like shit.
This isn't what I imagined.
You can quit now if you want.
No.
I stand by my decision.
Let's promise one thing.
We'll do whatever it takes,
but let's not do anything
that takes people's lives.
Mr. Pyo's full name is Pyo Hyeok-pil.
I've located his whereabouts. See you.
Let me come with you.
Stay here. He may be dangerous.
Victory and quantity go hand in hand.
There's no harm in me coming.
Sir.
Let me come with you.
I've finally learned about your plan.
What are you doing there?
I drank during the day
and fell asleep here.
You two woke me up.
You heard everything?
Yes, but I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
Anyway, I'd like to avenge Mr. Hong.
I'll do anything.
I've kept my skills hidden
for a long time.
Just tell me if you need them.
Skills?
When you make dirty money,
you're bound to lose them gambling.
Hey. Were you talking to me?
You're the only one here
who abetted murder.
Who are you?
I hate to admit it,
but I'm someone who needs you.
The floor is filthy.
My hands will get dirty moving him.
You two take care of this.
Please hold his arms,
and I'll hold his legs.
I don't think I've recovered fully
from my head injury.
Right, you need to recuperate.
PUNGMI RESTAURANT
-Yes?
-Hello, sir.
You should come here right now.
What's wrong?
The prison guard who tipped us off
is demanding more money.
I've tried talking to him,
but he just won't listen.
Damn it. Where are you right now?
Hey, where's that guard?
We're in huge trouble.
What do you mean?
He's not dead, is he?
His stomach is moving.
He has a bit of abdominal fat.
Come on.
This is a Russian pistol.
Tokarev TT-33.
Neither the military
nor the NIS uses this model.
So how did a civilian obtain this gun?
Then again, you both served
in the military's intelligence division.
It must be a cakewalk
to obtain a gun illegally.
Hurry up and answer me.
Who ordered you to kill
Mr. Hong and Mr. Yu?
I hate wasting time as much as I hate
uncooked macaroni.
If you refuse to spill,
you'll end up just like Lee Chung-il did.
Nod your head if you're willing to talk,
and I'll spare you.
If you don't talk,
I'll ram this into your head.
Talk!
This is your last chance.
Who was it?
Tell us. Hurry!
Sir.
Be careful
with that gun.
You have to talk now! This isn't a joke!
Hurry!
Did you think I wouldn't shoot?
A gun is a murder weapon.
Why did you do that?
We agreed not to kill anyone.
What if
he tells everyone about this?
In that case,
we should kill him.
24 HOURS SELF SERVICE LAUNDRY
RESTRICTED NUMBER
Who the hell…
Yes?
There's only one way humans are born,
-but there are countless ways to die.
-Who are you?
-Do you even know who I am?
-Ms. Choi, I wonder which way
-would suit you the best.
-Who the hell are you?
Someone you should fear.
It looks familiar, doesn't it?
Why are you doing this?
At least tell me the reason.
The owners of those bloody clothes told me
that you ordered them to kill
Mr. Hong and Mr. Yu.
That's ludicrous.
Who'd believe them?
I don't care what people believe.
All that matters is that I do.
It really has nothing to do with me.
I'm a patient man,
but I'm afraid I can't say the same
for that driver.
What do you want from me?
Why is negotiating so difficult?
What do you want?
Restore your victim Mr. Hong's honor
and those of the late test subjects
by tomorrow.
To do that,
you'll have to come clean
about what you did first.
Just kill me instead.
Restoring their honor matters
much more than your worthless lives.
Do you think I'll listen to you?
That's up to you.
But you should remember
that freedom comes with a price.
That darn punk…
You better stay well hidden.
The moment I find you,
you're as good as dead.
BABEL PHARMACEUTICALS SUPPLY WAREHOUSE
Store today's RDU-90 raw materials at 7°C.
Yes, I've read the manual.
-What is this?
-We're here to disinfect the area.
Gosh, has it already been that long?
-Vacate the room.
-Okay.
Vacate the premises for disinfection.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
RAW MATERIAL STORAGE
TRIANAMI ACID
TW ENVIRONMENT SERVICE
Gosh, it was scorching hot.
-There's a fire!
-Call 911!
Hurry!
-Get out of there!
-Put out the fire!
Hurry up and call 911!
Do you mind giving me a hand?
One, two…
You were almost late.
You should've pulled him faster.
It's not easy
to grab onto the piano string.
Mr. Nam's former profession paid off.
Who knew he used to be
a special effects makeup artist?
I'll spare you,
but you have to do as I say from now on.
Okay.
We need information on
Babel Pharmaceuticals' supply warehouse.
It's not hard at all.
I have a knack for turning the tables.
Please trust me on this. I can win this.
Sir! We're in trouble!
There's been a fire at our warehouse!
Move it!
-Hey!
-Watch out!
-Over here!
-What are you doing?
You should get out of here, sir
-There may be toxic gases.
-Did you call 911?
-They're on their way.
-What?
What about the sprinklers?
Why is the fire spreading so much?
Well…
AN HOUR AGO
-Run!
Let's get out of here!
Let's go!
Sir.
I saw this coming!
I'm certain that the bastards
who broke into my room did this!
Damn it!
I'll catch them myself
and make them kneel before you!
Shut up.
That's incredible.
Goodbye!
How could they make something like this?
I don't care if I go to prison.
I want to burn them down.
All of the drugs!
"Set, stars.
At dawn, I will win.
I will win.
I will win."
Mr. Jang might not be the real boss.
Then who could it be?
He must be Vincenzo.
That's why we need to change our approach.
We'll use the law and the court,
two things we know best.
I'll take all the cases
related to the Babel Group.
You have to follow my advice this time.
I'm going to give you advice
on how to become a real villain.
Cha-young. I can't keep going easy on you.
You can't do that.
You'll be in deep trouble.
Our goal is to keep fighting.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim