VINCENZO
Enjoy the party.
Let's talk.
This way.
Hey!
Stop. Stay there.
Damn it.
Let's go.
-What?
-What do you want?
I need to take your temperature.
Go on.
-Go in.
-Damn it.
Officer Kim, why are you here?
-What?
-You know you can't be here today.
Gosh, it wasn't my choice.
I'm on security detail today.
-Security detail?
-Yes.
For who?
MATTEO SPONZA
ITALIAN AMBASSADOR TO KOREA
Damn it.
What the…
EPISODE 3
You paid for this big party
out of your own pocket,
so you could stop them
from tearing this place down.
This isn't goodwill or bravado.
So what's your angle?
Why are you doing this? For what?
You wear
a different Booralro suit every day.
It makes me wonder what you could
possibly want to do with the plaza.
You know Booralro?
Doesn't everyone?
Booralro is Milan's master tailor.
So tell me why you are doing this.
I fell in love with this place.
Why?
Love has no reason.
It should.
Everyone pretends there's no reason,
but there always is.
I prefer love that has no reason.
What is this?
You're trying to make this sound romantic
when we both know it isn't.
Vincenzo.
Come here!
Sure. I'll be down there in a second,
Mr. Ambassador.
It's a great party.
Relax.
Why did he suddenly whisper like that?
My goodness! Hey!
-Oh, my. It's been a while, guys.
- Hello.
Take one.
My goodness.
What brings you all the way here?
-It's free. You're doing your job.
-Drink up.
Gosh, you look scary.
Food is the most important
Aspect of living
Yes.
What?
The Ambassador of Italy?
Why is he there?
Hey, just bulldoze…
Wrap it up.
Cha-young! You!
Gosh, this is driving me nuts.
This is a major problem.
You should've told me!
Were you even thinking or what?
How will you fix this?
What if the researcher talks to the press
or the victim's family?
Right!
He won't be able to
make a move right away.
What?
-How can you be so sure?
-Right.
I've been a lawyer for eight years now.
I assure you I have the best hunches.
Hunches?
I've been a prosecutor for 20 years.
I don't think you should be
talking about hunches before me.
-Right.
-You've been a prosecutor for 20 years,
-but it's your first year as a lawyer.
-What?
I'll make myself clear.
I didn't tell you
not because I was scared,
but because I knew I could fix it
and didn't want to worry you.
Goodness.
She thought about
how her bosses would feel.
Gosh, Ms. Hong with eight years
of experience is such a generous lawyer.
-Sir. Ms. Choi.
-There she goes again.
If you trust me, give me your confidence,
not your criticism.
Goodness. It scares me when she does this.
Let's trust her, then.
But if you fail to handle this,
we will no longer trust you
and you'll be fired. Okay?
Thank you for your understanding.
Don't think about going home today.
Get me a list of Yu Min-chul's family,
relatives, friends, and colleagues.
And…
get the expenses ready in cash
in the morning.
Okay.
Why do you need this much money?
So I can give the money
to anyone that gives me a clue
where he might be.
You're not hosting some TV show here.
Why give out money?
If a problem can be solved using money,
we should make use of it.
That way, no one gets hurt
and everyone is happy.
You're amazing. Brilliant. I love it.
-We did it!
-Yes!
-I'll get going now.
-We did it.
-No, join us.
-Mr. Hong!
-You should join us!
-Bye.
-Everyone, over there.
-Let's go.
-You know…
-Let's do this!
-Plaza.
-I'm good with anything.
-Go.
-Let's go.
-My gosh.
-All right.
-Geumga
-Plaza!
-We are the tenants.
-Yes, we are.
-We will win!
-Win!
-Geumga.
-Geumga. Let's go!
-Go, Geumga!
-Go!
-Good work.
-Yes.
-Come here!
-My gosh.
It's nice and warm here.
It's from yesterday. It didn't go bad.
Try some.
-Is it good?
-It's tteokbokki.
I bet the party must have cost
at least 10 million won.
No. It must have cost
at least 20 to 30 million won.
On top of that, Mr. Cassano
paid for everything.
Until yesterday,
you called him all kinds of names.
But today, he's Mr. Cassano?
Gosh, you punk.
I didn't trust him at first.
But seeing what he did for the plaza,
maybe, he's sincere.
If he had an ulterior motive,
-he wouldn't spend a fortune.
-She's right.
If they don't give up,
he'll keep throwing parties.
He'll spend 100 million won in no time!
-Listen.
-Yes?
-I don't trust him 100 percent.
-But?
But for now, I do believe
he is on our side.
-Right.
-Yes.
Lately, Mr. Cassano and I have been
communicating like people in Italy do.
Actually, I think you're hiding from him.
I'm not hiding from him.
It's a game we play.
In Italy, we hide from people
we click with.
It's like the Italian Mafia Game.
If he continues to help us like this,
he may be the savior
our merciful Buddha has sent for us.
Merciful Buddha.
-Amen.
-"Amen"? That's not the one.
Now that I think about it,
don't you think the lawyer
from Italy is really handsome?
He has such great skin.
And his cologne smells so good.
-Right? You noticed it, too.
-Yes.
-It smells great.
-I'll be completely honest.
He has such a great figure.
But I thought he wasn't your type at all.
What kind of woman
wouldn't like a man like him?
NANYAK TEMPLE BOILER CONSTRUCTION
DEMOLITION COUNTERMEASURE
Parties won't be enough
to stop the demolition.
I need a better plan.
RDU-90, KEY CHARACTERISTICS
BABEL PHARM LAWSUIT - DANGER
Please keep a closer eye
on your researchers.
Of course not.
They can't go out even for an hour.
Yes. Please, I really need your help here.
No way.
-Gosh. What's going on here?
-Good morning.
-Come here.
-Gosh, what's she doing?
-She's unbelievable.
-Gosh.
Awesome.
Awesome!
-No.
-Isn't that so weird?
What's she doing?
Awesome!
-Awesome.
-Unbelievable.
So this is how she made it to the top.
Nice bracelet.
What do you know about it?
Isn't that the new Blamino bracelet?
It's the most popular one.
Okay, Mr. Trivia.
What is it?
Since I'm Mr. Trivia,
let me end my internship,
so I can be your partner.
Why would I do that?
Well, we can work together,
go watch baseball together,
and have fried chicken and beer.
How nice is that?
That's not working. It's dating.
Even better.
We'll work hard
and rely on each other.
It's a dream come true.
I don't date people from work
because it's exhausting and immature.
Quit dreaming.
Okay.
-And the thing I asked for?
-Oh, right.
I got it from
the Italian Lawyer Association.
He's a real lawyer.
-Any criminal records?
-He's clean.
He's very handsome.
VINCENZO CASSANO
-Are you interested in him?
-"Interested"?
Right? Was it love at first sight?
-That's why you turned me down.
-Hey!
Don't talk about my life like that.
Why are you glaring at me like that?
You know what? You made me think
that I was an awful cook all this time.
But you were wrong.
Did you see yesterday?
Everyone at the party
enjoyed my margherita pizza.
Did you see that or not?
The Italian ambassador is from Italy.
The couple tasted my pizza
and gave me a thumbs-up.
That's all I need.
Well, the thing with drunk people is…
What's that Korean expression?
Oh, right. People can't tell
between poop and gold.
No, my food is good!
You're the only one who says otherwise.
-Everyone likes it.
-Make me the same pizza, then.
Okay. Fine. Wait here.
Taste it.
I know it tastes good.
Doesn't it taste amazing?
What? What is it this time? Why?
I guess the basil and cheese
are practicing social distancing.
They don't mix at all.
And are the tomatoes quarantined
or something?
I can't taste them at all.
Thanks for showing me
what a piece of garbage
that looks like pizza tastes like.
You know?
Damn it!
Hey, it's Vincenzo!
Have we met?
-We met at the party last night.
-The party.
-Is that where we met?
-No.
Yes. That was
our first time meeting there.
Are you sure about that?
Mr. Cassano!
Mr. Hong is here.
Okay.
By the way,
what's that cologne he's wearing?
-Hello.
-Hi.
I'm not here as a customer.
When I tasted your pizza
at the party yesterday,
I was incredibly moved.
So I came here, wishing
to become your culinary apprentice.
Right? Wasn't it really good?
-Yes.
-Damn it.
But I'm not looking for an assistant.
Please, leave.
Just give me a corner to sleep in.
You don't have to pay me or feed me.
I'll assist you, clean,
wait tables, and do menial jobs.
Master.
What?
As soon as I had
a bite of your pizza yesterday,
I heard the tolling
of Florence's Duomo bell.
And when I had my second bite,
the boat horn from a harbor in Naples
resonated throughout my body.
I want to create my own little Italy
with your guidance.
But you really don't need me
to pay for your labor or food?
No. I just need a place to sleep.
And…
I just need you, Master.
So what's your name?
I'm sure you know about
Babel Pharmaceuticals' new drug,
RDU-90's main component.
Yes.
It's a substance called coisanic.
Are you also aware
that coisanic is considered narcotic?
A narcotic?
That's news to me.
According to our expert's opinion,
it just relieves pain.
Babel Pharmaceuticals deceived you,
and everyone was in on it.
Gosh, I had no idea.
So if this drug hits the market,
aren't they basically selling narcotics?
Yes.
Officially, more people
will be addicted to painkillers.
What's more dangerous is,
because of narcotic pain meds,
more people will become drug addicts
like in the States.
Then,
this drug might open up the doors to
mass-distribution of narcotics in Korea.
Perhaps, like the States,
South America, and Italy,
huge drug cartels might spring up.
It hasn't happened yet,
but drugs will spread like wildfire
in this small country.
I don't even want to think about it,
but if this goes through,
even young kids will be able to buy drugs
like you see in movies.
-It'll be around their homes and schools.
-Jeez.
How could they make something like this?
I don't care if I go to prison.
I want to burn them down!
All of the drugs!
We must stop them. We must do
whatever it takes to stop them.
Yes.
Right away.
When you install it,
-be careful with the--
-There's no need for that.
What is all this?
Mr. Cassano, you cannot do this.
We didn't agree to this.
Save the money for the boiler
for your temple.
-Can you move your feet?
-No.
And I will foot the bill
for your monthly electricity.
Gosh, no. You cannot do that.
-Can you get that side?
-This side?
-But…
-I can put one right here.
Sir, can you lift
the right side of your bottom?
It's all set.
Thank you.
-Can you get that one? Put it right here.
-This one?
A member of the Mafia
who is Catholic
is putting electric pads for the monks.
What is happening?
-Two, three.
-Is it the union of religions?
This man is so generous.
-Give me a cigarette.
-Just one?
If you have one, hurry up.
How come you never have your own?
Hey, give me one, too.
-I want two.
-Give me one.
Come on. Be quiet.
Give me a lighter.
You don't have one?
-Of course, I do.
-Just give it to me already.
-Yes.
-Give me the lighter.
Didn't your mom tell you not to smoke?
Jeez. Don't bring her up now.
It's embarrassing.
-Beat it.
-Haven't you heard?
-If you smoke at an early age--
-That our bones will rot?
They're already rotten.
Give me some money before you go, mister.
Look at him. He's got a nice watch.
All right. If you promise me
that you will never smoke again,
I'll give you some money.
You have no idea
how scary kids are these days.
We go after everyone that pisses us off.
All right.
Toss all of your cigarettes
in this trash can here.
Guess what the scariest kind of drunk is.
If you say "punch drunk,"
I'll be disappointed.
Bingo.
My arm!
Damn it.
You little punks.
Lousy brats.
-Stop it.
-Damn it.
Let's go.
Come here.
-Toss it now.
-Damn it.
Fine. I'll throw it out.
I'll check every time I see you.
-Got it?
-Damn it. What the heck?
A Mafia member
who disciplines delinquents?
Is this a way of repenting
for his dark past?
The more I observe him,
the harder it is to figure him out.
It's my first and last advice to you.
Wait.
You can threaten me,
but you're in no position
to give me advice!
We'll see
which one of us will be
begging the other.
This will be fun.
Cheetah!
Cheetah, are you okay?
Mr. Cho.
Can you look into him?
We'll soon find out
who'll end up on their knees.
My youngest brother
also majored in pharmacology.
He works late every day in the lab.
Then, he comes home all exhausted.
And he worries about his career.
Cha-young.
No. Let me be.
Thanks.
That's why
Min-chul reminds me of my brother.
I'm sure things have been tough.
I'm worried that he might do something
he'll regret if he's alone.
It's been a few months
since I talked to Min-chul.
Please. If he did contact you,
tell me.
I will compensate you handsomely
for your information.
I have enough money.
It's a hefty sum.
We're really trying to help Min-chul.
If he contacted you--
If you don't leave, I'll call the police.
He'll call the police. Let's go.
Here.
How could he not fall for my tears?
I feel hotter because I cried.
No matter how hard I think about it,
if I were Min-chul, your dad would
be the only person I would go to.
Jipuragi.
Try to talk to your dad.
You're his daughter.
You two can have an honest conversation.
I would've done that if it'd work.
If he decides to blow the whistle,
you'll be in big trouble.
Hey, you're from New York.
Why are you so nosy?
Why worry about other people?
No. I only worry about you, Cha-young.
Without me,
who's going to play along with your skit?
Without me, how will you find your car?
Oh, right. Where did I park my car?
-Near Exit B in Basement Two.
-Okay.
Cha-young, doesn't working
for Wusang give you a lot of headaches?
Want to jump ship?
My friend from Boston is
starting a law firm in Korea.
A new law firm won't be able
to afford my salary.
Yes, Mr. Seo.
Ms. Choi invited lawyers
with experience of more than five years
for dinner today.
Tell her I can't go. I have work.
She told me you had to be there
even if other lawyers can't make it.
Fine.
Damn it. She cares about me way too much.
It's not hard at all.
I have a knack for turning the tables.
Gosh.
Please trust me on this. I can win this.
NAMDONGBU DISTRICT COURT
HEARING NOTIFICATION
I know this is a tough decision.
May I ask why?
I realized it when I watched the trial.
That if I stay silent,
a lot of people will be wronged.
Yes. I'm glad you made up your mind.
Thank you so much.
Then, what is their biggest lie
that they have been spreading?
The clinical trial of the new drug
was basically murder.
-Pardon?
-The higher-ups gave the order.
We were ordered to inject
the new drug, RDU-90,
to five test subjects infinitely.
They told us to see how much
they could endure.
How could they do that?
And RDU-90 is not just a painkiller.
It's a narcotic painkiller.
Babel Pharm didn't care about
the test subjects' lives from the start.
I tried to drop out of the experiment,
but they threatened to hurt my family.
Will you appear in court as a witness
and testify what you just told me?
You will guarantee
the safety of me and my family, right?
I can't guarantee it now,
but I'll do whatever it takes.
What do you mean?
How can I testify without that guarantee?
Besides…
there's no guarantee
that you will not expose me.
No, Mr. Yu. No one will find out
about our meeting today,
and I will take all the risks.
Please trust me.
No. Unless my family's safety
is guaranteed,
I cannot testify in court. I'm sorry.
Mr. Cassano,
I already knew what kind of drug it was.
I pretended to be clueless,
so I could take all the risks.
I will make sure to stop them.
-Mr. Hong.
-Mr. Cassano.
Do you have…
Right, you don't smoke.
Have you grasped the core problem
of this lawsuit?
The core problem?
Babel Pharmaceuticals,
the release of narcotic pain medication,
political lobbyists under the radar,
a huge rebate,
and fabrication of a lawsuit.
The entire ordeal is run like a cartel.
I know that much.
If you do, shouldn't you back off?
They're not businessmen. They're monsters.
They couldn't care less
about the lives of others.
If I keep fighting, I'll win one day.
Mr. Hong,
you cannot defeat these monsters.
People can defeat monsters.
No. That's only possible in myths.
You sound pessimistic today.
You've come to a dead end now.
You can't go further!
I'll do whatever it takes to break through
even if it breaks my fist.
When you reach a dead end,
the wisest thing you can do
is to turn back.
Hello?
Yes.
When?
Which hospital?
Okay. I'll be right there.
Okay.
You need to come with me.
Where?
You'll see.
Why did she have to go to work?
She shouldn't have.
Goodness.
Being a public defender is so hard.
Okay. Yes, over there.
Let's go.
CORRECTIONS
Let's go in.
Go ahead. I'll wait for you outside.
You're here, anyway.
Say a few nice things to her.
But…
Hello. I'm her attorney.
Okay.
I was right. Aren't you glad
you were close to a big hospital?
Yes.
Gosh, how can you smile right now?
You almost died!
Let's just say
this was a rehearsal for my funeral.
By the way, who is he?
This is…
He's a lawyer who's been helping me
with my recent case.
Isn't he handsome?
Yes.
He is indeed handsome.
I need to make a phone call.
I'll give you some privacy.
I'm going to file for a retrial.
You can't do anything about it
without my consent.
Suit yourself.
If you die like this,
you're only making life easier
for those criminals.
I stopped caring about getting justice
a long time ago.
Don't complicate things.
Yes.
This is Na Deok-jin from Barbel E&C.
You texted me this morning.
-Bottoms up.
-Thank you.
Bottoms up.
-This is expensive.
Thank you.
All right.
Today…
we'll forget that we're lawyers
and have some fun!
-Yes!
-Okay!
Ms. Choi, what is your idea of fun?
Does anyone here have
a special talent or something?
Mr. Seo is the best impersonator.
He does one heck of an impression.
Let's see it, then. Do it.
-Okay.
-Do it!
"I'm Ko Gwang-ryeol.
Goni asked me to come here.
He's very busy with work right now.
So he asked me to back you up.
It's a small company, you see.
It's a small apartment."
-This is it.
-He's good.
-Yes, he's good.
-It's Agui this time.
-Go ahead.
"Stop. Are you cheating?
You gave Madam Jung and me
the bottom cards.
-Do you think I'm a joke?"
-"Check the Cards!"
"Don't touch the cards.
Or you'll lose a hand.
Bring me the hammer."
"I shouldn't have done that."
Go to sleep. No, not here.
Go sleep over there.
Good job. Give it up for him.
-Good job.
-You're good.
Who's next? Anyone else?
Is that it?
All right, then. Ms. Hong,
Wusang's top dog. You're up.
Ms. Hong.
Hong Cha-young.
-Hong Cha-young.
I don't do stuff like that.
Of course, you do. Just do it.
This kind of thing makes me uncomfortable.
I'm not making you do this
to reward you, you know?
You've made a huge mistake.
I'm making you do it,
so you can make up for it
and redeem yourself.
Then, I'll impersonate someone as well.
Great. Let's give it up.
Awesome!
You're drinking coffee.
Why did you want to meet?
I'm a busy man, you know.
Do these two things I tell you to do.
-You're ordering me around now.
-First.
Make sure Geumga Plaza doesn't
get demolished for two months.
Second.
When we demolish the plaza,
my people will take care of it.
Have you gone mad or something?
What are you babbling on about?
Now I'm curious.
NAME: HWANG JAE-SUK
NAME: SUNG DONG-SU
Didn't I tell you?
That I'm not going to take it anymore.
It's the list of real estate agents
you secretly took bribes from.
The transcripts of the recording
in which Park Seok-do threatened
the store owners under your order.
How…
Photos of you at Shaina Hotel
with Kim Mo-ran of
Management Team Two, your mistress.
-In broad daylight and--
-Hey.
Can you stop, please?
This will be enough
to bury you professionally.
Yes. It's more than enough,
so I'm begging you.
These photos can never be revealed.
As long as you follow my orders,
they'll never see the light of day. But…
you should end things with Ms. Kim fast
and go back to your family.
You're married, for God's sake.
But I don't have any power
to postpone the demolition for two months.
A month is hard enough.
And I don't have much power at work.
-I'm a mere employee there.
-That's not my concern.
Get it done.
If you fail,
I'll make sure you'll be condemned
for the rest of your life.
And let me warn you.
Don't try anything funny.
You'll be dead if anything happens to me.
Wait, sir.
This is bad.
Goodness. I'm in big trouble.
One more round.
-Good night.
-What? You're sending me home?
Come here, Ms. Hong.
Hong Cha-young.
If you mess with me again,
that will be the end of you, you brat.
Do let me know when you get the chance.
I wouldn't mind a near-death experience.
Seriously. You're one big nutjob.
The three-strike rule
doesn't apply to you.
One strike, and you're done.
I'm sorry to bring this up,
but you should cut your nails.
I think you just scratched my neck.
Let's go.
-Good night.
Gosh, she could've infected me
with the germs from her nails.
Come home right now.
What? What is it this time?
Gosh. Why does he keep calling me?
Tear down everything
even if there's a party tonight.
-Yes, sir.
What if there are people
like the Italian Ambassador?
All right. Tear down everything
after you escort them somewhere else.
-Yes, sir.
-Get in.
-Let's go.
-Get ready.
-Go!
-Hey.
-Yes, Mr. Na.
Hey.
Leave Geumga Plaza alone
-for the next two months.
-Why?
Just do as I say!
If the plaza gets destroyed,
we'll be destroyed, too.
-Damn it. What is this?
-Hey, let's go!
-No, don't. Stop it.
-Destroy it!
Hey, stop! Wait! I told you to stop!
Why is that forklift going so fast?
Stop!
-Stop! Turn off the engines!
-Stop!
Turn off the engines. Gosh, the fumes.
LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
How could you leave without telling me?
Come to my house. Let's drink soju.
So the narcotic pain meds
of Babel Pharmaceuticals
will turn people into drug addicts.
And drug cartels will spring up in Korea.
So you want me to stop them?
At the expense of my lawsuit?
The lawsuit isn't what matters right now.
The core problem is narcotics.
Who fed you such nonsense?
Was it Vincenzo Cassano?
Are you guys on some kind of debate team?
He's from Italy.
He knows the severity of the danger
and drug cartels.
Other pharmaceutical companies
produce narcotic pain meds too.
-Why are you coming after Babel?
-They're different.
They'll use lobbyists
to make the drug accessible
and mass-produce the drug
like it's a digestive pill.
Then, a lot of people will--
I guess it's true that
no matter how smart,
people will cling to conspiracies
once they're cornered.
Cha-young, this isn't a conspiracy theory.
This is the truth and our future.
That must be your fellow debater.
Enjoy your debate then.
Please stop telling my dad nonsense.
Drugs? Cartels?
Do you think this is
some American TV show?
Does it sound that absurd?
Yes.
At this rate, Babel Pharmaceuticals
will rule the world or something.
When you continuously turn lies
into the truth,
you become blinded to the truth.
Now, you are diminishing
my honor as an attorney.
Care to translate?
There's no honor among thieves.
One day, when you're exposed as someone
who has no right to be saying such things,
I will mock you
every single second I see you
to the point you want to kill me.
Let me say one more thing
before you do that.
Stupid.
Idiot.
-Translate!
-No translation for that.
My gut tells me they weren't good words.
I bet he was cursing at me.
He's so annoying.
I'm so enraged that I'm feeling cathartic.
It's all my fault.
Yes. I'll fix it as soon as possible,
so it doesn't harm you.
Yes.
No. Whenever you scold me like this,
I can tell I'm growing.
Yes.
The villa?
No. Please do as you please.
Yes. Okay. Have a good night.
Bye.
What the hell does he want?
Mr. Hong.
That lady earlier…
Was her name Oh Gyeong-ja?
Is she okay?
She's not.
She only has six months to live.
If she's in the final stage,
she must be in a lot of pain, right?
If you were curious,
you should've asked your mom yourself.
Why don't you go visit her
and ask her yourself next time?
How did you know?
I've been a lawyer for 30 years.
I've got quite a hunch.
And why do you think
I dragged you to the hospital?
You're so slow.
When you asked me
if I was a public defender,
I already figured it out.
No. Actually, it was that day.
Defendant Oh Gyeong-ja
was often criticized
by Chairman Hwang Deok-bae
and his family for her improper behaviors
as a housekeeper.
On the day of the incident, when
he said she didn't do her job properly,
she was livid and assaulted him
which led to his death.
The defense rests.
Your Honor,
Defendant Oh Gyeong-ja
had abandoned her own child in the past.
I'm submitting her affidavit
of voluntary relinquishment
of parental rights
to an orphanage in Incheon.
That's irrelevant to this case.
Defendant. Be quiet.
You're my lawyer. Say something.
I was sexually harassed.
His whole family is lying!
Don't say anything.
-That day, five years ago,
-This will work against you.
I saw a young man in a rage.
And I could feel the rage
as I was sitting next to him.
No one would get so mad over some case
unless their family is involved.
And this confirmed my suspicion.
CHEONGJU WOMEN'S CORRECTIONAL INSTITUTION
Do you really not want to
visit your mother?
I won't force you.
And I won't ask you
to forgive your mother lightly.
But you shouldn't let your yearning
turn into regret.
What's this?
What is this smell?
What is this?
What?
Around 3:30 a.m. today, there was
an incident, believed to be
a gas explosion, at a villa in Yangyang,
Gangwon Province.
Employees of Babel Pharmaceuticals'
Drug Development Division
were at the villa for a company getaway
and were caught in the explosion, which
took the lives of the 14 researchers.
-No.
-The fire authority confirmed
-This isn't right!
-12 researchers were dead
at the scene.
And two survivors' entire bodies
were burned
-Mr. Hong.
-and were transported to a hospital.
But they died during treatment.
The police suspect the gas was…
Cha-young.
Can you not represent
Babel Pharmaceuticals?
How dare you ask me that?
So many people involved have died.
People related to the case
are dropping like flies.
I don't want anything to happen to you.
I'm not going to die.
Besides, I represent
Babel Pharmaceuticals.
People who died today
were their employees.
So that doesn't matter!
Why are you so sensitive lately?
Are you emotionally unstable or something?
For crying out loud, can you listen?
It's not...
Yell at me in Korean.
Okay. In Korean.
Do you think I'm worried just for kicks?
Is that what you think?
I've been thinking about this,
and I have a bad feeling about it.
Intern Jang Jun-woo.
Why are you suddenly so protective of me?
Don't cross the line.
And I told you not to speak English
when we're working.
Do you think we're in the States?
The briefing didn't even start yet.
I'm going out to pretend
that I'm in the States.
I won't talk to you in Korean.
Bye.
That punk…
Hey! Intern!
Do you want to die?
You're dead meat today!
Jeez. This was way too big.
Gosh, this…
How can he get rid of everyone?
Don't you think he's sending us a message?
"Get things sorted ruthlessly like this."
Or, "If you don't sort things out,
you'll end up like them."
Gosh, no way. That's ridiculous.
Come on, you're jumping to conclusions.
You're scaring me.
I'm not jumping to conclusions. I think
Chairman Jang is giving us a scolding.
It's not in his nature to think--
It's Chairman Jang.
It's…
Yes, sir.
We'll file a claim for compensation.
Yes. Pardon?
Yes.
I see.
Then, I will be there by noon
with Ms. Choi.
Yes--
-He hung up.
-Am I finally meeting him?
I should get it ready.
Get what ready?
My secret crystal ball
that gives me all the answers.
What was that?
Myung-hee. I mean, Ms. Choi.
That was hot!
I'm on my way.
The fire investigation's not over yet.
-How could the case be closed?
-Gosh.
We found enough evidence
at our initial inspection.
You must check if this was arson
with the NFS!
We have no evidence that it was.
Stop getting in our way.
I'm not getting in your way.
-I warned you.
-Warn me what?
I'm asking about the protocol.
Come on. Stop it!
-Let go of me.
-Hey!
-Don't lay a finger on him.
-Who are you?
If you don't follow the protocol,
I'll camp out here.
-Let's go.
-Suit yourself.
-Let go of me.
-Let's go.
-Wait. No.
-Suit yourself.
Damn it.
Let's go.
Why won't you take my advice?
That I should back off this case?
How can you say that
when 14 people were burned alive?
The only thing you can do now
is to be angry and mourn for them.
-But that's not a lawyer's job.
-It is for me.
I will not cave in without a fight.
If you don't, you'll pay the price for it.
I know that more than anyone.
As long as I can punish
Babel Pharmaceuticals, I can give my life.
Why are you being so reckless?
Because I was destined for this.
Even though I know
that the game has been rigged,
I must give it my all to beat them.
That's my fate.
Smart people may rule the world,
but reckless and stubborn people like me
protect this world.
Don't worry about the money. Make sure
the bereaved families are compensated.
Yes, sir. We will.
Gosh, my villa.
I used a lot of good materials
for the villa.
Come on.
Look at the trouble we're in
because of one researcher.
I'm sorry. We'll work harder.
Oh, right.
Thank you for giving us a scolding
with the villa incident.
What? That wasn't a scolding.
I was just blowing off steam.
Anyway, can't you really find
the researcher that ran away?
We'll find him in a few hours.
Apparently, Ms. Choi has
a magic crystal ball.
A magic crystal ball?
-A magic crystal ball?
-It's just something I have.
Ms. Choi, I recruited you to Wusang,
so tell me anything you want.
I'll get it for you.
In that case,
buy me the Namdongbu Prosecutors' Office.
Buy you what? What's that?
I'm talking about
the Namdongbu Prosecution Service.
I see.
That's…
How can I buy that for you?
Is that on the market?
Gosh, isn't he so funny?
He asked if that was on the market.
Is the listing based on rent or deposit?
Mr. Han, you're
such a bad judge of character.
What do you mean?
Do you really believe
that punk's the head of Babel Group?
He's young and wild.
So he's not the typical chairman
we're used to.
He's slow, can't grasp the situations,
-and acts pretentious.
-Gosh, what is it this time?
-What's the problem now?
-Never mind. It's nothing.
Goodness.
-Damn it.
-What is it?
It's my magic crystal ball.
We found the runaway researcher.
I knew you could do it!
Ms. Choi. No, Myung-hee!
Get off me.
But this is too bad.
The researcher and Hong Yu-chan
have already talked.
What?
Yes, Mr. Yu.
I will…
testify.
When I saw how my colleagues
got murdered at the villa,
it made me think that
I could end up like them.
So I've decided to reveal the truth
before that happens to me.
I'm glad to hear that.
Yes. I will go and get you
tomorrow morning.
Yes. See you tomorrow.
Okay.
See? It worked.
-That was legendary.
-Exactly.
-I'm your boss now.
-Of course.
-Go ahead.
-All right.
-Don't move. Bring it closer.
-Come on.
Should I teach it to the guys?
Of course. We can't be the only ones.
Let me see. It worked before.
What am I doing here?
This is stupid. Why am I doing this?
Yes.
I shouldn't be distracted anymore.
Let's wrap this up quickly and leave.
Well, we bought some time,
but we can't keep delaying
the demolition with parties.
-Right.
-That's right.
Now, it's time for us
to duke it out with them.
There must be blood from both--
It won't involve blood.
I would like to make
a better suggestion for you.
I'm planning to purchase a mall
in the neighboring area.
And I will relocate you guys there.
-What?
What do you mean? You'll relocate us?
I will give you the mall free of charge.
-What?
-For free?
-Yes.
-I don't believe it.
Why would you do that for us?
-Because that's the best way.
-Wait.
There's a Western proverb that goes,
"The only free cheese is
in the mouse trap."
He does have a point.
Free things in life can be dangerous.
No, it's not dangerous at all.
Once I purchase the building,
you can just move there.
I see. Then, we don't have to do a thing.
That's amazing.
But who are you?
-Right. Who are you?
-He's my apprentice.
He has so much respect for my food.
He's my pupil.
-I see.
-Nice to meet you.
-Hi.
Mr. Cassano sounds pretty genuine.
Why don't we trust him?
We just met him.
How do we know if he's genuine?
I think I do.
-Think about it.
-Okay.
Why would he try to con us?
We have nothing.
-We got nothing.
-Right.
You can never see through a person's mind.
-Larry.
-Yes?
You keep getting dumped
because you're a bad judge of character.
I've never been dumped in my life!
Because I've never dated anyone.
Everyone.
Faith and trust are the beginning
of good deeds
and the path to Nirvana.
Let's take this chance
to execute good deeds by trusting him.
Yes.
Thank you, sir.
Everyone.
Then, I'll take it
that you accepted my offer.
One, two.
Come on in.
Did you ask to see me?
Yes. One, two. Sit down.
All right.
As of today, you are off any cases
that involve Babel Group.
I can't do that.
This isn't coming from me.
It's coming from Mr. Han.
Even so, I cannot do that.
Who do you think you are?
Do you think you run this law firm?
I cannot comply with it
because this is an order
without any explanation.
Of course, there is an explanation.
You're going easy on your dad.
I've never gone easy on him.
He's my opposing counsel, not my dad.
Of course, you say that.
But family comes first, not your job.
You failed to beat him
at the first hearing.
That's all.
Yes. I'm telling you the truth.
We have hope now.
Yes. Just trust me.
Sure.
I have no idea what's going on with him.
But he's in a good mood all of a sudden.
-All of a sudden?
-Yes.
I'll call you again tomorrow night.
Okay.
Mr. Cassano. Did you have lunch yet?
Not yet.
-Order him something.
-Shall I?
How about we order tangsuyuk
and some drinks?
-Do you mean that? That's a first!
-Of course.
Hold on.
You and I need to talk, Mr. Hong Yu-chan.
She said, "Mr. Hong Yu-chan."
It's a red alert, so I'll evacuate.
Nuclear attack detected.
I can understand
that you don't want to help me.
-Then at least, don't ruin my future.
-When did I ruin your future?
Thanks to you,
I'm about to lose my ground at work.
I'm going from being the top dog
to a mutt.
Right. You got what you deserved.
You're a man of conscience.
Why won't you accept
our values are different?
It's not about being different.
It's about what's right and wrong.
As I always have,
I'll say some hurtful things.
If you lived a righteous life,
why did you let Mom die like that?
You were so busy taking care of others,
you let her die alone on the table.
I told you to stop bringing it up.
No. I will bring this up
as long as I'm alive.
The fact that you made
Mom and my life miserable.
Get out.
Do you even feel guilty
when I bring her up?
You'd jump into the fire to save others,
but why did you neglect her like that?
I don't want to hear it.
Leave.
You can save thousands of people
from injustice.
But you will never be forgiven
for letting her die like that.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
Sorry about that.
You saw the ugly side of my family.
No, I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Damn it.
How can he not apologize?
What is it?
Couldn't you have been more mature?
-What?
-Earlier,
you didn't sound like a hotshot lawyer,
but a spoiled brat
like the girl in the photos.
Don't play dirty.
Why bring up my humiliating past?
All the criticisms children give
their parents will come back as regrets.
Don't do something you'll regret.
Regret is the most painful thing in life.
He and I will drink at his regular spot.
Come if you want to.
You don't have to apologize.
You can just join us.
Gosh. "Apologize"?
As if.
CRYSTAL BALL
Hey.
You can start now.
No.
Both of them.
NAMDO AUNTIE'S RESTAURANT
I'd stay strong,
but days like this get to me.
I mean, when these jerks torture my girl.
No matter how much I scold her,
she's my precious little girl.
How dare they?
She'll get through it.
Ms. Hong is strong.
Aren't you truly the strong one?
I'm not that strong or good,
for that matter.
Weak people don't go to their moms' trials
if they were abandoned.
I only went to see how miserable she was.
Do you mean that?
Yes.
Don't give Ms. Hong a reason
to check how miserable you are.
You're telling me to stop fighting Babel
because I'll be miserable.
I will keep fighting them.
And I have more power to fight.
And that power will put you
in more danger, won't it?
I don't like that you're the only one
exposed to all those risks.
I want you to take
the coward's way out this time.
For me, running away
isn't the coward's way out.
It's putting other people in danger.
Okay?
I'm not going there to see my dad.
I'm going to the restaurant to eat tofu
with kimchi and an assortment of jeon.
Excuse me.
It's for you.
-What's that?
-The man you talked to earlier
told me to give this to you.
What?
Who is it?
-Who is it?
-We're from the police.
What's this about?
We're doing an inspection.
A murder suspect was seen around here.
We just need to check your identification.
I ask for your cooperation.
Could you open the door?
You don't have a Busan accent.
Right. I'm from Seoul.
I see. Hold on.
Open it quickly. I'm busy today.
Okay. Wait.
Damn it.
LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
Here's a thing. Jackie Chan.
I love his movies.
Why?
He wins not because
he's a master of martial arts,
but because he never gives up.
Even if he messes up,
he tries again for 10 or 100 times.
He keeps trying until he gets it right.
I'm going for a smoke.
Goodness, it's pouring.
NAMDO AUNTIE'S RESTAURANT
RDU-90, KEY CHARACTERISTICS
Sir, can I get a cigarette?
Sure.
Here you go.
The light?
Here.
-Enjoy.
-Thank you.
1 MISSED CALL
The number you have dialed is…
LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
Goodness.
It's pouring.
Mr. Hong.
Are you hiding something from me?
I am.
My sincerity which no one knows about.
"It takes a devil
to drive out another devil."
That's the only Italian proverb I know.
Remember what I told you?
Only monsters can beat monsters.
But I can't be a monster.
I wish a real monster would appear
and deal with all these evil men,
whether it's legal or not.
But that's not possible in real life.
Mr. Cassano.
You can't be that monster, right?
Someone has been calling you.
What? Who?
RDU. RDU-90.
Isn't that the researcher?
VINCENZO
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs