#ROMANTIC
#FREE-SPIRITED
#GIRLCRUSH
#VOLUNTARILY SINGLE
#IN A LONG-TERM RELATIONSHIP
HOW IS YOUR LOVE?
LOVESTRUCK IN THE CITY
This coffee is…
Smooth.
-The best coffee is…
-Cold-brewed?
You're good.
It's about this big.
What should we call it?
What comes to your mind
when you hear the word, "first"?
-"First"?
Why are you looking at me?
What are you thinking?
Nothing. It's nothing.
WOMEN-ONLY DRY SAUNA
"First"?
The word reminds me of…
My first love.
When I was in high school,
I ran into my elementary school partner
who transferred to another school.
He was my first love.
Now, I broke up with him.
She broke up with me so easily.
We dated for five years,
but it only took a moment to break up.
Fine. It was my fault.
But if we broke up
for every mistake we made…
You think you never messed up?
I had no idea what happened
with your mom in the UK.
You never told me. How could I have known?
How was I supposed to know?
Do you think I can read your mind?
If you told me,
I wouldn't have said what I said.
Damn it.
Fine, get out.
You too. Everyone, get out.
I've dated a lot of men.
But my first love was…
I don't think I had my first love yet.
How is this possible?
Do you think this is normal?
When I hear the word, "first," I think of…
my first kiss.
I heard it all.
You did?
The word reminds you of your first kiss.
Yes, my first kiss. What about you?
Who was the lucky girl?
No idea. I don't remember.
Seriously. I don't even remember her name.
Then, you must remember her face.
I don't remember her face either.
Wait, I do now.
You were my first kiss.
I first met her in kindergarten.
And when we were in third grade, boom!
She suddenly looked so pretty.
I lost my umbrella that day.
She walked me all the way home.
I still remember the path we walked
under her umbrella.
The rain, the smell, and the atmosphere.
What did she say?
My first love was…
She's talking about it now.
-Kang Geon.
-Hey!
In middle school.
He was wearing his school uniform.
All of a sudden,
he looked a little handsome.
Hey. What did you say?
-Nothing.
-What did you say?
-You said, "a little" something.
She talked about her first love, right?
Who was it?
It could be Rin-i
or Eun-o.
Or was it someone else?
Seon-yeong, are you watching this?
I bet you're livid now.
I bet you want to punch me now.
Geon, meet a nice woman.
Not someone like me,
but someone gentle and kindhearted.
I think of Hae-na.
She could be anyone's first love.
Right?
By the way, Dong-sik,
do you really have no dating experience?
No first love?
You may not have dated,
but you must have had a crush.
I don't think so. Not yet.
Why are you just wasting your good looks?
I don't get you.
Yes. I'm almost there.
I'll call you again
once I'm in the parking lot.
The second floor? Okay. Thank you.
Next scene!
Set up the next scene.
Excuse me. How can I get…
Excuse me.
How can I go to the second floor?
-Why are you so nervous?
-Sorry?
Is this your first kissing scene?
Even if this is your first kissing scene,
I'm sure you've kissed before.
What? You've never kissed anyone?
Really?
I see.
Then, I'll be your first kiss today.
What an honor.
Excuse me.
-Don't you like me?
-No.
What?
-What did I say?
-That you don't like me.
It's just that…
I have a lot on my mind lately.
I feel weird.
I think I'm kind of burnt out.
I'm sure you went through this, too.
Right. I did. "Burnt out."
But you're too young to be burnt out.
Pardon?
When I was your age,
I didn't have time to process my feelings.
I was just crazy about my work.
You have to be.
I think you're amazing.
No.
Thank you for your advice.
I'll get going now.
Wait.
If you haven't had your first kiss,
you probably
haven't slept with anyone yet.
I guess you're new to everything,
not just acting.
I'll just tell you the basic things.
Have a seat.
My goodness, Hae-na. Hello.
I'm here to meet Director Yoon
about the cultural heritage project,
but I don't know
how to get to the second floor.
-It's that way.
-That way?
How come I didn't see that?
Thank you. See you later, then.
Bye.
-Anyway--
-Get ready for the next scene.
Okay. I was giving her acting advice.
Next scene.
Anyway, I'm saying this for your good.
I need to know the degree
for me to adjust the level.
You understand that, right?
Don't worry. I'm good at this.
I'll give you a great first kiss.
Just trust me.
Take it easy, okay?
Relax.
It's a video campaign to promote
the Korean cultural heritage.
I marked Hae-na's parts separately.
I see.
She'll be working with these stars?
Yes. It will feature
practically every Korean world star.
Hae-na will be filming at Deoksugung.
Please check the theme photos
and the script one more time.
Okay.
-Hello?
-Everyone is on it.
What? Hae-na disappeared?
One moment, please.
Hey.
I'll call you after I review it.
She has to film her next scene now.
-I'll call you.
-Okay.
What's happening right now?
You don't know where she went?
-Is she out of her mind?
-We're looking for her now.
Call her now.
-Outside.
-Is she out of her mind?
I'm sorry.
Where did she go?
-Mr. Cha.
-I don't believe this.
Mr. Cha?
What will you do?
-What will you do now?
-I'm so sorry.
-Call her now.
-Okay.
-I'll call her outside.
-Hurry.
-Hae-na.
-Just drive now.
What? But…
I don't think I can do that--
Help me out this once.
I'll do my best for the campaign.
Please.
Okay, then.
This is insane.
I told you not to leave her alone.
Okay. I'll go look for her.
Why isn't she answering?
THE BAD
THE GOOD
THE HANDSOME
Hey!
Don't follow me!
-Go that way.
-Okay.
Damn it.
Let go of me.
Drop me off at the streetlamp there.
-Over there?
-Yes.
Hold on.
Thank you
for driving me here
without asking any questions.
No problem. You must have your reasons.
We'll meet again anyway.
You won't call Mr. Yoon, will you?
I won't tell anyone.
Thank you, Eun-o.
She must be cold.
Hey, Mom.
I've been busy.
I forgot to call you earlier.
Why seaweed soup?
Right. It's my birthday today.
Birthdays aren't a big deal.
Right. Mom.
Thank you for giving birth to me.
Thank you.
You're here again?
I said I wouldn't let you in
if you come again.
I'm cold. Open the door now.
What? What happened to your face?
Did you get hurt?
Where did you get that cut?
How did you get hurt?
Cover yourself with that.
It's not summer.
What's up with the outfit?
Are you okay? Any other injuries?
Dong-sik. Let me see.
-Let me see.
-Have a seat.
-Let me see your face.
-Why do you keep…
Why did you get that cut?
It must have hurt.
I was doing my job.
That's why I told you
not to work too hard.
They pay you chicken feed for your…
salary.
Just do the bare minimum.
Why do you work so hard
and hurt your face like that?
Sit down. Don't make a fuss.
Sit down.
Did you have dinner?
Do you want some tteokbokki?
Put lots of cheese on it.
Don't you know any tteokbokki places?
Why do you always eat it here?
You just offered to make it.
-I've been starving for a month.
-What? A month?
An apple for breakfast,
a tiny piece of chicken breast for lunch,
and a protein shake for dinner.
I haven't had any carbs for a month.
Don't you feel bad?
So just make me some tteokbokki.
Unbelievable.
Lots of cheese, please.
-Do you know Cha Chi-hun, the actor?
-Yes.
He's such a jerk.
Really?
-Cha Chi-hun?
-Yes.
How do you know?
-I was at Hae-na's movie shoot for work.
-Okay.
And I saw him there.
He has
no manners.
But Hae-na has to act like
she likes him in the movie.
-I felt so bad for her.
-That must be so hard.
Right?
-Eun-o.
-Yes?
When did you get so pretty?
Me?
You look gorgeous right now.
-Why?
-You look…
So beautiful.
I almost dropped my pizza.
-Really?
-Yes.
Then, when did you get so handsome?
After I met you.
It feels like I'm living a new life.
Same here.
You look so pretty.
I love you.
-I should stop.
-Yes, you should.
-Where are you?
-It's Rin-i.
-It's Kyeong-jun.
Do you want to go to the movies with me?
Do you want to get a drink?
Sorry.
I'm having a meeting
with a team leader I know,
and I think he's going through
a tough time.
I'm having a meeting with my client.
She's the pickiest client ever.
I don't know when it will end.
Guys, you know
today is our Halli Galli day, right?
Hurry up. I set up everything.
I'll crush all of you today.
Dong-sik, doesn't this look better on me?
Right? It could pass for mine.
Fine. You can keep it.
It's ready. Have a seat.
-It looks delicious.
-Let's eat.
I'm so scared.
Scared of what? Tteokbokki?
Guess how many calories
five pieces of these have.
It's 250 calories.
But I need to eat
less than 1,000 calories a day.
What's more, this contains cheese.
So how many calories?
Isn't that scary?
Don't eat then. I'll eat all of it.
But I can't let you overeat.
Overeating isn't good for your health.
I'll help you out.
You are way too skinny,
so don't think about that. Just enjoy.
Thanks. That sounds nice.
But what if I get fat and no one hires me?
Will you take care of me?
-Why would I do that?
-You fed me tteokbokki.
Don't eat, then.
No. I'll eat it all up.
It's so good.
I hate you. I mean it.
I caught a phone scammer today.
So he's the one who punched you.
But you're the police officer.
Is getting beat up your job?
Is hurting people my job then?
Whatever.
You always get hurt like an idiot.
Do you come here to scold me?
I won't come again.
I get nothing but tteokbokki, anyway.
Then, do you want to play a game?
I'm so sick that too.
You always want to play games.
Is that the only thing
you want to do with me?
Then, stop coming here.
Fine. I won't come back.
I'm never coming back here.
Nice. Faster.
Yes! I'm faster than you.
-I'm winning.
-Wait.
Yes! I won!
I won again.
Why are you so good
when you hate playing games?
That's all I ever do when I come here.
It's boring.
I cooked tteokbokki for you
and played games with you.
But you still complain.
Is there anything else
you want to do with me
other than games?
Shall we watch a movie?
THE HANDSOME GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
Forget it, you idiot.
I'm older than you.
Have some respect. Don't call me "idiot."
I have a delivery for you.
Go get it. I ordered it.
What is it?
It looks like a cake.
First, I told them
that your mother collapsed,
so you had to leave urgently.
Cha Chi-hun's commercial shoot
won't take long,
so they're going to film
your scene tonight.
You have to be here before midnight.
Hae-na, do this for my sake.
You have to come, please.
Is it the one I ordered?
How old are you now?
Aren't you turning 28?
You'll turn 30 soon.
I'm not 30 yet.
You'll be 30 soon,
but you don't have a girlfriend.
-What do you mean?
-You don't.
I asked your mom.
She said you didn't have one.
Stop calling my mom.
If you don't want me to call her,
answer my calls.
And stop calling me, too.
Why do you keep calling me
when you're busy?
If you want to know, use your brain.
Why would I call you?
THE HAND
THE USELESS
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Dong-sik
What? I didn't even pop the firecracker.
You don't know how to celebrate.
On top of that, you're ugly.
That's why you're single.
Everyone tells me I'm handsome.
No way.
You're
just ordinary for a non-celebrity.
How is this "handsome"?
Who told you that you were handsome?
Was it a girl?
Just eat the cake.
Who is she?
Do you see her every day?
Is she a cop, too?
Is she pretty?
Prettier than me?
Hae-na.
Fine. I won't come here again.
Thanks for coming today.
I forgot that it was my birthday today.
I had my birthday cake
and blew out the candles thanks to you.
So I wanted to thank you.
But don't come here again.
It's a hassle for me.
Okay. Fine.
-Dong-sik.
-Yes?
Do you have a toothbrush?
Dong-sik.
I have to go now.
On your own?
Mr. Yoon's going to pick me up.
Really?
Hold on.
Put this on.
Wait, Hae-na.
It's not that cold.
You're an actress.
What if someone recognizes you?
You knew.
I thought you didn't
because you don't treat me like one.
Where is he picking you up?
In front of the supermarket.
You should've told him
to come to my house.
Why? Did you leave something behind?
Your manager is waiting. Hurry up.
Dong-sik.
Can you give me
just one minute of your life?
One minute?
Think about it.
Our average life span is 80 years.
If you calculate that into minutes,
one day has 24 hours.
And multiply that by 80.
It's 700,800 hours.
If I multiply that by 60,
it's 42,048,000 minutes.
What are you doing?
I'm just asking for one minute
out of the countless minutes you have.
Can you just spare me
one minute?
Fine. That I can do.
What will you do with that one minute?
Not yet.
My one minute isn't over.
Did you just…
-I'm sorry.
-Sorry. I'm sorry.
-Let's get ready.
-I'm so sorry, sir.
-Hurry up and go.
I saved your career
because I waited for you.
I'm sorry, Chi-hun. I'll do my best.
You ought to. Let's see how good you are.
I'll do my best.
Thank you.
Hae-na, let me fix your makeup.
I'll do the lips myself.
Cha Chi-hun said something awful
to you, didn't he?
Everybody knows that he's nasty and rude
to rookie actors and actresses.
No, he didn't.
Then, why did you leave like that?
Just because.
I wanted to have my first kiss
with someone I liked.
The city is a lonely place.
But there are some heartwarming days.
Thank you for listening to our stories.
Thanks to you, I felt less lonely.
Thanks for pretending
to not know about my story.
I plucked up my courage
thanks to your support.
Will we be able to meet again?
It was really fun
listening to your stories.
-It sounded like my own story.
-And my friend's story.
I knew some of them.
Some of them might have passed me by.
And we might never meet again.
Just like you listened to my story
and supported me,
I'll root for you, too.
If you see me at my part-time job,
come in and say hello.
It'd be fun to run into each other.
-Let's meet again.
-Until then, take care.
-Bye.
Bye.
What are you doing?
Leave me alone.
-Hurry up and say goodbye.
-Why are we saying goodbye?
It's over, anyway.
Bye.
-Bye.
-Thank you.
Bye. Take care.
BYE
EDITOR'S HARD DRIVE COMPILATION.ZIP
1. RA-RA'S RAMYEON, YANGYANG
2. BIKER PARK JAE-WON
3. GUNMAN KANG GUN
4. DANCING MACHINE OH SEON-YEONG
CARRIED AWAY
5. KYEONG-JUN THESE DAYS
1) ZONE OUT
2) CHECK OUT RIN-I'S SOCIAL MEDIA
3) CHECKS TEXT AND GETS DISAPPOINTED
THAT IT'S FROM GEON
Here's the Mokdong pizza
you ordered. Enjoy.
RIN-I'S MONTHLY INCOME, INTERNET CAFE
837,120 WON
This is nice.
It's been three years
since you published anything.
7. JAE-WON AND EUN-O
TAKE PHOTOGRAPHY SERIOUSLY
-Sit down.
-Okay.
-Hold on.
-Don't laugh.
No.
Jae-won, come here.
Loosen up.
Okay. Let's look cool.
Focus. Pretend we're professional models.
Stretch your leg like this.
Jae-won, I'm slipping.
You're doing a great job.
Don't do that. Come here.
-Let's take it standing up.
-Sure.
Like this.
One, two, three.
That was…
That's all for me.
Wait for me!
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs