#ROMANTIC
#FREE-SPIRITED
#GIRLCRUSH
#VOLUNTARILY SINGLE
#IN A LONG-TERM RELATIONSHIP
HOW IS YOUR LOVE?
LOVESTRUCK IN THE CITY
WHAT'S YOUR IDEAL TYPE OF RELATIONSHIP?
-Hey, you can go first.
-No, you first.
First, I should meet someone who likes me.
What do you mean?
You should meet someone you like.
-What?
-You should like each other!
When you're still young,
you don't know how miraculous it is
to start a relationship
with someone who likes you back.
I bet it's only possible
when the whole universe helps you out.
After some time, you keep forgetting.
That we were able to meet
because the universe helped us.
I have no expectations now
since I always see couples
coming to the police after a fight.
They're asking you
about your ideal type of relationship.
-To be honest, I've never dated before.
-What?
Really?
With that handsome face of yours?
Anyway, I should find a date soon.
Someone will come to me one day
like a gift without me having to try
to find her.
Spontaneously.
He's only saying that
because he's handsome.
Do you really think you'll meet someone
without even trying?
-Are you talking to me?
-No, it's for the interview.
-We can speak casually in the interview.
-Excuse us.
What's up? We'll be late. Hurry.
Being considerate and trying your best
also counts, in my opinion.
Romance isn't just about excitement.
Did you see that?
My Kyeong-jun is an expert.
I always gave my all when I dated.
But now, it's too boring.
I still think
it's the most important thing in life.
You feel lonely on your own.
How reassuring would it be
to have someone on your side
in this big world?
When I broke up with Seon-yeong,
I told her this.
"Come to me whenever you miss your mom."
But now, I want to tell her this.
"Wander around
and do everything you want to do.
When you're done,
let's date one more time."
She doesn't know what that means.
She won't.
Just like how she didn't know back then.
The construction got delayed
because I had to move the stairs.
Honestly, we were worried about the delay.
But this looks much better than before.
I thought they would make a big fuss.
But you pulled it off.
I'm proud. Good job, Jae-won.
They even gave us a box of tangerines.
Hey, what did you take me for? Goodness.
It's over, right?
-Don't act out of your mind again.
-Okay. I won't.
Hey, give me the car keys.
I'll open the trunk.
We don't need keys in this era.
Aim for the middle and use your foot.
What's this? How's this possible?
Haven't you tried this?
Does my car also have this function?
Of course, you idiot.
SInce we're here,
let's check the townhouses in Gapyeong.
We can't. We have a meeting with Eun-o.
What time?
Hey, you should've told me in advance
if we had a meeting at 2 p.m.
You're the one who wasted our time
by coming here
when they had offered to visit us instead.
And she can wait.
-She's my friend, anyway.
-Hey, Kyeong-jun.
I'll give you advice as someone
with more experience in life and work.
What you're doing is an abuse of power.
What are you talking about?
You're making her wait!
-That's a power trip!
-Okay, be quiet!
I'm speeding up. Hold tight.
I came too early.
They will think I'm desperate.
I'm the one getting paid
so I should be on time.
Be bold. Be confident.
-I'm no longer the stupid old…
-Eun-o.
The old Eun-o wasn't stupid.
I was never stupid.
The old you. The new you.
Both of them are Eun-o.
They're all Eun-o.
She's right.
Old or new, I'm still Lee Eun-o.
I may make a mistake today
or botch the party tomorrow.
But it's okay.
I can do it.
In conclusion, the entire event
will end around 7 p.m.
Here are the details. Have a look.
Our workers gave
a generous score for your idea
of "a walk around the neighborhood."
I know. We said something similar
when we built this.
-"A place to age beautifully."
-You're right.
The thing that came to my mind
when I built it
was a zelkova tree.
You know how in rural areas,
there's always this one area
where neighbors gather to relax.
Right. It's like a zelkova tree
that's always there
no matter when you visit.
"It would be nice if there's a building
I can go to when I go for a walk."
That's how I came up with this project.
I heard that's why the main event
will be like a casual talk show.
But will he and I do a good job?
You'll give an honest talk
about how you built that place.
The catering service and the performance
will be casual rather than fancy.
Is that why we'll have a campfire
and bake sweet potatoes?
This is unique.
It's interesting. I like it.
Mr. Park, one minute.
Coming. Keep discussing.
-Okay.
-Oh, right, Kyeong-jun.
Check if we're allowed
to make a campfire there.
They might say no.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
Carry it out as planned.
Just send us the detailed budget.
Eun-o.
-What do you think?
-About what?
You kept staring at him.
-Is he good-looking?
-What are you talking about?
Okay, what should we do?
Let's see. Call the city hall.
Ask if they can lower the water pressure.
If they can't, we'll have to install
a reducing valve.
Mr. Park. One minute.
-What is it?
-We're going to step out.
-Where to?
-To have pizza at Rin-i's.
Sure.
-See you.
-Let's go.
Look at the balcony.
We should do something about it.
Ta-da!
-No way.
You really made this yourself?
Its taste is even more phenomenal. Dig in.
How is it?
How much is the prize
for this recipe contest?
-Five million won.
-It's yours.
I'll bet double the amount.
You guys planned this, right?
Why are you being so nice?
No. Objectively speaking,
it's really delicious.
The decoration is perfect.
You have a great sense of aesthetics.
So what's the name of this pizza?
I need to think about that.
Oh, don't be worried.
You have a marketer here.
And a writer.
Should I do some brainstorming?
Hey, hold on.
Something's coming to mind right now.
Wait.
Wait. Will we get something
in return for naming this?
You bet.
I'll treat you to a really nice meal
if I win.
You should invite Jae-won too.
Hey, Eun-o. While you're working with him,
why don't you make a move on him?
You guys were eyeing each other
back there.
What was that for?
Is this product placement? Do I have to?
I'll try my best.
Product placement.
Here. "Squeeze it and mix it with water"?
How convenient.
All right. Just squeeze it like this.
Why do you think he gave me this necklace?
I mean… What does this mean?
I'm not sure.
What could it mean?
Wow, it tastes so fresh.
There wasn't even a letter.
Why in the world
was this in my suitcase?
Maybe he left it there by accident.
If that's the case,
she should have given it
back to me earlier. Don't you agree?
-Is this even for me?
-Yes, it's hers.
I bought it
as soon as I came back to Seoul
to give it to Seon-a at Cheonggyecheon.
I never got to meet her,
but I still kept it.
I just couldn't throw it away.
I'm usually very nonchalant, but…
Gosh.
It bothers me so much.
What's bothering her?
Isn't she too busy finding herself?
To be honest,
that thing about her finding herself…
Gosh.
I should give it back
when I see him next time.
How can I possibly persuade her?
I just…
I did everything I could.
There wasn't even a single note,
so I have no clue what it means.
Does it matter what I mean?
If I didn't leave a note,
isn't it up to her to interpret it?
Should I call him?
No. I won't pick up her calls. Never.
Look at this. Gosh.
PRETTY IDIOT
No. I'm not answering.
The person you have called is unavailable.
-Please call…
-What's this?
What should I do?
Isn't it obvious?
She should follow her heart.
Why is she even asking?
What is this?
Kyeong-jun is incredible.
That building is his work.
Isn't he amazing?
It is indeed amazing.
My friend built this building
and is hosting the housewarming party.
They'll even have a book cafe.
Won't it be perfect
if you sell your new novel there?
What about you? You should join too.
Me?
I'll be a regular customer.
That's wonderful. Let's go.
Wait. Will they hire part-timers?
It'd be awesome if I could work here.
How will you manage four part-time jobs?
Why not?
-Eun-o, your walkie-takie.
-Oh, thank you.
Could you relocate the photo zone outside?
The harmony between the building
and nature is important,
so you need to capture it in one frame.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
-Can you first check the videos upstairs?
-Sure.
Eun-o.
I'm going to check
the experience zone upstairs.
-Pick up your walkie-talkie later.
-Okay.
She looks like a professional.
You had such a radiant smile
Like in that photo that I stared at
Countless times
What should I do with my heart?
What should I do with my love?
Your night
Your star
Every moment I spent
Loving you was beautiful
Hey, you look great today.
I'm a bit busy right now,
so I'll see you later.
Okay.
What are you looking at?
Oh, and check the food and beverage stock
on the ground floor later.
Sure.
-Anything to report?
-No.
The acoustic band is performing
on time as planned.
The separate events are going well
as planned.
However, I think this room
has too many people.
In that case,
let's split them into two groups.
Okay.
This is the monitoring room.
Please split the people
in Gallery Two into two groups.
Thank you.
Thank you for making time
despite your busy schedule.
My pleasure.
-Jae-won.
-Hello.
Sir, this is my son.
-Hello, I'm Park Jae-won.
-Goodness.
No wonder you brag about your son.
This is a wonderful place.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
-All right, then.
-Sure.
-All right.
-Goodbye.
-Dad.
I'm busy, so I should go.
-All right. See you.
-Okay.
Uncle.
This is my girlfriend.
-Hello, I'm Suh Rin-i.
-Nice to meet you.
Didn't we say hi a few times
in front of my company?
Yes, we've met a couple of times.
I wanted to formally introduce her.
I've heard a lot about you.
Maybe a bit too much.
Every time he talks about you,
his eyes glisten like crazy.
Oh, really?
I always look at you like this.
You two are still a loving couple
after all those years.
-It's nice to see.
-Thank you.
By the way, what do you do?
-Oh, I--
-Right.
You're preparing for graduate school.
Kyeong-jun has told me before,
but I keep forgetting.
Professor Park.
It was nice meeting you.
See you next time.
Sure.
-Mr. Choi.
-Yes, sir?
Let's talk later.
TALK ABOUT SPACE
Okay.
We faced countless crises.
But we were able to overcome them
thanks to
the tenacity of this man
who pestered everyone he worked with.
The tenacity of Team Leader Park Jae-won.
I refuse to acknowledge
anything else about him,
but his tenacity is
the one thing I acknowledge.
Hello, I'm Park Jae-won,
the man who pesters his co-workers.
Nice to meet you all.
Compared to the person I love the most
and respect the second most,
our president,
and my countless seniors,
I lack experience and wisdom.
That's why I have no choice
but to be tenacious.
I believe in the phrase, "Sincerity wins."
This could be applied to both construction
and building relationships with people.
Therefore,
I don't want to disappoint those
who have put their trust in me.
I'll hold you whenever you fall.
So don't worry, and focus on the waves.
I'll focus on you.
Eun-o, please come to the monitoring room.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Thank you!
-Good work.
-Thanks, Dad. Good night.
-Wrap up well.
-Yes, Uncle.
-Get home safely.
-Bye.
Good work. Go home now.
-What about you?
-I'll stay here and watch them wrap up.
The field team will take care of that.
Right. Can you drop Eun-o off?
I drove her here,
so she needs a ride home.
Sure. Don't worry.
-Bye.
-Good work, Kyeong-jun.
-You too.
Excuse me. Do you know where Ms. Lee is?
-I saw her going outside.
-Okay. Thanks.
Who is it?
I think I drank too much wine.
Why is it so cold in here?
Hey, turn on the heater.
Oh, it's already on.
Why am I so cold?
Are you guys listening to me?
So it's because of the mood
between you two.
The mood is as cold as Siberia here.
Did you two fight?
Damn it.
Can we talk?
Thanks for dropping me off. Bye.
-Bye.
It seems serious.
What did he mean back there?
Did you tell Jae-won's father
that I was preparing for graduate school?
That's what I told him
when he asked me about you.
Why did you say that?
It's not true.
Rin-i.
To be honest, when people ask me
what my girlfriend does for a living,
I don't know how I should answer.
Just tell them I work part-time.
What's wrong with that?
I don't want to tell them that.
They'll keep asking about you.
"Why does she still work part-time?
What was her major?
Did she even go to college?"
You hear that all the time.
Aren't you fed up as well?
It's annoying to explain.
But so what? That's how I live.
But I hate doing that.
That's why I lied.
I don't want to explain to those
who don't even know you.
And…
I don't like
your current lifestyle, either.
What do you mean?
I think you should go to graduate school
or look for a permanent job.
I'd like you to have a decent job.
Why?
Why should I do that?
-Rin-i.
-Kyeong-jun.
It seems like you know nothing about me.
Forget about other people.
You're the one
who knows the least about me.
I want to live on what I really need
instead of having many things.
I don't need to have something
just because everyone has one.
And that kind of lifestyle
doesn't suit me.
So I don't want to stay at one job
for many years.
I'm making less money,
but I prefer having more free time.
And I may not have a proper job,
but I enjoy living a minimal lifestyle.
Don't you know what I mean?
I know. I'm just worried.
Why would you be? I'm okay, Kyeong-jun.
I'm as hardworking as anyone else,
and I love my current self.
I don't understand
why you're so worried about me.
So you're fine?
-Yes, I'm--
-You got fired out of the blue.
How are you okay with that?
Then you hastily find
another part-time job to make ends meet.
You never know
when you'll get fired again.
Yet you're fine? How so?
I don't feel fine at all
watching you like this.
It still makes my blood boil
to know that you were treated that way.
Rin-i. I'm not asking you
to get a well-paying job.
I can make the money.
I just hate that people look down on you
and treat you badly.
Besides, you can't work part-time forever.
Do you think you can manage
multiple part-time jobs
when you're over 40?
Rin-i.
You can't keep living like this.
Okay, Kyeong-jun.
I understand how you feel.
But one thing.
You might think
my lifestyle has no vision,
but I'm devoted to this.
This is how I live. This is my life.
I'm working hard
and doing my utmost to be happy.
I'm not saying you're not hardworking.
But the world--
What the world thinks of me
doesn't matter!
What breaks my heart is
that's what you've been thinking
about me all this time.
You took me for a reckless child
who couldn't take care of herself.
That's what you've been thinking about me.
That's not true.
I thought you'd understand me.
I thought you respected and supported me
because you're Kyeong-jun,
not just anybody.
But if that's not the case…
If that's not true,
why should we keep seeing each other?
Hey.
Stop there.
-That's enough.
-Let's break up.
Rin-i.
Let's break up.
You deny me.
You deny my entire life.
-I told you that's not it!
-You lied to your uncle!
You don't know why I left my mom
in the UK and came here, do you?
It's true I came because I was worried
about Eun-o after she disappeared.
But also because
I wasn't happy at all there
because of my mom.
She lied to everyone about me as well.
She told them…
that I was her niece, not her daughter.
She kept denying me.
I want to break up.
Don't you ever contact me again.
I…
still don't know
what kind of person I am.
I'm not the Yoon Seon-a you know of.
Once you find out who I really am,
you may regret it.
I'm still a coward. I'm clumsy.
I'm a mess.
Yes. You're right.
You still don't know who you are.
And you're timid.
I am.
But
I'm not going to pretend
I'm tough anymore.
I'm scared and nervous right now.
But
I'll try to tell you how I truly feel.
I'm still a mess.
I'm not the Yoon Seon-a you knew of.
And I'm still not
the best version of Lee Eun-o.
There are countless things
that I still need to fix.
Are you still
okay with that?
To be honest,
I thought about sending her
a letter with the necklace.
But I thought it'd be better for her
to interpret the gift herself.
What I'm trying to say is…
Eun-o, there's something
I didn't tell you.
The old Eun-o who was kind and calm,
Seon-a whom I fell in love with,
and the current Eun-o
who showed up in front of me…
They're all you. They're all Lee Eun-o.
The woman I loved
is still inside you.
Are you still
okay with that?
"As you slowly discover yourself,
I'll slowly learn
about the current you as well.
I'll try my best to love you properly."
That's what it meant.
I hope she figures that out.
As for those things you want to fix…
Instead of removing them,
how about we get to know them together?
First…
Dating.
Let's find out what that means first.
Okay?
Why am I nervous?
This isn't even our first kiss.
Me too.
My heart's about to burst
as if it was our first kiss.
What do you think romance is?
A journey to finding my true self.
I've finally learned how it feels
to truly love someone.
It was very miserable and painful.
That's why it's more precious
and more cherishable.
It's too difficult for me.
Two people meeting,
and showing each other
their deepest feelings
and their worst moments,
then striving to become one.
-Isn't that it?
-It's fascinating.
I hated my stupid self,
so I kept running and hiding.
But I'm no longer scared.
I'm still a complete mess,
but if he's by my side,
I want to be braver
and take the bull by the horns.
It's unfair.
I admit I was wrong,
but I don't want to end it like this.
I think
there are no special relationships.
They can come to an end at any moment.
My grandpa's final letter
is like a bridge between Rin-i and me.
It's this one.
I'll tell you about it next time.
Anyway, because of this letter,
our breakup is
a little difficult to accept.
If there's a reason to break up,
then I think I should.
A relationship is like a war.
It's easy to start,
but it's never easy to end.
For now, my relationship is
like a ceasefire.
It's not over yet.
Seon-yeong, don't you give up.
End the ceasefire and keep searching.
Once you're exhausted,
come and ask me again,
"You like Eun-o, right?"
With that excuse,
we can see each other again.
We're officially a couple starting today.
What should we do?
-First…
-Yes.
Call me by my name.
Your name? Ms. Lee Eun-o.
Eun-o.
Lee Eun-o!
-Quiet!
-Eun-o!
Okay, I'll stop.
-Eun-o.
-What?
Let's go.
It's snowing.
Wow, it's snowing.
-Does Eun-o like snow?
-Yes, just as much as rain.
What else does she like?
-Sunny days.
-Okay.
-Hot lattes.
-Cats' paws.
-I see.
-Taking a walk with someone.
-Okay.
The aroma of lilacs.
-And…
-And?
And
Park Jae-won.
What?
How can Yoon Seon-a be Eun-o?
So Yoon Seon-a is
actually my friend, Eun-o?
Hey. Damn it. That's nonsense.
How's that possible?
Are you kidding me?
I would have known if that was true.
Everyone else knows but me?
Who else knows?
Wait.
Hold on. Let me make a call.
Geon isn't picking up.
Hold on, let me call Rin-i.
Wait.
Right, I shouldn't call her.
She picked up. Be quiet.
Hello?
I hear a man's voice.
-Is this Rin-i's number?
-Yes, it is.
Who are you?
Where's Rin-i?
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs