My plan is to love you.
Then, I'll be able to live...
without losing anything.
Then, let's do it right,
Love me to the point that you want to destroy the world for me.
What do you say? Should I kiss you now?
What happened to the girl who was willing to risk her life?
I won't forget.
I won't forget what happened today.
I will remember it...
and do exactly what you did to me.
Which one?
How I tried to kill you or save you?
Both.
Here's my key.
Come on in.
Or you can run away.
Is that your wish?
I'm asking you if that's your wish.
(Episode 4)
My plan is to love you.
What are you doing?
I asked you a question.
- It's a blanket. - Why are you putting it there?
Let's go to sleep together.
You said you don't sleep, right?
Then let's just lie next to each other.
Bring a pillow.
You're really acting up.
What's wrong? Are you scared...
that I might do something to you?
You should be the one that's scared...
that I might do something to you.
I'm not scared.
You can't love me.
No human has ever loved me before.
I can.
Everyone either resents me or just wants me.
But no one can love me.
I will because I must.
Then follow me.
You came in here willingly.
Don't regret it.
So what if I regret it?
I'll die anyway.
Hey.
Are you sleeping?
No, I'm not.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking that you're arrogant.
That you're insignificant.
That you're brave enough to act up when you're about to die.
That's what I'm thinking.
What about you?
That I must've been crazy...
and that I really could've died earlier.
That's what I'm thinking.
I'm also thinking...
that the way you looked at me earlier...
was so cold and scary.
And I also find it funny that I like...
how warm this feels right now.
Did you realize what it means to have compassion?
You smile a lot and feel bad for her, don't you?
Your feelings will grow.
Why is she such a know-it-all?
I hope she fails her test.
This is so darn annoying.
I don't want to go to work.
A group project?
Whatever. They can do it without me.
Is he nuts or what?
What's he looking at?
Compassion, my foot.
(The world is coming to an end.)
We must get ready for that day.
Doom is on its way.
Do you mean it?
What?
Do you really want the world to come to an end?
The world doesn't end simply because we wish for it.
It's all because of our sins...
The world should come to an end.
That way, I, the chosen one,
will get to be reborn again and live a happy life.
Who says you're the chosen one?
You know what? If that were true, things would've been a lot easier.
It's your fault.
You should've been more desperate.
What are you talking about?
Do you want to know a secret?
There is no next life.
This one is all you get.
That's not true.
The deity has given us a chance...
to live another life.
What do you think will happen to the manager...
if the people he or she manages all disappear?
Wouldn't he or she disappear too?
That's what I'm betting on.
("Final Trial for the Gusin-Dong Murder Case Takes Place")
("Prosecution Plans to Seek Punishment")
Did you realize what it means to have compassion?
No. Not one bit.
(How to fall in love)
(How to love)
(I remember the lyrics to a song...)
(Trend comes and goes like the Mobius strip.)
(Can anybody translate this for me?)
(How to love yourself)
(Right now, I'm learning how to love.)
(When you fall in love)
(When you fall in love...)
(When you feel lethargic...)
(How to separate glass cups...)
(Ways to prevent hair loss)
(Techniques on love)
(Let's share stories about how you suddenly fell in love.)
Let's share stories about how you suddenly fell in love.
Back when I was in high school,
I was on a bench during PE class because I was sick.
And suddenly, a ball flew toward me.
But this guy in class, who's usually really quiet,
got up and blocked the ball for me.
Then he asked me if I was okay.
And that suddenly made me fall for him.
- You're making my heart flutter. - Amazing.
Imagine a school senior...
sitting by the window in a library wearing a clean shirt.
That already says it all. He's my boyfriend now.
Tell us more.
Here's a classic. Seeing a guy reverse. Game over.
- And a parking ticket in his mouth. - I agree with the parking ticket.
These girls fall in love so easily.
(101 Ways to Fall in Love, Written by Lee Hyun)
Ms. Lee, where are you right now?
You want to love someone?
- Name. - "Name"?
What's the guy's name? Tell me.
Why do you want to know his name?
What do you think?
I want to find out everything about his life.
His name...
Come to think of it, I never asked.
What?
You fell in love with him when you don't even know his name?
I didn't fall in love with him. I want to love him.
That's the same thing.
Where did you meet?
Where did we meet?
- At a hospital? - Hospital?
- Is he a doctor? - I don't think so.
Is he a patient?
Was the funeral parlor the first place we met?
Funeral parlor?
He is alive... Right?
Just tell me...
the 101 ways to fall in love.
If you plan it, it isn't love.
It's not that easy.
How did you fall in love?
Me?
I just...
It happened in an instant.
- Oh my gosh. - Later.
- See you later. - He's so cute.
Oh my gosh.
He's so cute.
I smell soap.
Seriously, Ji Na.
You're such an easy-to-get girl.
Hey.
It's crazy hard to meet someone...
with that face, that body, that smile, in a moment like that.
It's not easy.
It was strange.
Everyone else smelled like sweat, but he smelled like soap.
Maybe only he washed up.
So, it happens in an instant.
Do I have to wait for that instant?
Can't I create it?
I really don't have time.
- Then ask him out. - Out of nowhere?
Emotions blow up out of control...
once you admit it out loud.
Is that how you are?
That's right, I was.
I crossed the bridge of no return.
You played a big part.
What? Why are you dragging me into it?
Do you remember the first time we met?
When you came to Jeju Island on a class trip?
Na Ji Na. Na Ji Na.
You can count on me, kids.
Our first meeting was a humdinger.
You were the first girl to climb over a wall...
to meet me.
Oh my gosh.
You don't look like you go to our school.
Do you live here?
Good.
Do you know where the closest grocery store is?
30 minutes.
- Thanks. - By car.
Darn it.
Is there a liquor store nearby?
Awesome.
How much?
A dollar?
You thief.
Fine.
Hey! Hyun Kyu!
I need to talk to you.
Hyun Kyu!
Lee Hyun Kyu! Get out here!
Hyun Kyu.
- What's going on? - Hyun Kyu.
Hyun Kyu! I know you're in here.
- She's so annoying. - What's wrong with her?
- I need to talk to you. - She must be drunk.
It's Hyun Kyu.
Hey.
I like you.
- Oh my gosh. - Go out with me!
Go out with her!
- Go out with her! - Go out with her!
You're the aggressive female protagonist.
We need the runaway male protagonist, and it's your novel.
Do you think that too?
Why? Did Mr. Cha tell you that?
No. Just because...
How could you forget a first love...
that amazing?
It's only natural that it left a mark in your life.
Forget it.
That jerk Mr. Cha knows nothing.
You're right. He knows nothing.
He used to show up in my dreams all the time.
Yes. Dreams.
Have a dream.
- A dream? - Think about him like mad...
just before you go to sleep.
Do you have a picture? Check his social media page...
and look at his picture before you go to sleep.
Once he appears in your dream, it's game over.
- Really? - That's right.
Okay. You just saved a life.
Your life?
Do you plan to love him with your whole life?
Who is this guy...
that has you burning with desire?
Give me three months.
I'll tell you everything after three months.
Three months?
Yes. Wait just three months.
I'll tell you myself after three months.
And I'll be totally fine.
You'll be fine?
You should plan to love until you're a wreck.
No matter how big a wreck I become because of my love,
I would never be as reckless as you.
What's the point?
I never even kissed him.
They say first loves always end with a little regret.
Anyway...
I recently met the guy I had my first kiss with.
What? Oh my gosh.
The guy whose name you don't know?
When? Where? How? Why?
Well...
Don't be too shocked.
What is it?
Cha Joo Ik.
His name is Cha Joo Ik. Mr. Cha.
- Your supervisor. - What?
That Cha... That Cha Joo Ik?
What? What is it?
- No. - No?
That doesn't answer either question.
- Say what you want to say. - What?
You've been staring at me since you got back.
I was not.
I really wasn't.
Fine, then.
- Mr. Cha. - What?
Never mind.
You know...
No, I don't.
What?
Have you ever fallen in love with someone you hated?
No. I've kissed someone I hated though.
Why?
I hated her because I pitied her,
but I ended up kissing her because I pitied her.
- Does that answer it? - What? Answer what?
Anything.
Yes, it did.
That's good.
Still, how could you kiss her?
I can hear you. Speak quietly.
Quieter.
Still, how could you kiss her?
- Stop saying that. - Yes, sir.
- Go home. - Yes, sir.
I'll go home... Then...
Okay.
What's for dinner?
Why are you asking me? You're cooking tonight.
Gosh, I almost had him. That was pretty smooth.
("The Romantic Egoist")
Have you been driving my car?
What?
No.
I'll kill you.
Joo Ik, since we're on the subject, let me ask you for a favor.
I have a school reunion next week. Let me borrow your car.
- Get lost. - Come on.
I haven't seen my school friends for ages.
Please. Come on, Joo Ik.
Why do you need my car for a school reunion?
I told you to tone down your pretentious side.
It's not like I want to be pretentious.
If I didn't eat the rice cake you gave me the day before the CSAT,
my life wouldn't be this hard.
Gosh. Forget I asked. I can't go to the reunion...
because I'm too embarrassed to face them.
- Fine. - Thank you. I love you.
The kindness of a teacher is as high as the sky
How did I let someone like him get into my life?
Think of it as paying back for the tutoring fees my dad paid you.
I worked for those tutoring fees.
Teaching a stupid-head like you was...
For what? I couldn't go to college because of you.
Why are you going to the reunion? Is your first love coming too?
Do you even remember how she looked?
I don't.
How can I remember her? It's ancient history.
Joo Ik.
The girl who asked for my number at the cafe texted me.
Usually, I separate work from my personal life.
But she was totally my type to just let her slip away.
Look. Isn't she gorgeous?
Isn't she pretty?
I'm getting a call.
Hello?
Yes. Oh, the school reunion?
Yes. Of course, I should be there.
Where are we meeting?
What?
(Every woman I liked was Francoise.)
(They were a copy of you.)
(From "The Romantic Egoist")
Of course, you remember her.
The train is approaching City Hall Station.
The doors are on your left.
The doors are opening.
- Excuse me. - I'm getting off.
- Let me pass through. - Excuse me.
Oh, no.
What is this?
Me?
Someone to hold onto.
If you're tired, do you want to hold hands?
Why are you doing this to me?
What?
Why are you acting nice all of a sudden?
Me?
Seriously. You always do whatever you want.
You disappear and show up as you please.
Are you curious about where I went today?
I'm not curious.
I went out today and listened to what people were thinking.
Hey, I told you reading people's minds is bad manners.
They are the same.
They still think they are the most important people...
who deserve everyone's affection.
I knew it, but confirming that again was a nail in the coffin.
What do you mean?
I was right. People don't deserve my compassion.
So...
Go on.
I won't back down from your fight.
I want to see you head over heels and give up everything for me.
- What are you doing? - I'm trying.
What are you trying?
To figure out what I must do to fall in love with a special being.
And did you find a solution?
- Yes. - What is it?
The looks.
Good looks are a must.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing good, I guess.
I guess you must've forgotten the first thing you said to me.
Yes, I did.
But I didn't.
I don't want to hear it.
You need to spend the night with me again tonight.
As you wish.
Should I go over? Or will you come over?
You should come over...
to my dream.
[VIU Ver] tvN E04 'Doom at Your Service'
"How to Love Myul Mang"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
I heard that if I see you in my dream, it'd be game over.
That's what my friend told me.
I can tell this is a dream.
You must love this place.
You took me here.
Your subconscious picked this place.
Really?
I guess I'm having a really tough time.
All right. Let's go to the second round.
- Second round? - Yes.
- To where? - On top of my head...
To a school.
(Dongseon High School)
How should I put it? At school, there are mystery students...
who would get sick often.
You know, the ones with fair skin.
That's my role.
Oh, no. Watch out!
Are you okay?
Next.
What is it this time?
It's continuing from the previous story.
That high school student graduated from school...
and got into the college her crush goes to.
By the way, they met at a church.
Her crush plays the piano for the choir at the church.
I see. A nice guy from a church?
Hey.
You should drink this.
Thanks.
Next.
What is it this time?
Drive in reverse.
Okay.
Stop.
You forgot this. Open it.
Gosh. I can't do this anymore.
Yes. Same here.
This won't work.
Is this it for tonight?
Tell me about you.
To love someone, I must know his world.
Show me your world.
My world?
Just like my subconscious picked this world,
there must be a place for your subconscious too.
Let me tell you again. I'm not human.
My world is nowhere near what you expect.
But if that's what you want,
then so be it.
This is my world.
The reason behind everything that disappears.
The deity that makes everything vanish.
It sure must be lonely to love the things...
that disappear...
the moment you touch them.
Lonely enough not to ever want to love them.
I think I finally understand...
what it is...
that you're running away from.
- Shouldn't you go to work? - It's the weekend.
Fine.
- About last night's dream... - I'm going to forgive you.
- What? - I said I'm going to forgive you.
Who do you think you are?
Someone who wants to love you.
Love begins with forgiveness.
What a joke. That good-for-nothing human thinks she can forgive me.
I know.
Plus, love starts with hate.
But then again,
I guess you need to hate someone in order to forgive them.
I'm not going to forgive you.
I just decided to call a truce today.
I know you have nobody to talk to.
It's the same with me.
Tak Dong Kyung is really starting to get on my nerves.
The wall looks pretty with all those drawings.
I guess Ji Na was right.
Who...
I was scared for nothing.
- What is it? - You were scared?
Why? Did you do something bad?
Did you fight with my brother-in-law?
He's not your brother-in-law.
You should've called before coming here.
Why?
Is my brother-in-law on his way?
My gosh, cut it out.
Gosh.
You never go anywhere during the weekends.
So I thought I'd drop by.
Hey, do you think...
you can lend me some money?
What?
Why? What kind of trouble did you get yourself into this time?
No, I didn't get myself in any trouble.
I want to take lessons.
- Lessons? - Yes.
I want to get a license.
A personal color consultant. It's a popular job these days.
Sun Kyung, what's your major?
Leisure sports. But I really have what it takes.
Ever since I was young, I was very sensitive...
about choosing the right colors for my clothes. You know that right?
Just get lost if you're here to talk nonsense.
I'm tired.
I don't want to listen to your nonsense on a weekend.
"Nonsense"?
I paid for your computer lessons, and you got addicted to games.
I paid for your cooking lessons, but you quit saying you got fat.
I paid for your jujitsu lessons, but you gave up...
saying it hurt whenever someone hit you.
You're seriously...
Will you keep living like this even after I die?
Just forget it if you don't want to lend me money.
You don't need to suddenly start talking about death.
Forget it. I never should've asked.
What would you know? You don't even have a dream.
What?
Don't you know whose fault that is?
Are you saying it's my fault?
Why else do you think I'm working so hard...
instead of having a dream of my own?
If you don't like your job, then just quit.
Just quit your job already.
- Why are you blaming it on me? - Then what?
How will I be able to take care of you?
Who asked you to take care of me?
I can take care of myself.
You got that job because you wanted to.
- What? - Stop blaming it on me.
You're not the only orphan.
I'm an orphan too.
But I still have a dream.
I have something I want to do.
Forget it. There's no point in talking to you.
You won't ever understand.
I don't understand you either.
Forget it. I'll deal with it.
I don't ever want to live like you.
Hey. What did you just say?
- Get off. - Hey.
You asked me to leave.
Hey... Let me see. Are you okay?
Forget it.
Hey...
I guess love isn't that big of a deal.
He meant everything he said.
I'm not in the mood to talk to you.
I just think he was too harsh.
You're trying so hard to make a living for him.
That's none of your business.
Why? Are you going to be forgiving again?
I think you have the wrong idea.
That the person who forgives is kinder.
That being kind wins.
I guess that bothered you.
Sorry. Satisfied?
That's right. You bother me. You keep bothering me.
Fine.
Please stop for today.
What will happen if I kill him right now?
There are many ways.
I can throw one of the many dooms lingering out there on him.
Would you still forgive me?
Can you still love me?
Take back what you said.
Why are you mad? I'm just curious, that's all.
Take it back.
Do you know how many stars collapse every second?
7.9 billion per second.
What makes you special?
Are you better than those stars?
Tell me.
Why should you live?
You just happened to be there.
It's like I want to throw a stone into a calm lake,
and you happen to be the closest stone.
A convenient coincidence.
I wish you'd die.
I wish...
you'd die. I wish you'd experience it.
Because then you'd understand how I feel.
Really?
If that's your wish.
Make your wish come true.
It's a wish I can't grant.
I would've died long ago if I were capable of dying.
If I can't kill you,
I'll at least make you miserable.
So that you can live in misery for all eternity.
Try it. Do it if you can.
But you're miserable immediately if I don't hold your hand.
Hey!
I did it, and I have to fix it in this life.
No one takes care of me in this life.
"I won't do anything. I won't even try."
"I'll... I'll just stay still."
My life had been a series of doing nothing.
I shouldn't have tried...
to feel compassion or love.
Humans are insignificant.
You're no different.
You are no different.
(Defense Counsel)
Thus, the prosecution requests...
that the defendant be sentenced to life in prison.
I rest my case.
Just execute me!
Execute me! Execute me!
Kill me now!
Silence!
I'm right.
Humans are still insignificant.
Give it back!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I said I'm sorry! Kill me!
Give it back!
You...
No!
Kill me! Kill me!
Please kill me!
Kill me!
(Wish, Doom, Sun Kyung, Aunt Soo Ja, Ji Na)
(Wish, Doom, Person I love most)
(Tak Brother)
Hey...
This is Seoul Sun Ho Hospital.
Are you Tak Sun Kyung's guardian?
No.
Taxi. Taxi.
I had a flashback.
Hello?
Is there an adult at home?
Mom and Dad will be home soon.
Who's this?
This is Tak Jong Won and Kang Soo Ha's home, right?
This is a hospital. There's been an accident.
Is there an adult I can call?
Hello?
That first moment my life started...
to become cruel.
Please drive quickly. Please.
Will that do?
- Thank you so much. - I'll be back.
(Building 3, Lower, 5)
It's all because of that jerk.
I'll get him.
I'm going to kill that jerk.
- Let go of me. Let me go! - Hurry!
I'm going to kill that jerk!
- Die! - Hold him!
Let go. Let go of me.
Hey.
- Call an ambulance right now. - Okay.
Hello.
(Jung Seung Jun)
Hey!
Hey.
What are you doing there?
What am I doing?
I'm looking at trees.
Can you see that tree over there?
The leaves are all dead.
No, no.
Let's not do this. We should talk this out.
We're both doctors. I'm sure we can see eye to eye on things.
Which department are you in?
Oh, right. Did you lose one of your patients?
Is that why you're doing this?
I've experienced that too. I know how that feels.
- You do? - Yes.
I've had my fair share of losing patients...
and the pain that comes with it.
So why don't you come down first? Let's talk about this.
People died and disappeared from the world because of me,
and those people keep watching me.
Does that happen to you too?
Yes!
It happens to me too.
It still happens now.
It's tough. We all want to save our patients so badly.
I'm in the same boat.
No, not even close.
I want to end everything.
No.
Come down from there.
Come down.
Should I?
I'll come down.
Okay. Good choice.
(Emergency Medical Center)
I'm here for Tak Sun Kyung.
Where's he right now?
You can check inside.
I bet my sister will get so scared and run to the ER.
I'm 100 percent sure.
She was mean to me before.
I bet she's going crazy right now.
Hey, let's sign up as soon as she gives me the money.
Exactly.
(Absolute Rest)
Dong Kyung.
Dong Kyung!
Big Sis! Tak Dong Kyung!
Wait. Are you...
Ms. Tak's family?
Pardon?
Well, yes.
I'm her brother.
(Emergency Dispatch)
(Building 3, Lower, 5)
Are you following me?
No way. I'm very busy.
Pretending to be a doctor that saves people must be fun for you.
It's not boring.
(Emergency Medical Center)
Move!
Die!
At this rate, she only has three months to live at most.
She must get treated right now.
Can someone call this in?
Your hand...
Let go!
Don't move.
- What just happened? - Don't look.
It's not even worth it.
Don't move. Stop!
Get away from me!
I'll give back...
what I took from you.
- What just happened? - Oh, my gosh!
I need some help here!
- Oh, my. - Did you see that?
I told you.
It's impossible to love me.
Everyone either resents me or wants me.
Or...
some fear me.
(Doom at Your Service)
I want to know too.
So you should just thank me too.
Did it really mean nothing?
Are you out of your mind? Why are you here?
Is Lee Hyun Kyu coming too?
Don't see him.
How long have you been following me?
Do you think it will go as planned?
If you can make a wish before dying,
what would you wish for?
I have a good idea.
Make a wish to fall in love with me.