♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaf clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage
and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 33=
You've started building
your house of love together already?
Mr. Xu, what are you doing here?
You seem to have a lot of free time.
There are some bricks over there.
Help us move them.
So cold?
If it weren't for my big mouth,
how can you two
be this lovey-dovey right now?
Thank you.
What are you doing here, Mr. Xu?
Chuan.
Something came up at the studio.
The landmark project proposal
needs to be amended.
Okay.
I'll head to the office after I'm done here.
Actually, no need.
I found someone and got it done already.
Who?
Su Man Lin.
Sister Man Lin's back?
You two finally
got back together.
I didn't want others
to bother you.
So I asked her
to come back to help out.
Helped you buy
some precious time together.
The amendments
have been sent to your email.
Take a look at night when you have time.
If you have time,
drop by the office tomorrow.
After all,
you're the lead designer on that project.
You can't not care.
Mr. Xu.
If you've already solved the problem,
why bother coming here?
You could have just called.
I'm here to see Xiao Ning, alright?
Of course. Thanks, Mr. Xu.
I'm here to drop something off for you.
Someone
forced me to lie to you to make you sign.
His will.
Take a look.
Don't get angry and don't quarrel.
A will?
Don't do anything like this again, okay?
I don't need you to
make all these plans for me.
I just want you
to include me in your future plans.
Of course you're in
my future plans.
Rules are rules.
Not even occasionally?
No.
I need to think for
your health.
Just once.
No.
Let's cuddle.
Good morning.
Didn't I tell you
to not come pick me up anymore?
Why?
How can I let my girlfriend
drive me around every day?
Aside from being your girlfriend,
I'm also your employee,
your assistant.
Driving is my job.
To make me have no qualms
about earning money,
please order me around
as much as you can.
This way,
if I get paid less,
I can bad-mouth you.
Let's walk to work today.
Can you?
Not every day.
Just today.
What do you mean?
Starting tomorrow,
if there are no special circumstances,
I don't plan on going back to work.
I want to spend more time
on other things.
Like spending time with my parents,
spending time with you.
Sure.
Then what about the studio?
You're the soul of the studio.
You can't keep making
Mr. Xu act on your behalf.
Then it won't be "Chuan Design Studio".
Then I can change it into "Ran Design Studio".
These things
aren't important to me anymore.
I've been working so hard for ten years.
It's not unreasonable
to take a break.
Okay.
Then I'll go with you.
Let's go.
But the person I just said
who doesn't have to work
is me.
You still have to go to work.
Do I really?
Of course.
You don't like working?
I do. A lot.
That's it.
Who's going to pay my bills if you don't work?
Everyone,
listen up.
Mr. Xu just informed me
Mr. Gu is coming back to the studio today.
Everybody, get to work.
Hurry.
Move.
That's so great.
I'm having a hard time making a decision.
What are you doing? Get to work.
Boss is back.
What are you scared of?
Xiao Ning must be
coming back with him.
How can you be so sure?
Maybe the negotiation went wrong
and they went their separate ways.
Shut your mouth.
Good morning.
Oh my gosh.
I thought it was Boss who came back.
So it's you, Xiao Ning.
Should be Mrs. Boss.
Xiao Ning,
you're finally back.
It was so boring
without you here.
As long as you're here,
we don't have to look at
Mr. Gu's ghostly face every day.
If it weren't...
If it weren't for
my infinite adoration
and admiration for Mr. Gu,
he's literally the beacon that lights the way
in my life.
I've always been wondering
how could a person
be this super-duper exceptional.
I'm just...
Hi, Mr. Gu.
Morning.
Looks pretty good.
It can be sent off right away
after I make some amendments.
In other words,
my job here is done.
To be honest,
I'm really happy to be able to have
this opportunity to make things up.
You're ready to go to your new job?
Thank you for giving me
this chance to make up for my mistakes.
And thank you for
sending my resume
to that company overseas.
They're willing to hire you
because you have the right qualifications.
A new company, a new environment,
a new life.
I hope I can also have a new beginning.
Good luck.
I'm going to
have dinner with Jiang Xiao Ning tonight.
Gu Chuan. Take care of yourself.
You don't look so well.
Thank you.
It was me who brought you to this company.
Who would have thought
you'd be the one to send me off today.
Sister Man Lin.
Thank you so much.
You've always been my role model
and you've taught me so much.
I've taught you so much,
but I've failed myself.
I used to think
the reason Gu Chuan didn't like me
is that I wasn't outstanding enough,
not good enough for him.
So I kept trying harder and harder.
But to what end?
You know how things went.
I still lost to you.
Don't say that.
You're brilliant.
One day, I hope you can
meet someone
who can make you happy
even during your saddest moments.
Now I know
why he fell for you.
You're like those
female leads in dramas.
Although you were
a little annoying in the beginning,
as time goes on,
you can't really get people to dislike you.
This is probably your charm.
This is the first time I've heard you compliment me.
You're indeed
more mature than when
you first came to the studio.
So that's why I keep
wanting to thank you.
It's me who should thank you.
Why?
If you didn't come into the picture,
I would've stayed by Gu Chuan's side
like I've always done.
Because I believed that
as long as I waited for him,
he'd be mine eventually.
But you made me realize that
no matter how hard I tried,
how long I waited,
the results would be the same.
He wouldn't fall for me.
You'll meet someone who you like
and likes you back for sure.
Who knows. I'll just let it be.
But I came here today
to tell you something.
Jiang Xiang Ning,
I wish you happiness.
Sister Man Lin, thank you.
How many bookings have you gotten tonight?
I haven't gotten any yet.
I have a feeling I'm going to
get bookings tonight.
At least one.
Isn't it hard for a girl like you
to be a designated driver?
It's okay. As long as you get used to it.
Still not here.
Right.
I'm hungry.
Hungry.
You guys take your time.
I've already paid the bill.
Once Xiao Ning gets here,
we'll leave first.
Mr. Gu, why are you in such a rush?
Once Xiao Ning gets here,
you should have something to eat before leaving.
Exactly.
Sorry, everyone.
I'm late.
Xiao Ning, come on.
Xiao Ning, we've been waiting for you.
We couldn't start without you.
I'm sorry.
Now that everyone's here,
let's...
let's drink to
Boss and Xiao Ning's
sweet comeback.
Thank you.
Cheers. Thank you.
Come on, give it to me.
I have to drink to that.
You can't drink.
This drink is to everyone.
Thank you for all your hard work these years.
Thank you.
Thank you, Boss.
Bottoms up.
Alright.
I'll leave with Xiao Ning first.
Her exam is coming up.
I have to tutor her.
You're tutoring her personally?
Yes.
We'll leave first then.
Okay.
Bye, Boss.
You guys take your time. Enjoy.
Bye-bye, Xiao Ning.
Bye-bye.
Why do I feel like
Boss is acting weird today?
I always thought Boss
would end up with Su Man Lin.
I didn't expect it to be Jiang Xiao Ning.
Are you that slow?
I knew a long time ago.
Mainly because neither of them said anything,
so I couldn't really gossip about it.
Being at the company for so long,
I've witnessed enough public displays
of affection.
When will I finally meet
my Prince Charming?
What are you looking at?
Cheng Dong.
What? I can't?
No.
You can't look at him.
Come with me.
Hurry.
I'm eating.
Where to?
Jia Jia, could you save some face
for me in front of our co-workers?
What's wrong with me looking at handsome guys?
You can't.
Fine. Then tell me
why looking at Cheng Dong is wrong.
Look, you're
a single lady.
Ogling like that
isn't good for your image.
Wang Kai, you're a chicken.
How am I chicken?
In every way.
You coward.
You like me.
Why can't you just say that directly?
Always beating around the bush.
Aren't you tired?
There are so many people at the office.
Look at Jiang Xiao Ning.
She made a public confession.
What are you afraid of?
Do you like me or not?
I...
Say it.
Are you telling me or not?
Ouch.
I like you.
Then kiss me.
No.
Wang Kai.
No, no, no.
The timing isn't right.
This setting isn't very fitting.
But can you feel
my burning heart?
Feel my heartbeat.
Feel it.
Okay, I got it.
I know you felt it.
Let's go eat.
I didn't feel it.
Let's go eat, okay?
Let's go eat. Eat.
This setting is really not right.
Really couldn't do it.
No.
I'm serious.
Before the tutoring session,
let's deal with
this first.
Xu Cheng Ran lied to me.
I didn't take a look at these carefully
before signing them.
I'll ask our legal department
to take a look at it
to see how we can
rescind these agreements.
Back then, I was scared,
in case...
There is no "in case".
Starting now,
you just need to think about
how you're going to live happily every day.
From now on, each of your days
must have me in them.
Also,
don't work too hard.
Don't do any housework either.
I got it.
Get to studying.
Do you agree with what I said?
I do.
Okay. Teacher.
You can start your lesson.
First, I have a question for you.
The minimum clearance of the upper and
lower aisles of a stairs landing
is 2 meters.
The minimum
headroom clearance for stairs is 2.2 meters.
Was that statement
correct or incorrect?
Correct.
Correct?
Incorrect?
Incorrect.
Are you just randomly guessing?
I know the answer.
You asked the question so suddenly,
so I doubted myself.
Ask another question.
Think carefully
about the question I just asked you.
Have you read this section?
This section.
I finished the entire book.
How about this?
Not yet.
Looks like you're in a bad mood.
Did you ask me to come drink with you?
Not to drink.
Something better.
You're really something.
The good things you talk about
never end up happening.
You don't need to invest anything this time.
Just need some physical strength.
Then tell me.
The thing is...
some money came into my branch.
I want to move this money
to Zhi Mu Design's account.
Help me find a way
to cash it out.
I'll give you 20 percent afterwards.
How much?
Thirty million.
That much?
Whose is it?
It's Xu Guo Xiang's for now,
but it'll be mine later.
You dare touch his money?
Aren't you scared he's going to kill you?
Zheng, relax.
I have something on him.
He wouldn't dare to touch me.
Plus, I've done
so much for him over the years.
If there were problems, I would've
gone to jail already.
I deserve this money.
Don't you worry.
I'll take responsibility if something
were to happen.
Thirty percent should be enough, right?
Alright, I'll do it.
But I'm telling you right now,
if something were to happen, you would
have to deal with it.
Don't worry.
Looking forward to working with you again.
Director Xu.
Xiao Xu. Why is it taking so long?
It has been more than a week already.
How come the money still hasn't been cashed out?
Didn't you ask me to be more careful?
I'm being thorough.
Don't want to get caught.
No matter how thorough you're being,
it should've been done already.
It didn't take this long last time.
Am I doing it or are you?
You can do it then.
Director Xu.
Director Xu. It's still going to take a few more days.
Xiao Xu.
Although we're not related by blood,
we've been living together for more than ten years.
You should know that
I think of you as my own son.
Of course, I do.
You've always been so good to me.
So, think about it.
Why do I ask you to transfer
that much money?
It's because I trust you.
Xiao Xu.
You can't let me down.
I won't, Director Xu.
I won't let you down.
You've treated me so well.
That's good.
Go on.
This isn't normal.
I think something has been
going on with this kid as well.
Keep an eye on him.
Find out what's going on.
Okay, right away.
Xiao Mi, is Xu Cheng Ran in?
Yes.
He has been
working overtime for several nights.
I know.
I'm going to go in to see him.
How about I give him a heads-up first?
That's alright.
Once he's done with work,
we'll go home together.
You've worked hard.
Thank you.
Wifey.
What are you doing here?
Wifey brought Hubby food.
Is that a problem?
Wifey.
I thought you didn't want anyone
to know about our relationship.
You're not afraid that someone will see us?
We're official and legal.
What's there to be scared of?
But before, you...
No more "but"s.
From today on,
I want to
be with you openly.
You've finally come around.
So cute.
Xu Cheng Ran.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want you to make
our relationship public
because I was overthinking everything,
not because you're not worthwhile.
Seeing Gu Chuan and Jiang Xiao Ning
getting back together
made me think that
I should cherish
every single day I get to spend with you.
Wifey is right.
You should cherish me.
Let's go home right now.
So you could make it up to me.
What's wrong with you?
I just gave you an inch
and now you want to take a mile?
Oh, right. Wifey.
I want you to come to a press conference
being held in a few days.
No, I'm just
a department manager.
What manager?
You're my wife.
You have to come.
I don't want you to miss
your husband's shining moment.
Get back to work.
Have it while it's hot.
I'm leaving.
What work?
Didn't I say
we're going home and you're making things up to me?
Let's go.
(Chairman's Office)
No need to work overtime today.
Go home early, everyone.
My wife came to pick me up.
I'm leaving now.
See you all tomorrow.
Nice going, Xu Cheng Ran.
So many female employees here.
All wearing short skirts.
It smells so good, Wifey.
What did you make?
(Indoor Plant Decor)
Isn't there a lot to do?
What are we doing at a nursery?
To buy some
flowers for the yard.
Then this is not a part of
architectural design.
It's landscape design.
These are pretty nice.
(Everything seems the same.)
(Yet, everything seems different.)
(I'm standing right next to him,)
(but I have to distance myself from him at all times.)
(Our hearts)
(have never been this closer together.)
(But like he said,)
(our future)
(has never been so unclear)
(and uncertain.)
(Although I don't know)
(how we can keep going,)
(as long as I'm by his side,)
(no matter in what way,)
(I'll feel at ease.)
Do you think
Grandma will like this?
She will.
What were you thinking?
Nothing.
I was wondering whether we have to buy a bunch?
Of course.
How will we bring everything back?
They do delivery.
Let's keep looking.
We have a pretty wide
variety of plants.
For example, these flamingo flowers over here
imply the blossoming of fortune.
You could consider buying several.
I've already taken out my share.
The rest
has been transferred to your account.
I've received it, Zheng.
Thanks.
Tomorrow, I'll be
away for a while.
I understand.
It's the right move to stay away for a while.
Come back when it's clear.
You're not leaving?
Why would I leave?
I have nothing to be afraid of.
Here. Enjoy your trip.
I've read the new proposal.
It's great. I'm very satisfied with it.
As long as all the board members are satisfied.
Actually,
we're not against this plan.
As long as the expenditures are reasonable,
there's nothing else wrong with it, right?
You're right.
The current spending plan
was revised
according to the suggestions put forward
by the board members at the last meeting.
I promise to implement it to a tee.
Good. Great.
Great.
Sure enough, Cheng Ran
is becoming more and more mature.
Like father, like son.
We're all very pleased that
you're able to take over so soon.
From now on,
the group is in your hands.
I'll do my very best.
Oh, right.
There will be a press conference in a few days.
I invited many journalist friends
to help promote us.
It'll also be live-streamed on the Internet.
This will be a great opportunity
to build our company's image.
I hope all the board members
can attend.
Such a great opportunity.
We've got to attend, right?
Exactly.
Alright.
Let me summarize.
We'll all go back you up.
How's that?
Alright?
Sure.
Then, thank you all
in advance.
Okay.
The time for the younger generation has come.
Young and promising indeed.
Yes.
Let me.
Just sit here.
Don't do anything.
Don't touch anything.
Leave everything to me.
Why are you like this all of a sudden?
Let me do it.
I said let me...
Gu Chuan.
What's wrong?
Help me to the charging room.
Okay.
Come on. Be careful.
Careful.
How do you feel?
Be careful.
Charging.
Charging interrupted.
What's happening?
Why is it happening?
Charging.
Charging interrupted.
Gu Chuan.
Gu Chuan. Wake up. Gu Chuan.
Don't do this to me.
Gu Chuan.
Gu Chuan. Wake up. Gu Chuan.
Gu Chuan. You're going to be okay. Gu Chuan.
Gu Chuan.
Charge. Gu Chuan.
Gu Chuan. You'll be okay.
It'll be okay. Gu Chuan.
Charge.
Charging.
You almost scared me to death, Gu Chuan.
I thought you were leaving
me by myself again.
I'm fine. Stop crying.
I'm not crying.
Safe Mode?
Yes. This way, the mechanical heart
will work at minimum capacity,
only maintaining the most basic functions.
But,
it will affect the blood flow.
For example,
it won't
respond to
human emotions.
The person
will become kind of dull and slow.
But at least,
it'll allow the person to live a little longer.
Wait.
Why do you have to
have this Safe Mode?
To prolong one's life.
This way, at least you'll have enough time
to say goodbye to this world.
You won't leave the world suddenly.
In other words,
if I'm in the Safe Mode,
that means it's reminding me that
I don't have much time left?
Right.
You can think of it that way.
This...
You're up.
Why are you in a daze?
Let's eat.
Do you remember
the first time I cooked for you?
I do.
Back then, I hoped
you could live a warmer and more emotional life.
What about now?
Now,
I want you to be healthy and happy.
I will.
Eat while it's still hot.
How is it?
It's good.
Then have some more.
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night. Ah~♪
What is it?
Nothing.
I just like looking at you.
Have some too.
♪The destined one♪
♪Guiding me forward♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
♪Total strangers during our first encounter♪
♪Why does my heart beat so fiercely♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
(Gu Chuan.)
(You will get better.)
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
Director Xu.
Director Xu, you asked for me?
Tang Xu.
You dare to touch my money?
Do you have a death wish?
Or do you think I'm getting old?
All these years,
I think I've done a lot for you.
Even if the work I've done doesn't get recognized,
the time and effort I put in cannot be denied.
So I think
I deserve that money.
Tang Xu, so you're saying that
you're keeping this money
no matter what?
Why? Can't I?
Do you think you should?
Tang Xu.
What you've said is all bollocks.
I've supported you for so many years and
treated you like my own son.
This is how you repay me?
Don't bother with the pretty words.
Who are you trying to fool?
Answer me.
Will you let Xu Cheng Ran
do something illegal with you?
If what you've said is true,
the two of us are the same to you.
Fine.
I'll transfer the money to him right now.
Let him be your pawn
for once.
You really are an ingrate.
Ungrateful bastard.
Tang Xu, I'm telling you.
Don't play tricks with me.
Give me back the money right now.
Otherwise, not only will I not spare you,
I won't spare Tang Zheng Cheng either.
If you dare to lay a finger on him,
I'll make sure all the evidence
I have on you get out.
You dare to challenge me?
Anyway, I'll drag you down with me.
I know too much about you.
Tang Xu.
If I can be so easily
manipulated by you,
I should get rid of my last name, Xu.
Go check as you wish.
But I can
tell you right now that
the only person who will be
found guilty is you.
You have three days
to give me back my money
and get lost.
(Hello.)
(Are you Dr. Peer's assistant,)
(Miss Qing Zi?)
(There is something very important that)
(I'd like to discuss with you.)
(I look forward to hearing back from you.)
(If you could give me your contact details,)
(I would appreciate it. Jiang Xiao Ning.)
Xiao Ning.
Go downstairs and
buy tomorrow's breakfast.
Where is she?
Mom.
What's going on with her?
What's she doing cooped up
in her room?
Studying.
Studying?
Ning Ning.
Studying hard.
Okay.
(Sorry, I just saw your email.)
(Here is my contact details...)
Hello?
I'm Gu Chuan's girlfriend.
Sorry to contact you out of the blue.
I have something very important
I'd like to ask you about face-to-face.
I'm in Shanghai for a business trip.
You can come meet me.
You're on a business trip in Shanghai?
Could I go meet you?
Okay, great.
Thank you.
(Gu Chuan.)
(I know you won't give up on me.)
(I won't give up on you either.)
Hello, Boss.
Hello.
I'd like to take some time off.
Why?
I want to take Grandma
to get a thorough check-up.
Need to be
vigilant at all times when it comes to seniors.
Grandma's got more and more
episodes of memory loss recently.
Aunty has a bad back, so she can't go.
I'll go with you.
No, that's okay.
It's only a check-up.
Alright.
If you need anything,
feel free to let me know.
Okay. Thanks, Boss.
You're still calling me "Boss"?
Thanks, my boyfriend.
Hello. Are you Qing Zi?
You must be Miss Jiang.
Please have a seat.
Miss Jiang came by
to ask me
about the mechanical heart, right?
Yes.
I did some research online.
I want to know
what kind of problem
is Gu Chuan's mechanical heart having.
I found these symptoms,
but they don't seem to be the same.
So I want...
Stop looking.
Mr. Gu's problem
is rare,
not common.
Even when Dr. Peer
was alive,
he couldn't solve the problem.
What you can find on the Internet
is even less useful.
Is there another way?
Can't it be replaced with a biological heart?
Mr. Gu has been using
a mechanical heart for ten years.
If he were to switch to
a biological heart now,
his survival rate will be very low.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night~~♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪