Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow
that fills up the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and
let's count down to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard
Episode 22
Charging.
Why would it be like this?
Just a light impact
causes the mechanical heart to work abnormally
and the battery power to drop.
Is the malfunction
more serious now?
Are you really insensitive to pain?
Chuan!
Chuan, what's going on?
Why is the alarm activated?
It's just a malfunction.
It's no big deal.
You scared the crap out of me.
Do you know
how worried I was
on my way here?
I was afraid
you would just...
All right now.
Stop being emotional.
So?
Have you told Jiang Xiao Ning?
I haven't gotten the chance to.
Also...
I lost my watch.
You lost your watch?
Perhaps,
Jiang Xiao Ning found it.
That's great.
You can't hide it anymore.
Have you made up your mind?
Yes.
Director Xu.
Where's Gu Chuan?
Is he all right?
He's fine.
He is waiting for you
in the charging room upstairs.
You two may talk.
I'll get going.
Charging room?
Charging interrupted.
Boss.
What are you doing?
This is a mechanical heart.
I need to recharge it to stay alive.
So...
you were charging it?
That's right.
I found your watch.
It says "charging".
All of a sudden,
I recalled many things.
Now that you have seen it.
This is my greatest secret.
Are you...
a robot?
I'm not.
Besides
having a mechanical heart,
I'm just like ordinary people
in every other aspect.
It's just that
at times,
there will be some glitches.
What glitches?
If my heart rate is high,
and I don't control it well,
there'll be electric discharge
from my body.
That's why you broke the car,
and electrocuted He Sheng
and me?
The reason I asked you here
is to tell you
about my mechanical heart
and the things between us.
There are still some problems
with the mechanical heart.
So I can't live
like a normal person.
But a few days ago,
the doctor
who developed the mechanical heart said
that he would solve all the problems
of the mechanical heart
within three months.
In other words,
except for the need for recharging,
I will be able to live
just like normal people.
The reason why I asked you
to wait for me for three months
is because I hope that
these problems can be solved
before we get together.
Well, why would your heart
be in such a state?
Ten years ago,
I suffered a very serious injury.
What happened?
A car accident.
I was driving on the mountain road
and saw a truck in front of me
hit a car.
I got out of my car to help.
The truck hit me and the car
and we plunged down the cliff.
When I woke up,
I was in the valley.
♪And light up the night♪
There was a little girl
next to me.
She was stuck in the car and couldn't move.
And she couldn't see her parents
who were in the front seat.
I knew her parents
might have stopped breathing.
But I couldn't tell her that
because
that day was her birthday.
You were badly injured
but you still used your last bit of strength
to encourage her to live
and you even gave her
a strawberry from the cake.
Here.
Make a wish.
If you make a wish
on your birthday,
it will come true.
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
That's right.
Were you that big brother?
Yes.
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
Sorry.
I didn't recognize you.
In the last 10 years,
I've been looking for this big brother.
I want to tell him,
"Thank you."
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
I didn't expect
that we would meet
in such a way
after 10 years.
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
From now on,
we'll never be apart again.
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪
I could feel the electric discharge.
Isn't it
that you couldn't feel the pain?
You didn't feel it before
when the electricity is discharged from my body.
Let me feel it again.
I could really feel it.
Why would it be like this?
Will you be afraid of me?
It's just electricity leakage.
I'm not afraid.
Back then, when I had dreams,
I couldn't see your face clearly.
Now, I finally know
what that big brother
looks like.
So the saying is true.
"All encounters in life
are reunions after a long time apart."
Well, I'll get going now.
Otherwise, my grandma and aunt
will be worried.
Can you manage it being by yourself?
I can.
If not,
you can stay and keep me company.
I think you look fine.
I'll go now.
I'll walk you.
Dr. Peel said
it's just three months, right?
That's right.
Will there be no electricity leakage
after three months?
Jiang Xiao Ning.
I believe you.
You came right away
without asking where I wanted to go?
I'll accompany you
wherever you want to go.
Never leave your side.
At your beck and call.
Pick somewhere nice.
Let's go for an outing.
Yan Yan.
This is the first time you asked me out.
Does it mean
that our relationship
has taken another step further?
That's right.
It's hot.
Yan Yan.
To let you get to know me better,
today, I decided to show
the talented side of me.
A moment, please.
You're being mysterious.
Self-heating hot pot
You can play guitar?
Not bad, right?
I composed it myself.
But no lyrics yet.
It's nice.
When I was a kid,
I used to secretly
practice the guitar.
But my mom doesn't like it.
She likes classical music.
So I've learned piano,
violin, cello, et cetera.
So you want to be a musician?
That never crossed my mind.
I just like listening to it.
It makes me happy.
I'm better at doing business.
I like maths too.
When I was young,
I dreamed of being a mathematician.
You're different
from what you appear to be.
Right?
Did you suddenly realize
there are many sides of mine
and each one of them is perfect?
Give you an inch and you'll take a mile.
Is the self-heating pot ready?
Do you remember the big brother
that I told you about?
Of course.
You've said it many a time.
It's destiny to meet
in the boundless huge crowd...
It's Gu Chuan.
That big brother is Gu Chuan.
You...
It's giving me
goosebumps.
The person that you've been thinking about
is the one you have a crush on?
What a plot twist.
Actually,
there's one more thing that I haven't told you.
He said yes to you?
How did you know?
I could tell from the look on your face.
I thought
it was Director Xu who told you.
That fool
is probably still none the wiser.
Don't underestimate him.
He has many admirers.
My colleague, Qiao Meng Jia,
seems to be really into him.
Don't get me started.
As my bestie,
how could you not tell me
who that girl was?
Those two...
It was an act.
But still,
she couldn't keep asking him for a kiss.
Just be honest.
Do you like him or not?
You keep playing hard to get.
It's not your style.
You've always been very resolute.
Either you like him,
or you don't.
I like him.
Accept him then.
I'm just scared.
I know what love is like.
Experiencing it once
is enough.
I...
I don't want to be fooled again.
It's not Director Xu's fault
to be born rich.
Besides,
he's definitely not a married guy.
He won't be like that scumbag.
He truly loves you.
Let's move on to you.
I'm more interested
with your stuff.
Have you two...
I...
We...
Spill!
I want feedback
on these documents before the end of the day.
Okay, Boss.
Also,
here.
I bought it for you.
First Blood!
Double Kill!
Chuan Design Studio
Triple Kill!
Brother Kai.
Have you noticed
those two are acting weird?
Why are you laughing?
Who?
Both of them.
Here's the thing.
It's not appropriate
for us, the Admin Department,
to make comments
on your Design Department.
Go back to your department then.
Watch your tongue.
Go on.
Jia Jia.
That's a brilliant move by Mr. Gu.
The love design specially made by Kai Kai Wang.
Jia Jia.
Two same design of Kai Kai Wang's
Meco Peach and Pink Grapefruit.
It's tasty, and it brings luck,
boosting your love luck.
You deserve it.
Are you not right in the head?
Wang Kai.
I want to use another way
to confess to you.
The fruit juice is nice.
But
you are not as good as it.
Don't switch styles as you wish.
I...
The day I become rich
will be the day I marry you.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Excuse me.
Could you help to take a look
if this is the right address?
Yes, this is the place.
It's correct.
I'm looking for Tang Xu.
Have you made an appointment?
Appointment?
If not,
I can't help you
get him.
I'm Tang Xu's dad.
Reindeer Group
Xu Guo Xiang and I
are old friends.
We've known each other for over two decades.
I'm sorry, sir.
Why don't you give him a call
and ask him out?
Look.
I'm Tang Xu's dad indeed.
If you don't believe me,
you can call him and check.
You...
Hi, Mr. Tang.
Xiao Xu.
Why are you here?
I came to see you.
It looks good around here.
Well, if you're busy,
I'll go and see Xu Guo Xiang.
I have things to talk to him about.
He's out.
Besides, he seldom comes to the company.
When will he come again?
I don't know.
I'll let you know if he comes.
How about having lunch together?
It's almost lunch time anyway.
I'm not free.
Look.
When I was in prison,
I could talk to others
when we were let out for exercise.
But now?
I'm out now.
Besides buying groceries, I'm all alone
at home.
There's no one to talk to.
If you are free,
come home some time.
Are you done yet?
Listen.
I don't have time.
I'm very busy.
Look.
You...
Come home when you're free.
You've been staring at me for a long time.
Boss.
Don't you think
we're a perfect match?
There's electric discharge from your body,
and I'm not afraid of the pain.
There's no one more suitable
to be with you than me.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Well, can I continue?
Do what?
Confessing.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
You're a girl.
You should be more reserved.
What's with that expression?
Do you accept me or not?
Don't just smile.
I do.
Where are we going now?
You'll know when we get there.
Okay.
Boss.
We're on the campus
at this late hour.
Are you thinking about
having campus romance with me?
Look at you.
What's on your mind all day?
You.
Here.
Take a look.
Clock of Time
Designer: Jiang Guang Da, in 2006
This is...
This is from your dad.
Clock of Time
Designer: Jiang Guang Da, in 2006
How did you know
it was here?
When I was going through the information,
I found
that the designer is called Jiang Guang Da.
I was wondering
if he was your dad
or just someone with the same name.
Then I checked the personnel list
and found that it was really your dad.
I don't even know about this.
It's been quite some time.
The land in this place
is getting more and more expensive.
The campus may have to relocate
to a new place.
In another two years.
This place will be demolished after two years.
How did you know
that he left this behind?
Was it really from him?
It's from your dad, really.
Actually, the designers are the people
working behind the scenes.
After the building is put into use,
not many people will care
who the designer is.
For example,
when we go to the mall, listen to the opera,
or go to the exhibition,
no one will ask
who built those buildings
or who the designer is.
That's why many designers
will leave their own marks
in their own designs.
Some designers
will incorporate some of their own styles,
whereas some designers
might leave behind
a piece of brick,
a tile,
or a cornerstone.
And so,
your dad left this.
I never thought
I would find something
related to my dad now.
Thank you.
Our company
will be responsible
for the design of the new project here.
If you take part in it,
your name
will be engraved on it too.
Then,
your name
will be engraved
with your dad's.
Consider it a gift from me.
Thank you.
Which faculty are you from?
What time is it now?
Why are you cuddling here?
Run.
Let's go.
♪What kind of me would you like♪
♪I'm at a loss for words♪
♪It's like I'm seeing the future♪
♪It's because you're by my side♪
Boss.
The safety belt is broken. I can't pull it.
♪Woo～～♪
Who taught you that?
Sister Yan Yan.
You don't have to learn these tricks anymore.
Why?
Because you're the one I like.
♪Woo～～♪
♪My heart beats because you are by my side♪
What's the matter?
You can sleep in the room.
I'll take the couch.
No, I'll take the couch.
Listen to me. It's not comfortable
sleeping on the couch.
Boss, go upstairs and sleep.
Don't mind me.
If that's the case,
I'll sleep on the couch too.
It's not comfortable.
I want to be closer to you.
Just sleep.
Boss, what time is it?
It's 9:30 am.
I'm sorry.
I must have slept soundly
that I slept through the alarm.
I turned off the alarm.
Get more rest.
I'm cooking porridge for breakfast.
I'll wake you when it's ready.
I need to get to work.
Wherever I am,
that's where you'll work.
I never thought I would be able to sleep in.
It's such a blessing to be able to do that.
I want to make more money
and retire early.
That way, I can live such a life sooner.
Thinking about retirement already?
There are decades to go.
I know.
That's why I'll be working hard.
Sister Man Lin.
Jiang Xiao Ning, what time is it now?
Where is the information I gave you yesterday?
I've organized the content
and sent it to your mailbox.
Perhaps, it didn't get through.
Help me buy an iced latte.
Buy coffee?
I haven't arrived at the office yet.
I'll buy it for you when I get there.
What time is it now?
You haven't come to the office yet?
Are you sick of this job
and don't want it anymore?
It's not that.
Jiang Xiao Ning is working on some stuff
at my place.
She will go to the office once it's done.
You can get back to sleep.
I can't sleep now.
It puts me on the edge,
and it's getting tougher.
Hello?
Didn't I tell you
that Jiang Xiao Ning is sleeping now?
You can order a takeaway.
You are...
Brother Xu
Brother Xu.
Go on.
Xiao Ning, where are you now?
I'm at the boss's house.
What's up?
Nothing.
Tang Zheng Cheng is out.
He wants to cook a meal for you.
Would you like to go?
Sure.
I'll be there.
Just text me
the time and location.
Also, make sure it doesn't clash
with my working hours.
Okay.
Get back to your work then.
You have so many friends, huh?
Why is Boss always angry?
He probably didn't sleep well,
and thus got a bad temper.
Let's see what kind of food
can help to ease that.
Xiao Ning, you're here.
Come on in.
This way.
Xiao Ning, you're here.
Mr. Tang.
It's been a while.
That's right.
You're a big girl now.
It's been ten years now.
That's right.
Xiao Ning, take a seat.
Right.
Here.
Here. Take a seat.
Mr. Tang, take a seat.
Sure.
I wanted to take you to eat out.
But he insisted to cook for you
at home.
The food outside
isn't as clean and hygienic
as home-cooked meals.
Mr. Tang.
Have you gotten used to your life now?
It's all right.
Something happened at home
a while ago.
So I was staying at your place
for some time.
Xiao Xu told me about it.
Did you enjoy your stay?
That's great.
Here, Xiao Ning.
Eat up.
That's right.
Here.
Eat up.
Try the prawns that I made.
What do you think?
How do you like the food?
Mr. Tang.
When I went to visit you,
you refused to see me.
Now that we have met,
I still have some questions for you.
Go ahead.
What happened back then,
was that the whole truth?
I'm not sure what you're asking about.
Did my dad really embezzle money?
He has passed away.
I can only ask you now.
Did he really embezzle money?
I know
what kind of man my dad was.
I'm sure you do as well, right?
So I just want to know
what really happened back then.
Mr. Tang.
I don't mean to rub your nose in the dirt.
But this
is really important to me.
Xiao Ning.
I get how you feel.
But this
was a long time ago.
There are many things
that I don't remember anymore.
If my dad committed the crime,
you can just tell me.
I can accept it.
But
if there is any misunderstanding
or something
that has not been investigated,
you should tell me.
You are the only witness
I can find.
I've waited for this answer for ten years.
I don't know.
I really don't know!
Mr. Tang.
If you could recall
any details
at all,
come to me.
All right?
Xiao Ning, I'm sorry.
I'm having a bad headache.
I...
Let's talk some other time.
Sorry.
I'm going to take a nap.
Xiao Ning.
Brother Xu, I'm sorry.
I wanted to have a good chat.
But I couldn't control myself.
I didn't mean
to upset Mr. Tang.
I know.
I...
I should get going.
I'll send you then.
It's fine.
I want to be alone.
Xiao Ning.
Gu Chuan's lawyer friend
has been investigating Chen Ao.
Jiang Guang Da's daughter, Jiang Xiao Ning
went to see Tang Zheng Cheng again today.
It seems a little dangerous.
Jiang Xiao Ning and Gu Chuan
were both survivors
in the valley.
Right now, Jiang Xiao Ning
is working
at Gu Chuan's company.
Do you think
there's such a coincidence in this world?
With both of them together,
I'm sure they have some information
to investigate what happened back then.
I even wonder
if Gu Chuan deliberately
became good friends
with Cheng Ran.
He made friends with Cheng Ran
to get closer to you.
This guy is becoming a threat.
If we let them keep digging for the truth,
they must cause great trouble for us.
No.
We can't let this happen.
We need to tie up loose ends.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪