(Episode 3)
I don't believe this.
That was a perfect high F.
What happened? You didn't say
you'd raise it to a high F.
It's hard enough to hit it
after a break.
It's nearly impossible to hit it
in one breath.
Did you intentionally hold back
what you could do?
You.
Who are you?
How...
How are you...
Finally, I get to say hi.
I hope we get along
from now on, Seo Jin.
How...
did you get in here?
Shouldn't you thank me?
How can you sing?
Your vocal cords were ruined.
Yes, thanks to you.
I guess it's a miracle.
I got the surgery done,
and I'm completely recovered.
My throat that you stabbed
with your trophy...
saved you from embarrassment today.
Isn't life so funny?
You...
really sang that?
No way.
I certainly talked
to Park Young Ran.
The number you have dialed is
not registered.
Please check the number again.
Why?
Are you flustered because the number
doesn't exist?
(Park Young Ran)
Did you set this up?
Did you set it up to fool me?
How could you? Did you stalk me?
How did you find out
that my voice was having issues?
Take your things and get out
right now.
I don't care whether you two
got married for real or not.
- But you can't live here.
- Why not?
Your daughter, Eun Byeol,
lives here.
Don't you care if she gets hurt?
Do you call yourself her dad?
(Installed)
Why are you so scared?
No one who made a debut.
Find an amateur.
She can't be too young or too old.
She has to be around my age.
We don't have time. We have a week.
This concert must be perfect...
no matter what.
What do you want?
There must be a reason why
you're doing all of this!
I'm just getting back everything...
that you took away from me.
You remember, right?
The best voice and Yoon Chul
were both mine...
initially.
What did you just say?
Who would've thought that you'd
look for someone to lip-sync to?
Life is full of surprises,
don't you think?
Cheon Seo Jin, the fake soprano.
She's right there!
Congratulations on making
new history in Korea's music scene!
Tell us how you feel about the best
performance you just had.
You've proven yourself to everyone
despite the retirement rumors.
You must've felt so pressured
as a soprano.
How did you overcome that?
What's the secret
to your perfect voice?
You're the biggest star.
Please say a word.
Seo Jin, that was
an amazing performance today.
Congratulations.
This is just the beginning.
Just you wait.
I'm going to get my place back.
Thank you.
I'd like to be interviewed
officially tomorrow.
I need some rest.
Secretary Do, please schedule
the interviews...
at their best convenience.
- Please!
- Just one thing.
- Please say a word.
- Please get out.
- Ms. Cheon!
- Please!
See you tomorrow.
That was so amazing.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Let's go.
How have you been?
I know I have no right to say this,
but I miss you so much.
Sorry.
Give me a little time.
I'll uncover the truth
behind what happened that day...
even if it kills me.
And...
I'll pay for my sins too. I promise.
Here's to the 20th anniversary...
of the beautiful prima donna
Cheon Seo Jin's debut.
- Cheers!
Congratulations.
I totally got goosebumps.
How could a human being
make such a sound?
The reviews praising you
are pouring in.
You really are the one and only
treasure of our country.
Is there anything that you lack?
You come from a good family.
You're the best in your field.
Your ex-husband is a doctor.
Your current boyfriend is
a successful businessman.
You got everything.
Life is so unfair.
Chairman Joo is the one
who has it good.
His business is thriving.
His future wife is successful.
He's besties with Kyu Jin.
He wouldn't change places
even with the president of Korea.
Thank you for celebrating with us.
Let's drink until late.
It's all on me.
Yes!
Your voice sounded very different
from usual.
You raised the final note
to a high F, didn't you?
Right?
I thought it was
a different person too.
What's your secret?
I want to share it with Jenny.
Yes, how did you do it?
Did you pick up a new skill?
There's nothing like that.
That's right. I saw Oh Yoon Hee
at the concert tonight.
I wonder if Dr. Ha was with her.
That couple keeps
elbowing their way in...
where they're not invited.
Oh Yoon Hee was there?
When? I didn't see her.
Let's stop talking about
useless things, and drink.
I'm sure she wanted to ruin
a nice day.
She always considered Seo Jin
a rival all her life...
and survived on
her inferiority complex.
She must've been jealous...
when she heard
about her solo concert...
Yoon Hee wasn't there!
My apologies.
I don't feel too well.
Please excuse me.
But... Ms. Cheon...
What the...
What's wrong with her?
Let's reschedule the celebration.
Why is she being like that
on this happy occasion?
Something did happen.
I bet Oh Yoon Hee...
That goes without saying.
She's been irritable
ever since she moved in.
She's such a brat.
That's why Dr. Ha switched over
to Oh Yoon Hee.
We'll have to watch
what we say for the time being.
I'm afraid it'll end up
hurting the kids.
Her and her nasty temper.
Poor Chairman Joo. Poor guy.
Why is he marrying someone like her?
It's better to grow old alone.
He is affection-deprived.
Fake soprano Cheon Seo Jin.
Stop! Stop!
You need to project!
Don't you know how important
this audition is?
It's an opportunity to sing with
the best opera company in Italy.
They only wanted to see Yoon Hee,
the top student in the school,
but I forced your way in.
I'll practice more, Father.
I can do it.
I know I can pass the audition.
Are you weeping
because I nagged a little?
You know I can't stand
seeing chicks cry.
Do it again!
How did it go?
Who made it, Yoon Hee or me?
Loser.
You can't beat her even once?
Then...
is Yoon Hee going to Italy?
I can't allow that.
We arranged it to say
Yoon Hee turned them down.
After what I did to get you in,
you almost lost it.
What a disgrace.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
What's Eun Byeol doing?
She just fell asleep
after finishing her assignment.
Good work.
You should rest too.
Eun Byeol.
Finally, I can breathe.
My mom's engagement...
and my dad's return
after getting remarried...
were all annoying me
and driving me crazy.
Thanks for coming with me,
Seok Hoon.
Just hang on a few more months.
During your mom
and my dad's wedding,
we'll drop our bombs
and each go our separate ways.
No one can find out before then.
You promised you wouldn't do this.
Can it really not be me?
Aren't you sick of asking me that?
I told you
I'm not interested in you.
We have the same goal, that's all.
Ruining the wedding.
Never becoming family.
You can't end up with Ro Na anyway.
You can use me to get over Ro Na.
So...
Eun Byeol. I told you
not to say Ro Na's name.
It's late. Let's go.
Wait for me.
Thanks for taking me out.
Get home safely.
Sweet dreams.
Where did you go?
To the studio.
I couldn't study,
so I went to practice instead.
What are you doing?
I went swimming.
You're the top student.
Why are you trying so hard?
Later.
She didn't hear me, did she?
Eun Byeol. So you're lying now.
Who's your boyfriend
that you were out this late?
Dr. Ha has been attending
business meetings...
or spending time with Oh Yoon Hee.
There hasn't been anything unusual.
What about her daughter?
I haven't seen her yet.
She hasn't seen her daughter.
Was Oh Yoon Hee at the concert?
Yes. She was in the dressing room
with Ms. Cheon.
She was with her.
I saw Oh Yoon Hee
at the concert tonight.
Yoon Hee wasn't there!
Put a tail on Cheon Seo Jin too.
Report anything suspicious.
Cheon Seo Jin and Oh Yoon Hee.
I'm sure there's something
going on between the two.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Is that it? "I'm sorry"?
Where did it go wrong?
How did Park Young Ran
turn into Oh Yoon Hee?
Who is the woman I met?
The broker has disappeared.
I have nothing to say.
What is Oh Yoon Hee thinking?
How much does she know?
What are you making?
You startled me.
This is against our contract.
- Go have a seat.
- Okay.
You didn't have to prepare so much.
This is enough for breakfast.
I just prepared what I want.
What are you doing today?
You're not allowed to ask
questions like that, remember?
I'm pretty busy.
That looks good. Can I try?
No. It's mine.
You're so petty. Let me try.
- No.
- Let me just try a little.
Okay, just a little.
Here.
This is so good.
(Cheong A Arts High School)
Is Seok Hoon seeing a girl?
- What?
- He came back very late...
on his motorbike last night.
And he had two helmets.
- Could it be Bae Ro Na?
- Bae Ro Na?
Does that make sense to you?
He was crazy for her.
Now that her mom has been acquitted,
what's stopping him?
He never liked her.
He was just fooling around.
If Bae Ro Na comes back
and bothers my brother again,
I won't sit back.
That's not going to happen.
She's not in Korea. Her mom said so.
She's still in the US.
Are you sure? She's not back yet?
Yes, I'm sure.
Thanks for the useful information.
You sure know everything
about your best friend.
That's not it.
I just happened to hear...
Don't come to our study group
meeting later.
A turncoat like you creeps me out.
Give me my backpack.
People will think
I made you carry it.
Stop pretending to be nice.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
- You look gorgeous.
- Thank you.
- I loved your concert.
- Can we take a picture together?
Of course. Here you go.
Here you go. Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Hello, what's your name?
It's Oh Yoon Hee.
What are you doing here?
I want your autograph too.
(Oh...)
This is for you.
Open it.
(Non-Disclosure Agreement)
(Cheon Seo Jin, Park Young Ran)
It seems like you've forgotten
our agreement.
Don't worry. I'll keep my word.
Thanks for your autograph.
I'll treasure it.
You're being more and more
recognized overseas as well.
Are you planning on any tours?
I feel like I still have a lot
to do in this country.
I'm going to take my time
and think about it.
Many people are complimenting
that you sang...
your first piece in perfect pitch
like an instrument.
When will the live album
be released?
I can't wait to listen to it.
Well...
Can't you sing it for us now?
"Una Voce Poco Fa".
That piece was absolutely beautiful.
Can we hear it?
Please sing for us.
- Please.
- We'd love to hear it.
Please.
I'm sorry. I haven't fully recovered
my voice yet.
I can't let Oh Yoon Hee
keep pushing me around.
Find something on her.
Search her house,
put a tail on her, or whatever.
I want something that can
back her into a corner.
Why don't you postpone
the alumni reunion tonight?
You don't seem so well.
It was going to be my treat to thank
them for coming to my concert.
Hi, it's me.
I'm so sorry.
I can't make it tonight
because I'm not feeling well.
I'll talk to the chef
so you can dine without me.
What are you talking about?
Why would she show up there?
We'll let you know as soon
as the new product is released.
Chairman Joo.
You may leave.
Hello, I'm assemblyman
Lee Kyu Jin of Gangnam.
I'm assemblyman
Considering their reaction,
I guess they don't live in Gangnam.
Anyway, with your
furniture business taking off,
you seem very busy.
I was just about to leave.
What brings you here?
Gosh, that chair looks amazing.
I was nearby and thought
I should stop by.
Partly that,
and my fingers were getting itchy.
Aren't you tired of playing
with me alone?
Also, I win your money
all the time anyway.
I feel bad.
That's why I'm thinking of
bringing in a pushover today.
Do you know anyone?
Thanks for letting me join.
We haven't done this in a while.
Now it feels real
that I'm back in Hera Club.
By the way, you brought
a beautiful lady with you.
Oh, I ran into her
when I just left home,
and she wanted to tag along.
To make sure the game is fair,
I'll be your dealer today.
Is it okay if we raise the stakes?
No limit.
- Sure.
- Of course.
Dr. Ha.
Ten more.
Mr. Lee, are you taking
all my money away?
If you're scared, quit.
- Call.
Oh, my.
- Gosh.
- What's wrong?
I'm out.
- Do you want to continue?
- Why not?
Dr. Ha, you've become quite bold
since you started your business.
This is the first round,
and I admire your spirit,
but too bad.
Flush.
Sorry, I win.
My cards are better.
- That was amazing.
- You're right.
- It's delicious.
- Look at you!
- I thought you couldn't make it.
- Welcome.
I was sad because I thought
we wouldn't be able to see you.
Did you catch a cold?
I guess I overworked myself.
I feel better now that I've taken
some medicine.
The seat is taken.
By who?
Hey.
You're late.
I can join you guys, right?
I know I wasn't invited,
but I wanted to come
to congratulate you.
This is...
the Seoul University of Music
alumni reunion.
Isn't it a little uncomfortable
for you?
Come on. Don't say that.
Yoon Hee is also a Cheong A
Arts High School alumni.
Apparently, she went to watch
your performance last night too.
She deserves to be here, no?
- Of course.
- Have a seat.
- Nice of you to join us.
- Come here.
- Cheers.
- All right.
I was surprised by Seo Jin's singing
last night.
It was the best.
Yoon Hee was better in school.
You remember
the Cheong A Art Festival, right?
I got goosebumps...
because I was reminded
of Yoon Hee last night.
You too?
When Seo Jin hit the high F,
I thought it sounded
just like Yoon Hee.
Had it not been for that incident,
Yoon Hee would've certainly made it
to Seoul University of Music.
She was the top-class
at Cheong A Arts School,
and won the grand prize
at every competition.
That's all history.
I don't even sing anymore.
Seo Jin, you really aren't
feeling well.
You're not even drinking.
Are you okay?
Right. You all know too, right?
The Hera Place incident.
Yoon Hee had quite the life
in the last few years.
From murder charges to running away.
It's nice to see you be free...
at last.
Why are you bringing that up now?
Why? Does it make you uncomfortable?
You joined us because you're fine
with all of that now, right?
You're right.
I was falsely accused,
but I've been proven innocent.
I'm as happy as can be now.
I'm a little shy to say,
but I got married again.
- Really?
- No way!
- To who?
- When?
- Girl!
What does your husband do?
He's a businessman.
You wouldn't know him
even if I said the company's name.
It's called JohnBIO.
I know that company!
It's a huge hit in the US.
- Really?
- No way.
What business is it?
I'm going to the bathroom.
Stop looking him up.
I'm embarrassed.
I can't believe you got remarried.
This man is Seo Jin's ex-husband.
He was a neurosurgeon
at Cheong A Medical Center.
- You're right.
- Really?
Did you get remarried
to Seo Jin's ex-husband?
Yes, it just happened.
Oh Yoon Hee...
I'll kill you.
It's so good to see you.
Tell us the truth
since Seo Jin isn't here.
Back then,
did you really
stab yourself in the neck?
It was just Seo Jin and you
in the room.
We couldn't say anything back then,
but nobody believed it.
We all thought that Seo Jin
stabbed you.
Tell us already.
What's the truth?
Come on.
Ask Seo Jin yourself.
She knows the truth too.
- Come on!
- Just tell us.
- Why can't you tell us?
- Tell us.
You're hilarious.
Come on.
Mr. Ha, what a game.
Unbelievable.
Is it not Player Joo's day today?
Would you please shut it?
I can't focus!
He's taking the anger out on us.
I hear one's real personality
comes out when they lose money.
This proves that right.
Should we stop here?
You've lost almost all of it.
Who do you think you are,
just ending the game whenever?
Let's go big one last round.
Can you be all in?
If not,
we can stop here.
I don't mind.
All right, then.
You're so cool, Ha Yoon Chul!
Let's play one last round
with everything in.
Sure.
These four cards are
very important.
- I'm nervous.
- Same here.
Finding the right timing to die is
the key to poker,
just like in life,
you must die before
you're 50 to remarry.
(Kyu Jin's)
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
Is he drinking out somewhere again?
His wife is working her bones off...
to volunteer in his district
all day long,
but he's out there,
living his best life.
I can't believe he's an assemblyman.
That's why our country is like this.
It's hard to read their faces.
What was that?
- What a game!
- Oh, my.
Chairman Joo, I'm sorry.
It's four Aces.
No way.
Oh, my.
Mr. Ha, did you only play poker
when you were in the US?
You're like a hoodwinker now.
I just got lucky.
It's beginner's luck.
Chairman Joo, how much
have you lost today?
A million dollars?
Let's play again sometime.
I won't go easy on you next time.
Thanks.
"Go easy"?
I saw you use your full brain power.
Bye!
Mr. Ha, you have to treat us
big time.
No, not today. It's time
for my wife to come back.
Next time.
Just let me off this time.
Come on!
I can't sleep well...
if I drink just a little like this.
What's there to worry about?
You can drink with me.
Just us two?
What are you saying?
That's not fun.
Do you not remember things...
when you get drunk?
No, I remember everything just fine.
Then do you remember?
You and I recently, you know,
did things.
What? What are you saying?
Are you serious?
You were the one who started.
Why are you acting innocent?
Do you not remember or what?
What did I do?
Why do you keep saying that?
You remember now, don't you?
Oh, my.
What are you trying to do?
What are you plotting?
Are you trying to kill me
with anxiety?
Why are you so scared,
Cheon Seo Jin?
That's not like you.
Relax.
I haven't even started yet.
I know you're in a rush,
so you're just coming at me,
but you're so pathetic
that I feel bad.
The more you do this,
the more I'm itching to expose you.
You want me to expose you?
And tell the world that
your singing is fake?
That the one who made it
a successful performance was...
me, Oh Yoon Hee?
Tell me what you want.
Tell me exactly
what you want from me.
Retire.
- What?
- Retire.
You've stepped on others,
stole others' opportunities,
and got there by faking.
So, let that all go yourself.
Aren't you ashamed to be called...
the best soprano of the time?
I didn't get here by faking.
I tried with all my life
to get here.
But you got off on the wrong foot.
You cut my throat...
and crushed my dreams.
But you didn't get punished.
So, everything you have right now...
is fake.
Cancel all of your planned
performances.
Hold a press conference...
and tell the world
that you can't sing anymore.
Then, I'll keep it a secret...
that I was your shadow singer.
How does that sound?
It sounds like
a generous deal to me.
Singing is my life.
It was...
also my life.
Oh Yoon Hee!
How does this Saturday sound...
for the press conference?
That's the press conference day
for your opera.
There will be lots of domestic
and international reporters.
Won't that be a good day for it?
All right. Go as far as you'd like.
I won't beg you.
Don't you underestimate me.
I'm different from Su Ryeon.
You should go and think...
about how much you'll lose
and how your downfall will go.
Does your daughter know?
That you're going around,
being like this?
Didn't your daughter leave you...
because she's mortified
by this side of you?
And that's why you came back here
on your own, right?
Shouldn't you worry
about your daughter first?
My plan includes...
your daughter too.
Don't you lay a finger
on my daughter.
Not Eun Byeol!
Oh Yoon Hee!
How was the dinner tonight?
It was okay.
Would you like a cocktail
at the lounge?
I'm exhausted.
With the fan meet and interviews,
I'm completely beat.
Come on.
I'll take care of Oh Yoon Hee.
Hera Palace is mine
and I sell it to who I want.
I have that much power.
Don't bother her. Don't anger her!
What do you mean?
At least for a little while.
Just let her be.
What could it be?
What does Cheon Seo Jin have...
to be afraid of Oh Yoon Hee?
It's me, Joo Dan Tae. Can we meet?
Did something happen to Director?
That's what I'd like to ask.
Secretary Do,
what have you done
that things are looking this messy?
You've caused this big
of an accident,
and left Director to clean up
on her own?
Can you really call yourself
her manager after this?
I don't know what you're saying.
What happened with Oh Yoon Hee.
I've heard it all
from Director Cheon.
Until when were you planning
on hiding it from me?
If that broke out,
didn't you think that it'd break
her career?
She was threatened just now...
by Oh Yoon Hee.
If the woman I'm marrying is
going through this,
I should've been the first to know.
Why didn't you say anything?
Secretary Do!
It's all my fault.
When Director Cheon had
vocal cord nodules,
I should've made her cancel
her performance.
She obviously would've wanted
to go forward with it.
I must've been fooled by the broker.
I was very secretive when I looked
for the replacement singer,
and I had no idea
that Oh Yoon Hee could sing.
I checked over and over again,
but she completely masked
her identity.
I'm so sorry, Chairman.
You're saying,
Oh Yoon Hee sang...
for Cheon Seo Jin
at her performance?
This is amusing.
You didn't know?
You said you knew everything...
Did you...
It's time for you to choose now.
Will you join me now? Or...
will you get fired by Seo Jin...
for running your mouth recklessly?
What are you doing? You startled me.
Why are you here at this hour?
I was going to give you
a wake-up call,
but I wanted to see you sleeping.
How about breakfast?
Don't do that again.
I was tossing and turning all night
and barely fell asleep.
You're too irritable.
The concert went well,
and many good things are happening.
Do you have a concern
that I don't know about...
or something?
A concern? Of course, not.
I'll wash up and come out.
Have some coffee and wait for me.
Oh Yoon Hee.
She really is impressive.
If I can use her properly,
she'll be useful in taming Seo Jin.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
Can't you have breakfast
at your penthouse?
I'm a high school senior.
It hurts my studies
if I'm in a bad mood.
Please stop talking.
You're making me lose my appetite.
What?
You said I didn't need to try.
So I'm going to drop the act.
I hate doing things
that are inefficient.
I can't stand you.
I love this place.
I made lots of friends
at school today.
I have you with me...
and I'm getting used to the school.
I'm so happy, I could die.
Ro Na.
I need to tell you something.
What is it?
You're making me nervous.
Just spit it out. Stop scaring me.
I have to go...
to Korea.
Why?
I can't live happily with you...
like nothing happened.
I...
I feel like I can't breathe.
I feel so guilty toward Su Ryeon.
You didn't kill her.
So why do you feel guilty?
I don't understand.
Still, I have to go.
I know I shouldn't do this to you,
but I have to go.
No, Mom.
Just live here with me.
Let's forget everything
that happened in Korea.
I'll pray...
that Ms. Shim and her daughter
will meet...
and live happily together
in their next life.
So please, don't go.
I...
killed that girl.
What?
I did that to Min Seol A,
Su Ryeon's daughter.
I'm sorry.
Liar.
Why are you lying?
You would never.
I'll pay...
for what I did.
Did you do it on purpose?
Because of me?
To get me into Cheong A?
No. It was definitely not
on purpose.
How could you kill her...
and move into her home...
and be happy
that it went up in value?
You're a monster.
You're scary! You make me sick!
You give me chills!
I really didn't remember
anything at the time.
It's true, Ro Na. Please believe me.
Stop it!
You're saying you killed her.
You killed Min Seol A because of me!
You're saying my mom is a murderer!
No. It wasn't because of you.
It was definitely not
because of you.
This is all me.
You had nothing to do with it.
So please, don't blame yourself.
Why did you tell me?
You should've kept it
a secret forever.
What am I supposed to do?
How am I supposed to live
with this guilt?
Ro Na. Ro Na!
Don't forgive me.
Hate me and resent me forever.
Did you confess to your daughter...
that you killed Seol A?
This is the last favor
I'll ask of you.
Please make sure...
Ro Na never goes back to Korea.
If you do that...
I'll do anything you want.
Don't worry about Ro Na.
I'll keep her with me.
You can't come here, Ro Na.
Not until I destroy
those evil people.
Are you preparing
for the press conference?
Don't forget. It's this Saturday.
You crazy little...
Come in.
How have you been?
It's been two years now.
Why...
are you...
Re-enroll?
Did you just say "re-enroll"?
Yes. I came because I want
to re-enroll at Cheong A.
Sorry, but that's impossible.
There's no opening.
And I have no desire to go
out of our way to accept you.
Does that answer your question?
I knew you'd say that.
But you'll have to admit me.
Are you doing this...
because you think
you can rely on your mom?
- Oh my gosh. Gosh.
- Is it good?
You look the prettiest
when you're drinking soda.
Drink faster.
Seok Kyung.
Cut it out already.
Stay out of it, Seok Hoon.
She's drinking it voluntarily
because she's thirsty.
Stay out of it.
I said, cut it out.
Me?
I'm not the Min Hyuk
you used to know.
How dare you?
You guys haven't changed a bit.
Bae Ro Na?
Gosh, seriously.
Jenny, are you okay?
Hey, how dare you show up
at our school?
You guys haven't quit this yet?
How can you still be the same
after what happened?
What is she saying?
Guys, I think I broke my arm.
I broke my arm!
That hurts!
Bae Ro Na won first prize
at the Elizabeth Competition?
According to our school rules,
an international competition winner
is allowed to re-enroll.
This is hot news.
Isn't she the country's
youngest winner so far?
- I should ask the PR team to...
- Do you think...
I called you here
to ask you to do that?
Pardon?
I need the head of
the art department to step in.
While studying here,
Bae Ro Na got in a lot of trouble.
If she re-enroll,
she might distract the seniors.
Don't you think
she'll raise an issue?
The school rules clearly state that
she may re-enroll.
But we can't let Bae Ro Na
come back here.
Find a way.
Can't you do that much
as the head of the art department?
Hello, Ms. Ko.
An accident?
Where's Ro Na?
Don't tell me...
you're here as Ro Na's guardian.
Did you forget that
Eun Byeol goes to this school?
What if she sees you?
Stop picking a fight.
Just explain what happened.
I already told you everything
on the phone.
Ro Na kicked Min Hyuk
to the ground,
and Min Hyuk ended up in the ER.
Cheong A Medical Center, right?
I'll go there.
I'll call you when I know how he is.
Don't worry too much.
Make sure Ro Na is okay.
Was Ro Na really here?
Why?
You really don't know?
She came with a prize
from international competition,
asking to be re-admitted.
I thought you sent her.
She did?
Where is she now?
As you may guess,
because of this violent incident,
she won't be able
to re-enter the school.
Since she isn't our student, she
won't be disciplined by the school,
she's likely to be investigated
by the police.
Explain what happened
so I can understand.
Bae Ro Na popped out of nowhere
and kicked Min Hyuk.
Jenny threw up from the shock.
- You all saw that, right?
- Yes.
- I saw it.
- I saw it too.
She's extremely strong.
I didn't do that.
They're lying.
You guys were bullying Jenny.
Why are you leaving that out?
They were bullying Jenny?
But they're our school's
model students.
Jenny, you tell me.
Did they bully you?
No.
We were just fooling around.
Jenny, how could you...
Ro Na!
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you back here?
Why would you come back
to this horrible place?
I want to graduate.
I also want the Cheong A
Art Festival grand prize trophy.
I don't need any of that.
Go back right now.
I don't care about Seoul National
University, the grand prize,
or something even better.
I don't care. I mean it.
Do you think I sing because of you?
What?
I'm not trying to win
the grand prize because of you.
It's for me.
I'm doing it for myself.
I want to go back
to Cheong A Arts High School.
And I'm going to enter
Cheong A Art Festival.
I have to.
Why? Why do you have to?
No.
Please go back to the US, okay?
Haven't you been through enough?
Who knows what they'll do to you?
Are you scared that I'll be bullied?
You're always so selfish.
Now that you know I'm alive,
can I go?
Ro Na!
Do you think
this can put things right?
My boy broke his arm!
His iron arm!
How can Ro Na be so strong?
I am a cultured woman,
but no one can stop me
when it comes to my boy!
Anyway, how are you going
to take responsibility for this?
My mom is filing a suit.
She's so upset that
she's refusing to eat.
An assemblyman's son...
was bullied at school!
How can this be possible?
The doctor said
he doesn't need to wear a cast,
but you insisted on it.
We're neighbors.
Give us a little break.
Mr. Ha! I'm disappointed in you.
Just because you're successful
doesn't mean you can be shameless!
I'm not going to...
let this slide.
Let's deal with it legally.
We're not going to settle
or go easy on you.
Then again, she's
a murderer's daughter.
She's so used to violence.
Come on. Hit me too.
Don't talk that way
about my wife and daughter!
Since you've been an attorney,
you must know that...
what you just said
counts as defamation.
Say anything like that again,
I'll rip your mouth out.
Hey.
It's not like...
she's your first wife
and Ro Na is your real daughter.
Right.
This might be my chance.
Ro Na might be able to protect me.
Hello? Who...
Ro Na?
Ro Na, what are you doing here?
Your daughter showed up
out of nowhere...
and is begging me
to re-admit her to the school.
Get up. Get up right now!
I won't cause any trouble at school.
I promise.
If anything happens,
I'll pay for it.
So please let me come back.
I want to graduate from
Cheong A Arts High School.
I beg you.
What are you talking about?
- Why would you beg for that?
- Let go.
This is none of your business.
You used to be my student.
Seeing you beg so desperately,
I feel bad.
I'll do think about it.
On one condition.
Bring me a written promise
from your mom that...
she won't cause any trouble
and will cooperate with the school.
Otherwise, I can't trust her.
I can do that.
- I'll take care of it.
- Ro Na, how could you...
Fine. You may leave.
What are you doing?
Ro Na will not attend Cheong A.
I won't allow it.
I thought you'd be very grateful.
I'm surprised.
Why is that?
I don't want her to go.
Whether or not you want it,
as the director, I'll decide
according to school policy.
I don't want people to accuse me
of keeping your daughter out...
because of
my ill feelings toward you.
I'm an educator after all.
An educator?
You must be trying to cut a deal...
using Ro Na...
I think...
we should bury that now.
If you want Min Hyuk's issue
to be resolved favorably.
If word gets out that she assaulted
an assemblyman's son,
it'll be a stumbling block for her.
Is that what you want?
Even if you want her
to go back to school in the US,
you should make sure she
doesn't have a prior for assault.
You conniving witch.
Do you think you can make it
go away just like that?
What do you gain
by hurting my reputation?
Do you not care
if you destroy Ro Na's life...
just to get me?
If you do anything to her,
I will make you regret it.
That...
depends on you now.
Ro Na. Why are you doing this to me?
Please, go back to the US. Please.
Do you want me...
to hide somewhere
you can never find me?
Or must I expose you...
for what you did?
Ro Na.
Don't try to do anything for me
ever again.
I'll take care of myself.
Where are you going at this hour?
Ro Na. Please talk to me!
What do you mean?
Don't raise your voice at the table.
Why are you accepting Ro Na?
What are you thinking?
I don't want to go to
the same school with her!
You're the director.
Can't you stop something like that?
Are you whining because
you're scared of someone like her?
You're the top student right now.
I think it would be good for you
to have a pacemaker.
Is this...
about Cheong A Art Festival?
In case you lose to Ro Na?
That will never happen.
I won't lose to a loser like her.
That's right. Now, that's my girl.
It's a blessing...
to have a rival.
Discussion over, okay?
Finish eating.
I have plans.
This isn't about the stupid trophy!
She doesn't know anything.
You must be upset...
that Seok Hoon
will go back to Ro Na, aren't you?
Yes.
I'm so nervous.
Seok Hoon is the only one for me.
Do you want me to call him?
I got the sample questions
for the mock exam.
I have an important meeting,
so I'm still at the office.
I'll see you at the hotel.
I won't be late. How do you feel?
Not bad.
I'm excited
about spending time with you.
So am I.
I love you.
Okay... So this...
is proof that someone else sang
at Seo Jin's concert, correct?
I included messages
exchanged with the broker.
(Non-Disclosure Agreement)
You're a very good worker.
No wonder Seo Jin
trusts you so much.
May I assume our relationship
has become stronger through this?
This is where it ends between us.
If you demand more,
I'll have to tell Ms. Cheon.
Hearing you say that
makes me trust you more.
I won't take your calls anymore.
Where are you?
Hurry up. I want to see you.
Eun Byeol.
Eun Byeol?
Are you inside?
Are you here?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Why are you here?
(The Penthouse 2)
You deceived me
and met another man.
How long have you been
keeping secrets from me?
We have no legal obligations
to each other yet.
I wondered how you were doing.
Didn't you wonder about me?
I'm acting in order to get you back.
Shut it! Your mom is the one
who killed my mom.
You promised to protect Ro Na.
I'll do whatever it takes...
to get the Cheong A
Art Festival trophy.
You've got some nerve.
I may just kill your daughter
Seok Kyung.