Sub by kisscambodia
♪How to separate♪
♪Our entangled fate♪
♪Love doesn’t need any logical thinking♪
♪Instead of right pace♪
♪Baby You’re my only remedy♪
♪I’m willing to be
treated by you all my life♪
♪On my heart you knock knock knock♪
♪There comes your exclusive summons♪
♪Your eyes are engraved on my mind♪
♪I want you to belong to me♪
♪A sure and happy future♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
My Little Happiness
Episode 25
Cong Rong, you’ll marry me eventually.
Wen Shaoqing,
what’s your Wi-Fi password again?
42633.
Yes.
Cong Rong, you’ll marry me eventually.
You can stop typing.
It’s “yes”.
Cong Rong, you’ll marry me eventually.
Yes.
♪I’m with you♪
♪Standing under the tree♪
♪Making a promise of the future♪
♪Marching forward to happiness♪
♪Promise I’ll be by your side♪
♪I’m with you♪
Rong.
It’s Zhong Zhen.
♪I’m with you♪
Keep him knocking.
♪Let me stay with you♪
Let me open the door,
lest he thinks the wrong way.
Boss,
why are you here?
Where’s Rong?
She’s turned in.
So early?
What’s up?
Do you want me to awake her?
No, thanks.
I just get off
and bring her some nutrition.
Then drop by your home
to grab the exam materials.
Don’t you know the password?
Get it yourself.
Boss,
are you anxious?
Seems you’re going to...
To what?
Nothing.
I dare not guess what is on your mind.
Take good care of Rong.
See you.
Dr. Wen,
let me tell you,
there is no such saying as “wife” in law.
The correct title should be “spouse”.
In another word,
wife is not protected by law.
Well, I got it.
But my wife should be protected by me.
Hello,
what’s up?
Good news.
When your boyfriend and
the patient’s family
had an argument,
a car was stopping outside the restaurant
and its data recorder may record the site.
Really?
Got the plate number?
Yes.
It’s not a local car.
The owner is unknown.
Need to go to the DMV tomorrow.
Send the plate number to me.
I’ll handle it.
OK.
I’ll send to your mobile.
Can you handle it?
My hand is hurt
not foot.
Relax.
Leave it to me.
Please show me
your and your client’s ID cards,
Department of Motor Vehicles
the power of attorney,
your original lawyer license,
investigation letter or certificate.
Excuse me?
Will you say it again?
OK.
Wait a minute.
Voice Memo
Please show me your
New recording 2
and your client’s ID cards…
Unit Certificate
Shenzhen Yun Ji Hospital Wen Shaoqing
Investigation Letter
Application of Driving License
Hello.
Are you Mr. Gu, the owner of the car
with the tail number 092?
Yes.
Who’s that?
Here is the situation.
I’m a lawyer with Daren Law Firm.
Your data recorder
may capture critical evidence.
Could you...?
I’ve seen tons of your tricks.
Then, you’ll ask for my ATM PIN, right?
You got me wrong.
I’m not a swindler.
If you don’t believe me,
I could provide my valid certificates.
ID card or work permit.
Identity information can be fake.
I’m in Shanghai.
If what you said is true,
come to meet me in Shanghai tomorrow.
I’ll go abroad tomorrow night.
I can’t make it, tomorrow.
Schedule: A case of online loans
comes to trial. Submit materials to court.
Attend a meeting.
Meet with clients.
An ice cream and a cake.
Thank you.
Okay.
Here.
You treat me pizza
in return for my help?
Next time, it’s up to you.
I’m dying to see you
because I’m helpless.
What’s up?
I found the car owner.
But he’s in Shanghai,
and will go abroad tomorrow night.
To get the evidence,
I have to go to Shanghai.
But tomorrow, the case of online loans
comes to trial.
What a bad luck.
Here is a solution.
What?
You go to Shanghai
and I go to the court for you.
Can this be okay?
Why not?
I work on this case from A to Z.
Besides,
I’m a professional.
I do not doubt your ability.
Mr. Shangguan will not agree.
Cong Rong.
This is your first case.
We know how important it is to you.
But you should make clear one thing.
Would you like to give up the chance
for Wen Shaoqing?
Daren Law Firm
Where’s Cong Rong?
She’s gone to do checkup.
The case of online loans disputes
will be heard this afternoon.
Tell her to review
the case.
Mr. Shangguan,
as for the case,
I’ve communicated with Cong Rong.
I also work on this case from A to Z.
I know the case well.
So, I’ll replace Cong Rong to appear
in the court.
Besides,
we also talked to the clients.
They also agreed.
Nonsense.
How dare you regard such important work
as a trifling matter?
Where on earth has Cong Rong gone?
She went to Shanghai for evidence.
Cong Rong
You two are good friends.
Go call her back.
Hello,
what do you want for dinner?
I’ll hold a victory party for you.
I’m at the supermarket now.
Bad luck,
after the session is ended,
I’ll go to Shanghai with Mr. Shangguan.
I won’t come back until tomorrow.
It’s so sudden.
Mr. Shangguan
does not sympathize with you at all.
It’s me who insists on going to Shanghai
not Mr. Shangguan.
This is not the first time for me.
Relax.
OK.
Take good care of yourself.
Send me your flight number.
I’ll go to pick you up.
Mr. Shangguan
Why did you make the decision privately?
Why not discuss with me?
Do you still treat me as your senior?
I know you won’t agree
if I told you.
So you made the decision
before telling me.
Making statement is a hard-won
opportunity for interns.
You just gave it up with ease.
I’m sorry.
Mr. Shangguan.
During the case investigation,
I learned a lot.
You gave me step-by-step directions.
That’s the most precious for me.
So, even if I can’t make the statement,
I won’t feel sorry.
You give up your future
for Wen Shaoqing like that?
You and he
are two individuals.
As a newbie, you shall be a lawyer first.
Then,
you’re his girlfriend.
Mr. Shangguan.
I know what you did is for my good.
But you’re wrong for one thing.
I’m an individual.
But he
is the one I want to protect.
Sorry, Mr. Shangguan.
I let you down.
Shangguan Yi,
why are you here?
You know?
She gave up her first court appearance
in her career
just to collect evidence for you.
How could you be so incompetent?
What?
Don’t you know
what an important chance it is for her?
If I were you,
I won’t let her give up the chance for me.
Follow me.
Why are you...?
Where to go?
Stop it.
Return my luggage.
Why are you here?
Cong Rong.
Drop my case.
Let’s settle out of court.
What are you talking about?
I know the whole truth.
You gave up your first court appearance
just to collect evidence for me.
I’ll pay the money
no matter how much it is.
You mean it?
I mean it.
Why drop the lawsuit?
I don’t get it.
There is no need to waste time.
It isn’t worth it.
How could it be not worth it?
If you drop the lawsuit,
the people who are unaware of the truth
will think you’re in the wrong.
You admit mistakes.
You’re wrong.
I’m a doctor.
As long as I don’t feel ashamed
before patients
and have a clear conscience,
that’s enough for me.
Wen Shaoqing,
what’s wrong with you?
You ignore obvious matters
and pretend they don’t exist.
Even they’ve wronged you,
you’ll accept it?
It’s not that I accept it.
I could ignore it.
But I couldn’t.
What did you tell me
when we first met each other?
You said, a doctor has his own dignity.
As long as you did nothing wrong,
you’d not yield regardless of pressure.
You said, you studied diligently
and cherished your reputation
just to be a good doctor.
Even when you get old,
you’d try to treat patients.
Isn’t it your principle?
I will not let you be treated wrongly.
Even if I’m a stranger to you,
as long as you could get justice,
I would do it.
But I don’t want you to give up
your chance for me.
This is not why I’m with you.
I wouldn’t allow you to give up
your principle either,
even for me.
Agent
Relax.
Take it easy.
Mr. Shangguan,
I feel a little giddy.
Thank you, Mr. Shangguan.
Clerk
All rise.
Welcome Chief Judge to his seat.
Be seated.
This court is now in session.
Plaintiff lawyer,
is your claim consistent with
the written indictment?
Is there any change or supplement
to the facts and reasons?
It’s consistent with the indictment.
No change or supplement.
Now, the plaintiff presents evidence,
stating the name of evidence
and all supporting facts.
Your honorable Chief Judge and judges.
I, entrusted by the plaintiff of the case,
act as agent ad litem of Zhang, Li, Yang,
Zhao, Du and Jiang,
and attend the case trial by law.
Now, as for the focus of dispute,
I present the following opinions
based on facts.
You gave up your first court appearance
just to collect evidence for me.
It isn’t worth it.
I will not let you be treated wrongly.
Even if I’m a stranger to you,
as long as you could get justice,
I would do it.
The defendant, Shen,
from August to November 2018,
in the name of doing business together,
used ID card from Zhang,
and borrowed money from multiple lenders,
causing our client to owe
a huge amount of money.
The borrower registered and
uploaded certification materials
for loan application.
In November 2018,
Li submitted the loan application
for RMB 400,000 to the lender.
The lender issued the loan contract.
We claim against the defendant
for returning the principal and interest,
totaling RMB 400,000 to our client.
Futian District People’s Court
Dr. Wen.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Why are you here?
This is Cong Rong’s first case.
She can’t make the statement in person,
but she must like to
know the result immediately.
If Cong Rong could be here today,
she would be happier.
Because she’s worked hard for the case.
File cover
And me, Mr. Shangguan.
I also gave a lot to the case.
Yes.
You did a great job today.
I’m off.
Cong’s boyfriend is so considerate.
Mr. Shangguan,
shall we go to have a meal?
There’s a lot work to do.
Let’s go back.
Febuxostat: Won. Congratulations, Miss Cong
Yes.
My dad is critically ill,
while you two enjoy a big meal.
Calm down. Stop it.
He was fine in the morning
but is critically ill now.
Calm down.
Aren’t you a quack?
Stop it.
I’ll submit the evidence to the court.
The video is complete,
showing the whole process.
What would happen
if it’s ruled by the court?
Mr. Yao should know it clearly.
So we strongly disagree on
your claim.
We accept proper compensation.
But there’s no doubt that
your client caused harm to mine.
So we’re entitled to
hold you accountable.
Well, we’ll also reserve
the right to prosecute.
I met with you
not to apply pressure on you.
I sincerely hope we could make a deal.
Today’s situation is unexpected,
which is caused by momentary impulse
rather than grudge.
I understand you,
because I’ve been there.
I’ve never thought
I will look at
the occupation of doctor
from another angle.
I would like to tell you
in a responsible manner
there is no doctor in the world
who will give up treatment on a patient.
Till now,
the hospital’s trying to rescue the patient.
I hope you could calm down,
focus on doctors’ efforts
and show basic respect for doctors
before the identification result
comes out.
Shenzhen Yun Ji Hospital
She’s all right?
Yes.
Doctor Zhao made special instructions.
Do proper hand exercise.
Avoid lifting heavy stuff.
Avoid energetic exercise.
That’s all?
Oh, and
wish an early recovery.
Shut up about irrelevant words.
Boss,
Rong is all right now
but why do you look unhappy?
Do you?
How about I get hurt again?
No, I hate to get you hurt again.
So, are we gonna remove the plaster?
Yes.
Then, who’s gonna do it?
How about
me?
Be careful.
Be gentle.
Haven’t you recovered?
Wen Shaoqing
Be careful.
Slowly.
Be gentle.
Thank you,
Rong and Boss.
I’m off.
Where are you going?
Return it to me.
It’s useless for you.
And it’s not yours.
It’s removed from my arm.
It’s not yours, either.
Besides,
what do you use it for?
For the prosperity and stability
of the hospital.
Seems he’s weirder than before.
It’s easy to make him normal.
Wen Shaoqing
Wait a minute,
I go get the case report.
Zhong Zhen,
what are you doing?
I finally got the signature.
Neither earlier
nor a bit too late,
you’ve timed it, right?
You took away my plaster
just for showing off Wen’s signature.
Of course not.
It’s for selling.
Boss’s peripherals
are so popular in the group
that many bid high prices.
You really have a head for business.
Exactly.
I’m talent.
Zhong Zhen,
don’t you use nine-grid keyboard?
Yes, I do.
What’s up?
How could you not know
which word has the same input sequence
as the word of “talent”?
You’re free, right?
Follow me.
Talent=SB
Why are we here?
I don’t need new clothing.
Yes, you do.
As a professional lawyer,
you should have decent clothes.
But, I have no idea
when I have a chance to wear them.
To celebrate on your removal of plaster,
I need to buy something for you.
Hello.
Welcome to our shop.
We have many new arrivals.
Have a look.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Cong Rong.
These are all nice.
Yes, they are wonderful.
But…
Miss,
get some white skirts for us.
But, what?
But we need to wear gown at the court.
I’ll be happier
if you wear the clothes I bought.
Thank you.
All right.
Go and try them on.
What do you think?
Does it fit?
Nice.
What do you think?
Very nice.
It’s tight on the shoulders, I think.
Doesn’t it fit?
Yes, it fits well.
Miss,
package all these, please.
Come.
Let me carry some.
I’m afraid you’re tired.
How could you deprive me
of the pleasure?
Why does carrying my bags
become your pleasure?
It’s the pleasure for your boyfriend.
When I studied abroad,
I teamed with a girl
in a research,
and I had a problem with her
for some reason.
Her boyfriend apologized to me,
saying she was spoiled
and had no manners.
I’m envious.
You were envious of a spoiled girl?
No.
I was envious of her boyfriend.
He could spoil his girlfriend
that much.
I wondered
if I met you earlier,
I would spoil you
and would not be envious of others.
Well,
you’re touched by me.
Not at all.
Cong Rong is totally a different girl
after falling in love.
Mr. Shangguan,
look at them.
When will I meet my Mr. Right?
Mr. Shangguan,
do you admire them?
Get off.
I’m gonna park the car.
You asked for leave to remove the plaster
but in fact to go dating.
I just dropped by.
Envy me?
Not at all.
Actually, I win the case the first time
I went to the court.
Do you envy me?
Indeed, I do.
Xiong Jingjing,
thank you for helping me.
You’re so polite
that I could not get used to it.
I know.
We win the case
mainly because of you.
But don’t look down upon me.
I’ll score a success on my own next time.
Great.
I’ll wait and see.
If you lose…
No way.
If I lose, I’ll treat you to a big meal.
That’s the deal.
OK.
Let’s go.
In January 2019,
though I missed the first chance
to go to court,
I do not regret.
There’s probably a long way to go
to become a good lawyer
but I’m grateful
that I took a step forward.
Mr. Shangguan
Mr. Shangguan,
what’s up?
Good news for you.
The case is officially withdrawn.
Is it true?
Great.
Director Yan,
your punishment is canceled.
Really?
Then I can restore my work tomorrow.
If your colleagues know your return,
they’ll be over the moon.
No, they should be the other way around.
What about the hospital?
Based on the investigation result,
Yun Ji did nothing illegal.
Luckily, the patient regained
consciousness.
His family also came to
realize the truth.
That’s great.
It’s a good day.
When you come back,
we’ll throw you a welcome party.
Thank you, Director Yan.
Good News
Girlfriend
You knew it.
Of course.
I got the first-hand news.
Thank you,
Miss Cong.
You’re welcome,
Dr. Wen.
Let’s bring everyone together
and celebrate tonight.
OK.
Rong.
Hello, everyone.
What are we going to eat?
How about hot pot?
OK.
Fine with me.
To enjoy the big meal,
I’ll be a couple with Chengcheng.
So none of us are a third wheel.
Perfect.
Leave me alone.
Go to get someone else.
There are crowds of guys pursuing me.
You have no chance.
Let’s go.
Wait a minute.
There is another person.
Who?
Isn’t he the Boss’s uncle?
What brings you here?
You go back to work.
As your uncle,
I should come to celebrate it.
Uncle,
no matter why you are here,
in a world featuring
public display of affection,
we can team up to enjoy hot pot.
Sorry,
I have a teammate.
He’s pursuing me
but I haven’t said yes.
The world is so crazy.
Blood curd.
OK.
What kind?
Pig or ox?
Pig.
No.
Crab sticks for Chengcheng.
Beef and mutton.
I wanna...
Both beef and mutton.
Special beef.
OK.
Order me a...
How much should I order?
One for each.
People like you
are not clever.
Miss,
bring me a bear.
Wait a minute.
Sugar-coated haws for each.
Strawberry hawthorn.
Two dishes of thousand-layered tripe.
I noticed
there is no plain broth.
Hello, here is the bear.
Thank you.
Only the double-flavor hot pot
is available.
Tofu sheet slices.
Your perfect matching
leaves no space for me.
You need no space.
Lettuce, potato, yam, white gourd;
one dish for each.
Well.
Thank you.
Seems you’re recovered mentally.
I need to thank you for your tricks.
It’s you who fooled me.
Obviously, you’re anxious
and saw nothing.
Fortunately, adopting the right trick
is my strength.
So, you’re welcome.
What are you talking about?
I mean,
the four of us could play cards.
Four?
Four of us?
I haven’t said yes.
But you will soon.
Do you think I’m nobody?
I’ll go get sauce.
Sit down.
Let me do it.
I go get it as well.
Well, let me get one for you.
Uncle,
take this.
OK.
Thank you.
I can’t call you uncle anymore.
Chengcheng is a sister to me.
So you’re my brother.
Boss is also my brother.
Wen Rang.
Chili.
They you two will be brothers.
But that’s wrong.
Boss,
Wen Rang is your uncle,
so Chengcheng is your aunt-in-law.
Boss.
In this way,
you need to call me uncle.
If I call you like that,
do you have the gut to say “yes”?
You like him so much.
Why don’t you accept him?
Why do you keep him guessing?
It’s not true.
What is not true?
Our affection.
Although I like him,
I never expected him to like me.
You pursued him hardly
to be with him, didn’t you?
Well,
now you start to doubt your affection?
Do you think
he and I are cut from the same cloth?
Even now I still have no idea
why he chose me but not Jiang Yao.
Have you told what you thought to him?
You were not indecisive before.
Even a specialist needs to inquire
before making a diagnosis.
Well,
you need to make it clear
but not guessing without ground.
Thank you.
Try mine
to see which one is better.
What are you going to do?
Isn’t it for me?
No.
Seasoning platform is over there.
Shouldn’t you prepare the sauce
and bring it to me?
I don’t know your taste.
You’d better prepare it by yourself.
Pass me the oyster sauce.
It’s boiling.
It’s boiling. Come.
Enjoy it.
Try mine?
No need.
I didn’t prefer green onion.
Make way. I’ll go get the sauce.
Seems you’re not recovered totally.
That’s right.
Try the lettuce.
Since when, she didn’t eat green onion?
Not yet done.
Well,
take a look.
This is my favorite sauce.
Prepare it for me like this.
Stand up.
Not bad.
How to prepare it?
Shouldn’t you figure it out?
Do you expect me to tell you?
OK.
Anyway, I’m literate.
Cong Rong.
This beverage seems delicious.
Let me pour you some.
OK.
I want some too.
You can’t.
You have stomach trouble.
Drink tea.
You’ve finally finished.
They went away.
If you don’t come out,
I’ll go to find you.
Well,
my sauce recipe.
No ghost words.
Wen Rang,
is it true that you want to be with me?
Does it seem that I’m teasing you?
Yes, it does.
And I can’t feel your affection to me.
How could you feel it?
I’m in my 30s.
I have no idea what you like or dislike.
How about making a list for me,
like this one?
OK.
Well…
Tips for pursuing me. Keep them in mind.
Follow it strictly.
Let me have a look.
1. Everyday morning call.
2. A bunch of flowers every week.
3. At least 2hrs phone talks every day.
4. Shopping, dating and dining.
What are these?
So many rules.
What?
You don’t want to follow them?
Never mind.
Bye.
Wen Rang is indeed
a straight man.
Zhou Chengcheng will suffer greatly.
You don’t understand.
Wen Rang is a sly old fox.
He’s just playing dumb.
Maybe Zhou Chengcheng can’t
stop being teased.
Really?
Why do you like such thing?
Totally girlish.
Right.
I’m shallow.
I’m a shadow girl,
so stop liking me.
Stop following me.
No way.
Although it’s hard for me,
I can fulfill the last one.
What’s the last one?
Why don’t you follow the sequence?
I wrote so many.
Some more?
OK.
I mean these instructions.
How could you treat me like this?
A cunning fox.
Then, I’m off.
Wait, you’re pursuing me,
so won’t you send me home?
I haven’t accepted you.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Finally we hold hands♪
♪Intimacy is assurance
of your tenderness♪
♪The unforgettable smile♪
♪I want to remember it each second♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪