♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 24
I'll ask some people to tie her up
and send to your Eagle Division.
No need.
I'm fed up with this servant.
Just let her take care of Sher.
I think they make a perfect match.
Okay.
I'll do as you want.
What else do you want?
I'll give them to you.
I heard Monan pay a jar of
good wine as tribute for Kurultai.
I want to drink a cup of that wine.
The whole jar is here.
You can drink as you want.
Let's drink together.
More.
Good!
Men in our tribe should be as bold as you.
You'll show your heroic
posture at tomorrow's hunting.
I'm injured.
If I can't hunt as many
preys as last year tomorrow,
I choose to be absent.
Sun.
That doesn't sound like you.
I won enough cheers in today's battle.
Let's give Sher a chance to win cheers tomorrow.
My injury today is more serious than yours.
I'm afraid you want to see me lose face again.
Uncle Khan.
No matter how serious my injury is,
I want to win my honor back from Ashile Sun.
If he doesn't go hunting,
even if I win, so what?
Look at you two brothers.
As an old saying goes in Central Plains,
why does the destiny make
Zhou Yu confront Zhuge Liang?
Okay.
You can stay here and cure
your injury in tomorrow's hunting.
Thank you, Father Khan.
Thank you, Uncle Khan.
Then I shall leave now.
What are Ashile Sun and you conspiring?
You misunderstand me.
I simply don't want to
go back to Eagle Division.
You think I'll believe you?
He suddenly said he wouldn't go hunting.
This is not like him.
What do you want?
I don't care whether you believe me.
I refused Ashile Sun in front
of Great Khan, that's true.
About what he is thinking,
you can go and ask him.
How would I know?
I don't know what you are doing.
If you don't want to go with him,
why didn't you say that earlier?
You don't want to go with him.
But maybe Mimi would like to go with me.
So you're anxious now.
You don't need to feel regretful.
I can guarantee Mimi would
rather die than come back.
Sun.
I'm sorry.
You abandoned the chance
and trapped yourself here.
How do you want to save Luo Yi?
How do you know that?
I've promised to someone.
I can't tell you.
Who did you promise to?
Princess Yicheng?
You can't save Luo
Yi, neither can Yicheng.
Stop overestimating your ability, okay?
Why didn't you go hunting?
Sher has noticed there's
something wrong with you.
I don't care what your plan is.
I hope you won't hinder my action.
How's your injury?
I won't die.
Sun.
Thank you so much.
If you really want to thank me,
listen to me this time.
Okay?
Just go.
Don't get involved in it.
Go back to Eagle Division.
I want to cure my injury.
Tegin, how did you...
Arrange a few people to guard here.
What do you want to do?
No matter what happened in
Khan's tent, report to me immediately.
Especially, the
news about Luo Yi.
Yes, Tegin.
Make sure Sher knows I have
gone back to Eagle Division.
I understand.
Go!
Xiao Wu.
Let's set off early, so that
we can arrive at Luoyang early.
When we arrive there, I'll find
you a doctor to cure your disease.
I have no disease.
I just want to have more sleep.
Our food is running out.
It's okay.
We're getting closer to Luoyang.
Didn't you notice it?
The villagers in near villages
are fleeing from famine.
If we keep going, I'm afraid
we can't ask for food anymore.
Xiao Wu.
There is always a way out.
We can make it to Luoyang.
Xiao Wu.
I thought you have became thinner recently.
Well, I have flatulence.
I have no appetite these days.
You can eat the two pancakes for today.
Sister.
You really don't know how to lie.
How could you survive in this world?
Right, there's some way out.
I'm here.
I won't let you starve to death.
Khan.
The division leaders who will go
hunting are waiting for you outside.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Yes, Khan!
Young Khan.
Ashile Sun went back to cure his injury.
Until Great Khan led a
team to go hunting just now,
he hadn't been back.
Maybe you thought too much this time.
Think too much?
His action is always beyond my imagination.
Keep an eye on him.
Yes, sir.
Young Khan.
What's wrong?
Great Khan's ferghana horse ran out somehow.
The guards are catching it.
It happened after Great Khan has left?
Right.
Maybe it noticed Great Khan
left, so it wanted to go with him.
That's not right.
What a coincidence.
Tuluk, let's go.
Go to the servant camp and
check if Li Changge is there.
Where's that new-coming slave?
Siqin.
He worked with us this morning.
But he's gone later.
She's not here.
I knew she did it.
When did she disappear?
They said she worked with them in the morning.
Did she sneak when the guards didn't notice her?
It's not right.
What on earth happened?
What will they do when Great Khan is not here?
All soldiers are guarding...
Luo Yi.
Hurry up! Go to Luo Yi's prison.
Alir.
Why do you go to fetch water so early?
Khatun has just fetched water two days ago.
You used it up so soon?
Toruch.
Khatun.
Stand up.
Thank you, Khatun.
I don't like soda water in Khan's Tent.
So I always ask Alir to
fetch river water for me.
You know this.
I took a shower for yesterday's Kurultai.
So I used up all water.
Did I cause you any trouble?
Not at all.
If you want water, I
can just let Alir go.
Go ahead.
Well,
I heard you had a baby girl recently.
I made a pair of shoes for the baby.
When you are off-duty, come and fetch it.
And take some cheese back.
Hand it out to our brothers.
Thank you so much.
You are so generous.
You treat our brothers so nicely.
It's just a gift for you.
Just as we expected.
Li Changge.
If no one helps her, she
can't take that old man away.
Besides, that old man is seriously injured.
They can't go far.
Tuluk.
Ask the guards to search Luo
Yi now instead of the horse.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Ask a team of Wolf Division to come here.
What's wrong, Young Khan?
I think they haven't gone far.
Let's separate to chase them.
Yes, sir.
I didn't imagine I can escape there.
Even if I die today, I won't regret!
Come on.
Mr. Luo.
Your leg is bleeding again.
It's okay.
Alir.
Thank you for what you've done
for us regardless of the risk of life.
Madam.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Changge.
Did you contact Luo Shiba?
Last night, I played that ballad as you said.
Okay.
She should be around here.
Mr. Luo, I'll help you walk.
Okay.
Tegin.
You're right.
Luo Yi was gone.
All the guards in the capital went to chase him.
Where's Sher?
He's also chasing them.
Lead a team and follow me.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Is Luo Yi's escape related to you?
It wasn't.
But it is related to me now.
Sun.
You can't go.
He is Great Khan's most hated person.
He's also a General of Tang.
If you get involved in
this, it'll be hard to explain.
Wait.
Why is there blood?
Take her away.
Yes, sir.
Go!
Young Khan.
When Alir came back just now,
Uncle Lei found blood on her water cart.
Alir has already been arrested by them.
It's Alir?
Did mom...
Take Alir to my tent.
Don't let others know it.
Yes, sir.
Which way did Luo Yi escape?
They went east along the
populus euphratica forest.
Uncle Lei went to chase them along the track.
Follow me.
Let's stop them from the south.
Yes, sir!
Go!
Nice horse.
I spend my whole life on the battlefield.
I won't regret since I can tame the horse.
General Luo.
I'll give you a swift horse.
Okay.
Luo Shiba.
Changge.
What did I say just now?
Shiba, good girl.
Stand up.
Let's go.
Go!
What a huge team!
They think so much of me.
Go!
Shiba.
Take General Luo away.
I'll draw their attention.
Someone must have helped us in this rescue.
Yongning can't simulate me.
It's a bad idea.
Then I'll leave with Shiba.
After we've drawn them
away, we'll pick you up.
No need.
It seems to be the god's will.
I may die here today.
For Tang,
I'm a rebel.
For tribes, I'm an enemy that
should be killed hundreds of times.
Where can I escape to?
Maybe I'll die today.
I choose here to die.
You won't.
General.
No matter what happened, I'll save you.
How lucky I am!
I survived until today.
And I got a chance to atone.
Even if we die here today, we
won't leave you here and run away.
Luo Shiba, listen to my order.
From now on, Li Changge
will be your new master.
Why don't you kneel down to her?
You want to betray me order?
Stop.
General Luo, what are you doing?
Princess Yongning.
Luo Shiba will work for you from now on.
18 Cavalrymen of Yanyun
have risked their lives with me.
Now there's only Shiba left.
I watched her grow up.
Instead of master and servant,
we're more like father and daughter.
Today,
I'll entrust my daughter to you.
General.
You're still young.
Don't die for me.
I spend my whole life fighting.
If I can die on the battlefield
as I wish, I would be very happy.
Luo Shiba.
This is my last order for you.
Take Changge away.
General.
Go!
Stop them.
Chase them!
Go!
Stop.
I didn't imagine you have some ability.
You can take a disabled man
out
of the capital which is full of guards.
Shiba.
Your kung fu is better than mine.
Once you get the chance, just escape.
Escape?
No one can escape.
I want to catch you alive.
Catch them!
Go!
Stop.
They're my people.
I want to take them away.
Why do you think you're
qualified to talk to me like that?
Tegin Sun.
Calm down.
Sher.
You'll never know what fighting for guard is.
I like to destroy the
thing you like most.
I want you to have a taste of
beloved one being taken away.
You're just a coward that
doesn't want to grow up.
Say that again.
Coward!
You should understand.
It's something between us.
It has nothing to do with them.
Tegin Sun.
Wolf Division can let Li Changge go.
Let's take a step back, okay?
Let's go.
Young Khan, don't chase them.
Let me go!
Didn't you hear what that asshole said to me?
Calm down, Young Khan.
Maybe this time, we can inflict
heavy losses on Eagle Division.
In Great Khan's opinion, that servant is yours.
She let Luo Yi go.
It means she is a
spy that colludes with Eagle Division.
It also means she shot the arrow
at
Weihe River to save Li Shimin on purpose.
But now, this spy was
saved by Ashile Sun.
Only if you let her go,
you won't get involved in it.
And we can get Eagle Division involved.
You can't get a better bargain.
Bargain?
I don't want to take advantage of Ashile Sun.
He's my prey.
I want to win him.
I want all divisions to
admit I'm better than him.
Have you ever thought for Princess?
It's my duty to help you get
the kingship in all divisions.
As long as we can wipe out
Eagle Division for Princess,
I'll do whatever it takes.
Sun.
Stop.
Sun!
What do you want now?
Sher has seen Eagle Division pick me up.
What can we do then?
I'll consider about it.
You don't need to care about it.
Mu Jin?
Sun, I finally find you.
Why are you here?
You saved her?
Yes.
A letter delivered by the pigeon.
Have a look.
What happened?
Take her away.
Don't ask so much.
No.
If I leave, what about you?
It's my own business.
You don't need to care about it.
But if I leave now, everyone
has seen you save me,
how would you explain it?
One should answer for what he did.
I won't leave like this.
If I leave, people in Eagle
Division will... Shut up!
Who do you think you are?
What do you think you can do?
You never belong to here.
No matter what happened in Eagle
Division,
it's none of your business!
Ashile Sun.
Don't you think you can
solve everything by yourself.
If you know things would go
like this, why would you save him?
Did you save Luo Yi?
What did I tell you?
Now Luo Yi died, and you
sacrificed Eagle Division and yourself!
Li Changge.
This is the result of your self-approbation.
I won't leave now.
You have caused me enough trouble.
From now on,
you have nothing to do with Eagle Division.
Go back to Central Plain.
Go away!
♫ The heart gradually
responds, gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
Mu Jin!
Ask your soldiers to tie her
up and throw her to the border.
I...
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
- Counsellor.
- No need.
I can leave on my own.
♫ The longing flows. ♫
Go!
♫ Which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
Didn't you hear what I said?
Follow her and send her back to Central Plain!
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
Go!
♫ Layer after layer, it turns into eternity. ♫
Shiba, just go.
Stand up.
No matter what General
Luo said, it won't work.
You don't need to regard
me as your master. You...
Yanyun Cavalrymen's rule,
after following one master,
we'll die rather than betray.
You can talk?
I can.
Then why didn't you talk before?
Because it's not necessary.
In all,
you don't need to regard
anyone as your master now.
You can leave now.
Leave?
Where can I go?
You can go wherever you want.
Do whatever you want to do.
You're free now.
No one can restrain you now.
Free?
Go!
Why are you here?
Are you afraid I won't leave?
According to Sun,
he is afraid of this.
Did you see the letter?
What?
Where did you get that letter?
It's from Khan's tent.
There's some pigeon blood on it.
It means it's urgent.
I didn't see the letter.
But there's something in it.
I saw it.
It's a pair of earrings.
Earrings?
Is any woman related to Sun in Khan's tent?
His mom!
His mom?
Isn't he an orphan?
She's his foster mother, called Alir.
If Alir didn't pick him and bring
him up when he was young,
he would have died.
For all these years,
Great Khan has been
asking Alir to work in his tent.
He wants Sun to be loyal to him.
No wonder Sun listens to Great Khan.
It's because of Alir.
Where're you going?
Mu Jin.
This is a trap.
If Sun goes back alone,
he'll be dangerous.
Now something must happen to Alir as well.
Just go!
Why are you here?
You said it.
I can go wherever I want.
I want to save Alir.
Call Eagle Division.
If we can't save her, we can just grab her.
Sher!
You're finally here.
Sher.
It's just something between us.
Don't let innocent people get involved.
Okay.
As long as you kneel down and apologize to me,
maybe I won't kill her.
Sher, how dare you!
Of course I dare.
Now her life is depending on you.
Kneel or not, make your choice.
It seems you need some help.
You threaten me with a woman.
Sher.
You're a coward!
You!
If you're a real man,
come and fight with me.
Don't let me look down on you!
Tegin Sun.
A wise man submits to fate.
You're not qualified to
negotiate with Young Khan now.
Kneel or not?
Let my mom go.
Since you have kneeled down,
what about having a kowtow?
Entertain us.
What?
Your dignity is more
important than your mom's life?
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad