♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 23
Stop!
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
I newly joined the Battalion of Slaves.
And I happened to pass by.
Passing by?
What about the guards on the ground?
I have no idea.
When I passed by,
they have been sleeping.
What a glib tongue.
If you don't tell the
truth, I'll cut your tongue.
I...
Aunt Alir, why are you here?
He is a slave from Khatun's tent?
Aunt Alir, thankfully
you're here in time.
Otherwise he won't be fine.
By the way, I didn't
do anything to him.
Please let Khatun forgive us.
Don't wander around anymore.
Get up!
What's wrong with you?
Please forgive us, General.
We're too tired for night shift.
Somehow we fell asleep.
Such an important prisoner.
How dare you fall asleep?
Guards here. Take them away.
Yes.
General!
It won't happen anymore.
Send more people guard here day and night.
General!
Yes.
Greetings to Khatun.
We're both women from Central Plains.
I prefer to be called Princess Yicheng.
How did Princess know...
How did I know that you're a woman?
People here might think we all look similar.
I used to be like you,
loving wearing men's clothes.
How can't I know it?
Good insight, Princess.
Alir, fetch some medicine
and food to this...
I still don't know how to call you.
I'm Li Changge.
Do it.
Why do you want to save General Luo?
You misunderstood, Princess.
I'm new in the capital and I got lost.
That's why I went to the prison by mistake.
No need to hoke me with these lies.
If I wanted to do harm to you,
I wouldn't have let Alir
take the risk saving you.
Princess wants to know why
I'd like to save General Luo.
But I wonder why Princess saved me.
You must have suffered a lot.
Otherwise such a young girl
like you wouldn't be so alert.
But if you want to survive here,
it's good to be wary.
I helped you, because
I don't want to see
you dying here with General Luo.
Princess is the daughter of one emperor of Sui.
You married here for Sui.
Though many years passed,
your reputation for righteousness
is still well known in Central Plains.
And people highly praise it.
Changge, Sui doesn't exist anymore.
Now we're just people from Central Plains.
Sorry for my slip of the tongue.
Princess.
General Luo has been fighting in
the battle
with my father for years.
He helped my whole family a lot.
I've respected General Luo since little.
And I take him as an elder of my family.
That's why I took the risk.
Your father worked for Luo Yi before?
Yes.
No wonder. I see.
When Sui still existed, General
has been staying in Zhuojun
and protecting the territory.
He's a loyal, brave and righteous hero.
I admire him.
But I can't do anything.
To protect you, I've
taken a huge risk.
Princess, I don't understand.
It's the first time that we meet.
Why are you so frank to me?
Because we two are so similar.
I also heard about what you did in Weishui.
If I guessed it correctly,
it's you that saved the emperor of Tang, right?
On behalf of people in Central Plains,
I have to kowtow to express my gratitude.
You protected Central Plains from wars.
Please get up, Princess.
Princess, that's too much.
In that case,
how about us thinking of a
way to get General Luo out?
That's an impossible task.
Khan's Tent is like a huge prison.
No one can escape.
But you're Khatun.
What you can do is surely
much more than what I can.
You don't understand.
Though I'm Khatun,
I'm only a woman they don't
believe from Central Plains.
Great Khan...
Never mind.
But...
We're both homeless people
wandering here in the poor northern region.
Changge, please try to survive.
Alir, put those things there.
I'm back.
I dare not go too far away,
so I just walked around.
Thankfully there are some dry wood.
What are you drawing?
Nothing.
I'm boring. Just draw it for fun.
Is this... your family?
You miss your parents, Xiao Wu?
No.
I don't even remember what they look like.
How can I miss them?
Then they must look like this.
So ugly.
Just like you now.
You're same.
I don't survive depending on my appearance.
But you do.
You're so ugly.
I'm afraid you can't get married in the future.
You're coughing again.
I'm not cold. Cover yourself.
You're my little brother.
You don't need to pretend
in front of your sister.
Understand?
Xiao Wu.
Missing someone isn't a humiliating thing.
I also miss my father very much.
Tell you a secret.
I even felt angry with him before.
Why?
Because he's always very busy.
He didn't even have time to meet me.
But now I can understand.
Though he's my own father,
he's more than my own father.
It's in famine everywhere now.
He must be working very hard.
Don't know whether he has a good rest or not.
Why doesn't he look for you?
He must have looked for me.
But it's such a big world.
How can he know where I am?
Therefore, as long as
we hold on together,
when we're in Luoyang, things will go well.
At that time, I'll take you to
Changan and meet my father.
Chang... Changan?
That's my hometown.
When we're in Changan, we won't
need to wander from place to place
or fight against anyone for food.
You can eat whatever you want.
And I'll teach you
literature, etiquette, music and poems.
If you really want to learn martial arts,
I'll find famous teachers
for you and teach you that.
If you like freedom,
I can take you to see
the beautiful scenery and
great mountains in Changan.
As long as we're in Luoyang,
things will be better.
I hope one day,
it'll be a peaceful and harmony world.
It's been long
since I saw someone from hometown.
Princess.
Do you miss your home?
I can't go back anymore.
But you still have the chance,
have the chance to go back to Central Plains,
to our hometown.
If it happens one day,
please look at it for me
whether it changes or not.
OK. I promise.
Kid. Don't take impulsive actions.
Being alive matters most.
Thank you.
You can go back. See you.
Why are you here?
Great Khan asked me to
accompany him in his tent.
I can't walk around at will.
I can only come out secretly to meet you.
Don't take the risk coming here anymore.
I'm fine.
Someone changed the dressing for you.
It's Princess Yicheng.
She also sent me some food and medicines.
Changge, in the capital,
don't trust anyone except me,
even though she's from Central Plains.
OK.
Kurultai is coming soon.
I'll try to get you out of here.
Sun. General Luo Yi is here.
Li Changge, are you crazy?
That's General Luo.
I can't just leave him here.
You want to get Luo Yi out.
Impossible.
I still have to take the risk.
I hope at that time,
you won't stop me.
Li Changge.
Please stay alive.
I have to go.
Great!
Who's that?
I can't believe you don't know her.
She's Lady Jinse.
Great Khan cherishes her most.
Really?
She's so pretty.
Great Khan.
How dare you!
My tent isn't a place that you
can come and go at your will.
I haven't been here for only three months.
And now I can't even enter it?
Great Khan is indeed fickle.
In Dingxiang, how is it going with
the orphans and widows of Sui?
Please be assured, Great Khan.
Empress Xiao and the little Prince of Sui
are now well-behaved after my 'guidance'.
They wouldn't dare cause any trouble.
Great Khan.
When Khan Shule picked up
Empress Xiao and little prince,
he promised to treat them well.
But now...
Now I'm Great Khan,
not Shule.
Are you trying to restrain me with Shule's rule?
I dare not do that.
However, Great Khan,
if you do it in this way,
I'm afraid you'll lose the
support of people in Dingxiang.
There are only tens of
thousand people in Dingxiang.
And they're all from Central Plains.
It doesn't matter whether I lose it or not.
I think you're worrying about
losing Shule's son's support.
No like that.
I haven't blamed Sher for what he did
during this expedition to the south.
I haven't looked into it.
On behalf of Sher, I have
to express my thankfulness.
I had better go,
so I won't disturb you, Great Khan.
Great Khan.
After this journey, I'm so tired.
Look, there's only one goblet.
Yicheng.
Haven't you heard Lady
Jinse saying that she's thirsty?
I've heard that.
Then come and serve her the wine.
Do you want me to serve?
Thank you, Khantun.
Why are you just standing there?
Look at her.
Useless!
You can't even serve the wine.
So useless.
You look so unpleasant again.
It was you that sent her to me.
Now you look like this.
Get out!
Yes, Great Khan. See you.
You're so pretty.
Khatun.
That's too offensive.
Khatun, are you okay?
Please don't mind.
You'll always be the only Khatun.
Sorry for what you saw, General Shixin.
I'm fine.
Go and get Changge here.
And don't get noticed by others.
Khatun.
Who hurt you?
Was that Great Khan?
I didn't ask you to come
here caring about my stuff.
How can Great Khan hurt you?
You're Khatun.
I'll help you to save General Luo.
Why?
I've had it enough.
I've had it enough staying here.
People only know I'm a princess of Sui.
And I marry here out of my willingness
for the righteousness and peace.
But no one knows what I've
been going through all these years.
Thirty years ago,
I got married with Khan Qimin.
When he died,
his son Khan Shibi married me.
Then it was Khan Shule.
At last it's Yanli.
I'm also a woman from Central Plains.
I've been receiving education since little.
But now I'm so disgraced like this.
I can't even meet my own son.
You have a son?
You've seen him.
Sher.
Sher?
But I can only be Yanli's Khatun,
not my son's mother.
Great Khan forced Sher to
swear that if he meets me secretly,
I'd be cursed by the God of
Sirius and I'd die immediately.
I didn't expect Sher's your son.
Changge.
Sher's a good boy.
Though he's a little
impatient, he won't harm you.
Listen,
Kurultai is a great festival here.
Leaders from all tribes will come.
Today Great Khan will host those aristocrats.
After Kurultai,
tomorrow morning,
Great Khan will go hunting with these leaders.
At that time...
Why were you in Khatun's tent?
I didn't really expect that.
You enchanted Ashile Sun and Mimi Guli.
Now you even enchanted Khatun.
You really seek by all
means to achieve your plan.
What are you trying to say?
You try in every way to get close to her.
What do you want?
Sher, she misses you very much.
You're not qualified to mention her.
She's living a hard life now.
Shut up!
You... You have no Adam's apple.
You're a woman!
Don't worry. I'm fine.
I'll return to Eagle Division safely.
That's why.
I was still wondering how Mimi
can fall in love with a man so soon
and why Ashile Sun cares about a man so much.
What do you want?
Now you're under my control.
If you don't want Ashile
Sun to see your dead body,
just do as what I tell you.
Khatun told me you're a good
boy and you won't hurt people.
Shut up.
What I do has nothing to do with her.
If Great Khan knew Ashile Sun brought a woman
who knows shooting arrows
and has set my Wolf Division up.
What would Great Khan do to Ashile Sun?
What do you want?
You have to do exactly as what I tell you.
Drink it.
Come here.
Open your mouth.
Let me fill this up.
Drink. Cheers.
Fill it up. Cheers.
Cheers.
Come. Drink it.
Fill it up.
Kurultai is a great festival here.
You're all invited here.
Allow me to toast to you.
Thank you, Great Khan.
Why hasn't Sher arrived?
Great Khan.
Young Khan must have been delayed by something.
I'll have a check.
I'm late.
I'm sorry for that, Uncle Khan.
You're so late.
Have a seat.
Why are you hiding?
Serve the wine for me.
One more.
Sher.
The slave beside you looks really pretty.
Uncle Khan,
she's just a slave from my tent.
She's nothing special.
Today I asked her to dress up
and liven things up here in Kurultai.
You're really in the mood.
But this salve... I think
she looks quiet familiar.
In our tent,
when did such a beauty join here?
Can't our pretty Khatun satisfy you, Khan?
What kind of beauty do you want?
Look at you, you're
not making any sense.
Was I wrong?
Khan can't be too greedy.
Khatun was the prettiest lady of Central Plains.
Khatun, am I right?
Enough.
You're not qualified to talk here.
Everyone, cheers.
You.
Go serve the wine for my brother Sun.
Can't you understand?
What do you think?
Don't you think it tastes better?
Father, I want to toast to
you and ask for an award.
What do you want, Sun?
Just go ahead.
Except for people from Khatun's
tent, I can give you anything.
Today is Kurultai.
I want to duel according to the custom.
I want to challenge Sher.
If I win,
give me the slave next to him as a reward.
You two were both taught by Khan since little.
In our Ashile Tribe,
you two's martial arts
are among the first-class.
If you two duel, that
must be spectacular.
Sher. Do you want to accept that?
Uncle Khan,
since Tegin Sun invited
me, how can I refuse?
But I also want some reward.
What do you want?
Since Ashile Sun wants the slave from my tent,
if I win the duel,
I want the female slave
called Mimi Guli in your tent.
Mimi.
Good!
You two duel for the beauty.
That's a much-told tale of our Ashile Tribe.
Do it!
I remember when you two were
little, you fought for a little wolf.
After so many years, you
two will fight for women.
You two are like the lions.
And you're the glory of Ashile Tribe.
Warriors always fight for the honor and belief.
Try your best!
Things happened years
before haven't been solved yet.
Good!
Give up now.
Otherwise you'd be disgraced.
That can't happen.
Do you know how she suffered at my place?
Enough!
Stop!
You are brothers!
Shut up!
Sher!
You lost!
Great!
Wonderful!
Bravo!
Great!
Bravo! Marvelous!
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
Great!
♫ There's always a moment ♫
Wonderful.
Father.
♫ Which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything ♫
She's yours now.
♫ Between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other ♫
Sher.
♫ In different time. ♫
Come with me.
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
Take Khatun back.
♫ Layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
Let's go.
Sher.
You're Khan Shule's son.
You're the real descendant
of the God of Sirius here.
But today on the Kurultai,
in front of all leaders,
you were defeated by Sun.
Do you want a man from
Central Plains to govern here?
Uncle Khan.
Great Khan.
I don't want to leave the capital.
Why?
I belong here, so I
want to follow my master.
I don't want to change to another master.
Have you heard that? Ashile Sun,
even a slave doesn't want to follow you.
Shut up.
You're too wordy as a loser.
Sun. I'll let people tie her up and
send her to your Eagle Division.
No need.
This female slave has made me sick.
Just let her stay with Sher.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad