Watch on kisskh.me
Official FilmyBRO movies site:
FilmyBRO.COM
[mysterious music]
[mysterious music continues]
[Yunxiang] Ladies and gentlemen,
if I were you, I'd buckle up.
It's gonna be a bumpy ride!
[wind gushing]
[man in Mandarin]
Some roads lead into the fire.
-Some roads lead into the sea.
-[giggles]
Some roads lead into the light.
-[metal squeaks]
-Some roads lead into a fight.
-[laughter in distance]
-Some roads lead into your heart.
-Some roads shake you.
-[chuckles]
Some roads take you…
-[crowd cheering]
-…to the start.
[engine revs]
[Yunxiang in English]
Everyone has an identity.
Depending on the time or place,
we all play our roles.
[racer screams]
[Yunxiang] Student, worker,
father, daughter, even hero.
[board chimes]
My name's Li Yunxiang.
And right now, I'm a racer.
Specifically a racer
who's about to become champion.
-[engine roars]
-[gasps, chuckles]
-Getting ahead of myself.
-[engine roars]
[in Mandarin] ♪ Each person finds
Their own place along the path ♪
♪ I'm still not the rider
Who has won your heart yet ♪
♪ My bike's roaring ♪
♪ The wind's soaring ♪
♪ Blow away all the numb indifference
In this troubled world ♪
♪ God knows if I am ♪
♪ How I should be yet ♪
♪ I know I just can't stand
The way you look at me ♪
♪ I risk my life finding myself
In chaos and speed ♪
♪ Only if I give it my all
Will I succeed ♪
[cheering]
[grunts]
[slow motion music]
[motorcycle clangs]
-[tires screeching]
-[grunts]
[tires thud]
[woman] Woo!
[all cheering]
[host] What a spectacular finish!
-All right!
-[crowd cheering]
Let's welcome
our new champion, Li Yunxiang!
-[host speaking indistinctly]
-[chuckles]
[coins clink]
-Thank you.
-[taps]
You almost messed it up. Good save, bro.
Li Yunxiang, sure you weren't distracted?
-Distracted? What do you know anyway?
-[silly mocking]
You're talking to the champion.
Honestly, I thought I was done for.
That last jump shouldn't even be possible.
Okay, big shot. You act tough,
but I know what's going on.
You just want to impress that girl,
even if it kills you.
[scoffs]
I wanted to win.
A champion has to be creative.
You like her. Just admit it.
-You should go talk to her.
-[grunts]
-Get off.
-What's the matter, champ? Are you scared?
-[tires screech]
-[engine clicks off]
GASOLINE
[clanks]
[sighs]
[scoffs]
I don't see what's so great about her.
In just a few years,
she'll be an old lady. Calling it now.
What? Don't be ridiculous.
Just be cool, okay?
[scoffs]
I'm cooler than you.
I hope you mess it up.
Hey, we meet again.
Hmm?
-Uh… So that was intense.
-[hair rustles]
-[exhales]
-[gas pump cranks]
That shortcut was smart.
[chuckles]
-You know, I still don't know your name.
-[gas pump clonks]
[chuckles]
-Your little girlfriend's getting upset.
-Uh…
-She's not… Wait--
-Catch you later.
-[revving]
-[Yunxiang] Uh, okay.
-I'm looking forward to it!
-[Kasha sighs]
That was pretty bad.
You're lucky you have me.
[sighs]
-[clicks]
-[engine starts]
-[Masked Man exclaims]
-[Kasha gasps]
-Ah, hey, kid, nice bike you got there.
-[mask clinks]
Can you modify mine
just like it? Huh? Huh?
-Why should I?
-[Masked Man laughs]
Whoa! Hey, hey, hey!
Don't go! I run this place!
I live up there!
Come hang out when you're free.
[Masked Man] Please mod my bike!
[daunting music]
THE NEW ORDER OF THE GODS
AROSE FROM CHAOS.
3,000 YEARS AGO, HAVOC REIGNED
AMONG GODS AND HUMANS.
THE GODS FOUGHT FOR SUPREMACY.
THE WORLD SETTLED
UNDER THE NEW CELESTIAL ORDER.
[fire roars]
ANOTHER ERA OF CHAOS
AND CONFLICT BEGAN.
IN DONGHAI CITY,
AN UNEASY TRUCE REIGNED.
DE, LI, SONG, AND SHUN,
FOUR CLANS RULED.
AMONG THEM,
DE CLAN WAS THE MOST POWERFUL.
IN RECENT YEARS,
DONGHAI HAD RUN OUT OF WATER.
[announcer] Fresh water
may cost more than gold.
But no price is too high for us
to help the citizens of Donghai.
-The De Clan is proud to supply water…
-[Tiger] Extra! Extra!
Water reserves at a ten-year low!
-The Anti-Smuggling Bureau…
-This is only half a bucket.
-Can I have some more?
-[Tiger yelling indistinctly]
-[man 1] Hey, I'll take one!
-[coin clinks]
[grunts]
Here's your paper!
Extra! Extra! Water shortage
accelerates at Donghai City!
-Here, kid, give me a paper.
-Ooh, here.
-[coin clinks]
-Thank you, sir!
Extra! Extra! Water shortage
accelerates in Donghai City!
-Extra--
-Tiger.
Do you think this water crisis
is a good chance to earn some extra money?
Hey, if I knew that,
I wouldn't be selling papers.
Get out of here.
The Anti-Smuggling Bureau cracks down--
[thuds]
-[gasps]
-[groans]
Watch where you're going.
This is a new dress.
Ms. San, you're looking pretty today.
-Maybe you'll catch the chairman's eye.
-[paper rustles]
-Talk about rags to riches.
-What do you mean rags?
-Do I look poor?
-No, of course not.
-[coin clinks]
-Thank you, Ms. San.
Extra! Extra! Water shortage
accelerates at Donghai City!
-[Mrs. Liu] Tiger, get me one.
-Here, catch!
-[grunts]
-Here.
-[Tiger] Extra! Extra!
-[gasps]
-Sorry, Mrs. Liu.
-Whoa.
[grunts]
-Mr. Cheng.
-Is that Six?
[Six] I hear you.
[children laughing]
-[exclaims, grunts]
-[kid] Hey, Six!
-Thank you!
-[Six] Watch where you kick that thing!
[water sloshing]
Six, there you are. Good timing.
-Bring this over too.
-[grunts]
No problem!
[grunts]
SPEEDY COURIERS
-[wrench creaking]
-[Six pants]
[indistinct chatter]
-Hey, Yunxiang, modding your bike?
-Yeah, adding a little something.
-[Liang] Six, give me a hand.
-Huh? Coming!
…I won't work for them.
-This, take it on the back.
-Outlaws only get away two ways.
They die or rat someone out.
I don't like either one.
Come on, looking for the clans
wouldn't be so bad.
You ever taken a good look at them?
I'm telling you, they're onto something.
How else did they get so rich, huh?
I'm just looking out for myself.
Who would choose to be a smuggler
if you could go straight?
What choice?
There's nothing for us with the clans.
-[Liang] Boss.
-We're smugglers.
-We've got no option but scamper out.
-That's right.
We gotta put food on the table,
take care of our families.
That's good enough.
[hard thump]
-Huh?
-Right.
Heh! I was just thinking out loud.
-Come, I have the goods.
-[clanks]
-[Six] Let's go, boys.
-Go to the border with Song.
-Okay.
-For the two of you.
Yunxiang, this is yours.
[taps]
[Smuggler Boss] They're cracking down.
-Be careful.
-Hmm. I will.
[engine rumbles]
[man] Hey, I paid for a dozen,
and there are only ten in here.
And look at this…
[indistinct chatter]
[Yunxiang] I've never been
to another city before.
Don't have to.
All cities are the same.
It's two sorts of people
living in two sorts of places.
In one place,
the trees and grass are so green
that it's like every leaf
was soaked in water.
[clinks]
But in the other place…
DE DRINKING WATER
-Hey, water!
-Water!
Give me that! Give me that!
[gloomy music]
Spare some change. Do a good deed.
-There's no more water today. Go home.
-But, sir, I have a water coin.
Can I have some?
-Look, no more.
-[taps]
-[gate clanks]
-[lock clanking]
-Come back tomorrow.
-[coin clinks]
[Yunxiang] It shouldn't be like this.
But it's always been this way.
[dark music]
I still believe
that things can be different.
[in Mandarin]
♪ Same air ♪
-♪ Different fates ♪
-[calling]
♪ Begin to feel ♪
♪ Don't live in this kind of world ♪
[clicks off]
DE WATER INDUSTRY
♪ Starting today ♪
-♪ We live in this kind of world ♪
-[dogs barking]
[barking continues]
NO ENTRY
[guard] Over there!
[engine roars]
[lever clanks]
[alarm blaring]
[zooms]
♪ Be who you are ♪
-[creaks]
-[glass shatters]
-[sobs]
-[water gushes]
-[people clamor]
-Water!
-Whoo! Water! Hurry! Get some more!
-[people clamor]
[water gushing]
[thuds]
[grunts]
Yunxiang, how did it go yesterday?
-They tightened the patrols.
-[smuggler 1]We can't keep doing this.
[Liang] This work keeps getting riskier.
It's starting to make me think, you know,
another job might be easier.
-Too bad. You don't have a choice.
-[smuggler 2] Where do I put it?
-[kitten meows]
-[smuggler 3] Remember the stack…
Huh? There's a kitten!
Huh?
[Smuggler Boss]
Six, where did it come from?
I don't know who brought this,
but there's a delivery address.
We should make an announcement,
remind everyone
we're just a fake courier service.
[Liang] We smuggle goods.
But what are we, the post office?
-[Six] We can't do that.
-I'll deliver it.
[meows]
-[engine roars]
-[tires screech]
[Smuggler Boss]
I think someone didn't want this kitten,
so they gave a fake address
and just threw it away.
Handle it, okay?
Hmm.
-[deep sigh]
-[cage clanging]
-Fake address.
-[meows]
[clinks]
Okay. Go on.
-[meows]
-See that? You don't need an owner.
No one to boss you around, okay?
-[meows]
-Mm-hm.
[sighs]
It's a big world.
You'll learn to be fine on your own.
[exhales deeply]
-[kitten meows]
-Hmm?
[meows]
Enough. Get out of here.
[kitten meows]
[emotional music]
-[meows]
-[Yunxiang sighs]
[chuckles]
I guess sending a kitten
out into the world alone
is a bit harsh, huh?
PALACE OF HAPPINESS
[match ignites]
[fire crackles]
[inhales, puffs]
PALACE OF HAPPINESS, NIGHTCLUB
-Hey, Ms. San.
-[exhales, chuckles]
[engine rumbles]
[light chuckle]
-[clicks off]
-[key clinks]
[Kasha singing in Mandarin]
♪ Such a big world ♪
♪ So many places ♪
♪ A free spirit like me ♪
♪ Could linger anywhere ♪
♪ Such a big world ♪
♪ So many young men ♪
♪ A free spirit like me ♪
♪ Could find love anywhere ♪
♪ There's a place ♪
♪ I cannot go ♪
♪ There's a young man ♪
♪ I can't even say hello to ♪
♪ That place is home ♪
♪ That man is you ♪
♪ But young man ♪
♪ What do you know? ♪
♪ Life and death go on ♪
♪ Flowers bloom and fade ♪
♪ But young man ♪
♪ Why are you hesitant? ♪
♪ Flowers will bloom again ♪
♪ Youth comes only once ♪
[jazz music plays]
[fingers snap]
-[cheers, applause]
-[woman in English] Great job.
[Kasha singing in Mandarin]
♪ But young man ♪
♪ Why are you hesitant? ♪
♪ What do you know? ♪
[kitten meows, purrs]
Yunxiang, what the heck
are you doing here?
-What's up, sis? I'm not allowed, huh?
-Don't touch the hair.
Thin crowd tonight, huh?
Someone busted up the water station.
They say that until they find him,
there won't be any water
for a few days, so--
[gasps]
Is that for me?
Huh? Oh, yeah, take it.
Oh, what a cute little guy!
How did you know I wanted a kitten?
[laughs]
-Are you smuggling again?
-[exhales]
-[Kasha] You…
-[kitten meows]
[Kasha] If Old Li finds out,
he'll be pissed.
Only I can call him that.
It's just to disrespect.
-[smooches]
-Speaking of Old Li,
why don't we have dinner
at his place tonight?
I thought that after
that big fight you had,
you didn't wanna see him again.
-Oh! Am I your excuse to go back?
-Cut it out!
-[Yunxiang] I'm driving. Sit still!
-What's in it for me, huh?
[foreboding music]
[Yaksa] The building is nearly ready.
Twenty stories higher
than anything else in the city.
The other clans won't like that.
They'll wanna build their own.
[water sprinkles]
They are far too busy
fighting one another.
-Not likely.
-[scoffs]
My father says to keep people
in their place,
you can't let them get too comfortable.
[Ao Bing] Full bellies
lead to free thinking.
Take Donghai's water shortage.
Shortage heightens need.
Control what people need,
then controlling people is easy.
[chuckles]
Your father knows what he's talking about.
He who commands the water
-commands all of Donghai.
-[man] Move these trucks!
[engine roars]
Hmm?
[tires screech]
[man] To the left! To the left!
What are you doing?
Hey, come on, over there!
That's a nice bike.
[meows]
That's a nice car.
[whispers]
Hey, his father runs the De Clan.
-Of course, he does.
-[gasps]
[meows]
-[taps]
-Hmm.
[henchman] Hey, kid, sell him the bike.
Name your price. He can afford it.
[engine roars]
-[scoffs]
-[bell ringing]
[squeaking]
Hey, Old Li! Miss me?
[exhales]
I came back.
Oh, Kasha,
you haven't visited here in ages.
Aren't I here now?
Brave girl calling him "Old Li."
Jinxiang, please you're not planning
to cook, are you?
-[both chuckle]
-Forget it. You boys have a good chat.
-I'll cook.
-Whoa! Hey, hey, hey!
Jinxiang, what brings you here?
So Anti-Smuggling Bureau
made another bust.
Dropped off the report to my boss.
So I was in the area.
How have you been lately?
-Courier job going well?
-[sighs]
-It's the same.
-Hey, five wrench.
Huh? Oh.
[Jinxiang] Hmm…
-[clanks]
-Hmm.
[announcer] Authorities continue
their search for the vandal
that struck Donghai's water system.
The damage has resulted
in widespread service interruption
-Oh, hey, enough with the bad news.
-[switch creaks]
[music playing on radio]
I wanna get my hands on that, that punk.
[thumps]
When I find him, I'll break both his legs.
[sighs]
Pour some for yourself.
-Let's drink. Here's to you, Dad.
-[clinks]
[exhales]
Despite everything, we do okay.
[Old Li] We're not rich,
but we're not poor either.
At least, every cent I have,
I made honorably.
-[thuds]
-[clacks]
[blows]
[sighs]
[munching]
-Careful, this thing's hot! Whoo!
-Oh! Here.
-Dad. Have some soup.
-[kitten meows]
[Jinxiang] Lucky for us,
the Anti-Smuggling Bureau still has water.
Otherwise, there would be
no dinner tonight.
[laughs]
-[grunts]
-[Jinxiang slurps]
-Oh, this soup is delicious.
-[sighs]
I'm glad we have the De Clan.
Really, we're in the best shape.
The areas under the other clans,
it's just chaos.
It's tough right now,
but it could always be worse.
Sure, the De Clan is strict,
but they're fair.
I'm not saying life is easy,
but we make out okay.
[clinks]
[slurps]
[gulps, exhales]
No, I'm not worried about you.
[loud munching]
Your job has honor, unlike certain others.
-[thumps]
-[kitten shrieks]
-[exhales]
-[light squeaking]
I'm full now.
[retreating footsteps]
[loud merry music]
[train bell clanging]
[train rumbles]
[sighs]
-[purrs]
-[chuckles]
-[taps]
-[grunts]
Old Li is just worried about you.
[Yunxiang] Worried?
-[purrs]
-[scratches]
Cats have it the best.
-No lectures for them.
-[Kasha grunts]
Spare me the pep talk.
[chuckles]
Just saying.
You have a dad and brother, at least.
-[heavy sigh]
-I wish my folks were still alive,
you know, to lecture me all they want.
[sighs]
I wouldn't even complain.
[Jinxiang] Kasha is right.
You know how Dad gets. Don't sweat it.
Hmm… You didn't hear this from me.
De Clan is cracking down on smuggling.
Just be careful with your work.
You know what I was thinking?
The Bureau could use a guy like you.
-See ya.
-Hey, you can't do it forever.
-[Jinxiang] Get out while you can.
-[Kasha] Catch you later, Jinxiang!
[engine rumbles]
[ominous music]
-We're being followed.
-[gasps]
-[alarm ringing]
-[tires screech]
[tires screech]
[engine rumbles]
[train whistles]
[train rumbles]
[snarls]
[lighter clicks]
You know, I like that bike.
You know, I like it too.
[chuckles]
When I like something, it belongs to me.
Well, not this time.
You'll have to take it.
[bike creaks]
-[engines revving]
-[Yunxiang] Hold on.
[engine revs]
-[loud thudding]
-[engine roars]
-[glass shatters]
-[gasps]
[thuds]
[engine revving]
[tense music]
[metal gate clangs]
[tires screech]
[gasps]
[metal rails clang]
[henchman groans]
[henchman screams]
[thrilling music]
[hard thudding]
-[tires screeching]
-[clock ticking]
-[gasps, grunts]
-[tires screech]
[glass shatters]
[loud clang]
[clonks]
[grunts]
-[scoffs]
-[mocking hum]
[snarls]
-[whooshes]
-[gasps]
[ominous music]
-[ice shards piercing]
-[groaning]
-[screams]
-[heavy thud]
[groaning]
-Kasha--
-[thumps]
What now, huh?
[grunting]
You should have listened the first time.
[thumping]
I said that when I want something,
it belongs to me.
[clonks]
[henchman] Sir.
[exhales]
[growls]
[grunts]
[energy humming]
-[ice pierces flesh]
-[thuds]
[Ao Bing spits]
[scoffs]
-[thumps]
-[grunts]
[motorbike clanks]
[upbeat music]
[seething]
[rock music]
[power yell]
[fire roars]
[groans]
[flesh hisses]
[fire roaring]
-Sir.
-Come on.
[angry breathing]
[mysterious music]
[Yunxiang groans]
[tires screech]
-[ice crackles]
-[cork squeaks]
[gulps]
[exhales, deep breathing]
-[Ao Bing groans]
-[flesh hisses]
[heartbeat intensifies]
[pained scream, groans]
-[yells]
-[glass shatters]
[Yaksa] Yes, Boss.
I think it's him.
Yes, I know.
It's been so many years.
[water trickling]
[glass clinks]
[foreboding music]
[Yaksa] That's right.
-A wall of flames.
-[bells tolling in distance]
[Ao Bing sighs]
-If it's really him…
-[metal clangs]
…then I'm afraid your son is in trouble.
[heartbeat intensifies]
[gasps, panting]
-[cart rattles]
-[nurse 1] I'm coming. Wait a second.
You, over there.
[Dr. Su] The patient should be stable now.
Observe him carefully.
-Dr. Su, her fever's down.
-Set up a consultation later.
-I'll find you.
-Dr. Su, please sign for the delivery.
-It's not much water. Don't waste it.
-Okay.
-[nurse 2] You, help me with this.
-[curtain rustles]
[groans]
It's you. What are you doing--
My name is Su Junzhu, I'm a doctor here.
How did I get here?
A strange man dropped you off last night.
I was on duty.
-[groans]
-Don't move.
-[grunts]
-[Dr. Su] You're badly hurt.
-What? It's healed?
-[groans]
[Dr. Su] Are you okay?
[water trickles]
[heartbeat thumping]
[groaning]
[pills rattle]
[yells]
[panting]
Kasha! Where's Kasha?
-[door opens]
-[Yunxiang panting]
[somber music]
-[sighs]
-[door creaks]
I'm truly sorry,
but we couldn't save her leg.
I'm afraid she's still not out of danger.
[sobbing]
CIJI HOSPITAL
DE GROUP
DONGHAI AUDIT
What are you doing up?
-Why do you look better?
-I am better.
How's Kasha?
-Kasha…
-[tires screech]
[engines revving]
The De Clan?
-[tires screech]
-[car doors open, close]
[daunting music]
[doorknob clanks]
[cane clangs]
[daunting music continues]
[cane clanging]
Hey, that's Mr. De.
Allow me to apologize for my son.
Youngsters can be so wild.
Please forgive him
for his foolish actions.
I know he offended you.
[Ao Guang]
We respectfully return your bike.
Along with a small token of our regret.
Kindly accept this apology
and let us move on.
[gasps]
Mr. De, this is too--
[fire crackles]
-[grunts]
-[Jinxiang] You--
You apologize?
Then bring your son's leg to me.
-[engine roars]
-[Jinxiang] Hey!
[nervous laughter]
Mr. De, I'm very sorry.
My younger brother, he has such a temper.
I'll… I'll go talk to him.
I'm gonna go right now.
[engine starts]
-[engine revs]
-[cane clangs]
Hmm…
[chuckles]
[Yaksa] Boss, is it really him?
[Ao Guang] Unless he's a mortal
who found power by some miracle,
I'm afraid that it really is him.
It happens the same way
in every reincarnation.
[Yaksa] But why?
[sighs]
The Will of Heaven.
There can be no other way.
It must play out like this in every cycle.
Before he masters his power, kill him.
[Ao Guang] Just as we've always done.
[Yaksa] The plan is already in place.
They move as we speak.
[engine roars]
What are you doing?
A man like Mr. De apologizes,
you accept it.
-After what they did to Kasha's leg?
-Hey!
-[horn honks]
-Listen.
The doctor told me over the phone.
With that box of gold,
Kasha will get the best treatment.
-You can set her up forever.
-[hard tapping]
You think we can afford that on our own?
-This is the way life is. Just accept it.
-I'll never accept it!
Do whatever you want,
but think about Kasha, okay?
How will she support herself after--
-[tires screech]
-[panicked yelling]
[ominous music]
[Yunxiang grunts]
[panicked yelling]
-[engine revs]
-[loud thud]
-Jinxiang, hop on!
-Wait, what?
-[whip cracks]
-[glass shatters]
[tense music]
-[Yunxiang] Jinxiang, quick!
-[gasps]
[rumbling]
-[Jinxiang shrieks]
-[crash]
[terrified yowl]
[whip cracks]
[both grunt]
[gasps]
CLIFF! DANGER!
The cliff!
-[engine revs]
-[terrified yowl]
[screams]
-[crash]
-[Jinxiang shouting]
-[wood clatters]
-[grunts]
[panting, coughs]
[ominous music]
-Who did you piss off now?
-Move!
-[thuds]
-[groans]
[engine whirs off]
[dreamy music]
[Yunxiang groaning]
-[woman giggling]
-[gasps]
-[titters]
-[grunting]
-[hisses, zaps]
-[groans]
-[metal clanks]
-[heavy footsteps]
[chuckles]
Take him out.
[chains rattle]
-[heart thumping]
-[power yell]
[clonks]
[wailing]
[screaming]
-[thuds]
-[moans]
[woman groaning]
[hisses]
[helmet clangs]
[grumbles, zapping]
[clanks]
[roars]
-[metal clinks]
-[gasps]
[yawns]
-[swish]
-[groans]
-[wind gusts]
-[Masked Man] And down!
[thuds]
-[metal whooshes]
-[Masked Man] Hoo!
[grunts]
[sighs]
[exhales]
I love the smell of grilled fish
in the morning.
[Masked Man sighs]
Who are they? Who are you?
-Nezha, you're always so, uh…
-[insect buzzing]
…forgetful.
What did you call me?
[laughs]
[Masked Man] We know each other, Nezha.
Huh?
Ah, you think my calling him "Nezha"
got his attention?
Hoo-hoo! He sure looks surprised.
[laughs]
[Masked Man] Later gator!
-[hurried footsteps]
-Doctor! Someone help!
-Hurry!
-[Dr. Su] Hurry! Take him to surgery!
[heart thumping]
[nurse] Make way! Make way!
[groans]
[yells]
-[heart thumping]
-[clangs]
[Yunxiang] Who are you?
I live here…
[screams, panting]
[boots clacking]
[ominous music]
[water burbles]
[cigar crunches]
[exhales]
[Ao Guang] It doesn't surprise me
their total defeat.
Father, please let me be the one
to defeat him for you.
[Ao Bing] I started this.
Let me finish it.
[Ao Guang chuckles]
-You say you can defeat him.
-[creaks]
[monocle clinks]
-[cigar hisses]
-[Ao Guang exhales]
[cane clangs]
[nervous breathing]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[coughing]
-[nervous breathing]
-Hmm…
[creaks]
[gulps]
[Ao Guang] Hmph.
[armor clanks]
Father, he hurt you too?
Yes, once long ago.
Me, Dragon King of the East Sea.
[ice cracking]
[Ao Guang] Even after 3,000 years,
I haven't fully recovered.
-[both plop]
-[water burbling]
[ominous music]
[Ao Guang] He is a terrible foe.
His power is incredible
and he shows no mercy.
He's killed gods and demons.
Men, women, children, he doesn't care.
He would kill his own father
without thinking.
His name is Nezha.
[engine revs]
[clonks, creaks]
[water gushing]
[monkeys mumbling]
[wheel creaking]
[hissing]
-[record player squeaks]
-[monkey shrieks]
[plops, hisses]
[squeaks]
[rustles]
[Masked Man]
Oh, look who the cat dragged in.
Why did you call me Nezha?
Oh, because that's who you are.
Oh, listen. When you were a kid,
did anyone tell you
about the story of Nezha
and the Dragon King?
Yeah, I heard that story.
Well, you are that Nezha.
Chaos-creating, sea-churning,
insufferably arrogant Nezha!
So, what's up, Nezha?
-[all gasp]
-[fire crackles]
[monkey whimpers]
-[groaning]
-[water splashing]
Hey, hey, hey, seriously.
You guys are wild camping a grill here.
Wait, what was I just saying?
-That I'm Nezha.
-[Masked Man] Hoo-hoo! Right.
With each reincarnation,
you get a new name and identity,
new parents, sibling, friends,
and, basically, play a few rounds
at the character casino.
You got a girlfriend? Huh?
Well, do you? Do you?
[crazy laughter]
Mr. De is the Dragon King of the East Sea.
His son, that little bastard,
is the Dragon King's Third Prince,
Ao Bing.
[Ao Bing grunts]
So in a past life, he killed me?
Your father used all his powers
to forge you a steel dragon spine
and bring you back to life.
[crackles]
[Yaksa] But the injury wiped away
all memories of your past life.
[corals clinking]
[Ao Guang] Three thousand years ago,
the four Dragon Kings agreed
to stop fighting one another.
We united, and forced Nezha
to kill himself for his crimes.
But even after his death,
a part of his soul escaped our trap
to be reincarnated again and again.
Everyone believes the Jing Clan
holds Nezha in their prison.
[Yaksa] But they hold nothing
but a wooden statue.
The real Nezha is still out there.
So for 3,000 years,
we've been guarding Donghai by ourselves.
If we suspect anyone
to be his reincarnation,
we make sure the man dies.
It's the only way to keep us safe.
-[lever cranks]
-[chimes]
-[whirs]
-[Masked Man] Oh! Ah!
It's my lucky day. Drink with me.
[laughs]
-[Masked Man mumbling]
-[chain rattles]
The fire that burst all around me
and these powers I have, that's all?
Well, that's your primordial spirit.
You are the reincarnation of Nezha, man!
[exclaims]
What you doing up there? Let's drink.
Wha--
[sighs]
Ah, Nezha always had
that terrible unrelenting fire.
Once it gets released, oh, boy, watch out!
[snickers]
Not even you can control it.
-[laughs]
-[fire crackles]
-[fire roars]
-[gasps]
Oh! See what I mean?
Oh! Full disclosure. Even I'm scared.
So if I'm Nezha, then who are you?
Me?
Oh, sorry, buddy,
I am not going to tell you that.
[wheezes]
[water burbles]
This reincarnation is especially powerful.
We cannot provoke him.
Without my revenge,
what kind of Dragon Prince am I?
[metal clanking]
-Quiet!
-[cane clangs]
-[crackles]
-[swishes]
[plops]
[grunting]
[corals clinking]
[shark wailing]
[metal clanks]
[crackles]
[sighs]
Now leave me.
I…
[grunts]
[retreating footsteps]
[Ao Guang sighs]
I don't have the Dragon Pearl.
I can't yet face him myself.
But in the meantime,
we hire someone who can.
-[sneezes]
-[bird chirping]
As you can see, the pillars
of heaven are collapsing.
-My powers…
-[Masked Man] In no time at all
-…uncontrollable?
-…the world will fall…
[scoffs]
We'll see about that.
[engine roars]
[birds chirping]
[foreboding music]
[clangs]
[bag thuds]
[Yaksa sighs]
[grunts excitedly]
-[thuds]
-[squeals]
-You want me to kill again?
-[cane clanks]
[Ao Guang] My old friend,
you've done excellent work before.
Don't act so surprised.
[grill squeaking]
I recognize this fish.
Oh, yeah? It's really tasty.
Go on. Have some.
You saw it all.
Ooh, yeah, I was passing by.
I couldn't help but notice.
He's just a kid.
[Masked Man] Why is he
so important to you, huh?
If you really want him dead,
there are plenty of assassins in Donghai
a lot cheaper than me.
[both laugh]
This boy is Nezha.
-[thumps]
-[pops, squeaks]
[sighs]
Ao Guang.
Sounds like you've got a problem, hmm?
[squealing]
You expect me to believe
you didn't know already.
Ooh, lots of other people have fire powers
like, uh… the Fire Imp, remember?
[gasps]
Wait, if the kid really is Nezha,
I don't stand a chance against him either.
-[gasps]
-[cash register chimes]
You conceal your identity
nearly as well as your powers.
[rustles]
[Yaksa] We trust you have plenty
of tricks up your sleeve.
Oh, impressive, Yaksa,
you know a lot of things.
But if you know so much, how come
Nezha defeat you in every lifetime?
We all have our roles to play.
Mine sometimes means to lose.
Yours is to disappear.
However, an enemy will knock
on your door one day,
so that even if you turn
yourself into a rat,
you won't be able to hide.
A rat?
Good idea! Hoo-hoo! A rat!
[mimicking rat squeaks]
[Ao Guang] I'm sure you know
that the Order of the Gods
has been falling apart.
Finally, a new order will arise
from the old one.
Very soon, the Chan and Jie clans
will be forced to resume
their battle to the death.
There won't be any clean hands this time.
-Then what hole will you crawl into?
-[clanks]
[taps]
[Ao Guang] Help me now,
and perhaps the Dragon Clan of East Sea
can help you later.
[chuckles]
Goodbye, old friend.
[ominous music]
[Yaksa] Do you think he'll do it?
He always comes around,
so long as the price is right.
Every monster has his price,
and our little friend is no different.
[Ao Guang] Be patient.
[wind chimes ringing]
[Dr. Su] This way. He's in here.
-[door slams]
-[gasps]
-I--
-Get out of here.
[sighs]
[bird squawks]
[exhales]
[metal clanks]
[sharp exhale]
[worried gasp]
[waves crashing]
[jacket rustles]
[wrench creaking]
-[sighs, gasps]
-[hisses]
-[Nezha] Father!
-Apologize!
-I won't let you!
-[Nezha's father] You're a monster!
[fire roars]
[gasps]
-[man 1] Fire!
-[Yunxiang grunting]
-[man 2] Hurry!
-[man 3] Help me out put out the fire!
[man 4] Over there too!
Fire! Left side! Fire!
-[woman 1] Where?
-[man 4] There! Right there!
[somber music]
Hey! Can you teach me?
[clinks]
[Yunxiang] Hey!
[Masked Man] No, I can't.
I thought you wanted
a motorcycle like mine.
I'll build you one.
[clinks]
All I want is a way to control the fire.
[thuds]
A bike even cooler than yours?
[chuckles]
You got it.
-[creaking]
-[sighs]
Okay, fine. However, I can't guarantee
the lesson will stick.
So let's get it straight.
Even if you fail,
I still get the motorcycle. Huh?
I'll learn.
[chuckles]
Okay.
[clanking]
You may have fire
in your primordial spirit.
[yelping]
But your body is just flesh and blood.
[Masked Man]
The fire inside you is too fierce.
So you will need iron and steel
to channel it out.
-[clanks]
-[Masked Man laughs]
And most importantly, to put it out.
What happens if I can't put it out?
Oh, if that happens,
the fire will burn your heart
and roast the skin off your body.
You'll be dead, ha,
until the next reincarnation.
[groans]
[Masked Man]
What you need is a suit of armor
to channel your internal fire.
-[blasts]
-[shrieks]
-[fire hisses]
-[yelps]
If you can master this True Fire,
you can even burn underwater.
Are you sure you know
what you're talking about?
[dramatic music]
[fire crackles]
[grunts, groans]
[rock music]
-[screams]
-[Masked Man] Maintain focus at all times.
Don't let your primordial spirit
control you.
[guffaws]
-[blasts]
-[groans]
[titters]
-[paper rustles]
-Huh?
[giggles]
[grunting]
Nope.
[screams]
-[groans]
-[splashes]
-[grunting]
-[clanking]
[crackling]
[whirring]
[squeaks]
[clanks]
What?
Oh, just looking!
[chuckles]
[rock music]
[zooms]
[metal swishes]
[clangs]
-[weapons clink]
-[engine revs]
[clangs]
[burbles]
[glass cracks]
You ready?
YUN
-[swishing]
-[fire blazes]
[Masked Man]Hmm…
Hm.
[clinks]
-[grunts]
-[spear clangs]
[groans, grunts]
-[challenging hum]
-[spear clangs]
[yells]
Woo-hoo!
[grunts]
[whimpers]
-[weapons clang]
-[swish]
[grunts]
-[Yunxiang grunts]
-[fire roars]
[clangs]
[panting]
[laughing]
-Oh, boy! That was fun!
-[laughs]
[guffaws]
[grunts]
Who are you, really?
I am the Six-Eared Macaque.
[grunts]
-The Six-Eared Macaque?
-[spear clangs]
In the story, the Six-Eared Macaque
was a trickster, not a good person.
You're the one to talk, huh?
Do you know how many crimes
you've committed, huh?
Troubles you've caused?
People you've killed?
How many friends and families
you've brought to ruin?
You are the bad person, Nezha.
What did you say?
[ominous music]
Ah, long time no see, Nezha.
[fire roars]
See? I forgot to, uh, mention your temper.
[chitters]
[focused exhale, inhales]
[grunt, sighs]
[cackling]
Why can't I do it again?
Well, you still haven't united
with Nezha's primordial spirit.
[grunts]
You can't just summon him when you want.
"Not united"?
Ha! Listen.
In this life, Nezha was reborn
as you, Li Yunxiang.
But he's been reborn many times before
and many times after.
He was Zhang Yunxiang, Zhao Yunxiang,
Wang Yunxiang, Sun Yunxiang.
But up until now,
none of Nezha's reincarnation
has been worthy of his name.
Some of them never even realize
that they were Nezha,
and died without knowing.
They were failures! Not Nezha enough.
[grunts]
Also, if you really want
to use Nezha's powers,
you have to get your Astras back.
"Astras"?
What are Astras?
Magic weapons, the Sky Ribbon
and Cosmic Ring.
[disgusted groan]
No offense,
but this armor is a pile of crap.
Good luck with that.
SPEEDY COURIERS
[ominous music]
Your father has made
the proper arrangements.
I'd listen to him if I were you.
We shouldn't make a move
until the time is right.
Why take any risks?
We must be patient.
You'll get your revenge.
That's not good enough.
I want my revenge now.
[Yaksa sighs]
My boy, if that is what you want,
let me try something.
This is not the first reincarnation
of Nezha to die by my hand.
Yunxiang, that's so cool.
-[Six] Let me see.
-What a show-off.
[Dr. Su] Li Yunxiang.
Doctor, why are you here?
I just came to let you know
your brother's doing well.
-I don't know.
-You should come visit.
-That's great! Thank you.
-That was all.
Actually, if you have the time,
I'd love a bike mod.
[chuckles]
If I do that, I'll never win another race.
Is that really such a problem?
[giggles]
-[indistinct chatter]
-Uh…
[gasps]
Dr. Su!
[spear whooshes]
-[screams]
-[grunts]
-[clanks]
[ominous music]
[thumps]
-[gunshot]
-[bullet ricochets]
[exhales]
-[gun clanks]
-[grunts]
[thwacking]
Yunxiang!
-[flesh rips]
-[screams]
[thuds]
[croaking]
[tongue slithers, gulps]
[snickers]
Six!
What now?
-[heavy thud]
-[clothes rip]
[grunts]
[gasps]
-[weapon swishes]
-[fire roars]
Ah! You think you're safe
under that pile of scrap iron?
-[croaks]
-[squelching]
[swishing]
This pile of scrap iron
will let me kill you!
[both grunt]
-[grunt]
-[gasps]
[sighs]
[croaks]
-[hard thwack]
-[groans]
[thuds]
-[spear clangs]
-[roars]
-[gasps]
[grunts]
[panicked grunts]
-[gasps]
-[disgusted exhale]
-[Yunxiang yells]
-[hard thud]
[fire crackles]
-[Yaksa yells]
-[grunts]
-[zapping]
[Yunxiang yells]
[thuds]
[Yaksa groaning]
[panting]
[steam hisses]
[Dr. Su] Li Yunxiang!
[exhales]
-[wind blows]
-[groaning]
Get out!
[clangs]
[henchmen grunting]
[bells tolling in distance]
You understand, Mr. De,
why I had to come to you?
[exhales]
I was just being naive.
I thought that by smuggling,
I'd be able to make something of myself.
[sighs]
[Liang] But what I really need
is a new master.
-[Ao Bing] Is that right?
-[Liang] I mean,
who does Li Yunxiang think he is?
He's a nobody trying to be a big shot.
He's got those powers. What do I get?
[grunts]
I don't have a job anymore.
Ooh!
[chuckles]
These are nice.
[ice cubes clink]
Hmm.
[giggles]
[sharp inhale]
You know what you have to do, right?
[Liang chuckles]
Come on, I'm a smart guy, hard worker.
I just need a little capital, you know.
Maybe if I had a rich dad,
we'd be the same.
[scoffs]
I have the money.
Will you live to see it?
[gasps]
Being a traitor doesn't bother you?
[chuckles]
What else is a successful man,
but a traitor who got away with it.
[chuckles]
[crunches]
-[clanks]
-[Liang] Wait and see.
Plus, you can never be sure.
Maybe I have secret powers too.
[ominous music]
[somber music]
[somber music continues]
Your dad is with your brother.
You should talk to him.
I can watch her.
[dramatic music]
[inhales, sighs]
[Old Li] There were
so many wars back then.
We didn't get far.
It wasn't long before your mom
got sick and died.
I carried a pole on my shoulder.
You were in the front basket,
and your younger brother was in the back.
The night was dark,
and the hill was steep,
and the baskets were heavy.
I tripped and rolled down the hill.
I was so scared.
I scrambled back to the baskets,
and I saw your brother was laughing.
He was… He was laughing with such joy.
[laughs]
He thought it was fun.
[sorrowful laughter]
[Old Li] The years have passed so quickly.
Your brother has been getting
into trouble since he was little.
[gasps]
I thought that when he grew up,
he'd learn his lesson
and get some sense for once.
But the troubles only grew bigger.
Now, even you…
[doorknob hisses]
[waves crashing]
[Yunxiang breathing heavily]
[Dr. Su] They're both out of danger now.
Don't worry.
Mm-hm.
[rustles]
I've wanted to be a doctor
since I was little.
I guess I thought
I could help a lot of people that way.
And I do help them.
I only understood later
that some people
can't be helped by a doctor.
But you can help them.
Me?
[scoffs]
I only cause trouble.
[Dr. Su] Don't blame yourself.
It wasn't you that hurt them.
[sighs]
It's all the same.
[exhales]
You know what?
[Dr. Su] The first time I saw you,
I knew you weren't like the others.
[sighs]
So cheer up.
The guy I saw earlier, that guy
looked like a hero in the making,
who is just discovering his power.
-[heavy footsteps]
-[gasps]
-Kasha!
-Kasha.
-You should be in bed.
-I'm fine.
I'm going for a walk.
[heavy footsteps]
[gasps]
[panting]
[grunting]
[exhales]
[metal leg thuds]
[panting]
[squeaking]
[sobbing]
[door squeaks]
[foreboding music]
[nervous exhale]
[clangs, squeaks]
[gasps]
Hey, what are you doing here?
[shushes]
It's okay, keep it down.
It's okay.
-Go back to sleep.
-[Six] Let me go!
-[gasps]
-Who's there?
-[muffled grunts]
-[bones crack]
[panicked breathing]
[yelps]
[suspenseful music]
[thuds, grunts]
-Help!
-[tanks clatter]
He's trying to kill me!
Help!
-[muffled whimper]
-[thwacks]
-[groans]
-[panting]
[yelps, thuds]
[suspenseful music]
[loud explosion]
-[acid burbles]
-[grunts]
[loud rumble]
-[gasps]
-[knife clanks]
[wind howls]
[grunts]
-[loud explosion]
-[yelping]
-[acid hisses]
-[groans]
-[armor clanks]
-[terrified screams]
[thwacks]
Come on! This way!
-[screams]
-[grunts]
[crash]
[grunts]
[yelps]
-[grunts]
-[explosion]
-[gasps]
-[man] Get me out of here!
[thrilling music]
[spurts]
-[fire roars]
-[yells]
[action music]
[gasps]
[grunts]
-[pops]
-[grunts]
Grab it!
Don't let it go!
-[thuds]
-[people screaming]
[clamoring]
[terrified screaming]
-[fire humming]
-[angered breathing]
[seething]
[thwacks]
-[clangs]
-[loud explosion]
-[grunts]
-[man screaming]
-[panting]
-[swishes]
[weapon swishes]
[eerie music]
[weapons clang]
[grunts]
-[blazes]
-[grunts]
[swishing]
[grunts, groans]
[oriental string music]
[swishes]
It's time to repay your blood debt, Nezha.
[grunts]
[clangs]
[fire roars]
[gasps, groans]
[thumps]
[swishes]
-[clinks]
-[gasps]
[panting]
-[nurse 1] We need more nurses here.
-[nurse 2] Hold on, hold on.
-[people sobbing]
-[groaning in pain]
-There's a few patients on the second…
-[Smuggler Boss] Hey, Li!
Li Yunxiang, hurry! It's your dad.
[gasps]
-Hey!
-[man groans]
Old Li!
Doctor.
-Doctor! Can you help him?
-[gasps]
There must be something.
Aren't you a doctor, huh?
[panting]
Why can't you save him?
-[Old Li groaning]
-[Yunxiang] Why?
[groaning]
Yunxiang.
Old Li!
Whatever trouble you get into later,
I promise I won't nag you anymore.
You'll be fine, we're in a hospital.
They'll help.
I knew since the beginning…
[groans]
…that I had been blessed
with an amazing son.
Don't try to talk.
You should rest.
You…
have all your friends.
[Old Li] You have your brother.
And you have your life.
[inhales]
Please don't die.
Old Li, please don't.
Live a good life.
Do it for me.
Live…
[Yunxiang sobbing]
[dramatic music]
Dad.
Dad!
Dad…
[sobbing]
[wind howls]
Dad!
[dramatic music]
[seething]
-[Dr. Su] Where are you going?
-[Yunxiang] I'm going to kill them all!
[engine roars]
[yawns]
Oh, there sure are a lot of you.
[glass clanks]
Hmm…
[light chuckle]
[scoffs]
I'll make myself at home.
[laughs]
What is this? Give me that. Huh?
Hmm.
[sniffs, groans in disgust]
You drink that?
Hey, what you got? What you got there?
Oh, you have a King. Throw it out.
That's a pretty good hand, dummy.
[cackles]
[foreboding music]
[Six-Eared Macaque] Oh.
[laughs]
Take a good look.
-[grumbles]
-Huh?
Oh, that's a good boy.
[chuckles]
[irked groan, blows raspberries]
I'm not dressed for this.
Oh…
-[thunder rumbles]
-[gasps, guffaws]
[water sloshing]
[growls]
What do you think of my new pets?
Powerful, aren't they?
[guffaws]
So that's it.
This is where all the water
in Donghai City went.
These blue guys are hoarding it all,
so that's it.
[light chuckle]
I merely had to take their pup.
Now they serve me.
-[whimpers]
-[snarls]
They wouldn't dare to disobey me.
The waters of the East Sea are fed
by thousands upon thousands of rivers.
[Ao Guang] It draws
from even the smallest springs.
How else could it grow so large?
[cackles]
Genius! Brilliant stuff.
[Ao Guang] I invited you here to ask you
if there has been progress
in the favor I asked of you.
[clears throat]
Um, I've been busy,
but I'm on it. Trust me.
[scoffs]
You don't say.
I'm hoping you can help me
understand something.
That brat's power has grown so quickly,
he even defeated Yaksa.
Someone must have trained him,
don't you think?
Oh, maybe he is so naturally talented
that he got there on his own.
That's true.
But perhaps it was you.
Who me?
Why would I do that? It's crazy.
Anything is possible.
In fact, you might be afraid
I'll reveal what you're hiding
behind that mask.
Perhaps that's why
you want me dead so badly.
So you can shut me up!
-[zaps]
-[mask clangs]
[dramatic music]
[Ao Guang] The Six-Eared Macaque.
[growls]
[chuckles]
So you're a demon after all.
I thought the Monkey King
had killed you long ago.
-[magical hum]
-Yes, he did.
Now I'm just a nameless demon in a mask.
Dragon King, a few years ago,
Donghai's lakes and rivers
dried up overnight.
And river dragons
who ruled them disappeared.
That was you?
A nosy demon.
You have six ears after all.
You deserve your reputation.
No one could trick you.
The Order of the Gods is finished!
We, Dragons, won't have
our tails stepped on again.
[Ao Guang] Once I have gathered
all the lakes and rivers
and added them to my power,
I shall create a new universal order.
[chuckles]
Universal order?
So this master plan of yours
is the reason you have brought
such suffering to the people of Donghai?
Ao Guang, don't you fear
the Court of Heaven?
[scoffs]
It's total chaos up there.
How could they handle me?
Besides, who dare testify against me?
Just like plants,
people need to be weeded.
If the grass won't bend
when a strong wind blows over it,
then I'll have to mow it down. There, see?
[scoffs]
So brutal. Ruthless.
How else will my new order be imposed?
Imposed?
-[cackles]
-[grunts]
-[squeaks]
-[swishes]
[rustles]
[struggled grunting]
[laughter]
I wouldn't expect her to work for you.
Nezha has many enemies.
The East Sea clan is not the only one.
-[fire roars]
-[metal clanging]
-[gasps]
-Hmm?
[bike engine rumbles]
-[spear clangs]
-[body thuds]
-[gasps]
-Hmm…
-[grunts]
-Hmm.
-[gasps]
-[rustling]
-[thuds]
-[spear clangs]
[grunting]
[groans]
[grunting, yelling]
[growls]
[irked grunt]
Oh, come on. You didn't think
he would go down that easy.
[yells]
-[fire roars]
-[groans]
[groaning, panting]
Hmph.
[rustling]
[whimpers]
[gibbering]
[babbling]
[yelps]
[grunting]
[Ao Guang] I don't yet have
the Dragon Pearl.
Let's retreat for now.
Come on.
[cane clangs]
-[thuds]
-[cane clangs]
Useless.
[scoffs]
[Ao Bing] Father.
I…
I swear I'll kill him.
[heavy sigh]
Son, don't embarrass me.
Nezha.
I promise, you won't humiliate me
like you did the last time.
[crackles]
[Ao Bing] Come on.
Let's finish this.
Don't tell me you're too afraid.
Prepare to die!
[thrilling music]
[grunts]
[shards crackle]
[grunting]
[hard thwack]
[suspenseful music]
-[wallops]
-[cracks]
-[yells]
-[groans]
-[squeaks]
-[exhales]
[daunting music]
[heavy thump]
[roars]
[snarls]
-[growls]
-[gasps]
[grunts]
-[thwacks]
-[groans]
[clinks]
[groans]
[spear clangs]
[snarls]
[suspenseful music]
[yells]
[ice crackles]
[grunting]
[power yell]
[thumping]
-[sharp inhale]
-[wallops]
[thuds]
[rock music]
[Yunxiang grunting]
-[power yell]
-[clangs]
[Yunxiang roaring]
[growls]
[loud thud]
[grunts]
[groans]
-[whooshing]
-Huh?
Now die!
[metal clinks]
-[metal whooshes]
-Boop!
-[grunts]
-[weapons clashing]
-[metal clinking]
-[grunts]
-[groans]
Ms. Rosy Cloud,
it's not nice to ambush people.
-[Yunxiang] Wait.
-[gasps]
-Huh? Are you talking to me?
-Who is she?
Oh, this! This is the disciple
of Demoness Shiji.
You can't help yourself, can you?
[Rosy Cloud] You bring disaster
wherever you go.
Disaster?
Don't pretend you don't remember.
Playing with your master's bow and arrow,
from 1,000 miles away,
you killed my friend to amuse yourself.
You ripped out Prince's Dragon Spine,
causing his citizens to suffer needlessly.
[Rosy Cloud] No matter who you're
reborn as, you hurt those closest to you.
It's your destiny.
Nezha, you killed my son!
I will drown everyone in the city!
[Nezha] Father, where are my Astras?
Where did you hide them?
Nezha, you must apologize!
-Give me back my Astras!
-[Nezha's father] Listen to me!
Nezha, you are a threat to all existence.
[citizens] Apologize!
Apologize!
-Apologize!
-If you don't apologize,
everyone will die because of you!
Please, son, you must stop!
I won't do it!
He should apologize to me!
You…
-You're a monster. You're a monster.
-[sword clangs]
[laughs]
[foreboding music]
Dragon King…
you want an apology?
[maniacal laughter]
-[flesh ripping]
-[heart thumping]
[gasps, panting]
[Rosy Cloud grunts]
Let her go.
What?
I said let her go.
[sighs]
-You heard him. Hmm.
-[grunts]
-He's letting you go.
-[exhales]
-[weapon sheathes]
-It won't change who you are.
Nothing can ever change that.
[grunts]
[sighs]
[exhales]
I really am a monster.
Why are you helping me?
[scoffs]
[Six-Eared Macaque] I'm not helping you.
I'm helping your past life self.
[scoffs]
Nezha?
No. Someone even older than that.
[inhales sharply]
So long ago, back
when the First Goddess patched the sky.
[sighs]
You?
The Six-Eared Macaque?
[cackles]
[Six-Eared Macaque] Yeah.
About that…
[rock music]
[roars]
[Six-Eared Macaque]
I am the Monkey King, kid!
Back when I stole the Holy Scriptures
from Heaven, I saw how useless they were.
You must know that words alone
can't end the world's suffering.
You're the Monkey King,
the greatest hero to ever live.
Where there's suffering in the world,
you know exactly what to do.
Oh, is that what they told you?
[wheezes]
Much like the waves of the East Sea,
time comes and goes, goes and comes.
For something called
the Order of the Gods,
it sure gets messed up a lot.
[scoffs]
I've been fixing it
for thousands of years.
But nothing ever changes.
[Six-Eared Macaque] Turns out I'm useless.
Just like you.
[scoffs]
Ao Guang thinks
that I'm hiding from my enemies.
[chuckles]
But I'm just tired.
I don't even know
where my Golden Staff is.
Li Yunxiang.
The Red Ribbon the Dragon King uses,
that's not just Astra.
The Sky Ribbon.
[panicked gasp]
[Six-Eared Macaque]
This hole leads to the East Sea.
There, beneath the waterfall
on the ocean floor
is the Dragon King's greatest palace.
That's where he keeps
his captured river dragons,
harnessing their strength
to create his Dragon Pearl.
Since they're river dragons,
they need fresh water to live.
That's why he stole the water
in Donghai City.
Exactly!
He used Nezha's Sky Ribbon
to bind those dragons.
[Six-Eared Macaque]
It's too bad, Li Yunxiang.
I mean, what can you do about it, huh?
You can't use the Sky Ribbon.
You're not Nezha.
I'm not Nezha?
That evil kid who shows up
whenever you're feeling murderous.
Have you noticed,
when you try to help people,
the kid's nowhere to be seen?
[Six-Eared Macaque]
How can Nezha, being so evil,
that everyone and his own parents
wanted him dead,
have the heart to try to save people, huh?
So nope, you're not Nezha.
Not Nezha enough.
[somber music]
[indistinct murmurs]
Yunxiang, your brother's awake.
Huh?
[sobbing]
Brother.
I'm sorry.
[Liang] Tsk. Spare us your tears.
Six's death was all your fault.
Who will you kill next, huh?
I know. I'm sorry for everything.
[Liang] Now, he apologizes?
You offended the De Clan.
Now all of us are their enemies.
Just look. Look around this room.
Dead and wounded everywhere.
It's all his fault.
He is a walking disaster.
-You were the one who murdered Six!
-How did you…
-What are you talking about?
-I watched you kill Six.
Then you sabotaged Yunxiang's armor!
[gasps]
So it was you?
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[Liang] Don't move!
Stay back! Take one more step,
and I'll kill her.
It doesn't matter.
You know it's his fault.
He just wants to play hero.
-But what about us, huh? What about us?
-[Kasha grunts]
-[groans, gasps]
-[coins clatter]
Kasha!
[Liang screams]
[body thuds]
WATER
[exhales]
[wind gushing]
[Kasha singing in Mandarin]
♪ Such a big world ♪
♪ So many places ♪
-[bottle clinks]
-[wine sloshes]
♪ A free spirit like me ♪
-♪ Could make memories anywhere ♪
-[clinks]
[gulps, coughs]
-♪ But there's a place ♪
-[sobbing]
♪ I cannot go ♪
-♪ That place is home ♪
-[Yunxiang] I can't change anything.
It was all for nothing.
♪ That place is home ♪
[water gushing]
[solemn music]
[mystical music]
[wind blows]
[somber music]
[sobbing]
[sighs]
[Dr. Su exhales]
Maybe we're just delaying the inevitable.
Just like my patients in the hospital.
Whether you cure them or not,
they all die someday.
But if I can cure them,
that gives them more time
to spend with their loved ones.
I know that any time
I can give back to them,
it's all worth it for the ones
that are still here.
[wheelchair rattles]
-Hmm…
-[taps]
Li Yunxiang, cheer up, huh?
[Kasha] I agree with her, you know.
I don't think you're useless.
I think you're a hero.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[dramatic music]
[Yunxiang inhales sharply]
I know what's expected of me.
Maybe I'll fail,
but you can't say I didn't try.
I'm going to the Dragon Palace.
I will defeat the Dragon King
and bring back the water.
[waves crash]
That's what I owe to everyone,
those who are alive today,
and everyone who will be born long after.
Everyone.
What I'm going to do
will be useful to them.
That will be enough for me.
-[cup clinks]
-[gasps]
[shatters]
[Yunxiang] Show yourself, Nezha.
We need to talk.
[fire roars]
[spear clanking]
[Yunxiang] Are we really the same person?
You're just a kid after all.
Hurts my brain to think about it.
Listen, I'm going to save people.
Not just one person, either.
I'm saving the whole city.
You wouldn't know any of them.
Maybe this sort of thing isn't your style.
Probably after eons of selfish behavior,
you're not gonna change now.
So I, Li Yunxiang, will go alone.
[exhales]
This armor is all that I'm taking.
I made it myself, you know.
Hide if you want.
I don't need you.
[fire blazes]
Go figure.
He really is a disaster.
[deep exhale]
[water splashes]
[mystical music]
[roars]
[gasps]
-[growls]
-[muffled grunts]
[suspenseful music]
[grunts]
[growling]
[clanks, cranks]
[growls]
[clicks, shoots]
-[whooshes]
-[gasps]
[thuds]
[thrilling music]
[smashes]
[creaking]
[clanking]
[grunts]
[epic music]
[thwacking]
[groans]
[grunts]
[thumps]
[wallops]
[shark howls]
[thrilling music]
[water splashes]
-[water splashes]
-[Yunxiang grunts]
[growls]
Thank you.
-[grunts]
-[clanking]
-[water splashes]
[somber music]
[mystical music]
-[growls]
-[chains rattle]
-[swishes]
-[snarls]
-[grunts]
-[chains break]
[roars]
[pup whimpers]
[grunting]
[Yunxiang screaming]
-[water burbles]
-[waves roaring]
[both gasp]
-[gasps]
[grunting]
[chains rattle]
[whimpers]
-[panting]
-[Ao Guang laughs]
[Ao Guang] So you are here to kill us all.
There's no rush.
Why don't you take a moment
to say hello to my guest?
[Dr. Su] Yunxiang!
-[grunts]
-[groans]
-[chuckles]
[groans]
[foreboding music]
-[zaps]
-[groans]
-Yunxiang!
-[thwacks]
-[gasps]
-[zaps]
[zapping]
-[groans]
-[thumps]
-[Yunxiang] Dr. Su!
Why me?
[laughs]
Isn't it obvious?
We're trying to mess with his head.
-[grunts]
-[gears crank]
[grunts]
[pants]
Yunxiang!
-[grunts]
-[zaps]
[grunts, groans]
[grunting]
[yells]
-[gasps]
-[squelches]
You think you can defeat me?
[thunder rumbles]
[grunting]
[ominous music]
-[zapping]
-[Yunxiang screams]
[groans]
[grunts]
[laughs]
[grunting]
[sighs]
[snarls]
[tense music]
[zaps]
[grunting, shrieking]
Yunxiang!
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
[yelps]
[panting]
[Rosy Cloud laughs]
Sorry about all this.
-[Rosy Cloud] Time to finish you off.
-[grunts]
[gasps]
[Dr. Su screams]
-[gasps, grunts]
-[zaps]
[laughs]
[Rosy Cloud]
You can't help yourself, can you?
You bring disaster wherever you go.
-[maniacal laughter]
-[indistinct whispers]
[indistinct whispers continue]
[laughter]
[Dr. Su] Yunxiang!
-Li Yunxiang!
-[growls]
-[gasps]
-What?
[grunting]
[screaming]
-[spear clangs]
-[yells]
[gasps]
[yells]
[grunts]
-[zapping]
-[fire roaring]
[power yell]
-[chains rattle]
-[Dr. Su grunts]
[grunting]
[panting]
[water sloshing]
-[gasps]
-[mystical music]
[gentle snarl]
Thank you.
[flesh pierces]
[Dragon King laughs]
Did you think this is the end?
I've been waiting 3,000 years
preparing all this time,
mastering Tao to prepare for you.
[laughter]
[mystical music]
-[rumbles]
-[whimpers]
-[chains rattle]
-[roars]
[Dragon King] Nezha, you gave me no choice
but to swallow the Dragon Pearl.
-[munches]
-[thumps]
Without it, the river dragons will escape.
They'll create a tsunami
better than the world has ever seen.
It will engulf every living thing
in Donghai.
Because of you, countless
innocent people will die once again.
[zaps]
-[beam blazes]
-[grunts, groans]
[Dr. Su grunts]
[panting]
[chains rattle]
[maniacal laughter]
Huh?
[thunder rumbles]
[groans]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[yells]
[whimpers]
[roars]
-[fire roars]
-[grunts]
[rumbles]
[snarls]
[grunting]
[zaps]
[groans]
[rumbling]
[grunting]
[yells]
[roars]
[epic music]
[armor clanks]
[gasps]
[yells]
[suspenseful music]
[grunting continues]
[mystical music]
[dramatic music]
-[growls]
-[whimpers]
[chains rattle]
[roars]
[roaring]
[loud crash]
Hurry! Run! Run!
[panicked yelling]
-[man] Run! Come on! Let's go!
-[woman] Come on!
[ominous music]
[whimpers]
[exhales]
[grunts]
-[wood clatters]
-[grunts]
[Dr. Su] Yunxiang.
-[liquid sloshes]
-[coughs]
[scoffs]
Hear that?
[Ao Guang] That horrible noise outside,
it's the sound of the tsunami.
Donghai City will be gone.
-[thwacks]
-[groans]
[moans]
[muffled]
[Ao Guang] You're just a mortal.
No need to struggle.
Relax. Just give up.
Your life is not your own.
-Heaven gave it.
-[creaking]
So Heaven can take it back.
Return it.
-[flesh squelches]
-[Yunxiang groans]
[pained screams]
[Ao Guang] Give up.
-You were never Nezha.
-[electricity zaps]
[screams]
[water gushes]
-[Tiger] Oh!
-[Ms. San] Tiger!
[metal clanging]
[people clamoring]
[woman] Run! Run!
-[groans]
-[maniacal laughter]
[zapping]
[grunting]
[Yunxiang] This life was given to me,
so that means it belongs to me.
[fire roars]
You don't get to tell me who I am.
[exhales]
I'll show you…
[groaning]
Who I really am!
-[both screaming]
-[fire blazes]
[epic music]
[yells]
[dramatic music]
[ashes rustle]
[thuds]
[sobbing]
[Dr. Su] You can't die.
You can't die. You won't.
Aren't you Nezha?
[sobs]
You can't die.
[gasps]
[labored breathing]
[weeping]
[sobbing]
[clanks]
[somber music]
[dragons roaring]
[somber music continues]
[mystical music]
[groans]
[Yunxiang] So, we meet again.
[labored breathing]
Shouldn't you be hiding?
What are you doing here?
[groans]
I did my best.
The tsunami outside…
Donghai…
All of those people,
can you save everyone?
Hey.
[exhales]
You…
better find your next incarnation.
[mystical music]
[gasps]
[fire roars]
[daunting music]
-[gasps]
-[heart thumping]
[mystical music]
[suspenseful music]
[fire roars]
[loud explosion]
[rock music]
[sighs]
[yells]
[epic music]
[waves crashing]
[epic music continues]
[growls]
-[grunts]
-[roars]
[power yell]
[roars]
-[giggles]
-[Jinxiang] Huh?
[rain pattering]
-[chuckles]
-[people cheering]
[Kasha giggles]
[people clamoring]
Ms. San, is that what rain is?
-Huh?
-[excited babble]
[engine rumbles]
[water sloshing]
[mystical music]
[giggles]
[waves crashing]
[victorious music]
[victorious music continues]
[waves crashing]
I got my Magic Ribbon back.
I'm Nezha enough.
-[giggles]
-[keys jingle]
Hey, bring it back in one piece.
[Yunxiang] Will do.
[whines]
[engine revs]
[chuckles, grunts]
[splashes]
[Six-Eared Macaque sighs]
He got the Sky Ribbon back.
No reason he shouldn't have other Astras.
Hmm, let me see.
Cosmic Ring, Fire Wheel, Dragon Catcher.
I'm forgetting one.
Oh, yeah!
[dramatic music]
[Yunxiang] In my last moment,
when I was dead,
that's when I became Nezha.
-Turns out he and I…
-There you are, Yunxiang?
-…weren't that different after all.
-[tires screeching]
-Ready to go?
-[Yunxiang] Because both of us know,
-in this world…
-[giggles]
[pup whines]
-…if you don't like your fate…
-What's this?
-…you have to fight.
-[Kasha] Oh, boy, he's so cute!
[chuckles]
[in Mandarin]
♪ In my dream ♪
♪ There were you and me ♪
♪ It never seemed real ♪
♪ From the beginning ♪
♪ When a true heart ♪
[Yunxiang] This is my world.
♪ Of youth anymore ♪
This is our world.
♪ Tomorrow, today, and yesterday's fate ♪
My name is Li Yunxiang.
♪ Had been decided at that moment ♪
My name is Nezha.
NEW GODS: NEZHA REBORN
[in Mandarin]
♪ How many souls are at war? ♪
♪ After saying goodbye
To the confusing youth ♪
♪ How many still hold onto dreams? ♪
♪ The wind blew past the seasons ♪
♪ Flowers bloomed and faded again ♪
♪ The rain seeped into my heart ♪
♪ Wandering in the vast sea of people ♪
♪ A pure heart ♪
♪ Spends the entire lifetime
Pursuing a dream ♪
♪ A sincere person ♪
♪ Is willing to end with a good dream ♪
♪ One burns for his dream in this life ♪
♪ It's what he yearns for in this life ♪
♪ Dream comes true in this life ♪
♪ It comes from what the heart wants ♪
STAY TUNED FOR POST-CREDITS SCENE
[in Mandarin]
♪ Walking through a bustling city ♪
♪ Slowly ignoring worldly affairs ♪
♪ A sigh by the window ♪
♪ Reveals whispered dreams in this life ♪
♪ Pondering under the moon ♪
♪ Who decides what happens in life? ♪
♪ The loyal heart
Of a child is unstoppable ♪
♪ Showing his ambition ♪
♪ Yesterday's flowers ♪
♪ Faded without regrets ♪
♪ Fallen leaves have wilted ♪
♪ Who else but me? ♪
[metal clanking]
[bird chirps]
[chirping]
-[thuds]
-[chirps]
[wood clatters]
[thuds]
[mystical music]
[squeaks]
-[rumbles]
-[metal clangs]
[sniffs, squeaks]
-[squeaks]
-[metal clangs]
[mystical music]
[squeaks]
MO LIQING
AO BING
[mystical music continues]
ORDER OF THE GODS
[zapping]
STAY TUNED FOR POST-CREDITS SCENE
[in Mandarin]
♪ Such a big world ♪
♪ So many places ♪
♪ A free spirit like me ♪
♪ Could linger anywhere ♪
♪ Such a big world ♪
♪ So many young men ♪
♪ A free spirit like me ♪
♪ Could find love anywhere ♪
♪ There's a place ♪
♪ I cannot go ♪
♪ There's a young man ♪
♪ I can't even say hello to ♪
♪ That place is home ♪
♪ That man is you ♪
♪ But young man ♪
♪ Why are you hesitant? ♪
♪ Flowers will bloom again ♪
♪ Youth comes only once ♪
[in Mandarin]
♪ It has always been this kind of world ♪
♪ Same air ♪
♪ Different fates ♪
♪ Begin to feel ♪
♪ Don't live in this kind of world ♪
♪ Starting today ♪
♪ We live in this kind of world ♪
♪ Be who you are ♪
[Blanca] Verta.
-[mystical music]
-[Verta] Blanca…
THE WHITE SNAKE TEAM CONTINUES
THEIR DESTINY FROM THE PAST
[Fahai] You'll be my prisoner forever!
Verta, keep living.
[Verta] Blanca!
You think you can keep us apart?
I'll kill you if it's the last thing I do!
I can promise you that.
[loud rumble]
[foreboding music]
[gasps]
[mysterious music]
[siren wailing in distance]
[suspenseful music]
WHITE SNAKE 2
DISASTER ENCOUNTERED BY THE GREEN SNAKE
COMING SOON IN 2021
[engine rumbles]
[tires screech]
[dog barking]
[somber music]
NEW GOD LIST: YANG JIAN
PLEASE LOOK FORWARD TO IT IN 2022
[closing theme music]