Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
00:01:25,120
credit
The Long Ballad
Episode 16
From now on,
you're just a slave of Eagle Division.
What do you want to do to me?
I want you to disappear from Tang.
Only I can decide my life or death.
What you say is useless.
It depends on your ability.
Your keeping me beside you
is no different from keeping a snake in your bosom.
Think about it after you can survive.
The only law of survival here is that
the big fish eat up the small ones.
Behind me is Shuozhou,
which has been plundered but undamaged.
Behind it are the mountains.
Thousands of miles away is my hometown,
Chang'an.
I can't return anymore.
You used to win honor for our country,
but now you're reduced to be a slave.
Li Changge.
Even I feel sorry for you.
[Fuju Inn]
Upon receiving your order, I rushed over here.
What can I do for you?
Follow Ashile Tribe right now.
I want to know the end of Li Changge.
Kill her?
If she colludes with Ashile Tribe,
kill her.
What if not?
Then Ashile Tribe won't allow her to survive.
Yes.
Send me the information with a carrier pigeon.
You can leave now.
Yes.
My closest relatives are killed like dogs.
I'm exiled by the place where I grow up.
I consider life worse than death.
But I must finish what I should do.
It's not late for you to kill me after I finish it.
Li Changge.
Hope you can sacrifice yourself for our country.
In recent days, the county governments all over the country
are secretly looking for the whereabouts of the princess.
But the portraits sent to the capital have no semblance of Princess.
The four northern cities where she once appeared
haven't sent any information.
Your Highness.
Princess Yong'an is always fortunate.
Li Chunfeng has predicted that she would return safe and sound.
I hope so.
Recently,
I've always dreamed of Leyan and Changge in their childhood.
They're playing in the garden.
I wave to them, but they can't see me.
I call them, but they can't hear me.
And they run farther and farther.
You've been thinking too much
so you have these strange dreams.
Your Highness.
I'll ask the imperial kitchen to stew some soothing and healthy soup.
Will they be farther away from me?
No.
They are your most intimate daughter and minister respectively.
Perhaps it's the best news that we have no news.
Yes.
Your Highness! Emergency!
Ashile Tribe suddenly attacked our northern border.
Sima Tu, the military governor,
and Gongsun Heng, the governor of Shuozhou, both died.
When did that happen?
Why hasn't anyone reported this before?
Ashile Tribe encircled the city.
So the frontier had never been able to send out war reports.
Hao Du sent a man to hurry up all the way.
It costs us five horses to send the letter to Chang'an.
Send troops right now to recover the northern border.
Do expel Ashile Tribe from our border!
Then, the troops should be stationed there to comfort local people.
Yes.
Mr. Du.
Mr. Du. I have something to discuss with you.
Mr. Fang, you're always thoughtful.
What do you want to discuss?
Mr. Du. Don't make me embarrassed.
Don't make me embarrassed.
We're both officials of court.
We should discuss the matters.
And I really need your help this time.
Just make it clear.
It's the biggest worry of his Highness that Princess Yong'an is gone.
We've sent the portraits of Princess to the governments all over the country to let them investigate in secret,
but in vain.
Only the northern border hasn't sent any information yet.
I'm worried.
What can I do for you?
People on the northern border have never seen the Princess.
It happens that your adopted son is also there.
Although Mr. Wei shoulders the whole responsibility of the missing of Princess,
Hao Du was also with Princess then.
So one more man means more help.
- And under your wise instruction, your adopted son...
- Fine.
- your adopted son...
Just tell me your business.
Don't flatter me.
Since his Highness entrusts this matter to you,
it's fine that you arrange everything.
Yes.
Eat more.
Come on.
Why do you keep that guy?
You'd better kill him.
Here you are.
Put it there.
One more pie, please.
Here you are.
Where are you going?
I didn't expect to meet you here.
In fact, Eagle Division is not far from Shuozhou.
It is near the river with trees.
You'll get used to living here.
Have some food.
Listen.
If Tegin Sun doesn't care about you, I won't care about your life.
Stubborn!
Your friend seems to be quite stubborn.
I think you'll have no benefits from him.
He's too weak to survive in grasslands.
No.
Why?
He has the strongest desire for survival.
Such situation can't beat him down.
It seems that you know him very well.
But I think he just treats you as an enemy.
I don't care.
You've never treated me that kindly these years.
That guy has followed us all the way.
I know.
He comes to see Shisi.
Do me a favor.
What do you want to do?
Let me go!
Listen.
You're our slave.
You must listen to us.
You refuse to work?
I think you ask for death!
Take him away!
Cut him off and feed dogs!
Yes!
What do you want to do?
Let me go!
Go!
Hurry up!
Mr. Qin.
I feel sorry for Yuan.
She's braved the wind and dew with us for a long time.
I don't think so.
She has the best dad and mom in the world.
What's the situation of Shuozhou?
I've got the news.
Ashile Tribe has left.
The court will send someone to take over the rest.
And...
And?
Do you want to tell me the news of Young Master?
Her assassination failed.
She was killed.
Got it.
She's so stubborn.
It's easy for her to suffer losses.
If...
Don't be sad.
I think she's still alive.
Still alive?
Since Ashile Sun has an agreement with the governor,
he won't kill her.
Perhaps he's taken her to the grassland.
So we don't need to wait for her. We should find her!
We should find her!
The grassland is full of their spies.
We can't do anything there.
Let's arrange for Yuan first.
Try to use the previous intelligence network to get information.
Then make decisions.
[The target has been killed by Ashile Tribe.]
Li Changge.
Perhaps it's your best end.
Why are you here?
It's a question that I should ask you.
It's strange that his Highness doesn't blame you for losing Princess.
I'll find Leyan for sure.
I'll wait.
You haven't been back to Chang'an for a long time.
Are you looking for Changge?
What's wrong with her?
She died.
How did she die?
You killed her?
Tell me!
Wei Shuyu.
Are you going to revenge for your loved girl,
regardless of the safety of your family?
After I kill you,
I'll commit suicide.
Do you think his Highness will kill my family for you?
Why haven't you taken any action?
When Li Changge was alive, you could do nothing.
But you have the courage to revenge after her death.
I think you know that once Li Changge dies,
your family's glory won't be affected.
If you want to revenge, you get the wrong person.
I didn't kill Li Changge.
She was killed by Ashile Tribe.
Ashile Tribe?
After Ashile Tribe occupied Shuozhou, Li Changge was captured.
Considering her stubbornness,
do you think she can survive?
I never expect that you're the man that ran after me with him.
From now on, you and I have nothing to do with each other.
From now on,
I'll lead my own life.
The amulet given by Leyan is of no use.
In the end,
I fail to protect neither of them.
Come on.
Li Changge has died.
Don't let Princess be in trouble.
And I receive a letter from Chang'an.
They ask me to stay in the north to look for Princess.
Obviously, they don't trust you.
I'll find Leyan earlier than you.
I don't care.
I disdain to compete with you.
But I can give you a hint.
Li Changge is a well-known commandant in Shuozhou.
If Princess Yong'an is in Shuozhou, there must be some traces.
So you shouldn't come to Shuozhou.
What happened last night?
Why did you knock me out after putting the headgear on my head?
Why didn't you kill me?
Last night, a slave died for you.
Take him away!
Cut off him and feed dogs!
Yes!
- Let me go!
- Go!
Let me go!
Go!
Hurry up!
Don't resist!
What does Ashile Sun want to do?
I don't understand it, too.
If I were him, I would have been impatient!
You've been challenging the bottom line of Eagle Division.
You'll never realize our power without any suffering.
How delicate you are!
I don't know why he brought you back.
[Yunzhou County Government]
Sir, this way.
Sir.
Are you the magistrate?
Where are you from?
You even don't know our magistrate!
Magistrate. Please do me a favor.
How dare you!
Don't you know the rules?
Magistrate is busy with official business.
Go away!
Magistrate!
You're the local magistrate of Yunzhou.
If I didn't ask for something urgent,
I wouldn't have been so presumptuous.
Go away!
If you want to redress the injustice, beat the drum.
What do you want to say?
Listen.
It's inconvenient to tell you my identity.
But could you send a letter to Chang'an or Luoyang
if it is convenient for you?
What's your identity?
I'm Princess Yong'an.
I lost touch with my valet by accident.
After the city was occupied, I ran all the away and arrived here.
Magistrate.
If you can help me return to the capital,
his Highness will give you a big reward.
Do you have any keepsake?
Keepsake?
I kept no keepsake when lost.
But I'm really a princess.
My dad gave me the title in person.
Do you have any things made by the palace?
I can recognize it immediately.
All the keepsakes were robbed.
Where did you get the news?
You're well-informed.
The court gave us a secret order to find a princess in secret.
But I can't identify you based on what you say.
I know dad must have sent people to look for me.
Magistrate.
I'm really a princess. Believe me.
Really. Magistrate.
I beg you. Send a letter to Luoyang!
- You impersonate Princess. Flog to death.
- I'm not cheating you!
Come on! Catch her!
Yes!
Magistrate! Magistrate...
Why not trust me?
Don't be stunned! Catch her!
Catch her!
Come on.
Let her go.
What a poor girl!
Now the situation is very chaotic.
The new governor will arrive in days.
I have no time to deal with the refugee.
Be careful.
Dad.
Why haven't you taken me home?
Have you abandoned me?
Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
If you think you have endless strength, run a few laps outside.
I'm really confused.
How will you treat Shisi?
You made great efforts to rescue Shisi.
But now you don't care about him, leaving him bullied.
You're becoming more and more strange.
The more I care about her, the more painful she will be.
Instead of letting her hate herself,
I'd better let her hate me.
You're really strange!
Are you bewitched by him?
Shall I ask a witch doctor to diagnose you?
I think you want to clean up horse dung.
Clean horse dung?
I'm the military counsellor of Eagle Division.
Don't make me embarrassed.
She has to get a foothold here on her own.
I can't see all of her actions.
He's just a clever man from Central Plains.
Is she worth your deeds?
I don't think she's grateful at all.
I don't need her gratitude.
I just hope she can survive.
Tegin.
Counsellor.
The slave you asked me to keep an eye on fainted.
You have been burnt out for Shuozhou
and refused to eat and drink all the way.
Do you try to seek death?
Do you think I'll do anything on you?
I'm not interested in women like you.
When did you...
I knew you're a girl when I saved you beside the river.
I found that you want to conceal it.
I'm not interested in exposing you.
You've always been kidding me?
I don't care what you think.
Tegin! Here's your medicine you want and...
The doctor said you become ill due to worries and are deficient in qi and blood.
If you don't want to die, take the medicine.
Take it!
Li Shisi!
I didn't expect that you're so sheepish! People in Shuozhou are safe and sound.
I've met my commitment. Now it's your turn.
Don't forget that you're at the mercy of me.
Ridiculous.
You want a person from Central Plain to work for you?
You'd better kill me so that you won't regret later.
I tell you the last time. Take the medicine.
Can you only solve the problems in this way?
That's better than living in disgrace.
Now that I'm at the mercy of you, why do you humiliate me?
Humiliate you?
I just don't want you to die so easily.
Li Shisi. You'd better try to survive.
Even if you want to kill me or revenge for Gongsun Heng one day.
Revenge?
Yes. Revenge!
Have you forgotten the hatred of Gongsun Heng and the people and army of Shuozhou?
It's ridiculous that Gongsun Heng entrusted everything to you.
If I were you, I would try every means to get a firm foothold here
and win others' trust at any cost so as to find the chance to kill them.
If you want to live up to his expectation, struggle to survive.
If I can entrust Shuozhou people's lives to the princess of Tang,
I will die without regret.
I can't let the families in the city down
but I am doomed to fail my wife and daughter.
A' Dou!
Not only the hatred of Gongsun and Shuozhou.
Yes.
I can't just die.
I can't die here.
It's easy to die.
It has always been the hardest to live on.
Go!
Stop!
- Go.
- Don't go there.
We just came from there. Yan is not there.
Turn left. To Yunzhou.
Go!
It's magistrate's office! You are not allowed to break in!
Magistrate.
I come to look for Princess under his Highness' order. We need your people for help.
I am at your service.
Immediately arrange people to go to all refugee settlements to find the woman in the picture.
Yes.
Well... Well...
Did you see her? Where's she?
She had no keepsake to prove her identity.
I mistook her as a refugee. So I drove her away.
Find her at all costs!
Yes.
- Ms. Chai. Where are you going?
- Just hang around.
Bye.
Your embroidery is terrible. You should work harder to earn money.
Got it.
Mrs. Xiang. How is your incense business?
Good.
You need to burn more incense.
Fragrant and crisp sesame cake!
- Open for business today?
- Yes.
Give me three.
You have many workers. Three is not enough.
Nonsense.
It's already hard for them to have meals, let alone sesame cakes.
Hurry up. I'm hungry.
Ok. Wait a minute.
So many things here! Look at it!
It's not a charity. Beg for food elsewhere.
I have money.
I want to buy cakes.
You frightened her.
Three coppers each. Don't consider it expensive.
It's a time of chaos. Food is expensive everywhere.
Here you are.
Miss. In bright daylight, will you do anything to...
Miss. I've got married.
I've got married.
Three coppers each. No other alternative.
No. I was afraid of being robbed,
so I put my purse in the innermost layer of my clothes.
Okay.
Obviously you don't know how to embroider. What's this?
An ugly purse!
I think it's the most beautiful purse in the world.
Okay. Wait a minute.
Here's your cake.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
Sorry.
That's alright. I had dirtier food before.
If you don't mind, I can share a half.
I can share with you.
I mean no harm.
In recent years, kind people are bullied by bad ones.
Miss, check your purse right now.
It's stupid that you want to share your cake with him!
Have a look!
My purse! My purse!
Stop!
My purse!
Return my purse. You can take away the money.
Well. Here you are.
Here you are.
So ugly! What's this?
To make it, I got my hands punctured. But you think it ugly.
Well, I won't give you.
Though it's ugly, I like it.
Changge.
Where are you?
Have you seen the woman in the portrait?
No.
- Have you seen this woman?
- No.
Have you seen the woman in the portrait?
No.
- Have you seen her?
- No.
- Have you?
They want to catch me.
You! Stop!
Stop!
Go!
You lost money. But why do you follow me?
- They want to catch me.
- What crime have you committed?
Nothing. They said I impersonate Princess.
You'd better impersonate anyone else.
Miss. Are you a fool?
I don't impersonate Princess. I'm really...
Open the door!
I'm coming! Will you compensate if the door is broken?
It's daytime. Why are you in a hurry?
Do you want to buy cloth?
We're arresting a girl. We saw her walking down the street.
Have you seen her?
The girl in the portrait.
Yes.
The girl's purse was stolen in the street before.
She ran south after the thief.
Sir. What crime has she committed?
Hope she's not an infamous robber. It's been very restless here.
Search!
Sir! Sir!
- What's the matter?
- No idea.
What is happening?
- Not here.
Not there.
Sir, I've told you that she's not here.
My workshop should do business.
You search everywhere, and the impact is bad.
Come on. Inform us if you see her next time.
Of course.
Go.
You're so clever that you hid in the tank.
Thank you, Miss.  I thought you don't want to save me.
Come on. I think you're innocent.
The government really makes a fuss of it.
It's nothing serious to impersonate Princess.
Miss. I don't impersonate Princess. I'm really Princess.
Come on. I don't care whether you're a princess or a master.
I'm busy now. You should leave now.
Miss. If I go out now, I'll be killed.
Please do me a favor. Allow me to stay here one more day. I beg you.
OK. Go in and change your clothes.
Don't get ill and stay here for a long time.
Thank you, Miss.
It's grassland.
So vast.
Ms. Su Yili. Do you have any cheese?
- Leave a bit more for me.
- Yes!
Come to my tent later. You'll eat as much as you can.
Tegin! Have you prepared gifts for us?
Yes. Everyone can get a gift.
Yaro.
Tegin. The herbs are all dried. Here you are.
How about them?
Good.
- Tegin.
- Look.
Help yourselves.
- Gift!  - I want this!
This one is good.
- Look!
- Let me see.
Second Uncle! Where's my award?
- Where's my award?
Stand still! Stand still! Stand sill and close your eyes!
Close your eyes!
Where's mine, uncle? Where's mine?
I have only one little horse.
Try to reach it!
- Give me, dad!
- Give me!
Dad!
Second Uncle!
Dad, don't cheat me!
Dad!
Second Uncle!
Give me, Second Uncle! You promised me!
Let me help you.
Good.
Interesting!
Since you're good at playing football, here you are.
Bro! Could you lend your ball?
Here you are.
- Stop!
- Let's go.
Wait!
Slow down!
- Give me!
- No!
I'll bring the gifts to them. Be careful.
Help him carry the gifts.
The monthly salary this year is too low.
Ms. Zhang, don't be too greedy.
At least we have a job to keep from starving.
That's good.
Yes, you're right. Are the looms more and more difficult to use?
Yes.
Ms. Chai. You've finally hired a new weaver.
I picked her in the street. She just stay here for a night.
Nice to meet you.
Stop looking around! Go on with your work!
What a pretty girl!
What etiquette did she show?
I don't know. It looks good.
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
No. Like this.
No. Just like her!
Just share this room with others.
You have to leave tomorrow. I don't raise idlers.
Thanks, Miss. I'll repay you one day.
Thank you in advance.
What should I do tomorrow?
Magistrate, what did you say just now?
I'm sorry.
We found her but failed to take her back.
You'd better say you failed to find her. What do you mean by that?
We saw a similar woman in the street.
But... She ran away.
What similar woman? Why did she just run away?
Mr. Hao. I'll make further research.
But Princess has feet.
I'm not sure whether she's still in Yunzhou.
How dare you shirk responsibility!
Well. We'll keep searching her.
- I'll search her tomorrow! Get lost!
OK.
Yan.
Where are you?
Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad