Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 17
Your Highness.
Hao Du sent a message,
saying that Princess Yongning used Li Shisi as the alias name
and assisted the governor Gongsun Heng in Shuozhou
to protect the city from enemies' attack.
After Shuozhou was conquered,
Princess Yongning got caught by Ashile Tribe.
Hao Du sent someone following them.
And the scout saw it himself, that Princess Yongning
was executed by people of Ashile Tribe.
[Weaving Workshop of Western Suburb]
Wake up!
It's so late now. And you're still sleeping!
Get up now!
Don't you know how late it is?
Look at you...
Miss.
After finishing breakfast, leave here immediately.
About your case, I can't afford the responsibility.
Ms. Chai.
I... I... dare not go out.
How about... how about letting me stay here?
I can do any work.
You said that you'd leave in one day.
Why are you just hanging on here now?
No way.
Leave here after finishing your meal.
Ms. Chai.
I will return to Changan.
In several days, I'll definitely leave here.
I can do any work. I mean it.
Have you done any work before?
But I know embroidery.
Embroidery?
Like the pouch you embroidered?
That's the ugliest pouch I've ever seen.
With such level of embroidery,
my weaving workshop has to close someday.
No. Not like that.
Ms. Chai.
That pouch... That pouch was embroidered by my best friend.
I really know how to embroider.
You look delicate.
I don't think you did any heavy work before.
I have to warn you.
Though you can stay here,
you won't be paid much.
Enjoy your meal.
[Virtue Brings Fortune]
Please pause for a second.
I have something to announce.
Let me introduce.
This miss is...
Li Leyan.
From now on, she'll work with you.
Yesterday, didn't you say that she'd stay for only one day?
I'm in a good mood today.
Can't I keep her?
Surely you can.
But she can't know how to work, according to her appearance.
You can employ anyone but her.
I want to employ her, because her salary is low.
I'd love to.
Well.
She hasn't done any work before.
Please help her a little bit.
OK. That's it.
Come.
Let's go. Continue working.
Ms. Wei.
From now on, she's your apprentice.
This miss will learn from you.
Please teach her by heart.
Learn it by heart.
OK. I'll teach her.
This is shuttle.
And this is thread.
Put your feet here.
Go through it. Like this.
Then you step on it.
Understand?
Tegin, the list of spoils in Shuozhou has been sorted.
Should I send it to Khan's Tent?
Let several reliable men send it.
Yes.
You're not gonna send it on your own?
It's such an achievement.
And you don't show your loyalty in front of Great Khan.
Since he's very suspicious, he might think you wanna betray him.
I used to let others send it.
If I go there myself this time, he will get suspicious.
What are you doing here?
I have something to tell you.
You've seen it.
Sun doesn't want to talk to you.
- Just go.
- I can be your military counselor.
Now you're bragging.
I mean. Who are you?
Are you making decisions in Eagle Division?
Stop driving a wedge between Sun and me.
You...
Your reason?
Since I work for you, and mainly assistant you,
I have to do something useful.
I'm good at strategies.
That Tegin brought me here must be out of that reason.
Please allow me to be your assistant.
My defeated opponent.
You can really brag.
Tell me, why should I use a stranger like you as my assistant.
Actually, I've been thinking about a question.
Great Khan let Eagle Division be the pioneer to attack Shuozhou.
However, the army that Tegin led was not for attacking a city.
Besides, you haven't fought against Tang before.
Therefore, Great Khan seemed not to care about the result.
What's worse, he might want you to lose.
Nonsense!
Go on.
It reminds me of what was like in Shuozhou that day.
Eagle Division and Bear Division hindered each other.
And you were even competing in public.
If Bear Division wasn't supported by someone,
it's hard for him to do that.
After all, you're the adopted son of Great Khan.
What exactly are you trying to say?
So I guessed it correctly.
Tegin's position in Ashile Tribe
is way less solid than what others think about.
But you're the adopted son of Great Khan.
And you have an army.
I don't believe you want to do nothing.
I'm loyal to Great Khan.
Great Khan also trusts me.
You don't need to incite between us two.
About your words, does Great Khan believe it?
Do Great Khan's nephews believe that?
How did you know these things?
So, do you think I'm qualified to be your assistant?
What's your requirement?
I'll be your military counselor, and can realize three wishes for you.
However, you can't do harm to Tang.
And you can't do ruthless things.
When I finish the three tasks, please let me leave here.
Okay.
Sun!
From now on, you're no longer a slave.
But I won't help you, either.
You need to depend on your ability to survive here in Eagle Division.
When you finished three wishes, I would set you free.
After that,
if you still want to take revenge on me,
I'd wait for you.
Have you decided your three wishes?
Not yet.
But it's like making wishes.
The time when I decide it, you should realize it for me.
Okay. I accept that.
But just as what I said, you can't do harm to Tang.
And you can't do ruthless things.
These days, I'll depend on my own ability
to get a firm foothold here in Eagle Division.
Please wait for my performance, Tegin.
OK. Deal.
Unlock her iron chain.
[Weaving Workshop of Western Suburb]
Let's pause and have a rest.
You must feel tired.
I bought some pastries.
Everyone can eat.
Pastries?
- Pastries!
- Pastries.
Come here.
Come.
Thank you.
You all can enjoy it.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
- Ms. Chai.
Why are you so generous today?
- Right.
- Yeah.
You didn't even buy sesame cakes in normal days.
Did you get any order?
Right.
A businessman Mr. Hu ordered a batch of goods.
It's enough for us to spend for several months!
Really?
- Great!
- That's great.
So you have to work hard.
After finishing the pastries, continue working.
Okay. Let's go.
Continue working.
That's tasty.
Miss Li.
Have some pastries also.
You can do it later.
You're new here.
I don't have any expectation for you.
Whether you do it well or badly, it doesn't matter.
Ms. Chai.
If I do it badly, I can start over.
It doesn't matter.
Eat some pastries first.
You can do it later.
Li Leyan!
What have you done?
Look!
Look at it!
Did you see?
I'll do it again.
I'll start over.
No. No. Don't do it.
Please stop. Please.
Look at the thread on your head.
I...
That's...
Sun.
Great Khan is suddenly coming. And he's with Sher.
Great Khan never came here on his own initiative.
I suppose something big might happen.
Could it be about Shuozhou?
About Shuozhou,
it's me that made agreements secretly with Gongsun Heng.
You knew nothing.
It also has nothing to do with men in Eagle Division.
Understand?
What are you gonna do?
Since I accepted Gongsun Heng's offer,
I'd thought about things that would happen today.
I made the decision myself.
If Great Khan wants to blame us,
you only need to protect yourself.
Have you thought of a way to get yourself out of this?
No one can be totally sure about anything.
I'll do my best.
Prepare the list of spoils to welcome Great Khan.
Come.
You...
Li Shisi. Let me go.
Tell me what happened exactly.
I don't know.
Stop playing dumb.
What are you gonna do?
I wanna know the truth.
Pardoning Shuozhou was Sun's own decision.
Great Khan didn't know that.
If Great Khan were there, almost everyone in Shuozhou would die.
Though Sun looks indifferent and cold,
he's actually the most humane one.
He already knew it was you that led the army in Shuozhou.
About that arrow to you, he missed the target on purpose.
He even worried if he's too good at shooting.
And he kept asking me if you were fine.
Also, before taking you away from Shuozhou,
he posted that you tried to kill the leader of Ashile Tribe but failed
and have been executed and died for the people.
That was for your reputation as the Commandant of Shuozhou.
And you?
How did you treat him?
I don't wanna talk too much with you.
Great Khan comes here this time.
Sun did disobey Great Khan's order.
As for Sher.
He's Sun's sworn enemy.
If his plot works, Sun will be in danger.
I have to think of a way to save him.
Did Ashile Sun tell you how he would deal with that?
I don't know.
Greetings to Great Khan from Ashile Sun.
Stand up.
Father comes here on your own this time.
I wonder what your instruction is.
No need to be so serious.
Take a seat.
Yes.
Sun.
We two haven't seen each other for long.
I want to visit here out of whim.
Now Eagle Division is well trained and equipped.
Your people all look energetic.
That's good.
I feel relieved.
The prosperity in Ashile Tribe owes to father.
What Eagle Division depends on is also father's grace.
Sun, that's too modest for you to say that.
I dare not lie to you, father.
I've been hearing that Sun's the God of War here.
I thought that was boasting.
I didn't expect at the first battle between Eagle Division and Tang,
you successfully conquered Shuozhou within only ten days.
Sun, you're indeed the God of War.
Ashile Tribe is well known for its battle-wise soildiers.
It's natural that Eagle Division can conquer Shuozhou successfully.
Ashile Sun.
You're indeed good at the art of language.
But you seemed not to have told the truth.
What do you mean?
Shuozhou has been hard to conquer.
Uncle Khan has been attacking for years,
but still couldn't conquer it.
Why did they open the city gate for you once you were there?
Uncle Khan. Don't you think that's too strange?
Sher, tell me why it's strange.
Just be straightforward.
Great Khan has ordered that after conquering the city,
you have to eliminate all of the soldiers and supplies.
Shuozhou is the key place to the northern pass.
Only by so can we give Tang no chance to take a breath.
But I heard that after you conquered the city,
you not only held an elaborate funeral for Gongsun Heng,
but also pardoned everyone in the city.
Ashile Sun, is it because you're afraid of death
so that you want to betray us?
Sun. Is that true?
Right. I did give the order.
Uncle Khan, have you heard that?
He admitted that he betrayed you and Ashile Tribe.
Are you doubting my loyalty, father?
He already knew it was you that led the army in Shuozhou.
About that arrow to you, he missed the target on purpose.
He even worried if he's too good at shooting.
And he kept asking me if you were fine.
As for Sher, he's Sun's sworn enemy.
If his plot works, Sun will be in danger.
Though Ashile Sun didn't do exactly as what Great Khan ordered,
he won the battle at such a low price after all.
Anyway, that can't be a fault.
Great Khan came here on his own to inquire Sun.
There should be something more complicated.
What's that exactly?
Go get some water.
Yes.
If it weren't Young Khan that wanna make use of you,
I'd definitely beat you to death. Bastard Tang man.
You kept making the request.
Do you really think you're a big figure?
I'll kill you someday.
Tang man?
Why did Young Khan bring a Tang man here?
Something's wrong.
If I don't trust you,
I won't give you any chance to explain.
Thank you, father.
This is the letter that Gongsun Heng,
governor of Shuozhou, wrote to me.
Please have a check, father.
Gongsun Heng's been guarding the frontier for years.
Our tribe launched many attacks but was defeated by him.
We lost a lot.
[Tegin Sun...]
If I attacked Shuozhou by force, many of our men would die.
Gongsun Heng sued for peace this time.
He'd like to suicide for people's lives in that city.
When he died, big harm to our tribe would disappear,
and we can also win at the lowest price.
That's why I accepted his offer.
You even pardoned Tang's soldiers.
How can you explain that?
Most of soldiers in Shuozhou died.
There were only old and disabled soldiers left.
They can't attack at all.
If not so, Gongsun Heng wouldn't have the request.
He killed himself as promised and opened the city gate for us.
As the son of Great Khan, how could I break my promise?
Father, please pass judgment.
These are Gong Sunheng's head and the list of all spoils.
Please have a look, Great Khan.
Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Enough. No need to check it.
Sun. You were right.
The descendants born in the grasslands
have always been upright and magnanimous.
Gongsun Heng is a respectable opponent.
Just hold the funeral on behalf of me according to our etiquette.
Yes, father.
Sun.
I have another thing to ask you this time.
Nuer.
What are you doing?
Though you're not a slave now,
you still can't order me to do anything.
Nuer. You have to help me this time.
You're indeed not taking yourself as a stranger.
Listen, if you don't help me this time,
your Tegin and the whole Eagle Division would face a disaster.
Ashile Sun, if you admit it yourself,
I can still plead for you to Uncle Khan.
I don't know what you're talking about.
So you refuse to admit until you face the reality.
Uncle Khan, Ashile Sun colluded with Tang and harmed our tribe.
That's venomously slander!
When I was in Youzhou, I could almost succeed.
But Ashile Sun, you colluded the envoy of Tang
and let him take the army to assist.
Then Tang won back Youzhou again.
And my Wolf Division's effort was in vain.
You betrayed Great Khan and colluded with Tang.
Stop pretending to be loyal.
Sun, is that true?
I swear to God of Sirius, that it never happens.
Uncle Khan, there's a general betraying Tang.
He escaped on his way being sent to Changan.
And he's finally under my control.
He used to work for King of Lujiang, called Wang Junkuo.
Young Khan, you ruined things in Youzhou yourself.
And now you want to slander Tegin Sun.
What do you mean?
Mu Jin. Stop.
Ashile Sun, you must be familiar with him.
If you haven't done anything, dare you talk with him in person?
Uncle Khan,
my men of Wolf Division all died for nothing. That's unfair.
Guards.
- Bring the traitor here.
- Yes.
I might be insane that I'd follow you here.
You want to do it in front of Great Khan.
That's impossible.
Even Tegin Sun can't protect you.
I didn't say I'd do anything.
You won't do anything? You wanna win by just talking?
I indeed plan to win by talking.
Later I'll yell that Young Khan's horse is lost.
I'll keep away the guards.
You should finish the rest part.
What do you mean?
I'm just here helping you.
The man that Young Khan brought here was the General of Youzhou.
He met me before.
I can't go inside.
Only you can do this.
You...
Do you mean it?
I'll teach you how to do it.
Come here.
When you get in...
Will it work?
It's on you now.
Young Khan's horse's running away!
Young Khan's horse's running away! Get it!
Ashile Sun, have you well considered it?
If you admit your mistake now, maybe Uncle Khan would spare your life
considering your previous achievements.
When Wang Junkuo gets here and explains everything,
you won't feel easy by that time.
Even if you don't care about yourself,
you should think about Eagle Division.
Sun, as long as you can admit your mistake and explain yourself,
I'll forgive you.
I feel no shame.
I haven't done anything harmful to father.
Great Khan. The man is here.
Bring him in.
Greetings to Great Khan from Wang Junkuo.
Explain to me what happened in Youzhou.
Wang Junkuo.
Have you seen Ashile Sun in Youzhou?
Great Khan.
I don't have those things.
I gave the key to Young Khan.
Everything was done by Young Khan himself.
As for the loss of treasury, I think...
only Young Khan knows what happened.
Wang Junkuo.
What are you talking about?
Explain first what you have seen about Ashile Sun in Youzhou.
Please. Great Khan. It's true.
I want to work for you sincerely.
How would I dare occupy the treasury myself?
About those things... Young Khan must have them.
He has been following Tegin Sun.
I think he must want something from Sun.
Uncle Khan.
Ashile Sun, you conquered Shuozhou within ten days.
That was a great achievement.
You deserve a big award.
You can take half of the spoils of the war in Shuozhou.
Thank you, father.
Sun, you seem not to have enough people in your tent.
When I'm back, I'll carefully select several bondwomen for you
and send them to your tent.
Thanks a lot, father.
Sher.
Uncle Khan.
That's quite a 'good job' this time.
Uncle Khan, please allow me to explain.
I was so scared.
Well done.
How did you know about the treasury in Youzhou?
When Wang Junkuo heard that Young Khan
would say he secretly occupied the treasury in Youzhou,
he got panic instantly.
Then he didn't remember to slander Tegin Sun.
Actually Sher didn't occupy the treasury.
But Wang Junkuo knew nothing.
He had nothing, so he cherished his life very much.
He was afraid that Great Khan would think he stole the treasury,
that's why he said Sher did that.
Actually I just wanted to gamble.
I didn't expect that was quite a success.
It must be because Tegin is lucky, so we could win the bet.
Thanks to God of Sirius.
Military counselor. You're marvelous.
You saved not only Tegin, but also the whole Eagle Division.
I really admire you.
From now on, we're friends.
I knew you're here.
Every time when Great Khan did something to you due to Sher,
you'd stay here and say nothing.
What happened today,
wasn't solved by you, right?
What? You don't think I can do that?
Fine.
It was Li Shisi. He solved it.
He can think of different ideas and is good at using people's mind.
I don't know where he got the information
that the taboo here is secretly holding spoils.
That's why he could entrap Sher.
Thanks to my wisdom.
I told him everything about what you did in Shuozhou.
Otherwise he might not help you.
You...
Wait. What are you going?
Sun.
Roast lamb leg!
You asked Nuer to keep an eye on Li Shisi.
I think it's not gonna work.
What do you mean?
They live in the same tent.
And today they uncovered Sher's plot together.
Naturally their relationship would be better.
Look at Nuer.
He treats Li Shisi with food and wine.
Good wine.
You can really drink.
Mu Jin.
Arrange a single tent for Li Shisi.
OK.
I'll do it tomorrow.
Do it now.
Look at your eyes.
I want to arrange it tomorrow.
Never mind.
I don't care about your pettiness.
One more cup.
Cheers.
Really tasty.
Not bad, right?
Why are you here?
Newly roasted lamb leg. Wanna taste?
No.
Within only one day, you're already bribed by him.
Bribe?
Don't talk nonsense.
Well.
So you can't bear seeing me in harmony with your people?
It's not me that can't bear it, but someone else.
Pack up your things and follow me.
Where to?
Since you're the military counselor now, how can you live with Nuer?
Come.
I prepared a wide and good tent.
You must forget who you are,
getting drunk in such a little county government.
Isn't it humiliating?
I know.
You despise me.
You think I'm just an indecisive exalted man.
Without my father,
in your eyes, I might be even less than a magistrate.
Right?
I'm asking you. Yes or no?
You're drunk.
Let me tell you one more thing.
Actually Changge despises me as well.
Otherwise,
in all these years, can't she understand my feelings for her?
You're still thinking about Li Changge.
I thought you're worrying about Noble Princess.
I am worried.
I'm worried. I'm afraid.
I feel guilty for that.
Leyan is lost.
We haven't found her until now.
Changge is dead.
I didn't see her before she died.
I even despise myself.
Come. Sit here.
Drink with me.
So you don't wanna drink.
You always look so indifferent about everything.
Isn't it boring?
Have you been drunk before?
Have you felt heart-broken before?
Hao Du.
I feel sorry for you.
You're like a doll, a doll of... your adoptive father.
Wei Shuyu, if you dare talk any rubbish again, you won't be fine.
Hit me.
I wish you can beat me to death.
If I can't find Leyan, I feel ashamed to return to Changan,
and even more ashamed to meet my father.
[County Government in Yunzhou]
Mr. Wei. Good morning.
Have you found Noble Princess?
Not yet. But... Commander Hao has left.
What?
- He left?
- Right.
He said it's a waste of time to search together.
Better separately.
He left early in the morning.
Where did he go?
About that... I don't know.
Mr. Wei.
Mr. Wei!
Where are you going?
To look for Noble Princess, of course.
That's...
Greetings to your Majesty.
Wei. Get up.
We've known each other for long.
No need for that.
I dare not accept that kindness.
I need your assistance.
Your Majesty, I'll do whatever I can.
Come.
Your Majesty, I've already known what happened in Jingzhou.
Luo Yi has been good friends with Jiancheng.
The Tianjie Army he leads
has indeed contributed a lot to Tang all these years.
I knew that.
Wei, you don't want the royal court
to punish these meritorious officials, but now...
Your Majesty misunderstood me.
I'm not a stupid man caring only about personal feelings
but unaware of loyalty.
No. I just think
that you wouldn't want to see me
being ruthless to Luo Yi.
Quite the contrary.
After your Majesty was enthroned, everyone has been pardoned.
But Luo Yi ignored your Majesty's kindness and wanted to revolt.
Jingzhou is a key place to defend Ashile Tribe.
If your Majesty doesn't make a quick move
and eliminate Luo Yi and his Tianjie Army,
I'm afraid the turmoil happened in the late Sui Dynasty
would start again.
Besides, I've got some news
that the traitor Wang Junkuo flew to Ashile Tribe.
But he was killed by Ashile people for some reason.
Your Majesty can't hesitate now.
Wang Junkuo.
He was asking for an insult.
No one would feel sorry for his death.
After talking with you, I feel relieved now.
But... if Tianjie Army got defeated,
Ashile Tribe would definitely swoop in.
Could Tang be safe if your Majesty doesn't deal with Jingzhou?
Would Ashile Tribe stop attacking Tang if it's fine with Jingzhou?
Your Majesty, whether showing weakness or toughness
wouldn't let Ashile give up coveting Tang's territory.
I understand.
I'll ask General Yuchi to meet me now.
Please be assured, your Majesty.
Whatever it is, we'd stand behind your Majesty.
By the way, Mr. Wei Junior has been looking for Yan for days.
I think he must have suffered a lot.
I'll arrange more people to search for her.
Let him come back now.
I have another arrangement for him.
I also haven't heard from him for days.
I think he must feel embarrassed for not having found Noble Princess.
You were too strict with Shuyu.
Shuyu focuses only on searching for Yan,
which must be harmful to his health both mentally and physically.
Fang still needs a Supervisory Censor.
I've thought about it.
Shuyu is perfect for that.
Your Majesty. He's not proper to do it.
Shuyu often makes big mistakes.
It's already decided.
Your Majesty.
Thanks to your Majesty on behalf of Shuyu.
Li Leyan.
Do you have too much free time?
What are you doing?
I'm just doing it for fun.
You even have the time to do that?
Why didn't you put more strength in working?
I'll learn how to do it soon.
Just give me some more time.
When I was in the Palace, I didn't take charge of such things.
Palace?
Really? Palace?
She dreams of being a princess again.
Dear 'Princess', in the Palace, are they using gold shuttles to weave?
Miss, did your head get hit?
Or were you seriously ill?
Why do you keep talking nonsense?
Does she need to see a doctor?
We should ask Ms. Chai not to beat her head.
She's already so dumb.
I'll hand these bondwomen to you now.
As for the rest part, you should take care of it.
What's going on?
Bondwomen from Khan's Tent.
It's said to be the award for Tegin.
Tegin never keeps bondwoman in his tent.
Take them away.
How Great Khan treats Tegin is like giving sweets after slapping you.
That's a pity.
You can't tell if those are poisonous or not.
Things from Khan have always been difficult to deal with.
Keep an eye on them.
Don't let them wander.
Okay.
Mother.
Please turn back and look at me.
Please turn back... Please... Turn back and look at me.
Let me go!
Come.
Let go!
Let go of me!
Don't hide from us, beauty.
Drink with us two.
- Come.
- Let me go!
Good.
Stop.
Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad