[English subtitles are available]
[Moonlight]
[Episode 13]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox: Like Jiang Yu Cheng?
You girls like a phony man? ]
I sent a "yes"?
[The message above is unfinished.]
[It's yes and no.]
[I wish my destined one]
[could be a warm person]
[like Mr Jiang Yu Cheng.]
[But Mr Jiang Yu Cheng]
[is like a respectful senior to me.]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[I even want to bow
when talking to him.]
So,
she rejected Jiang Yu Cheng, right?
It won't do.
I'll try it again.
Hello.
Right,
my work is a trash and it's not
qualified for the selection.
Only the work of an old author like you
is qualified.
But
which book of yours is awarded
after winning Hong Ying Award?
I guess the old author like you
has been drained,
that's why they want
the young authors
like us to be the fillers.
Forget it.
I never thought
you were my father.
I won't be surprised
if you tell me
that I was adopted.
I wonder why
a person who never calls me
gave me a call all of a sudden.
So, it was Mr Xia told you that.
Are you afraid that
I'll embarrass the Zhou family
if my work is sent to
the selection of Huazhi Award?
Oh my god, Mr Zhou senior!
You're getting me
in trouble.
All right.
I know what to do then.
Gentleman, this is a toast to you.
Are you sleep walking?
I will only dare to flatter my mother
and secretly complain about her.
I really respect the one who dares to
fight face-to-face like you.
You should be ashamed
of eavesdropping.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
Don't waste your chance
because of your father.
I think you worry that
I might hold up on you.
Promise me to send your work to
Huazhi Award's selection for my sake.
Book of Luo He God
managed to sell well.
The honour and bonus
are all given
to the circulation department.
Miao and Liang Chong Lang
even grossed me out
with the figure 349,000.
I've been depressed
for a whole day by this matter.
As for Ah Xiang,
she has been editing the poster.
This deepens
her myopia.
And for Mr Xia,
he has a weak body,
but still insists to supervise
the progress of the project.
It breaks my heart
whenever I think about it.
Use your words.
Why are you crying?
I don't know why.
But I always want to cry lately.
Stop crying.
Probably because I think it's unfair.
Why does all the credit
go to the circulation department?
But there's nothing
for our editorial department.
I've seen your effort.
Just that I didn't get
a chance to say thank you.
I'm glad that
I'd signed Book of Luo He God
over to you.
Thank you.
Mr Zhou Chuan,
so you've seen my effort.
All right, don't cry.
Why do you cry over anything?
Aren't you usually
a domineering person?
Why are you crying so much recently?
Can I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
Can you send Book of Luo He God
to Huazhi Award's selection?
Okay.
I'll do as you wish.
I think you deserve
the most credit anyway.
I'll let you call the shots.
Thank you, Mr Zhou Chuan.
Don't mention it. Don't cry.
Cheers!
We didn't get a chance to celebrate
the great sale of
Book of Luo He God.
Congratulations on
becoming the top author!
Slow down!
Why are you more excited than me?
Because I'm happy.
Since your bonus is gone,
then just stay in my house.
Do you have only one bedding set?
Go and acquire one more set.
Are you going to pay for it?
You've just cried in my arms
this afternoon.
And now
you started to swindle me, right?
Of course.
Money is the most important thing.
The royalty on
Book of Luo He God that I got
is enough for you to
buy ten mattresses.
No, besides the mattress,
there're a lot of stuffs I want to buy.
For example, my new clothes,
new pillow,
and also a beanbag.
Then I just buy you a new house.
All right, stop drinking.
You're not allowed to
go out drinking as
you're a bad drinker.
I refuse.
You're not my boyfriend.
Why are you telling me what to do?
I tell you what. I'm a good drinker.
Give it back to me!
Give it back to me! Give it back to me!
♫ I want to hide like a kid
who made mistakes ♫
♫ My heart skipped a beat ♫
♫ When you look at me
everything seems so cute ♫
♫ I am the only one feeling strange ♫
♫ I have got a million whys ♫
♫ But I can't tell ♫
♫ I still have my sanity ♫
♫ I fled for a week ♫
♫ You don't seem to be surprised ♫
♫ Because when you look into my eyes ♫
♫ I have told you a thousand times ♫
♫ The world is on
the verge of elimination ♫
♫ Only you are still favoured by me ♫
♫ Because when you hold me in your arms ♫
♫ I have never felt so right ♫
♫ If this is not love ♫
♫ What can I tell myself ♫
♫ I have got a million whys ♫
How is it? Did you
sleep well last night?
Last night?
Nothing happened last night, right?
Probably...
Nothing happened, right?
Rest assured.
I'll take the responsibility
no matter what happened.
Then... I shall go to work first.
Oh my god!
What should I do?
Did something really happen?
He wants to be responsible for me?
What is that about?
What am I going
to explain to my father?
Chu Li, what's the matter?
You look awful.
Last night...
What happened last night?
Last night,
there's a friend of mine
and she was drunk.
Then?
Then an indescribable matter seemed to
have happened between her and a man.
Then?
Then I...
My friend doesn't know what to do.
Then does your friend
like the guy?
She seems
kind of
likes that guy.
Just ask your friend
try dating the guy.
It's not right.
That guy's best friend is pursuing her.
It's confusing.
Then who exactly
does your friend like?
Of course she likes...
Why didn't you answer
Mr Zhou Chuan's call?
Did she just hang up on me?
[When are you coming back?]
[I want to have hotpot tonight.]
[Zhou Chuan]
Hello.
The books are here?
All right, I'm coming.
Meeting in the conference room.
Let's go to the meeting.
Hurry up! Let's go to the meeting.
It doesn't feel right.
Who's her friend?
Isn't that me?
Yuan Yue's annual
Interactive Cultural Festival
between authors and readers
is coming soon.
Story relay event is held every year
to increase the interaction between
the journal and
Yuan Yue Publishing House.
Contact each author you handle.
Understood.
Chu Li,
have you heard me?
Yes, I heard you.
That's perfect. I have something to add.
What did she say?
Mr Liang suggests that
we can examine
the popularity of our authors
with this Interactive Culture Festival.
For those who have less popularity,
we will
cancel their serial stories
in Moonlight Magazine.
Do you mean
terminating the contract
with those authors?
Right, it's the survival
of the fittest.
It's very normal.
I think Mr Liang's suggestion
is reasonable.
I agree.
Did Director Yang agree with it?
Director Yang said
Yuan Yue is not a charitable institution.
In this Interactive Culture Festival,
please be sure to do
your best for each author
so that they could
perform at their best.
In this way, the editorial department
can have a clear conscience.
Chu Li, you have Zhou Chuan
and Jiang Yu Cheng these two geniuses.
What are you worried about?
I'm not worried about that.
They can't take advantage
of others like this.
They keep asking them to
write manuscripts without paying them.
How can they do that?
Listen to me.
You don't have to write 6,000 words.
Just 3,000 words are enough.
It's just the new pattern once a year.
Then I'll wait for
your starting article.
It's a deal, goodbye.
I forgot to tell Suo Heng
that she doesn't have
to write many versions.
I can't read that much.
Miao doesn't worry about
how the writing's going.
He doesn't care
if those unpopular authors get fired.
[Not Drama King, it's Saviour: When are you
coming back? I want to have hotpot tonight.]
[When are you coming back?]
[I want to have hotpot tonight.]
Why does he act
like nothing happened?
This is awkward.
This Stinky Monkey is indeed disloyal.
She already sneaked out to date
after only a few hours.
For this year's
Interactive Culture Festival,
my company asks every editor
to find our author to
create a story relay.
Mr Jiang, I'm begging you.
Okay, when do you need it?
Really?
Preferably within this week.
Mr Jiang, I'll never
forget your kindness.
I will never turn down your request.
But why didn't you ask Zhou Chuan?
Such activity without pay,
he will say that I'm insulting him
if I ask him to do it.
It's better for me not
to ask for trouble.
What is the activity?
But he'll know it
sooner or later.
And again he'll think that
you don't think much of him
if he finds out about this.
It's all right.
I already got used to it anyway.
You don't seem fine today.
Why are you avoiding whenever
we talk about Zhou Chuan?
Did something happen
between you two?
Am I? I'm not avoiding.
Nothing happened between us.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
What can happen between us?
Nothing happened.
Mr Jiang,
I'll leave first as I got work to do.
Come out, she didn't say anything.
How did you know I was here?
Look at your size,
you're like a groundhog,
sneaking around.
Do you think I'm blind?
I think you are.
This is so-called
James Bond's hiding skills.
Do you know that?
A cup of coffee, please.
I think you're more
like James the groundhog.
I wonder
what happened between you and Chu Li.
Normally, you'd have rushed in
if you saw us talking.
But today you were hiding instead.
Who's hiding?
I was standing there
to rest for a while.
Did you two
have a fight?
That's great!
What do you mean great?
Where are the books?
Thank you.
What exactly is the story of
Huang Quan Inn you wrote?
Why do you need many
ancient architecture books?
What is the theme?
You'll know once it's serialized.
I'm going.
Keep your aggressiveness
away from Chu Li.
[Little Monkey]
[Mr Zhou, I'm going to
work overtime today.]
[You and Er Gou are
on your own for dinner.]
Mr Zhou,
why are you still up this late hour?
[What is he trying to do?]
You didn't answer my call and
reply my WeChat message this whole day.
Are you purposely avoiding me?
I'm not.
I was just busy working.
Why didn't you
stay in the office then?
No place is more comfortable
than our own house.
Whose house are you saying?
My mistake.
I heard you're going to launch
an activity without any pay.
And you've asked
Jiang Yu Cheng for help.
Why didn't you ask me?
That is Interactive Culture Festival.
I'm thinking that we can
discuss about it
when I'm back home.
There's no need to discuss.
I agree.
Consider it as
the compensation for last night.
[This won't do, I must clarify it.]
Did I hug you
last night?
Or did I kiss you?
Don't tell me that...
You did nothing.
That's good.
I can pretend
that nothing had ever happened.
Then let's pretend
that nothing had happened.
I'm going to rest first.
Right.
You must help me in the activity.
Interesting.
Why are you looking at me?
I know.
I should've done
what I should last night.
Wasn't she drunk?
What can I do?
[Father]
Father,
I'm an unfilial child.
I've betrayed you.
It's not right.
What if I didn't do it?
Forget it.
Just pretend nothing had ever happened.
Right, nothing had happened.
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
Just pretend nothing had ever happened?
Then what exactly
had happened between them?
Did they hold hands?
Did they hug?
Did they kiss?
Don't tell me it was...
I've told you, nothing had happened!
Ah Xiang, Elephant,
stop asking me.
Chu Li,
I think your friend
is doing the right thing.
Perhaps that guy
doesn't really like your friend.
Ms Suo Heng.
Are you here for Miao?
Why don't you go up?
I...
Forget it, I'll come again next time.
Suo Heng.
Why did you come?
Deputy Editor Miao.
I've been thinking
about the start of
the Interactive Culture Festival
since you told me last time.
But all I can think
is only the historical themes.
But you said this kind of themes
is going to be outdated soon
so I'm very anxious.
I want to come and
ask your opinion.
Why did you come all the way here?
You just have to send me a message.
I think it's better to
communicate in person.
Because I don't really understand
what you're saying
on the phone or in the message.
I mean I have poor
understanding ability.
I need your guidance.
Look, why are you being humble?
Editors like us
should learn more from the authors.
Since you're here,
let's go upstairs and talk about it.
Meet you in the conference room.
Chu Li, get some water.
Follow me.
Here.
Suo Heng, here.
Have a seat.
Deputy Editor Miao,
tell me your suggestion.
All right.
You don't need to record it.
I'm here to get the ball rolling.
Just take it as a conversation,
a little chitchat.
Right, Suo Heng.
Have you watched Star Trek?
I've never watched it.
Suo Heng,
do you usually
have no hobbies?
My favourite hobby is writing.
Never mind.
No wonder
you can insist on writing for so long.
So, what my suggestion for you is
that I hope that you could
think out of the box.
To start with a science fiction theme.
You'll definitely come as a bombshell.
But I'm bad at writing
in science fiction.
It's not that hard, look.
You just have to watch a few movies.
And then read more
science fiction novels.
You had little contact with
humanities book too.
I think you're good at
writing in this genre now.
Actually, it was quite hard for me
to write in that genre.
I even forced myself to play games.
And I always got complaints
of being a bad player.
What if you write in the genre
that you're good at?
It's none of your business.
Are you in charge?
Or I just get out?
Deputy Editor Miao, have some water.
Look at her,
interrupting our conversation.
How rude.
I mean
you just have to write
2,000 to 3,000 words.
It's not like you have to
write 200,000 to 300,000 words,
right?
The deadline is on the day
after tomorrow. You can do it.
It's raining. Get the laundry.
Hurry up!
A clearance sale!
Six dollars for one catty!
Ten dollars for two catties!
Knowledge is power!
-Knowledge can change your faith!
-I'm sorry.
You're going to be rich soon!
Hurry up and come buy the books!
This is not buying, it's snapping up!
-Hurry up!
-Boss.
Do you have science fiction novel?
Yes, I do. I'll find it for you.
There are a few of them.
Science fiction
and...
[Clearance Sales]
[Golden Spears and Armoured Horses]
Golden Spears and Armoured Horses.
If you like histories,
this is a nice book.
This author is pretty cool.
This book is quite nice.
But the subsequent book is not
as good as the previous one.
The debut work got
the author to the peak.
But there's no news of the author now.
How is it? Do you like it?
I'm selling it for two dollars.
No, thank you.
Don't go.
I sell it for 50 cents.
There're many other books, pick some!
You're not going to work
overtime this weekend, right?
Let's go and buy two beanbags.
What's wrong? Who made you angry?
Don't start it.
Today, Miao asked one of his authors
to write in the genre
which she is bad at.
What does that have to do with you?
That author is Suo Heng.
I've read her Golden Spears
and Armoured Horses.
She is suitable in
writing historical novel.
Asking her to write science fiction,
isn't that ruining her career?
Then
did she agree?
It looked like she didn't reject him.
She asked for it.
If you have the time to feel aggrieved,
you might as well prepare the dinner.
Do you have compassion?
She chose to compromise.
Do I still have to show my compassion?
There're many authors
like her in this world.
You can find them everywhere.
Do you think every author could
write the stories they like?
To earn a living,
they will give up on
what they insisted.
For this kind of author,
I advise you to mind your own business.
Ms Suo Heng, is your hand all right?
I'm fine. It comes from years of writing.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Wait a little longer,
Miao will be here soon.
I have to go.
Here, did you write it?
Let me take a look.
You're done for now. Get out.
Deputy Editor Miao,
I was cramming last night.
I watched dozens
science fiction movies.
And I wrote three
introductions in total.
I'm more confident
about the first one.
About the third introduction,
I personally think that
there's some problem on the setting,
it's not clear enough.
In these few introductions of yours,
I think
the third one is the best.
The third one?
The third one.
This one, look.
In these three introductions of yours,
as for the first one,
it is a historical plot
which is cloaked in science fiction.
You're skilled at writing
in historical theme, it is common.
The readers are used to it.
As for the second one,
it's just a historical theme.
This is already outdated.
The young readers
are not interested in this.
As for the third one...
Look, it's really eye-catching.
Look at this.
The Eighth Universe...
This... This... This...
The Husky Planet...
The story about the fallen
of the youngest great man...
It's
the Watt Empire of the Husgy Planet.
Is it Husgy?
Look, I've mistaken.
Right, it's the Husgy Planet.
The youngest great man
in the Watt Empire
is going to fall.
Look at this introduction,
it caught my eyes.
But I think the third introduction
is too fanciful.
There's a few conversion
rules of the universe
that I haven't set clear.
Didn't I tell you that?
You don't have to think about it.
Let the readers think.
But I'm afraid the readers
can't understand.
It's not possible.
Right.
It's alright that they can't understand.
Just think this way.
The more odd it is,
the more serious they will read it.
There're many young readers,
they will think
that only they can understand it.
It's good.
Speed is the soldier's asset.
This...
I'll take this and
proofread it right away.
This...
Suo Heng,
you are always the benchmark
of Yuan Yue Publishing House
and the first person to
hand in the manuscript.
This time, there's no exception too.
Good, you deserve the encouragement.
Keep going.
This is for you.
Apply it for 15 to 20 minutes.
It helps the circulation
to reduce the pain.
If you haven't consulted doctor,
you can go to the hospital
to have a check-up.
You can only keep writing
if you have a healthy body.
Thank you, Chu Li.
Then I'll off to work first.
Chu Li.
Ms Suo Heng.
I've told you not to call me "Miss".
I'm here to return your warm pouch.
Thank you.
Never mind.
I think your hand's condition
is quite bad.
Maybe you should see a doctor
after submitting the manuscripts.
It's fine. I'll go
after finishing the next serial.
Suo Heng, wait.
Are you going to the club's gathering?
I'm not going.
I'm busy. I'll leave first.
Suo Heng.
There's an old injury on your hand.
Don't go all out when writing.
Hello.
Honey.
I can't attend Qiu Qiu's sports day.
I have something to do.
[Golden Spears and Armoured Horses]
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
My advice is,
for the resume of the authors...
Chief Editor Yu,
you don't seem to get enough rest.
Did something happen at your home?
You've received the manuscripts
for the Interactive Culture Festival.
The next step is to
take care of the page layout.
Mr Xia takes the Interactive
Culture Festival very seriously.
Because it's not only a chance for
the readers and authors to interact,
it's also a traditional activity for us
to discover new talent.
So, work hard
in the following month.
Rest assured, Chief Editor Yu.
Chu Li,
you're here.
Chief Editor Yu is asking
for your typography.
This introduction of Ms Suo Heng
is much worse than
the previous version I read.
Ms Suo Heng usually
will write several introductions
for Miao to choose.
This must be chosen by Miao.
It started with a large framework of
science fiction in the current version.
The begin of a war,
the federal and empire,
the fallen of the youngest great man.
It's too complicated.
Perhaps man
likes this concept more.
Other authors are trying to make
the introduction as simple as they could.
What Nian Nian writes
is a sweet article.
The dog of the male lead passed away.
and come back as a human to repay him.
Even Mr Zhou Chuan wrote
a sweet story
so that the readers from
various levels can continue writing it.
Only Ms Suo Heng
takes the opposite track.
I don't understand why
Miao asked her to write
this kind of introduction.
I have no idea too.
Perhaps Miao wants to give up on her.
Go now.
Chief Editor Yu is calling for you.
♫ Dream flies above the horizon ♫
The weather forecast nowadays
is becoming inaccurate.
It said to be clear turning to cloudy.
♫ Night asks for dawn to come ♫
I guess
it's going to rain heavily.
The store will be overcrowded
during off hours.
♫ Yet I'm still here ♫
They come to get a shelter
as they didn't bring umbrella.
♫ Waiting for a mapless journey ♫
Xiao Bai, I'm going out.
Look after the store.
Okay.
♫ The stillness you stirred ♫
♫ Fear is forgotten and
so is that time on the rooftop ♫
♫ Every footprint turns into
a stubborn silhouette ♫
It's pouring rain.
I wonder if she brings the umbrella.
♫ Nobody wants to be the first
to let their heart sway ♫
It's pouring rain.
Did you bring the umbrella?
♫ The wind quietly brought in a letter ♫
Am I being too blunt?
♫ It tells that meetings and partings ♫
♫ Are to carry on the eternal light ♫
Don't work overtime,
come back and cook chicken broth.
♫ Glaring thoughts should not be heard ♫
[Zhou Chuan]
This is just right.
♫ Hide in a corner away from the light ♫
♫ Waiting for you to come ♫
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
[Not Drama King, it's Saviour: Don't work
overtime, come back and cook chicken broth.]
Cook chicken broth?
I'm getting drenched.
♫ I'm willing to make an eternal promise ♫
Chu Li,
why haven't you left?
Let me take you home
as it's raining heavily.
♫ Be the rotating star ♫
It's alright.
The bus stop and the subway station
are in different directions.
♫ Changing the life
from gloomy to crystal-clear ♫
Hurry up and go home.
-But out there...
-No "but".
You'll miss the bus.
Go!
All right.
Then I'm off.
-Goodbye.
Chu Li.
Mr Jiang?
How can you rush out
while it's raining heavily?
Aren't you afraid of catching cold?
I thought I can run to
the subway station
as it's close by.
Mr Jiang, what are you doing here?
Of course I'm here to pick you up.
Let's go. I'll take you home.
-Thank you, Mr Jiang.
-Let's go.
Has Stinky Monkey already left?
Jiang Yu Cheng!
What a coincidence!
Lucky that I meet you guys.
I didn't bring my umbrella.
Is that a coincidence?
Isn't Yuan Yue Publishing house nearby?
Yes.
I went to your bookstore
to get some books.
Where are the books?
I didn't get them.
Then I should ask Xiao Bai
why he didn't prepare the books.
I didn't get a chance to go there.
Didn't you come from
the direction of the bookstore?
Keep your mouth shut.
Don't tell me
you're here to pick Chu Li up.
Are you a dumb?
Why didn't I bring umbrella
if I was here to pick someone up?
Am I a fool?
I don't see you get drenched.
I...
I run fast.
He came from
the direction of the bookstore
and he didn't take any book.
Could he be...
Why are you sneaking around
at my door?
The hair dryer in my room is broken.
I want to ask if you can lend me yours.
Okay, hold on.
Why are you standing there?
Do you want me to teach you
how to use the hair dryer?
No.
Well, I'm going back to my room.
Wait.
You don't have to
return the hair dryer.
Everything you use will be broken.
I wonder
how your parents raised you.
Good night.
Are you
in love with me?