[English subtitles are available]
[Moonlight]
[Episode 14]
Good night.
Do
you like me?
How can I possibly like you?
I don't even think of you as a woman.
Why are you doing this then?
Don't tell me that to you,
I am the same as Er Gou.
That's right, you are
no different from Er Gou to me.
Why did you come out?
That was scary.
Luckily, I was sharp.
I am like Er Gou to him?
Will Er Gou clean his house, make dinner,
or read his manuscript for him?
What was I thinking?
I actually thought that he liked me.
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[I must be out of my mind
after being rained on.]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[Forget it, don't mind me.]
Tang, set up the venue first.
I will be late.
Can't he give me a hand?
Mr Jiang.
Jiang Yu Cheng, it's you again.
Did you put a tracker on me?
You are everywhere.
I am everywhere?
You are letting a girl carrying
so many stuff by herself.
Shouldn't you get yourself checked to see
if there is something
wrong with your body?
Like muscular weakness
or something like that.
What are you laughing about?
These are my stuff.
By the way, don't forget the...
So, it's your stuff.
I thought it's Chu Li's.
It's mine indeed.
What is hers is mine.
She is mine too.
I mean she is my editor.
So, you do know that she is your editor,
not your maid.
Is that any of your business?
I just can't stand the way
you treat the girl I'm courting.
The girl you are courting?
Save it for after she says yes.
Let's go.
Mr Jiang, see you next time.
Mr Liu.
It's been a long time. How are you?
How's your book coming along?
Mr Wang, happy married life!
Why didn't you invite me? Congratulations.
Thank you.
What are you guys talking about?
You seem to have a great time.
-Mr Wang,
-Have some food.
I have read your new book.
I am not hungry.
It is brilliant.
There is a part in
which I particularly like.
What gave you the inspiration?
Are you leaving soon?
Happy married life!
Thank you.
Isn't that Jiang Yu Cheng?
Jiang Yu Cheng is here.
Aren't he on bad terms
with Gu Bai Zhi?
Why is he still attending
our Xin Dun Books' event?
I thought you weren't coming.
You know nothing.
That's old love.
Hello, Mr Jiang.
Hello.
Hold on.
I need to go the airport now.
When I return from France,
I want to talk to you.
We will see.
Bai Zhi.
I'd better get going.
Talk to other experienced
writers and learn from them.
Don't mess it up.
Don't worry.
When you return,
I will pick you up at the airport.
Focus on your book.
Let's talk inside, come on.
Let's go.
I heard that Yuan Yue Publishing House
is holding
some kind of
interactive cultural festival.
Isn't that some outdated stuff?
Exactly.
Gu Bai Zhi is working for Xin Dun Books.
I have a friend who really
wants to get signed to her.
Is your friend man or woman?
Woman.
Woman? It's not going to happen.
Let me tell you, Gu Bai Zhi
only signs male writer,
especially young and handsome man.
No way.
Seriously?
Seriously.
You know Yun Fei, right?
She made him famous.
I heard that
they are secretly dating now.
That's why she is working
so hard to make him famous.
Her parachute appointment
in Xin Dun Books,
do you know anything about it?
I do know a little bit about it.
Their company has
a president surnamed Luo.
He admires her.
Why else would she be
able to stay in the company
after she missed out on Zhou Chuan
and Jiang Yu Cheng's new book?
There might be something
going on between them.
What nonsense are you talking about?
Say it again if you dare.
Who are you?
Do you believe that I can sue you
for defamation and bankrupt you?
I will call the cops now.
I will sue you for
physically threatening me.
Excuse me,
I tripped.
You know,
about Bai Zhi,
I know exactly what kind of person she is.
Parachute appointment?
She has got connections?
Those are nonsense.
I know that it has been tough
for her in the company.
When she signed me
back then,
no one
read my stupid book
I could barely afford food at that time.
Bai Zhi,
she rented a house for me,
she even hired a maid for me.
So that I could focus
and write something out.
So, my new book this time,
it has to be a hit.
She will continue to have a rough time
until I get famous, you know?
Do you know why is she going to
France this time?
She is going to see Maurer.
To sign his new book.
If she fails this time,
she will have to leave Xin Dun Books.
Do you know that?
She never told me.
That's because you don't care about her.
Mr Jiang,
if you don't like her,
convince her to give up.
We have broken up a long time ago.
But she still loves you.
Can you stop getting her hopes up?
I don't want to see
her keep being like this.
Because I really,
really like her.
Don't you have food at your house?
Why did you have to come here to eat?
If Chu Li hadn't invited me here,
I wouldn't have wanted to come too.
It's good to hear that.
The door is right there, go ahead.
He is not going anywhere.
Mr Jiang is my guest.
This is my house.
Yes! This is your house.
And I am just a pet in your house.
I don't deserve to invite
a friend over for breakfast.
I never...
I never said something like that.
You offended her?
Given your intelligence,
you wouldn't have realized it
even if you really offended her.
I really didn't.
Mr Jiang,
thank you for your help for
the Interactive Cultural Festival.
You wrote the openings for me.
You are welcome.
You made all of these?
Yes, I made all of these.
Eat up.
Okay.
This is yours.
I wrote the openings too.
Why do I get only a bowl of peanuts?
Why are you staring at me?
I said nothing wrong.
Why does he get a luxurious breakfast
while I get this
beggar set meal?
Beggar set meal?
A beggar wouldn't be called a beggar,
if he could eat so well.
Mr Jiang, it's too noisy here.
Why don't I take you out to eat?
Sure.
Let's go.
What are you guys trying to do?
Oh I know.
You guys are leaving me behind so that
you don't have to share the food.
Mr Zhou, all these dishes
on the table are now yours.
Don't be so ungrateful.
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[How are you today?]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[I am feeling great.]
[Zhou Chuan]
[didn't piss you off?]
Are you in a bad mood?
No.
Looks like you don't
consider me a friend either
No, no, Mr Jiang.
Fine,
it's true that I am in a bad mood today.
Zhou Chuan that...
Zhou Chuan actually said that
to him, I am no different from Er Gou.
That does sound like
something he would say.
Right? No one can feel good
after hearing those words.
I am in a difficult spot right now.
As your friend,
I should enlighten you at time like this.
But as a man who is courting you,
if I say something good
about another man now,
doesn't that make me uncommitted?
Mr Jiang, stop teasing me.
Do I look like I'm not serious?
Very much so.
I think
if what Zhou Chuan said
upsets you,
my advice is tell him directly.
Otherwise, a single-celled
living being like him
may never realize that
he had said something wrong.
What he said wasn't exactly wrong.
I can't mandate that what place
I must have in his heart.
From what you've said,
if I didn't know
the one you like is Mr Fox,
I would have thought you like Zhou Chuan.
How's...
How's that possible?
How can I possibly like him?
[Submissions]
Is this all?
There isn't even one to Ms Suo Heng.
Morning, Chu Li.
Morning.
Let me look at the submissions.
Half of the submissions are to
Zhou Chuan and Jiang Yu Cheng.
You are awesome, Chu Li.
What does this have
anything to do with me?
It's all thanks to them.
But there were only about 60 submissions.
That's a lot less than
what I thought it would be.
What do you mean by only?
Do you know how many
we received last year?
We received only a total
of 135 submissions last year.
So, based on what you said,
this number is actually a miracle?
Yes.
Speaking of which,
I heard that Xin Dun Books
has released a new app.
Enormous amount of fan fictions
were uploaded to the app.
Why do we only receive a few?
Morning.
Morning, Chief Editor Yu.
Online platforms Xin Dun Books and Wen Hai
are dominating the
entire content industry.
The fact that Yuan Yue still has
so many enthusiastic readers
that keep us in mind,
that's good enough for me.
How many submissions for
Suo Heng's work did we receive today?
[That's one awkward question to answer.]
Just a few,
and the qualities aren't great.
We can't publish it on Moonlight Magazine.
But it's okay,
this is only the first day.
It will get better.
Let's be patient.
Okay, get on with your work.
Now this is what Huang Quan Inn
should look like.
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[Hello?]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[He didn't.]
[He did nothing wrong.]
[I just feel that I should know my place]
[since I am living in his house.]
Hello, where are you?
I will come and see you now.
Do you know what's on
Stinky Monkey's mind?
Have you fallen so low that you
are now seeking relationship advice
from your love rival?
You are not my love rival.
I just can't stand
her attitude towards me.
I didn't do anything to offend her.
What is she angry about?
What do you think?
She said I thought of her
as a pet this morning.
Is it because I said
she's no different from Er Gou?
But that's just anthropomorphic metaphor.
You understand that, right?
I am talking about Er Gou.
Other than my mum, you,
Er Gou holds the third place in my heart.
The most important presence to me.
Take your time to figure it out.
Do you know anything or not?
Lend me your car.
Don't you have a car yourself?
Why do you need my car?
I am going to drive your car
and pick up Chu Li from work tonight.
Don't follow us, can you do that?
No.
Do you want the answer or not?
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
Mr Jiang, what are you doing here?
Isn't this Mr Zhou Chuan's car?
Yes, I'm going to take you for a spin
and do an experiment.
It's about the ending.
Come on, get in.
How long does it take?
30 minutes.
Mr Jiang, what experiment is this?
There is an escape plot in the ending.
I want to see how long it takes
for the male lead to
escape with his girlfriend
in a high horsepower car
without breaking any traffic rules.
So, what do you think about the result?
It's too slow, it's ten minutes too slow.
In this case, the male lead
is bound to be caught.
It seems I have to
write in a different way.
Such a pity.
You have wasted a lot
of brain cells for nothing.
But I get to take a ride with you,
and we get to
watch the sunset by the river.
It's beautiful.
Mr Jiang, why do you keep staring at me?
I just feel
very relaxed when I am with you.
Who do you get nervous around?
Let me take you home.
It's fine, I have to go back to
the office to work overtime.
You are going back to the office to work?
I have kept you for so long,
is there anything I can do to help?
It's fine.
All you need to do is write the ending
and submit without any delays.
Look at the time now,
why isn't she back yet?
Not only did he take away my girl,
he even took my car this time.
What are you barking at?
This is your fault.
Go back to your room.
♫ Dream flies above the horizon ♫
♫ Night asks for dawn to come ♫
♫ Yet I'm still here ♫
Follow-up for Book of Luo He God.
♫ Waiting for a mapless journey ♫
Author name.
The Ghost Behind You.
♫ The stillness you stirred ♫
♫ Fear is forgotten and
so is that time on the rooftop ♫
♫ Every footprint turns into
a stubborn silhouette ♫
♫ Nobody wants to be the first
to let their heart sway ♫
Kids nowadays,
their pseudonyms are just shocking.
♫ The wind quietly brought in a letter ♫
♫ It tells that meetings and partings ♫
Among this thick pile of works,
this is the only one
that is interesting.
♫ Are to carry on the eternal light ♫
♫ Glaring thoughts should not be heard ♫
♫ Hide in a corner away from the light ♫
♫ Waiting for you to come ♫
♫ Love is a variation ♫
♫ Occasionally melancholy,
occasionally full of bliss ♫
I am going back to my room.
♫ I once looked up and
the rain stopped filling the sky ♫
Take Er Gou to bed.
I don't think of you as Er Gou.
♫ Because you sheltered my tears ♫
Have you ever seen me tucking in Er Gou?
♫ The wind quietly brought in a letter ♫
Have you seen me waiting
for it until 3:00 in the morning?
♫ It tells that meetings and partings ♫
Because Er Gou is more
well-behaved than you.
♫ Are to carry on the eternal light ♫
At least it knows it
shouldn't be home this late.
♫ Glaring thoughts should not be heard ♫
I am going to sleep.
♫ Hide in a corner away from the light ♫
♫ Waiting for you to come ♫
Seriously?
Your friend forgave him just like that?
What else can she do?
Chu Li,
your friend might be falling deep in it.
No way.
Think about it,
her joys and sorrows change
because of what he said.
That's love.
Sounds like you got a point.
Ah Xiang,
you know so much about love.
Haven't you been single all your life?
I learnt these from dramas.
Second section of editorial department,
meeting in the conference room now.
What is the status of
the submissions for the week?
In seven days,
we received a total of 335 submissions.
105 follow-up fan fictions based
on Mr Zhou Chuan's works.
92 for Mr Jiang Yu Cheng's works.
79 for Mr He Ma's works.
54 for Mr Nian Nian's works.
And Ms Suo Heng
only got 5.
Are you sure you've sorted
through all the replies?
So far, yes.
So few.
Quantity is not good enough,
what about quality?
Basically unusable.
Keep this from the author first.
Miao, you are responsible for Suo Heng.
Is there anything you can do?
What solution can I come up with?
I have tried everything I can.
Is that so?
What have you tried? Tell me.
When she didn't write well, I got
someone to pick up where she left off.
But her openings are too intricate.
No one can pick it up.
You chose this piece yourself, didn't you?
How come you didn't
realize this issue before?
What do you think?
That's because her other articles
are not as good as this one.
That can't be.
I have read Ms Suo Heng's other articles,
they are much better to pick up than this.
That's your own opinion.
Have you read more articles
than I have?
Chief Editor Yu,
can we use another article
written by Ms Suo Heng?
Sure.
Didn't we hold this event for Suo Heng?
Because Suo Heng can't write well,
we had to get someone to write for her.
When no one is capable
of writing for her,
we just change to another article.
Right, looks like
Yuan Yue Publishing House
is opening only for Suo Heng.
Are we giving up on
the author just like this?
So what else can we do
if we don't give up on her?
Can she bring any value to
Yuan Yue Publishing House now?
That's enough.
The quality and quantity of submissions
are not up to standard,
it's not only the author's problem,
we editors are also responsible.
Miao, I don't care if
the selection of this article
was a mistake,
but we are having a problem now,
and you have to take care of it.
Please keep in mind that
authors and editors are tied together.
You rise or fall together.
Find a few tight-lipped authors
to help write the follow-up.
We can't afford to have any problem.
Meeting adjourned.
Chu Li,
since you care about Suo Heng so much,
why don't you get
someone to write for her?
Fine, I will do it.
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
Mr Cao,
for this year's
Interactive Culture Festival,
I'd like your help in writing a follow-up
for a science fiction's openings.
You are the best at science fiction.
Yes.
But you only have three days.
Thank you for your help.
Okay, okay.
Bye, bye.
Mum, Dad and I are here
to pick you up from work.
I am here.
Qiu Qiu, thank you for you and
Dad to come pick me up.
I didn't drive here today.
I was just thinking about
hailing a cab home.
I knew you would get off late from work.
By the way, my mom's
birthday is coming soon.
I want to gather the family
to have a meal together by then.
Don't forget it.
I won't forget her birthday.
I have got her gift.
Mum, let me tell you a secret,
I have prepared a gift for Grandma too.
Really? You have really grown up, Qiu Qiu.
The results of
the submissions came out today.
Mr Zhou, would you like to guess
how many submissions have you got?
No, it's predicable.
105 submissions in total.
105?
Is that many?
Yuan Yue Publishing House
is out of date indeed.
Don't you dare insult
Yuan Yue Publishing House.
How many have Jiang Yu Cheng received?
Less than me?
So,
what exactly is
the ranking of submissions?
Did Jiang Yu Cheng receive
much lesser submissions than me?
Only the author can know
the number of submissions for his article.
Other people is not allowed to know.
I am other people?
Especially certain people
with bad intentions.
Now I am other people.
Who begged to be
my managing editor back then?
We are all on the same team.
Don't you forget that
even though I am managing editor
of Book of Luo He God,
but I am also the managing editor of
Mr Jiang's
The Disappearing Amusement Park.
So,
how many submissions does
Jiang Yu Cheng actually receive?
If you sign your new novel
to Yuan Yue Publishing House,
I can consider that I will
only have eyes for you
in future.
Very tactical, you.
Tell me then.
Are there authors who receive submissions
so little that that can be
counted on one hand?
Mr Zhou, since you care
so much about your peers,
will you consider writing a follow-up
for author who receive
poor quality submissions?
Who is it?
Just tell me will you do it or not?
There is no way I would
be a ghostwriter for others.
Move, move, get out of my way.
You think I can't find out
about it if you don't tell me?
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[How's work these days?]
[Have you been busy?]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[The interactive activity launched by]
[your publishing agency
seems quite interesting.]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[I heard that
the submission is closing soon.]
[Do you think my work will
get picked if I participate?]
[Is it competitive?]
[Tell me some inside information now.]
[I'm not in the industry anyway.]
[I won't be able to tell anyone else.]
What are the odds of this happening?
How come both of them
are prying about this?
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[Which author do you want to write for?]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[Every author's works seem fine to me.]
[Which one do you think I should pick?]
[I have trouble in decision making.]
[This is great.]
[Write a follow-up]
[for Suo Heng's openings.]
[Just send it to me after you are done.]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[Actually, I have seen]
[another better openings written by her.]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[If back then...]
[Forget it.]
[Can you finish it and send it
to me as soon as possible?]
So, it's Suo Heng.
The editor in charge
is not taking responsibility.
While the editor who is not in charge
is fussing around it.
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[Best friends have each other's back,
I will help you.]
Mr Zhou, help me set the table.
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[You haven't told me about
the results of the submission.]
[I bet Zhou Chuan receives the
highest number of submissions,]
[am I right?]
[That look on his face,]
[it's so tender.]
Hello, Gu Bai Zhi.
I just saw the message.
You are coming back?
You are thinking about my new book,
despite you are not even back yet?
That's enough.
About Huang Quan Inn,
let's talk about it after you return.
Bye.
Ms Chu, is the dinner ready?
Did you stay up all night
because you were worrying
about Suo Heng's submission?
Not only this.
Also, it's that friend of mine.
She saw the guy talking with
another woman on the phone,
they were talking and laughing.
Somehow,
she felt upset.
It's obvious that
that friend of yours was jealous.
Chu Li,
is that guy a playboy?
Calling him a playboy is
a flattering term for him.
Except for
my friend,
no one can stand him at all.
Mr Fox finished it so soon.
I thought Mr Fox would get rusty
in writing since he hadn't written
anything over the past years.
I didn't expect that he still got it.
Let me see, let me see.
How good can it be that
it impressed you so much?
Mr Zhou Chuan wrote this, isn't it?
The writer has such a wild imagination.
I even feel that
his wonderful storytelling skill
has completely surpassed
the openings written by Suo Heng.
This was not written by Zhou Chuan.
It's my friend.
Their styles are so similar.
It is obviously the same person.
Forget it, I am sending it
to Chief Editor Yu now.
I am sure of it.
Chu Li.
I read the draft.
It's nice.
The writing style is
sophisticated and neat.
The plots are brilliant.
Who wrote it?
Why do I feel that
his writing style is a bit similar
to Mr Zhou Chuan?
No, no, this wasn't written by Zhou Chuan.
It's my friend.
But he has mimicked
Zhou Chuan's writing style before.
He is known as Junior Zhou Chuan.
He has stopped writing for many years,
I am surprised that he is
still as good as ever.
He has saved the day for Suo Heng.
Thank him for me.
You can ask him to
write some short articles.
Really?
You really think he can write?
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[Interested to write articles for us?
The money is good.]
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
Be honest with me,
was it written by Mr Zhou Chuan?
It really was not.
I swear that if I lie,
I would gain 20 pounds.
I asked him before,
he denied it immediately.
This is so strange.
What is so strange about it?
There are many authors
who write in the same style.
No, Chu Li.
I have been keeping watch on Mr Zhou Chuan
since he published his first book.
Every one of his books,
I have read them
more than ten times from beginning to end.
I noticed that Mr Zhou Chuan
has a special habit in writing books.
Between the paragraphs
of significant plot like this,
he always uses five ellipses.
At the end of his work,
he also uses five ellipses
and writes an End.
See.
This book is the same.
[End]
See this.
And look at that again.
[End]
It's the same, isn't it?
How's that possible? You must
have been watching too many dramas.
One, two, three, four, five.
After Zhou Chuan became famous,
Mr Fox started to stop writing.
Oh my god.
No way.
What should I do?
If Mr Zhou Chuan really is Mr Fox,
I have been mocking him every day
and calling him a Drama King.
That doesn't make sense.
If Mr Zhou Chuan
really is Mr Fox,
he would have killed me already
under these circumstances.
How could he be possibly
letting me freeloading off of him
and live in his house for free?
No.
It's not like that.
If Mr Zhou Chuan isn't Mr Fox,
we are not that close for him to
sacrifice his millions dollars worth
of house to let me live for free.
But I...
I clean his house,
make dinners and walk the dog for him.
But he can get anyone to do that for him.
No, no.
I have to ask him for answer.
If Mr Zhou Chuan
and Mr Fox are the same person,
then haven't I been fooling
by the same person
with two accounts?
No.
I will send him a message and bluff him.
[I twisted my ankle at the door,]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[I am not sure if my bone is fractured.]
[Open the door for me now.]
She managed to twist
her ankle while walking.
I am impressed.
Mr Zhou Chuan!
Your ankle...
What's wrong with my ankle?
[I twisted my ankle at the door,]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[I am not sure if my bone is fractured.]
[Open the door for me now.]
Your shoes are dirty,
you should wash it.
[I didn't get busted, did I?]
Good for you.
You have been coming
home late every night.
You didn't even walk Er Gou.
I let you live here for free.
Did Yu Yao pay you for working overtime?
Can't you tell which side
is more important?
Such a fool.
Yes, yes, yes.
I don't know what's good
for me, and I am a fool.
After all, when you advised me
not to join the publishing industry,
that I should first stay alive
before I go after my dreams,
I didn't listen to you.
That's right. When did
you ever listen to me?
[Oh no, that's what Mr Fox said to her.]