(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 42)
(Quadrangular Courtyard)
That's so ridiculous.
Why did my father agree to it?
What are you afraid of?
Didn't they say that it doesn't matter who is it,
anyone can take the stage?
Does that mean...
people of the Tang Dynasty can join the open competition too?
What's wrong?
Are you worried that Shu Yu...
refuses to go on stage?
Le Yan.
Well...
Young Khan of Ashina Tribe is good, isn't he?
If no one can fight him,
what should I do?
With a top-notch horse, Tian Ji...
defeated King Wei of Qi's second-rated horse.
I can defeat him too.
I refuse.
Why?
It's boring.
Chang Ge.
It's okay. Let's forget about it.
Just fight this once for Le Yan.
Firstly, you defeat She Er.
Then, you lose to Wei Shu Yu on purpose.
That's all.
Do you really think Wei Shu Yu can defeat me?
No way.
That's why you should lose to him on purpose.
Why should I do that?
What do you mean "why"?
You're not going to marry Le Yan.
It's only natural that you lose to him.
Chang Ge, you don't have to fight...
because of me.
It's impossible that I lose to that guy...
in front of you.
Forget it. I don't want to talk to him.
Chang Ge.
You don't have to force your friend.
You don't have to force Shu Yu either.
If he likes me,
he'll figure it out when he's in the ring.
If he doesn't like me,
then just let it be.
There are so many nice men in the Tang Dynasty.
Of course, I can get married to someone.
Le Yan.
I'm really impressed.
Forget it.
Even if we can't beat She Er,
it's good to exhaust him a little.
You can't go in.
Keep going.
Here.
Li Cheng Qian.
It's you.
Li Chang Ge.
I haven't sought revenge for what happened in Luoyang.
Fine.
People!
Li Cheng Qian.
Le Yan.
Everyone, get out.
Come here.
Le Yan, calm down.
You can't hit me.
I'll beg for forgiveness from Father later.
- Come here. - No.
Don't. Let go of me.
It's them. They brought me here.
- No. - No.
You're just unlucky today...
that I'm still alive.
But since we're old friends,
I won't hold it against you.
But from now on, if there's any rumor in Chang'an...
saying that Princess Yongning...
is still alive,
you should know the consequences.
Why are you so afraid of her?
Li Cheng Qian, you're too young.
You don't know a lot of things.
What they're playing now...
are leftovers from what I played.
Tell him.
What did I do back then?
Deputy Minister Wang...
is the son of Prince Dongjin.
He once stole a girl by force.
Princess Yongning broke three of his bones.
Later on, he ran away whenever he saw females.
He's still single until now.
The youngest son of Councilor Chen...
peed in the Free Life Pond at the East Market.
Princess Yongning immersed him in the pond for two days.
From then on, he focused on practicing Buddhism.
He advocates for setting animals free.
When I was young,
I disrespected Princess Yongning once.
Her Highness beat me up whenever she saw me.
To run away,
I trained myself really hard.
That's how I got the body.
Are you Fatty?
You're the one who bullied me all my life.
Li Cheng Qian, come here.
Has he been playing with all of you all this while?
Why should I tell you?
Come closer.
I want him...
to save your sister...
at the martial arts competition.
Zhangsun Jing is not our friend.
He's here today to make up the numbers.
You saw it.
He's watching at the side.
He didn't do anything.
You have good taste.
I can attest to that.
He's a good man.
All right.
You'll do it.
At the martial arts competition tomorrow,
you need to defeat the representative from Ashina Tribe.
Don't let anyone win our princess away.
Godfather.
Moving forward,
I'm afraid...
I can't teach you anymore.
Don't be so pessimistic.
We'll get the best doctor...
to cure you.
I know my condition...
very well.
Be loyal...
to His Majesty.
Don't worry, Godfather.
I'll be loyal to the Tang Dynasty.
There are many ways to show loyalty.
Tomorrow, when you compete with Ashina Tribe...
in the ring,
make sure you don't lose.
I know how you feel.
Think about it.
If you feel like you're not worthy,
you can choose to beat Young Khan first...
and then pretend to lose...
to the other contestants from noble families.
But...
you can also opt to win until the end.
If you didn't raise me,
I'd still be an illegitimate child.
I wouldn't dare to cross the line to marry a princess.
All my life,
I sacrificed for the country.
I've never thought about myself.
You don't have to follow my path.
Just do as you wish.
Follow your heart but never cross the line.
That might be the best way to survive in the world.
I'm coming.
Master.
You're here too.
- I wonder who will win. - Yes.
I'm mad at Ashina Sun.
He really didn't come as he said.
Ashina Sun shouldn't be here.
If he's here,
he'll win for sure.
If he won,
he would have to marry the princess of the Tang Dynasty.
No.
I can't digest the fact...
that he's going to marry you.
If he marries the princess of the Tang Dynasty,
I can't take it.
Chang Ge.
Why isn't the Emperor of Tang here?
He just needs to know the result.
The result?
Please welcome the guardian warrior,
Young Khan of Ashina Tribe.
Greetings, envoys.
Is there anyone who volunteers to fight on the stage?
If no one is willing to fight, then...
I'm in.
- That's Zhi Xi. - It's Zhi Xi.
- He's doing it. - Right.
Why did Zhi Xi go up there?
Tegreg Tribe fawns over Ashina Tribe.
They go against the alliance the most.
Do they plan to surrender to the Tang Dynasty?
Young Khan is so bold and brave.
He's indeed the best warrior on the grassland.
He is definitely qualified to marry the princess of the Tang Dynasty.
I, Zhi Xi, congratulate Young Khan in advance...
for marrying the new Khatun.
Look at Zhi Xi.
Young Khan won.
Do people from Tegreg Tribe...
all lack a spine?
If you don't want to form an alliance with the Tang Dynasty,
just go back to the desert.
Don't embarrass the rest of us who also come from the desert.
Your Highness.
No doubt I'm no match for Young Khan.
If any of you from the Southern Desert...
can fight Young Khan of Ashina Tribe,
please come forward.
Be it the Northern Desert or the Southern Desert,
is there no one who dares to fight me?
The Southern Desert intends to form an alliance with Tang.
Isn't it because you can't defeat anyone?
That's why you can only rely on Tang.
However, the princess of the Tang Dynasty...
is going to marry Young Khan.
Can't you see the state of affairs?
Are you really going to blindly follow...
the princess of the Northern Desert?
You!
I'm so going to beat you up,
you spineless man.
Don't stoop to his level.
Sit down.
What took you so long?
What are you wearing?
Don't touch my crown.
I'm here to accept the challenge.
Of course I have to dress like a warrior.
What are you laughing at?
Who are you?
Are you making fun of me?
She's Princess Tu Jia from the Southern Desert.
She's one of us.
Zhen Zhu, he's the crown prince of the Tang Dynasty.
The crown prince...
looks so brave and extraordinary.
I just can't contain my joy.
Why are you dressed like that?
Princess Yong'an shouldn't be present at the scene.
I want to see how it ends for me too.
It's okay, Chang Ge.
No one will notice.
Both of you are indeed siblings.
Forget it. It's too late.
Let's go in.
Is there no one else from the desert?
In that case, the betrothal with the Tang Dynasty...
It's too early to tell.
Welcome, Your Highness.
Are you Young Khan of Ashina Tribe...
who wants to marry my sister?
Your Highness.
The young man on the stage is my son.
Thanks for the courtesy, Khatun.
That's not necessary anyway.
After all, we won't become a family.
It's better to keep a distance.
Did you bring anyone to take part in the competition?
Whether we are going to become a family or not,
we'll find out soon.
Zhangsun Jing.
I'll leave my sister in your hands.
I won't let you down.
I have a good relationship with the two princesses.
I allow both of you...
to watch the match together.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Cheng Qian.
Will it work?
Don't worry.
Zhangsun Jing is the best fighter among Mother's nephews.
If he can't do it,
the rest won't be able to do it.
- In the blink of an eye, - He lost.
he lost even before he got to make a move.
Yes.
Young Khan of Ashina Tribe is winning consecutively.
What?
Is that the end?
Is there anyone else who would like to challenge Young Khan?
Do we really have no one that can fight?
I guess no one dares to challenge me.
What's the hurry?
Marriage is a major life event.
You should give them more time to think about it.
Since Crown Prince has spoken,
I'll give every one of you...
more time to consider...
if you want to fight me in the ring.
I didn't expect Zhangsun Jing...
to be so weak.
What should we do now?
I don't want my sister...
to marry to such a poor place.
Furthermore, She Er...
really gets on my nerves.
I don't want him to be my brother-in-law.
Don't worry, Le Yan.
I'm sure Shu Yu will come.
Mr. Wei is here.
What happened?
That's good.
Shu Yu.
Le Yan.
Before I get into the ring,
I have something to tell you.
I've been thinking about it...
and I decided to tell you that...
I will fight in the ring for sure.
You're like my sister.
I won't allow you to marry to the grassland.
Protecting is one thing.
But I can't lie to you.
If I win in the competition,
that doesn't mean we're getting married.
Le Yan.
You're so brave now.
I'm glad to see that.
That's why I can't be a coward...
that won't move forward.
I hope you can understand my goodwill...
as your big brother.
I'm sorry.
I understand.
Since you're not joining for the sake of marrying me,
then you don't have to go on the stage.
What I'm looking forward to...
isn't a victory in the fight.
I want someone who truly loves me.
I've thought it through.
It's not supposed to be a relationship between siblings.
I want a relationship where both persons...
can live together as husband and wife forever.
The man in the ring...
should fight for me because he loves me.
It's not about protecting me.
If it's only about protecting me,
I don't need it.
Even if you win the fight,
to me,
that's sheer humiliation.
But the competition...
As for the competition,
I won't trouble you, Shu Yu.
I'm no longer the old Le Yan.
It's my business.
I can take care of myself.
Thank you, Shu Yu.
Le Yan.
What's wrong?
Where is Shu Yu? Why isn't he coming along?
Did he bully you?
- I'll go get him. - No.
I don't want to force him.
I don't want to make life difficult for myself either.
Have you made yourself clear?
Loud and clear.
I'll get Ashina Sun.
It's okay.
- Why not? - I don't want to force anyone.
You're not forcing anyone.
It's about your marriage.
Let's go through this for now.
- Wait for me. - Chang Ge.
Ashina Sun.
You finally came.
Come on, get in the ring.
I'm just here to watch.
What are you talking about?
You're already here. You obviously have the heart to help.
Why are you still lying?
I don't help others.
Le Yan is not just anyone.
Ashina Sun, stop talking.
As much as I hate to let you go on the stage,
but now, there's no other way.
You should go up.
How is it?
Is there no one who dares to go on stage?
If no one dares to challenge my son,
I'll take that as a yes...
to the betrothal with the Tang Dynasty.
Go now, Ashina Sun!
It's urgent. We'll talk about it after the fight.
We'll deal with the rest later.
Exactly.
Even if Chang Ge agrees with it, I won't allow it.
What is this?
An ample time has been given for your consideration.
I'll count to three.
If no one takes the stage,
it's settled then.
- Three. - Ashina Sun.
Ashina Sun.
Look at how smug he is.
Don't you want to punch him?
Two.
Hurry, jump from here.
I...
One.
Ashina Sun.
I'm here.
Hao Du.
Who are you?
A pawn of the Tang Dynasty who can defeat you.
- Good job. - Good job.
He's badly injured.
Get up.
Hao Du.
That's enough.
No more fighting. We admit defeat.
We admit defeat.
Hao Du, stop it.
I'm resigned to my fate. That's enough.
Hao Du.
I won't admit defeat.
That's enough.
You must not surrender to fate either.
She Er.
Stop wasting time.
Let's get this over with.
Strangle him.
Hao Du, hurry up!
She Er.
Stop it!
The warrior of the Tang Dynasty won!
- That's great! - Great!
- Well done. - That's great!
- Okay. - Great!
We won!
- That's great! - Great!
He's a hero.
- He deserves to be respected. - Great!
Hao Du.
Thank you.
I will return to the palace to report to His Majesty.
- That's great. - Goodbye.
Well done.
Sure.
I won.
You don't have to marry him.
I know that...
you've met with Le Yan...
and made it clear to her.
Yes.
I don't want to hurt her.
You did the right thing.
You shouldn't have deceived her.
But if Hao Du didn't appear,
I don't think it would end well.
Even if Hao Du didn't come,
I'd already prepared...
to go on the stage.
I will never let Ashina Tribe take Le Yan away.
Then, I will ask His Majesty for forgiveness.
I believe that given a little bit of time,
Le Yan will come to her senses.
I don't expect the three of us...
to go back to how we were.
But at least,
you and Le Yan have to live well.
At any time.
I'm still your brother.
Thank you, Shu Yu.
Shu Yu.
There's something you need to pay more attention to.
The Tang Dynasty has to be more careful...
with Khatun from Ashina Tribe.
Why did you get in the ring?
I...
I worry that Ashina Tribe...
would bully the Tang Dynasty.
So...
You're just like Shu Yu.
You went on the stage...
just to save the Tang Dynasty's reputation.
You didn't do it for me.
Hao Du.
I, Li Le Yan, will find a way...
to salvage the reputation of the Tang Dynasty.
I don't need your help.
No, I'm actually...
I don't wish to see you...
being forced into a marriage...
with someone you don't like.
This is a sparring competition.
I'll marry whoever wins.
You've won the fight.
I'll marry you as I promised.
So, you think...
You think that I like you?
I know who you love.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
The fight doesn't count.
I will talk to His Majesty tomorrow.
You didn't even...
think about marrying me.
I am just a warrior.
How can I think too much?
Why are you always so humble before me?
You could've done something greater.
Why did you risk your life...
- because of me? - That's because you deserve it.
But...
But I'm not good enough for you.
Do you want to know what I see in you?
When I first met you,
you were like an ice cube.
Your face is cold.
So does your heart.
And I was afraid of you.
I wouldn't dare nor want to go near you.
Later,
you're chasing after Chang Ge to kill her.
I hated you even more.
I guess I was wrong.
You're not cold-hearted.
You have no heart.
But...
when I was in the North...
running all the way to Luoyang,
you saved me.
The moment you hugged me...
and said that you would bring me home,
I was not afraid of you anymore.
Later on,
I relied on you more and more.
I started to feel that...
your heart is warm.
Only when I am with you,
I can feel a sense of security.
I'm at ease.
Actually, I gradually realized that...
you did many things...
because you had no choice.
You said many things...
but you didn't mean it.
Hao Du.
Actually, you're a nice person...
but you tend to hide your emotions.
You always make things hard for yourself...
to please others.
Today, in the ring,
I saw you being beaten over and over again.
I was really scared.
I was scared that I might not be able to see you again.
When I thought that I might not be able to see you again, I...
Let me ask you one last time.
Why did you get on the stage?
I got on the stage...
because I just didn't want you to be sad.
At the same time, I wanted to fight for myself too.
Fight for what?
Your Highness, you said this before.
You asked me to protect your precious life.
In the past,
I was protecting you as a royal guard.
But moving forward...
What were you trying to say?
Moving forward,
I'll protect you as your husband.
Why are you so bold now?
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
Just forget what I said.
Forget it?
Are you going to go back on your own words?
No, I didn't want to...
I told you.
You need to be careful.
If you don't take care of yourself,
how are you going to protect me?
I...
You...
Didn't you get hurt pretty badly?
You're still so strong.
It's suffocating.
I don't know what happened to me.
After hearing what you said,
I think I'm fine now.
Since you're all better now,
we should go to the farmhouse tomorrow.
It's been a while since I last went there.
I wonder how the people are doing.
Okay.
No matter where you go,
I'll be with you.
(Quadrangular Courtyard)
Look at your feet.
I didn't expect...
that this bunny...
would be getting married soon.
Le Yan,
can you forget Shu Yu for real?
Getting married is a big deal.
If you don't like Hao Du,
no one can force you.
Chang Ge.
I'm no longer...
the crybaby.
I've always...
seen Shu Yu...
as a hero.
I relied on him and admired him.
Gradually, it became a habit.
Until the day of the competition,
I realized that...
I've been neglecting Hao Du...
who was always next to me.
Shu Yu...
I'll always treat him as a brother.
Are you sure you really like Hao Du?
How about...
you and Ashina Sun?
How do you feel about him?
You're getting worse.
I was asking you a question.
In front of Ashina Sun,
do you feel the most relaxed?
It's as if you can show him...
all your emotions.
Furthermore,
you're not afraid that he'll find you hard to like.
You just want to show him...
your true self.
When I met him,
I was in the most awkward situation.
I was at my worst.
That's right.
In front of Hao Du,
I feel the most relaxed and natural.
On the other hand, in front of Shu Yu,
I'm so clumsy.
I should have let go of myself.
I shouldn't make him guilty either.
Everyone should enjoy...
being the most relaxed.
We should look into our hearts.
That's how we can be happy.
By the way,
I'm going to bed early.
Tomorrow, Hao Du and I...
are going to the farmhouse.
You just can't wait to go on a secret date with him.
That's not the case.
It's called...
"concerning about society".
They want us to sign the treaty right now?
No way.
It's late.
Why is it so noisy outside?
You don't want to offend the Ashina Tribe.
The treaty?
Then we came here for nothing.
- That's right. - You shouldn't sign it.
It's a dilemma.
That's right. You can't sign it.
Why is Tegreg Tribe so afraid of Ashina Tribe?
The Northern and Southern Desert... suggested the alliance...
to save your guts.
They've just won the fight today.
Now, the Emperor of Tang...
wants us to sign the treaty.
Isn't it obvious that he wants us...
to take sides in front of Ashina Tribe?
Look at their moves.
The Tang Dynasty could be the other Ashina Tribe.
You...
He's distorting my father's intention.
That's enough. Stop it.
Let go of me.
Chang Ge.
Everyone.
Emperor of Tang means to say that...
as long as Tang is here,
there's no need to be afraid of Ashina Tribe.
Of course.
Since the alliance was brought up by the Northern Desert,
if the Tang Dynasty turns into another Ashina Tribe,
the Northern Desert will fight against it.
That's right.
The treaty was initiated by the Northern Desert.
Tegreg Tribe doesn't acknowledge it.
And let me tell you something.
There's no way the Tegreg Tribe...
will sign the treaty.
People.
Think about it.
Once you sign the treaty,
it means you're clearly going against the Ashina Tribe.
We can't afford to offend the Ashina Tribe.
- Right. - We can't offend them.
So what if you offend Ashina Tribe?
The Tang Dynasty will protect its allies.
Even if the Ashina Tribe intends to attack any of the tribes,
they will have to think about it again.
Don't you agree?
- Yes, that's right. - That's right.
But...
Ashina Tribe is too strong.
I can't stop the princess of the Northern Desert...
to rely on the Tang Dynasty...
but don't give us a hard time.
Let's go.
- This... - Wait.
He left just like that.
It's a dilemma.
(The Long Ballad)