(The Long Ballad)
(This is a work of fiction.)
(Episode 41)
Your Highness.
An Rou.
Do you think I'll be sent to the Ashina Tribe?
Your Highness.
You mean the world to His Majesty.
I believe His Majesty wouldn't be able to bear...
to let you marry to a faraway place.
Your Highness.
Nothing is certain yet.
Don't worry too much first.
You also saw...
Ashina Tribe's Khatun today.
From what I heard from the elders in the palace...
about her story,
she married to the grasslands for so long.
She has had many husbands.
She seems to be doing well,
but who knows...
what she has been through?
Tell me, Hao Du.
Am I being too selfish?
I'm only thinking about myself.
Your Highness.
If you're willing,
I...
Le Yan.
Shu Yu.
You're here.
You don't have to tell me. I know everything.
I heard about what happened at the Quadrangular Courtyard.
Shu Yu.
What should I do?
I don't know what I should do.
Shu Yu.
Don't be afraid.
I will go and write a letter to His Majesty.
I'll write thousands of letters.
I'll surely get His Majesty to take back his orders.
If it doesn't work...
If it doesn't work, I'll plead with my father...
and tell him to talk to His Majesty with me.
In consideration of my father,
- His Majesty... - It's no use.
We're currently in a critical phase...
of our alliance with the Great Desert.
This is what Ashina Tribe is holding onto.
If Father changes his mind,
they'll surely make an issue about it.
If the alliance is affected because of me,
how can I face everyone?
If Tang's princess...
dies...
No one would let a dead person intermarry.
Le Yan.
- Don't do anything stupid. - Shu Yu.
I'm not doing something stupid.
When King Nan of Zhou was on the throne,
Fan Ju faked his death to avoid disaster.
Chang Ge...
Chang Ge has the most experience in faking death.
She'll surely figure something out for me.
If Princess Yong'an is gone,
then...
no one can force me to intermarry again.
And I won't drag my father down with me.
But...
That would be the last resort.
What should I do then?
Sit and do nothing?
We'll figure something out.
If the Ashina Tribe...
officially talks to Father about this,
when everything is settled,
I must really marry to the grasslands.
I'm sure there's a way.
Shu Yu.
If I marry to the grasslands,
to you,
it actually doesn't matter, does it?
Of course not.
We grew up together.
I've always thought of you as my own sister.
As my own sister.
Thought of you as my own sister.
Your sister?
So that day,
when I told you how I felt,
you thought of me...
as a younger sister?
Le Yan.
You may go.
I want to be alone.
Wei Shu Yu.
What are you going to do now?
You can't answer me?
So all this time,
you didn't think about how to deal with this?
In negotiating peace with Tang,
of course they need a useful hostage.
Princess Yong'an is His Majesty's precious daughter.
Anyone can think of this.
I can't believe you didn't think of this at all.
I'm asking you now,
and you couldn't even answer.
Hao Du.
You're crossing the line.
If you're just an official in the imperial court,
of course I won't ask you.
But don't you know?
She likes you.
She has always cared about how you feel and what you think.
Can you bear to let her be sad?
Stay out of my business.
Stop arguing!
You can both go.
I want to be alone.
(Gather beautiful scenery and auspiciousness)
Mimi.
- Mimi. - Are they here?
Yes.
Don't worry. I won't let them find you.
I'm fine, Chang Ge.
I'm not scared anymore.
I figured it out.
Since I'm still alive,
it's only a matter of time before they find me.
There's no point in evading this.
Since I'm still alive,
I should live happily.
Since she's here, I don't need to hide...
like a ghost and live an ignoble existence.
The Eagle Army sent a message.
Mu Jin has already successfully entered the capital.
By now, I'm sure he's already...
in the old Dingxiang Palace.
Really?
This isn't right.
They already know that Mu Jin lied to them.
What if they find out...
that Mu Jin sneaked into Dingxiang, will they...
Mu Jin once saved a soldier in the capital.
They're friends.
I think he'll go to him this time.
Heavenly Wolf God, please protect him.
I hope Mu Jin can turn disaster into a blessing.
But it doesn't look good at all now.
Yicheng definitely came prepared.
I think Le Yan is also doing badly.
Is Your Highness very disappointed...
that it wasn't Wei Shu Yu who came?
I forbid you to go to him.
Your Highness.
If you really like him,
I'll kidnap him for you.
Just elope.
I'll take full responsibility.
How will you take responsibility?
With your position and status,
if I leave,
and Father becomes furious,
how are you going to take responsibility?
I'm an upright man.
I'm concerned about the heavens and earth.
And I'm concerned...
And I'm concerned with my friends and family.
Your Highness regards me highly.
If you think of me as a friend,
I'll prepare the money and horses for you.
Just leave.
I'm not leaving.
I'm Princess Yong'an.
Since I buried Xiao Wu,
I've made up my mind...
to be a good Tang princess.
That's why I can't leave.
I must face all of this.
Then you're going to intermarry?
No.
I'm not going to.
But I don't want to rely on anyone.
I want to fight for it myself.
Hao Du.
Will you support me?
Khatun.
Don't you want to run far away?
Why did you come here yourself?
Why did you come to Chang'an?
Are you questioning me?
So what if I am?
Since when are you in charge...
of Ashina Tribe's internal affairs?
What's the matter?
As Ashina Tribe's Khatun,
am I just a figurehead?
To you,
aside from your father,
who else do you look up to?
I'm the one asking you.
Regardless,
I'm your elder.
It's fine if you're looking down on me.
But you must respect your father.
My father was the one who sent you?
Who else can it be?
How is he?
As long as you're willing to return with the Eagle Army...
and work for the grasslands again,
your father will let you return to the capital...
and let bygones be bygones.
I'm afraid this is just your idea.
Is there a difference?
I came to Chang'an this time.
It's enough to prove...
that I can represent your father.
What a shame.
You're nothing to me.
What about Li Chang Ge?
I can't believe that the well-known commander...
of Ashina Tribe's Eagle Army back then...
is willing to become...
Li Chang Ge's guard.
Ashina Sun, sometimes,
I really can't figure you out.
What's so good about Li Chang Ge?
How did she become...
the weakness of the grasslands' God of War?
If you want to be invincible on the battlefield,
the enemy's swords...
and your comrades' arrows aren't scary.
What's scary is that you have a weakness.
Your weakness...
is just right there.
If you dare to touch her,
I'll make sure you die a horrible death.
Greetings, Your Highness.
What's the matter?
I can't believe Mimi Guli is still alive.
She's part of the Great Desert's entourage.
Your Highness, aren't you surprised?
Ever since I saw Ashina Sun,
I knew that Mimi Guli must still be alive.
Then should we...
Send a message to Dingxiang.
Tell Lei Meng...
that those who should have died didn't die at all.
Yes, Your Highness.
What did you find out?
I checked...
what you told me to look into.
Those medicines are poisonous.
The poison isn't fatal.
But it will slowly...
invade your body's organs.
As time passes by,
you'll die of organ failure.
That woman is ruthless.
You saved my life before.
We're even now.
I'll keep it a secret that you're in Dingxiang.
- But hopefully... - I know.
Thank you.
I won't bother you about this anymore.
Uncle Lei's patrols are very strict daily.
Don't let him find you.
Wait.
One more thing.
Have you heard...
of a prisoner of war named Bu Zhen?
It's a kid.
A kid?
There are no kids in the prison.
In the Dingxiang Palace,
perhaps only the King of Sui's Palace has kids.
King of Sui's Palace?
I don't know about the rest.
Take care.
Why did my mother ask you to come?
I'm asking you.
Move.
Does she want you...
to go back with the Eagle Army?
Go back?
In Northern Desert, that arrow your mother released...
almost killed me.
Tell me.
How is my father?
My mother is taking good care of him.
Don't worry about it.
Why are you looking at me that way?
Do you really want to live like a fool?
Say that again.
Haven't you thought about it?
My father was very healthy.
Why did he suddenly fall ill?
And he even wanted to relocate the capital to Dingxiang.
My father is sick.
The power has been transferred to Dingxiang.
Do you think...
all of these happened naturally?
Don't try to blame me and my mother.
Don't include yourself.
You won't...
be able to do it without leaving any trace.
I've already confirmed it.
Yicheng is the one who holds the real power in Ashina Tribe now.
I see.
It turns out that she has been trying to trick me before.
She's onto you now.
It's only a matter of time before she finds out your identity.
We'll deal with them when they come.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I wish I didn't take you to the grasslands back then.
If you didn't take me to the grasslands back then,
how would you be willing to protect me this way now?
You're a high and mighty army commander.
How can you like a traitor of Tang like me?
You came.
What's the matter?
Are you unwilling to accept that I found you?
Do you think that by reporting your fake death,
you'll be able to get away?
You should know...
that death isn't the end.
If someone living a miserable life...
wants to die,
then the other one who is alive...
must live miserably.
How can I bear to do that?
What did you do to Bu Zhen?
Why?
How dare you?
He's just a kid!
Why are you doing this to him?
Why?
Because you betrayed me.
If you do well, I wouldn't have mistreated him.
But you betrayed me.
I just took one finger from him.
Don't you think...
that I'm already very kind?
Bu Zhen.
Mimi.
- Mimi. - What's the matter?
Ashina Sun, Mimi is gone.
She's afraid of Yicheng.
I'm worried that...
Don't panic first.
Let's split up. I'm sure we can find her.
All right.
Mimi.
Father!
Father.
Are you going to see His Majesty...
to discuss the intermarriage?
I beseech you, Father,
please persuade His Majesty to let Her Highness...
Shu Yu, let me ask you.
You and Her Highness grew up together.
Do you have other thoughts about her?
Father, I...
Whether Princess Yong'an will marry somewhere faraway...
is an important matter in the imperial court.
You don't have any right...
to negotiate with His Majesty, understand?
If you're serious...
about your affection for Her Highness,
fight for it yourself.
There's only one identity who can do that.
Prince Consort.
You're all grown up now.
You know what you want.
If you've thought about it carefully,
fight for it yourself.
Bu Zhen.
It's all my fault.
I couldn't protect you.
You must live well.
Wait for me to reunite with you,
I'm sorry.
If you want to see your brother,
obey orders.
Her Highness...
wants you to do something.
If you don't do it,
the consequence won't be just one finger.
Mimi.
It's really you, Mimi.
Ashina Sun faked his death.
I knew you must be alive as well.
I'll get going.
Do you hate me that much?
Young Khan, you have a prestigious status.
Why should you harass a slave like me?
I've never treated you as a slave.
Mimi.
Can you go back with me?
I promise I'll be good to you.
Mimi.
Listen to me.
Marrying Tang's princess is just...
I promise.
I would never be true to her.
Why are you telling a slave...
who you will be true to?
Of course I must tell you.
And I have to tell you that I...
I like you.
When we were little, you used to ride the horse next to me.
I thought, "Your hair looks amazing."
When it flies in the wind, it's like Central Plains' silk.
In this world,
you're the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
And you're the best.
When I played with you then,
- did you feel happy? - Yes.
When you played with me, I'd feel happy.
That's because I was afraid to make you unhappy.
Because if you're unhappy,
I don't know what kind of punishment will be given to me and Bu Zhen.
Actually, every time I saw you,
I felt scared.
I would even resent you.
Why did you save us?
I'd rather die.
I'm a living human being.
I'm not an emotionless plaything.
I don't want to feel scared and try to please someone daily.
And I don't want to be beaten, starved, and scolded...
for some minor mistakes daily.
Do you understand how I feel?
You don't understand at all.
So, Young Khan,
I won't go back with you.
Mimi.
Where did you go? I've been looking everywhere for you.
I'm fine.
I just walked around a bit.
Don't be scared. You have us.
Chang Ge, Young Khan marrying the princess is just a strategy.
If the princess really goes to the grasslands,
she'll surely suffer.
Don't worry.
I definitely won't let her marry into the Ashina Tribe.
All right.
Chang Ge.
Shu Yu, shouldn't you be in Taichi Palace today...
to discuss the intermarriage?
Why did you come to see me?
Shu Yu.
I want to stop the intermarriage.
But I'm not qualified.
You're stopping the intermarriage for Le Yan's happiness.
Why are you talking about qualifications?
What exactly are you worried about?
Father told me...
that if I try to persuade His Majesty as the Prince Consort,
it might work.
That makes sense.
Based on your long friendship with her,
he'll surely consider these things.
And Le Yan will also be very happy.
- You know that she has always... - I know.
She confessed her feelings to me.
Then what are you hesitating about?
That's the most effective way...
to stop the intermarriage right now.
Shu Yu,
- you and I... - I know.
I won't force you.
But I don't want to hurt her either.
I don't want to disappoint her.
I don't want her to marry to the grasslands.
But I know clearly...
that if I propose,
isn't that like pulling her out from one fiery pit...
and pushing her into another one?
To me,
she's really like my own sister.
I got it.
In that case,
Le Yan also doesn't need forced love.
All we can do is see what happens.
Let's see what Ashina Tribe will do.
We'll deal with them when the time comes.
Chang Ge.
Since what happened at the East Palace,
I feel like the gap between you, me,
and Le Yan is becoming bigger.
I can't catch up with you two anymore.
When you say these things,
you're already not the same as before.
Sometimes, it's most difficult...
to face yourself.
You've already done that.
Actually, you don't need to be so pessimistic.
Because the one who can stop this...
isn't just you and me.
You mean...
- His Majesty? - He may be the emperor,
but he's also a father.
He definitely doesn't want to destroy Le Yan's happiness.
However...
We might still need an opportunity.
What opportunity?
Let's wait and see.
It's hard to say at the moment.
Your Majesty.
Regarding Princess Yong'an's intermarriage,
it definitely can't be changed.
It's already been decided a long time ago.
If Tang breaks the agreement,
I'm afraid Ashina Tribe will accuse us...
of being sly, fickle, and a promise-breaker.
How can we gain the Great Desert's trust then?
You mean...
we're only considering the current situation.
Princess Yong'an is His Majesty's daughter.
She's not just someone from the imperial family.
Given her status,
wouldn't the Ashina Tribe...
make a fuss about this intermarriage?
Your Majesty.
The intermarriage is indeed very troublesome.
But that will only happen later on.
Now, only by not breaking what was agreed upon...
is the fastest way...
to gain the trust of Great Desert's tribes.
Your Majesty, I strongly agree.
If we hesitate...
in the intermarriage with the Ashina Tribe...
and break what was agreed upon,
I'm afraid...
they won't let this go.
And our alliance with the Great Desert's tribes...
will fall through.
Your Majesty.
I believe intermarriage must be done.
If we must intermarry,
it can't be with the Ashina Tribe.
That's right.
If we agree to this,
Ashina Tribe will surely push their luck.
Your Majesty, at the moment,
Ashina Tribe is obviously using the intermarriage...
to challenge us.
If we don't keep our promise,
how can we convince the Great Desert's tribes?
Your Majesty.
I think that Princess Yong'an's intermarriage...
is a magnanimous act taken for the greater good.
She's intermarrying for the citizens and the nation.
In the future, if Ashina Tribe becomes disloyal,
and they want to make a fuss...
regarding the intermarriage,
we can't let Her Highness...
come back then.
You've studied hundreds of books.
But it seems like you didn't study them well.
You only learned how to be generous at the expense of others.
Your Majesty.
Forgive me, Your Majesty.
I failed to stop Her Highness.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Why is Her Highness here? It's ridiculous.
Your Majesty.
Just now, in front of all the officials,
Her Highness said that I didn't study well.
But in front of all the officials,
Her Highness is discussing her own marriage.
It can be considered as interfering in political affairs...
and it's rude.
I wonder if that makes sense.
The late emperor gave Princess Yong'an her title.
How can it be rude for her...
to discuss her marriage?
You're Minister Chen from the Ministry of Rites, right?
Since my marriage...
is a major matter in the imperial court,
as His Majesty's loyal subject,
of course I should speak my mind.
Your Majesty, I have something to say.
Go ahead.
Your Majesty.
Forgive me for overstepping.
I'm your daughter.
But I'm no different...
from the other ladies in Tang.
We were born into this world...
to live for our father, emperor, and for the great cause.
But we can't just live for these things.
Home is the basis of the nation.
Tang is prosperous...
because it can protect its citizens.
If Tang's prosperity is achieved...
through compromise,
may I ask what is a nation...
and what is a home?
What her Highness said is right.
In what way?
This is ridiculous.
Her Highness obviously doesn't want to intermarry.
That's right.
Your Majesty.
Even if Princess Yong'an does not wish to intermarry,
she doesn't need to say such lofty words.
Ashina Tribe's Khatun,
who came to discuss the intermarriage this time,
was Princess Yicheng...
from the Sui Dynasty back then.
Princess Yicheng's great act back then...
was very admirable.
Is our princess...
incomparable to the princess of the previous dynasty?
Minister Chen, you're very straightforward.
I admire you.
But what you said...
insulted all the men in Tang.
What does she mean?
What did she say?
What is she saying?
It's ridiculous.
Please watch what you say, Your Highness.
Minister Chen, do you know...
how Princess Yicheng...
endured it until today?
She was a princess of the previous dynasty.
In the unfamiliar grasslands,
she lived like a nobody.
She didn't have any dignity at all.
The Sui Dynasty was weak and easily bullied.
They were afraid of the Ashina Tribe.
That was why they let a weak woman...
make such a sacrifice.
Are the thousands of men in Tang...
afraid of strong enemies?
If Tang can't even protect...
their own children,
how would Great Deserts' tribes...
trust Tang...
to protect them?
Yes.
That makes sense.
You are right, Your Highness.
Mr. Du.
There's no need for courtesy. Have a seat.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
I believe what Her Highness said...
is just an excuse to refuse the intermarriage.
Mr. Du,
what do you think?
As a woman,
Her Highness wouldn't bow down...
to the strong people in the grasslands.
I deeply admire what Her Highness said.
All right.
Just one word from the Ashina Tribe,
and Tang is presenting...
its princess.
How is it different from surrendering to them?
Your Majesty is brilliant.
We'll opt for the lesser of two evils.
I think that if the Ashina Tribe...
just uses verbal threats,
and they're able to take our princess,
it's a great evil.
If Ashina Tribe...
slanders us for breaking our promise,
we can still do something about it.
It's the lesser evil.
Tang Dynasty...
will never sacrifice a woman...
to get a brief moment of peace.
It's not because...
Yong'an is my daughter.
All the women in this nation...
are my people.
I will...
never sacrifice a single person.
Yong'an, in three days,
come with me to Quadrangular Courtyard.
If Ashina Tribe...
dares to bring up this matter again,
you can tell them yourself...
that the former agreement is canceled.
Welcome, His Majesty!
(Aspire for virtue and eliminate doubts)
Due to the alliance,
you've come all the way here.
I would like to thank you first.
Emperor of Tang.
Yan Li Khan has fallen ill.
That is why he told me to ask you...
if my son...
and Tang's princess's marriage can be confirmed...
before we chat about other matters.
Well...
Khatun is not giving any consideration...
to Emperor of Tang.
Even if Great Khan is ill,
he's still worried about this marriage.
Today,
I'll give him an answer then.
Tell Khatun on my behalf.
I, thank the favor...
that you, Great Khan, and Ashina Tribe are showing me, Khatun.
I have weak health.
I don't deserve this marriage.
Please excuse me for not being able to comply.
What's going on?
You're turning down...
the marriage proposal?
Khatun, you're very talented.
What I can do...
might not even be half of what you're capable of.
So I can only disappoint you.
Emperor of Tang, do you think...
that since you have Great Desert's tribes now,
you can give up...
on your former agreement with our tribe?
What if something changes again in the future?
Will Tang...
also treat you the same way?
- Yes. - She's right.
How can they do this to us?
They're doing this to us.
They must keep their word.
Tang was the one who agreed to the marriage...
as proof of amity with the Ashina Tribe.
Now, Emperor of Tang is going back on his word.
If something happens, later on,
you can't blame us anymore.
Why is everyone hesitating?
We all traveled a long way to Chang'an...
to discuss the alliance.
That means we're willing to renew our friendship with Tang.
That also means...
that every single one of you...
has a chance to become Prince Consort.
- Become Prince Consort? - What does that mean?
I stand a chance too.
What do you mean?
Young Khan, you just said...
that intermarriage is proof of amity.
Everyone here...
wants to be friends with Tang.
In that case, may the best man win.
Let's ask Emperor of Tang...
to hold a martial arts competition for the Prince Consort.
This way,
it would be fair for all of us.
Great.
Only the winner...
deserves to be Princess Yong'an's husband.
Young Khan, do you dare to participate?
What's the matter, Young Khan?
Are you scared?
What are you talking about?
Why would I be afraid?
All right.
You're indeed a young hero, Young Khan.
In that case,
let's set it up here tomorrow.
It doesn't matter where you come from.
You may all compete.
The undefeatable winner...
deserves to be Yong'an's husband.
(The Long Ballad)