Sub by kisscambodia
Episode 7
No need to be afraid.
You only have to master the Soul Power.
Parasite, I see.
Your second Soul Ring
inherited the power of the Haunted Vine.
And my wound
doesn't hurt at all.
It's Blue Silver Plant.
Your first Soul Ring's poison
has a transitory numbing effect.
But growing plants on the skin
doesn't seem that useful.
These Soul Skills can combine
and immobilize your enemy.
For example,
cover your enemy's
skin with Blue Silver Plant seeds.
The poison will numb the skin.
As such,
the seeds can grow
unbeknownst to the enemy.
It's foolproof.
Tang San can then
bind the enemy.
I was just planning to be a nuisance
but when I asked around...
You are cruel.
You kill for fun.
The hunter will become the hunted.
You already know this, don't you?
Dude,
no curfew today?
The governor is dead.
No more curfew.
What?
The governor is dead?
This afternoon,
when he was out with his guards,
a masked man appeared.
The masked man was so strong.
He rushed in,
knocked away all the Soul Masters,
and
with just one punch,
he smashed the governor and his litter.
What happened to our world?
You can tidy up
but it can never be restored.
But this is my home.
I should keep it clean and tidy.
Yu Xiao Gang.
They can't hear me.
I'm outside.
This can treat Martial Soul injury.
It's enough for you three.
Take it,
sleep well,
then you'll be fully healed.
No time for this.
We need to
deal with
the governor of Nuoding first.
This is only the first assault.
The governor won't give up so easily.
We need to leave soon.
The governor is gone.
You...
Farewell then.
Take care of Tang San.
He's your son.
You don't want to say hi to him?
Meeting me
will make him suffer.
And one day...
How did you find out?
I thought the governor would attack
so I buried some Blue Silver Plants.
I'll know when someone's near.
Who taught you that?
I came up with it.
Give us some time alone.
Master,
does Tang San's dad
hate him?
Why do you say so?
He came back only to meet you.
Obviously, he didn't want
to show himself.
Is he leaving?
Kids nowadays
are getting smarter.
Dad.
Sorry, dad.
I shouldn't have left home.
I shouldn’t have gone to school.
I won't ask any questions anymore.
I'll stay with you.
No.
You're smart.
You already know that
I'm no ordinary blacksmith.
Yet you never asked me.
Blacksmith or Soul Master,
none of this matters.
What matters is you're my dad.
Isn't that good enough?
I still have a business to tend to.
You won't be able to keep up.
I can learn.
I can be stronger.
Dad.
I have two Soul Rings now.
Look.
It's not enough.
Our family has a lot of secrets
but I can't tell you them
because they are related
to too many powerful individuals.
You're too weak for that.
Dad.
I can learn from you.
I can be stronger.
Dad.
We can retire together.
Let me take care of you.
A man shouldn't be so spineless.
You took the first step
and you decided to be
someone extraordinary.
Then you should
use your own power
to face the world.
Hiding in my shadow
won't make you grow.
But I want to train
and learn from you.
Master will bring you
to somewhere more suitable.
He's a good teacher.
Trust him.
Dad.
Are you abandoning me?
You're my son.
Forever will be.
When your willpower and Martial Soul
are more than powerful,
then
I will appear before you.
Dad.
I hope that day will come sooner.
Where are you going?
You have your own path
and I
have to face my fate.
Dad.
You're back.
What happened?
Master,
you're aware of my dad's identity.
What?
Why else
would he come and say goodbye to me?
I promised him to keep it as secret.
It's fine.
Once I'm strong enough,
I'll ask him myself.
Master,
I want to attend the best school
and be the strongest Soul Master.
I'll be with you.
The governor of Nuoding
is looking for you.
Most schools are no-go.
Any alternatives?
Martial Soul Hall or the seven clans.
Comparing both,
Martial Soul Hall
has the best resource and teachers.
But my dad prohibits me
from attending Martial Soul Hall.
It's okay.
Wu can go.
Master, can you help Wu then?
I'll go wherever you go.
No need to persuade me.
You're wasting your time.
Master.
What about the seven clans?
Other than normal schools
and Martial Soul Hall,
in Douluo Continent, there are
seven renowned Soul Master tribes.
These seven tribes stick to themselves
and established their own school.
Can we join?
Yes,
but when you're done,
you have to work for the clan.
That's only fair.
For how long?
The rest of your life.
And outsiders
are shunned
by the in-house Soul Masters.
So outsiders like us
can never succeed then?
Who do these clans
treat outsiders so?
Every clan
wants to control their own Soul Masters.
This is inevitable.
Any other option?
If you don't want
to be bound to any party,
there's one option:
Devil's School.
Stop!
It's not like this.
No?
Of course not.
Devil's School is a nickname.
Every student there
is powerful beyond comprehension,
like a real devil.
That powerful?
The first principal, Shi,
is a legendary being.
Hence the school name.
What's his full name?
Shi Lan Ke.
Devil's School sounds better.
Regardless of your status
or secret,
everyone is equal there.
Where is this Shi Lan Ke School?
In Suo Tuo City.
Suo Tuo City belongs to Tian Dou Empire.
To commemorate
an old but beautiful love story,
the two cities in this empire
are named after
Suo Tuo and Fei Ren.
As time goes by,
Fei Ren City is in ruin
while Suo Tuo City continues to prosper.
All right. That's all.
It's quite far from here.
Rest early.
We'll move at sunrise.
Okay!
Wait,
one more thing.
What?
The rite.
Hold on.
The rite of apprenticeship is no
trifling matter on Douluo Continent.
We can only
have one mentor in our life.
I know. I'll kowtow.
I have two Soul Rings like you.
You'll surpass me in no time.
But you've long studied Martial Soul.
You're knowledgeable.
You deserve a better, stronger mentor.
But that's not what I want.
What then?
The confidence you gave me.
You told me that
Blue Silver Plant was useful.
You accompanied me
to Soul Hunting Forest.
You helped me find my Soul Ring.
That's just a deal.
I walked the talk.
But you used
your body to block the attack
from Thorn Apple Snake.
It was the heat of the moment.
This time,
you could've escaped alone.
Yet you came to
Saint of Soul Village with me.
You saved me
when the Haunted Vine attacked me.
You were injured due to me.
You saved me too.
And now
my wounds are healed.
Also,
my dad trusts you.
Need I say more?
You don't understand.
I'm useless.
If you want to be stronger,
you need to pick
someone powerful with a lot of resources
as your mentor.
If becoming stronger
means abandoning
my friend with whom
I went through life and death,
then what's the point of being strong?
You're the teacher
I trust and respect the most.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
You're crying.
Crying?
No, I'm not.
Impossible.
Do you miss your dad?
I...
I don't know when
he'll be back again.
Last time when I left Nuoding
and home,
I felt like he'd be at home,
waiting for me.
It reassured me.
But this time,
I really don't have anyone else.
Cry it all out then.
I think
crying makes people weak.
Really?
Truth be told,
I cried a lot
when my parents died.
When I thought that
I couldn't see them again,
my tears came gushing out.
That time,
my eyes were as red as bunny eyes.
But Da Ming told me that
tears built character.
So I think you should cry.
After crying,
I felt much better.
Tang San,
you don't have a family now.
Neither do I.
What if from now onwards,
we'll be each other family.
And during tough times,
we can stand by each other.
Perhaps we'll feel better.
No?
Sure.
For real?
Then that's a promise.
From now onwards,
you're my sister.
I've always wanted a sister.
What?
Does this mean
I have to call you Brother San?
I'll sound like a kid.
You just have to keep it in mind.
You can still call me Tang San as usual.
All right then.
Will you
still braid my hair?
Of course.
Great.
That's a deal then.
From now onwards,
you're my sister.
No matter what happens,
I'll protect you.
I swear.
I'm also very strong.
I can protect you.
Rose Inn
Come.
Come here.
This is Rose Inn.
Why are we here
instead of the school?
Yeah.
Shi Lan Ke School has no fixed location.
To enter Shi Lan Ke,
the first step
is to enter this inn
and take the admission exam.
What kind of exam?
It's different every time.
In short, it's unorthodox.
Here.
Go ahead.
Let's see what
Devil's School has to offer.
That sounds interesting.
Let's go.
Hi.
We here to enroll into Devil's School.
Pay the registration fee.
How much?
50 Gold Soul Coins.
Fif...
So expensive.
25 per student?
No, 50 per student.
Check if we have it.
Give us a moment.
Too expensive.
That's all?
This is Rose Inn.
He should be inside.
For registration?
50 Gold Soul Coins, please.
Backyard.
Find a room yourself.
Move along then.
Sir.
She's so rich.
How about you two?
We
still need some money.
Learning tricks out in the wild
is no easy feat.
If it's just 7 or 8 Gold Soul Coins,
we can still make an exception.
Other than this one Gold Soul Coin
and other changes,
we still need
3,000...
3,975 Copper Soul Coins.
That's a lot.
Let's go then.
Uhm...
the amount doesn't matter.
After all, fate brought us together.
Right?
What matters the most?
Kindness, don't you think?
Kindness.
Where are you two from?
Saint of Soul Village.
I see.
You've heard of it?
No.
You must be from somewhere far away.
You two must be exhausted, right?
As for Gold Soul Coins,
every bit counts.
No?
I couldn't agree more.
You're here,
just leave after the exam.
I mean,
you might as well take the exam.
Here, please.
Come.
Kindness is so important.
Remember that.
Where's Dai Mu Bai?
Looking for me?
I'd like a duel.
Sure.
No! No!
Who's going to pay
when you break everything here?
Inside.
Okay.
You...
Miss.
Today is not a good day for a duel.
Move away.
No,
he's gone.
I've been looking for him.
Move away.
Miss.
Today
is the first day of registration.
It's a sacred day.
We shouldn't fight.
Back off.
I have an idea.
An idea, Miss.
You can pay for the registration.
What?
Once you pay up,
you can find Dai Mu Bai in the backyard.
When you find him,
you can challenge him to a duel.
I'm not here for the registration.
Who cares?
Look,
if you pay,
you can find Dai Mu Bai
and duel him in the backyard.
Target achieved!
How much?
50 Gold Soul Coins.
Boss, look, more than 50.
This girl is decisive.
Exactly.
So decisive.
You two,
backyard, please.
Here.
It's not refundable.
No.
Is this for sale?
Boss.
This crystal
is murky and opaque.
No one wants it.
I want it.
It may look ugly
but it has potential.
Look,
you don't seem like a bad person.
How about 10 Gold Soul Coins?
10 Gold Soul Coins?
I don't have money.
How much do you have?
All my money
is in that pouch.
Oh well. Too bad.
Let's go then.
Hold on.
Can we buy it with this?
This is some excellent herbal medicine
found deep within the Star Forest.
Is this worth 10 Gold Soul Coins?
Let me see.
I...
That's worth 20 Gold Soul Coins.
Take it then.
We want this.
Not enough.
What do you mean?
I made a mistake.
The crystal costs 30 Gold Soul Coins.
But you said 10 Gold Soul Coins.
No, 30 Gold Soul Coins.
Look.
You can't increase the price on a whim!
I'm forgetful.
This huge crystal
costs 50 Gold Soul Coins.
Fif...
We're not interested.
Sorry.
Let's go, Wu.
Why do you want this?
Because it's
a good smelting material.
How good?
High quality.
Honesty.
You two passed the first test.
Why speak the truth?
If you say it's useless,
perhaps
I'll name a cheaper price.
But I shouldn't lie.
Let's go.
I really don't have money.
It's a gift.
A gift?
Thanks, sir.
Let's go to the backyard then.
Give me a sec.
Miss.
Where's Dai Mu Bai?
He disappeared.
Hi, I'm Ou Si Ke.
I'm here for Dai Mu Bai.
Here.
I've heard of
your situation with him.
But the registration is over
and we have to organise
the admission exam.
We have rules
for everything, right?
You can't fight whenever you want.
Summon him.
I'll tell him myself.
Let's go somewhere.
Here.
This
is how I see it.
I'm fine
with a duel
but you plan to win,
right?
You arrived here
after a long journey.
Fighting him now
is disadvantageous.
After a long journey,
your stamina and mental state
are not at their peak.
What you need now
is some rest.
Don't you think?
Rest and recover
before fighting him.
There's an empty room there.
You can rest a bit.
I'll bring you some refreshments
and food.
Face wash too.
I'll bring them.
Cool?
Sorry.
Come with me.
This is the room for students.
Individual suite.
This is yours.
This is an individual suite?
Others paid 50 Gold Soul Coins.
You two can only afford
the price of one room.
I have some change here.
I think we're good here.
No worries.
Thanks.
I mean, boy and girl alone...
I don't mind.
It's not like that.
I'm not thinking about anything.
When's the exam?
What do we need?
I'm not sure
about the time and date.
But try not to
leave the backyard.
Are you from Shi Lan Ke School?
Not at all.
I'm just an inn staff.
I'm Tang San.
I'm Wu.
Tang San, Tang Wu.
Where's Tang Si?
It's the dancing "Wu".
My bad.
I shouldn't assume.
I'm
Ou Si Ke.
"Si" means yearning and "Ke" means guests.
Interesting name.
Really?
I prefer
you guys' name.
Simple and easy to remember.
Brother Ou,
can you lend me a hammer?
A hammer?
Here.
Thanks, Brother Ou.
If you need something else,
ask me.
Okay.
Why do you need a hammer?
What is this?
A tabular crystal.
[*It sounds similar to beef backstrap.]
For roasting?
It's a crystal.
Look carefully.
Impurity?
Acicular crystal.
I want them.
Cover the ears.
I mean your own ears.
It's not broken.
And then?
Are you looking for those thin strips?
I can't find any.
Are they destroyed?
Here.
It's not a thin strip.
What's this?
It will appear
once it's infused with Soul Power.
Try pulling it out.
This thing
can pierce a lot of things.
It will shrink without Soul Power.
Once ingested,
it can open the wound instantly.
Interesting.
It also goes by
Dragon's Beard.
Tiny but fatal.
Tabular crystal is rare
but Dragon's Beard of such quality
is even rarer.
How do you know so much?
It's on Xuan Tian Records.
What's that?
It's a book.
When I was small, my dad let me
learn some skills from it.
Some to train my eyes.
Some to train my dodging.
Some about
machinery and rare items.
Dragon's Beard was on it.
It sounds so cool.
What's odd is that
after getting my Martial Soul,
I realize I can mix Soul Power
with those skills I learnt
from Xuan Tian Records.
They are even more powerful.
How so?
I don't know.
Why didn't you ask Master?
I can't.
I promised my dad
not to tell anyone about
Xuan Tian Records.
Then why did you tell me?
Because you're my sister now.
Right, I'm your sister now.
Don't worry.
Your secret is safe with me.
Let's take half each.
This thing is strong.
Only use it as your
last resort.
Don't forget.
Hold on.
Come in.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
Here.
Thanks.
You're done with it?
What did you destroy?
Tabular crystal.
Backstrap?
Why use a hammer on the backstrap?
Isn't it supposed to be roasted?
Not that. It's a tabular crystal.
Not beef backstrap?
Anything else?
Oh yes.
Come.
From now onwards,
we have to be careful
in this backyard.
Why?
One night,
I couldn't sleep well so I got up.
Guess what I found out?
Why couldn't you sleep?
Too cold.
The windows were open?
Maybe.
No blanket?
It's on the floor.
Your sleeping posture was bad.
In that case,
it'd be...
What sleeping posture?
I...
Where was I?
Bad sleeping posture.
It's...
Before that.
You woke up one night.
I woke up one night.
Guess what I saw.
I saw a human shadow
on my window.
A human shadow?
He's moving left and right
on my windows.
And poof, he's gone.
Isn't that scary?
You have bad eyesight.
Astigmatism I reckon.
I'm talking about a shadow.
A human shadow.
I'm...
Perhaps it was the admission exam?
It might be a school teacher.
What if it's a bad guy?
I don't think so.
Looks can be deceiving.
What if those people
are the enemies of the school.
What to do?
Also, look,
an admission exam
of a never-before-seen school
in an inn.
Isn't it odd?
Then why did you take the money?
It's...
My job and the school
are two different things.
Just be careful
from now onwards.
Be very cautious.
Sure.
Also,
never have a barbecue indoor.
If you break anything,
you have to pay.
Thank you.
Bye then.
Be very, very cautious.
Sweet dream.
Stay alert!
Is the school safe?
I don't know
but we have no other choice.
Master said that
there's only this school left for us.
True.
I wonder when the exam starts.
Those here for the exam,
come out now.
A troublemaker?
Is he looking for a fight?
Eh?
I didn't know Shi Lan Ke School
was for cowards.
No one?
Ou Si Ke?
What should we do?
Let's see what he wants first.
I'm not from Shi Lan Ke.
I'm just an inn staff.
I...
To put it simply,
Shi Lan Ke School and I have a history.
Rose Inn helps Shi Lan Ke
organize the admission exam,
which means it's just as guilty.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪