Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 6
If you don't let go now,
your Martial Soul will be destroyed.
Let go of your hand!
Without pain, without sacrifice,
how I'm going to lead my way?
No.
You have burned your Blue Silver Plant.
If you don't want to lose your power
you better stop that right now!
Tang San!
Let go of your hand.
Open...!
Tang San! Tang San!
Finally.
Tang san!
Tang San!
Are you okay?
Don't waste your energy anymore.
Master.
Tang San... Tang San's
Blue Silver Plant.
Is it damaged?
Wu.
Wu!
Tang San.
What a surprise.
Wu got the Century Soul Ring as well.
Both of you are incredible.
Anyway.
No matter how impressive you are
you couldn't beat all of us.
Also, one of you had injured.
Whilst the other one...
has lost his power.
Last chance.
Be my follower.
Your Martial Soul has damaged and
you still want to fight back?
You're such a stubborn person.
You are just a footman
and you want to save him?
Double Soul Rings.
That's a pity. Only you alone.
I wonder what makes you stand out
in my uncle's mind.
Rubbish!
Plug your nose.
Watch properly.
This is my Second Soul Skill.
Break wind like mist,
mesmerize to deep sleep Luo San Pao!
I've seen this before.
Hold your breath.
What kind of Soul Skill is this?
Let's go!
You... You can't run away from me.
I will go to Saint of Soul Village
and catch all of your family members.
Don't you mess with a footman.
One more punch for me.
I'm the son of the governor.
You can't hit me.
I'm going to teach you
some manners today.
I'm bringing justice
to those people
who are oppressed by you.
I want to kill you.
I'm going to torture your whole family.
I'm going to torture your whole family!
My whole family?
I'd like to see you try!
Stop! Stop it.
I'm sorry.
Please don't hit me anymore.
This school failed to teach you
how to respect people.
That's why you became so disrespectful.
Before I leave,
I teach you this lesson.
You better learn from it.
It seems like fists are sometimes
quite effective at solving problems.
Let's go.
I want to kill you.
I want to kill all of you!
Xiao Chen Yu won't let us go.
We must leave Nuoding City now.
I need to go to the
Saint of Soul Village.
I'm going to bring my dad along.
Okay.
You planned to kill me from the
beginning, don't you?
I can release you and your dad.
Master.
The Luo San Pao just now
is your Second Soul Skill?
Yes.
That smog can cause dizziness.
You are invincible then.
Depend on your opponent.
If your opponent has more than
two Soul Rings,
it won't work anymore.
We need to be quick.
Soul Honour set up the cage.
If the Soul Honour finds us,
we won't be able to defeat him.
Move faster, Wu.
Quick.
Officer Ling Feng.
Who killed the young master?
What?
Young master.
Tell me. Who did this?
It's Tang San.
Who is Tang San?
Tang San...
Tang San is one of the students.
And there is another student called Wu.
And a footman in school backing him up.
Why did nobody ask me to come here?
Young master said that
he doesn't want the governor
to know about this matter.
Where is Tang San?
Tang San comes from the
Saint of Soul Village.
What is the level of the two students?
Tang San and Wu
both have a century Soul Ring.
How about the footman?
I... I ... I...
I lost my consciousness.
I didn't know about
things that come up later.
But
that master is close to the headmaster.
We do not dare to hurt him.
But based on your capability,
they will surely fall into your hands.
I didn't plan to catch them.
Not... Not catching them?
Wake up the rest.
Head to Saint of Soul Village.
You know what kind of person
the governor is.
If we don't kill the murderer
everyone here
has to die.
This is the place I lived
since I was born.
My house is right in front.
Dad, I'm back.
He must have been drunk again.
I guess he is inside.
Dad.
Not here.
Perhaps he went to the
neighbour's house.
Based on the condition of this house
seems like it has been deserted
for quite some time.
How... How could that be possible?
Let's talk about your problem first.
Show me your Martial Soul.
What... What happened to it?
Is it damaged?
Not really.
But the basis has been affected.
The electric current on the cage
is the power of the Soul Honour.
You held on to it for too long.
That will cause some bad effects.
How long will it take to recover?
Will it get better?
We still have a choice.
What is that?
Get the Second Soul Ring
as soon as possible.
On our way here,
I've been thinking about
how to heal your Blue Silver Plant.
According to my analysis,
there is a prerequisite.
That is finding
a Soul Beast that has the same
traits as plants.
But...
Plant?
Why?
But you just got your First Soul Ring.
You didn't have time to refine
and accumulate your Soul Power.
If you absorb
the Second Soul Ring now,
the chances of failure
will be very high.
How high is it?
Over ninety percent.
How could this be?
Even so, we still have
ten percent of hope.
And the worst thing is
we might not be able to find
the Second Soul Ring that suits you
in a short time.
It's all my fault. I'm too weak.
Unable to protect both of you.
But instead, put both of you
into trouble.
Master. No one is to blame.
It was me who ask your help to
get the Soul Ring.
Also, you being caught
because of me.
I can't just walk away.
Remember to kill all of them later.
Bring back their body.
As an explanation.
Yes.
Seize them.
Let the governor handle them.
Officer.
Three of them.
All bring back?
Kill on the spot.
What?
Not bringing them to the governor?
Officer.
Are you going to kill all of them now?
But...
Don't you feel that is too hasty?
Kill now,
or I will kill you later.
And send you together
with their body
to the governor.
Things had happened.
We didn't have any choice.
Dad.
Three of you.
Leave the Saint of Soul Village
immediately.
Runaway as far as you can and
don't come back again.
Leave Saint of Soul Village?
No, dad.
The reason we came back today
is due to some unexpected situations.
We fought with people in school.
Xiao Chen Yu has died.
Xiao Chen Yu has died?
That's impossible.
We just punch him several times.
But they insist that you killed him.
Dad.
No. I didn't kill anyone.
Those people in Nuoding City
might want all of you to pay for it.
I didn't kill Xiao Chen Yu.
They don't care about it.
They couldn't find the murderer.
So they want all of you to pay for it.
That doesn't make any sense.
Xiao Chen Yu has been killed.
The governor won't take it
lying down.
Wu.
I'll leave you here.
I got to go now.
Where are you going?
Find the village head.
You and master go first.
What are you talking about?
I'm not leaving.
I'm the one who has conflicts
with Xiao Chen Yu.
Also, I'm the person they want to find.
Both of us created the mess.
We should face it together.
No way.
Both of you leave now.
I will take full responsibility
for what I did.
I'm not leaving. I want to follow you.
But I worried I didn't have
enough strength
and unable to protect you.
I can protect you too.
Saint of Soul Village has
nothing to do with you.
But you have something
to do with me.
But...
No more excuses.
I'm a smart person.
You'll never get rid of me.
And this time
we can work together.
There will be higher chances
of winning.
If we didn't defeat them this time,
they will surely
keep troubling us.
Alright.
That's great!
I can fight together with you again.
This time
I'm going to beat the pants off them.
You are such a brave girl.
Of course. I'm the boss.
Quick. I'm afraid they might
arrive here soon.
Let's go.
Why are you still here?
You look familiar.
Did you work here before
as a knife smith?
No.
But I'm sure we met a long time ago.
Is you?
I thought you were dead?
Have you ever thought
what will happen to you
after find out who am I?
Hao Tian Hammer!
I almost couldn't
recognize you.
This is a Meteorite.
It is tougher than most substances
in the world.
What is it used for?
To seal.
There is a Hunted Vine underneath.
How old is it?
Six hundred years.
Almost to its limit.
And a Plant Branch Soul Beast.
It can be used as Tang San's Second Soul Ring.
The Martial Soul of Tang San
can finally restore.
Looks like you didn't
break it completely.
It has been sealed for many years.
I'm afraid it hasn't awakened.
A Hunted Vine with Plant Branch Soul Beast
is rarely seen.
How did you find it?
Tang San's mother kept it for him.
She also prepared
the Soul Beast of the First Soul Ring.
But...
the Thorn Apple Snake
you chose for him in Soul Hunting Forest
is more suitable.
So you were there during that time.
When you witness Tang San
fighting between life and death
with Thorn Apple Snake
why you didn't help him out?
He had to depend
on himself.
How about the Governor Office?
Do you plan to let him die too?
I will help him for the last time.
But you must promise me that
you won't say a word
about my past to him.
That's what happened in Nuoding City.
Those people in Governor Office
will arrive here in no time.
Village Head.
I know I have made a big mess this time
and might get everyone into trouble.
I have an idea.
Village Head, please tie me up
and send me to them.
I...
Only in this way
I can disassociate myself
from the Saint of Soul Village
and won't get the others into trouble.
You...
Please tie me up.
Me too.
I...
Officer.
Over there.
Officer. It's them.
Tang San and Wu.
Is it true that
young master Xiao has died?
Do you want to say that
you didn't kill him?
I really didn't kill him.
I never kill anyone.
Officer. We have got them.
Are we bringing them back
and send to the governor
for interrogation?
I remember the record in the
Office of Administration
clearly stated that
he has a dad who works as a
metalsmith in this village.
Yes.
Where is his house?
This thing has nothing to do
with my dad.
Young master has died.
Both of you are simply not enough.
I didn't kill anyone.
You want Tang San
to carry it alone?
I'll leave everything here to you.
What do you mean?
All of you stay in this village.
I will go to Nuoding City
to settle the source of this problem.
What if they reach here?
You can help him.
But how?
I only have double Soul Rings.
You're from the Blue Lightning
Tyrant tribe, right?
How did you know about that?
The Martial Soul of your family
is Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon.
And the mutation of Luo San Pao
is clearly because of
Blue Lightning Tyrant Dragon
mutate in the wrong way.
Since you know about my strength,
you should aware that if here comes
someone stronger than me,
I won't be able to defeat him.
Let Tang San help you.
Tang San only has one Soul Ring.
Also, his ring is not stable.
You have Hunted Vine under the bed.
What if we fail?
Have you ever thought about
what will happen to Tang San?
He has to take full
responsibility for his action.
I need to go now.
Tang San has nothing to do with me.
Why should I stay?
Don't you worry I run away?
Whatever.
I won't risk my life staying here.
Did I owe both of you anything?
Officer.
Since we are here
how about we let the village head go?
Kill him.
He is the village head.
He is unlucky today.
Why?
Why you want to kill an
innocent person.
He is your village head.
So he is not considered innocent.
I said kill him.
Do you hear me?
Officer.
That guy is with them.
Bring him out.
What is the thing down there?
Nothing down there.
How dare you lie to me.
I...
Plant Branch Soul Beast.
Thunderbird Spike!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Village Head, you leave first.
You heard him. He wants to
kill the villagers.
Tang San, I...
Parasite.
This thing can parasitize.
Electric Light Rotation!
Let's go.
Master. Where is my dad?
What... What is this thing?
This is Hunted Vine.
Six hundred years old.
It can be used as your
Second Soul Ring.
The Hunted Vine can grow in an
adverse environment.
According to my mimicry theory,
It can make up your
damaged Martial Soul.
But... But why is it
under my house?
This creature is too strong.
How are we going to kill it?
Not now.
We can borrow its power
to attack the Soul Honour outside.
I think his Martial Soul is
Thunderbird.
The First Soul Skill is
Electric Current Spike.
And his Third Soul Skill is
Electric Ring Defense.
Beware of these.
Then we will get the chance
to attack him.
What about his Second Soul skill?
When he caught us,
an electric current was set
on the cage
I guess that is his Second Soul Skill.
Can we use Hunted Vine to attack him?
We can't.
The Hunted Vine will bring the
electric current through
the roots to the earth
for it to attack temporarily.
After a long time,
it will still be defeated.
I will attack him from behind.
You can't.
Tang San must do it by himself.
Why?
The Martial Soul of Tang San is
Blue Silver Plant.
Soul Power will diffuse.
The Hunted Vine will treat
you as a plant in short term.
So, it won't attack you.
But... But my Blue Silver Plant had...
You don't need a complete Martial Soul.
Maintain your Soul Power.
Just like that.
I will go right now.
Tang San.
You must remember that
you can't use your Martial Soul now
and couldn't kill.
So, find a way to
let the Hunted Vine coil around him.
The Hunted Vine can parasitize.
That way, he will be defeated.
Purple Demon Eye!
Electric. Fade.
Electric.
Fade!
A simple trick
doesn't work on my third Soul Ring.
Mesmerize to deep sleep Luo San Pao!
I will let Luo San Pao
divert his attention.
But you need to find something
to block his electric current
temporarily.
How about the plank in the courtyard?
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
I did it.
He has been parasitized.
Chop it off right away?
What... What if it attacks me?
What I'm going to do?
Try to avoid it.
Alright. I got it.
Let me remind you again.
You just got your First Soul Ring.
So, if you absorb
the Second Soul Ring right now,
you will put your body under
extreme stress.
The pain you feel will be
much higher than usual.
Survive or not,
it all depends on your will.
How about we try it next time.
The Hunted Vine is very hard to find.
And the worst thing is
if he doesn't
absorb the Second Soul Ring now
his Blue Silver Plant will be
completely damaged.
Tang San.
You still have ten percent
of hope.
It's up to you to decide
whether want to give it a go.
I must become a Soul Master.
I'm going to risk it all no matter what.
I want to stay by his side.
Upgrade Soul Power
is the ordeal that everyone
must go through by themselves.
No one can help.
Endure no matter how hard it is.
You will be alright after wake up.
Trust me.
No.
Better trust my Martial Soul theory.
You can't go wrong.
It is just a plant.
I chop firewood since I was
a kid. No problem.
Tang San.
You need it more than me now.
Wait for me outside.
Alright.
Ghostly Trace.
Watch out!
Master!
Hang in there.
Tang San!
The governor won't forgive
all of you.
Tang San.
Tang San. Wake up.
What...
What should I do?
Tang San. Wake up.
Tang San!
He will be fine as long as
he could wake up.
Why he is not awake?
Let me try this.
Tang San.
Tang San. Wake up.
Tang San. You are awake.
Wu.
Master.
Master protected me from
a sudden attack by The Hunted Vine just now.
Where is he?
Over there.
Bring me there.
Master.
Master, wake up.
Master. He is awake.
He is awake.
Come.
Over here.
I knew you can make it.
Come.
Release Martial Soul.
You did it!
Tang San,
I guess you are the fastest among
all the Soul Masters
to get the double Soul Rings.
What kind of Soul Skill
does your Second Soul Ring bring to you?
I guess it only works on living things.
Living things?
Master, you had injured.
How about trying it on me.
I can make it.
Come on.
Aren't you wanting to save me just now?
The branch of this Hunted Vine
has parasitized my body.
I guess
only your Blue Silver Plant
can wipe them out entirely.
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Just control the intensity of
your Soul Power.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪