(Episode 7)
How did the necklace
investigation go?
We found a trace
of Bae Ro Na's blood.
It matches precisely
with Bae Ro Na's DNA.
Bae Ro Na's blood
on Ha Eun Byeol's necklace?
Things are getting fun.
- When is her funeral?
- It's today.
Who's attending?
Ms. Oh Yoon Hee didn't break
the news to anyone.
I believe it'll be
just her husband, Mr. Ha.
I guess her parents weren't
too good to the people around them.
Looks like it'll be
a lonely funeral.
(Cheon Seo Jin)
I told you that today is
Ro Na's funeral!
I told you to not call!
Our Eun Byeol!
You need to come home right now.
- Eun Byeol!
- What's going on?
Mom!
You need to come right now!
Eun Byeol!
No! Eun Byeol!
I'm sorry, Yoon Hee. There's
an emergency at work.
I can't get out of it.
(Bae Ro Na)
Are you in that big a rush to die?
Let go.
I'm going to Ro Na.
I can't let my daughter go
all by herself.
Do you think I saved you to do this?
I'll punish myself.
You can die when you want to,
but you need to find out
who did this to Ro Na.
The real killer...
is someone else.
The real killer?
Who is it?
Ha Eun Byeol.
And behind that, is Cheon Seo Jin.
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! What's wrong with you?
- Get away from me!
- Eun Byeol!
No! Eun Byeol!
Go away!
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol, Mom is right here.
Please come back to your senses!
Mom.
Over there. There's Ro Na.
Over there!
No, she isn't!
Ro Na is dead.
How many times do I need to tell you
that she's not coming back?
No! She's over there.
There's Ro Na right there.
Don't come.
No!
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol.
- Eun Byeol!
- It's okay, Eun Byeol.
It's okay, my child.
Please save me, Dad.
I'm too scared.
It's driving me crazy.
Ro Na keeps showing up.
She tells me to die.
That laugh...
Eun Byeol.
What should I do?
Please carve it out of my brain.
You're a doctor.
Please remove Ro Na
from my brain!
Eun Byeol. Eun Byeol. No.
Eun Byeol!
Please help me, Dad.
I want to sleep.
I'll protect you.
Trust me.
I'll do whatever it takes...
to erase your memory.
Dad...
- Eun Byeol...
- Dad...
Get it together, Yoon Hee.
Will you crumble like this?
Are you sure...
it was Eun Byeol?
Stay alive and confirm for yourself.
No.
I don't want to.
What can I do now, anyway?
If I hadn't come back
to get revenge,
Ro Na wouldn't have died.
Why did I care so much
about taking revenge?
Why did you send my daughter here?
You should've stopped her.
You should've
stopped her at all costs!
Do you really not know
why Ro Na came back?
She asked me.
Please send me to Korea.
No. It's too dangerous.
I want to fulfill
Seol A's dream for her.
I promise to win
the grand prize trophy...
from Cheong A Art Festival.
Then Seol A...
may forgive my mom a little bit.
Why did you do it?
For me...
Why did you do that for me?
Why did you do that for me, Ro Na?
Will you still die?
Why did you do that?
- No!
- If you truly wish to die...
- What am I supposed to do?
- Just die.
If you're going to fall into despair
and implode like this,
just die as those scumbags want.
But remember one thing.
Ha Yoon Chul...
was involved in Ro Na's death.
Wait.
What did you just say?
Did you say "Yoon Chul"?
No way.
You're mistaken. He'd never do that.
Yoon Chul is with
Eun Byeol right now.
He knows that his daughter did it.
What?
If your daughter's murderer
living happily is fine with you,
do as you wish.
No.
Yoon Chul wouldn't...
Yoon Chul wouldn't do that. No.
No! It can't be!
Yoon Chul wouldn't do that!
That's the only way.
It's what Eun Byeol wants.
There may be side effects.
There may not be.
She's only 19 years old.
She has more days to live
than the stars in the sky.
We can't tell her...
to live each of them in torment.
How could we?
Yes. I'm sure it'll be fine.
It'll be fine.
Please join me...
so Ro Na isn't lonely
as she leaves. Please.
I'll wait for you.
Who are you?
Su Ryeon?
How have you been?
It's been a while,
Joo Dan Tae.
What are you doing?
You're always so rough
with your greetings.
Ae Gyo?
Zip it back up.
What?
Did you think Su Ryeon
came back to life?
Were you shocked, Dan Tae?
You really were.
How adorable.
What's going on? When did you come?
I came straight here...
as soon as I landed.
So?
Did you like your surprise?
You're still a pro
at surprising people.
You should've told me
you were coming.
I would've picked you up.
That's so lame.
You know I hate things like that.
I was trapped
in that hick town for two years.
It was hot and humid.
That annoying weather
drove me crazy.
Then you should've come sooner.
Why did you refuse to come?
If you refused again this month,
I was planning to go get you
personally.
Su Ryeon died.
It felt weird.
As if...
I had died.
Sure. I guess that's understandable.
You lived half of your life
as Su Ryeon.
No one saw you, right?
All the helpers went out.
They're coming after 3 p.m.
The penthouse.
This place is insane.
How much is all of this worth?
Just these few items here...
would be about a million dollars.
Su Ryeon was so lucky.
She enjoyed this luxury
all her life.
But what's the use?
It's over once you drop dead.
You can't stay here.
The kids will be back soon.
We don't want the other residents
to see you either,
so let's talk somewhere else.
So what?
Aren't they going to
find out soon anyway?
That I'm Seok Hoon
and Seok Kyung's real mom.
Then why did you tell me to come?
I didn't tell the kids yet.
They're sensitive right now.
They need time to accept it.
Gibberish!
Why do they still need time?
It's not like
I'm going to raise them.
What I want is this penthouse.
Not being their mom.
Wearing long dresses
that are so not my style,
chugging expensive wine
that I don't even like...
I lived as Su Ryeon for...
20 years!
Aren't I qualified
to enjoy this now?
Hello. I'm Shim Su Ryeon.
I heard so much about you
from my late father.
So you have a special relationship
with Simoon Construction?
Gosh, I'm sick of it.
Didn't you say that I can live
as Na Ae Gyo at this penthouse?
You will, I promise.
Just wait until I sort things out.
How can I trust you?
This drug is still being
clinically tested.
It can make a person forget
recent traumatic events.
What are the side effects?
The patient may have a seizure
while the drug is administered.
It can also distort
the patient's memories.
In the worst-case scenario,
she may lose all her memories.
Eun Byeol has...
always been a lucky girl.
Please get started.
(Yoon Hee)
The person you have reached is
unavailable. Please leave...
Ro Na, wait for me.
Ro Na, wait!
Let's go.
Get your hands off of my daughter!
Ro Na!
If you lay a finger on
our Ro Na one more time,
I'm going to sue you all.
No. It can't be.
I don't believe that Yoon Chul
can be so mean.
Logan must be mistaken.
Yoon Chul will come. I'm sure of it.
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! What should we do?
What is going on?
- Eun Byeol!
- Move.
Eun Byeol, are you okay?
Eun Byeol, I'm right here.
Eun Byeol! What should we do?
The drug was administered too fast,
so she went into shock.
I gave her a sedative.
She'll be fine now.
(Yoon Hee)
Was our goal Hera Palace
that has only 100 floors?
A taller, fancier building
will be built soon.
In Cheonsoo District.
Did you win the development rights?
The land compensation
must be immense.
Not a problem.
I know Seo Jin's weakness.
Her weakness?
I didn't expect a woman like her
to have weaknesses.
Intriguing.
So what is it?
Her daughter killed a girl.
What's more, the girl's mother
detests Seo Jin more than anyone.
To be fair, Seo Jin loathes her
quite strongly as well.
She killed a girl?
No matter how cold-hearted
Seo Jin can be,
she couldn't sit back
and let her daughter...
end up in prison.
This is my chance to take over
the entire Cheong A Group.
Cheong A will be ours.
Are you serious?
Are you saying that Joo Dan Tae
Village will be completed soon?
Just be careful not to get caught.
If anyone finds you out,
all our plans will go up in smoke.
This is exciting.
A new penthouse
in Cheonsoo District?
Just the thought of it
makes me thrilled.
You know it's mine, right?
So don't act up and do as I say.
You've been waiting all your life...
to live with Seok Hoon
and Seok Kyung...
in a penthouse.
This is nice.
I can finally hear you
breathe again.
It must be the kids. Do you
want to see them from a distance?
Forget it. That's unnecessary.
I've been fine without seeing them
all these years.
It's not like I feel
any affection for them.
Come this way.
Don't you have a lesson today?
Are you skipping it again?
- Why?
- Leave me alone.
Gosh, I can't believe you.
Ladies first.
Do you like it?
(May the flower that fell too early
become a bright star in the sky.)
Ms. Oh.
Who was it?
Who bought you off that day?
Please don't do this.
Please forgive me. I'm sorry.
Who was it? Answer me!
Well...
(Ha Yoon Chul)
Ha Yoon Chul?
(Logan Lee)
Ha Yoon Chul...
Where is that jerk right now?
Get some sleep.
You didn't sleep at all last night.
Eun Byeol will...
wake up safe, right?
And all the bad memories
will be gone, right?
Yes, definitely.
Without you,
I couldn't have done this.
Seeing you genuinely worry
about Eun Byeol...
and do all you can do for her,
I realized this.
Both Eun Byeol...
and I...
need you.
(Restricted Area)
(Cheong A Medical Center)
But remember one thing.
Ha Yoon Chul was
involved in Ro Na's death.
My daughter is dead.
And you're busy trying to save your
daughter from becoming a murderer?
My baby died
because of your daughter!
Do you feel more sorry for your
murderer daughter than my daughter?
Why should your daughter be happy?
She doesn't deserve happiness.
- No!
- Yoon Hee! No!
No!
Seok Hoon, are you really being
like this because of Ro Na?
You won't eat, you won't talk,
and won't do anything.
How many days has it been?
Don't you think you're overreacting?
Shut up...
if you're the slightest bit sorry.
Why should I be sorry?
I'm not the one
who committed the murder.
I know who killed Ro Na.
She must be so happy...
now that her eyesore is gone.
That's right.
It's who you think it is.
Ha Eun Byeol. It's her.
What proof do you have?
I played a little joke on Eun Byeol,
telling her that you're
absolutely in love with Ro Na.
She then went crazy.
But still, how can she kill someone?
I didn't expect this at all!
What have you done?
Why did you do that?
What has...
Ro Na ever done?
Don't go.
Don't go to Yoon Hee.
I have to go.
I missed Ro Na's funeral.
She must be struggling alone.
Don't you think this is
even harsher on Yoon Hee?
Your daughter killed Yoon Hee's,
and yet, you want to lie to her
and stay with her?
Don't you think that's truly insane?
What will she say
when she finds out?
She'll probably rip
all of us apart...
because she's mortified.
So what?
If Yoon Hee wants me to die,
so be it.
Both you...
and I.
Can we...
start over?
- Are you insane?
- I know...
how much of a heartbreak
I've caused you.
I'm sorry. I'll be sorry
until the day I die.
Forgive me.
Give me one more chance.
I'll be good to you forever.
Don't you dare to think...
that I'm here because I love you
and I feel bad for you.
I'm here...
because I have no choice.
I'm Eun Byeol's dad.
I'm not yours anymore.
My head is only filled
with Yoon Hee.
You and Yoon Hee are over!
Don't you understand?
I'm not doing this only for myself.
It's for Eun Byeol.
If you would just change your mind,
our family can go back
to how things were before.
We can be happy.
Happy?
You think...
we deserve any happiness?
Don't leave.
Don't leave me!
Don't leave me for Yoon Hee!
Please.
Goodness.
Poor you.
You must be so disheartened
that Ro Na is dead.
When's the funeral?
Make sure to give me a call.
I, Kyu Jin,
will at least send the biggest
flower arrangement.
You need a floral arrangement
from an assemblyman at a funeral...
to make the funeral look good.
Poor Yoon Hee!
What is she going to do?
You're drunk. Let's head in.
But you know,
the more I think about it,
the person who killed Ro Na,
I don't think it's Mr. Park.
Min Hyuk told me...
that Mr. Park absolutely
adored Ro Na.
The case is already closed.
He turned himself in.
You're right.
The murderer turned himself in.
But you know,
even when Min Seol A died,
everyone said it was a suicide...
except for me.
I knew that she was murdered.
It could be...
that the murderer is
inside Hera Palace again.
Hey!
Cheon Seo Jin.
It's not her, is it?
She didn't kill Ro Na
out of wrath...
after hearing that you and Yoon Hee
are getting married?
You punk!
If you're drunk, shut up
and go to sleep.
Don't blabber nonsense.
The phone is turned off.
Please leave a message
after the tone.
Are you awake now?
Are you okay?
You kept talking in sleep...
and were in pain all night.
How can you handle...
Cheon Seo Jin and Joo Dan Tae
when you're so fragile?
You'll have to battle
against Ha Yoon Chul too.
How much do you know
about Ro Na's death?
Tell me what I'm missing out on.
This is Eun Byeol and Seo Jin...
on the night of the incident.
I'm guessing...
that Eun Byeol's dress was in there.
I checked the dress myself.
There was nothing on it.
It took a lot of work to get this.
I went to every dress shop in Seoul.
They got the exact same dress made
at a different shop.
Then who set off the fire alarm?
Was that Cheon Seo Jin too?
Or...
Ha Yoon Chul?
Based on what we know so far,
those two didn't do that.
The time and their locations
don't match.
Are you saying it really went off
on its own? Right at that moment?
They must've told someone to do it.
Secretary Do or someone.
There's a good enough reason
for that to be possible.
We only have guessed so far.
We don't have definite evidence.
I'm going to kill Cheon Seo Jin.
I'm going to kill them all,
Ha Yoon Chul and Ha Eun Byeol!
Oh Yoon Hee!
It's too early for you to move.
I don't care.
I can just kill them...
and kill myself.
I don't want to live
a second longer.
Just being awake right now feels
like a nightmare.
You also made
someone else's child die.
If you're going to die,
you need to pay back...
what you owe Seol A
and Su Ryeon first.
That way, you'll be a little less
ashamed when you meet Ro Na.
What makes you so shameless?
You're the one who just took
the marrow and left her!
If you feel so sorry for Seol A,
your parents should pay
for what they've done first!
Ms. Oh!
Could you step outside for a bit?
I'm flying to the US soon.
Once I'm gone,
you're the only one who can take
revenge for Su Ryeon and Seol A.
I killed Min Seol A.
What right do I have to take
revenge for Seol A?
What can I possibly do?
Look for Na Ae Gyo.
The twins' real mother.
She knows
all of Joo Dan Tae's secrets.
I'm Na Ae Gyo.
I have something to tell you
before I leave.
I know what Joo Dan Tae did
to Shim Su Ryeon...
and what kind of a person he is.
I might never get to tell you
if I don't tell you today.
And as she said,
she disappeared that day.
- That's...
- It's Na Ae Gyo.
She looks just like Shim Su Ryeon.
- No way.
- You have to find her.
I've been tracing
Joo Dan Tae's move every day...
for the past two years,
and I couldn't find her.
But recently,
I got some news on her.
She just entered Korea
from Thailand last week.
She'll surely get in touch
with Joo Dan Tae.
What a surprise.
You're never awake at this hour,
let alone eat breakfast.
I woke up early. Maybe it's
because it's a different bed.
I got hungry.
What brings you here so early?
There are some things that need
to be taken care of urgently.
I need to sell all the buildings
in Gangnam under your name.
I need cash.
There are some great deals
in Cheonsoo District.
Before the redevelopment plans
are announced,
I need to purchase the land
at a good price.
Is that why...
you insisted so much
that I come to Korea early?
So that you can sell my buildings?
Of course not.
More than anything, I missed you.
Now that I think about it,
you've been looking great.
Is dating Seo Jin that great?
You know that it's all just a play.
You're the only woman I'll love.
Your acting improved.
Want to play a game?
We haven't played in a while.
You've gotten much better.
Seems like you've only been
playing pool in Thailand.
You were never a match for me.
I know.
Mom?
Mom!
Eun Byeol! I'm here.
Are you awake now?
Why did I sleep for so long?
Aren't I late for school?
You're at the hospital.
The hospital? Why am I here?
You couldn't sleep
and that must've thrown you off.
You just suddenly passed out.
I passed out?
What date is it today?
I need to get ready
for Cheong A Arts Festival.
It's over already.
What do you mean?
I don't remember any of it.
What about the grand prize?
Who won the grand prize?
The grand prize?
Ro Na got it.
Ro Na?
She really got the grand prize?
I'm sorry, Mom.
You must be so mad.
You really don't remember any of it?
Not even the fact
that Ro Na is dead?
Why is Ro Na dead?
Why all of a sudden?
Well,
there has been an accident.
I'll fill you in on it all.
Don't force yourself
to remember anything.
Why don't I remember anything?
Is something wrong with me?
I have midterms coming up.
The mock tests are coming up too.
I can't just ruin them all.
I need to go home right now.
I need to study.
No, you're not ill. It's fine.
You just need some rest at home.
It's all in the past.
Nothing happened.
It's okay.
She really doesn't seem
to remember anything,
from singing at
Cheong A Arts Festival...
to Ro Na's death.
She doesn't remember any of it.
There seem to be no side effects.
It's too early to relax.
Keep a good eye on her.
I'm taking her out of the hospital
as soon as I can.
She'll feel more at ease at home.
You'll...
come to see Eun Byeol, right?
I'll pick you up.
Where are you, Yoon Hee?
Welcome to the Hera Palace's lobby!
Doesn't it look like a lobby
at a luxury hotel abroad?
And this fountain.
It's our Hera Palace's landmark.
You should take a picture here.
Assemblyman Lee is the only member
of the National Assembly...
who lives in Hera Palace, isn't he?
We worry about
what people may think,
so we live in rentals.
That's ridiculous.
Is it a crime to be wealthy?
If you're going to be
an assemblyman,
you should know how to make money...
and scam people just enough.
If your family is poor,
how can you manage a nation?
I know, right?
It's not like you get paid
for being honorable.
Right? Let's take a picture.
Stand right there.
Okay. Kimchi. Cheeze.
Smile.
Sorry.
What's your problem?
I almost fell flat on my face.
Do those people know
that a person died here?
Are you insane?
What if they hear you?
How do you get more and more
shameless by the day?
How long has it been
since Ro Na died,
that you bring people here
with your "Kimchi. Cheese."
And laugh loudly like that?
You're an assemblyman's wife.
You need to work on
your personality.
Why that woman...
(Body scrub waitlist)
Number three!
Coming.
It's so nice seeing you here.
I hear you give
an amazing body scrub.
I wanted to see if your hands
are as fierce...
as your mouth, Ms. Jincheon.
Please lie down, ma'am.
That hurts.
Why are you scrubbing so hard?
Hey, lady. Are you trying
to skin me alive?
My apologies, ma'am.
I'll scrub lighter.
That's cold!
How can you make any money...
if you can't even get
the water temperature right?
It's hot.
My gosh. That feels nice.
Ms. Jincheon. Clip my toenails too.
For the ladies with me too.
That's not included
in the list of services.
I'll pay you five dollars more.
What? You won't do it?
Is five dollars not real money?
I guess you're too rich for that.
Where's the owner?
Is this the type of help you use?
Get the owner in here!
Hi.
Which of you old hags is the owner?
Which one of you is it?
Is this how you train your help?
Madam Chairman.
What brings you here?
Chairman?
She's Chairman Song Hee Soo
of Hyeyeon Group.
She's Chairman Byun
and she's Chairman Choi.
Get up and introduce yourself.
Hyeyeon...
Madam... Madam Chairman.
- Ms. Kang.
- Yes, ma'am.
Why are you taking low-lives
as customers and ruining your ears?
This is my job.
It's fine, madam.
I'm not fine.
You are someone I cherish.
And we're the only ones
who can call you "Ms. Jincheon".
Who dares to insult Ms. Jincheon?
Who was it?
Also. I won't use the same water
as political sewer rats.
Replace the water in the tubs.
Yes, madam.
Drain the tubs!
Okay!
How's my dear niece Jenny?
She's doing well.
She's busy preparing for college.
I said to call me if
anyone ever harasses you.
We'll go
and snuff the life out of them.
You keep too much to yourself.
You never ask for any favors.
I'll make you all
some nice, cold iced coffee.
- Let's go.
- Sure. Of all the...
What is going on here?
Darn it.
Honey. It's me, Kyu Jin.
Oh dear.
You must've had many clients.
You're all puffy.
You're totally...
Ms. Kang. You know
he's an annoying dirtbag.
Please be understanding
with your magnanimous heart.
Seriously. I could take you down
with a single punch. You...
What... Has that woman
lost her mind? How dare...
How dare you talk to
our Lady Kang that way?
"Lady Kang"?
Have you lost your mind?
Let go. Let go.
Hold it in.
Whatever it takes,
hold it in, please!
She's way on top of us.
Jenny's mom has secret connections
to the highest people.
What?
How do you feel?
Eun Byeol, I haven't seen you
since the festival.
What brings you here?
I came to see you...
and Eun Byeol.
Go to your room.
You weren't answering your phone.
Is something wrong?
Eun Byeol wasn't feeling well,
so I took her to the hospital
to get an IV.
I see. You went to the hospital.
Don't forget we're having lunch
with Assemblyman Lee tomorrow.
We are?
I forgot.
Can't we reschedule?
If we do,
who knows
what that big mouth may say.
He keeps going on and on
about how he helped us...
get the approval to construct
Cheong A Art Center.
It's driving me crazy.
It's just lunch,
so we can make it quick.
Okay?
(Cheong A Arts High School)
This is the song I'm going to sing
at the festival.
What do you think?
It'll be a good match...
with your voice.
I want to do a solo...
at the graduation.
Will you be my accompanist?
I never thought about it.
Please do it for me.
You will, right?
I'll think about it.
(Cheong A Arts High School)
So this is where you were.
I still can't believe
that Ro Na's dead.
I know who killed Ro Na.
Ha Eun Byeol. It's her.
How do you feel? Do you feel better?
You must've been very sick
if you had to miss school.
Yes. I was in the hospital.
Where were you...
when the festival ended?
That night?
They say I took too many sedatives,
so I had fainted in the school.
Mr. Do must have found me
and carried me home.
I don't remember anything else.
You were carried out?
Yes.
You didn't see Ro Na before
the grand prize announcement?
I didn't see her.
At least,
I don't remember seeing her.
You must be devastated
by Ro Na's death.
It's true that I hated her,
but I don't want to be jealous
of a dead girl.
So grieve as much as you want.
Seok Hoon.
What's wrong?
Eun Byeol.
Will you go out with me?
What?
Go out with me.
I think I really like you now.
Are you serious? Do you mean it?
- Cheers, everyone.
- Cheers.
Nothing beats drinking
during the day, right, Chairman Joo?
You seem to be slacking off
more and more blatantly.
Why did you insist on meeting
during your office hours?
I have three appointments tonight.
I have to eat three dinners.
Korean, Chinese, and Japanese.
Gosh, I'm way too popular.
Why are there so many weddings
and funerals in this country?
It takes so much time
to attend all of them.
It's so nice to see you two.
We haven't done this in a while.
Then again, so much has happened
at Hera Palace lately.
Why don't we start a separate group?
The other families
can't keep up with us.
The four of us are perfect,
don't you think?
Ms. Cheon, is something wrong?
You haven't even touched any caviar.
Nothing's wrong.
Then I suggest that
we take a picture together.
I just started
a social media account.
More people will follow me...
if they see that
I'm friends with you.
- Smile, Ms. Cheon.
- Look at the camera.
Make a V.
That looks great.
Does it look good?
I'll post it right away.
Let me see.
Seo Jin, you sure are a celebrity.
I'm already getting
a ton of comments.
What is this?
Chairman Joo,
is Ms. Cheon in trouble?
What? What's wrong?
(Fake soprano Cheon Seo Jin,
Liar Cheon Seo Jin)
What is it? What happened?
What are they saying?
"Fake soprano Cheon Seo Jin".
"Liar Cheon Seo Jin".
A "shocking lie"?
What are these comments?
The nation's most renowned
prima donna, Cheon Seo Jin,
allegedly used a ghost singer...
at her 20th-anniversary concert,
leaving the whole country in shock.
The news couldn't be
farther from the truth.
An official statement
will be announced soon.
- Are you saying...
- Do you have anything more...
Evidence shows that Cheon Seo Jin
paid a large amount of money...
to an unknown amateur singer.
Cheon Seo Jin's agency has not made
any official statement yet.
The public is criticizing
the celebrated prima donna...
for hiding and
not taking responsibility.
That's all for today.
"Reporter Kim's Eye" seeks truth.
A police investigation?
The press is keeping a close eye.
She can't hide forever.
Many Cheong A Group stockholders
have called as well,
demanding that she step down.
That's not important right now!
Find a way to delay
the police investigation.
And tell Lawyer Park
to come up with a plan immediately.
- You two may leave now.
- Yes, sir.
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
I think you should spend some time
away from the company.
We need to calm down
the stockholders first.
Why didn't you discuss it
with me earlier?
You didn't have to keep it
to yourself.
It's Oh Yoon Hee.
- What?
- The ghost singer was...
Oh Yoon Hee.
Was it really Oh Yoon Hee?
What happened between you two?
Tell me everything
so I can help you.
(Oh Yoon Hee)
- I'll take it.
- It's okay.
We should meet, shouldn't we?
We have a lot to talk about.
Why was it such a big deal...
to stand on this stage?
To you, me,
and our kids.
It was to be on this stage
that Ro Na went against me...
and came back.
To win the Cheong A Art Festival
grand prize.
For me.
Why are you telling me this?
Are you trying to blame me
for Ro Na's death?
Ro Na died
because of your stupid greed.
You're right.
It angers me even more...
that my girl died...
because of her foolish mom.
So...
I'm seeing red right now.
Don't even try to cover up
the ghost singer deal.
It'll only provoke me even more.
Why now, of all times?
Eun Byeol isn't well.
Because...
my daughter died.
She kept taking things away from me.
She kept getting in my way
and badmouthed you.
That you slit her mom's throat.
That you lost to her mom.
What is it you want?
I'll do anything.
Just don't reveal that
you were my ghost singer.
If you do, you'll be punished too.
Keep your mouth shut
for your own good.
You want to keep your pride
even in this situation?
Why?
Are you afraid that people will
find out that you're below me?
That your daughter will?
Yes! I hate it!
I'd risk anything...
to hide the fact that
I borrowed your voice.
So...
please...
I beg you.
Then get on your knees.
What?
Get on your knees and apologize...
for slashing my throat. Beg and beg.
Admit that you lost to me
already 25 years ago.
Get on your knees!
I'm sorry.
I lost to you.
I stole your grand prize.
I apologize.
(Cheong A Art Festival 1996)
(Soprano Cheon Seo Jin
Retirement Announcement)
I'm here...
(Cheon Seo Jin)
to apologize to my fans...
who supported me...
and to the public.
(Soprano Cheon Seo Jin
Retirement Announcement)
As of this day forth,
there is no Soprano Cheon Seo Jin.
I will never take the stage...
or sing ever again.
The name Cheon So Jin...
became Korea's representative
soprano...
- thanks to the support of my fans.
- It can't be.
- Thank you for your love and trust.
That's what made it possible.
I believed...
- I owed it to you to give you...
- Eun Byeol.
A good performance.
This is truly shocking.
How could she think of
scamming the entire nation?
You didn't know
she was like that, did you?
I'm worried they'll lump us together
and humiliate us too.
Don't worry about it.
Just focus on
your college applications.
Will you really marry her?
We're engaged already.
Am I supposed to break it off...
just because she can't sing?
This isn't a big deal.
I know I can't undo it.
You'll regret it.
What?
Because I will destroy her.
Joo Seok Hoon.
Joo Seok Hoon!
That little...
Are you officially
announcing your retirement?
Yes, I am.
Will you step down as director
of Cheong A Foundation as well?
As an educator,
I will hold myself accountable...
and follow the decision
of the foundation's board.
Moreover, I will do my best
to reimburse and compensate...
the attendants of the concert.
The people want to know who it was
that showcased the best voice ever.
Can you tell us who sang for you?
I'll take full responsibility.
I hope no one will be harmed
because of me.
I will cooperate with the police
and submit to an investigation.
(Soprano Cheon Seo Jin
Retirement Announcement)
Who was your ghost singer?
Don't tell me it was Ro Na's mom.
No.
It was.
What a disgrace.
What?
It's a disgrace that you're my mom.
Don't you have self-respect?
How could you make Ro Na's mom
your ghost singer?
You lost in high school too,
didn't you?
That's why you slit her throat.
Eun Byeol!
So how dare you hound me
to beat Ro Na?
Why were you acting out
your inferiority complex on me?
Don't order me around anymore.
Don't try to teach me.
Don't act like you're all that.
You disgust me.
Cheon Seo Jin! You fake!
You imposter!
You stole someone else's voice?
You're the absolute worst!
You were so arrogant.
You thug! You loser!
Maybe Eun Byeol is a fake too.
I thought it was strange...
that she got into
Cheong A with no skills.
Like mother like daughter.
You should leave the school
for the school's sake.
Our kids' image can't be tainted
because of one piece of garbage.
That's enough.
I'm fine.
It'll all pass.
This humiliation...
I can just ignore it.
As long as Eun Byeol
goes unscathed.
I can do anything...
for her.
Because I'm a mother.
It's okay.
I'm really okay.
I'm terrified.
Can I live...
without singing
for the rest of my life?
Can I live like that?
I don't think I can do it.
Yoon Hee.
I don't think I can ever
go back to you.
Cheong A Foundation is preventing
the articles from publishing,
but the public is very critical.
Pressure the media companies...
to keep publishing the articles.
More powerful and more nasty ones.
So that every
person in Korea can see.
Seo Jin must be dying right now.
Also. Did you find out
why Eun Byeol was hospitalized?
She received
sleep brainwave therapy...
which is highly confidential
even among doctors.
Sleep brainwave...
Are they trying to manipulate...
her memory of killing a person?
She must be losing her mind
trying to save her kid.
Something is strange though.
- What is it?
- I checked today,
and the land in Joo Hye In's name
was transferred to someone else.
Who? Was it that rat Logan Lee?
(Oh Yoon Hee)
Oh Yoon Hee?
That's absurd. How did she...
Okay.
I'll go see you tomorrow night,
Chairman Joo.
You're here early.
He said to come at 6 p.m.
He told me it's 7 p.m.
I must have misheard.
Please wait here.
He isn't home yet.
He said to wait in his study.
Pardon?
Okay. It's that way.
I'll have tea with Chairman Joo
when he comes home.
Yes, ma'am.
Su Ryeon?
Inside the study, you'll see
an odd-looking bookcase.
Open it, and there's a door
to this secret room.
There, you need Joo Dan Tae's
fingerprint to get in.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Bring Ms. Oh to the study.
She's already waiting inside.
What?
When you open the door,
you'll see a sculpture.
Tilt its head and you'll see
a secret button.
Looking over here
And over there
But I still can't see
Yoon Hee
(The Penthouse 2)
Whoever dares to betray me will die.
We're over.
Get out!
I just realized that I'm catching
feelings for Seo Jin again.
You're Su Ryeon!
I'm sorry for being late.
The day Ro Na died...
Do you remember something?
You killed Ms. Bae Ro Na
by the stairs that night, right?
Isn't it cold?
I'll be back tomorrow.
Once I open my mouth,
your name will be gone.
This is insane!
You really think you can do
anything I tell you?