- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Bring Ms. Oh to the study.
She's already waiting inside.
What?
Looking over here
And over there
But I still can't see
Yoon Hee
She looks too much like Su Ryeon.
It's you?
Did you come for me?
Of course.
What a surprise.
I missed you.
Father, may I come in?
What is it?
Ro Na's mom came by and left.
She had to go because she had
an urgent matter to take care of.
Ms. Ahn said that she didn't see her
walking out of the house.
Oh, I saw her.
She told me to tell you.
All right, then. Go and study.
- Ms. Oh, where are you?
- What?
My father is home. I told him
that you left. Just so you know.
Thank you, Seok Hoon.
I didn't expect you to just come
out of the blue like this.
Aren't you the one in a rush?
I'm here to give you the contract
for the Gangnam properties.
You know that...
I own half of
these properties, right?
We're going to half it precisely.
Don't you dare
play any tricks on me.
Once I open my mouth,
your name will be gone.
Don't you forget.
Na Ae Gyo, do you think
I won't know you well enough?
I've seen you since you were 10.
I don't trust anything...
except for the money in my hands.
Not even you,
or me.
Isn't life too lonely for you
if you don't even trust me?
I only have you.
My lifelong dream is to live
a happy life with you...
in this penthouse forever.
We're almost there.
I guess I'm getting suspicious
for no reason again.
I was crazy lonely
when I was in Thailand.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
Here.
Thank you.
Great.
I'm leaving.
My taxi is waiting for me.
No, take mine.
It's fine.
I'm going to disappear
so that nobody will know.
Na Ae Gyo?
Look for Na Ae Gyo.
She knows
all of Joo Dan Tae's secrets.
(Premium taxi)
Who are you?
And how dare you follow me?
Su Ryeon!
You were alive?
Su Ryeon.
It's me. Don't you recognize me?
How would I know you?
You're Su Ryeon.
Don't you remember me?
Why are you lying?
Are you dense?
I don't know you or anyone like you.
You freak.
Wait. Let's talk.
(Na Ae Gyo)
Satisfied?
I'm sorry.
You look so much
like someone I know.
Don't touch my things.
(Installed)
(Premium Taxi)
Wait a second.
Your phone.
You're so annoying.
I'm sorry.
Logan. I found Na Ae Gyo.
Where? I'll come right away.
I installed the tracking app,
so I'll contact you
once I confirm where she's staying.
Okay then. Call me.
I'll be waiting.
I'm sorry Su Ryeon...
for coming so late.
What are those bags?
Let's stop.
I left the divorce papers there.
(Petition for Uncontested Divorce)
(Ha Yoon Chul)
Why must we do that?
I've lost interest in the revenge.
Look at us.
You've lost Ro Na,
and I've only hurt Eun Byeol.
I can't do it anymore.
So...
Must you do this right now?
I buried Ro Na...
only four days ago.
It was a contract marriage anyway.
What do you expect
from someone like me?
It's all for show.
Did you want me to be
a real husband or something?
Go in. Yes!
Nice. How did you get that in?
Get it together.
You're only giving them
what they want.
Why are you back?
I said to stop coming.
Look.
See that?
Thanks to that scumbag Joo Dan Tae,
I can't even be a doctor anymore.
So what can I do?
My life is a mess already.
I should be a mess to match.
Yoon Chul.
Let's go back to Korea.
Let's go and get revenge...
on Joo Dan Tae and Seo Jin.
Together.
Yoon Hee.
You and I've lost.
We were shut out.
What can we do?
No hospital...
will take me
even if I do go back to Korea.
No one will welcome you either.
Why can't you start over?
Start a business, get a job...
Do something. I'll help you.
We've been to
the world of torment and back.
We have nothing to fear.
Joo Dan Tae and Seo Jin...
are getting engaged soon.
I wanted revenge...
because I still loved Seo Jin.
Because I couldn't let go.
I just realized...
that I'm catching
feelings for Seo Jin again.
Do you feel better...
if you say that?
Are you stupid?
Are you dense or playing stupid?
I wanted to use you...
to build a successful business
and show off to Seo Jin.
I used you.
I can never let her go.
That's the piece of trash that I am!
You jerk.
I'll move out...
until the divorce is finalized.
Ro Na...
liked you so much.
1, 2...
You should get in too.
- What?
- Get in the picture with us.
But... Shall I?
Excuse me.
Would you take our picture for us?
Sure.
Here we go.
1, 2...
What's with the bag?
Are you going somewhere this late?
You're not... No, right?
You didn't fight in the midst of
all this, did you?
Even still, how could a man
pack his things and leave home?
Is that it?
Let go. Stay out of
other people's affairs.
"Other people"?
Yoon Hee is like a sister to me.
You're running away
because of your guilty conscience.
I said to stay out of it!
Oh my gosh.
You... You'd better not be
getting any ideas.
I'll kill you myself.
I keep hearing a strange melody.
Mi fa sol fa mi mi mi re ti re mi
Everything is a mess.
With Ro Na's death...
Mom retiring...
Everything in my head is jumbled.
It's driving me crazy.
You still can't remember
anything from that day?
I can't remember anything...
other than what Mom told me.
It'll come back to you slowly.
Don't be anxious.
Ro Na died...
without even knowing
that she won the grand prize.
She was punished for coveting
something that wasn't hers.
I'll sleep with you
until you fall asleep.
She's coming.
Cheon Seo Jin.
How do you feel about being expelled
permanently from the Vocal Society?
There's a rumor
that your ghost singer...
was your high school classmate.
Is that true?
Did you know that Cheong A scheduled
an emergency board meeting...
to discuss your removal?
Please say a few words.
Please get in.
Please save a few words
before you get in.
- Cheon Seo Jin.
Is it true?
- Please say something!
- Please say a few words.
- Is it true?
- How do you feel?
Cheon Seo Jin.
You're holding an emergency
board meeting without telling me?
You disgraced the family.
How dare you raise your voice?
You don't deserve
Cheong A Foundation.
You damaged
your father's reputation.
Hand over
Cheong A Foundation to me now.
I'll take good care of Cheong A
Art Center too, so don't worry.
My in-laws can pull some strings
so you can avoid being arrested.
Don't be absurd.
I don't need your help.
Also, forget about
Cheong A Art Center.
Not a single brick or stair was
laid without my supervision.
Stop being greedy.
This is the last time
you'll see me as your mom.
If you don't stop,
we'll have to meet in court.
Go as far as you want.
This is the last time
I'll treat you as my mother.
Unless Father comes back alive
and takes my place,
I won't step down.
Cheong A Foundation is...
the last present
that Father left me.
You're not allowed
to be in a crowded place.
So? Am I supposed to be stuck
in the woods all day?
I'll drive you
to your accommodation.
It's Chairman Joo's order.
Get lost.
Anyone who is stupid enough
to lay a finger on me...
should be prepared
to become crippled.
Eun Byeol.
Do you want breakfast?
Should I make you a sandwich?
Ms. Jin, could you make
some juice for me?
I'll do it.
How do I make it?
Did I ask you to act like a mom?
You're annoying.
Eun Byeol!
She's a bit on edge.
I'll pack some snacks for her,
so don't worry.
What do you mean?
Things don't seem right
at Cheong A Group?
Even the stockholders on your side
seem to have turned their backs.
The recent event must have
damaged their trust in me.
It'll take a while to recover.
You shouldn't sit back and watch.
A few days ago,
Chairman Joo met with...
Cheong A's
major stockholders alone.
What are you talking about?
You shouldn't trust him too much.
He was aware
of your ghost singer deal.
Even the fact that
the singer was Ms. Oh.
What did you say?
How could he possibly know that?
It's all my fault.
I fell into his trap.
Punish me.
I'll accept
whatever decision you make.
Joo Dan Tae knew?
(Noise control)
Sit down, everyone.
Let me announce a decision that was
made at today's teachers' meeting.
As Bae Ro Na, who won
the grand prize...
at Cheong A Art Festival,
is deceased,
the principal will recommend
the second prize winner,
Joo Seok Kyung, to Seoul
National University instead.
Seok Kyung will be recommended
to Seoul National University?
That's unbelievable.
(187 days to performance test,
221 days to CSAT)
The midterms have started.
Your grades in your senior year
are extremely important.
Leave all the
distracting events behind...
and focus on your studies, okay?
- Okay.
On that note, why don't we
put those flowers away already?
I think we've mourned enough.
Okay. I'll put them away.
Get your hands off.
Whoever even touches the flowers...
is dead meat.
Eun Woo, have you lost your mind?
I completely agree with Seok Hoon.
Guys, how can you be so cold?
Your classmate is dead. How come
no one seems to genuinely grieve?
Seok Hoon, where are you going?
Oh, you're leaving early today?
Be careful on your way. "I will."
That's my boy.
What are you guys looking at?
Open your books.
(Bae Ro Na)
(Chocolate Milk)
Thanks for the milk, Ro Na.
I appreciate it.
Sure.
Why are you keeping this?
It's good.
Isn't it cold?
I'll be back tomorrow.
- I'm not...
- You'll change your mind.
What are you doing outside my door?
Oh, there you are.
I was so disappointed,
thinking you were away.
You know what a great cook
Ms. Wang is, right?
I asked her to make
your favorite dishes.
Do you want to try?
- I'm busy.
- With what?
It's none of your business.
Can I tag along?
Are you on your way to meet
the Three Queens?
Forget it.
I can see right through you.
It really takes
all my appetite away.
You're making my place
smell like food.
Take it and leave.
That vulgar woman.
How dare she talk to me that way?
I should be patient.
I should put up with this
for Kyu Jin's sake.
Okay. Watch and learn.
First, hold the brush firmly.
And brush thoroughly.
- Ms. Kang.
- To remove water stains,
use quick, short movements.
Otherwise, you'll sprain your wrist.
Why are you just standing there?
The cold bath is yours.
If you don't do a proper job,
you won't get paid.
Hurry up!
Don't forget the corners.
Brush thoroughly.
- Okay.
- Good.
Hold the brush firmly
using your wrist and arm.
Okay.
There you go. You can do this.
Let's do this. We can do this.
When things get tough,
look up at the sky
You're never alone
After heavy rain and strong winds
- The sun will shine again
- Good!
- When it hurts too much
Give a loud shout
Make the weak sadness
Run away from you
Here. Dig in.
Jajangmyeon tastes best
at a bathhouse.
I'm...
hungry.
How dare I, right?
Whether you lost
your husband or your child,
it's not a sin to feed yourself.
Eat up.
You must feel shattered inside.
I saw Mr. Ha, no,
that punk, pack his things
and leave.
It doesn't just look
like it was a small argument.
Does he want to get a divorce?
Are you serious?
That despicable jerk!
Humans show their true selves
when they're at their worst.
How can he turn his back on you...
after seeing you faint?
The jjajangmyeon is getting cold.
Eat up.
I can't possibly say anything
to comfort...
a woman who's lost her child.
You have to stay strong.
You have to stand your ground.
That's what Ro Na wants.
You know what I mean, right?
I'm going to survive somehow.
I'll get through this somehow.
Yes.
Aren't these noodles amazing?
Look at her.
What?
That's hilarious.
(A fake junior soprano,
Ha Eun Byeol)
Who is it?
How dare you all act like kids?
I heard that Ms. Cheon is getting
fired from her Director position.
What a strong girl you are.
Your mom is about to go to jail,
but you're here to memorize
some English vocabulary?
Shouldn't you apologize to us
on behalf of your mom?
You're fake too.
It was always so annoying
to see you be a brat...
when you're not even talented.
To be honest, Bae Ro Na was
so much better than you.
You know that, right?
Go away. Get out of my way!
- What are you doing?
- Go away!
Why did you guys keep
a dead girl's desk? That's bad luck!
Watch what you say. Bad luck?
Why?
Don't you dare talk like that
when she had such a sad death!
Did you just slap me?
How dare you?
Jenny is right.
I feel bad for Ro Na.
Joo Seok Kyung, you think you have
a right to say that?
Why not?
Was I the one who killed her?
I've been meaning to ask you.
You were with Ro Na
during the awards announcement...
at Cheong A Arts Festival,
weren't you?
No. I didn't see her.
You and Ro Na were the only two
who were missing.
Tell me. What were you doing
and where were you?
I was...
You overdosed on medicine,
so you were lying down
at the infirmary.
Then, you passed out
right before the announcement,
so Secretary Do took you home.
I was at the infirmary...
because all the pills I took
that day made me dizzy.
Are you sure? Really?
Any witnesses?
Are you okay?
Seok Hoon!
What happened?
You suddenly passed out in class.
My head feels like
it's going to burst.
I don't think you're feeling well.
I heard that you passed out
during Cheong A Arts Festival too.
Yes, I did.
I'm a little disappointed...
that you don't seem to remember
what happened on that day.
Don't you remember what you told me
by the stairs?
What did I say to you?
You really don't remember?
Hearing you say that was
what made me ask you out.
Because I liked what you said.
I'll get going.
Seok Hoon!
What did I tell him here?
I can't remember anything!
Get your memories back,
Ha Eun Byeol.
Recall what you've done.
What a pleasant surprise, Ms. Oh.
I didn't expect you to come
and see me.
As you know,
there's nobody I can rely on.
I was thinking,
and I thought of you, who treated
me like your younger sibling.
I'm known to be the assemblyman
who listens to his people.
Not only that, we're like siblings.
I'm even more all ears for you.
Look at me.
You trust me, right?
Tell me everything.
What do I do now?
Hey!
No!
Hey.
I totally saw that coming.
I just had a feeling.
Recently, I ran into
Ha Yoon Chul late at night.
I talked slightly bad
about Seo Jin,
then, he said,
"If you're drunk, shut up
and go to sleep."
"Don't blabber nonsense."
That's what he said.
They were already divorced,
so I couldn't understand why
he was being so defensive.
Everything makes sense now.
What a trashy man he is!
You know, even cheaters have rules.
If anyone's going to cheat, they
must cheat with a stranger.
If they don't know a stranger,
I can introduce one to them.
You know, something like a pen pal.
But he cheated on you
with his ex-wife?
He's insane!
I don't even know what to think.
This divorce came so suddenly.
It's me.
Don't worry.
I was so well-off
as a divorce lawyer.
All you need to do is
to do what I tell you.
What am I supposed to do?
The key to a divorce is...
the reason for divorce.
First, you need to start
by gathering proof...
that he's cheating on you
with Seo Jin.
I'll introduce you...
to a very good ex-colleague
who's a divorce lawyer.
You've lost so much weight!
Does Joo Dan Tae know
this important news or what?
Don't stop yourself. Go, run.
I only want one thing from you.
You ladies are paying
for my paycheck.
You pay taxes, right?
Thank you all.
I don't have anything to give
but this. Here you go.
Assemblyman Lee, why are we
meeting up at a place like this?
Looks like you got yourself
some bonus.
I'm going to enjoy the night
since you're paying.
Don't stop me. Okay?
Order us something
expensive and amazing.
I don't owe you anything, though.
You will soon enough.
Have a glass.
What is it that you're
stalling so much?
My mom told me that patience is
the key to making good rice.
Just wait.
I have a special relationship
with Seo Jin, as you know.
We attended the private
English kindergarten together,
and were neighbors
when we first moved...
into Simoon Mansion.
Stop playing around
and just tell me.
Ha Yoon Chul and Oh Yoon Hee
are getting a divorce.
- Why?
- Why would they?
Isn't this man so thick-headed?
Because of Seo Jin, of course.
Ha Yoon Chul and Seo Jin...
are back together.
Why don't you tell me more,
since you're not thick-headed?
I think you should spend some time
away from the company.
We need to calm down
the stockholders first.
Why didn't you discuss it
with me earlier?
You didn't have to keep it
to yourself.
It's Oh Yoon Hee.
- What?
- The ghost singer was...
Oh Yoon Hee.
Was it really Oh Yoon Hee?
What happened between you two?
Joo Dan Tae.
He did all of this to get
Cheong A Group in his hands?
You're right.
That's the kind of a man you were.
Is everything you told me
about the night Ro Na died true?
What do you mean?
Is it true that I passed out
and was brought home?
Of course. I have no reason
to lie to you.
Why do you ask?
Do you remember anything?
Why? Is there something
that I shouldn't remember?
It's me. Where are you right now?
What? Did you sleep here?
What's with the luggage?
I left my home.
And you're staying here?
I'm busy with work anyway,
so it's better here.
Booking a hotel is too much work.
What happened with Oh Yoon Hee?
I told her that I'd like a divorce.
That doesn't mean that
I'll get back together with you.
I just feel too ashamed
to be with Yoon Hee.
That's why I left her.
Good job.
You should start looking
for a place to stay first.
You can't stay here forever.
I'll take care of it.
How's Eun Byeol?
Are you sure her memory is gone?
I'm making sure she takes
her pills, but I'm so anxious.
She looks like she's starting
to remember something,
and she won't talk to me.
Are you eating well?
You have to get through this
for Eun Byeol.
If you get shaken,
it's the end for Eun Byeol.
What's with your hand?
I think it's cramping.
Did you...
hurt your hand?
Is that what happened?
Who are you? Why are you doing this?
It looks like you put your hands
on the wrong woman.
Who sent you?
Was it Joo Dan Tae? Jerk!
Break his hands.
Why are you telling me this now?
This all happened because of me!
It's not because of you.
No need to care. It's my business.
It's mine too!
I know what it took for you
to become a doctor...
and how much you loved your job.
It's all because of Joo Dan Tae.
I can't stand this anymore.
That jerk!
What are you going to do?
I'm going to call
the wedding off right now.
I never loved that man.
I hated that you were always
longing for Yoon Hee,
and I needed someone who'll
treat me like a lady.
It's my fault for thinking
that it was love.
If I marry him,
Eun Byeol won't be happy either.
I'm sorry...
for giving you a hard time
because of a jerk like him.
And I broke us.
It's all in the past.
We can't turn anything back now.
We can!
I'm letting go of my ego
and asking you to come back.
Please stay with me.
I told you to not do that!
You're late.
Where were you?
I almost fell asleep.
Like you care?
My fiancee couldn't be reached
late into the night.
Of course, I was worried.
What happened with
your dismissal matter?
Should I meet the board members
and talk to them?
What are you really after?
For me to leave Cheong A Group
completely to you...
and just be the high school director
until I grow old and die?
Why are you so angry?
I understand.
Things are tough, aren't they?
I heard you knew
Yoon Hee was my ghost singer.
You're the one who ratted me out
to the foundation, aren't you?
How dare you threaten my personal
assistant and do something so low?
Why? Were you anxious
to get the merger through?
You didn't want me,
you wanted Cheong A Group!
Deny it if you can!
Your family...
is equally as obsessed with money.
You scumbag.
Now that I know
what kind of a jerk you are,
I can't marry you.
We're over.
Get out!
Cheon Seo Jin.
You'll regret doing that.
Hello, Lawyer Park.
I want to break off our engagement
as soon as possible.
Please void the merger as well.
It says in the agreement...
that it will take effect
after the wedding.
Yes. Thank you.
You need to come out for a minute.
Detectives are here.
Detectives?
There are too many
eyes and ears in our home.
Let's speak comfortably here.
Why did you come...
to speak with Eun Byeol?
There are some things
we need to confirm with her...
regarding Bae Ro Na's death.
Isn't the case closed already?
It's a shame that Ro Na died,
but why must you speak
with Eun Byeol because of that?
Because Eun Byeol is
our prime suspect.
We've found solid evidence as well.
Evidence?
This necklace belongs
to your daughter, correct?
We found her DNA...
and the victim's blood on it.
We already got
the janitor's confession...
that he was paid
to give a false confession.
Ha Yoon Chul is at the station
being questioned as we speak.
Your daughter killed Bae Ro Na,
didn't she?
The person who struck the victim
on the head with the trophy...
was Ha Eun Byeol, wasn't it?
You and Ha Yoon Chul tried
to cover that up...
and send someone else
to take the fall!
Did you kill Bae Ro Na
in the hospital...
out of fear that the truth
would be revealed?
No.
Arrest Ha Eun Byeol!
No! No.
Eun Byeol did nothing wrong.
I did it.
I bribed Mr. Park.
I killed Ro Na. I did it all.
My Eun Byeol knows nothing.
I'll kill you
if you touch my daughter!
What an amazing motherly love.
Your love for your daughter
and for your ex-husband.
I'm all choked up.
Dan Tae.
- Chairman Joo.
- Yes.
Take your men out for dinner.
Thank you.
Let's eat meat tonight.
Yes, sir.
- It was moving.
- Arrest Ha Eun Byeol!
No! No.
What a confession.
- Did you...
- Eun Byeol did nothing wrong.
- I did it.
- Plan this?
You want to break off
our engagement.
Why?
To go back to Ha Yoon Chul?
How long has it been?
Ever since the jerk returned
to Hera Palace?
Or the night I shattered his hand?
You scumbag.
"You scumbag"?
Did you think I wouldn't know...
that you and that jerk...
betrayed me in New York?
Get away.
Get away from me!
Should I take this evidence...
to the police now?
No, no.
It would be much more fun
to send it to Oh Yoon Hee.
If I let the woman
who lost her only child know...
that her husband betrayed her
on top of that...
I wonder how she'll rip you
and Eun Byeol to shreds...
and kill you.
You've lost your mind.
It's the price for betraying me.
Did you not expect this much...
when you decided to call off
our wedding?
What should I do?
What must I do to break
Eun Byeol's heart excruciatingly?
You choose.
I think...
telling Oh Yoon Hee would be
the most fun.
No.
You can't do that! No.
No. You can't do that! No.
I'll do anything you say,
so don't do anything.
I'll do whatever you say,
So please leave Eun Byeol alone.
Please. I'm begging you. Please.
Please.
Can you...
really do everything I say?
What is this?
(Please join us
to celebrate our union.)
What...
What garbage...
The phone is turned off...
(Unit 8501, Paging)
Seo Jin, open up. We need to talk.
Seo Jin!
Open up! We need to talk!
Open up!
We need to talk! We need to talk!
Seo Jin.
Seo Jin!
Did you get it?
The wedding invitation.
I did. It's in two weeks.
I didn't know
Chairman Joo would do this.
He's insisting on getting married...
after finding out
Seo Jin betrayed him.
Is that how much he loves her?
There must be an important reason...
why he can't dump her.
I have an appointment,
so I need to go.
What appointment?
You promised to tell me everything.
Hello?
- Hee? Hee.
- Hee?
What?
Hee?
Hee
Please look at me
You used to like me
Hee
I'm sorry
I couldn't keep our appointment.
But why did you want to meet...
I'm sure you know.
I want to know how you ended up
owning Hye In's land.
She's my daughter.
You mean, Su Ryeon's daughter.
I guess you didn't get the notice
because Su Ryeon...
gave the power of attorney
to someone else.
True. You were never qualified
to be her dad.
So it's only natural.
There are no plans to develop
Cheonsoo District.
Why did you want the land
in such a run-down area?
Aren't you the one
who built Cheong A Art Center...
in that district?
You're quite greedy for someone
who just lost her child.
Before, my biggest goal was
to raise my daughter well.
But now that she's gone,
my goal has changed.
I want to become extremely wealthy.
I'll do whatever it takes
to accumulate wealth...
so that I can own this penthouse.
Ro Na always wanted to live here.
The penthouse?
Why don't we make a bet?
Who do you think
will be living here in a year?
Ms. Cheon is here.
Why are you so surprised?
I just stopped by to discuss
business. Don't get the wrong idea.
I didn't know you were having
a guest. I'll come back later.
You don't have to.
I was about to leave anyway.
Eun Byeol, it's been a while.
I heard that you were unwell.
Are you okay now?
- Yes.
- That's a relief.
It's so nice to see you
healthy again.
Do you meet your dad often?
Why would you ask that?
It's just that I feel jealous.
Ro Na grew up without her dad.
And she can't even see
her new dad anymore...
because she's dead.
By the way, congratulations
on your wedding.
Chairman Joo was kind enough...
to send me an invitation.
I'll see you at your wedding.
What? Aren't you two
high school friends?
We're having a wedding in two weeks.
We're becoming family for real.
I hope everyone gets along.
Nonsense. That's a stupid idea.
I thought things were good again
between you and Dad.
How much are you
going to hurt me again?
At school, I have to put up
with kids pointing the finger at me.
And now I have to put up with
you two getting married?
Tell him right now.
Tell him that you can't marry him!
This is...
my choice.
I guess you're not ready
to accept me as your dad yet.
It's okay. We can get used
to each other from now on.
I hate it.
I'll never accept this marriage.
I agree with Eun Byeol for once.
I'll never accept
this ridiculous marriage either.
Congratulations.
You two are perfect for each other.
- This is insane!
- Sit back down.
Please stop.
If you want money,
I'll compensate you as much
as you want, so please...
Cut it out!
In this game, you have no choice.
I get to decide whether
we get married or not.
All you have to do is
move into this penthouse...
as my wife on the day I choose.
Understood?
Ms. Ahn.
Yes, sir.
Call the dress shop
and tell them we're coming.
Sure, sir.
Try this on.
I think it'll look gorgeous on you.
(Cheong A Arts High School)
(The 28th Cheong A Art Festival)
What took you so long?
- Stop!
- Ro Na!
- Mom!
- Jenny!
(Fire alarm)
Fire!
Bae Ro Na.
Thanks to her,
things have become a lot simpler.
I would thank her,
but I can't.
It's me, Secretary Do.
Go to my place and get
me and Eun Byeol's passports.
And book us
the first flight tonight.
The destination doesn't matter.
(Passport)
Are you looking for these?
What? Are you disappointed?
Did you think
I wouldn't prepare this much?
Let's not waste each other's energy.
Wherever you go, I'll find you.
Are you okay?
No, not this.
I don't think it's for you.
This looks a bit funny too.
Why don't you just kill me now?
She must not be so happy
with the dresses.
She seems very upset.
She has pretty high standards.
Can you show her some other designs?
You're crazy.
You disgusting jerk.
- What's this?
- A present.
This is totally my style.
Did something good happen today?
The best thing that happened is
that you came back.
I missed you so much.
You're being so sweet today.
- I'll go change.
- Okay.
I wonder how Joo Dan Tae
really feels.
Is she special to him because
she gave birth to his children?
Even a monster like him
can love someone sincerely?
It's hard to believe.
Something doesn't feel right.
Two years ago,
Na Ae Gyo was determined...
to escape from Joo Dan Tae.
They're completely on the same side.
I don't care.
We don't have much time.
I have to meet Ae Gyo and ask her...
what Joo Dan Tae did to Su Ryeon.
I won't make another mistake.
What was going on
between you and Su Ryeon?
Seol A's birth mother
and stepbrother.
Nothing more?
I wanted...
to make her happy.
I should have protected her
no matter what.
I was such a fool.
I can't forgive myself.
All my apartments sold out.
At the highest prices.
Is that why you look so happy?
It's a stellar location,
so it's no surprise.
The prices may go up even more.
Why did you sell them already?
The prices are at
their peak right now.
The district will be designated
as a speculative zone soon,
preventing people from taking loans.
How many people
do you think can pay...
tens of millions of dollars
without taking loans?
I guess Mr. Jung is still providing
you with useful information.
And I have you to thank for that.
You're the perfect partner for me.
You have been for the past 20 years.
You just now realized that?
Come to think of it,
I feel sorry for Su Ryeon.
In her whole life, she knew
so little about her own husband.
I wouldn't want to talk about her
on a happy day like today.
We have only one bullet left each.
I'll go first.
Are you getting nervous?
Look who's talking.
Tell me the truth.
You tried to betray me
two years ago, didn't you?
What are you doing?
Tell me!
You can't fool me.
I knew from the get-go
that you had changed.
You wouldn't take my calls,
you wouldn't come back...
There must have been a reason why
you avoided me.
What are you up to?
Were you planning to leave me?
Shoot me if you can.
If you think you can keep
your fortune without me,
shoot me.
You scumbag.
Whoever dares to betray me will die.
You are no exception.
Don't die, Mom.
No. No. No.
No. No!
No.
No!
Sir!
What happened?
Wake up.
Na Ae Gyo is gone.
- Find her!
- Yes, sir.
Wake up.
Open your eyes!
She's not breathing.
What?
We have to get out of here.
We have no time. Hurry!
(The Penthouse 2)
You're marrying Chairman Joo?
I told you.
You can never be free of me.
Leave before the wedding!
Our mom's killer...
I found out.
I'll kill you, Joo Dan Tae!
Trophy?
What if I really end up going crazy?
Seok Hoon, Seok Kyung,
your biological mom is alive.
Oh Yoon Hee? You again?
Would you trust the person
who tried to kill you?
You meant it.
I know it's you!