Who the hell would do that?
They are investigating now.
So we should wait.
It must have done some damage to Babel.
That's an understatement.
It's as bad as getting hit by a tsunami.
What are we going to do?
Okay. I got it. See you tomorrow.
What the hell is this?
Please give me one more chance
to get even.
I'll find them
and destroy them to pieces.
And just how will you find them?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
Just do what I tell you to do. Okay?
I know I can do something here!
Don't raise your voice.
You startled me.
I mean…
-Han-seo.
-Sir.
Have you lost your mind
now that people call you the chairman?
No, that's not it. Sir.
Sir…
You're nothing but a puppet of mine.
Yes.
So don't you dare think for yourself.
Yes, I got it. Yes, sir.
The cause today's fire will be
electrical overheating, not arson.
But it will still affect the stock prices,
so get the board members
for an emergency meeting.
Oh, right.
And tell Wusang what I told you earlier.
Yes, sir.
Han-seo, go home now.
I'm glad I'm just a puppet.
I can just cut off the strings.
EPISODE 5
Cheers.
I'm glad that you're getting started.
They'll catch on to us if we keep blasting
fireworks like we did today.
That's why we need to change our approach.
We'll use the law and the court,
the two things we know best.
They'll be better at that than we are.
We need to beat them at their own game
to make victory taste sweeter.
But Mr. Cassano.
You can't practice law in Korea.
But I have you.
Are you trying to make me
take the heat in your place?
So that I go down alone?
I'll be the one putting the heat on them.
Let's focus on our next step for now.
Shall I guess what your next step is?
Since when could you read my mind?
I can't do that. I'm not a psychic.
I'm the person who knows
Babel's dirty little secrets
more than anyone else in Korea.
Well, then…
let's see what you've got.
Babel's most vulnerable subsidiary.
The subsidiary that rigs
the stock prices the most.
And the subsidiary whose ethics
will be damaged at the greatest degree.
Which subsidiary is it?
THE ALCHEMISTS OF FUTURE SCIENCE
BABEL CHEMICALS
-Hey.
-What?
Be honest.
You don't do all 108 bows, right?
I bet you skip a few.
I don't skip anything.
What do you take me for? Seriously.
I bet you eat sausages
behind his back. Right?
Pork belly and green onions too.
Shut your mouth, jerk.
Shut it, man. Help me, merciful Buddha.
Can't we eat out next time?
I come here once a month.
We always eat vegetables.
-Hey, your nose is bleeding.
-Darn it.
Hey, are you okay?
You've lost a lot of weight
and even have nosebleeds.
Hey, I'm good.
Seriously.
We used to run all over the place
15 years ago, right?
Right.
Back then, you were no match for me.
Look how far you've come.
Stop kidding me.
You couldn't even look me in the eye.
Look at you. I should teach you a lesson.
-You're bringing out the old me.
-You're ridiculous. Come on.
I ought to… Don't swear.
Watch it. It's heavy.
You should be careful.
Aren't you
Mr. Jang Han-seo?
Yes.
No, let me do that for you.
This is incredible. Amazing.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
Can I get a handshake?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Here. Have this.
-Thanks.
-Sure.
You work out here.
In one of your interviews,
you said nothing is impossible for Babel.
I became a fan after reading how daring
your corporate philosophy is.
Sorry about that.
Innovation and business go hand in hand.
"Creative destruction. Innovation is
the driving force of economic growth."
Were you influenced by George Soros?
What?
Soros. I have so much respect for him.
I knew it. When I studied
your investments in your subsidiaries,
you seemed flexible dealing with them.
-You were influenced by Joseph Schumpeter?
-Right. Joseph…
That's right.
I read his books. You know a lot.
Gosh, you're so smart.
Oh, right. Yesterday… Let me help you.
I saw the news about the fire
at Babel Pharmaceuticals yesterday.
How could that happen?
I'm so sorry.
It was just a minor accident.
By the way,
I'm not sure if I should say this.
I read in the tabloid
that it was actually arson.
Who said that?
Don't believe what you read in tabloids.
I guess you don't know
about these tabloids.
Sometimes, they are right.
-Hey.
-By the way,
-I own Babel Pharmaceuticals' shares.
-Leave.
Please. Please go if you're done.
I need to work out.
Right. Sorry I got in the way.
Then I will
go and sell my shares of Babel.
-They're worth nothing. Awful.
-Hey.
This is mine.
What was that?
Come on.
What are they writing in that tabloid?
You're not the boss.
The stock price of Babel Pharmaceuticals
took another sharp dive.
Amid speculations that the fire last night
at the storage room
was in fact an arson,
the stocks plummeted.
Aren't you happy that I'm gone?
No one is nagging you now.
I've missed you
since the day you left the firm.
I even miss your nagging.
Wait until you make partner.
You won't have time for this.
Did you watch the news
about the fire at Babel Pharmaceuticals?
Of course, I did. My goodness.
All the materials burnt down.
Maybe they had it coming.
They did all sorts of evil things.
I think so, too.
It's like retributive justice. Right?
That's right.
I'm having a muscle spasm.
My gosh. I'll call you back.
Cha-young. Bye.
So you were the one who punished me.
I told you where Chairman Jang would be,
so you're buying.
That's the perfect reward
for the quality of your intel.
Why did you go see him?
Facing the boss of the enemy
before starting a fight
puts me at ease.
That's a weird way
to find peace with yourself.
So what did you think?
Chairman Jang…
might not be the real boss.
I switched quotes from
George Soros and Joseph Schumpeter,
but he didn't catch it.
No wonder. He did look like an airhead.
If he isn't,
then who could be the real chairman?
Usually, when there's war
between the Mafia,
it's customary to let each other know
who the boss is.
That way, you can set up a meeting
between the bosses
to resolve things diplomatically.
And the surest way to draw out
the real boss behind the puppet is…
To destroy the puppet.
You know a lot about the Mafia.
I told you.
People here are just as bad as the Mafia.
Anyway, to find out
if Chairman Jang is a puppet or not,
I'll make him dry up
like a wet wipe out in the open.
Do you think I'll listen to you?
That's up to you.
But you should remember
that freedom comes with a price.
ATTORNEY CHOI MYUNG-HEE
He's clean. He's very clean.
You know the lawyer from Italy?
The one with Cha-young?
Vincenzo Cassano.
His name is Vincenzo Cassano?
Yes. I talked to someone
from the Italian Lawyer Association.
His record is perfectly clean.
Is this your first rodeo?
A spotless record means something is up.
I knew you'd say that.
So I already talked to my guy at the NIS
to take a look at his background.
No. Something is iffy about him.
No, I said he's clean.
Just because he's from Italy,
he's a member of the Mafia or something?
I bet he was just a regular lawyer.
Where are you going?
To see what this Vincenzo Cassano guy
looks like.
Goodness.
You can never be at ease
until you see them in person, do you?
Is anyone here?
Is Ms. Hong Cha-young here?
I'm sorry. She's not here right now.
Are you Mr. Vincenzo Cassano?
SANGCHEON OPTICIAN'S
Who am I speaking to?
Oh, right. I am…
My name is Choi Myung-hee
from Law Firm Wusang.
I heard a lot about you.
I'm Vincenzo
Cassano.
That's my name.
What is this? He sounds like a drunk.
What an ugly face.
Greasy hair and aimless eyes.
Gray skin…
and the awkwardly protruding mouth.
You're not Vincenzo.
Yes, I am.
Goodness!
How dare you lie to me?
Take it.
No. It's obvious
that I'm Vincenzo Cassano.
Do that again and I'll rip your mouth
in every direction, you asshole.
JIPURAGI LAW FIRM
LAWYER HONG CHA-YOUNG
How creative of them, those assholes.
He must be Vincenzo.
Seriously.
When you threatened her,
did you alter your voice?
No.
It's been a while.
What brings you to this humble building?
I was in the neighborhood.
Is this…
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano?
This is Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
He can't speak today
because his tonsils are swollen.
I'm Choi Myung-hee from Wusang.
This is our first time meeting, right?
Tell us why you're here.
Come on.
That's no way to treat your guest.
Offer me some tea, and we'll talk.
Did you think you could fool me?
Why would you impersonate him?
I actually enjoy cosplays.
Today, I dressed up as Vincenzo Cassano.
Never do that again.
Please spare me some time
Is he serious? What's your name?
Vincenzo.
Now that we served you some warm tea,
tell us why you're here.
This hits the spot.
You run your own law firm now.
I'm here to share a few words of blessing.
I got that plant over there.
That's called a "stuckyi."
I hear it survives well no matter what.
You don't have to water it often.
Won't that be easy?
Anyway, I wanted your law firm
to last long like that plant.
And what should you do to last long?
You shouldn't act recklessly or foolishly.
Just lie low
and be as silent as the grave.
Thank you for your tip on survival.
You, too, Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
Did you understand that?
I'm still older than you.
Shouldn't you at least answer me?
All right. Enough of that.
Let's have a brief conversation. Okay?
Okay.
I couldn't hear you. Say that again.
All right, then. I won't see you off.
Goodbye.
Sure. I should leave
when I'm asked to leave.
I'm off.
Gosh, it's hot.
Mr. Nam.
I need some napkins.
It's hot.
This is confusing.
There's no way he's a bozo like that.
I will try to handle what you asked
as soon as possible.
Okay. Have a good day.
Thank you. Bye.
Farewell, Sir.
Joon-woo.
I told you to stop calling me that.
When did you…
Your boss needs to see you in his office.
This is so frustrating.
As of today, you are officially…
a partner at Wusang.
What?
Yes. You. That's right. You.
Gosh. But why you? Who the heck are you?
-Pardon?
-Never mind.
We should negotiate your annual salary.
Do that with the director.
Do you need your own office?
You should get one. You like Cha-young.
Take her office.
What? How could I…
You find it weird too, right?
I'm very unhappy right now.
But I've got no choice. He…
Just work hard.
-Okay.
-Back to work.
-Get out!
Okay. I'm leaving.
That fool.
Why does Chairman Jang want me
to promote a fool like him?
Is Joon-woo a relative of his?
BRING DESTRUCTION TO BABEL CHEMICALS
Let me begin.
There are 42 victims in total.
And nine of them are dead.
They all had blood-related diseases.
All the victims died from leukemia.
The report said it was caused by BLSD.
What is that?
Well, that's…
Damn it.
Why did you make it look so tacky?
I'm sorry.
I just like vivid colors.
It's a chemical expected to revolutionize
the next-gen display panels.
But its manufacture was banned in the US
because of its toxicity.
It's just like RDU-90.
It shouldn't be used on people.
That proves how heinous they are.
Next, it's the lawyer representing
the victims in the Babel lawsuit.
What the heck?
I thought he was a ghost.
Sorry.
I'm not particularly good at taking
screenshots of the interview.
This is So Hyeon-u,
who represents the victims.
Also known as "Stinking So."
He's one dirty lawyer.
Let me tell you this
as a lawyer who specializes
in industrial accident suits.
You must settle with the company.
When you file an industrial accident
lawsuit against a conglomerate,
the more time you waste,
you will receive less settlement…
They filed the lawsuit two months ago.
The first hearing is in five days,
but he keeps recommending them to settle.
Recommending to settle
isn't against the law.
Of course not.
But what if he is already in on it
with Wusang
in trying to persuade
the victims' families?
-Where's your proof?
-It came from my informant,
so I can't tell you.
I bet it's not that reliable.
You seem to occasionally look down on me.
That's your thing, right?
But you will
-tell me, right?
-No.
And the hospital?
It says here that
the hospital belongs to Babel.
That's right. Before Haemun became Babel,
Jang Han-seo's father,
Jang Guk-han, founded it.
Director Gil Jong-Moon
of Haemun Medical Center.
He's also the chief
of the Hemato-oncology Department.
Are you sure you have
nothing to do with Babel Chemicals?
We have nothing to do with them.
He fabricated the diagnosis
to quash the insurance lawsuit.
He's a quack who doesn't give a shit
about the oath he made.
And the press?
Make sure Babel stands out
in the articles.
Director Chun Il-su of Daechang Daily.
HOW BABEL CONTRIBUTED TO SOCIETY
He sucks up to Babel
to get more advertisers on his paper.
They're trashy reporters.
Make it look believable!
When researchers
cough up blood and collapse,
they publish articles like this.
They are quite the assholes, aren't they?
BABEL REWARDS RESEARCHERS
FOR WORK ON BLSD
Evil conglomerate, quack doctors,
trashy reporters,
and lowlife lawyers.
They're the whole package.
No one can beat them.
Of course, except for me.
We should represent the victims.
There are only five days left
until the trial.
Even if we represent them,
the trial will be tough.
He has a point.
If we go to trial unprepared like this,
we'll be crushed.
I bet whatever evidence
that crooked lawyer submitted
would be insufficient.
We'll think about that later.
Even if you try to persuade him,
I doubt he'll give in that easily.
-I don't need to do that.
-Then, what?
So, you're saying
that I should resign from
representing my clients?
Why would I?
I heard the only thing you're doing
is recommending them to settle.
That's because
the victims' families are in bad shape.
Beware of the first person
who recommends to settle.
-That person is…
-A traitor.
A traitor who offers to settle
is strangled to death in movies.
Attacked from behind.
Well…
I wanted to fight at first.
But I realized it'd be in vain.
You should have at least pretended
to throw a punch
before recommending them to settle.
You have no conscience.
Only a vulgar law broker would do
something like this, not a lawyer.
Or a piece of trash.
Let me explain. Okay?
I have to grasp the situation quickly,
so I can get a better deal
for the victims.
Didn't you make that decision
to help yourself, not to help the victims?
To help myself?
My goodness. What do you take me for?
Hey, here's a thing about me.
I always fight for my clients.
I fight on their behalf,
only thinking about how to do
what's best for them.
That's all I have in mind.
I haven't slept since I took this case.
Look at all the medicine I take.
How can you…
Do you know what
the only evil I can't condone is?
It's hypocrisy.
When a hypocrite repents,
even that is a lie.
I can't believe this!
Let me make this simple.
Send us a document that says you will
resign from this case by tomorrow.
Let's say I do that.
Do you think my clients will accept that?
You have no idea
how much the families trust me.
That's none of my business.
Just send the document.
And make sure you pay the courier.
What if I can't do that?
I plan to send you to a deserted place.
A place where people can't hear you
whatever you yap about.
Go ahead. Do it.
Don't you think
I can see right through you?
Look at these assholes.
You're threatening me to steal my case
to make some money.
Yes, we are threatening you,
but that's not why.
Our goal is to keep fighting.
And to win, of course.
You should clean your office.
LAWYER SO HYEON-U
Why aren't you eating?
If you don't want to eat it,
give me a plan.
The stocks are plummeting
and the tabloids are saying it was arson.
How come you people
still haven't come up with a plan?
Why is that?
Hey, give me water.
Not until he finishes the bowl.
Water, my ass.
HIM
Yes, sir.
Are you torturing them
with spicy food again?
No, I'm not.
Is a high tolerance for spicy food
something to brag about?
I wasn't bragging.
I was just teaching them a lesson.
All they do is talk.
Stop fooling around and listen carefully.
Go to Babel Chemicals with a reporter
from Daechang Daily today.
And make it sound as if BLSD
is ready to hit the market.
-Got it?
-What?
But it's not ready yet. Can we do that?
Chairman Jang.
These conglomerates in Korea
are just like bodybuilders on steroids.
Whether it's a lie or an exaggeration,
a good appearance is all they care about.
Yes, sir. I got it.
Okay. Bye.
Damn it. This is so humiliating.
I told her to hold the ketchup.
There's too much.
You know, persuading the families
into firing Mr. So would've been easier.
That would be harder.
That's why I didn't go for it.
I've persuaded hundreds
of clients like them.
I only need five minutes.
Asking them to fight is like
dragging them into the pits of hell.
I wouldn't ask them to fight
like some soldiers.
I have my ways.
I can do it.
You want to bet on it?
Sure. Let's do that.
What should we bet?
-Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors.
A finger flick.
A finger flick?
This?
Yes. That.
A single finger flick with all your might.
We're not kids.
I don't hit women even if it's a game.
This isn't like that. It's a simple
punishment for losing the bet.
If I lose, I'll let you hit me.
No.
I plan to live by my principles.
Anyway, watch and learn.
THE TRUTH ABOUT BABEL CHEMICALS
WILL BE UNCOVERED
Everyone here…
The victims…
I'm only saying this
because you are like my family.
I will be your family and fight with you.
You cannot give up.
I'm sorry.
But we will see this through with Mr. So.
Please, listen to me.
Sister.
My brothers.
Big sister.
Can't you see I'm genuine?
Why do you keep telling us to start
a fight that we can't win?
After the Babel Pharmaceuticals' lawsuit,
we made up our decision for good.
We will not fight them.
Babel could've lost
if the victims' families held out longer.
We heard their lawyer died
because he coerced witnesses
to perjure in exchange for money.
What did you just say?
It was on the news.
Didn't you see it?
You know firsthand
how the news is full of lies,
and you still believe the news?
Why are you taking it out on us?
The lawyer who died
fighting Babel Pharmaceuticals
is my father.
Lawyer Hong Yu-chan.
Since my father couldn't beat them,
I shouldn't fight them, right?
Because I'll lose anyway.
But do you know why I want to fight?
Because we might be able to beat them
with a few more punches.
I can see that. That's why.
Gosh, I'm sorry to say this,
but it doesn't look that way to us.
Please trust me.
We can beat them.
We're signing
the settlement papers tomorrow.
We already made our decision.
Please, stop confusing us and leave.
I'm not confusing you.
I'm giving you hope.
Why won't you trust me? I can win this.
Testing. It's working now.
Do you know why you can't win?
Because you didn't have
lawyers like us.
Lawyers like us are used to winning,
don't get tired,
and never have any doubts.
If you turn us down,
you're basically throwing away
the chance to win.
There he is.
BABEL CHEMICALS HAS SUCCEEDED
IN DEVELOPING BLSD
Babel's BLSD will finally
get to see the light of day. It's…
It's a dream come true.
Now, the display panel market in Korea
will undergo a rapid change
thanks to our BLSD.
I thank our dear researchers.
Thank you so much for your hard work.
BABEL CHEMICALS
-Hey.
-What's going on?
What happened?
What the hell?
-To the hospital, now!
-Call 911 now and move him!
No, not him.
I'm talking about me, asshole!
-Let's go.
-Blood!
-Take me to the hospital!
-What happened?
-He's bleeding.
-What's going on?
-Hey, call 911 now.
-Damn it.
Come on, we have to help him.
Sign the paper, or we won't
take you to the hospital. Okay?
-What happened? U-yeong!
-Come on.
-Gosh, come on.
-What?
-What's this?
-I mean,
why would thugs like them
have a meal at a place like this?
I know, right?
It's not like they're the Mafia.
What?
Why is that in there?
Unbelievable.
How did a nail get mixed up
in the spaghetti?
We should upload this
to all the social media pages.
I think it pierced my mouth.
And it's rusty, too.
This is bad.
-You never got the DPT vaccine.
-No.
What if you get tetanus?
Do you have any penicillin?
Come on!
I see that you've decided to play dirty.
Trying to drive us out, are you?
You're asking for a beating, aren't you?
-Why you…
-Hold it!
Just pay up and leave.
Oh, look. I'm done.
-How much is it?
-What about this?
What about this nail?
It was in my food!
What are you doing with that, Su-nam?
Don't do that.
Sit down. Stay calm and sit down.
-Let's go!
-Damn it.
You asshole.
I told you to stop.
How will you get through life
with no self-control?
Hey, stop that.
Disruptive customers may face
a maximum fine of 15 million won fine
or a five-year prison sentence
depending on the offense.
You'd better watch it.
Are you happy now? You idiot.
You're embarrassing, so just get up.
Keep your restaurant clean. Let's go.
Go. Hurry.
-Go.
-Did you pay?
I was going to do that next.
Here goes my hand to my back pocket
Goodness. What's the rush?
-Here you go.
-It's 95,000 won.
You need to pay more.
Here.
Sir.
I can't open my eyes.
I can't see anything.
Where are you? Sir.
-This way.
-Okay.
Make some sounds. Clap.
-Hurry.
-This way.
Be careful. One, two.
-Oh, my babies.
-One, two.
My plates. What do I do?
My goodness.
-I'm sorry. I'll pay for the plates.
-What?
That's a lot of money.
He's not even hiding it now.
He's just outright hot.
Jeez. I'm so sick of those thugs.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I need to leave early today.
-Is something wrong?
-What should I do?
I have a blind date.
It's been three years.
You should go. Hurry. Good luck!
I can do it!
-Don't talk too much.
-Okay.
And one more thing.
And don't play any weird games.
Oh, right.
The finger flick.
Should we go for dinner?
What are you doing?
We made a bet earlier.
You said you didn't hit women
even if it was a game.
You said it was okay.
Yes, I did say that.
Do you need to warm up
just for a finger flick?
Shall we proceed?
"Proceed"? Am I being sentenced?
Okay.
What's all the fuss?
It's against your principles.
Fine. Do it!
Get it over with.
What was that? Do it right.
I tried,
but I missed.
Until next time, then.
Right, it's over there.
-Cha-young!
-Jeez!
Don't sneak up on me like that.
Hi.
Do you want to guess what happened today?
I…
became an official partner.
I'm no longer an intern.
I'm a partner at Wusang.
Right. Good for you.
Wait.
You don't seem happy.
I'm a partner now.
Yes. Good for you.
Congratulations.
You're so mean.
It was only natural.
Did you want to be an intern forever?
You didn't congratulate me properly.
To make up for that,
I'll buy you something delicious.
Let's go have jjamppong.
The spiciest there is.
-Can't we get something else?
-Forget it.
I'm buying, so it's up to me.
Okay. Fine. I'll eat it. Let's go.
I'm good. Enjoy your meal.
People from Italy can't eat spicy food.
-Let's go.
-I guess he can't handle it.
Italian people love spicy chilis.
They even carry pepperoncini with them.
And I do, too.
They're 20,000 on the Scoville scale.
I love bird's eye chilis from Thailand.
That's 100,000 Scoville.
I have Red Savina habaneros in Mexico.
They're 300,000 Scoville.
Do you know ghost peppers from India?
They are 800,000 Scoville.
-You can eat 800,000-Scoville chilis?
-Yes.
-I guess you can handle some spicy food.
-Shall we go for jjamppong?
-Sure.
Let's go.
There's no chilly that's 800,000 Scoville.
What's up with them?
Thank you.
Did you get any cases?
Yes. The elks filed a lawsuit.
The elks?
An environmental organization
filed a lawsuit on behalf of the elks
against TQ E&amp;C for building a tunnel.
How absurd.
That's common in the US and Europe.
I guess you didn't know.
I see. I guess I don't know much.
This hits the spot.
What kind of lawsuits
did you handle in Italy?
Company disputes and mediation.
That must've been a tough job.
And there's the Mafia in Italy.
Actually, the Mafia
don't meddle in the lives of
regular people and businesses.
They do businesses amongst themselves.
They don't cross the line.
-"The line."
-No more shoptalk.
This won't do. Want more chili oil?
What?
I'm actually good.
It's too spicy for you.
-Have something else.
-This is delicious.
Is that so?
Then, are you guys working together?
Well, for now.
Don't make Cha-young's life difficult.
You look a little hard-boiled.
Do I?
It's just a feeling I got.
You seem gentle on the outside,
but you might be cold and cruel
on the inside.
I'm not like that.
Just eat.
Enjoy your meal, Mr. C.
You sure can eat spicy food.
EMERGENCY WARD
Lee U-yeong…
Hey, what did they say?
Did I cough up too much blood?
This is embarrassing.
That's not the problem. Look at you.
Hey, if I die,
go to the mountain and pray for me.
So I can go peacefully.
Stop talking nonsense.
Damn it. When the others collapsed,
I never thought it would happen to me.
Anyway, I can't believe that chairman.
How can he make a fuss
because my blood got on him
when I was the one who collapsed?
Don't get too worked up.
-Yes.
-Focus on your breathing.
-Okay?
-Hey.
I'm okay.
I'm Lee U-yeong from Sapgyocheon.
Lee U-yeong.
Are you the guardian?
Yes.
My friend is an orphan.
He doesn't have anyone but me.
So I'm… But what does he have?
It's chronic myelogenous leukemia.
It's a hematologic malignancy
from a genetic mutation.
Did he smoke or work a lot?
Well, yes.
But he only smoked a little.
He did seem to be swamped with work.
Is that the cause?
The cause hasn't been identified yet,
but it could have been a factor.
My friend works at Babel Chemicals.
Does it have anything to do with his job?
Babel Chemicals takes
their protocol very seriously.
If there was a problem at work,
your friend probably
failed to follow the protocol.
Goodness.
You two look like hell
from trying to show off.
We should go for round two.
This isn't the time for that.
Go get ready for the trial.
I can do that tomorrow.
Right, Mr. Cassano?
Listen to her.
Come on.
Hong Cha-young speaking.
Hello, Monk Chaesin.
-Is she a Buddhist now?
-Don't talk to me.
Okay. See you soon.
You can't handle spicy food at all.
We should head back to the plaza now.
-What is it?
-Go home. Call me if you need help.
Let's go.
Heave ho.
You'll be okay. Heave ho.
-Cha-young.
-One, two.
Was I being lied to then?
Yes. The director lied to you.
Haemun Medical Center is owned by Babel.
Anyone related to Babel is a scumbag.
How could this happen?
He used to be so healthy.
-His diagnosis was--
-Chronic myelogenous leukemia.
Yes, that's it.
He got it from working
with a toxic substance called BLSD.
Of course, the hospital said
it was his fault.
Then, isn't this an industrial accident?
Yes, it is. There are many victims.
Shouldn't he fight Babel?
No one wants to fight them.
Why the hell not?
I would've sued them already.
Is it because they offered
a lot of settlement money?
Not really.
They want to settle it quietly
because they know they'll lose.
But they didn't even try fighting them.
They ought to at least try something.
-Stop it.
-This is frustrating.
Poor thing. All he did was work.
Please help U-yeong.
He was such a decent man.
DRY CLEANING
Mr. Tak, the cause of the water leakage
was the trap gasket.
What's that?
It'll be done soon. I need ten minutes.
Okay.
-Goodness. Thank you for your help.
-Gosh.
-He helped fix our problems like his own.
-Thanks.
He was good-natured and polite.
He was so nice.
-Why are you guys fighting?
-We're not fighting.
-Look.
-It's working. Do it.
It's working?
-He was like family to us.
-It's working!
-Why did you call him then?
-Hey.
We'll do everything we can,
so he's not wronged.
Sir. Are you finally done?
I know this is sudden,
but I've completed my training.
I can help now.
Sir.
Gosh.
Help us, merciful Buddha.
Congratulations.
We should get started.
Okay.
I love this sound.
What's this?
"So Hyeon-u not allowed"?
PRAYER FOR MR. CASSANO
AND MS. HONG'S VICTORY
What's going on?
Sir. Excuse me.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you see
that you're not allowed here?
You have no shame.
What's going on?
That evil man.
"Evil"?
You covered their eyes and ears
with your lies. You are evil!
-"Evil"?
-Get out of here, evil-doer!
-Evil man!
-Why are you here?
-Get out of here. Out!
BABEL CHEMICALS
VICTIMS' FAMILIES OFFICE
My gosh!
The notice of your dismissal
by the victims' families.
What did you do to them?
You're the one who started this.
Wusang bribed you to urge them to settle.
Do you have proof?
What if we do?
Don't you know where I used to work?
Wusang?
A junior of mine at Wusang
is in charge of buying off
small crooked law firms like yours.
-Hey, listen.
-Yes?
-I'm about to go broke.
-What?
I lost all of my money
on stock investment.
Damn it.
So I decided to throw in the white towel
and took an interview
for a job opening at a law firm.
Was it Sudan And Bangbeop?
Sudan And Bangbeop?
They work for us.
Besides, that guy, Mr. So,
is just a bottom feeder.
What is it?
Does he only care about money?
Don't even get me started.
He whines for more money
even when we give him enough.
He's so annoying.
-Unbelievable.
-Seriously?
They never gave me money.
They're lying.
Did you think we wouldn't be able to
track the money since it was cash?
When people hide money,
they keep it close to them.
At home or their frequent spot, because…
they need easy access.
You shouldn't have left a trace
if you hid it in the office.
Or you could have cleaned up better.
If you leave prints,
it makes it so obvious
that you hid something.
Just like that?
Of course, we told the families
what you were up to.
My money.
Oh, right.
What did we do with the money?
What did we do?
Please.
DONATION RECEIPT
CERTIFICATE OF DONATION
DONATED BY: SO HYEON-U
DONATION AMOUNT: 613,000,000 WON
Hi.
Why don't you say hi?
-Cha-young.
-Yes?
What brings you here?
You'll find out soon enough!
Hello.
The attorney representing
the victims' families
resigned from the case.
With the consent from victims' families,
Jipuragi Law Firm decided
to take on this case.
You brat!
Cha-young.
You can't throw a grenade
on my lap like this.
Leave that alone. It's expensive.
We need to make a bang
in order for people to notice us.
There's only one way humans are born,
but there are countless ways to die.
I take it that your tonsils are fine now.
Right.
Thanks to you.
I get that you don't know how it's done
in Korea, but you can't be this reckless.
You'll be in big trouble.
You can't be this reckless
just because you don't know me.
You'll be in big trouble.
You have some guts.
I'll ask out of courtesy.
Do you have any terms for settlement
or advice for us?
If Babel Chemicals admits
their wrongdoings,
apologizes sincerely,
and sufficiently compensates the victims,
we'll drop the lawsuit.
And cease the manufacture of BLSD
and correct the lies they've spread.
Goodness. Forget it.
You're practically asking me
to shut down my law firm.
I am very sorry
to hear that you think that way.
It's up to you whether to accept or not.
But…
you should remember
that freedom comes with a price.
-Let's go, Ms. Hong.
-Sure.
I won't see you off.
Please don't.
So that guy, Vincenzo,
stabbed Chairman Jang's pillow
with syringes,
killed your crystal balls,
threatened you on the phone,
and burnt down the Babel Pharmaceuticals
warehouse?
Why bring up my crystal balls?
You're breaking my heart.
But now that I've met him,
it all seems to make sense.
By the way, I kind of want him.
From this point on,
I'll take all the cases
related to the Babel Group.
Leave them all to me.
Exactly!
Myung-hee, that's what
I wanted all along! Goodness.
Tell everyone in Seocho-dong.
I'm done warming up,
and I'm about to get in the ring.
I'll post a photo.
"Hashtag, here we come."
Why the long faces? What's the problem?
Mr. Cassano.
You have to stop her. Babel is dangerous!
I'm sorry, but I don't plan to do that.
You both know that.
You saw what happened.
That's why we're doing this. We can win.
Cha-young.
Let's go, Ms. Hong.
Oh, right.
Good luck with the elks.
Good luck.
Bye, Joon-woo.
Cha-young.
I can't keep going easy on you.
I didn't expect Ms. Choi
to get involved herself.
It all worked out.
I had to take her down eventually.
Do you think you can win?
She's a rookie who just joined the firm,
but it won't be easy.
It's more than that.
There's a 90-percent chance you'll lose.
No. The chance is always 50-50.
Before you fight,
you must consider three things first.
Their skill, their greed,
and their cunning.
I'm not a pushover either.
I am skilled and I'm also greedy.
Your skill and your greed
don't allow you to harm others.
Don't work yourself up.
Winning the first hearing isn't our goal.
But that'll make the second hearing
more difficult.
If we can't win,
we have to make sure
no one can win or lose.
You have to follow my advice this time.
I've been a lawyer for eight years.
I don't need any advice.
I'm not trying to downplay
your experience.
I'm going to give you advice
on how to become a real villain.
Fine.
I'll take your advice just this once.
But…
when it's my turn to give you advice,
you have to do as I say.
Sure.
Right. I remembered about Mr. So.
I hope he's doing well.
Of course.
He should be up by now.
Where am I? What?
Where am I?
What's this?
What's all this?
GREEN ONION, CARROT
Carrot seeds and perilla seeds?
Damn it. What's this?
Gosh. It must be a dream.
"Only for Mr. So"? What's this?
What the hell? It's not a dream!
What's going on?
Where am I?
It's cold!
That's my apartment!
Honey!
-Yes.
-Honey.
-The name's So Hyeon-u.
-Honey!
He's a lawyer.
He hasn't come home in two days.
Yes.
What do I do?
I'm right here!
Honey!
Once in a while, professional gamblers
attend Mafia-run gambling joints.
Like Chow Yun-fat in God of Gamblers.
Don't get worked up. Quiet.
Right before he was about to
win an astronomical sum,
do you know what they did?
They take him outside,
break both of his hands,
and tell him to never come back.
The Mafia these days don't
intimidate people as the times are hard.
-Gosh.
-I see.
Then they would try to void the game
one way or another.
They nullify the game without
raising any suspicions to make him leave.
I know what this is.
When we play cards with our family
on holidays,
the dads who lose would
turn over the table to void the game.
So you want to invalidate the trial.
We can't postpone the trial
or drop the case at the moment.
That's not what I had in mind.
-We'll do it during the trial.
-What?
Ruining a game of cards is easy
because the Mafia owns the gambling joint,
but we have no power
or the means to do that.
We can make that happen…
in our own way.
I can't wait.
I'm getting an adrenaline rush. Goodness.
What do I do?
This is driving me nuts. Where is it?
Yes. Please do that, Mr. Cho. Okay.
Bye.
We're about ready.
Once the lawsuit is over,
what's your next plan?
This is the last one.
I'll leave after taking care of the plaza.
Without watching Babel Group crumble down?
I think this will be enough
to pacify my anger.
I was wondering
if you were planning to stay in Korea.
I don't have much attachment
to this country.
I want to leave soon.
Sure. You should leave.
You have your own life to live.
Mr. Tak. What brings you here this early?
Give me your clothes
you're wearing to the trial.
-Our clothes?
-Yes.
I'll do that.
This way.
Just this once. Come this way.
Well…
since you don't like my food,
I prepared this for you instead.
My mother cooked everything herself.
I'm sure it tastes great. I promise.
My mom's touch.
You did it.
I'm sorry.
My car keys. I left them at home.
I always do this on an important day.
Let's take my car.
-You have a car?
-Yes.
It's parked on the way to the courthouse.
That's a hassle. Let's call a cab.
You need a sleek ride when you're headed
to the battlefield.
They're here.
-Hold on. Stop pushing!
-Stop pushing.
-Why are you pushing me?
-Gosh.
-Sir.
-Excuse me.
How will you compensate them?
What about the toxic substance?
Please, move out of the way.
-Sir.
-Just a comment, sir.
-I'm not leading the trial.
-The plaintiffs said they'll demand
-maximum compensation.
-She's leading it. Talk to her.
They're claiming it's due to
a toxic chemical called BLSD.
Is this true?
There are 40 victims in total.
Nine people have died from it.
Is this true?
My dear reporters,
you cannot ask me such questions
based on some online tabloids.
Please ask me questions based on facts.
Are you saying
the plaintiffs' claims are false?
Just because they're weak,
you believe them without question.
Why don't you check the facts?
So you're saying
the plaintiffs' claims are lying.
Not all weak people are just.
The plaintiffs are using their position
as the weak
to paint all the rich people as evil.
Therefore, I urge you not to believe them
when the plaintiffs claim they are weak
and that we are the ones who are lying.
The same goes for the opportunistic
lawyers representing the plaintiffs.
The claims are groundless?
So they're only putting on an act.
Hey, the plaintiffs' lawyers are here!
-What? Where?
-Where?
Move it!
-Excuse me.
-Where are they?
-A comment, please.
-Excuse me.
-The windows are tinted.
-Hey.
-I can't see anything.
-Say something.
What?
Why are you blocking the road?
You're pissing me off.
I'm pissed off as it is
because I lost the lawsuit.
Get away from my car.
Step back! Now!
You assholes!
Step back!
-What was that?
-Why curse at us?
Stop honking. Just go!
-It wasn't them!
-Come on.
-What was that?
-Goodness.
Who are you?
I'm representing the plaintiffs,
Hong Cha-young of Jipuragi Law Firm.
-Don't push me.
-Step back.
-Move aside.
-Stop pushing.
Come on. Stop pushing me!
What if you scratch it?
Your annual salary can't cover that!
Excuse me, Babel Chemicals said
that your claims were all false.
Hold on a second.
Come on. Stop pushing me!
Are you also a lawyer?
I'm an advisor of Jipuragi Law Firm.
-What? Hey, it's dangerous on the steps.
-What's going on?
-The public wants answers!
-Care to comment?
-Say something for them.
-Don't push me.
What do you think about the case?
Only evil can punish…
evil.
-What? Is it English or French?
-What?
-What did he say? "Diavolo"?
-"Diablo"?
-He's talking about the game, right?
-A game?
Is a game company involved in this case?
A comment, please.
The heinous Babel Chemicals
must repent!
-Repent!
OUT WITH BABEL CHEMICALS
BABEL CHEMICALS MUST BE HELD RESPONSIBLE
I can't live my life coughing up blood.
-What's that now?
-Babel Chemicals must repent!
This performance shows
the painful struggle of the victims,
everyone!
BRING DESTRUCTION TO BABEL CHEMICALS
THE TRUTH WILL BE REVEALED
We should take a video of this.
Put more soul in it.
Hold it up. Come on.
-You, too.
-You should repent. You're killing us.
What are those assholes doing?
Let's go.
Unbelievable.
SPECIAL THANKS TO SHIN SEUNG-HWAN
AND JUNG YOUNG-JU
It's highly unlikely.
There's nothing we can do
but stall for time.
No matter what they do,
they can never outwit me.
We must find out who their enemies are.
Because the enemy of my enemy…
is a friend.
I guess it's time I make a move.
They may provoke them in other ways.
If you can't beat him,
just get rid of him.
I'm going to win no matter what!
The last witness we have is…
-We need a witness…
-It's perfect.
…who is infallible.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim