(All characters, locations, organizations, religions,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
Misfortunes are like unwelcome guests...
that they show up out of the blue.
They're our family,
so someone in the family should raise them.
It's not like you're going to volunteer.
It's not easy to raise someone else's children.
She has a point.
They shouldn't grow up walking on eggshells.
Why don't we just send them to an orphanage...
They'll hear you.
- What about Soo Ja? - She just got on the flight.
She's coming from Jeju Island. So it will take her some time.
You think having her here would make any difference?
No matter how much she loved her sister,
I doubt that a single woman like her would raise two kids on her own.
It will be harder to let them go after getting attached to them.
For the sake of their future,
sending them to an orphanage is the best option.
As if! You're only thinking about yourselves, not the kids!
Soo Ja...
Even good fortunes...
don't come to us with a gentle knock.
I'm...
taking the kids.
Gosh. What in the world? You're not even married.
She's right. I understand that you care for them deeply.
I'm going to raise them!
At times, misery and fortunes come with the same face.
And I still have a hard time distinguishing the two.
You were the only person who had the same thought at the same time.
I'm grateful.
In many ways.
Hey.
This won't do.
Let's live together.
You and me.
Which one of the faces are you showing me?
Did you bring me luck...
or misery?
Or are you...
neither?
Sure.
What?
Of course, it's misery.
Why even ask?
Why did I ask him to live with me there?
Let's take it back.
The embarrassment only lasts so long.
Hey, I was being absurd earlier...
- What? - I don't mind living together,
but I can't stand your place.
What did you just say again? You were being absurd?
What? Me? No.
I've never once said anything absurd in my entire life.
That's too far stretched.
Where's the nearest train station from here?
Which neighborhood is this? Which subway line?
I'll just take my time to get to know all that.
Look at all this alcohol.
Are they expensive?
What is this table?
Is it expensive?
What's this sofa? Is it expensive?
Why do you keep talking to me?
Can't you see I'm reading?
You're just like me. You only look at me when I pick a fight.
Do you have feelings for me?
What?
- I guess you do. - No, I don't.
- Fine. - I really don't.
If you really don't, that means you have a problem...
considering you asked me to live with you.
I asked you to live with me because you're special.
You said I should be more clingy.
I'm saying you should be more clingy.
To your fate that came to you.
You said this is fate.
Something came to my mind as you started walking away.
"What if he just disappears without even telling me?"
That won't happen.
You were nice to me as if you were going to disappear.
People who are nice to me always disappear.
It was always like that with me.
You say it like you're not even sad about it.
What if you don't show up when the clock strikes 12?
What if I think of a wish but you don't show up?
That's why I asked you to live with me.
- Fine. - That's why.
- I said, fine. - I'm serious.
I don't know if I should believe you or not.
If I think of a wish... No.
If my wish comes true, I'll set you free.
I'm not a hostage. I should be saying that to you.
Where do you eat?
Where do you sleep?
Where's my room? Where should I sleep?
I don't sleep or eat.
You don't get your own room. You can sleep...
upstairs wherever.
But there are tons of rooms here.
But there isn't one for you.
Excuse me for looking around.
Darn it.
- Hey. - I said you don't get a room.
Dong Kyung.
What was that? Where is that sound coming from?
It's that puppy I saw in front of your place.
- "Puppy"? - Yes.
If you think about it, he sort of looks like one.
Dong Kyung! Hey! Dong Kyung.
Sun Kyung?
How does he know this place?
He's at your place.
What are you talking about?
You'll find out once you go outside.
My gosh, he's incredible.
Hey, Sun Kyung. Have you been well? Did you eat?
Yes, Aunt Soo Ja.
Let me tell you what happened today. Dong Kyung...
I'll kill you if you tell her anything.
She's really nice to me.
She's so nice to me, and I'm really happy.
I can't live without her.
Soo Ja, you look even more beautiful today...
with that sunlight shining over you.
Whatever it was, I'm sure it was your fault, Sun Kyung.
What do you mean it was my fault?
You're always on her side.
I wired you money.
I love you, Aunt Soo Ja. I'll be a good nephew.
I, Tak Sun Kyung, live with a goal to be a good nephew.
You punk.
Just be good to your sister. I wired the money to her account.
What? Why?
You're obviously favoring her over me.
Why did you wire money?
I make my own money.
That way, I get to have the right to be an adult and nag at you.
If Sun Kyung doesn't behave, you can keep every penny.
Aunt, Dong Kyung is a scrooge.
Once she receives money, she never spits it out.
Did you just call me a Scrooge? I'm surprised you know that word.
I guess your college degree really pays off.
Gosh, you guys still behave like little kids.
Aunt, he even finished his military service. Look at his dark skin.
I don't have dark skin.
I have brighter skin than Dong Kyung.
I just got tanned. That's all.
I don't think Dong Kyung will give you any money...
judging by how you're behaving.
It's nighttime in Korea, isn't it?
That's enough arguing, my babies.
- Good night. - You too, Aunt.
Don't worry. Talk to you next time.
Aunt, wait...
(Call ended)
What? What do you want?
"What? What do you want?"
You're so brazen.
You really are unbelievable.
What did you just say?
Have some respect for your older sister.
Why couldn't you be like this to that jerk?
Why are you always so hard on your brother instead?
What did you do to him?
Did you beat him up?
Are you worried about that married man?
No, I'm worried about you.
I'm worried you might go to jail for messing with that jerk.
Don't worry. I took care of him.
The skies helped.
- Hey! - Help!
Stop right there!
Help!
911? I called to report a car accident.
He didn't die.
He had amazing reflexes.
It means he was really fast.
But I bet he'll get hospitalized for about eight weeks.
Now that he's out of the way,
where's the other guy?
Why aren't you asking me anything?
Why aren't you asking me why I dated a married man?
What's there to ask? It's pretty obvious.
How could you have known that he lied to you?
Was he nice to you?
You always fall for guys who are nice to you.
This is why I told you not all nice people are good.
My gosh, you're such a fool.
Get out of the way. Where's the other guy hiding?
He's home, isn't he? You just wait.
Hey! Sun Kyung!
Hey, wait.
Hey, wait. No, wait...
I'm not going to wait. Tell me where he is right now.
- No, he's not here. - Don't lie to me.
He's not here, right?
I told you he isn't here. Come on. Let's go.
- Get off me! - My gosh.
I told you he's not here.
Hello, my brother-in-law.
He's not your brother-in-law.
You really did a great job of hiding him.
Look at him lying proudly on your bed.
I tried my best.
There was nowhere to hide.
Why don't you move to a bigger place, honey?
Hey.
Don't call me that. Call me "honey".
"Honey"?
No.
Honey.
No...
So you're telling me you faked it on purpose?
You purposely told him you guys were living together?
Yes, exactly.
It was to get rid of him.
Stay out of it, Dong Kyung.
He's so calm and relaxed.
That kind of vibe normally comes from money.
How dare he smirk?
Let's have a drink.
A drink? Why are you suddenly asking him to drink?
Will you just stay still?
The only way to see a man's true colors...
is to get him drunk.
Do you have money to buy drinks?
So while we're on that subject,
can you lend me 10 dollars?
He looks unrealistic.
He's rich and good-looking.
Why does he like my sister, who has nothing?
Let's do that.
- What? - Let's have a drink.
My sister thinks I'm thoughtless...
and reckless.
You are.
Darn it. This is so frustrating.
I have plans too. I think too.
Sure. You have plans and you think too, right?
Right! You're right.
You're so right.
You don't know anything.
I'm going to start tomorrow.
People always ask when you'll do it...
right before you're about to,
and kill your mood.
Are you a mind reader?
You are so good at reading people's minds.
No one understands how I feel.
No matter how lonely and hard it is,
I pretend to be strong and positive.
If you're lonely, act lonely.
If things are hard, act like things are hard.
Don't act strong all the time, okay?
Okay. You pass.
What? He passes?
Please be good to my sister.
Who are you to say that?
Let go.
It's nice to meet you, brother-in-law.
Hey.
My gosh! Look at the time!
I should go now.
Out of nowhere? It's late. Just sleep over.
No, it's fine.
I'm not clueless, you know.
What are you talking about? Do you want a beating?
Have fun, brother-in-law.
- Hey. Are you really leaving? - Brother-in-law.
- Sun Kyung. - Yes.
- Hey. - Yes.
I'll say bye from here, brother-in-law.
Okay.
Darn it.
Cheers.
Of course, I know he's lonely and life is hard.
And what's wrong with you?
How could you listen to it just because you hear it?
That's so rude.
But I hear it. What can I do?
You should try not to hear.
I thought you were different, but where are your manners?
Hey!
What?
Can't I smoke in my own home?
Exactly. This is my home.
How is that your home?
What happened earlier may happen again.
I need to smoke.
And I didn't like how you liked my home.
Fine, if that's how you want to play.
This is nice. My place just got a whole lot bigger.
Why did he say let's live together then?
You're the one who said let's live together.
That's him, right?
The person you love the most.
No, it isn't.
I said it isn't.
Don't even think about hurting him.
You're the one...
who should think about what happens to him, not I.
Fine. If that's how you want to play.
Why are you putting a blanket there?
In case you do something to my home while I'm asleep.
I will if you want.
I'm a light sleeper.
Are we bragging now?
I can kill people.
Forget it. Go to sleep.
I told you before.
I don't eat or sleep since I'm not human.
- You ate the cake. - I was playing along.
I see, is that right?
Then play along, and turn off the lights.
I'm reading.
Do you think the world has to end?
Not really.
Then why are you doing this?
Because it doesn't have to exist either.
Beings like you usually pity humans.
Especially humans like me.
Are you close to someone like me?
That's how they are in the fantasy movies I've watched.
Humans are all terminal.
They live eternally only until they realize that.
They're all insignificant. They're all the same.
That's why there's no need to pity anyone in particular.
Pitying someone comes from the heart.
It's not a need.
I have no heart since I'm not human.
Liar.
You said you felt the same thing I did...
at the same time.
Here. Dong Kyung.
Mine is bigger.
Let's go on the Ferris wheel.
- Yes! - Let's go.
Sun Kyung! Come have some watermelon!
- Happy birthday, Dong Kyung. - Happy birthday.
Did you sleep well?
You must've had a good dream.
Did you come into my dream?
Me?
No.
I'm only in your home.
What are you doing?
Instilling fear.
Get out.
All right. Let's settle our terms.
The terms are...
I have to ask you...
to destroy the world before I die.
During the period of our contract, my last 100 days,
I will not feel any pain.
You're like Cinderella.
You need to recharge before midnight.
Other than asking you...
to destroy the world before I die,
you have to grant me a real wish.
I'm regretting that now.
Without that condition, things would've been much easier.
If I violate the terms of the contract,
the person I love the most...
in the world will die at that very moment.
Why are you so negative?
You could still live.
Wait.
Then, either way, that person is going to die.
If I violate the contract, that person will die.
But even if I don't, that person will still die.
Who? Tak Sun Kyung?
Fine. Let's just kill him then. That works for me too.
When you wanted the world to end, you didn't even think about him.
Because I didn't mean that.
No, you did.
I wouldn't have heard it unless you meant it.
See you later.
Have a good day.
Your last 100 days are starting today.
(Ask the world to end before dying.)
(Free of any physical pain for the last 100 days.)
(Make another wish before dying.)
(The person I love the most will die if I violate the terms.)
(Wish, doom, and the person I love the most)
Seriously. Young Prince is amazing.
His post got thousands of views the moment it was uploaded.
Episode 94 will be good too, right?
Of course. Why would you even ask that?
Jijo King is dead set against making the revisions.
I guess even your good looks didn't work on him.
I guess I'm not that good-looking.
Gosh. Don't say stuff like that.
You are very good-looking.
My good looks aren't for you.
Did Siberia sign a new contract for the upcoming novel?
Siberia came a few days ago and met with Ms. Tak.
He's already posting two novels right now.
So handling three novels at the same time would be too much.
So we'll sign a new contract when one of the novels is over.
How's his speed?
You know that he's not slow.
I haven't heard from him for a while now.
But he already gave us a lot of episodes in advance,
so I'm keeping my eye on him for now.
Really?
I'll call him and see how he's doing.
Look at that. Mr. Good-looking feels confident that...
Siberia is going to answer his calls.
That's it for today.
- Good work. - Good work.
(Hey, the boiler...)
Hey, the boiler at your house is running.
- What was that? - Darn him. What?
Didn't that get typed on its own?
What are you talking about?
My gosh. The meeting today was so long, wasn't it?
- No... - It was way too long.
I'm so tired. Aren't you tired? Gosh. I'm so tired.
Please insert a card.
I won't ask a lot. Just wire me 300 dollars.
That depends on you.
Then, 200 dollars.
That might drive up the heating bill a lot.
Come on. Darn it.
- Then, just 50 dollars. - Gosh.
Hey!
Lunch is the reason I come to work.
I need to cure my hangover. I want jjamppong.
What should I eat today?
I wanted to turn it off,
but the number keeps going up.
You know, I have no experience in this.
How many minutes do we have left for our lunch break?
What is it?
About 40 minutes?
Sorry. You guys should eat without me.
Hey, where are you going?
What?
Hey!
Darn it.
(Absent Mode)
I figured out the system when I tried out a few buttons.
You should thank me.
Come on. This guy...
Yes, Ms. Cha.
I'm on my way right now.
Yes. Go to the funeral now.
Pardon?
I'm sorry. I had an urgent call.
This should be the most urgent matter on your hands.
My ranking got pushed down.
Right. I see.
What? Shanghai Park?
This writer I've never heard of is climbing up now.
This industry has a lot of competition.
I heard that all the writers you handle are in the top 10.
What's your secret?
I'm not sure.
The writers work really hard.
Gosh. Don't be a stranger now.
I'll tell you if you pay me.
Gosh. You make such nasty jokes.
I wasn't joking.
Do you want to sign with me?
A personal contract with just me.
You will do exactly what I tell you to do.
If you get into the top 10 writers, I get a bonus.
Do you mean that?
That was a joke. No way.
The school reunion?
- Why all of a sudden? - It's not all of a sudden.
We've been having reunions for nine years without you.
The girls really want to catch up with you.
Tell them I'm still in Japan.
Seriously?
What was your nickname? Swimming Prince?
That's all in the past now.
The girls called you the Swimming Prince.
They said that you always smelled like soap.
And they were crazy about you.
When Na Ji Na made a banner with that line,
it was hilarious.
Who's coming?
Da Young, Eun Bi, and Jung Hwa.
Hey, I heard that Na Ji Na is coming too.
- Really? - Na Ji Na is coming too?
Hey, I'm busy. Bye.
Will you come or not? Just tell me that.
Fine. I'll come.
- You have to come. - Okay.
What would you like?
What do you want?
It's a glioblastoma.
You have multifocal glioblastomas.
I will find out more with a biopsy.
I'll do it.
I'll do everything. Please help me.
With the surgery, you have 1 year. Without it, you have 3 months.
Even if you get the surgery, you may suffer from hemiplegia,
a speech disorder, and a cognitive disorder as well.
I'll get the surgery. I'll get it now.
Please help me. Help me, doctor.
Right. This is the normal reaction.
Pardon?
I mean, you should be the one clinging on to me, right?
She's so weird.
Pardon?
What was that?
Why am I crying?
I'm not sure. Because you got lost?
Turn right for the otolaryngology department.
Thank you.
(Intensive Care Unit)
The patient in Room 302 went out.
[VIU Ver] tvN E03 'Doom at Your Service'
"Living Together with Myul Mang"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
My grandfather was proud that I was a writer.
He always asked me what I was writing,
but I was always too embarrassed...
to tell him.
I'm sure he would've loved it.
I also love your work.
Really?
You enjoyed reading "You Were Never a Friend to Me"?
("You Were Never a Friend to Me")
You really think my grandpa would've liked it?
(Writer: Siberia, Genre: BL, Rating: 3)
No, I enjoyed reading your other work called,
"I, the Leader of Demons, Am Just an Average..."
"Office Worker in This World".
To be frank,
I'm really proud of my work called "Love During an Apocalypse".
(Writer: Siberia, Genre: Romance, Rating: 1)
You see,
that's your problem.
The stuff you love isn't exactly the stuff you're good at.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have said that here.
It's okay. It's about work anyway.
I didn't even show up to our last meeting.
The writer is wandering around somewhere.
I needed time with you.
By any chance, were you lost that day?
I was lost in my dreams. I thought I was gone for good.
I don't know why I slept for so long.
I woke up, and the entire day had already passed by.
You were asleep?
Gosh.
Thank you for coming.
I know I already put you through enough.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
No, don't say that. You didn't put me through anything.
Don't worry about finishing your story for now.
We'll take care of it.
You should take enough time to grieve and feel better.
Thank you.
Sure.
(RIP Joo Seon Jin)
Excuse...
A bus will arrive shortly.
Hey, which bus do I need to take...
to get to Myeong-dong?
This one.
You need to take this one.
But it's leaving.
So that's what I need to take?
(031G 7370)
Hey, I love your bracelet.
Where did you buy it?
Dong Kyung.
Hey.
How did you know I was here?
I actually had something to ask.
Let's go. Let's talk later.
- No, but... - Let's talk at home.
What's with you?
I've seen you before.
What?
I've seen you before at a funeral hall.
You were crying that day.
I suddenly remembered.
You told me you don't eat or sleep,
have no feelings,
and never feel sorry for anyone.
But it was all a lie.
How are you going to explain all those tears?
What are you talking about? That wasn't me.
I see.
I guess adults cry too.
A bus will arrive shortly.
My bus is here.
(Jung-gu, Euljiro-4-ga, Myeong-dong, Sinchon Rotary...)
Yes, it was you.
No, it wasn't me.
Yes, it was.
Hey, you told me you don't sleep.
Why are you suddenly pretending to sleep?
Let's say you really do sleep.
But why do you sleep there when you have tons of other rooms?
Because I'm worried about you.
Are you serious?
You're not worried I might do something to your place?
Hey, you should quit work.
All of a sudden?
Just quit and stay home.
I may be dying soon,
but I still need to earn money for food.
I need to pay my rent, food,
and heating bill.
How will I afford to pay my living expenses?
Make a wish and ask for money.
Say a number and you'll get it.
I can't do that.
I don't want to waste my wish on that.
You need to put your guard up.
Don't show that bracelet to anyone.
It could become your weakness.
What's with you today?
You don't...
have feelings for me, do you?
Okay, I guess you don't. But don't give me that look.
You're making me feel embarrassed.
I'm not human,
so I don't exactly know what that feels like.
You're really weird.
- You know that? - If anything happens,
don't say I didn't warn you.
My gosh, how scary.
I'm so scared that I might even cry.
I didn't cry.
If you're not human,
why do you get worked up every time I ask if you cried?
Getting worked up is also a form of emotion.
It's almost time for midnight.
Give me your hand.
But do you really not remember me?
I was right across the hall.
I was just as pretty as I was back when I was young.
I guess you're sleeping.
You told me you don't eat or sleep...
and that you have no emotions,
but look at you sleeping right now.
I don't sleep.
Not once even when you're asleep.
It means I'm always awake when you're defenseless.
That means I'm dangerous.
By the way,
why did you cry so much that day?
Whom did you lose?
My mother.
- Your mother? - Yes, I guess.
She was something similar.
So you did cry.
I said I didn't cry.
Were you sad when I died?
Do you enjoy showing up unannounced these days?
You acted so cold,
but I guess you even know how to cry.
Why did you approach her?
I said I'll do anything.
Forget it. She'll die soon anyway.
That's what I should be saying.
At least I won't be harming her.
I guess you guys are pretty close now.
Just close enough.
That's good.
It was your first time having a human remember you, right?
But then again,
I bet it was hard to forget...
since you were crying your eyes out that day.
Don't get the wrong idea.
I need to go now. Bye.
Don't cry because I'm gone.
Hey. Hey!
Darn it. Dong Kyung.
Your blood pressure and heart rate are good today.
Your condition improved a lot recently.
At this rate, you can go home soon.
Really?
Liar.
Your condition improved a lot too.
At this rate, a flower will bloom soon.
What...
is this?
The new writer is kind of old.
He only writes on paper.
- And? - You're in charge.
Says who?
Says the CEO.
Is he back?
He is. Tragically.
I don't know if it's been too long since I've seen him,
but he seems different.
That's our CEO? That?
I don't think he seems that different.
He's driving me insane.
Are you insane?
No, I'm totally sane.
Is this because I teased you for crying?
- No way. - Oh my gosh, it is.
You seem to like living with me,
so I thought you'd like working with me too.
Why are you doing this at someone else's company?
A company isn't a playground.
Someone else's company? I'm the CEO.
Why you...
I ought to... Get over here. Get...
Sir. We have the date for the web novel conference.
Were you in the middle of something important?
Yes.
We were in the middle of a very important discussion.
I see. I'll let you continue.
Ms. Tak. Isn't it time for your meeting with Lee Hyun?
You go for me.
What?
As you can see,
I'm very busy right now, so you go in my place.
Okay, sure.
She's acting weird.
She has changed.
Do you like him?
What? Why?
Does that punk like me?
No.
I meant, give up if you do.
He was cursing you inside.
At least I say it out loud.
Why you... Seriously...
Are you coming to the reunion? Hyun Kyu's coming.
(Are you coming to the reunion? Hyun Kyu's coming.)
(Lee Hyun Kyu)
(Lee Hyun Kyu, YouTuber)
(Lee Hyun Kyu, Images)
("National High School Swim Meet 200m Freestyle Bronze Medalist")
Couldn't you just win the gold?
Hyun Kyu went to study abroad for swimming.
But he failed and came back and opened a cafe in Korea.
This can't be it, can it?
(101 Ways to Fall in Love)
It's so boring.
Mr. Cha Joo Ik?
("Must we wear name tags?")
Ms. Tak was busy with work.
I had something to give you regarding ending the series.
And I had feedback for you on the new series.
Should we discuss the new series first?
- Sure. - I don't know...
how to even begin.
It's fine. Just speak comfortably.
I will. It's our job to say it even if it's uncomfortable.
I see.
Do you think a man who avoids problems...
whenever something happens is attractive?
- What? - This is the pattern...
for all of your male main characters.
When the woman says she likes him, he runs away and rejects her.
If something happens, he takes off by himself.
There needs to be a conflict for them to get together.
I'm asking if that conflict is attractive.
I must write it because I think so.
- Ms. Lee. - What?
So, your real name is...
Na Ji Na?
Yes, It's Na Ji Na.
Is "Lee Hyun" from his name?
Lee Hyun Kyu.
I guess I'm right.
That's why they're all like that.
Because they're based on him.
Is this okay?
People will get the wrong idea if you're in here for too long.
Let them.
It'll all be over once I die anyway.
Next page.
Exactly.
It'll all be over once you die anyway.
Why are you working so hard?
My boss told me to do it, so naturally, I have to work hard.
Let's share the pain since we share a common fate.
Who says we share a common fate?
If we felt the same thing at the same time, well...
Hey. Forget it.
Can't you just beg nicely?
"Let's cancel the whole thing." How easy is that?
Why don't you know how to beg?
Will you do this then?
I can't type.
I don't eat, sleep, cry, or type...
Then how did you type into my laptop?
Strictly put, I didn't type into it.
I just showed it to you.
Seriously, the mouth on this one.
Does that mean you can't eat, sleep, or talk?
Since you can cry?
Memories are very easily distorted.
Exactly. How did I forget that?
You don't have a common face.
That's true.
It's very common.
This face is much more common than you'd think.
It's amazing.
I couldn't remember at all,
but when someone bumped into me, all of it came rushing back.
What?
I was standing there in the funeral parlor.
And someone bumped into me.
Sorry...
Wait.
It was her.
The girl from the bus stop.
Then I must do whatever it takes.
I said I'll do anything.
Hey. Where are you going?
Hey. Hey!
Is this the "anything" you said you'd do?
- You're here. - Is this what you meant?
What did I do?
All I did was make her remember things that happened.
You're the one who got close to her.
Did you realize what it means to have compassion?
- I don't know what that is. - No, you do.
You just tell yourself that.
You smile a lot and feel bad for her, don't you?
- Your feelings will grow. - Never.
Do you think you can let her die?
She was fated to die, to begin with.
Can't you change her fate?
How can I worry about her?
How can I feel bad for her?
You pity yourself the most in the world, don't you?
What about you?
Do you know what compassion is?
I pity the person who will die...
in place of her in case you break the contract.
Seriously. I'll die before my time because of you.
How could you just ditch me after making that huge mess?
Wait. Why can't I find my key?
I should change it to a smart door lock.
I had to stay and work late today because of you.
Why do you keep staring at me?
You said...
you remembered me, right?
What? Yes.
I remember you too.
Everyone was crying, but a young girl was smiling.
It was sad to watch you, so I remember you.
It was sad?
I don't know where and when this all started.
Hey, what are you talking about?
But I don't care.
I don't plan on making you smile.
Hey, why are you saying stuff like that?
Is it because I teased you for crying?
Hey, I'm sorry if I offended you.
It will be midnight soon.
But I will not hold your hand.
What are you saying?
I've been too nice for no reason.
I need...
Give me your hand.
Is that your wish?
I need your hand. Give me your hand!
I'm asking you if that's your wish.
Please...
Is it?
I told you that you shouldn't lower your guard.
That bracelet could make you vulnerable.
I'm not human.
I don't eat, sleep, or cry.
I don't feel compassion or love.
Such feelings don't exist for me.
That's what I decided a long time ago.
I pity you.
No, you should pity yourself.
You will cry because of me.
And you will want to destroy the world...
because that's the only way to kill me.
Is that...
your grand plan?
Then, this is my plan.
- Have you gone mad? - I knew it.
I knew you would stop me.
I figured you out.
You don't eat, sleep, or cry?
You don't feel compassion or love?
Because you're not human?
But I do because I'm human.
So my plan is...
to love you.
(Doom)
(Doom, person I love the most)
Then, I'll be able to live...
without losing anything.
Then, let's do it right,
Love me to the point that you want to destroy the world for me.
(Doom at Your Service)
Everyone either resents me or wants me.
No one loves me.
I will love you because I have to.
Don't regret it.
I don't remember.
Why would she like someone like him?
Why can't she get over him?
You're signing it with me. A personal contract.
It's game over if he shows up in your dream.
What would happen if I were to kill him now?
Die!
I'm here for Tak Sun Kyung.
If I can't kill you, I'll make you miserable.
I told you. You won't be able to love me.