Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 12
Girl,
I am not a monster.
don’t be scared.
I have dispelled all the evil people.
I am not a monster.
Don’t be scared.
Your father
saved my life.
Are you Jia’s daughter?
I am not a monster.
What is your name?
Don’t kill me.
I am not a monster.
I am not…
Don’t kill me.
-Don’t kill me.
-Who is going to kill you?
I… I am not coming to kill you.
I am coming to help you.
Your father
died to save me
because he believed I could help you
cure your disease.
I am not a disease.
Are you hiding
because you don’t want others
to see how you look?
Girl,
let me tell you a story.
Both my wife and daughter can transform.
They look even weirder than you
after transformation.
Look,
so I am not afraid of you at all.
Your father said
you started to look like this
after you got sick 17 years ago.
Is it true?
No.
It is not a disease.
My father didn’t know.
I am not who I am.
I am not a disease.
Not a disease?
What is it then?
Girl,
you…
Do you know a girl named Jin’er?
She
may be a little older than you.
Jin’er?
Yes.
She is much prettier than me.
They all love her.
Who are they?
You know Jin’er?
All love her.
Do you also love her?
Do you also want to kill me?
You also want to kill me!
-I don’t want to kill you.
-Come and kill me!
I am a monster.
-Girl.
I... I won’t.
I also want to kill myself.
Calm down.
Put down the knife.
I am not who I am.
I can’t kill myself.
Father.
I want to die.
Girl, calm down.
Give me the knife.
Come on.
Do you also want to kill me?
Come and kill me!
Kill me.
Just kill me.
Come and kill me.
Father.
Help me.
Hey, girl.
Do you really know Jin’er?
Can you tell me
who on earth she is?
Let me out.
Just kill me.
Come and kill me.
Master,
the thing that Marquis Pingjiang wants
is ready now.
Has he boarded?
Yes.
He chose your fish boat.
One more thing,
Ms. Yin Zhuang visited
all foundries in Pingting today.
What did she do there?
She showed two very ugly crystal stones
with mediocre textures and asked them
to make a pair of bracelets
as her dowry.
It happened suddenly
and no workshop owner dared to
accept her order.
Everybody is waiting outside.
Please kindly provide your advice.
What kind of crystal stone?
Nobody knows it,
but they all claim it to be valueless.
Ms. Yin Zhuang insisted it was
an heirloom of the Yin Family.
Just ask Mr. Liu to take the order
and present it to me.
Yes.
Ms. Yin Zhuang is really a wise girl.
Master.
What’s up? Why are you in a hurry?
Ms. Yin Zhuang
she…
She visited Wu Yan’s jewelry workshop.
What?
Why did she go there?
None of our foundries
dared to take her order.
But Tan the shoe repairman
outside Lan’s jewelry workshop
gave her a hint,
telling her that Wu Yan
was the best jewelry maker in Pingting.
Bracelet
What a diehard!
I should have killed him
when I took over his workshop then.
Is she alone?
Where is Yin Xiao?
Master,
Yin Xiao is still inquiring about
the whereabouts of Huotu Xin.
Keep a close eye on him.
Aye.
Prepare the carriage.
Marquis Pingjiang is waiting for me.
Heirloom.
Are you treasures
only in the countryside?
In Pingting,
nobody knows you.
This is your last hope.
Just cheer up.
Anybody here?
May I know
if it is the workshop of Master Wu Yan?
Yin Zhuang?
Huotu Xin?
Bracelet
Wish Marquis
a smooth
and successful trip
to Zhaodu!
Weisheng Yan,
I haven’t used your fish boat
for some days
and it looks even more magnificent.
You are almost
as majestic as I am.
They are all prepared
for Your Highness.
Everything at my home
belongs to Your Highness.
Really?
I thought you had
prepared them for the Yin Family.
Your Highness
has the highest esteem today
and your territory
covers half of Suchuan.
The daughter of the Yin family
married to a merchant
miserably,
and became a civilian.
How can the Yin family
be comparable with Your Highness?
Weisheng Yan,
you have made unknown sacrifices
on your way to becoming
Suchuan’s rich merchant in Pingting.
But I know it well.
So my advice for you is that
focus on your own business,
never indulge yourself in girls
and become lost among them.
None of them is real.
Thanks for your advice, Your Highness.
Where is the thing I want?
I gathered the best jewelry makers
in Pingting to make it the soonest.
There is never a mistake.
What is that?
Does Your Highness
take any gift on the trip to Zhaodu?
A grand gift.
Master!
Where are you going?
Look for Yin Zhuang.
I am afraid she is in danger.
You…
How come did you get here?
Is anybody following you?
Are you sure
you are alone?
I can put my hand away.
But you must promise me
not to yell
and shout.
Dude,
you are dating a girl so soon
after you came here.
You are mistaken, sir.
No.
We have been looking for him.
Looking for him?
Girl,
please.
This way, please.
Please, please.
How did you come here?
Are you really coming for
jewelry making instead of me?
It is said
he is the best jewelry maker
in Pingting.
Are you really not coming for me?
Weisheng Yan doesn’t know I’m here?
It is just a coincidence.
But my brother did look for you.
He even broke into
the jail of Marquis Pingjiang
If so,
will Marquis let him leave safely?
Weisheng Yan spent a lot.
Then why didn’t your brother
say the same
in his letter addressed to Zhaodu?
He said I was safe and sound here.
It will spare Linglong’s worries
and it is not a mistake.
-But…
-No.
In his reply letter to Zhaodu,
my brother only told the truth.
We lost you
and we all felt sorry.
He even asked His Majesty for a penalty.
Sir,
what she said
is different from
what your granddaughter said.
Who shall I trust then?
Trust her.
Thanks, Sir.
But,
my granddaughter must have
her reasons to do that.
Do you still not trust me now?
I… I do.
Just let go of me then.
I didn’t mean to not trust you.
I just don’t trust Weisheng Yan.
He gave me to Zhu Xi
and cheated you.
It seems
he is really a tricky and cunning guy.
Maybe you have been used by him
without realizing it.
I know.
You know?
You still married him if you knew it?
It is my own business.
Moreover,
all merchants are profiteers.
Girl,
where did you get
the two crystal stones?
They are our ancestral treasures
passed down through generations.
Originally,
it is
my brother…
You…
Don’t you expect
to
make something out of it?
I want to make a pair of bracelets
as my dowry.
But all the workshops in Pingting
claimed it was valueless.
But this is all
I can give you.
Those mediocre official craftsmen
know nothing about it
and they are valueless actually.
But I have changed my mind.
I don’t like to make anything.
Let’s go back to my brother.
Girl,
why…
Why don’t you change your mind?
What a pity!
You don’t trust me.
Nobody except me
in Suchuan
is qualified to make a jewelry
out of the two crystal stones.
No, I…
No more nonsense!
I won’t return them to you. I…
I can’t tolerate
to see those mediocre craftsmen
spoil them.
They can be invaluable
only in my hand.
Just take it easy, girl.
I will give you
the best dowry
in Suchuan.
Wait for me.
Sir!
No more nonsense.
Sir.
It is not your property anyway.
Stop your nonsense!
Sir.
I have a question for you.
Go ahead.
I visited Jia’s home.
There must be something wrong
with his daughter.
But it is not a disease.
Do you know anything
about the plague
seventeen years ago?
The plague seventeen years ago
is nothing compared with
the two stones.
Just forget it.
Are they your stones?
They are not yours.
Are you nuts, old man?
Just return them to the owner.
I am doing it for her good.
After my work is finished,
she will know it all.
But she didn’t approve it.
Okay, just go away.
Don’t interfere with me.
Girl, get onto the sedan.
Look,
he seems bewitched
and turns a deaf ear to me
when he looks at the two stones.
Just go and take them back yourself.
A person will forget himself
only when he sees his beloved.
It is for him then.
You changed your mind?
Only someone who knows them
can realize their value.
There are liquors here.
I couldn’t drink liquors so freely
on Bright Moon Island before.
Weisheng Yan’s people are
everywhere in Pingting.
It is a good place for drinking indeed.
Why are you laughing?
I didn’t expect that
an aristocratic girl
drank liquors this way.
How do you think
an aristocratic girl should drink then?
You are the only one I know.
According to the rules of aristocrats,
I shouldn’t get drunk
even after a whole night’s drinking.
Zhu Xi already set out for Zhaodu
with his people.
Report.
What’s up?
Your Majesty,
everything is clear around Zhaodu.
No ambushing army is there.
Zhu Xi’s entourage was found
some tens of kilometers away,
but they had only
one hundred people or so.
They have arrived,
but no message
has been received from Pingting.
It seems
the previous messages from Pingting
are not reliable.
Zhu Xi has made preparations for it.
Don’t worry, Your Majesty.
Whatever trick Zhu Xi may have,
he has just
one hundred people or so.
It is not a big deal.
Yuan Yi,
what happened?
Zhu Xi is coming.
That quick?
But you just arrested
Marquis Shuo yesterday, right?
Fei Tian,
I will
arrange for the defense now.
You look worried.
The one I am going to marry
is the richest person in Suchuan.
Look at what I have
on me.
They are all gifts from him.
He can give my brother a hand
and guarantee a good life for me.
No other man
is a better husband than him for me.
So I must be the happiest girl
in the world.
How can I feel worried then?
What are you doing then?
I am happy.
After the jewelry is finished,
I will offer it
to Weisheng Yan as my dowry.
We are going to get married.
Don’t you feel happy for me?
A happy drink
isn’t taken this way.
Please tell me
how a happy drink should be taken.
Let me tell you.
A happy drink should be taken
when somebody is talking
and drinking with you.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Greetings, Minister Fei.
You finally thought of me.
What?
Are you going to kill me?
Not the right time.
Do you mean
you have some questions for me?
Whether I kill you or interrogate you,
just be sure
you won’t
suffer less pain.
Tell me,
what on earth does Zhu Xi plan to do?
Isn’t it clear enough
what Marquis Pingjiang wants to do?
He wants to kill Linglong.
Does Zhu Xi believe she is Goddess too?
Does it matter
if he believes or not?
Have you witnessed her power?
I have.
It is an invincible power.
Otherwise,
Fozhuan wouldn’t
have died for her.
What they say
about Minister Fei is true.
You don’t seem to be so ruthless.
Kill me!
Bracelet
Master.
No action.
It seems my worries are in vain.
Zhu Xi doesn’t plan on any action.
Then
Ms. Yin Zhuang is still in there?
I don’t know.
I have never seen you
like this.
Master.
Please remain calm and sober.
I suggest
you go in and have a look.
If I go in now,
my care for her will be too evident.
Master, you are kindhearted.
When a servant girl was lost last time,
you dispatched lots of people
in search of her.
Moreover,
she is your wife-to-be.
Don’t flatter me again.
Or just pack up and go back home.
Yes.
Then?
What to do then?
How can I continue
if you laugh that way?
Okay,
I won’t laugh any more.
Then,
Linglong was upset
hearing the words of that boy.
She hates to hear
bad words against her mother the most.
Guess what happened
after that?
What happened?
From then on,
she would pour liquors of Fire Tribe
into the fish pond of his family
at daybreak every day,
and his fish
would jump out of the pond crazily.
The boy had to
catch the fish jumping out of the pond
beside the pond every morning
without knowing the reason.
It is so lucky that Linglong
has such a father as you.
Tell me
something about your parents.
Just forget them.
It gets dark so early.
Is it time for you to go back now?
Do you plan to escape
from the wedding by hiding here?
How about you?
What are you escaping from
by hiding here?
I…
I am running away from fate
instead of a wedding.
I am not running away from fate here.
I have
very important things to do here.
Really?
I appreciate that.
Just allow me to be free for a night.
Okay.
Will you
escape with me?
No.
I mean
you don’t have to face a dilemma
if you don’t like the marriage.
You can choose to be single.
Weisheng Yan
isn’t a good guy anyway.
I don’t mean to be single.
No more pretending.
You don’t know me.
I really don’t understand.
Just think about it.
You are an aristocratic girl
and look so…
What?
I...
mean...
not
bad.
You racked up your mind
just for this word?
I mean
you don’t have to face a dilemma
if you don’t want to marry him.
You are the apple
of your brother’s eye.
If he knows you don’t want to marry,
he won’t allow it.
My brother?
My brother is really a powerful man,
isn’t he?
He can defeat anyone
in Suchuan
basically within three moves.
So he has always protected me
since my childhood.
But do you know
who can guard his dreams?
Anyone
who can be herself freely
must have someone
to protect her behind her.
I don’t want to always
hide behind my brother.
I hope to stand
in front of him and protect him
as he has done to me.
Must it be realized by marriage?
I can understand your sorrows.
By so doing,
you will not only
marry someone you don’t love,
but also lose the chance to love
who you really love in the future.
Lose the chance to love who I love?
I have a question for you.
Did you marry
someone who you love?
We didn’t care about it then.
Maybe I was too young to realize it.
Moreover,
there isn’t any girl like Jin’er
at Fire Tribe.
But
she really gave me
someone whom I love most.
You are lucky
if so.
Not everyone is so lucky
to have such a daughter
as Linglong.
You are an expert in comforting others.
Guard the jail carefully and
prevent intrusion of Zhu Xi’s people.
Aye.
Fei Tian,
I am coming to discuss with you.
Zhu Xi has chased me all the way
from Fire Tribe to Zhaodu.
He came here hurriedly and strangely
and it must be a well-prepared trip.
I don’t know
the purposes of his trip,
but we must take some actions.
You have come to the wrong place.
If you have a solution,
just talk to His Majesty
and Chief Priest.
You are right.
I came to you
because all people in Suchuan
know they will help me.
You said you admired Linglong
as she could
do anything she likes
when I was beside her.
Don’t you hope
to have such a person beside you?
It is not up to me.
I don’t mean
a family member.
Can Weisheng Yan
do this for you?
It is not my duty
to consider it.
Yin Zhuang…
Do I look
very lousy today?
One certainly looks very lousy
when she pretends to be happy
just for the happiness of others.
I am not the one you said.
The one who will marry Weisheng Yan
isn’t you either.
It is me
when the sun rises tomorrow.
Master,
how do you feel?
Why am I
so eager to kill someone?
But Marquis Pingjiang allows
the man from Fire Tribe to survive
as he is useful.
If Master is to blame…
No,
I have many ways
to deal with him.
I will do it right away.
Do you think
how worried a brother will feel
if his sister stays outside overnight?
I see.
I seem…
I seem to have drunk too much.
Impossible!
You haven’t drunk much.
Hey,
are you OK?
Wake up.
Why did you get drunk so easily.
Yin Zhuang!
Yin Zhuang?
♪Love is so transient♪
You can’t sleep here.
♪Lost girls♪
♪Are beyond rescue♪
It is not suitable.
♪Romance continues
in reincarnations♪
♪Who can read romance
of previous incarnation♪
Not suitable.
♪Poems laud love♪
Excuse me.
♪But it is rarely seen in life♪
♪I am reluctant to forget you♪
♪And keep looking for you♪
Hope his brother won’t see it.
♪One fades away easily♪
The liquor today...
♪Put on a glass armor against snows♪
♪Gain honors and wealth via study♪
♪My soul wanders in this incarnation♪
♪So easy and free♪
Girl.
Look.
My goodness!
I have stayed outside overnight.
My brother will go crazy.
Forget it.
Just let it be.
Huotu Xin,
wake up.
Girl.
Look.
Huotu Xin, wake up.
Sir, you’ve finished the bracelets?
Do you feel numb all over?
Let me help you.
Do you feel better?
Remember this acupuncture point.
Yin Zhuang’s Secret Skill.
Girl,
finished.
Wow, so beautiful!
Drop the act.
Sir,
I really feel
they look much more beautiful
than before.
It doesn’t matter for you to pretend
because you don’t know
their powers.
Sir,
how are these bracelets special?
She needs dowries.
I am sure
it is the best dowry
you can ever find in Suchuan.
Girl,
do you know
how miraculous
are the two crystal stones
you gave me?
It doesn’t matter if you don’t know,
because
nobody except me
can release their powers.
Just get straight to the point.
How are they special?
One is Yin and the other is Yang.
Just touch them slightly and
the Yang bracelet
will control water and fire.
Even an ordinary person
can become a great master
after wearing it.
You touched them just now,
but nothing has happened.
Moron.
I haven’t worn it.
A man wears the Yang bracelet
and a woman wears the Yin bracelet.
They will be empowered
only upon a touch.
How about the Yin bracelet?
Isn’t it empowered?
No.
It is my dowry.
Why isn’t the Yin bracelet empowered?
Silly girl.
The Yin bracelet can protect you.
So long as you wear it,
when you and your lover
are together,
together,
nobody
can harm you.
Who can harm her?
She is going to marry
someone who is rich
and tricky.
Her brother is a Kungfu master.
Sir, you don’t know her brother.
Her brother…
You have stayed outside overnight.
Your brother…
Sir,
what other powerful treasures
and weapons do you have?
Show them to me now.
Hurry up.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Yin Zhuang.
Crap!
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪