Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 11
What are you thinking about?
I’m thinking
what it’d look like if it’s lighted up.
Before I found you,
I had imagined that
so many times.
What about after?
After?
When it’s lighted up,
posterity will remember
the moment forever.
Suchuan has gone through
Fall of God for 500 years.
I will break it.
After that, Suchuan
will be revived in our hands.
It sounds you’re so confident.
Aren’t you afraid I can’t do that?
Are you worried?
Surely I do.
Now there’re many mysteries.
All clues are pointing to Chief Priest.
But whatever I do,
I can’t make him talk.
Dukes are coming soon.
Of course I’m worried.
How about I marry you?
Are you sick?
How can you say that?
If I marry you,
you’ll be the empress of Suchuan.
Whether you can do it or not,
no one dares to give you a hard time.
In that case,
the officials
don’t have to
choose ladies for me each year.
Are you…?
Are you using me as a shield?
Goddess and empress.
Isn’t it remarkable?
There may be
no one to object me.
My father.
That is to say,
you agree with me?
I’m leaving.
This is mine then.
Why
do you have it?
The servant girl told me
you are embroidering a handkerchief
for me.
I’ve waited for a long time,
but I didn’t see you giving it to me.
I’m afraid you can’t finish it,
and almost sent some men to help you.
No need.
I’m capable…
Yes, you are.
Give it to me.
Your embroidering skills
are good indeed.
But
is it you?
It looks exactly like you.
It’s your Yuan family’s badge.
When I finish,
you’ll know how marvelous it is.
Give it to me.
I don’t care about how marvelous it is.
What matters is that you gave it to me.
Who said that it’s for you?
You just robbed it.
Is it not for me?
Yeah.
Then
are you embroidering my family badge
for yourself?
I…!
Sir, you’re awake.
Great.
Do you feel better?
I prepared porridge
and some dishes for you.
It’s a pity that you can’t drink now.
What’s wrong?
Are you still angry with me?
I’ve apologized to Wu Yuan.
She’s forgiven me.
Leave.
Go.
You can leave.
I can’t.
I promised Wu Yuan
to take good care of you.
I’m sorry for you, too.
I’ve made my apologies to you.
If you still feel angry,
and want to scold me,
you can eat some porridge.
As the old saying goes,
you can scold someone badly only
with your stomach full.
Is it right?
However,
to be honest,
it’s
also your granddaughter’s fault.
My granddaughter’s fault?
What’s her fault?
She saved you and took you in.
Do you know she works for Zhu Xi?
Do you know how bad Zhu Xi is?
If you worry about your granddaughter,
you should control her more often.
Pooh!
Do…
Do you…
Do you know...
Alright. Alright.
what she has been through?
-Easy. Easy.
-Do you know that?
Easy.
Tell me then.
What has she been through?
Forget it. Forget it.
It’s none of your business.
Tell me.
Is it that
she lost her parents since little?
So did Linglong.
Her mother was gone when she’s born.
Kids like them
are hard to control.
I also spend all my efforts
to raise her up.
When she’s little, she’s also wayward.
But the more she’s like that,
the more we parents need to control her.
Did I
say something that irritates you?
But I was telling the truth.
It’s the parents’ fault
if their kids go wrong.
Alright.
Well.
Let me tell you about
my granddaughter,
Wu Yuan.
Actually she
is not my biological granddaughter.
When she’s little,
her parents sold her to others
for ten gold coins.
It’s worth the same as your life.
She was sold to
a brothel.
Do you know what’s a brothel?
Don’t your Fire Tribe have one?
No.
Here
it has
all forms of torture that
you can imagine.
It’s even much crueler
than you can imagine.
But Wu Yuan was tough.
Soon
a plague broke out in Pingting.
All men in the brothel were dead.
Only she survived.
Just after she got out from dead bodies,
she went to Pingting,
the human purgatory.
The Earth Fire is horrible.
But the evils in people’s hearts
are more horrifying.
In Pingting,
secret deals are around all city.
Sometimes,
to deceive the public,
they would hire kids
to do the most horrible business.
You dare to rob me?
Here!
You want to die?
Go!
Go away!
Catch him!
Take the stuff.
Stop!
Go!
Give me my bag!
You’ve met Pingting’s kids.
To survive,
they can do everything.
Even an adult
finds it hard to survive here.
But she made it.
Did she…
Did she kill people
at that little age?
How come
she became your granddaughter?
There was a period that
Weisheng Yan wanted to monopolize
the entire forging industry in Pingting.
Many blacksmiths didn’t agree to join in
and died a violent death.
Though they were so cautious,
you could still
hear men dying.
That day she showed up in my shop
with her sick body,
looking like a mess.
If she were not seriously ill that day,
perhaps
I would have been dead
under her innocent eyes.
You’re awake.
Alright.
Let’s take the medicine.
I’ll go to take a bowl.
What happened later?
After a few days,
she showed up again.
Here.
Take it.
Drink.
It’s bitter in the first sip.
But it will taste better.
Okay.
Look how dirty you are.
Kid.
Wait a minute.
Here.
In that period,
I can see many kids walking around.
But the shop
was quite peaceful.
Weisheng Yan seems to have forgotten me.
And Wu Yuan also seems
to have forgotten me.
Later on,
I saw her hiding in the street corner,
but wasn’t willing to come out.
I brought her back to the shop.
You’ve finished changing?
Let me have a look.
It’s quite fit.
You must be hungry.
I’ll get you something to eat.
After that,
I hadn’t seen her for long.
But one day,
she appeared
suddenly before me.
Ten gold coins.
Can I buy you?
It turned out that she still remembered
because of ten gold coins, she separated
with her families when she’s little.
She thought that
only if she had ten gold coins,
can she buy her families back.
She was taking me as her family.
You made up the story, right?
I…
I wish it’s just a story I made up.
But…
For…
For Wu Yuan,
her story
is far less than her experience!
Her…
Her experience!
Sir.
I’m sorry.
Sorry.
Lord,
Marquis has been waiting for you.
Please.
Your Highness,
all are ready.
Well done.
Your Highness,
I always think
he’ll be a trouble.
He is a trouble indeed.
A big trouble that we send to Zhaodu.
Father.
Greetings to Father.
How’s your lesson going?
I’ve learned to the second volume
of the books on the art of war.
This is the thing that
you asked your mother for.
Thank you, Fath…
Keep it in mind.
A man can strive for what he wants
with blood
but never with tears.
You understand?
Then I can strive for it with your love.
I have so many children.
But I can’t do anything with him.
He’s smart and talented.
People will surely like him.
The first gift for Zhaodu.
I think they must have received it.
Hope Goddess likes it.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Greetings to Your Majesty.
You may rise.
Thanks, Your Majesty.
I’ve never
seen some of you.
It must be your first time to Zhaodu.
Your Majesty.
My legs have been painful these years.
So I haven’t come to court for long.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
Marquis De,
a few days ago,
I saw you were drunk
in Marquis Pingjiang’s banquet.
You insisted on dancing
with a singer.
Why are your legs painful now?
Did you sprain your legs because
you danced too much that day?
Everyone,
we’re here in Zhaodu
to meet the Goddess, aren’t we?
It’s no need
to use the highfalutin excuses
to fool His Majesty.
After a long time,
Marquis Shuo’s comments
are still so trenchant.
Forgive me.
Did I say something wrong?
I’ve been living leisurely
and carefreely these years.
I beg Your Majesty’s pardon.
You haven’t come to Zhaodu for long.
It’s common that you forget the rules.
No worry.
You have plenty of time
to learn it slowly.
You may rise.
Thanks, Your Majesty.
It’s Suchuan’s luck
to see you living in peace.
Marquis Shuo.
I remember
you’ve finished the building that you
built for Zhu Xi’s banquets.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
If it’s called Flowers Pavilion,
it sounds so girlish.
How about
changing to Talents Pavilion?
What do you think, Marquis Shuo?
Thanks for the name, Your Majesty.
But
why doesn’t Marquis Pingjiang come?
Though Your Majesty lives in the palace,
you know what happens elsewhere.
I’m so impressed.
As you can know Flowers Pavilion,
the name that I mentioned
only once to servants,
why do you bother asking us
why Marquis Pingjiang doesn’t come?
Marquis Shuo,
don’t be so rude.
His Majesty doesn’t scold me.
What’s your rush?
Speaking of politeness,
I am more thoughtful than you are.
Your Majesty,
I brought a gift to Goddess this time.
What is this?
Goddess comes back
and the world is celebrating it.
However,
Goddess was born
in the body of a guilty girl
of Fire Tribe.
I’m so worrying
that the guilty girl of Fire Tribe
would sully Goddess.
I
spent a lot of money on
the bell that can remove evils
to Goddess.
What did you say?
What
guilty girl of Fire Tribe?
Marquis Shuo,
stop your nonsense.
What are you talking about?
Your Majesty,
doesn’t Goddess know
her ancestor’s guilt?
It’s in the history.
It’s not worth mentioning.
He can go on.
Goddess
allows no lies.
Goddess, you don’t know.
The Earth Fire in Flame Chilling Wall
was set on by the Fire Tribe’s ancestor
for their selfish desires.
Your tribesmen have been guarding it.
It’s not an honor
but an atonement for the ancestors.
And
the one set on the Earth Fire
was the former emperor of Fire Tribe,
Huotu Ke.
People with the name Huotu
are unforgivable.
Goddess,
as long as you put on my bell,
the guilt the ancestor committed
has nothing to do with you then.
Bring you stuff
and get out of here.
Goddess,
we are caring about you.
If you are guilty,
it may affect
your reputation.
There is no such a thing.
Goddess
will not be affected
by this trifle.
If Goddess is
indeed so powerful as the legend says,
today
why don’t you just show us?
-Yes.
Do you agree?
Yes.
I
will send out my order when I’m back.
The entire city
shall eulogize Goddess’ work
and believe in Goddess.
If anyone
dares to doubt Goddess,
he shall be sentenced to death.
If Goddess blesses anyone
depends on Goddess will.
Even His Majesty
has to pray for that.
How dare you ask Goddess
to prove herself?
Chief Priest is right.
If we want Goddess’ blessing,
we must pray sincerely.
I
pray for Goddess’ blessing.
I pray for Goddess’ blessing.
Your blessing will be brought
back to our vassal states
and spread to all.
Enough!
You talk sheer nonsense,
offend your superiors,
incite others
and slander Goddess.
With any of them,
I can order to kill you.
Someone!
Take him away!
Your Majesty,
Marquis Shuo behaves impolitely,
but it’s not such a big crime.
Please
reconsider it, Your Majesty.
Please reconsider it!
So,
you all think
offending Goddess
and damaging her reputation
are not such a big crime?
Take them all away then!
Keep a close watch on them!
Without my orders,
no one can step out of Zhaodu.
Your Majesty,
we are here to pay our respects.
All know it.
If we can’t go back,
who dares
to come to Zhaodu again?
Can’t go back?
It’s you
who worship Goddess so much
after seeing her.
You’re willing to pray in Tianqi.
I won’t kill you.
The Fall of God will be ended soon.
Goddess is coming back.
This is just the beginning.
I will save you
to see the light in Ritual of Eternity.
But if you
dare to offend Goddess again,
I can’t protect you more
if Goddess punishes you.
Take them away!
Um…
Linglong!
Keep a close watch on Tianqi.
If someone steps out of the court,
kill him!
Fire Tribe.
Where are the books of Fire Tribe?
Fire…
Fire Tribe.
Were they lying to me?
Were they making it up to question me?
Weren’t they?
You said you will not lie to me.
Linglong.
Answer me!
Don’t just call my name!
Where are the books of Fire Tribe?
Calm down.
Give it to me.
You look
just like what they want you to look.
Jinshi City used to be
the most prosperous place in Suchuan.
It’s the Fire Tribe’s ancestors’ credit.
Yeah.
No one
can be good at mining
and quenching skills
as your ancestors did.
The Founding Father Huotu Ke
was born for it.
So many people gave all out
only for getting a stone he quenched.
Under his leading,
Jinshi City had attracted
numerous people.
He’s the first man
with his name written on Glory Rock.
But obsession
is the root of disasters.
To quench the legendary stone of life,
Spirit Combing Stone,
Huotu Ke made a reckless move.
He mined in the deep center
of the earth,
and used Earth Fire’s power.
And Earth Fire
destroyed everything.
No.
Not everything.
It destroyed
the civilization that Huotu Ke built,
not Huotu Ke himself.
Before him,
Suchuan had never had
such a prosperous Jinshi City.
After him,
no one was able to build
such a remarkable Flame Chilling Wall.
But my surname is Huotu.
If Huotu Ke is guilty,
how come my father doesn’t know?
My tribesmen have been guarding
the Wall for generations.
How come they don’t know?
When the Wall locked the Earth Fire,
Huotu Ke alone
went to Zhaodu to ask for punishment.
He was willing to take the blame
and accept curses in all ages,
but only asked for hiding the truth
so that the decedents of Fire Tribe
can safeguard the glory
of protecting the Flame Chilling Wall.
The Earth Fire
was just Huotu Ke’s guilt.
But it’s the entire Fire Tribe’s glory.
That day,
in the study,
you asked if I have anything to ask you.
Were you trying to tell me
about the Earth Fire Judgement?
So
this is the origin of Earth Fire.
Indeed.
It’s none of my business.
It’s someone else’s fault.
What does it have to do with me?
If my father is here,
he must say so.
When I was little,
Mountain Team came to him one day.
They wanted to put out
a center of the fire.
But they were short-handed.
Since I was born,
my father stepped away
from the Earth Fire
as far as he can.
My father didn’t agree
and said their fire map was wrong.
He persuaded them not to go.
In that mission,
two tribesmen were dead.
The Earth Fire got
a small hill collapsed.
The bodies were not found.
Their fire map was really wrong.
But the tribesmen scolded and sneered
my father for his selfishness
and weakness.
I can still remember
that day the sun was big,
and it was so hot.
The women who tried to get into my home
were wearing sweat or tears.
My father was standing at the door.
I felt he’s extraordinarily tall.
His cries were like
falling from the sky.
Alright!
None of my business!
It’s not my fault.
What does it have to do with me?
Huotu Xin.
Save them, please.
-Please save them.
-Huotu Xin.
After that,
my father left me with three-day food
and went out with his Fire Spear.
Three days later at night,
my father brought the two bodies
back to the village.
Huotu Xin.
My father said
they had promised to each other.
If whoever died in the Wall,
the one alive
should bring their bodies back.
He also said...
What they did has nothing to do with me.
But what I said
was real.
Those might be the most heroic words
I’ve ever heard.
My ambition
is to put out the Earth Fire.
As to who set on it,
it has nothing to do with me.
You’re indeed Huotu Xin’s daughter.
Yeah.
Huotu Xin’s daughter
will not be scared away
by their words.
Sir.
The stone monkey outside the third
gate tower in the southern city.
Do you know it?
Do you know how to get there?
What?
You want to go out?
Wu Yuan said you can’t go out.
A man was killed
by Zhu Xi
because of saving me.
His daughter is seriously ill.
I need to go to visit her.
A little girl in Pingting
fooled you easily.
Did you forget?
Actually Pingting is not that horrible.
Those people that I’ve met in the way,
no matter they’ve helped me or hurt me,
like
Wu Yuan,
you,
and Jia,
or even the little girl
who used me to get reward money,
and no matter they’re good or evil,
all are doing it
for the person they love.
When we were in the Fire Tribe,
they said Linglong and Jin’er
were monsters.
And now we came to Zhaodu.
Linglong was worshiped as Goddess
and became the hope of Suchuan.
Sometimes,
is it so distinct from good and evil?
You all told me
not to trust anyone in Pingting.
But I think
people
are trusting me here.
Sir.
If Linglong can cure your disease,
I will definitely help you.
I’m not sick.
You’re the one who’s sick.
Fine.
I am.
Then I’m leaving.
Wait.
I’ve told you so much.
Do you still want to stop me?
The stone monkey outside the third
gate tower in southern city.
Do you know how to get there?
Xiao.
What’re you doing?
Here you are.
No.
This treasure has been passed by
for generations in the Yin family.
It is
only passed to the eldest legal son.
It’s for you
and my future sister-in-law.
When I was little,
Father didn’t even allow me
to have a look.
What do you give me for?
As a dowry.
I don’t really need it.
Look at all the rare treasures
in Weisheng’s family.
Weisheng Yan
also gave me many of them.
In recent days,
what I put on
and wear
almost weighs me down.
Even if I change
three different clothes a day,
I figure that
I can’t try all of them in my life.
But this is all
I can give you.
Alright.
This is our ancestors’
blessing.
It can protect the Yins
for generations and generations.
I heard from Mother that
there is a pair
of Guardian Stones
to bless lovers
for a lifelong
companionship.
Now
it’s passed to you.
But Xiao,
you are wrong.
This is not what you can only give me.
You are the guardian of my life.
Silly girl.
Open it.
Xiao, did you take it wrong?
No way.
I’ve never seen it before.
But
if they’re the family heirloom,
it would be so ugly.
Yin Zhuang,
these are the heirloom.
I see.
Get out!
Who are you?
Let go of me!
Father!
What are you scared of?
Let go of me!
Your father will not come back.
From now on,
you’ll be all alone.
Who can take care of you?
I
will take you to a wonderful place.
The men there
will love you much more.
No!
Let go of me!
This is for you.
The men there
will give you more money.
I’m trying to be nice to you.
I told you.
Your father’s head has been
hanging on the city wall for days.
No one in Pingting dares to
care about your life.
Why does she look like this?
With this horrible face,
who will pay for her?
No wonder Jia had hidden her for years.
Jia’s daughter
was so beautiful before.
Why would she turn into this look?
Only if she can give birth,
people will buy her.
This look…
Go away.
I dropped this.
Give me that.
I heard that
you’re going to sell her to a brothel?
What brothel?
It’s Fuyan House.
You must have gone there.
Never.
That makes sense.
If a handsome man like you
ever came,
I will definitely remember.
What?
You’re interested in the girl?
Let me told you.
She’s still a
virgin…
You bastard.
You dare to take our Fuyan House’s girl?
Beat him to death!
Where’s the money?
No spitting!
Get away!
Damn it.
What the heck is it?
Stop talking.
Her father has gone.
She will be ours sooner or later.
We can sell her to a demote place
and still benefit from it.
Who are you?
What do you want?
Are you a team with the man?
He?
How can I be a team with him?
He’s such a busybody.
How come
there is such a busybody
in Pingting?
You’ve never known that, right?
Me neither.
Whoever sells women
shall die.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪