Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 22
See you, sir.
I’m here.
You said you have a way
to help Feixian out.
What is it?
It’s simple.
But it depends on
how intimate you are
with her.
To save her, I’ll do anything.
Don’t speak so rashly.
You may not dare to do it.
If it can save her,
I’ll do whatever you ask.
Good.
The only evidence to save Shi Feixian
is the copy your brother used
to imitate Count Cheng’an’s handwriting.
How’s it? You dare to do it?
One is your brother,
the other is your bosom friend.
Whom you will choose
is difficult to decide.
But you have to act quickly.
Shi Feixian will be condemned by
the Court of Judicial Review tomorrow.
Well...
You are the only one in my heart.
See you at the west temple.
Brother.
What are you doing here, Your Grace?
Feixian,
she comes to help you out.
I’m afraid she’s happy to
see me here.
How could she help me?
Shi Feixian,
I’m sorry I wronged you that day.
I apologize.
I’m in the prison now.
What’s the use of apology?
I come here today
to ask you to be
my witness.
Find the one who forged the letter
and prove your innocence.
Forged?
It’s obviously true.
How could it be forged?
Feixian, don’t cheat yourself anymore.
It’s a critical time for you.
I don’t.
Since I worked hard in disaster relief,
His Grace began to admire me,
so he wrote to me,
asking me out and confessing his love.
Feixian,
Rong Xia loves Princess Ban,
and they’ve been engaged.
The letter is forged.
Brother.
Are you asking me to ruin
all my dignity
and my beautiful dream
in front of everyone?
Shi Feixian,
I can’t control Count Cheng’an’s mind,
and I’ll never give up my love
to you.
But,
the real one who did it
is unapprehended.
You and Count Cheng’an
shouldn’t be trapped here.
So, I’m asking you
to help me find out the truth.
When you clarified everything
in the court that day,
I thought you are not
the one who only
pretends to be weak and poor.
Why? Are you afraid?
It seems I overrated you.
Who tells you I’m afraid?
If you, Ban Hua,
can let go of your grudges
and beg me for Count Cheng’an,
how can I lose to you?
That’s it.
You are really the woman
I hate most in the whole country.
After raining, I passed by my friend’s
village and saw a beautiful lady.
This is written by Count Cheng’an?
This is a letter forged by Xie Chongjin.
Xie Chongjin?
I have no grudges against him.
Why should he frame me?
Xie Chongjin tried every means,
thinking he mastered everyone’s mind,
but he never expected
I will cooperate with you
one day.
Feixian,
if you’d like to be the witness,
we can find out the truth.
In the court trial tomorrow,
we can bring Xie Chongjin to justice.
Jin,
how’s your sister Feixian?
The prison is cold and hard.
She lost a lot of weight.
Grandpa, don’t worry too much.
Maybe she’ll be back
in a few days.
It has been a bad time for the Shis.
Besides the natural disaster,
we don’t get along well with the Bans.
Suyue makes His Majesty unhappy
because of your sister.
Suyue?
What’s wrong with her?
Don’t worry about her.
It’s more urgent to
solve Feixian’s matter.
Grandpa, don’t worry.
I’ve joined hands with Princess Ban.
In the court trial tomorrow,
we’ll bring Xie Chongjin to justice.
Xie Chongjin?
Isn’t he the subordinate of Prince Luo?
We’ve got all the evidence.
No matter whose subordinate he is,
he’ll be punished by Daye’s law.
Good.
If so, I’ll have to do something.
Jin.
Go get my official robe for me.
Are you going to enter the palace?
Yes.
If you want to arrest Xie Chongjin,
the Xies won’t let this happen.
I’ll report to His Majesty
as soon as possible,
so as not to hurt you and Feixian.
Jin,
you’re all my beloved.
How could I see you suffer?
But without evidence,
how could His Majesty believe me?
Grandpa.
Feixian.
Grandpa, you’re here finally.
My brother must tell you everything.
I didn’t intend to stir the situation
and shame our family.
When I’m cleared tomorrow,
I’ll do more
to earn honor for our family.
Grandpa, I’ll get justice.
Why aren’t you happy?
Did you just come back from the palace?
What happened? Tell me!
His Majesty
will dethrone your sister
as crown princess.
It’s impossible.
My sister and Crown Prince
love each other so much.
His Majesty can’t...
Everything is possible for His Majesty.
Your sister offended the Bans
to help you out.
His Majesty said
she interfered with the court affairs,
so he wants to revoke her status.
Now, our family is doomed.
We won’t.
I’ll go find Ban Hua,
and ask her to plead for us.
I can go to Prince Luo, too.
He surely will help me.
Feixian.
What’s your relation with Prince Luo?
Grandpa.
I’m clear with him.
We don’t have any relation.
But His Majesty said
you induced Prince Luo with your pretty
and made him make such a mistake.
To save the face of the royal family,
he...
He’ll kill you.
His...
His Majesty will kill me?
Impossible.
Feixian, you know I love you the most.
Even I have to give up my official post,
and your sister’s status of
crown princess.
I will save your life.
But
even if I give up my official post
and your sister’s status,
it’s useless to His Majesty.
Grandpa.
There is only one way now.
What?
You admit that
it’s you who assassinated Duke Ban.
Only by this, you can save yourself.
Only by this, you can keep your life,
and save our family.
Are you coming here
to tell me this?
I’ll go plead His Majesty.
He will be lenient
and send you to Liangzhou.
No, Xizhou.
Don’t bother.
Even if I’m out of prison,
I’ll be despised by others.
Feixian.
Only by expelling me,
can the Shis
keep the previous glory.
Only if I keep my position,
and your sister keeps hers,
can we save you.
But I didn’t do that.
You’re my grandpa.
Shouldn’t you seek justice for me?
Like what Duke Jingting did.
No matter whom bullied his daughter,
he’d seek justice for her,
spoil her, and protect her
from a little bit of harm.
Isn’t that what a family should do?
What kind of people are they?
He’s a hooligan.
We’re officials for generations.
Can they compare with us?
No, they can’t.
Since I was born,
I’m just a commodity for sale,
but Ban Hua is a real person.
I know what to do.
Grandpa, you can go now.
Shi Feixian admitted her crime,
and is expelled to Xizhou
Miss Shi, think it over.
If you press your fingerprint,
the expel will never be revoked.
End: Shi Feixian admitted her crime,
and is expelled to Xizhou
Thank you for reminding me.
We didn’t teach her well,
so she made such a big mistake.
She should be punished for the crime.
Stop it!
Grandpa, you...
Shi Feixian, it’s not you,
why did you admit it?
Didn’t we reach an agreement?
Your Grace,
the one who assassinated your father
is me.
I don’t know what dirty things
you did in the dark.
With me here today,
I will never watch you treat
Shi Feixian unjustly.
Shi Jin, evidence.
Show it to Mr. Liu.
I...
Where’s it?
I’d like to thank you, Your Grace.
But everything is done.
Please go back now.
It’s you!
You took the evidence, right?
You know it’s not her, right?
Shi Feixian is your own granddaughter.
Why did you force her to admit it?
Is it because the criminal
is Xie Chongjin?
and Prince Luo?
Minister Shi,
you’re selling your grandchild
for success.
Shut up!
It doesn’t matter if you slander me.
But how can you speak ill
of the royal family?
I never expect
you’re such a kind of person.
I’m so disappointed in you.
Your Grace, I...
Now that you won’t find it out,
I’ll do it.
I don’t care he’s an official
or a prince,
I believe there is justice in the world.
Your Grace,
do you mean His Majesty is unjust?
Minister Shi, you’re wrong.
Her Grace means
there is justice in everyone’s heart.
But what you have done today
is so impressive.
Her Grace won’t forget.
I won’t forget either.
It’s easy for me to help you out.
Your Grace, don’t thank me.
Hua!
With Mr. Shi’s personality,
if it’s not His Majesty’s intention,
he won’t do this.
This is not the capital where I grew up.
Shi Feixian is not wrong,
but she’s expelled.
Hua, if they don’t find it out,
you and I
still can do it.
Your Grace,
I can see the intrigues behind it,
but I don’t want to behave like that.
But
maybe I’m wrong.
Hua, you’re not wrong.
I want to go home.
Fine. I’ll send you home.
I want to stay alone and think it over.
Wude Mansion
Prince Luo, why are you in such a hurry?
Where are you going?
It’s just in time. Where is my father?
His Majesty has an order.
He asked me to bring you a message.
What did Father say?
His Majesty asked you not to go out.
It’s impossible.
I want to see Father. Feixian...
Prince Luo, His Majesty and Her Highness
have known what you want to say.
Please go back to your mansion.
Don’t disappoint His Majesty
and Her Highness.
Come on. See Prince Luo off.
Please!
After some thought, I decided to
abolish the system of two ministers.
Shi Chonghai will be
the only Prime Minister
and lead all the officials.
Shi Jin is promoted to
Commander of Imperial Guards
to safeguard the security of the palace.
The end.
Your Majesty, the Shis has a daughter
who’s expelled.
How could he be Prime Minister?
Do you have any objections?
I...
I dare not. I dare not.
But Duke Ban has.
Look,
he’s so angry that his head swells.
Your Majesty, my head was hit by others.
If there’s an objection,
it’s from Count Xie.
Look, his face is red.
Is my face red?
Of course.
That’s because you made me angry.
You can say what you want.
Don’t feel ashamed.
You’re making things worse.
I find you are...
-Enough!
-No one can do it.
Do you have anything else to report?
Dismiss.
Dismiss!
See you, Your Majesty.
Commander Shi, you...
I want to see His Majesty,
and ask His Majesty
to take back his order.
My sister is innocent.
His Majesty is resting at the harem.
It’s useless for you to kneel here.
Minister, you come just in time.
Mr. Shi is so stubborn.
If he annoys His Majesty,
I’m afraid
he’ll be charged with insurrection.
Come on, stand up!
Do you hear me? Stand up!
How dare you not attend the meeting
and come here to force His Majesty?
What on earth do you want?
Right is right and wrong is wrong.
Even His Majesty is angry,
I will take the responsibility alone,
and not get the Shis involved.
Absurd!
Who do you think you are?
If you are not from the Shis,
you should be on the battlefield
and live a risky life.
How could you become like this?
You are the imperial commander now,
the third highest position.
I’d rather His Majesty revoke his order
and send me to the borderline
to return Feixian’s innocence.
You... Foolish!
Do you want to see
all our family members being killed
because of this?
Wait!
Feixian.
What are you doing here?
Feixian, sorry to see you suffering.
I end like this.
Is your family satisfied?
Feixian, you misunderstood me.
To save you...
I don’t have a friend like you.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Courier
Let’s go.
I prepared these for you.
You may need it on the way.
I never expected
the only one to see me off
is Your Grace.
I’m sorry.
You did nothing wrong.
You needn’t apologize.
Although I’m in a prison van,
I’m not a prisoner.
No matter where I live,
I am still
that Shi Feixian who’s unapproachable.
The title of the noblest lady in Daye
belongs to you now.
I hope you can do as you wish as always.
Don’t waste this title.
I won’t lose to you.
I won’t lose to anyone.
Your Grace, before I go,
I’d like to ask you a question.
Over the past years,
have you ever
had a feeling for me?
In my heart,
I only love Hua from the beginning.
How am I worse than Her Grace?
You are good,
but it has nothing to do with me.
How I hope
that letter was written by you.
Time is up! Let’s go!
Yes!
Rong Xia,
why should a girl
sacrifice for her family?
She’s innocent,
but is sent to Xizhou.
Hua.
You have done a lot.
I’ll ask others
to protect Shi Feixian on the way.
But I won’t let
Jiang Luo go for this.
With your own power,
how could you fight against a prince?
I’ve never been alone.
Jin!
I’ve told you
the whole story.
What are you going to do?
Feixian is expelled today.
As her brother,
I can’t let her
leave alone.
What can you do by yourself?
His Majesty has decided
to put a lid on the matter.
You still want to change it?
When will you let it go?
Do you think the lives of
all the family members
are less important than your sister?
Grandpa, don’t cheat yourself.
You gave up Feixian not for
the lives of the family members,
but for the high position.
Young Master,
you misunderstand him.
None of your business!
Stop!
If you insist on doing so,
you can go after
you kill me.
Zhang, please read this letter carefully
Without my good writing skills,
Prince Luo won’t have today’s success!
Brother!
Please find a way to save Feixian.
I tried so hard to send her away.
Why should I save her?
If she comes back,
you may lose your position
as the crown princess.
I don’t care whether
I can be the crown princess or not.
But Feixian is innocent.
Innocent?
Wanyu, there are many innocent people.
If we want a higher position,
someone must be sacrificed.
What I did
is for your good,
and for the family’s good.
You liar!
You did it just for yourself.
Since you arranged my marriage
with Prince Luo,
I’m just a pawn to you,
or a bird you raised.
I am a joke.
I am a joke in the eyes of
all the people in the capital.
Fine.
Tell me then,
what on earth do you want?
I want Feixian to come back.
She’s the only one who cares about me.
Wanyu!
Young Master.
Where are we going at such a late time?
Hua doesn’t want to stop here.
I have to help her seek justice.
So I decide to ask Xie Chongjin.
Young Master,
are you as crazy as Her Grace?
How can Xie Chongjin tell you the truth?
I’m afraid
he won’t see you at such time.
So I ask you to come with me.
Young Master.
Wanyu!
Wanyu, you can’t be so self-willed.
Wanyu, time to go back to Wude Palace.
It’s so late!
Why doesn’t Xie Chongjin come?!
Is it that
His Majesty knew our plan
and arrested Xie Chongjin?
Someone! Someone!
Someone, come!
How could she run in such a hurry?
If not that I have to use your family...
Right, Xie Chongjin...
Ban Hua, why do you come to my mansion?
What do you want?
Nothing.
I just want to have a talk with you.
I have nothing to talk with you.
Go out now!
Without Xie Chongjin,
you look so anxious!
Ban Hua, what will you do to me?
Ban Hua! Ban Hua!
You dare to act wildly in my mansion,
my father won’t forgive you!
Will His Majesty see you?
I heard that
you’re ordered to be grounded.
So what?
I am His Majesty’s own son.
When His Majesty sees me...
How could you know
you can see His Majesty again?
Ban...Ban Hua!
If you kill me,
all your family members will be killed.
Don’t worry. I won’t kill you.
I come here today
to make a deal with you.
I’ll never surrender to a threat,
or make a deal with others.
It seems you don’t care about
Shi Feixian’s life.
What do you mean?
What did do to her?
I never expected that
you love Shi Feixian so much.
Ban Hua,
if you don’t make yourself clear today,
I won’t let you leave here.
I don’t care whether I can leave or not.
But the killers to kill Shi Feixian
are on the way.
Don’t you worry?
How dare you!
If you hurt Shi Feixian a little bit,
I’ll kill you!
Don’t be so anxious! It’s not me.
I don’t have such grudges against her.
But
don’t you always think you’re clever?
Why are you fooled so much
by your counselor?
Nonsense!
How could Xie Chongjin treat her...
Xie Wanyu will marry you.
But everyone knows
you only love Shi Feixian.
Cousin, think it over.
Xie Chongjin follows you,
but he has no position or guarantee.
Although his sister married you,
Shi Feixian is the only one you love.
What will he get?
Now Shi Feixian is on the way to Xizhou,
it’s a good opportunity to kill her.
In the whole country,
who is more eager than Young Master Xie
to kill Shi Feixian?
I know Xie Chongjin better than you.
I won’t fall into your traps.
Really?
It seems that it is you
who ordered others to frame Shi Feixian
for killing my dad.
But
don’t worry too much.
I, Ban Hua,
won’t stand by
and watch Shi Feixian get killed.
I’ve arranged secret protectors for her.
Hua, where is Shi Feixian now?
I won’t tell you.
Do you believe I’ll kill you now?
If so, you’ll never see her.
Ban Hua,
tell me, what are your conditions?
You’re really clever.
You understand me so fast.
I only have a few conditions.
First,
don’t touch the people of my family.
Second,
stop coveting the throne.
Third,
from now on,
greet me when you see me.
Impossible!
No hurry. Another one.
What’s this?
Repentance letter for hitting my dad.
Sign it.
It means you apologize for your crime.
Why it says I’m brutal, cold-blooded
and worse than pigs or dogs?
Ban Hua, don’t go too far!
Will you sign it or not?
No! In your dream!
I was born as a noble!
How could I lower my head
to apologize to you?
Do you think I like your apology?
If you don’t sign it,
I’ll take it as you deny your crime.
If you deny it,
Shi Feixian couldn’t clear her name.
If she couldn’t, who can save her?
Just think about it.
Alright,
I’ll lower my head this time.
But Ban Hua, remember it,
I’m not afraid of you.
I’m just doing it for Shi Feixian.
It’s out of thin air. I won’t admit it.
Jiang Luo
That’s right.
I am so sorry
for taking you here like this.
Kidnap me.
Haven’t you thought
about the consequence?
Anyone else
may report this to Prince Luo,
but you won’t.
You are a smart person.
You’re good at reading other’s minds.
So am I.
You imitated my handwriting at first,
and led Miss Shi to the trap.
Then you hired an assassin
to murder Duke Jingting,
provoking the conflict
between the Shis and the Bans,
and involving me in it.
But what will
Prince Luo and the Xies
get from this?
I thought for a long time.
Finally, I figured it out.
You are just betting that
Prince Luo will ascend to the throne.
To get the position of Empress
for the Xies,
you must kill Shi Feixian first.
You murdered Duke Jingting
because you know the crown prince will
plead for his beloved
and annoy His Majesty.
So that you can strike
crown prince’s position.
I’ve said that long ago
you’re my doomed rival.
You are cautious enough
and even take a further step.
Maybe you haven’t told Prince Luo
the killers you sent to kill Shi Feixian
are on the way.
What do you mean by this?
I don’t understand.
Miss Shi is a thousand miles away.
Even she has an accident.
What’s the matter with me?
I’m so ashamed that
I can’t imitate others’ handwriting
as good as you.
I’ve never expected
Count Cheng’an
may break into other’s house
to steal things.
If Jiang Luo knows
that letter was written by you,
Xie Wanyu’s title of the crown princess,
no,
all the Xies may disappear.
Count Cheng’an,
if you really want to do this,
you won’t meet me here.
Except the murder of Duke Jingting,
you must have some other things to ask.
Please tell me directly.
Thank you.
The day before yesterday,
our butler died from a cart accident.
It’s really strange,
but it must have a reason.
Is the killer from your Fude House?
Fude House makes deals by rules.
We just take money
and do what we’re asked,
without asking reasons.
I’m afraid I can’t help you with this.
The rules or the Xies,
which is more important.
You can have a think.
As I expect,
you still can’t let go of your revenge.
Stop!
Who’s standing in the way!
If you want to pass from here,
you should ask for my permission first.
How dare you!
You dare to stop the official carts!
It’s far away from the capital!
What can you do to me?
You!
Fight!
Report!
The carts with female prisoners
are attacked by bandits!
As Hua expected,
Xie Chongjin wants to take
this opportunity to kill Shi Feixian.
Everyone!
Yes!
Save her!
Next one!
Go! Next one!
You! Come here!
Go, go, go!
You! Turn around!
I said you! Turn around!
Such a tender skin.
She doesn’t look like a prisoner.
How dare you rob the official carts!
Catch all of them!
It’s her! Catch her!
Go!
Stop!
Freeze!
Run! Where are you running to?
I’m the granddaughter
of the Prime Minister,
and the Crown Princess’s sister.
If you hurt me,
do you know the result?
It’s your bad luck.
You were born in the wrong family.
Let go of me.
-Come here!
-Let go!
Bro!
I’m the noblest lady in Daye.
How could I be humiliated like this?
I can’t get what I love.
I won’t be happy in this life.
If there is a next life,
I wish to be an ordinary girl
and no longer be fooled by might.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪