Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 19
Hua.
How will you award me?
Don’t move.
See you at the range tomorrow.
Ban’s Mansion
You really kissed him?
Of course.
When I wanted to kiss him,
how would he refuse me?
Doomed.
Your Grace.
You’re a young lady
who hasn’t got married yet!
When can you behave like a lady?
What are you fussing about?
Anyway,
it wasn’t our first time to kiss.
What...? Not your first time?
-Doomed. Doomed.
-How many times have you kissed?
All right. All right.
Since when did you care
for such love affairs?
What’s the time?
Go get the dress ready for tomorrow.
Remember.
It should be simple, but also...
Dazzling!
Your Grace, it’s Prince Luo’s wedding.
But you want a dazzling dress.
Are you going to make trouble?
I just want to see
if the thing I dreamed of
will happen.
Count Cheng’an, you just arrived?
What a coincidence!
Yeah.
It’s not a coincidence.
He waited for you for an hour.
Hua, did you have
enough sleep last night?
Did you have breakfast?
If you’re not full,
I’ve got snacks in my carriage.
Would you like to have some?
I’m not tired, sleepy, or hungry.
Let’s get in.
Okay. You call the shots.
Du Jiu.
Miss Softy is carrying so many things.
Why don’t you help her?
Young Master.
Miss Softy can carry something
ten times as heavy as me.
I don’t think she needs help.
Be a gentleman.
Oh.
Let’s go.
I’ll carry them for you.
Thank you, Mr. Du.
Wedding
The luminous pearl of the East Sea
is my wedding present for you.
Hope you’ll like it.
I certainly like it.
I haven’t seen any luminous pearl
as big as this before.
Miss Xie is always modest.
After you marry Prince Luo,
don’t forget to take us
to get out more.
Is there anything bothering you?
Not really.
I just wonder
if I should marry him.
Miss Xie, don’t talk nonsense.
This is Prince Luo’s mansion.
Watch your tongue.
The Empress has arrived!
You may rise.
You all look beautiful.
I’m happy to see that.
Good girl.
This is what I used when I got married.
I’m giving it to you as a present.
Do you like it?
Thank you, Your Highness. I like it.
My son
can be a bit irritable.
But he’s a good man.
If you feel aggrieved,
come to me.
I’ll certainly help you.
Thank you, Your Highness.
It’s getting late.
I’m going to the front yard.
I’ll leave you alone.
See you, Your Highness.
First, bow to the heaven and earth!
Second, bow to parents!
Bow to each other!
Prince Luo
is marrying Miss Xie.
As Princess, she’ll enjoy the offering
from two hundred counties.
We put this down in paper
to show the heaven
so that their marriage
will be recorded
and they will have children
when our country lasts long.
Conferring Booklet for Princess
Hey, Blabbermouth.
Your daughter is just getting married.
What are you showing off?
I’m now a relative of His Majesty.
I like to show off, so what?
I’ll piss you off! Piss you off!
Suyue, the wine tastes sweet.
Have a try.
Your Highness, I don’t drink wine.
Why don’t you enjoy it?
Fine. Feed me, then.
Your Highness.
Hua.
The plum tastes sweet.
Have a try.
I have some, too.
Your Grace, if you like it,
enjoy mine.
Fine. Feed me, then.
What?
Nothing.
My hand is wounded
when practicing archery
and I can hardly help myself
to the food.
If you don’t like it,
forget it.
Your Highness, see?
Aunt has picked the right man.
A young man and a young girl like them
make such a perfect match.
The food you fed me tastes better.
My daughter is getting married next.
I’ll give her a better wedding
than this one.
Everybody.
I’m happy to see so many young couples
in the capital city.
His Majesty and I
want you to hold more weddings
so that our nation will look livelier.
Minister Shi, I remember
you have another daughter
except the Crown Princess.
I wonder if she’s engaged.
Thanks for the concern, Your Highness.
My granddaughter Shi Feixian
isn’t engaged yet.
The Crown Princess is known
to be virtuous.
Your other granddaughter
must be good, too.
Minister Shi.
I want to be a matchmaker for her.
Would you like that?
Since you bring it up,
I’d certainly like it.
I wonder which young man you mean.
You’ve made the trouble, son.
I have to make up for it.
The second son of the Xie family
is handsome, talented, and virtuous.
I think
they’ll make a perfect match.
Xie Qilin?
Isn’t he a blind man?
Thank you, Your Highness.
We’re grateful to you.
Your Highness, you have good taste!
My second son is excellent.
He’s a perfect match for Miss Shi!
He’ll be a very good husband!
Your Highness!
Your Highness, I...
Your Highness.
Sorry, but I can’t do it.
Thank you for your favor.
But I’ve missed the girl
I want to marry most.
Now,
I don’t want to get married.
Please take back your order!
Xie Qilin.
Do you think Miss Shi isn’t good enough
to be your wife?
No. She’s a good girl.
She’s from a famous family
and she’s good at literature.
Many young men adore her.
But...
She isn’t the girl I adore.
However excellent she is,
she’s a normal girl
to me.
Who does Xie Qilin refer to?
Could it be Princess Ban?
Shi Feixian is the most talented girl
in our nation.
But even a blind man doesn’t want
to marry her.
Your son is more sensible than you.
Fine. Fine.
The Empress was just kidding.
Xie Qilin, since you adore someone,
you can ask me to get you married.
Everyone in the Xie family is loyal.
I’ll always satisfy them.
Come on. Let’s cheers.
Ban Hua, stop!
You promised me
you wouldn’t tell anyone about the thing
between Prince Luo and me.
But today,
you stirred up trouble
in front of the Empress
on Prince Luo’s wedding.
I’m not you.
I don’t need to do that.
Stop quibbling!
If you didn’t,
who else could have framed me up?
You already have Count Cheng’an.
Why can’t you let go of me?
Can’t you be satisfied
until you destroy my life
with a blind man?
Would you cut it out?
Like I said,
I didn’t tell anyone about your affair.
If you didn’t,
go explain to the Empress
that Blind Xie Qilin likes you
and you should marry him.
Shi Feixian, stop calling him blind!
He was blind because of you!
Watch your tongue!
Your Grace.
I know you’re jealous of me.
That’s why you always frame me up.
But now,
why are you still slandering me?
Do you have to kill me
to be satisfied?
Enough.
No one else is here.
Stop pretending, all right?
Stop being a drama queen
in front of me!
You disgust me.
I don’t like Xie Qilin.
But I think highly of him.
Luckily, he refused to marry you today.
Otherwise,
it would be bad luck
to the Xie family
if you marry him.
What a filthy speech!
Why does Count Cheng’an adore
such a rude girl like you?
You know what?
Count Cheng’an already knew
what kind of girl I was.
But he still likes me.
What can you do about that?
I’ve never lost to you.
I’ll never give up, either.
Well, keep watching our love, then.
Ban’s Mansion
Your Grace, I’m home.
You can go back now.
Hua, it’s such a cold night.
Don’t you invite me in for some hot tea?
It’s a warm night, I think.
Besides,
you have hot tea at home.
When you go back,
ask Mr. Shi to make tea for you.
Hua.
What wrong have I done today?
Nothing.
Did I behave
very badly
so that people complained about you?
No one complained about me.
But many girls are jealous of me.
I saw the Crown Prince
do this to his wife.
I thought you would like it.
Don’t worry, Hua.
I’m sorry for what I did today.
I won’t do that anymore.
I like that.
Keep doing that.
Anyway, I’m used to it
when people are jealous of me.
Your Highness.
Get out!
Hurry!
How dare you stare at me like that!
Jiang Luo, what’s this?
Xie Wanyu.
How dare you break into my study!
Did you make Mother want
to marry Shi Feixian to someone?
Am I so bad
in your eyes?
Why did you marry me
if you didn’t want to?
Funny.
Your family insisted
on marrying you to me.
Do you think
I really wanted to marry you?
Well,
let’s divorce, then.
I don’t want to be your wife!
Xie Wanyu.
No one dares to talk to me like this!
Don’t think I don’t dare to kill you.
Your family is only my dog!
South Gate
How dare you punch my man!
He’s the man I want to punch.
I punched you to avenge you
for taking away my beloved girl.
Hua, I’m leaving.
I don’t know
when I can come back.
If you have something to tell me,
just say it.
Well, I do have something to tell you.
Have a nice trip.
Don’t you feel sad at all?
All good things will come to an end.
Even if she doesn’t want you to go,
you’d better leave early.
After all, you’ve stayed for months.
If I didn’t know
what kind of man you were,
I would suspect your purpose.
You’re a scheming man.
I can’t outargue you.
But remember.
If you’re rude to Hua,
I’ll come back with my army
and deal with you!
Don’t worry, Your Highness.
I’ll be nice to her
and never let her feel aggrieved.
But Your Highness,
I’d like to remind you.
Your army can’t come to the capital.
You can’t even reach the border.
People in your nation are so sly.
All right.
Don’t worry, man.
You’re my friend.
Here.
Seems like I don’t have a chance.
But it’s okay.
I have a good friend at least.
Hua, if you leave your nation someday,
remember to see me in Aipo State.
Mm.
Your Majesty.
The assassin who killed Princess Royal
was hidden deep.
It’s hard to figure out the man
behind the killing.
After a long investigation,
I’ve got nothing.
I owe my aunt a great debt of gratitude
and I fail to pay her back.
If I can’t find out the murderer,
I won’t feel relieved.
I’m sorry, Your Majesty.
Please punish me.
But...
I have a guess.
I wonder if I should tell you.
You’re always good at judging things.
Feel free to tell me.
Many powerful clans
raise private soldiers.
But such a well-trained assassin...
I’m afraid
he has something to do
with the resentment of predecessors.
How dare you!
Don’t talk nonsense!
Stop investigating the case.
Leave me.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Surprisingly, you’re not only
a good scholar,
but also good at archery.
It’s been only a few days,
and you can already shoot
whatever you want.
With a good teacher,
I get double results with half the work.
I’m doing good,
because you teach me well.
You’re right.
But...
people practice differently.
Look at Ban Heng.
I taught him so well,
but he still couldn’t learn it.
Anyway, it’s clever of you.
Officer. Officer.
Please let us pass.
-We’re refugees.
-What’s happening?
We’re fleeing from calamity.
How dare you!
Hua.
How dare you
walk on the government-financed road!
Please spare us, Officer.
We’ve never come to the capital before.
We didn’t know anything
about government-financed roads.
Please show some mercy
and let us pass.
Do you think you can come to the capital
just as you wish?
Arrest them!
Don’t touch my grandmother!
Come here.
You brat! I...
Bully others?
Let me teach you a lesson today!
Your... Your Grace?
Boy, hold your grandmother
and come with me.
What is going on?
Looks like she’s too hungry.
We haven’t had anything to eat for days.
Many people died of hunger.
Miss.
Madam.
My grandson was born in a good family
in Qizhou.
His parents were killed by villains.
Please take care of him.
I’ll pay you back in my next life.
Grandmother, wake up!
Grandmother!
Come over.
From now on,
this is your room.
If you need anything,
tell me.
Thank you, Miss.
This is the amulet Mother gave me.
It’s such an important thing.
Keep it carefully.
My mother said
the amulet is for a good person.
You’re a good person.
Fine. I can take it.
But you must have something to eat.
I’m not hungry.
Come.
Shunzi, your grandmother wants you
to grow into a real man.
Whatever happens,
you must face it bravely.
But now, you don’t even eat.
What kind of man will you be?
You like this?
Eat it.
Good boy.
Hua.
What’s on your mind?
I’m thinking.
We have enough food to eat.
But what can those hungry people eat
outside of the capital city?
In fact,
people in Xuezhou, Qizhou and Zhongzhou
have had nothing to eat
for quite a long time.
Didn’t His Majesty know?
He did.
He granted hundreds of dan of grains.
Where have the grains been?
Officials sell posts
and embezzle the grains.
After that,
people will get few grains
even if His Majesty grants
a thousand dan.
Famine outside the capital city
can’t be solved with money only.
But I not only have money.
I also have you.
If we join hands,
we can do something.
Grandfather.
I hear many people in Qizhou
died of hunger
and their condition was horrible.
Yeah.
May I ask
if the famine
has anything to do with our family?
It’s a natural disaster.
Why does it have anything to do
with our family?
But the magistrate of Qizhou
is your disciple.
Many of our clansmen
also work in Qizhou.
I fear some of them did evil things
and ruined our reputation.
Jin, don’t worry.
If someone dares to ruin our reputation,
I will make a thorough investigation
and never condone them.
You have hard work, Grandfather.
Get back to your business.
Even my grandson suspects this.
I’m afraid other officials are waiting
to find out my mistake.
Don’t worry, Minister Shi.
Official Zhao of Qizhou and his wife
have died in a fire.
No matter who investigates the case,
he’ll find them burnt themselves.
But I hear
before Official Zhao died,
he left a letter to His Majesty
written in his blood.
His mother and son disappeared.
I’m afraid they have the letter.
Letter written in his blood?
Yes.
What is the letter about?
I’m afraid it’s about something
we mustn’t let His Majesty know.
Send men to get the letter
and don’t leave any trouble.
Aye.
What have you got about Qizhou?
The magistrate Official Zhao
was dismissed a month ago.
A new official took his place
the next day.
Three days later,
Official Zhao and his wife
burned themselves in their home.
Burned themselves?
Did he suicide because he was dismissed?
He had a mother and a son.
But he died with his wife.
Sounds very weird.
Nearly all officials in Qizhou
were promoted by Minister Shi.
So was this new magistrate.
You mean
this is concerning Minister Shi?
Yes.
Shall we destroy Shi Chonghai
with this case?
We must figure out this case
for both private and public purposes.
Give me some.
It’s for everyone! Everyone!
It’s for everyone! Don’t push!
Don’t push!
Ban
Don’t push! It’s for everyone!
Don’t push! Don’t push!
Kind men!
It’s for everyone!
Don’t push! I asked you not to push!
Her Grace said
Ban
there would be enough porridge.
If anyone makes trouble,
he’ll be sorry!
He’ll be sorry! Line up!
I came first.
Leave it to me. Go keep the order.
Okay.
Come on. We have enough porridge.
You must be exhausted
after the long trip.
-Thank you.
When you finish the porridge,
you can have a rest
in the inn across the street.
Come one by one.
-Thank you.
Sir.
We’re regular customers.
How dare you fool me!
It’s so unkind of you!
I don’t dare to fool you,
Young Master Ban!
Zhou Changxiao,
show him the account book.
Okay.
Look.
How much is the accommodation fee?
49 taels and a half.
How much did I give you? Fifty.
What about the other half tael?
See?
He and I
recorded every penny used.
But, uh...
Young Master.
Isn’t it our old rule?
The rest is our tip.
Tip?
The half tael is enough
for a pot of porridge.
Give it back to me!
But...
Such little money
isn’t even enough for your liquor.
Why are you suddenly
so tight-fisted?
This is different.
My sister said
such money was special.
Every penny is the life-saving money
for disaster relief.
Every penny should be used
on all refugees.
Fine. Fine.
Ban
Take it.
It’s my turn. Give me some.
Princess Ban is beautiful and kind.
She’s just like
a kindhearted Bodhisattva.
Yeah.
Princess Ban is as great
as Princess Royal!
Precisely.
-Thank you, Your Grace.
Come on.
Her shed looks dirty and messy.
How can refugees eat without concern?
Come on. Take it.
Here. Take it.
Thank you.
-Here. This is for you.
-Thank you.
Enjoy it.
Shi Feixian?
With a beautiful condition and music,
refugees can relax and stop worrying.
Ban Hua, you won’t understand.
What is she doing?
I don’t know. We don’t understand.
It’s hot. Be careful.
-Thank you.
-Come on.
Shi
Come and get the porridge.
It’s for everyone.
Thank you. Thank you, Your Grace.
Thank you, Your Grace.
It’s hot. Be careful.
Come on. Take it.
It’s for everyone. Don’t be anxious.
Come on.
I’ll give better food.
They’ll all come to mine.
Shi
Shi’s Mansion
Come on. Make way.
Make way. Make way.
What are they doing?
Free roast chicken from the Shi family!
Come and get it, everyone!
Free roast chicken for everyone!
We’re late. Sorry to let you suffer.
Come on. Come here.
Roast chicken?
Free roast chicken!
Free roast chicken for so many refugees?
The Shi family can be so rich!
They’re not rich.
They’re being stupid!
Make way. Make way.
Make way.
You have a hard day, Your Grace.
Would you like a drumstick?
Shi Feixian, what are you doing?
You’re angry, Your Grace?
I just think they’ve been hungry
and have no meat to eat
and I want to provide them
with something better.
I didn’t expect to annoy you.
Don’t pretend
to be a kind girl, all right?
To relieve the people,
we should give enough food
so that more people will
have something to eat!
If you do this, there’ll be trouble.
It’s silly of me.
I just worry if the refugees
will have enough food to eat.
I wonder what wrong I’ve done.
Uh...
Miss Shi is kindhearted.
She has done nothing wrong.
But...
Yeah.
Yeah, she gives porridge,
but doesn’t want the Shi family
to give roast chicken.
Her family is rich, but she’s so stingy.
What are you talking about?
What are you talking about? Shut up!
Say no more!
Shut up!
My family isn’t as rich
as yours, Your Grace.
But I also want to help
as much as I can.
Your Grace, let’s work together
to help people get over the difficulty.
Shi... Shi Feixian, you!
Your Grace. Your Grace.
Hua.
Miss Shi and Princess Ban
both consider for refugees.
They’re both doing charity.
But she shouldn’t run wild!
Yeah!
You’re right, Your Grace.
I was narrow-minded.
Well, Miss Shi,
I’d like to thank you
on behalf of the refugees.
Everybody, do you have anything
to report to me?
Your Majesty,
people in Qizhou have nothing to eat.
Refugees are everywhere.
The magistrate of Qizhou suddenly died
after being dismissed.
The new magistrate took office
against the rule.
The problem in Qizhou
isn’t natural disaster,
but man-caused problem.
His Majesty cares about the problem
in Qizhou.
Count Cheng’an,
why did you talk nonsense?
Your Majesty, I have something
to report.
This is the account book for Qizhou
and the letter to appoint
the new magistrate.
Account Book
Two days ago,
the new magistrate
sent hundreds of taels of silver
to some official.
Then he took the post.
The new magistrate
bought his post from a minister
who has jurisdiction over Qizhou.
Count Cheng’an!
How dare you talk nonsense
in front of His Majesty!
Your Majesty.
The famine in Qizhou has lasted
for over one month.
You granted grains and money
for disaster relief.
If the magistrate of Qizhou
didn’t embezzle them,
the problem wouldn’t be so serious.
If senior officials didn’t shield him
and he wasn’t scared,
how would so many grains
be gone?
Minister Xie, what do you think of it?
Your Majesty, I...
Just say it.
I think we should handle it carefully.
These are wasted words.
What do you think, Ban Huai?
Your Majesty.
This is a very important problem.
We’d better be very careful.
Aren’t these wasted words, too?
Shut up!
Minister Shi.
Tell me what you think.
Your Majesty, Count Cheng’an is right.
I have something to do
with the problem in Qizhou.
I recommended the magistrate of Qizhou.
Why did I recommend him?
Because he’s a disciple
of Count Cheng’an’s father.
I didn’t accept any of his money.
I used it to buy food
and give it to the refugees.
Please kindly check, Your Majesty.
Memorial to the Throne
What a coincidence!
This morning, Princess Fule wrote
a memorial to the throne
about your family.
Your Majesty, don’t listen to a girl.
How can girls handle political affairs?
Who told you
girls couldn’t handle political affairs?
When my mother
handled political affairs,
you didn’t even enter
for the imperial examination!
Memorial to the Throne
In the memorial to the throne,
Princess Fule put in a good word
for your family.
What are you worried about?
Memorial to the Throne
The Shi family cared for refugees
and bought roast chicken for them.
I’m writing to request you
to award them.
Is that true?
It’s true, Your Majesty.
Minister Shi.
You’re really the pillar of our nation.
I feel so relieved.
I’ll encourage such good deeds!
Come and get the decree, Minister Shi.
Aye.
From today on,
you should buy roast chicken
for refugees.
Do it every day within a month.
Aye, Your Majesty.
Don’t pretend to be wealthy.
Roast chicken for a month
will dissipate your fortune!
Count Cheng’an, come and get the decree.
Aye.
I’m making you Minister of Revenue
to investigate the case of Qizhou!
I won’t let you down, Your Majesty!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪