Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 21
Shi’s Mansion
Grandfather!
Jin.
It concerns the Shi family’s reputation.
There is no place for you to speak.
There must be some misunderstanding.
Just ask Shi Feixian to come out
and we will know
if there is any misunderstanding.
Your Shi family
had the balls to do it,
why are you afraid to admit it?
Princess Ban,
you’re used to
running wild in the capital.
It seems like no one
can control you now.
You broke into my mansion today
and want to arraign my granddaughter.
Who gives you the power?
Court of Judicial Review
Princess Ban has no right to arraign her.
What about Court of Judicial Review?
Mr. Shi.
The Court of Judicial Review
has the sole right for investigation.
Please assist with my work
and let Miss Shi out for questions.
You took soldiers here
for the case or to humiliate me?
It’s an emergency.
Please pardon me.
Today Duke Ban was attacked.
The assassin said he’s hired
by Miss Shi,
and gave me this as evidence.
If Miss Shi can prove that
she didn’t lose
the two pearls she bought,
her name will be cleared.
Ridiculous!
Mr. Shi, it’s His Majesty’s order.
Please don’t make it hard for me.
It’s my daughter’s room.
How can you search it at will?
Just one question to her.
Why are you stopping us?
Princess Ban.
The search of her room by the Court
will impair her reputation.
As a girl,
you surely know the importance of it.
Do you mean
your sister’s reputation
is more important than my father’s life?
I...
You are so aggressive.
If Her Grace is wronged,
what are you gonna do?
If I get her wronged,
I’ll apologize to everyone.
If I’m right,
I’ll put all of you into prison!
Count Cheng’an,
your wife is unreasonable
and you are no better than her.
You are really a disgrace
to all the scholars.
Why do you say so, Mr. Shi?
Filial piety is also
the way of scholars.
No more arguing.
Your Grace.
That pearl is indeed the one I lost,
but I’ve never hired any assassin.
Do you believe me?
Whether you’re innocent or not,
the court will investigate it.
I don’t have the say.
You... You really want me
to go to the Court?
The truth is to be found out.
Please assist us with it.
Tomorrow morning,
I will go to the court.
Your Majesty!
I cannot be the Prime Minister!
Come on.
Rise, please.
Tell me.
How did you get hurt so badly?
Your Majesty.
I just became the Prime Minister,
and an assassin was hired
to hurt my head!
I’ll get killed if it goes on like this!
Ridiculous!
Someone dared to
assassinate you under my nose!
Where is Liu Banshan,
the Minister of Judicial Review?
Go! Summon him to me!
Don’t worry, Your Majesty.
I have an idea.
Why don’t you let Count Xie
be Prime Minister?
I’ll be safe when he is attacked.
Count Xie?
Yes.
Won’t you vie with him?
No, not anymore. Your Majesty.
My life matters more, Your Majesty!
My aunt was gone not long ago
before such things happened.
Rest assured.
I’ll order the court to find it out
and uphold justice for you.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Alright. Alright.
Duke Jingting. You may go back and rest.
Yes. Thank you, Your Majesty.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Insightful and Honest
Why is she peeking at you?
Is she?
I only have you in my eyes.
I didn’t pay attention to her.
Who are you?
Mr. Liu, yesterday,
you went to my mansion to question me.
Don’t you know who I am?
Miss. Shi.
Do you know what I’m going to ask
about the case?
I do.
Is the pearl yours, Miss Shi?
Yes, it’s mine.
I lost it days ago.
Lost? Where did you lose it?
Your Grace.
Do you want me
to tell it here?
Just tell the truth, Miss Shi.
It was a pearl embroidered on my shoes.
The other day, I went to the west grove
and lost it there.
You seldom go out of your mansion.
Why did you go there?
For an appointment, of course.
Appointment? Who did you meet?
The culprit, certainly.
Yeah.
Miss Shi.
Any witness for your statement?
This is the invitation letter,
a material evidence.
The letter was written
by Count Cheng’an.
Count Cheng’an?
Did Count Cheng’an meet her?
What was it?
You are the only one in my heart.
See you at the west temple.
You may leave me alone.
Yes.
You are the only one in my heart.
See you at the west temple.
Wait! Miss Shi.
You said he invited you by the letter,
yet he didn’t go there.
Why didn’t you go?
Hua, it’s not written by me.
Why should I go there?
You mean,
you would go if it’s written by you?
I... But...
I...
You are the only one in my heart.
See you at the west temple.
Miss Shi, one more question.
There’s no signature on the letter.
Why are you so sure
it’s written by Count Cheng’an?
Because... Because...
Because I collect many
calligraphy and paintings of his,
and study them every day.
I’m not sure of others’ handwriting,
but I can surely
recognize his.
You are the only one in my heart.
See you at the west temple.
It is your handwriting!
Hua, you don’t know about calligraphy.
Don’t jump to the conclusion.
Mr. Liu. You are a famous calligrapher.
Can you make a judgement?
Your Grace, I’ve checked it carefully.
It is yours.
Impossible!
Your Grace.
You do have feelings for me,
but you don’t dare to make it public.
As a woman, I’ve confessed it.
Are you still hiding it?
Listen to her.
Let’s see what happened.
Hua, you must trust me.
It has nothing to do with me.
There’s no way I could do that!
Count Cheng’an, you deceived my sister.
Now, you are lying to Her Grace
in public!
Shut up!
Your Grace.
I will not allow him to be close to you.
I mean you shut up.
It’s between Count Cheng’an and me.
I don’t want anyone else to step in.
I’ve eaten out.
Give me another pack. Come on.
Silence!
The case will be retried later.
Guards.
Aye.
Take Shi Feixian to the back hall.
Wait.
Mr. Liu.
The case has nothing to do
with my sister.
Why don’t you release her?
Calm down, Mr. Shi.
His Majesty ordered me to look into it.
All people concerned will be detained.
Your sister...
Count Cheng’an, you’ll be detained, too.
Mr. Liu. Mr. Liu.
News updated!
Count Cheng’an loves Miss Shi for long.
The engagement
with Princess Ban is fake.
Cut it out. Your news is out of date.
I’ve long heard that
Count Cheng’an loves Miss Shi,
but her brother disagrees.
Is it also true that
Mr. Shi loves Princess Ban?
Melon
Of course.
So, you know,
Count Cheng’an doesn’t love
Princess Ban.
He... He flirted her
just to irrigate Mr. Shi Jin.
I’m completely confused.
Who loves whom then?
Melon
I got it.
Count Cheng’an loves Mr. Shi Jin.
Shut up!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Get out of my way!
Your Highness, I know you are anxious.
But she’s in the Court
of Judicial Review.
How will you save her?
I’ll beg my father and mother for it.
Or I will go to the Ban family
and let Duke Jingting drop the charge.
Given your relationship
with Princess Ban,
I don’t think it will work.
Then I’ll tear down the Court.
I won’t allow my sister to suffer.
Your recklessness
will get His Majesty suspicious of you!
What should I do then?
You proposed the plan.
Now you are stopping me.
Ban Huai didn’t die,
while Feixian got in trouble.
If anything happens to her,
you’ll be punished!
To save Miss Shi,
you can’t make it this way.
Do you have an idea?
Darn it, Count Cheng’an!
You broke into my mansion
behind His Majesty’s back!
He delivered a fake edict.
Sir, only a report to His Majesty
can get him killed.
No.
Feixian is still a suspect.
A reckless report
will get us stuck in trouble.
It’s complicated and confusing.
Rong Xia got himself in custody.
Is it his plot?
It occurred right after Qizhou’s issue.
I can’t make out
the inner connection either.
Always assume the worst.
Sir, you mean...
Tell our allies in the court
not to take action.
The letter written in blood
shall not be obtained by the Ban family.
-Sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
Your Grace.
Did you really have feelings
for Feixian?
Don’t mistake it, Hua.
I apologized
for getting both of us in it
and making it a farce.
I’m sorry for getting you upset.
I trust you, certainly.
It’s unexpected in the law court.
I just lost my head.
Do you mean it?
Um.
Then why did you...
Stop... Stop it.
I came to tell you something.
I thought a lot after I went back.
And I suppose
something is fishy.
I don’t think
Shi Feixian is the culprit.
You’re right. Look.
If she is the culprit,
why did she try
to assassinate my father?
I should’ve been her target.
I agree with you.
The assassin hirer and the letter forger
could be accomplices,
or the same person.
The purpose
was to sow discord between us,
and the Shi family.
We got tricked. What to do?
We can do nothing
until they give the game away.
Now I am not by your side.
The top priority
is to protect yourself
and your father.
Without chicken, I’ll make do with duck.
Speak. What do you want?
I’m caring about your father
out of kindness.
Xie Wanyu.
We’ve been friends for long.
Stop being so defensive.
Don’t you feel bad?
I’ll cut to the chase then.
Truth to be told,
I’m here
to plead for Miss Feixian.
That wasn’t her doing.
Your sister wronged her.
I’ve never seen anyone
so silly as you.
What’s the relationship
between Jiang Luo and her?
Have you forgotten it?
And you even plead for her.
Don’t talk nonsense.
It’s not like that.
I’ve figured it out.
Husband is nothing but an identity.
But Feixian
is my best friend.
I cannot stand by.
Marriage is predestined.
Both of you are around her.
What... What do you mean?
Forget it.
Why give me the head?
You need some brains.
You...!
Guess who I am?
Jiang Luo, stop it.
Have a seat, please.
Your Highness.
We were intimate in childhood.
Why are we estranged now?
Luo. What brings you here?
Do you mean
you don’t want to see me?
No, I mean,
I didn’t expect
someday
you and I
could be so intimate again.
I’m overjoyed.
Alright. What you said
is really touching.
I’m greatly blessed
to be your brother.
Jiang Luo.
Do you feel unwell?
Do you need to see the physician?
No, no need.
I heard you suffered a disaster.
I was anxious, so I came.
Disaster?
Don’t you know it?
In the capital, it’s rumored that
the Crown Princess’s family
plotted to kill Duke Jingting.
Shi Feixian has been imprisoned.
Jiang Luo. You must hear it wrong.
She just went for some questions,
not being convicted.
Zhang, the Shi family is high-ranking.
And you are their son-in-law.
How come you don’t worry at all?
It’s not my business.
Why should I?
Zhang.
If your wife is too worried about it,
it will influence
your relationship with her.
That’s why I come to remind you.
Thanks for reminding me timely.
Or else, I couldn’t have thought of it.
But... What... What am I to do?
Let me think.
How about a gift to them?
Go to console Duke Jingting?
I... I’ll see to it now.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Ban’s Mansion
What’s going on?
Didn’t they know I’d come today?
Your Highness.
The notice and gifts were delivered
this morning.
But they said...
What did they say?
They said they didn’t deserve them
and wouldn’t accept them.
The case concerned the Shi family.
Crown Prince and you
shouldn’t intervene.
Ridiculous.
Ban Hua broke into Shi’s mansion.
I didn’t hold her accountable,
yet they dare to refuse to see me.
Calm down, Your Highness.
Never mind.
Get the gifts off the carriage.
Now that I’ve come,
they must accept it
whether they want it or not.
Your Grace! Madam! Bad news!
Crown Princess is breaking in
with others!
She comes for Shi Feixian, I guess.
I’m going to stop her.
Let her in.
I’m gonna see
what the Shi family is up to.
Crown Princess has arrived!
Come and welcome Her Highness!
No bother.
Since Princess Ban is
Crown Prince’s cousin,
that makes her my cousin.
No etiquette for families.
Your Highness comes.
It’s our great honor.
I’m here to apologize for my sister.
Do you admit she’s guilty?
She incurred the rumor and
hurt Count Cheng’an and you.
She is indeed guilty.
I got you some gifts.
Please accept them.
I cannot accept them.
What?
Did the rumor
estrange you from Count Cheng’an?
A rumor
doesn’t bother me at all.
There is more than one thing
that your family should apologize for.
My father got attacked for no reason.
I couldn’t just accept them.
How dare you
be so rude to Her Highness?
disrespect Her Grace?
You...!
The Court will definitely find out
the assassin hirer.
These gifts are not from the Shi family.
They are from Crown Prince.
You really got me puzzled.
Since they’re from Crown Prince,
why are you bringing Shi family up?
Better make friends than make enemies.
Princess Royal is gone.
The relationship
between our two families
relies on us to maintain.
Don’t forget it, Princess Ban.
Daye is no longer
what it used to be.
You are not here to deliver gifts,
but to push us
to drop the charge, right?
I will cut to the chase.
Before my father’s attacker
is found out,
you can do nothing,
neither Crown Prince
nor Prime Minister Shi himself.
How bold!
How dare you talk to me like this!
Kneel!
You want me to kneel?
I’m the Crown Princess.
My name is in the royal ancestral book.
Why can’t you kneel to me?
It’s you
who shall kneel to my grandmother,
Princess Royal Dening
of Daye.
You...!
Hurry and go back to your mansion.
Don’t throw your weight around here.
This is the exquisite kettle of Ru Ware,
one and the only.
Your Highness! Is my dignity
less important than a kettle?
Suyue. You’re more important, of course.
But
it’s no use smashing it.
If you really value me more,
how can you stand that I’m humiliated?
If it’s known by people,
it would be a great shame to me.
Suyue.
Ban Hua is actually nice.
Alright. Stop crying.
I promise whatever you want.
How is it?
Report it to His Majesty and punish her.
Well...
We’re families.
That’s not good, is it?
Harmony matters the most.
All things prosper in harmony.
Your Highness, you are so weak.
Even the Ban family
shows no respect to us.
How will you be the leader of ministers?
It’s not that serious.
It is!
The Ban family tries to bring us down
over and over again.
Who knows what they are up to?
Your Highness, if my family falls,
who else can help you ascend the throne?
Without my family,
you’ll lose the kingdom.
Watch your tongue, Suyue.
Did she really say so?
Yes, Your Majesty.
She said the exact words.
Absurd!
Without the Shi family,
Crown Prince couldn’t be enthroned?
Crown Prince is conferred by me.
What is it to do with Shi Chonghai?
Calm down, Your Majesty.
Crown Princess must’ve
had a slip of her tongue.
Your Majesty, please don’t...
A woman
dares to intervene the state affairs.
How can she
be the queen of the state in the future?
Your Majesty, are you going to...
Father, are you busy?
I have something to talk to you.
Come in.
Father, you are occupied.
Thanks for meeting me.
I appreciate it.
What’s the matter?
I wonder
if the Court of Judicial Review
can release Shi Feixian.
I... I’m just asking.
It’s fine if you disagree.
You good-for-nothing!
How come I have a son like you!
You are the Crown Prince of the state
before you are
the Shi family’s son-in-law.
Calm down! Father!
I... I didn’t mean that.
How should I calm down?
The only son of your great-aunt
got attacked!
You don’t go after the assassin,
yet you come to plead
for the Shi family?
Father! Father!
I... I’m wrong.
Don’t be mad, Father
Not mad,
I’m just sad.
Even Crown Princess
can order you around.
You’re timid and cowardly,
yet I’ll have to hand over the kingdom
to you.
-Your Majesty!
-Father!
Your Majesty!
-Your Majesty!
-Father! Father!
Imperial physician!
Father, are you alright?
Your Majesty.
How is His Majesty?
Your Highness.
His Majesty suffers poor blood flow
due to overwork.
He could have a stroke.
Stroke?
Please tell me.
How to treat this disease?
I’ll prescribe medicines to
pacify his mind.
His Majesty needs more rest.
Don’t anger him once again.
I understand.
Physician Chen. Keep it a secret.
Do not leak it out.
Mother, it’s my fault.
Hadn’t I got him mad, Father wouldn’t...
Keep your voice down, Zhang.
Let your father have a good rest.
The storm is coming.
We all need to prepare for it.
Miss Feixian.
Are you alright?
You are the only one in my heart.
See you at the west temple.
What brings you here?
Feixian, I went to beg the Ban family
to release you.
But they refused.
I’m so useless.
Watching you suffer here,
I cannot do anything to help.
I’m really pleased
for your kindness.
Also, for others,
it’s a place of pain.
But not for me.
What do you mean?
Since I came to the Court,
I’ve burned my bridges.
Whatever the cost is,
I’ll be with Count Cheng’an.
Although it’s a prison,
for me,
it’s the nearest place
to Count Cheng’an.
Seeing the same moon with him,
and having the same food,
I don’t feel pain
at all.
Feixian, even now,
you still think
the letter was written
by Count Cheng’an?
I’m sure
that is his handwriting.
Come on. Let’s drink.
Come on, drink.
Let’s play a game.
Finger-guessing, alright?
Come on.
-Six!
-Two!
You lose! Drink!
Come on. Go on.
-Three.
-Eight.
-Six.
-Two.
-Eight.
-Five.
-Six.
-Three.
Young Master, looks like
the prison is more comfortable
than home.
Ban Hua arranged this for me.
I told her it’s unnecessary.
She said I was not used to a prison,
and insisted on it.
I come here today
to tell you something.
You asked me to
keep an eye on that assassin.
Last night, some skilled masters
really came to the prison.
I talked with them
and then tailed them.
Take a guess. Who ordered them to come?
Xie Chongjin.
Do you know it?
Why did you ask me
to keep an eye on it then?
A letter was forged by my handwriting.
Then Shi Feixian was asked out
for an appointment.
The assassin attacked Prime Minister
and deliberately left clues
so that Hua broke into Shi’s mansion.
It’s meticulously planned.
Other than Xie Chongjin,
no one else can do that in Daye.
Young Master Xie
made so many efforts to do these.
What’s his purpose?
To kill someone with others’ hand
is his usual trick.
Kill the target with no blood shedding
and get away with it.
Du Jiu.
Who is guarding
the assassin’s cell?
Our men have all been withdrawn.
Only the guards from the Court,
I suppose.
Go ahead! He’s in danger!
Why did you frame my sister?
I didn’t.
No way could she hire an assassin.
The only possibility is
that you are lying.
You tailed her to the Red Earth Temple,
stole her pearl,
and pinned the assassination on her.
Believe it or not,
it’s Shi Feixian
who gave me the pearl
and ordered the assassination.
Who ordered you?
You sow the discord between
the Shi family and Ban family.
What’s your motive?
Your sister committed the crime,
and you want me to be the scapegoat.
I won’t!
Shi Feixian is the culprit!
You won’t kill me, will you?
You think I dare not kill you?
Go ahead. Kill me,
and your sister will not leave alive.
Court of Judicial Review
Mr. Liu.
Citronella fragrance
is in the letter paper,
which is only sold in one shop
in capital.
I’ve brought the shop owner to you.
Ask him yourself, please.
Is the paper from your shop?
You are the only one in my heart.
See you at the west temple.
Sir, the paper is indeed from my shop.
But Count Cheng’an
has never bought things in my shop.
Sir, please release Count Cheng’an.
Calm down, Your Grace.
The paper can rule out his suspicion,
but it can’t show the real culprit.
Other than the paper, there is ink.
The culprit focused on the handwriting,
but he missed the details.
It’s not difficult
to find out the culprit.
It’s intelligent of you. Thanks.
I’ll look into it right now.
It’s just that
to clear Miss Shi’s name,
more direct evidences are needed.
I understand. I’ll figure a way out.
Sir! Bad news!
Mr. Shi Jin got into the prison angrily!
He is killing him!
What?
Mr. Shi.
Mr. Shi, chill out.
His Majesty ordered
to find out the truth.
Please don’t kill him.
My master said
the assassin is the key to the case.
He can’t get hurt or starved.
Please wait a moment
if you mean to interrogate him.
Is that the food for prisoners?
Does my sister also eat this?
She’s a prisoner, too.
It’s already good for her to have food.
Shut up!
It’s you!
Mr. Shi killed the assassin!
Mr. Shi,
you’re eager to save your sister,
but don’t hurt the innocent.
You’ve killed a man.
Don’t do it again.
You mistook it.
He’s killed by that guard!
Your Grace! Seize him!
He’s the culprit!
How is he?
He’s dead.
Who could be so vicious
to use poison?
Fude House.
Fude House?
Yes.
Fude House is
the top organization of assassins.
It cost a big price to hire them.
Was my father’s attacker
also from Fude House?
It doesn’t make sense.
Xie Chongjin is an ordinary official.
How could he have connections
with assassins?
Whatever he’s up to,
just capture and interrogate him.
Don’t be reckless, Hua.
Xie Chongjin is crafty.
It’s not so simple as it seems.
We should wait.
The assassin has been silenced.
Wait for what?
As long as
we make public Chongjin’s dirty deeds,
everything will be clear.
But he’s backed up by Prince Luo.
Shi Feixian is backed up
by Crown Prince.
Rest assured, Your Grace.
I know what to do.
I’ll take him by surprise.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪