Sub by kisscambodia
♪The breeze blows through the alley♪
♪The fragrance of ink on you♪
♪The brush meandering on the paper♪
♪This love will last forever♪
♪The moonlight pours in the water♪
♪I can’t help but start to sing♪
♪You play a melodious song♪
♪It recorded our sweet time♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to break
from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
♪Being drunk but happy in the world♪
♪Spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪Watch the wood in a deep dye♪
♪Let’s ride a horse to see the world♪
♪With you in my life♪
♪I’m not afraid of any storm♪
♪I feel safe♪
♪You whisper in my ear♪
♪There is a distant call♪
♪I fell into the light of your halo♪
♪It’s too hard to
break from your embrace♪
♪Immersed in wine and time goes by♪
A Girl Like Me
Episode 20
Young Master.
Congratulations!
Congratulations. You are
the Minister of Revenue now.
Young Master Ban. Hua.
Father told us about
what happened in court.
I thought Hua would
tell on the Shi family
because of the roast chicken.
I didn’t expect you to praise them.
I was going to tell on her.
But after second thoughts,
if the refugees
can’t have meat because of me,
then I would be the bad person.
Therefore, I started to compliment her,
and also make His Majesty
compliment her.
Then she has to keep
giving out roast chickens.
That’s right. Let her do it.
Her family will die of poverty.
I’m not that bad as you.
First of all,
it’s not a bad thing
for the refugees to have more meat.
Everyone is having a good time,
and I’m not losing anything.
Second,
I have to let Shi Feixian know
that she will make trouble
if she horses around.
But she won’t listen to me.
It’s better to
let her wait and see the result.
I have reminded her anyway.
Hua, you have changed.
You’ve become a cunning fox now.
This is called turning her trick
against herself.
I learned it from my
grandfather’s military book.
It’s a counterplot.
I have to thank Hua
on behave of the refugees.
Minister Rong, you are welcome.
His Majesty was clearly
making it difficult for you.
Why did you accept
the imperial decree of
giving out roast chicken for one month?
The chicken doesn’t matter.
What matters is Qizhou.
Although I gave the runaround today,
I’m afraid His Majesty
would keep it in mind
and mention it again.
If it’s as you said,
the grandfather and grandson
should have blended in with
the refugees and fled Qizhou.
They should have arrived at
the capital these days.
But there are too many
refugees in the capital.
I don’t know where to find them.
I heard that the kid
from the Zhao family likes chicken.
We can just wait for windfalls
to erase this clue
before His Majesty finds out.
You are wise indeed.
Shunzi.
We haven’t had any meat
these days.
I’ll take you to
eat something good today.
Heng, you want to eat meat, right?
I don’t like meat.
No, you do.
You are shooting up.
You have to eat meat.
Sir.
Young Master Ban, welcome.
Come in, please.
Come on, sit.
Young Master Ban.
Do you still want porridge today?
It has been many days.
A kid can’t only eat porridge.
You are right.
He needs to eat something nutritive.
Okay.
I’ll have one large steamed chicken
with scallion oil.
Young Master Ban, just so you know,
there is nothing lacking in the capital
but chicken.
No chicken?
Eggs will also work.
Think about it,
how can there be eggs without chickens?
Let alone eggs,
you can’t even find
a chicken feather on the street.
Where are the chickens?
All the chickens
were bought by the Shi family.
The Shi family?
Come on!
Don’t miss it!
What’s the noise?
It should be
the disaster relief assembly
organized by Miss Shi
and other well-known families.
Shi Feixian?
Disaster relief assembly?
Shunzi, let’s go take a look.
Come on.
Young Master Ban, take care.
I’m bringing it to you.
There is a show over there.
Yes.
What’s happening?
There is a show of
the Six Fairies in the Bamboo Forest.
There will be no place later.
Streamed buns are better than fairies.
Let’s go eat food.
Okay.
Excellent!
That’s beautiful.
Shouldn’t there be six fairies?
Why are there five people?
What do you know?
There were six fairies.
After Xie Wanyu
married the Second Prince,
she chose to be a concubine
rather than a fairy.
So there are only five fairies now.
Shi Feixian, the one in the middle,
and Li Xiaoru are
two fairies in the sky.
What about the rest?
Go away.
The three fairies on the ground.
Great!
Excellent!
It sounds amazing.
West Gate
Excellent!
Great!
It sounds good!
You came all the way to the capital.
It’s fate that we gather here.
We prepared
basic necessities for you.
Please rest assured and enjoy it.
Take the capital as your second home.
Good!
Miss Shi has a heart of gold!
Miss Shi is the first fairy!
Great!
Well done!
-Great!
-Good!
Good! Good!
When did you come here?
I passed by
and was attracted by
the pleasing sound of the zither.
I’m flattered.
Miss Shi, you are too modest.
You are not only good at zither,
but also considerate.
It’s very thoughtful of you
to prepare so much for the refugees.
I want to thank you for them.
You are overpraising me.
This is what I should do.
If all the ladies in Daye
can be like you,
the refugees are lucky indeed.
There are many refugees out there,
I’m going to give out
roast chickens now.
Does anyone want porridge?
-Does anyone want porridge?
Your Grace, why don’t we
upgrade our food?
It’s embarrassing to have no one here.
We are here to rescue people,
not to make us look good.
There is nothing to compare with them.
That’s right.
They only take one bite of each dish.
This food they threw away
can feed the whole Qizhou.
If they don’t eat it, I will.
I will eat it, too.
But there are people
who can’t even have
any porridge like this.
If there are still
hungry people out there
who feels faint because of hunger,
and they can come to our shed
to have a bowl of porridge
and fill the stomach,
that’s enough.
Your Grace is right.
Freshly roasted chicken
of the Shi family!
Delicious roast chicken
Thank you.
Freshly roasted chicken
of the Shi family!
Everyone has a share!
Come on!
Come to eat our delicious roast chicken!
Roast chicken?
Delicious roast chicken
of the Shi family!
No, for my sister’s reputation,
we can’t eat it.
Even to starve to death,
I won’t eat anything
from the Xie family.
Young Master Ban, do you want some?
Your food looks too plain,
I’m not interested.
I’ll put the noodles here.
Don’t feel restrained.
Your noodles are soft and greasy.
It makes me lose my appetite.
It won’t be tasty.
I can’t let her fool people
with such unpalatable noodles.
I’ll just take one bite.
It’s delicious!
Shunzi, you...
Shunzi?
Shunzi!
Come, one for each person.
Everyone gets one!
Don’t push. One for each person.
One for each person!
You can only take one!
Stop!
Children are voracious.
It’s okay for them to take more.
Yes.
Here, have more.
Tell me if it’s not enough.
Thank you.
We need to find useful information
from these papers sent by
the agent in Qizhou.
I heard from the agent
that Official Zhao knew
he has nowhere to escape,
so he wrote a letter with his own blood,
accusing Prime Minister Shi,
and asked his mother and his son
to present the letter to His Majesty.
If the letter is
presented to His Majesty,
I’m afraid no one can
protect Shi Chonghai
no matter how many supporters he has.
But Prime Minister Shi should know
the existence of this letter.
Why hasn’t he made a move?
No, he has been looking for it.
You mean the disaster relief
of the Shi family is to find people?
Why do you stop talking?
The son of Official Zhao in Qizhou.
What happened to his son?
It’s Shunzi.
No, we have to tell Count Cheng’an now.
Ban
Young Master!
What happened?
Hua!
Bad news.
I lost Shunzi!
What?
You mean Shunzi is
the son of Official Zhao in Qizhou?
If Shunzi has the letter
written in blood,
it can prove the bribery is true.
Prime Minister Shi
won’t do nothing about it.
Hua!
We found him!
Where is he?
I asked Zhou Changxiao.
He said that all the orphans
in the capital
were sent to the Shi family’s
Charity House.
Shunzi is also there.
Minister Shi is such a cunning fox.
Heng, where is this Charity House?
I mean, what are you talking about?
Ban Heng, lead the way.
I’m going to take him back
from the Charity House.
Step aside!
-Who are you?
-What do you want?
-You can’t go inside!
Charity House
What’s wrong?
Why do you stop playing?
Brother.
I’m scared.
Mr. Shi, what’s this?
Your Grace, I...
No!
Give it to me!
-No!
-Give it to me!
-No! I won’t give it to you!
-Give it to me! Come on!
No!
-Hua.
-Give it to me!
Shunzi!
No. I won’t give it to you!
Xia, Hua, you are all here.
Are you okay?
I’m fine. Brother Shi also gave me this.
This is really
your family’s Charity House.
Your Grace.
This is indeed our family’s
Charity House.
Well, these kids...
Come on, go to play.
Have fun. Be safe.
These are homeless children.
No matter how much food we give out,
they won’t get any.
Therefore, I gathered them here.
They can make friends here.
There are food
and teachers.
Living in such a yard,
they may be able to grow up
without being hungry and cold every day.
Sorry, I misunderstood you.
I didn’t expect the dignified
Commander of the Imperial Guard
is so kind and considerate.
Brother Shi!
Come to catch me!
Okay, I’ll do it one more time.
It’s getting late.
We should take Shunzi home earlier.
Young Master, we’ve got the evidence.
It’s the perfect time
to bring down the Shi family.
Young Master.
What is your concern?
Shunzi has no idea about
what happened to his family.
The key is to find the letter
written in blood.
Wang Qu.
Pay close attention to every move
of Prime Minister Shi’s henchmen.
Report to me immediately
if you have any news.
Yes.
What did you say?
Zhao Shunzi is at
Marquis Jingting’s mansion?
Exactly.
Minister.
What should we do?
Rong Xia accused me last time.
He is openly against me now.
If he gets the letter,
he will present it
to His Majesty immediately.
Zhao Shunzi has been staying
at the Ban family for half a month,
but nothing happens.
You mean they don’t have the letter?
Or they don’t know the identity
of Zhao Shunzi at all.
This cat is so cute.
What’s its name?
It’s called Huahua.
You also like cat?
Shunzi.
I have something to ask you.
On your way here,
did your grandma tell you anything?
No.
Did your grandma give you any stuff?
Stuff...
No.
By the way,
my grandma told me not to trouble Hua
and remember what my parents said.
What did your parents say?
My parents said
they don’t want anything.
They just want me to be happy
and be a good person after I grow up.
Are you sure you won’t keep asking him?
Do you already know where the letter is?
It seems that Shunzi doesn’t know it.
But I will look into
this case thoroughly.
I won’t allow corrupt officials
to exploit the people.
Your Grace, go ahead and look into it.
Shunzi will stay with me.
No one dares to hurt him.
Shunzi is lucky to meet you.
After all,
I have never met such a cute
and sensible little brother in my life.
Hua, you are too harsh on Heng.
Although Heng is a little bit playful,
he has a pleasing personality.
He is not just playful,
he is unreliable. He only eats
and gambles every day.
He gets up at noon every day.
He is bad at learning
and worse at martial arts.
No matter how many flaws Heng has,
you still won’t allow anyone
to say anything bad about him.
Isn’t it?
Of course.
The more complicated our situation is,
the more I know
how much Grandma
silently did for us in those years.
Now Grandma is gone.
Ban Heng hasn’t grown up yet.
I’ve been thinking
how I can protect the Ban family
like Grandma did for us.
Hua, you’ve been doing a good job.
Haven’t you realized
that you can handle things alone
most of the time?
I’m not good enough.
It’s enough.
No.
I know nothing about
literature or politics.
But I know. That’s enough.
Isn’t it a waste to have
one more person knowing these things?
But I don’t know how to cook.
And I have a bad temper.
I don’t allow you
to say anything bad about yourself.
Since we swore an oath together
on that day,
I’ve decided,
no matter what difficulties
I will meet in the rest of my life,
I will guard the Ban family with you.
I’ll protect you.
Green bean cake!
Delicious green bean cake!
Sir.
Do you want a piece?
Here, take it.
Green bean cake!
Hua, it’s your favorite green bean cake.
There are many people watching us.
We are a perfect couple.
What does it matter?
Hua!
Father?
Where’s Father? Where’s Father?
He went to the Palace.
What did you dream of again?
It’s Father
who will be in trouble this time.
You’ve worked hard
for this disaster relief.
I’ve relieved.
Ban Huai.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I want you to take the position
of Deputy Prime Minister.
What do you think?
No. No.
Your Majesty, thank you for your grace.
I have no ambition.
I can’t take the position
of Deputy Prime Minister.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
This is a golden opportunity
that countless people
have been yearning for.
I know. I know.
Have you decided?
I’ve decided. I can’t take the position.
Your Majesty, I really can’t.
Since Marquis Ban has no intention.
What about Count Xie?
Are you willing to take on
this important task?
Thank you for your appreciation!
I will shrink from no sacrifice!
Your Majesty, hold on!
What are you doing?
Your Majesty, after second thoughts,
I think a person
should change himself in his life.
I’m willing to assume the responsibility
of the Deputy Prime Minister.
You...!
Ban.
What do you mean?
His Majesty has appointed me.
What do you mean what I mean?
His Majesty asked me first.
I can’t reject His Majesty’s grace.
Is there any problem?
You...!
Your Majesty, the Deputy Prime Minister
should be a real talent.
Marquis Jingting has
little talent and knowledge.
I am afraid he is unqualified.
Your Majesty,
in terms of disaster relief,
the Ban family bears the brunt.
You...! You old...
Your Majesty.
I’ve been assuming a position
in court for twenty years.
I’ve made countless achievements.
I’m definitely the best candidate
for Deputy Prime Minister.
You said countless yourself,
which means there is no
achievement to count, Your Majesty.
You...!
All right, stop it.
Prime Minister Shi.
What’s your opinion?
Your Majesty, I think
that the major families
are all offering relief aid.
This is the top priority.
The position of Deputy Prime Minister
is too important
to be decided in such a short time.
What’s your opinion?
I think
Prime Minister Shi does have a point.
Father.
I’m not familiar with
the national affairs.
I shouldn’t make a comment.
In that case,
I’ll think about it.
Luo.
From now on, you will
go to court with me.
Pay more attention to national affairs,
so you can assist your brother more.
Thank you for your appreciation!
I’m truly grateful!
Get off!
What?
Make way for Deputy Prime Minister Ban.
I won’t!
What are you doing?
Blabbermouth.
You old bastard!
Virtue Gate
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Was His Majesty satisfied with you?
It was just as you expected.
Father changed his attitude towards me.
He asked me to go to the court
and get familiar with national affairs.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
Chongjin.
You didn’t let me down this time.
But it’s ridiculous that Father actually
asked Ban Huai to be
the Deputy Prime Minister.
Your Highness, rest assured.
Ban Huai won’t become
the Deputy Prime Minister.
You are going to
make a move against him?
Good.
In this way,
the position of Deputy Prime Minister
will be your father’s.
He can check the power
of the Crown Prince for me.
Someone in the court will do it.
Who?
Prime Minister Shi is already overwhelmed
by the letter written in blood.
If Ban Huai gets promoted,
the inside story of Qizhou
will be harder to conceal.
You want me to work with
Prime Minister Shi?
No.
Just cut to the chase.
If you don’t say it,
I’ll throw you out of the carriage.
Your Highness, be patient.
I have a plan.
The third party benefits
from the tussle.
Why can’t I be
the Deputy Prime Minister?
Don’t forget.
I brought Yan Hui down
in person back then.
Come on, Father.
If it wasn’t for Count Cheng’an,
you would have been
gnawed out of with no bones left.
You are good at playing cards.
As for the way of being an official...
I’m the son of Princess Royal
and Old General Ban.
I grew up learning from them.
By the way,
tomorrow we should go to
the ancestral hall
and pay respects to our parents.
I need to let them know
that their son is a big figure now!
What’s more,
you will be the wife
of Deputy Prime Minister soon,
you should learn from
Mrs. Yan.
Look at her style.
-Master...
-You mean
I’m not as good as that Mrs. Yan.
Dear, I didn’t say that.
Keep reading the account book.
Read the account book.
Father.
I agree with Heng.
It concerns the situation of the court.
I’m afraid you will
get yourself into trouble.
My dear daughter.
You don’t know it.
This is a war between me
and that blabbermouth.
All right, I should leave.
Don’t wait for me for dinner.
Dad, where are you going?
I should have an understanding of
the people’s lives
and be prepared for the campaign.
I can’t lose to that blabbermouth.
Close the door, Softy!
Yes!
No, you...!
First thing first.
As long as there is
a slight chance of this happening,
you have to stay at home.
Master, just listen to Hua.
Well...
How long should I stay at home?
In my dream, it happens in early spring,
which means you can go out in summer.
Summer?
Daughter.
I’m also doing this for our family.
You can’t support the whole family
all by yourself.
Besides, we can’t count on
your useless little brother at all.
I...
You have to
let me go out and do my things.
Dad, it’s about your life.
I won’t give in.
Who dares to stop me!
What are you doing? You...!
Well...
Looks like this time
I’m going to lose to Blabbermouth.
You guys.
Guard every corner
of Ban’s mansion.
If you notice any suspicious person,
take him down immediately.
Yes! Let’s go!
Let’s go!
Master is gone!
You locked me up.
How can I not come out?
I can’t lose to Blabbermouth.
Furui Clothing Store
Sir.
How is your business?
Your Excellency! Have a seat.
Okay.
Sit down. I’ll get some tea for you.
I am thirsty.
This tea is freshly brewed.
Your Excellency,
why are you dressing like this?
I want to
experience the feeling
of being a servant.
Not good looking?
Good, very good. Excellent.
Your Excellency deserves your title.
You are unique and extraordinary.
Your Excellency, what do you
want to buy today?
Right.
I need to show my prestige
as the Deputy Prime Minister
in a few days.
Well,
go and get me the best
and the most expensive
suit you have. Go ahead.
All right, Your Excellency.
Wait for me.
Hua.
Did you find him?
No.
I’ve checked all the places
he usually visits. He is not there.
I’m afraid Father knows
that we will look for him,
so he avoided the stores
he usually visits.
Hua, could your dream
be wrong this time?
I remember it was inaccurate
several times.
Will Dad be fine this time?
Green bean cake!
Delicious green bean cake!
You want a piece?
Green bean cake!
Hua.
It’s today.
Father!
Ban Huai, stop!
Daughter, we can talk.
You don’t need to beat me.
Let’s talk.
Father!
-Father!
What should we do?
Uncle!
-These bastards!
-Hua!
Let’s save Uncle first.
Father.
Heng, send Father home.
Then go get Physician Yu immediately.
What about you?
I would like to see
who is bold enough to make a move
against our Ban family!
-Hua...!
-Hua!
Father.
Your Grace, you can
interrogate him as you want.
This restaurant is
the Rong family’s business.
Tell me.
Who asked you to do it?
Even if you kill me today,
I won’t say a word.
Will you say it or not?
Hua.
A few days ago,
someone found you
and gave you a sum of money.
You are ordered to wait here today
for Marquis Jingting.
This matter is extremely confidential.
Only you and the other person know it.
Don’t act sophisticated.
You won’t get a word from me.
Normally,
there shouldn’t be
a third person who knows it.
But why does Princess Ban
know something would happen today?
Why did she come to
the restaurant early,
saved him and arrested you?
I don’t know.
Yeah, it feels strange.
Could it be...
Could it be that the other person
wants to sacrifice you long ago?
It’s impossible.
Shi Feixian won’t sell me out.
Shi Feixian?
Don’t you dare to smear other people!
Let me ask you again.
Who asked you to do it?
I have a pearl on me.
Shi Feixian gave it to me.
If you don’t believe me,
just take a look by yourself.
Qi Rouge Store
Clean up that place.
Okay.
Sir!
Princess Ban, inside, please.
I’m not here to buy jewelry today.
Do you recognize this pearl?
Yes.
This is the Southern Pearl from Yuezhou.
Only my store sells such pearls
in the whole capital.
Do you still remember
who you sold it to?
I only got four pearls in total.
There are still two in the store.
The other two pearls...
Did you sell them to the Shi family?
Your Grace, how do you know it?
Shi’s Mansion
Hua.
It’s a felony to break in Shi’s mansion.
Of course I know.
I just want to commit a felony.
Hua, I understand your feelings.
But you can’t act on impulse.
Your Grace, I’m not acting on impulse.
We can’t find out the truth
just by the words of a bandit
and some pearls.
It this matter ends up unclear,
then tomorrow,
this flowerpot may fall on my head,
Shi’s Mansion
on Heng’s head and my mother’s head.
Therefore,
I have to break in Shi’s Mansion today.
I will make a big scene,
so big that His Majesty
has to look into it.
I know.
Go ahead and do it.
I’ll take care of the rest of it.
Minister, Ban Huai was attacked today.
Marquis Jingting’ Mansion
should have no time
to care about Qizhou for some time.
As long as Zhao Shunzi
is still at Ban family,
they will get the letter
written in blood one day.
We still need to prepare ourselves.
We can’t wait for
the Ban family to make a move.
Yes.
Shi Feixian, get out!
Princess Ban.
It’s a felony to break into
Prime Minister’s mansion.
Please go back.
Ban Hua?
What ungraceful things
did the Shi family do?
Why are you so afraid of letting me in?
Today,
I’m going to turn
your mansion upside down!
You dare not admit what you did.
Is that all what the Shi family can do?
Minister, could it be about the letter?
Why do you panic?
We’ll bridge over the troubled water.
She is just a young woman.
Look how panicked you are.
Princess Ban, why do you
suddenly come here?
My father was attacked
on the street today.
I’m here to ask for an explanation.
Marquis Jingting was attacked?
Is he all right?
If you want to ask for an explanation,
you should report it to the government.
Why do you come to my place?
Because Shi Feixian did it!
If I can’t meet Shi Feixian today,
no one can make me go back!
That’s ridiculous!
Shi’s Mansion
Stop, who are you?
Court of Judicial Review
Court of Judicial Review is under order
to investigate a case.
Unrelated people should step aside.
Your Grace, if you make such a visit,
there will no room for mediation
between you and Prime Minister Shi.
Mr. Liu, rest assured.
I know what I’m doing.
I’ll bear all the blame today.
Shi’s Mansion
Grandfather!
Jin.
It concerns the Shi family’s reputation.
There is no place for you to speak.
There must be some misunderstanding.
Just ask Shi Feixian to come out
and we will know
if there is any misunderstanding.
Your Shi family
had the balls to do it,
why are you afraid to admit it?
Princess Ban, you’re used to
running wild in the capital.
It seems like no one
can control you now.
You broke into my mansion today
and want to arraign my granddaughter.
Who gives you the power?
Court of Judicial Review
Princess Ban has no right to arraign her.
What about Court of Judicial Review?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Paper kite blue tiles
Begonia in midsummer♪
♪Make jasmine tea in the room♪
♪Sing a song and fiddle with Pipa♪
♪Her bright smile
and gloomy countenance♪
♪Crimson clouds flew into the house♪
♪Can’t control the feelings
It’s all in the dream♪
♪The rain pours down in a sunny day♪
♪Wash out all the attachments♪
♪Faith is like a flower♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪
♪We promised to live a free life♪
♪Flick away the dust with fingers♪
♪Only want to live
a carefree life with her♪
♪Travel around the world
in the younger days♪
♪Nothing is impossible in the dream♪
♪Go to the end of the world together♪
♪The fleeting life is just a moment♪
♪With no fear
Take her hands to see the big world♪