[English subtitles are available]
[Moonlight]
[Episode 3]
The contract, sir!
What contract?
I thought you've signed and
sealed the contract.
I didn't say that.
I can't find the seal.
So, I'm asking for your help
and clean up my room while at it.
Clean up?
Mr Zhou.
You want me to look for the seal
or to clean up your room?
To look for the seal, of course.
But you have to clean up to find it.
It'll get messier.
I only have half an hour.
Let's split up! Hurry!
I'll help you.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I mean, are you in a relationship?
Online relationship counts.
I barely have time for work.
How can I date anyone?
Mr Zhou Chuan.
You read Madam Cocoon's picture book too?
I will never read a low class
artist's work.
I forgot who gave it to me.
I burnt the midnight oil
to buy this picture book
for my friend before.
But then...
Never mind, I'll stop here.
Who is it?
Yes?
I must visit you often to
get your Book of Luo He God.
Who want Book of Luo He God?
Who? Who?
Ms Gu?
Why are you here?
That's a long story.
I've made a deal on that.
Stop thinking about it.
Who gave you a better offer
than Xin Dun Books?
You signed for her?
Yes, he is.
It's none of your business.
You've signed the contract?
Of course we did.
Signed and sealed.
The Book of Luo He God
is not yours to get anymore.
Goodbye, Ms Gu.
So, you prefer humane editors?
We're incompatible indeed.
See you next time, Chu Li.
I hope that we won't mark on
the same target again.
What do you mean by incompatible?
You're saying it like you're ditching me!
I'm telling you, Gu Bai Zhi!
I'm the one who's not signing you today!
What was that?
You're really childlike, Mr Zhou.
I'm protecting my honour.
Why were you so agitated?
I'm just signing your contract.
I'm not giving myself to you.
Oh gosh, Mr Zhou!
I have to go back! I can't make it!
If you can't find the seal,
make a new one.
It only takes a few days.
Call me when it's done.
You're leaving?
Am I useless
after the contract is signed now?
You...
Why should I call you when it's done?
Can't I call you before it's done?
[Sorry.]
[The number you have dialled
is not available.]
[Please call again later.]
[Hello, Chu Li.]
Hello, Xiao Niao.
Can you tidy up the book storage for me?
I'm in a huge traffic jam
and I can't return on time.
But I'm busy with
the PowerPoint presentation
for Mr Jiang Yu Cheng.
It's only five minutes.
I was almost done before I left.
Fine.
Can you help me
with the PowerPoint presentation?
I have a tight schedule too.
Sure.
Delivery!
[I mean, are you in a relationship?]
Online relationship counts.
I barely have time for work.
How can I date anyone?
Chu Li!
Where have you been?
I went to Mr Zhou Chuan's house
to look for his seal.
Why are you looking for his seal again?
You're an editor, not his nanny.
Fulfil your duty as an editor.
I don't care with the seal.
When will you sign the contract?
Do you want to stay here?
Of course I do.
I'm trying, Ms Yu.
Try harder!
I'm not seeing you leaving the office
for such matters.
Understand?
Yes.
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
[Audience analysis]
[Corner Bookstore]
Just as I said, Xiao Niao.
Thank goodness
for your PowerPoint presentation.
If not, Jiang Yu Cheng would not agree
to meet us so soon.
I studied hard
by reading Mr Jiang Yu Cheng's
previous works.
Good. I was right about you.
Look at that Chu Li.
She always says that she's a fan of
Jiang Yu Cheng
and was totally mesmerised by him.
I don't think she'll do a great job
like you for the PowerPoint presentation.
No way.
Chu Li has her own qualities too.
Very well.
Your humble attitude
makes you better than her.
I'll pick up a call.
Go ahead.
Oh no!
-Hurry!
-I'm sorry!
Clean it up.
The laptop is not lighting up.
Hurry and call the office
for a backup laptop now.
I'm on it.
I'll be there in five minutes.
She's here.
Deputy Editor.
Here's the laptop.
You're late!
Place it here.
Thank you.
Put the pen drive in.
Is Mr Jiang here?
It's none of your business.
Why should you worry?
I'm asking you, Chu Li.
Have you found the seal?
Mr Zhou Chuan had applied for a new seal.
I'll give him a rush.
I say,
try and look for your brains
before looking for the seal.
Don't be infatuated in everything
every day.
Go and get busy.
Okay.
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[Nervous! Excited! Agitated!]
[My colleague is meeting with Mr Jiang.]
[I'm hiding]
[to have a look at him]
[and take a snap shot for remembrance.]
No...
She had to rush back to office
after meeting me
but she can slack off for Jiang Yu Cheng?
What is this?
Why is it him?
Hello?
Come to my house now!
If not, I won't sign the contract!
What's going on?
It's broken?
Yes.
You called me here for a broken
washing machine?
Can't you ask for a technician?
I'm in a rush.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
Don't you know
how to check the power source?
I don't know.
I have a nanny to settle it for me.
This is common sense!
Why are you shouting?
I'm sorry.
I have to leave for my errands.
Wait.
Now that you're here,
you can continue cleaning up
the remaining mess.
Since that you have a lot of free time.
I'm not! I'm really busy!
I've only slept for three hours
from yesterday.
I was tidying up the shelves yesterday,
but you tricked me here
and made me late.
Ms Yu scolded me so badly.
I was thinking to work hard today,
but something happened to Mr Miao.
I had to rush my way to send him a laptop.
I was able to get some rest
and take a peek at my idol.
But I'm here for a washing machine!
A washing machine!
You must use electric for it!
Don't you know?
You...
Are you thirsty?
Do you want a drink?
I'm not thirsty.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
I was in a wrong mood.
I'm not saying that I'm not cleaning up.
I'm just too tired to do it.
If you don't mind,
I'll clean up your house tomorrow.
See you tomorrow!
Scared me to death.
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
This time,
I must give Xiao Niao an appraisal.
If she didn't
make a good presentation
and obtain Mr Jiang's trust,
I'm afraid
we won't even get a chance to meet.
It's nothing.
It's my duty.
Chu Li.
What's your progress with Mr Zhou Chuan?
That's a huge progress.
She went from looking for the seal
to applying for a new seal.
Just as I said, Ms Yu.
We mustn't accept
non-professionals.
Your probation
had went by half.
The person who will stay will be decided
by the contract.
That stinky fox
is not replying me.
[Is she still mad at me?]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[Did you see him?]
[No.]
[I'm furious with Zhou Chuan!]
[He called me urgently]
[as if there was an emergency.]
[In the end, his washing machine
was broken.]
[And it's not really broken,]
[but it's just unplugged.]
[I've never seen such a dimwit before.]
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[You hate him so much?]
[Can we stop talking about him?]
[Chu Li.]
[You don't have to come tomorrow.]
Mr Jiang.
From the moment I read you book titled
The Disappearing Zoo,
I made a goal for myself.
If I have the chance,
I'll definitely film this into a movie.
Didn't I obtain the chance now?
Actually, plenty of people had
reached out to Mr Jiang
for his book's copyright.
He didn't say yes to anyone.
But he said yes
when he heard it was you.
Mr Jiang is your fan.
Which films do you like?
Besides Yesterday,
I like No Man's Land and Straw.
These are my earliest works.
You saw every film
I directed?
I was sure that
you'll come along.
My sentiments exactly when I
read the Disappearing Zoo
for the first time.
A toast to you.
Here! Our collaboration
this time will be a pleasant one.
That's a must!
I remember I told you
that I'm not selling it.
You're too late.
From the moment you accepted
the invitation,
the copyright was sold.
Didn't you admire him?
I admire his work.
But that doesn't mean
I admire his personality
or that I'll work with him.
Are you going to offend Li Yu?
He's Li Yu.
If you offend him,
no one will dare to film your work
into movies.
Do you believe it or not?
What are you trying to do?
What am I trying to do?
I'm pulling you away
from the rusty publishing house.
I'm helping you to start anew.
You were the one
who made me into such a mess.
Don't you feel guilty to speak with me
in such a rightful manner?
Gu Bai Zhi doesn't know about guilt
in her life yet.
Let's stop for a while.
What's wrong? Who made you angry?
You.
Me?
I was busy with Yuan Yue Publishing House
that I didn't make time for you.
What's wrong?
You're joining Yuan Yue Publishing House?
Hello?
Hello, Mr Jiang.
I'm Miao.
I'm calling
to ask about
the contract with us.
What are your thoughts?
After your presentation,
I pondered for a while.
[I think we're not on the same path.]
I think we can wait for
another chance to work together.
I'll hang up as I'm occupied.
Hello? Hello? Hello?
What is it?
Jiang Yu Cheng refused to work with us.
Why?
You refused?
The deputy editor and editor
tried to brainwash me
into writing fantasy and
immortal cultivation.
Miao is capable to do this.
He thinks about the market
and the top hits,
but not the authors.
Miao.
Is Jiang Yu Cheng's Weibo
related to your meeting with
him yesterday?
I know.
The readers were saying that his new work
is controversial.
He was unhappy?
I reminded you.
Famous young authors like Jiang Yu Cheng
are difficult to handle.
Do you think the arrogance of a author
only appears in fictional works?
It was all my fault.
I followed the PowerPoint presentation
and spoke directly.
You didn't make the slides?
Not entirely.
Not entirely?
Chu Li.
Did you work on the slides?
It's not entirely Chu Li's fault.
I thought Chu Li will understand
Jiang Yu Cheng better
as she is his loyal reader.
So I asked her to amend it for me.
But I never thought...
Yes.
But I don't think Mr Jiang
is such a narrow-minded man.
He'll never get mad with
such trivial matters.
Do you think you know Jiang Yu Cheng?
This is great.
You failed to sign Zhou Chuan,
and Xiao Niao failed to
get Jiang Yu Cheng because of you!
No.
How can you put the blame on me?
I admit that I made the slides.
But you agreed to the content
and went with the meeting.
Why...
Stop fighting!
Think of a way to
salvage this.
All of you are really
unprofessional beyond my expectation.
We'll look at the contracts.
If you can't get it,
none of you will stay.
I have an old reader
working at Yuan Yue.
I thought she'll come
when I saw the slides.
What old reader?
She's at Yuan Yue?
What's her name?
I didn't hear about her from you.
When did you feel interested
at my reader?
Who's interested in her?
I have higher quality readers than you.
Who would care about your readers?
Ugly and ill-tempered.
What a joke.
Hello, Mr Xia.
How many times did I tell you?
An author must have passion
for his work.
Hence, a masterpiece will be made.
As editors,
we must never try
to control them.
No.
Mr Xia, I...
I'm not controlling him.
You're not controlling Jiang Yu Cheng
by asking him to write
about fantasy and immortal cultivation?
Fantasy and immortal cultivation?
Mr Jiang's expertise is suspense
and thriller.
Miao.
You didn't tell me about asking
Jiang Yu Cheng to switch genres.
The reason I did it
is because...
I hope that Mr Jiang can have
a change in his preference.
After all,
fantasy and cultivation
is the most popular genre in the market.
I did it for his own good.
Have you considered about
his feelings?
Will he like it?
This time,
if I didn't
contact Jiang Yu Cheng on my own,
I'll still be in the dark until now.
I'm reminding all of you.
As an editor,
we must respect the authors.
I don't wish to see this
happen again.
Understand?
Yes.
Xiang, thank you
for tidying up the place with me.
You're welcome.
I wish everyone in the office
can be as kind as you.
I'm not expecting them to be so kind.
But they should at least be fair.
They shouldn't push the blame on me.
Chu Li.
I think you should keep a low profile
from now on.
If you offend Deputy Editor,
you'll have a hard time.
Someone has his back.
Who?
Have some sweets.
No, I don't.
Take it.
No, I have glycosuria.
Eat it yourself.
Mr Liang?
Rumours said
that Mr Xia is retiring.
The position of the Vice President
will be chosen between Mr Liang and Ms Yu.
But Mr Yang had already decided
to put Mr Liang on the seat.
Didn't you see?
Mr Liang is beginning
to take over other departments.
[Zui Qian Yu Winehouse]
Miao.
How many years have we met?
It's been five years.
Five years.
Where were you five years before?
I was at the circulation department
as a promoter.
I ran around in various bookstores
regardless of the weather.
Bookstores back then had a hard time.
Unlike the modern ones now
that sells creative works and coffee.
Every day when the sun comes up,
those old trademarks
would fall like dominos.
Mr Liang.
This is actually my greatest concern.
I'm worried that
Yuan Yue Publishing House
will share the same fate
if we don't change our module.
Yuan Yue Publishing House is not stubborn,
but the manager of
Yuan Yue Publishing House.
You know the person I'm directing at.
I knew right away without
your hint, Mr Liang.
That's right.
Yuan Yue Publishing House had promoted
some famous authors.
But look at where we are.
We're getting beaten by
huge companies like Xin Dun Books.
And we don't stand a chance.
This is the market discipline.
Passion? Who doesn't have passion?
Yuan Yue Publishing House will be gone.
Where will the passion be?
Right?
They're making a fuss over nothing.
They're acting coy.
I won't joke with you.
Here's an inside news.
Mr Yang gave his word.
When Mr Xia retires,
Yuan Yue Publishing House
will be under my command.
You mean...
Don't you understand?
Don't act silly here.
Miao.
I know about your personality.
And I know about your capability.
So from now on,
the editorial department depends on you.
Guard it well.
You'll be my right-hand man in the future.
Understand?
Yes! I'll give you a toast.
Stop it.
Here's another inside scope.
Sure.
Yue Dong Games is interested
to obtain the animation
and gaming copyright of
the Oriental Beauty.
Their boss loves the book.
Mr Zhang from Yue Dong?
He's the pioneer of the gaming industry.
You know Mr Zhang's ability.
Everything that he has his eyes
on will be popular.
Zhou Chuan will be extremely valuable.
Place the rest of authors aside.
Do you best to get Zhou Chuan
into our company, understand?
You must take him down personally.
Understand?
Chu Li.
Give me a copy of Zhou Chuan's contract.
Mr Zhou Chuan's contract is with him.
He said he'll give it to me
after he seals it.
Fine, then print me another copy.
Deputy Editor.
May I know why do you need the contract?
From today onwards,
Zhou Chuan is off your hands.
I'll take over.
Off my hands?
Why?
Don't ask why.
Never mind.
I'll do it myself.
If he's taking me away from
Zhou Chuan's case,
does he want me to leave
the publishing house?
Chu Li.
How about this?
Call Mr Zhou Chuan
in front of Deputy Editor Miao
to confirm his decision.
[Sorry, the number you have dialled...]
Xiang, I'm going to Mr Zhou Chuan's house.
What's that face?
Mr Zhou.
I didn't see you for a day.
You've exerted yourself
like this for work?
Did your flu get worse?
What do you think?
The thing is, Mr Zhou Chuan...
I have an presumptuous request.
Can you please...
Drink hot water if you caught a cold!
How are you?
I'm fine.
I'll help you.
Careful.
Do you have a thermometer?
I don't know.
Leave if there's no urgency.
Don't disturb me.
Xiao Niao.
Where is she?
She went to Mr Zhou Chuan's house.
No, that's because...
No?
Do you have to cover up for her?
Didn't I tell her
that I'll be in charge of Zhou Chuan?
Is she really a dimwit?
It's related to the internship result.
It's common for her to be nervous.
Why didn't you leave?
No! I want to sleep!
Place the thermometer under the tongue.
Thirty eight degrees?
Have some porridge and flu medicine.
You must visit the hospital
if you feel unwell tomorrow, okay?
There's no meat.
How unpalatable.
There's meat below.
I made this beef porridge for you.
You made it?
Then?
Did I procure it with magic?
I have no strength to drink it.
Brother.
Do you want me to feed you?
It's fine.
I can fall sick until I die.
Didn't I ask you to leave?
Am I such a person who will abandon
a sick and lonely man behind?
Don't you hate me?
You're overthinking.
How would I hate you?
I can't wait to hold you like
a treasure in my hands.
I'm not eating.
You have to eat!
I don't eat food from people I dislike.
Who told you that I hate you?
No one told me.
I can see it myself.
You even threw tantrums.
It's just a temporary
mental breakdown from adults.
Fine.
I did hate you before.
But I don't hate you anymore.
Why?
That's because you're
eating the porridge obediently.
Drink this.
Mr Zhou Chuan.
Can you please help me tomorrow...
How great it'll be
if you're this obedient.
Come in.
Chief Editor.
Chu Li can't do this.
How did she offend you again?
She didn't offend me.
I think her capability
and working attitude are problematic.
Look.
She always leave the office
without a reason.
Then,
she'll try to defy her leaders.
She didn't contribute
to the publishing house at all.
I think
she's not suitable to work here.
You mean...
I mean
we should end her probation early.
That's going against the regulations.
There's no regulations about it.
Look, Chief Editor.
The current situation of
our office is obvious.
We can't afford to employ useless people.
You gave her time
to sign Zhou Chuan with us.
But I think
she'll never get it done
no matter how much time you give her.
If that's so,
I'd rather we place our concentration
entirely on Xiao Niao instead.
Even though she didn't get to
sign Jiang Yu Cheng,
but
Mr He Ma had signed under us.
He agreed to publish his works
through our publishing house.
She had already exceeded our expectations.
Fine, we'll do as you say.
I'm on it!
Miao.
I wonder who taught her to
go against her leaders.
You're right.
Take your temperature, Mr Zhou.
You're fine if it's 37 degrees.
There's porridge in the pot.
Microwave it for two minutes
before consumption.
[Yuan Yue Publishing House]
We will come to
a decision on Xiao Niao and Chu Li's
stay or departure
in our meeting today.
The both of them weren't allowed to stay
because they failed their tasks.
But Xiao Niao
was able to contact Mr He Ma
and obtained his copyrights
for the next five years.
So, Xiao Niao gets to stay.
Chu Li.
You might not
be suitable as an editor.
Your probation will end now.
Chief Editor Yu.
I can call Mr Zhou Chuan
to prove that he's willing to join us.
I can complete my task.
Sure, you may call him.
Can you give me an hour?
I'll visit him.
I don't think it's necessary.
You can't even reach
Zhou Chuan's house in an hour.
Chief Editor Yu.
Do you believe Zhou Chuan
lost his seal for the contract?
Isn't there plenty of authors
who behaved like him?
Therefore, Chu Li.
Don't waste our time.
Can't you pack up your belongings
and just work in any bank you like?
Deputy Editor.
Mr Zhou Chuan is not such a person.
If you're using this
as an excuse to fire me,
I can't accept it.
So what if you can't accept it?
Will Zhou Chuan seal
the contract if you can't accept it?
I hope I didn't disturb you.
Mr Zhou Chuan?
I've signed the contract.
If there's anything
to discuss in the future,
Chu Li can contact me directly.
Sure.
Thank you for visiting us, Mr Zhou Chuan.
I'll take my leave.
♫ I want to hide like a kid
who made mistakes ♫
Send Mr Zhou Chuan off!
♫ My heart skipped a beat ♫
Mr Zhou Chuan!
♫ When you look at me
everything seems so cute ♫
Are you feeling better?
I'm here at Yuan Yue personally.
♫ I am the only one feeling strange ♫
What do you think?
Thank goodness.
♫ I have got a million whys ♫
Thank you for coming all this way
to send the contract.
I might get fired if you didn't.
♫ But I can't tell ♫
Does that make me your saviour?
Of course!
♫ I still have my sanity ♫
I'll send you the full text later.
Thank you!
♫ I fled for a week ♫
♫ You don't seem to be surprised ♫
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
[I just saw your text message.]
♫ Because when you look into my eyes ♫
[Are your problems settled?]
♫ I have told you a thousand times ♫
[The Navy Hired by the Monkey]
[Thanks to Mr Zhou Chuan!]
[I've changed his alias too.]
♫ The world is on
the verge of elimination ♫
[The Disappearing Mr Fox]
♫ Only you are still favoured by me ♫
[Superb Hero Mr Chuan?]
[Not Drama King, but Saviour.]
♫ Because when you hold me in your arms ♫
♫ I have never felt so right ♫
Not Drama King, but Saviour?
♫ If this is not love ♫
I've finally seen Mr Zhou Chuan in person!
♫ What can I tell myself ♫
He's just like how I imagined.
The Gentle and Kind Mr Chuan.
What are you doing, Chu Li?
A daily inspection to see if I'm alive.
Was everything I experienced
just now a dream?
I'm sure that I'm not dreaming.
I really saw Mr Zhou Chuan!
I was going to call you.
What's the matter?
I found some illustrations
about ancient customs.
I'll take all of them.
You're in a good mood.
Do you need my help?
I do have a good mood.
I'll tell you.
My father is having a seminar here.
He invited us for dinner tonight.
So I want to wait for you.
My father will be there too?
We despise each other.
Why should I go?
I'm occupied tonight.
You two haven't met for a long time.
Speciality Preserving Porridge.
A medicinal porridge for
digestive diseases prevention.
It's not fluent.
What?
There's no direct object in the sentence.
You should add the word "function"
after the word "prevention".
It's not that strict now.
Dad.
Xiao Cheng, you're here!
Why are you alone?
You two are still concerned about
the decadence
of the Chinese proficiency?
Zhou Chuan will be here soon.
We'll wait for him.
Who cares about him?
I'll have no appetite with him around.
Then you shouldn't eat.
You can curb your Three Highs.
You're too rude to your father,
Xiao Chuan.
That's it. It's my treat today.
I finally get to meet my son.
Let's eat in peace
and show me some face, okay?
Hungry?
Let's eat.
Sure.
The braised meat here
tastes authentic.
Dad.
I think
you shouldn't eat the braised meat.
You have Three Highs too.
Look, he's even stricter than his mother.
Alright then.
Uncle Zhou.
Their fish is exceptionally fresh.
Have a taste.
Zhou Chuan.
Get Uncle Zhou some fish.
I'm not used to serve food to others.
Others? Who's the others?
I'm your father!
When did you ever carry out
your duty as a father?
Look at him! Look at him!
He's already so arrogant now that
he accomplished nothing!
Old Zhou.
Your words might be too harsh.
From what I know,
Little Zhou's works are being prepared
for animation and gaming production.
Am I right?
Yes.
The aesthetics nowadays
are really crooked.
Those who are on trend
can be developed even
if they're at the tertiary level.
I think you're jealous of me.
Just by your level of expertise,
are you worthy of my jealousy?
I want to see
after a decade
if anyone will be interested
in your works.
I'm done eating.
Stop right there!
Zhou Chuan!
Old Zhou! Look at your fiery temper!
The lights are still on.
Where is he?
Behind you.