Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 4
Linglong!
Get her!
Take me hostage!
Hurry! Take me hostage!
Stop!
Don’t… Don’t move!
Don’t move!
Put your swords down!
Now what?
Leave here!
Go!
Move away!
Back off!
You okay?
Follow me.
Move away!
Hurry!
Go!
Linglong,
you’re awake.
Father.
How do you feel, Linglong?
You alright?
Are you still feeling unwell?
We did it?
Great!
Are my tribesmen alright?
They’re alright.
Great!
Brat,
now she’s fine.
Why are you
still holding her hands?
What do you want?
What about you?
How long do you want to hug me?
Who is she?
I don’t know her.
Who do you work for?
I work for you.
Don’t talk nonsense.
Then who is she?
I don’t know her.
Why did you help us?
To
make you owe me one.
What do you want me to do?
Can you heal his wound?
You’re injured, Father?
I’m fine.
It’s just
a scratch.
You call this a scratch?
It’s fine. It’s fine.
Let me take a look.
You see?
My daughter has grown up.
She cares so much about me.
It’s really good.
Knock it off.
Don’t move.
Let me take a look.
You know what?
Some herbs are all I need
to heal the wound.
There’s no need to worry about it.
Can you heal it?
She didn’t know how to do it.
I
might
not be able to do that now.
It’s alright. It’s alright.
When can you do it then?
I’m not sure about that.
Good girl.
My skin is thick.
I’ll recover in two days.
I’ll pick some herbs
in the mountains myself.
Forget it then.
Now you’ve got no use
for me at all.
I’m fine.
It’s alright. It’s alright.
You can
pay me back in the future.
You should go now!
The soldiers will be here soon.
However,
where can you go?
I’m afraid you can’t
go back to Fire Tribe now.
This medicine can heal your wound.
I guarantee your skin will become
as delicate as before.
I’ll go back then.
Don’t forget me.
Only... Only a fool will believe you!
Damn your medicine!
What’s the relationship
between you two?
What are you talking about?
You were wearing
a different outfit yesterday.
So many things happened,
yet you still had time
to change your clothes?
I changed my clothes because...
What are you implying?
Speaking of which,
what’s your relationship?
Why did he come back?
Brat,
you didn’t take my words
seriously at all, did you?
Father,
Yuan Yi helped me save you.
Him?
Again!
Not a big deal!
We’re not safe yet.
Let’s leave here first.
Leave here?
Is it that simple?
Where can we go?
We can’t even go home now.
It was all your fault.
We can...
How about we
hide in the Wall for a while?
Father,
we’re not going back to the Fire Tribe.
Then where are we going?
Leader has had it all arranged.
Chi Fang!
There you are!
Chi Fang,
where are the other tribesmen?
Are they alright?
Don’t worry.
All of them are alright.
Leader has found a safe place
for them to stay.
Those bad guys
will not find them.
That’s great.
Hasn't the ship arrived yet?
Not yet.
Ship?
What ship?
What are inside the boxes?
Those are Flammable Stones
to be sold.
We’re waiting for the buyer’s ship.
We can hide in the ship
and then leave here.
You!
What is that?
How come the fish is flying?
That’s a ship of Weisheng Yan’s.
Only the Weisheng family
has a ship like this in Suchuan.
A flying ship?
Who is Weisheng Yan?
The richest man in Suchuan.
A fish that can fly?
I never knew there were
such things in the world.
Suchuan is very big.
There’re many wonders you don’t know.
I’ll show you around.
I also want to take a look.
Um…
You can sneak in
when we load up the ship later.
Where are we going?
Did I permit it?
Did you ask my opinion?
Father,
I know that
you disagree to this,
but,
are you willing to let me
board the ship alone?
If I stay here,
I’d put the whole tribe
in danger.
Everyone will help me
if I want to leave.
You can’t stop me.
Then I’ll try and see if I can.
Alright. Alright.
Huotu Xin,
Linglong has already
grown up.
Bug off.
Don’t make trouble.
You!
It’s all right.
Linglong,
I want to say sorry to you
about the Earth Fire Test.
I haven’t given up yet.
I’ll definitely find the way
to extinguish the Earth Fire.
Good.
Here.
Your sword.
Take it.
Thank you.
Sorry for what we’ve done to you.
It’ll be a tiring journey.
Be careful.
Father!
Don’t try to leave me behind
no matter where you go.
I never thought about that!
But how’re we supposed
to board the ship?
Over here.
Be careful!
Okay.
Be gentle!
What if you break them?
Over here.
Put this on the top.
Be gentle!
Okay. Okay.
Be gentler.
Seems this one’s very heavy.
Sir,
the stones are all here.
You said you don’t want money.
How can I explain it to my master?
It’s all right.
Leader said
it’d be all alright
if you can bring the rest of the things
on the list to us next time.
Our tribe
seldom interacts with outsiders.
We have no use for money.
Fine.
I’ll tell our master this when I’m back.
Okay.
Our tribe
hasn’t been at peace lately.
You should depart soon
if there’s nothing else to do.
Okay.
Please be quiet.
Miss Yin doesn’t feel well.
She just fell asleep.
Okay.
Sorry. Sorry.
Never mind.
I have several guests
from Bright Moon Island.
I’ll go take a look.
Go ahead.
It’ll be a bumpy journey.
Please be careful!
Father.
Over here.
Help me!
Brat, you’re so immoral!
Hide!
Search the ship!
Yes!
Who are you?
None of your business.
Do you know whose ship this is?
Who cares?
What are you doing?
Let him be.
Just search the ship.
It’s her again!
Hurry!
Make room! Make room!
I can’t close it, Father!
Do you still remember who I am?
You...
Someone!
-Go inside to search!
-Shh!
No one’s here!
Yes!
What about now?
You owe me another one.
Now you know who’s reliable,
and who treats you well, right?
Wait a minute.
What’s your name?
Wu Yuan.
Did you find them?
No.
Keep searching.
Yes!
Can you keep it quiet?
You woke Miss Yin up.
Nothing.
Not even a dead mouse.
Keep searching.
Weisheng Yan’s ship
appeared here for no reason.
There must be something fishy.
Why don’t you search them yourself?
What?
You’re afraid of that little girl?
Report!
We’ve found nothing.
I told you to keep it quiet!
Can’t you understand?
Who the heck are you?
Bug off!
What?
You should use honorifics
when talking to the elderly.
Don’t you know?
My sister is resting.
If you don’t know
how to keep quiet,
I can teach you.
Xiao,
I’m fine.
Don’t fight with them.
It’s windy outside.
You should go inside.
So handsome!
Who is he exactly?
Not long ago
Xiao,
can I change
my hairstyle?
You don’t like it?
It’s the hairstyle Mother taught us.
I just want to
try a new one.
But this is
the only one I can do.
Juan.
Come on in.
Greetings!
My master is so lucky!
Is my hairstyle
a bit outdated?
It’s indeed
not the most fashionable hairstyle
in Pingting.
What is it?
Here’s the thing.
Our ship
will stop by the Fire Tribe’s
White Forest Lake later.
We’ll pick up some goods
and take them to Pingting.
Yin Zhuang has a head disease.
She doesn’t feel comfortable on ship.
I hope we don’t stop
during the journey.
This...
Our ship
is indeed poorly adorned.
It’s too shabby for the future
female master of the Weisheng family.
Please bear with it.
We don’t need your ship
to manifest our nobility.
Yes!
Besides the Yuan family,
no families in Suchuan
are qualified to
hold a candle to the Yin family.
You!
Tell me your name!
Yin Xiao
from the Yin family.
What did he say?
I think he said
the Yin family.
Xiao,
stop fighting.
I’m going to get married.
I shouldn’t see too much blood.
I’ll be back in a moment.
I’ll wait for you here then.
I came to arrest people
on Zhu Xi, Marquis Pingjiang’s order.
Forgive me for offending the descendants
of the Yin family.
We’re on the land of the Fire Tribe.
Since when
Marquis Pingjiang got to govern it?
Seems you’ve been away for too long.
I heard the Yin descendants
wandered across many remote islands,
so it’s understandable you’re not
familiar with the current situation
of Suchuan.
I guess
you’re going to Pingting, right?
How about this?
You can come to me
whenever you need anything.
If we had a chance to meet again...
Xiao!
Miss Yin,
your brother knows what he’s doing.
Go ahead if you still want to
search the ship,
but please keep it quiet.
No need.
I believe this is a misunderstanding.
Alright then.
See you again.
There are such people out there!
Shh.
Lower your voice.
Look
how ignorant you are!
You know them?
I didn’t expect the Yin family
has a descendant like him.
What’s special
about the Yin family?
It’s one of the oldest families
in Suchuan.
It’s also known as a divine tribe,
along with the Yuan and Li families.
The Yin family once held the position
of Judicial Director.
They can
perceive the emotions of others
and even control their wills.
It’s said that
no guilty person
can escape their judgement.
That’s why
he could control that sword
at will?
Control others?
Then isn’t he just like
that weirdo with a stone
embedded on his head?
You mean Gu Shi?
Those are
imitators of the Yin tribesmen.
They rely on implanted objects
in their bodies
to enhance a certain strength.
But the Yin tribesmen are different.
It’s flowing in their blood.
It’s a born strength inherited from God.
Innate.
It’s undoubted.
Just like you.
But after the Fall of God,
the Yin family’s power also disappeared
and they gradually met their downfall.
Only an
ancient noble surname was left.
Then,
will he take your orders?
We will no longer
need to hide here
if we have his help.
I have control over things in Zhaodu,
but not things
outside of Zhaodu.
Who on earth are you?
Now you want to know?
The journey is still very long.
I’ll tell you later.
Father,
it’s going up!
Have you seen it?
You let them go like this?
Even if the Yin family has waned,
you still
have no confidence to beat him.
I indeed have no confidence.
If the descendants of the Yin family
go to Pingting,
they’ll
pose a threat to the Marquis.
But they’ve left,
in a flying ship.
A flying ship?
It’s easier to kill them in the sky.
Get up.
Here is a knife
that can cause thunderstorms.
Go to Scale Valley
and knock down the ship.
Keep the man from the Fire Tribe alive.
He’s useful.
Scale Valley?
Evil Souls hang around out there.
There’s also something you’re afraid of?
Mortals are all
afraid of the Evil Souls.
What if
the girl is really on the ship?
The Marquis wants her alive.
Will Goddess die that easily?
Don’t you
want to see how capable she is?
Hold. It’s this girl.
That’s how it went.
I secretly left Zhaodu
and came to the Fire Tribe
after hearing the words
of Tianqi’s chief priest.
I didn’t expect
I would actually find Linglong.
Well,
how did you find the Palace of Flames?
In the library of Zhaodu,
there’re many books about
the Fire Tribe.
I can remember everything I see,
be it text or maps.
Now you know?
I’m an emperor in Suchuan.
Just ignore him.
He’s never been
so far away from home.
Right.
I’ve never left our home,
and I never wanted to leave.
You’ve seen
how scary those people
who came to the Fire Tribe were!
It’s dangerous outside!
But,
there’s also a lot of fun outside.
And things we’ve never seen before!
For example,
this flying ship.
There’re also good people
out there.
For example,
Yuan Yi.
Don’t worry.
I’ll protect you.
Zhaodu will be your new home.
We don’t need your protection.
I also don’t trust you.
If you don’t trust Yuan Yi,
why do you trust that woman?
When did I trust her?
You don’t?
Then why did you use this medicine?
I... I...
You applied the medicine
for me, alright?
By the way,
don’t trust him so easily.
If he really is an emperor,
since now he’s so far away from Zhaodu,
those people in Zhaodu
would search all over Suchuan for him.
In fact,
many people in Suchuan want to
replace me.
Zhaodu couldn’t let the news out.
Linglong,
will you choose me
or him?
What are you saying, Father?
Isn’t it obvious?
Even if he is an emperor,
he might lose his position soon.
Why did he come to you?
He wants you to help him
keep his position.
He’s using you.
And these things
are all life-critical.
I feel scared upon the thought of it.
Listen,
if you are in any danger,
I’ll protect you
at the cost of my life.
I...
Alright.
I know that
no one could change your mind
if you’ve made up your mind
even when you were a kid.
So,
will you choose me or him?
Make your choice.
Father!
You got it wrong.
Linglong is the Goddess of Suchuan.
Her position is much higher
than mine.
It’s not she’s going to protect me,
but everyone in Suchuan is
going to protect her.
There’s no need to explain to him.
He is fooling around.
Father,
don’t you want to find out
Mother’s secret?
Have you ever thought
if I really am the Goddess of Suchuan
like Yuan Yi said?
Then it’s impossible that my mother
was a monster.
Who was she?
Why did she come to the Fire Tribe?
Where did she come from?
Don’t you
want to know?
She’s your mother.
Who else could she be?
Now only Yuan Yi can help me
understand the power in my body,
and guide me to become Goddess.
As long as he can help,
I’m sure I can find out the truth,
and even,
the way
to extinguish the Earth Fire.
Maybe
that was also the reason
why my mother came to the Fire Tribe.
It’s possible.
Goddess is the guardian
of the entire Suchuan.
Right!
There’s no way that
my mother was a monster.
She came to our tribe
to help them extinguish the Earth Fire.
I have to prove it
and tell our tribesmen the truth.
Miss,
where are you from?
Pingting.
Pingting?
Is this ship going to Pingting?
Right.
But don’t worry.
Fei Tian’s secret sentinels in Pingting
will pick up us soon
and escort us to Zhaodu.
Let’s go to Pingting then.
But,
you have to listen to me.
After we arrive at Pingting,
I’ll find a job first.
Let’s keep a low profile for a while.
We’ll make a new plan
after this period.
We’re not going to Zhaodu.
You want to stay in Pingting?
Isn’t this ship going to Pingting?
Don’t you know
Zhu Xi, Marquis Pingjiang,
controls Pingting?
Those after Linglong
all came from Pingting.
Pingting
is the capital of Pingjiang.
Then...
Then... Then...
Then
will you choose me or him?
You...
You came back to this question again!
No, I...
Brat,
why are you blushing?
What’s it got to do with you?
Am I blushing?
Huotu Xin!
How can you call me that?
Behave!
Come at me if you’re angry!
-Come at you, you dirty brat?
-Stop quarreling!
You even carry a weapon!
What do you want?
Give it to me!
Don’t be so impulsive!
Let go!
-Don’t be so impulsive!
-Shh!
Lower your voice!
As stowaways,
shouldn’t you keep it quiet?
Who are you?
Do you know how they
treat stowaways?
They’ll throw them out.
I knew someone snuck in.
I didn’t expect
you brought two kids with you.
You’re so reckless.
You’ll get them killed.
Keep quiet!
I’ll kill you
if you tell anyone
we’re here.
Didn’t
my brother save you just now?
Don’t you remember?
He asked them to search the ship!
I heard that.
Where are those people then?
They...
Father,
is it appropriate to point your sword
at a girl like this?
Oh yeah?
My name is Huotu Linglong.
This is my father Huotu Xin.
We’re from the Fire Tribe.
I apologize to you for my father.
You don’t need to be afraid of him.
He likes to bluff,
especially before beautiful girls.
Don’t talk nonsense.
My name is Yin Zhuang.
Sis Yin Zhuang?
What are you doing?
I’m warning you,
don’t come close.
Your hairstyle is pretty.
Who did it for you?
What is it?
I don’t know how to say it.
You better come and see for yourself.
You must keep your words.
I’ll do a hairstyle for you,
and you’ll keep us safe.
Did he
do hairstyles for you all the time?
My mother passed away early.
My father did it for me.
Does it look good?
Very good.
If we
have a daughter in the future,
we’ll wear the same hairstyle.
What is it?
Doesn’t it look good?
Very good.
Crap!
What?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪