Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 5
You… You…
Listen to me.
I… I…
I’ve made a deal with your sister
that if I combed her hair,
she’d allow us to get on the ship.
Just let my father go first.
We mean you no harm.
Please listen to us.
Xiao.
What they said is true.
I had a deal with them.
Be careful not to hurt him.
He has two kids here.
Yes. Right.
How
would you guys
deal with stowaways?
Throw them off the ship.
You can’t drop us off.
Don’t drop us off.
I’ve added fuses
in the Flammable Stone on the ship.
If you drop me off,
the entire ship will be burnt to ashes.
I knew what you’re capable of.
To protect ourselves,
I have to take such action.
I’m going to throw
the cargo from Fire Tribe
off the ship.
Wait. Wait!
I was lying!
That’s not true!
There’s no fuse.
I… I…
I have other reasons.
I… I have no way to go.
As you see,
those violent and wicked people
are chasing us.
Why?
Because…
Because they want to catch my daughter.
Why?
If your daughter did something wrong,
they have a right to take her.
Of course not!
You are from Fire Tribe, right?
How would you mess up
with Marquis Pingjiang?
Because
Marquis Pingjiang
has taken a fancy
to my daughter Linglong.
Marquis Pingjiang
wanted to take her back
as his concubine.
That’s too much!
Linglong is just a kid.
That’s right.
She is just a little girl.
So you should know
that we have no way to go.
You believe him?
You cajole Yin Zhuang to lie with you.
It’s unforgivable.
Father.
How can you still not tell the truth?
I’ve told you.
No one can lie
before the Yin family’s judgment.
I was telling the truth!
I was not lying!
It’s because I lighted
the Pillar of Eternity.
Linglong.
Go on.
A few days ago,
we still lived a common life
in Fire Tribe.
Later on,
when I went to Earth Fire,
I lighted the Pillar of Eternity
somehow.
And then they came to Fire Tribe.
They used women and children
to threaten my tribe members
for taking me,
and almost killed my father.
I don’t know
why they did that.
But if I didn’t go,
my tribe would be in danger.
So I sneaked into your ship.
It’s said that the Yins are good at
distinguishing the good from the bad.
Then show me
what you can do.
The Pillar of Eternity will
only be lightened for the Goddess.
I hope it’s true.
Though what she said is weirder
than that of her father,
I believe she’s telling the truth.
Yin Zhuang believes you.
It means that you’re not lying.
Father.
They are strange.
Step away from them.
Go.
Father.
Are you okay?
How can you tell him that?
My intuition.
It’s better than your story anyway.
Now that the Yins believe you,
I have no reason to doubt you then.
Thank…
-Huotu Xin!
-Father!
Linglong!
Father!
What did you do?
No matter what reasons they said,
they are stowaways.
Moreover,
they’ve messed up
with Marquis Pingjiang.
Bringing them will only get
our business in Pingting involved,
or worse, get Master involved.
But how can you do that?
It’s so brutal.
You can bring them.
Anyway, when we arrive Pingting,
we’ll take them to Marquis Pingjiang.
Land right now.
Save my father!
Even if you can find him,
he may have been broken.
Land.
It’s an order.
You’re the offspring of the Yins.
You must recognize it.
Your Majesty.
Fine.
Land.
Find Huotu Xin.
Father.
We still have hope.
You once saved your father.
You can do it.
Xiao.
Be careful.
Control it.
Steer well.
Land.
No way.
It has lost control.
What happened?
I don’t know.
The thunderstorm is so heavy
that Goldfish stopped working.
Move.
Quick.
Open all side sails.
Yes!
Open all side sails!
Don’t panic.
It’ll be okay after the thunderstorm.
Hold me tightly.
Juan.
Juan is still in the room.
Don’t worry.
I’ll protect you.
If I’m hurt,
you must save me.
Yin Zhuang.
Juan.
Don’t get close to the edge
of the Abyss.
Juan…
She…
I saw Juan
falling down to the Abyss.
Xiao.
How would it happen?
Everything was fine.
Juan… She…
Sorry.
I didn’t manage to save Juan.
It’s lucky that
you’re alive.
What I mean is…
Sorry for your loss.
You are alive.
Yes.
I was born to be lowly.
I have to learn how to survive.
As the ship owner,
at the most dangerous moment,
you left your crew and guests behind
and sought for your own living.
I need to take you two to Pingting
to finish the wedding
of your sister and my master.
As a servant,
you risked your masters’ life
at danger.
Seems that you didn’t take good care
of your own master, either.
The top priority now
is His Majesty’s life.
What’s that?
Trackers.
Seems that
what we met
is not a normal thunderstorm.
When we arrive Pingting,
you should
apologize to Marquis Pingjiang.
Yuan Yi.
Are you okay?
What about you?
You saved me again.
It seems that
you saved me this time.
What’s this?
Trackers.
Your Majesty.
You are all alive.
What a good luck.
I failed to protect Your Majesty.
I’m culpable.
Never mind.
It’s good that you all are okay.
We are in a more urgent situation now.
Our location has been exposed.
We must withdraw immediately.
No.
I have to find my father first.
You’re so lucky
to survive.
You did something
to the ship, didn’t you?
Where are the two kids?
I see no kids.
Only we three here.
You two keep looking.
Xiao.
No need to show mercy this time.
Father!
Yin Xiao is capable.
Don’t worry.
Let’s find your father first.
What’s the sound?
It may be
the Evil Soul.
Evil Soul?
Evil Souls are real?
You know Evil Souls?
The seniors in my tribe said
Evil Souls are the most horrible
monsters in Suchuan.
But no one has ever seen them.
We are in Scale Valley.
It’s close to the edge of the Abyss.
Caravans often
disappear here out of the void.
It’s said that
they met Evil Souls.
The ship crashed here.
They must have planned it early.
Zhu Xi.
It’s daytime now.
Evil Souls will not show up.
Only if we step away from the Abyss,
can we stay safe.
What if my father is in there?
I need to find him quickly
in case he meets Evil Souls.
Crap.
Run.
Found them.
Catch them up.
Xiao.
Take Yin Zhuang away.
Don’t worry.
I will take her
to Pingting safely.
-Go.
-Xiao.
Go.
You go first,
or I’ll be distracted.
Go.
No.
You surely are worthy of being a Yin.
I can’t control you wholly.
You know how to control minds.
Are you familiar with it?
How dare you copy
the Yin family’s power.
Now let me show your power
in front of you.
Xiao!
What the heck?
Last night
Father!
You have wings?
You…
Do you belong to
the legendary Moon Tribe?
Did you save me just now?
Thank you. Thanks so much.
No need to thank me.
They want you to be alive.
They?
Who’s them?
When you’re
in Marquis Pingjiang’s death row,
you’d rather fall to your death here.
Big wings.
Do you
hatch them out?
Or what?
Are you born to know how to fly?
Linglong!
Let me go!
My daughter is on the above.
I know.
Didn’t you say you want us to be alive?
Go to save her then.
Or she’ll fall down.
What’s the use of catching me?
Go to save her.
Linglong!
Take Yin Zhuang and go.
Xiao.
Don’t worry.
I will take her to Pingting safely.
-Go.
-Xiao.
Go.
You go first,
or I’ll be distracted.
Go.
No.
You surely are worthy of being a Yin.
Where’s Linglong?
I can’t control you wholly.
Now let me show your power
in front of you.
The bastard.
Xiao!
What the heck?
Where’s Linglong?
Linglong.
Are you okay?
I’m fine.
Who’s there?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Someone’s killing us.
Who?
Who’s killing you?
What’s the matter, sirs?
Have you seen two kids?
A boy and a girl.
Ye… Yes.
They’re
over there.
They ran towards that direction.
Yes. It’s there.
I think
they are on your carriage.
No, no, no. I dare not.
No. They are not there.
I…
My carriage is empty.
I’m the only one here.
You dare lie to us.
It’s a waste of time.
Exactly.
I told you that the carriage is empty.
You didn’t trust me.
Nowadays,
you don’t even have
the least of reverence
for the God.
Don’t try to frighten us.
Now that you can’t hear
a plaintive cry from human,
I will show you
the fury of God.
Who are you?
You.
Do you have reverence for God?
Yes.
Yes, I do.
Then ran away now.
May God bless you.
Hope you can still live to tomorrow.
It’s okay!
Thank you.
Greetings to Your Majesty.
Who are you?
I am Fozhuan.
Fozhuan?
Master.
You must save my father.
You’re such a great master.
You can surely save my father.
Please.
Wait a minute.
Your Majesty.
Do you remember me?
It doesn’t matter.
Your Majesty,
why are you here?
You’re mistaken.
If you say so.
Master.
What did you say?
My father was pushed down
from the ship.
We must find him.
You can save him, can’t you?
The ship?
Linglong!
Here!
I found her.
Over there.
Where?
That’s great.
Over there.
Linglong.
Wait.
How about doing me a favor?
Yin Zhuang.
Are you okay?
I’m good.
We found your father.
You found him?
Where is him?
What’s wrong with my father?
Father.
Are you alright?
Wake up.
Father.
Yuan Yi.
Yuan Yi, help me.
Help me summon the Goddess out.
I want to save my father.
Father.
Master.
Please help me save my father.
You can surely save him.
Bring his life back.
Father.
This man
fell from the sky?
He has a complete body.
No blood here.
You find it interesting
to lie to your daughter?
You… You…
You know nothing.
Linglong.
Look, I’m fine.
You tricked me, Huotu Xin!
Linglong.
Don’t be angry.
How did you feel?
Did you think I’m the most important
and the others can be left behind?
At that moment,
you can’t trick yourself.
Save it.
There.
Don’t you feel happy
when knowing I’m okay?
Don’t fake it.
Here. Give me a hug.
I…
I thought…
There. There.
Good girl.
Everything’s fine.
They’re so close.
There. There.
Look. I’m fine.
I am a lucky man.
Just now I also helped
the brother in poker face.
You’re smiling, aren’t you?
Linglong.
Who’s he?
Yeah.
Should I introduce myself first?
Father.
Drink it.
What’re you doing? Hurry up.
They will catch us up soon.
No hurry.
Just a moment.
Your Majesty.
If what he said is true,
Moon Tribe
can’t be trusted.
Why would I lie to you?
Or why
didn’t I die
when falling from such a high place?
It’s true.
Report.
Minister Fei,
no word is heard from His Majesty.
Hope that no word
is the best news.
Add more force
to find His Majesty quickly.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Where are you?
Your Majesty,
do you recognize it?
This is
a feather from Fei Tian?
Yes.
Fozhuan.
Oh, I remember it.
Are you the disciple
who was dispelled from Tianqi
because you had a secret crush
on Fei Tian?
Why do you have Fei Tian’s feather?
You stole it?
It…
How can it be that I stole it?
Well.
The bastards in Zhaodu
must be jealous of me.
So they slandered me.
How dare they.
I’ve heard a lot about you.
I didn’t expect that
I can see you in person.
Your Majesty.
Don’t believe
the rumors.
I am extremely serious
towards Fei Tian.
Who is Fei Tian?
The leader of Moon Tribe.
My minister.
She’s a woman?
Yes.
Right.
She has been long believing that
she can be the most important person
by His Majesty’s side.
I also trusted that
she can do that.
What’s this?
Guiding Stone.
Split a complete Guiding Stone
into two pieces.
They will
guide the one
to find the other.
With it,
the travelers afar
can always find their home.
Before,
in Jinshi City,
where our ancestor was living,
there’s a variety of
interesting stones.
This
may be
brought out at that time.
That’s where Zhaodu is located.
Yes.
Will Fei Tian
receive your signal?
Yes.
Fei Tian sent me the feather as a gift.
She told me
no matter when
and no matter where,
as long as I need her,
she will show up by my side.
Over a decade has gone by.
I never imagine that
I can see you again.
Fozhuan.
Everyone is fine?
We should drink some wine together.
Where are Zhu Xi’s men?
You beat them away, didn’t you?
You bastard.
Bastard.
You should remember.
Human’s life is never inferior.
I was doing my duty.
I had no intention of killing.
Now you’re doing good,
and I’ve done my job well.
Isn’t it a win-win result?
You…!
Don’t be angry with him.
Xiao.
I remember Father told us that
the one who can light up
the Pillar of Eternity is the Goddess.
Is Linglong the Goddess?
Whether she is the Goddess,
it depends on if Zhaodu accepts her.
Let’s stop guessing that.
But
it’s His Majesty who found her.
Actually, His Majesty can’t decide it.
Wow.
Master has so much stuff.
They are so lovely.
I hope they can always be fine.
What’s the matter?
Is it okay?
What are you doing?
Cooking.
Do you know fire will
attract our enemies’ attention?
I need to cook something nice
for Linglong.
She’s growing up.
She didn’t have something nice to eat
and she was frightened.
I must cook for her
to replenish the nutrition she needs.
What’s more important now?
Just a moment.
Please keep an eye on the enemies.
What do you want to cook?
Can we have it?
Yes.
It’s for us all.
I heard from Linglong that
you can make nice fish soup.
Can I taste it?
You…
Are you good at swordsmanship?
Would you help me catch two fishes?
I can make it with fishes.
Xiao.
I’ll help him.
It can be finished before it’s dark.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Has Your Majesty thought about
what
Zhaodu means
to her?
As long as I can find her,
I will confront everything
with her.
But does she know?
I will find a chance
to tell her.
Maybe it’s too long.
The Goddess has been a legend.
I can’t even
believe that
the Goddess will get out from the void
into the human world.
Maybe the people in the world
haven’t been well-prepared.
Maybe even the Goddess herself
has not been well-prepared yet.
Being the Goddess
is never an option.
Just like I am the king.
Well.
I, Fozhuan,
would escort the Goddess
to Zhaodu
even I have to risk my like.
Linglong.
Tell me.
When can I
have the power of a Goddess?
No hurry.
When we arrive in Zhaodu…
I can’t wait any more.
When I thought my father
was dead,
why can’t I do anything?
Do I
really have the power you said?
Am I really the Goddess?
You surely are.
We’ve seen it.
Do you forget that?
What happened today
will happen a lot more, right?
I want to go with you
to Zhaodu so much.
I also expect
what will happen next
and whom we will meet.
But
if the cost
is my father,
I’d rather go nowhere
and stay in my tribe forever.
I understand.
You can’t understand.
You’re born to be king.
You have had so many things
since you were born.
To be a king,
His Majesty has also lost a lot.
Fozhuan!
Your Majesty,
just now you said
you will confront everything
with the Goddess.
It’s true that
from ancient times,
the Yuan family has been chosen
to be the only king in Suchuan.
But after the Goddess descended,
Suchuan has been disintegrating
and vassal states have been rising.
Though Zhaodu
is the capital of Suchuan,
and I am
the king of Suchuan,
actually…
So
last time
you said your parents…
I wasn’t born in Zhaodu.
My father
is the lord of a fief
in northern Suchuan.
The king at that time
was my uncle.
Soon after I was born,
my uncle died of illness.
As his only successor,
I was sent to Zhaodu.
Back then, Fei Tian
was my father’s retainer.
To protect me,
my father ordered her
to accompany me to Zhaodu.
But after that,
the news came that
Ransu people in the north invaded,
my father died in the battles,
and no one in the family survived.
I was young.
I can only remember Fei Tian
kept telling me that,
Your Majesty,
remember,
you are the last decedent
of the Yuan family.
Sorry.
I shouldn’t
have said that.
Now the world is disintegrating.
People are suffering.
My experience is nothing.
But I hope
all these
can come to an end in my hands.
Have you
come back
to your hometown in the north?
Ever since I can remember,
I have been in Zhaodu.
Zhaodu is good.
You will like it.
I heard from Fei Tian that
when His Majesty came to Zhaodu,
he felt depressed all the time
and cared no state affairs.
But when His Majesty
stood on the Calculator
and the Star Map shone for him,
His Majesty
stopped being depressed.
In his three-year ruling,
he promoted Moon Tribe,
cleared old parties,
and became an honored man
of the world.
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
What is
Star Map?
Star Map…
Your Majesty,
sorry for my offense.
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
Star Map
symbolizes king.
As long as His Majesty
stands on the Calculator,
the sun, moon and stars
in entire Suchuan
will fall for the king.
The priests
calculate astronomical phenomena
and enact calendar
according to the movement of stars.
So
His Majesty
is the only
chosen people.
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪In the starry sky♪
Back.
♪If one still♪
♪Shines for us♪
I thought
the wonder can only be summoned
when I am standing on the Calculator.
The king and the wonder are bounded.
So the wonder can appear
wherever you are.
So
it is
what a king should be like.
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪