Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 7
Put them down.
My name is Huotu
Linglong.
What’s your name?
My name is Ziyuan.
Are they
your friends?
They are…
Yes,
we are all servant girls
dispatched to your palace.
Why did they leave then?
There are so many dishes here.
Let’s eat together.
Miss.
As servants, we eat in the wing room.
Wing room?
I think we are of a similar age.
I hope to eat with you
in the wing room later.
Take these with you.
Miss,
never do that.
Okay.
Why the people in Zhaodu also avoid me?
How can I finish
a full table of dishes?
His Majesty is coming!
Yuan Yi,
you are finally here.
I have figured out an idea for you.
What idea do you have for me?
You have fled for me.
Fei Tian was angry with you
all the way along for it.
She will surely blame you after return.
I have an idea for you
so that Fei Tian won’t blame you.
What are you drawing?
Look,
you may
pretend
to have been hurt for me.
First,
she must feel sad for your injury.
Second,
she will carry
out her anger on me.
You won’t be blamed in that case.
Playing sick is a trick
that has never failed on my father.
Fei Tian
looks even harsher than my father.
But all parents
love and care for their kids.
They are generally the same.
Linglong,
you don’t have to do that.
It doesn’t matter.
I am a guest anyway.
She can do nothing about me.
Maybe
I am Goddess.
Just take it easy.
I am more experienced than you
in dealing with parents.
Look.
Linglong,
I am the emperor.
Even if I make any mistakes,
nobody dares to blame me.
Not even
Fei Tian?
She won’t blame me.
But she has even more horrible ways.
You don’t know Fei Tian much.
Your plans won’t work on her.
You will know it later.
You have written down all the plans
to gloss it over with Fei Tian?
No.
These are all my plans
to become Goddess the soonest
and receive my father to Zhaodu.
Are you worried about your father?
Is it because of Master Fozhuan?
What’s the use of worrying?
Look,
this is a letter I wrote to my father.
Can you dispatch someone
to deliver it to Pingting?
I have sent someone to Pingting
to tell your father that you’re safe.
I believe he will receive
the letter soon.
Let’s go.
I will show you around Zhaodu.
Linglong.
Welcome to Zhaodu.
How powerful is the Moon Tribe!
The Moon Tribe is the last barrier
for the royal family.
We have to thank Fei Tian for it.
Fei Tian…
I still don’t have a chance
to apologize to Fei Tian.
Master Fozhuan
died for his faith.
It is not your fault.
Moreover, Fei Tian is someone
who controls her emotions well.
Yuan Yi,
have you ever loved someone?
No.
If you haven’t
fallen in love with a girl;
if you haven’t anticipated so much
for seeing her again;
if you haven’t
vowed to abandon the world
just to make her happy
and smile;
or if you haven’t had the determination
to overcome all difficulties
just to see her.
If you haven’t had any of such feelings,
you will never feel
identified with Fei Tian.
Maybe
you are right.
Then
have you had any such feelings?
No.
But I have imagined
and anticipated that.
Later,
I found such feelings
in the eyes of Fei Tian.
You are right.
What’s up?
What do the chimes mean?
The funeral of Tianqi Gang.
Get away.
Fei Tian.
I am already
fed up with
your arrogance
at the court.
Today,
you sounded the Tianqi Bell
without permission
and even intended to break into my
Tianqi Cemetery.
You have
gone too far.
I am justified
to sound the bell.
Who is in the coffin?
Fozhuan.
Fozhuan?
He died?
No hypocrisy.
You are liable
for his death in part.
Were it not for you,
he wouldn’t have left Zhaodu.
How did he die?
Does it make any difference to you?
You know it is Fozhuan.
Please dismiss your disciples.
No.
Fozhuan
is no longer a Tianqi disciple.
He can’t be buried in Tianqi Cemetery.
Do you think I wish to bury him
with those corrupted disciples
and believe in
the nonsense of serving God?
If it is his last wish,
I must help him fulfill it.
Nonsense!
Fozhuan
has abandoned his status
as a disciple of Tianqi.
He won’t be admitted
into Zhaodu alive,
nor be qualified
to be buried in the Tianqi Cemetery.
You can’t break my rules
even if you are the minister.
Your rules are nothing to me.
I must bury him
here today.
Who dares to stop me!
Stop her.
Stop!
Your Majesty!
-Your Majesty!
Great to see you, Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
Fei Tian is…
Fei Tian,
let’s go back.
Okay.
I will go back
after I bury Fozhuan.
I understand your feelings.
If you really understand,
don’t stop me
this time.
You haven’t changed
in these years.
You have always violated the rules
and lost yourself
for anything
relating to Fozhuan.
Yes, exactly.
Don’t you realize that
you have ruined Fozhuan
simply for what you have done.
He used to be my best disciple
and should have become our master.
But he lost his life-time glory
just for you.
Finally, he only ended up
in a mud-covered corpse.
No.
Fozhuan didn’t ruin his life.
He sacrificed his life
simply to deliver God to Zhaodu.
He is more qualified than anyone else
to be buried in the Tianqi Cemetery.
What’s God?
Who are you on earth?
-Retreat from here.
-I…
It is none of your business.
Fei Tian,
who is she?
Your Majesty.
Please take her away.
I won’t leave here.
Master Fozhuan
died just to save me.
If it is so important for him
to be buried in the Tianqi Cemetery,
it will certainly
be my business.
I am Goddess.
What?
Now, in the name of God, I order you
to bury Fozhuan in the Tianqi Cemetery.
Help me.
Hungry?
This is the dish I have prepared for you
at the request of the Marquis.
I know it.
It is called the Last Meal,
isn’t it?
It is never so easy
to kill me through poisoning.
It is a misunderstanding.
The Marquis never uses poisons.
It is a great tonic.
It is a rare chance
for common people to have it.
This tonic works to
make you fitter
and smarter.
Moreover,
all your sensory organs
will become
even more acute.
When the Marquis
is exercising any punishment on you,
you won’t faint away immediately.
I…
What is the sound?
It doesn’t sound like a human being.
It is a sound of a brass bull.
Brass bull?
Exactly.
Cast a big hollow bull
with brasses.
The Marquis
puts a man into the bull’s belly
and a fire basin under it.
When the brass bull is heated up,
the man will have
a miserable experience in it.
His screams
will be amplified via the bull head
and sound like the screams
as you’re hearing.
Listen, listen.
Listen to this sound.
Do you want to see it?
What on earth
does the Marquis want?
Ask him to visit me here
or take me to him.
-Marquis Pingjiang is coming!
-I…
Don’t make a fuss
without the Marquis’ permission.
Just answer his questions.
Got it?
Okay?
Greetings to Your Highness.
Are you Zhu Xi?
What do you want?
Do my daughter and I know you?
What on earth do you want then?
Why are you looking for my daughter?
I am talking to you.
Is there
any misunderstandings between us?
Make it clear if so.
If you have any questions,
just go and ask
Weisheng Yan.
He certainly knows it all.
Buddy!
Is the Marquis deaf?
Hushed!
No?
Do you hear me?
It is too noisy.
What is that?
What are you doing?
You…
What on earth are you doing?
Why is this comb so blunt?
Even if a person is washed
with boiling water for three times,
you still can’t peel his flesh
with this comb.
I will sharpen it right away.
The spiked pile is full
of wooden spikes.
The intestines will be shredded by it.
Moreover,
the tongue hook
must be more carefully designed
as it is put in mouth.
Look at this bone saw.
It is already curled up.
The flesh will be mashed
before it reaches the bone.
Look at those mice.
They are as fat as
you guys are.
Do you think they will be interested
in the human beings upon release?
Do you use torture devices
like this normally?
My reputation
will just be damaged by it.
Take it easy, Your Highness!
I will find a good solution.
Go and check
if he is dead or has confessed.
Yes.
Remember,
be sure to clean away
the blood and flesh
in the brass bull.
He is an important guest here.
Take good care of him.
Yes.
Is it okay to treat an important guest
this way?
Do you think you can hoax
and fool me this way?
Goddess is your daughter.
Who dares to fool you?
Do you know what is most important
between people?
What is that?
It is trust.
It pays heavily
for two strangers
to trust each other.
I have many questions for you.
But without any payment,
how can I trust
what you say?
What nonsense are you talking about?
I hope
we can trust each other
next time when we meet.
Clean up the torture tools
before I come again.
Yes.
Is your daughter
really Goddess?
She isn’t Goddess at all.
She is just an unknown little girl.
Fei Tian,
how dare you disrespect
Goddess that way?
As the chief priest,
you will just harm the reputation
of Tianqi if you pay tribute
before further confirmation.
How did you find her?
You purposefully covered the reason
of His Majesty’s long absence
from the court
simply because of it, right?
It has nothing to do with you.
If she is really Goddess,
has there been anything else more
important to me and the Tianqi Gang
in the past five hundred years?
It is just her allegation.
In the past hundreds of years,
many fake Gods and Goddesses
have been decapitated
on the scaffold of Zhaodu.
There isn’t any God in the world.
It is just
an illusion
of old diehards like you
in the divine palace.
Fei Tian,
how dare you
profane Goddess with such words?
With the arrival of Goddess,
Suchuan will be revived.
It is good news
to be celebrated by all of us.
But you just
doubted about Goddess.
Are you doubting about
His Majesty too?
Can the revival of Suchuan
be realized by
old diehards like you
who keep praying in the divine palace?
It is all because of
His Majesty’s diligence,
the royal guards’ royalty
and also
the Moon Tribe people’s
dedicated efforts in various states.
Only through their efforts
can the vassals
returned to Zhaodu
Revival of Suchuan
and our great success
can never rely on
Gods or ghosts.
Fei Tian,
you keep talking about such nonsense
for fear of His Majesty’s reluctance
to rely on the Moon Tribe
and deprival of your powers
upon Goddess’s return to Suchuan.
I am afraid
it is because you
see the hope
of gaining powers again.
It is Goddess’ power.
It is beyond our control,
and your doubt.
I see.
What do you see?
Master Fozhuan protected me
out of his faith.
They strived for me
just for power.
My father is right.
Why are you looking at me that way?
I didn’t expect you had such an idea.
Do you think
I am just a foolish girl
who is completely ignorant?
Fei Tian isn’t a powerful minister.
She did it just to protect me,
so did the chief priest.
Since my childhood,
the chief priest has taught me
everything about God.
So who do you support?
Who do I support?
Who do you support,
Fei Tian or the chief priest?
As the emperor,
I shouldn’t use anyone simply out of
my personal preference.
I must listen to others’ opinions
and maintain balance.
I see.
I choose Fei Tian.
What?
The chief priest has blind trusts
in Goddess
and can hardly be impartial.
Fei Tian doubts about me.
It is good
because I don’t know
what Goddess really means
and what Goddess can do.
If I can convince Fei Tian,
I will convince myself better.
I didn’t expect
you really didn’t choose someone
out of your personal preference.
What is your plan then?
That is just your Goddess.
She isn’t Goddess of Suchuan.
Nonsense!
This girl is Goddess!
-You said she was…
-Stop quarreling.
Your Majesty!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Allow Linglong to prove
if Goddess is true or false.
How can she prove it?
Ritual of Eternity.
Ritual of Eternity
is the best way
to reveal the trails of God.
If Linglong can illuminate
the Pillar of Eternity of Zhaodu,
she can not only prove herself,
but declare to all people of Suchuan
that Goddess
has come again.
No.
I honor your order, Your Majesty!
I will do it right away.
Immediately!
Your Majesty,
it is not a joke.
I have seen Linglong lighting up the
Pillar of Eternity of the Fire Tribe.
Trust me.
It is time to show to
the unruly vassals
that the emperor of Suchuan
has cooperated
with Goddess
again.
Your Majesty,
how did the chief priest
fool you?
Why are you so stubborn?
Don’t you find
anything strange in it?
Why did the chief priest
suddenly lead you to the Fire Tribe?
Why did Zhu Xi show up there?
Isn’t there any plots
behind so many coincidences?
Moreover,
how can you trust
an unknown little girl
and ignore
the security of Suchuan?
You are Goddess.
Prove to me right now.
I…
Now I am
not very good at it.
Little girl,
you should take a second thought.
If you fail to light up
the Pillar of Eternity
at the Ritual of Eternity,
I will kill you.
Yuan Yi has told me.
I will make preparations.
Good job.
But the Ritual of Eternity
is never a possibility.
Linglong.
Why don’t you agree?
Please allow me to have a try.
Whatever consequences there may be,
I will bear them myself.
Do you think I will care about you?
Why don’t you agree then?
I know
you hate me because of
the death of Master Fozhuan.
But he sacrificed his life
to deliver me to Zhaodu.
So please give me a chance
at least to prove he didn’t die in vain.
Do you think I am angry with you
because of Fozhuan’s death?
If Fozhuan didn’t sacrifice his life
to protect you,
I would have decapitated you
and asked a guard to put it on the spear
to show to everybody of Suchuan.
I want everyone
in Suchuan to see it clearly
and to make sure nobody dares
to play such a trick again.
You won’t scare me!
I won’t give up!
I won’t give up.
Never.
Go and prepare the logs
and kerosene.
The Marquis will come at any time.
Yes.
Don’t cheat me.
Can you really honor
your promise to me?
Otherwise,
I would be the one
in the brass bull.
Jia,
I didn’t lie to you.
My daughter really cured me.
But I can’t promise
she can also cure your daughter.
Goddess
is omnipotent.
Hushed!
Okay, no problem.
I have tried all medicines
to cure my daughter’s disease.
But
none of them worked.
My wife
died early.
We have a child.
Although
she survived the big plaque
17 years ago,
she developed
this strange disease.
She has endured the pains every day
in the past ten years and more.
She feels painful.
But I am even more painful.
So long as you can
cure her disease,
I would do anything for you.
Can I drink some water?
Okay.
I will fetch you some water.
Come on,
Jia,
do you know
a girl named Jin’er?
She is also a native of Pingting
but was lost 17 years ago
possibly
at the age of 18 then.
Well,
I have no idea.
You…
Please think it over.
Her name is Jin’er,
a very pretty girl.
Jin’er,
a native of Pingting
Well, I…
Don’t know.
Impossible!
If a girl is lost,
all our villagers will search for her
at our village.
How is it possible you have no idea?
Pingting has a big population.
It is just a girl who is lost.
Nobody will care even
all residents along a street
are gone.
Many people died at the plague
17 years ago.
The street was full of orphans.
It is not a big deal
that a girl
was lost then.
Have you ever
seen a big monster in Pingting?
A monster with horns on head
and shells on body,
whose screams
are unbearable to the human being.
Well, I…
I don’t know.
Drink water.
Drink some more water.
Somebody must know it other than me.
So long as your daughter,
no, so long as Goddess
saves my daughter,
I will excavate the corpse of anyone
who died some hundred years ago
for you, let alone finding a girl.
Quieter, quieter!
Quieter!
Thank you.
Let’s escape first.
Okay.
Hold on for a little more while.
I will be back tonight.
Take good care of yourself.
Okay.
I hope there is still time for it.
Dispatch the fastest pigeon
to notify various local Tianqi’s priests
and declare
on the Ritual of Eternity.
I must make it known
to all people of Suchuan
that Goddess
will come again soon.
But Fei Tian…
Forget her.
Goddess will naturally dispel
all doubts.
I am afraid the pigeon may be
intercepted by the Moon Guards.
What?
Your new divine music score was
intercepted on the way to Pingting.
My brothers and I were interrogated
by the Moon Guards one by one.
It was hard to finally convince them
it was just a score
instead of any secret signals.
Release all pigeons then.
I don’t think the Moon Guards
can intercept them all.
That is really too much.
Yes.
Goddess?
Go away.
Goddess!
Chief priest!
What can I do for you, Goddess?
May I show you
around the divine palace
and tell you the great achievements
of the historic Gods?
Or…
You don’t have to.
I have come here for one thing.
Bury Master Fozhuan in Tianqi Cemetery.
Well…
Are there any problems?
Tianqi abides by the divine doctrines
and I never dare to violate them.
But Fozhuan
chose to be exiled
and he isn’t qualified
to serve Gods and Goddesses.
Will you dishonor
the order of Goddess?
No, no.
I say he is qualified.
You are just Goddess of me
instead of all people of Suchuan now.
Even Fei Tian…
Is it a deal between you and me?
No, no.
Sorry, Goddess.
Is there any other way out?
Unless
Fozhuan is qualified as a God servant.
Who is a God servant?
Anyone who believes in God
and is enlightened by God can be
buried in Tianqi Cemetery after death.
Moreover,
a God servant enjoys a higher grade
of funeral than the chief priest.
Master Fozhuan is certainly enlightened
and he is a God servant.
He needs to prove himself.
He is dead now.
How can he prove himself?
God will leave a message.
It is just pure empty talk
from you.
Sorry, Goddess.
Goddess,
don’t be angry.
After the Ritual of Eternity,
all the people of Suchuan
will be at your service.
I must get Fei Tian’s approval first.
Am I Goddess
or not?
They just expect me
to receive the approval of Fei Tian.
They are all
so shrewd.
Linglong,
have you visited the chief priest?
How did you know it?
The peach is a tribute
of the Tianqi Gang.
But
I always believe the chief priest loves
to eat it personally.
I…
They keep a close eye on me now.
Fei Tian must feel very angry to know
you left the palace for me.
If my father had such a team,
I would also have a long tail behind me
wherever I go.
Do you like it?
I can organize a team of guards for you.
No, no.
I can protect myself.
Tell me.
What did the chief priest say?
He said nothing.
He is a firm believer
in the divine doctrines
and always abides by the gang rules.
It is never possible
to change his faith.
How did you put it there?
Use a crystal blunderbuss.
What’s up?
Crystal blunderbuss?
It sounds
okay.
But
can you do it?
I…
This apparel
only works to make me an ornament.
May I ask them to…?
Take it for me.
Close your eyes and turn around!
Linglong,
what are you doing?
What are you doing? You scared me.
Please
pull down your dress first.
Wait a minute.
Okay.
Linglong,
it is not the Fire Tribe.
I know.
It is Zhaodu.
It is your territory.
They must obey you.
I finally understand
the worries of your father.
Look.
Within one hundred steps,
I can throw a Stone Freezing Ball
into the bowl-size center of fire.
I have prepared it for 16 years
in order to join the Mountain Team.
Okay.
Then,
please make your orders.
Are you okay?
Don’t speak later.
Your voice is easily identified.
Can you manage it?
Nothing can stop me
in my life.
Let’s go.
We are coming
for two crystal blunderbusses
and two crystal letters.
Show me the approval.
Wait.
What is that?
How dare you ask for them
without knowing the approval?
Don’t you have one?
I can issue one to myself.
Do you have the approval?
Without an approval,
you won’t take anything away from me.
Let’s go first.
Wait a minute.
Bro,
do you still remember how Minister Fei
was angry When His Majesty sneaked
out of the palace?
Of course, I remember.
All the guards
were punished in the imperial city.
My leader was directly dismissed
and returned home for farming
even if he had guarded
the imperial city for decades.
I have a secret message for you.
His Majesty is gone again.
What?
Why did you tell me the message?
I am just a warehouse keeper.
It is no use telling me.
His Majesty is absent
and we can’t get the approval.
But we are in a hurry to deliver
the message and find His Majesty.
You know the truth now but
you refuse to give us
the crystal letters.
If Minister Fei must
hold someone responsible one day,
I am afraid
you may be the one.
Okay, okay,
I will give them to you right away.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪