Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 8
Oh, my God.
If you want this,
I can ask others to get it.
Why should we make so much ado?
I don’t want others to know
it’s us who get this.
Why is this so heavy?
It’s lucky we are not caught.
If anyone discovers
I pretend to be a guard,
they may think I am absurd.
Do you know
how the children in our tribe
speak of me?
They said,
even pigs team up with me,
and enter the Flame Chilling Wall,
they won’t lose a single hair.
Do you know what pigs are?
Yes.
I... I don’t mean that.
Look, the pigs
can do nothing.
But I have another thing.
I need your help.
What will you do again?
It’s not difficult, nor dangerous.
I’m the Emperor of Suchuan.
A man should be prudent and dignified,
act magnanimously,
and keep his words.
I will never do
what I did today.
Come down.
What I ask you to do now
is absolutely magnanimous.
Say it.
Lure Fei Tian away for me.
I want to enter her room.
Linglong.
Do you have any misunderstandings to
the word “magnanimous”?
I...
What are you doing?
You want to play the woman?
I am not Huotu Xin.
Right.
You are not my father.
Only he can see me play the woman.
Anyway,
I won’t do anything sneakily
for you anymore.
It’s not to help me.
It’s to help Master Fozhuan.
Remember, this is the last time.
I thought after you died,
I can finish your wish for you.
I never expected
the old man would aim at me.
It’s fine.
We can’t stay together when we’re alive.
But
we can be buried together after death.
I don’t believe in your God.
So I have to leave you
in the cave at Moon Tribe.
If you can speak now,
you must argue with me.
When you were alive,
I abandoned you.
But I keep you after you died.
Will you blame me?
Fozhuan.
Yuan Yi,
I must make Master Fozhuan
bury in the Tianqi Cemetery.
Fei Tian.
Come in, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Come with me.
I have something to discuss with you.
Your Majesty,
if it’s about the Ritual of Eternity,
I
will never agree with it.
I want to discuss
the matter about Marquis Pingjiang.
Master Fozhuan,
you can rest assured.
I will protect
your beloved Fei Tian for you.
You’re dead,
but I still need your help.
I’m so sorry.
Jia.
Slow down.
Drink slowly.
Jia.
How will you take me out?
Get into its belly.
You
must ask Goddess
to cure my daughter.
Fine.
I am Jia,
living beside the stone monkey,
outside the third gate tower
in southern city
The house with a red door
is my home.
Do you remember?
Yes.
You’re lucky.
The Marquis didn’t remember you
for a whole day.
I’ll go have a check.
Get in it quickly.
Fine.
J...
This is what hope brings.
Even you don’t know whether it’s true,
you will still fight for it
with your life.
A man believes your daughter’s story.
He dares to rescue my prisoner.
If one thousand persons believe it,
they will break my city gate,
and occupy my city.
The greater God is,
The more terrible his killer is.
What are you going to do?
Nothing is more shocking
than killing Goddess
at the house of worship.
This useless Jia
nearly got me killed.
Did you count
how many times is it?
Who’s it?
Did you think of me?
It's you!
Why it's you again?
I’ve stayed there for a whole day,
and ate nothing.
How come
you don’t ask a word
about me?
Why are you staying there?
Do you think I like staying in it?
If I were burned to death by Zhu Xi,
can you see me now?
Since you're so poor,
I will
show my mercy on you again.
Thank you.
I never expected you’ll save me again.
What is my name?
My name.
I’ve told you that.
If you forget,
I will leave now.
Wu...
Wu Yuan
You’re lucky.
Done!
Let’s go!
Aren’t you afraid of Zhu Xi?
Yes.
I’m so afraid that
my hands are trembling.
I’ll try my best to fight out.
Let’s meet at the gate.
Forget it.
You’ve caused Jia’s death.
Don’t implicate me now.
You wait here.
I’ll go clear the way.
Southern city,
outside the third gate tower,
beside the stone monkey,
the house with a red door.
I remember it.
Look at me.
After you see the dead persons’ face,
and look at me again,
do you think I’m more beautiful?
The...
They are killed by you?
Why?
You can’t bear it?
If so,
how can you live in Pingting?
You killed so many people.
Why there is no blood on your clothes?
I am a girl.
Let’s go now!
If we don’t,
when the next shift comes,
we can’t leave anymore.
Alright.
This way.
You run your guts out.
Where are you going?
Leave here far away.
Do you know the way?
When the Earth Fire is out of control,
just run away,
to any direction.
The farther, the better.
Listen.
Do the people in your Fire Tribe
know nothing
unrelated to the Earth Fire?
What do you mean?
We have run around
the prison of Marquis Pingjiang
for eight times.
What?
This is a ring road.
How could it be?
I used to run
by looking at trees and stones.
Here is no tree or stone.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
I thought you have your idea.
I...
Well...
Are you really coming to help me?
Yes.
What can I do for you?
Find my daughter.
Fine. Where to find her?
Zhao...
I see.
These are all your tricks.
Just like you did in the Fire Tribe.
It’s the same.
The purpose is...
To ask me to find Linglong,
right?
The cruel torture in brass bull
is just a disguise.
Even Jia didn’t save me,
you will release me.
Look.
Look at you.
Your clothes are so clean,
without any blood.
Because you didn’t kill anyone.
Those people were just
cooperating with you,
right?
Good!
You get it so fast.
Never believe anyone.
This is the only principle
to live in Pingting.
Keep it in mind.
But Zhu Xi should have known
Linglong was going to Zhaodu long ago.
What are you doing?
The letter in your pocket
was copied by Weisheng Yan
and sent to Zhu Xi long ago.
But
it seems Linglong doesn’t want
you to find her in Zhaodu.
She hopes you to stay at Pingting
and find a girl named Jin’er.
Who’s Jin’er?
Linglong’s mother?
None of your business.
This is Pingting.
You can’t hide any secrets.
Well... Then…
What... What do you want to do?
Why did you save me once and again?
Can’t you make it out?
If so,
just follow me.
You’ll know it one day.
You have a lot
to learn in Pingting.
Maybe when I’m happy one day,
I’ll help you find Jin’er.
Fine.
I’ll follow you.
Really?
Take me a pair of shoes first.
The hunters may come soon.
I can’t do it. It hurts!
I can’t walk anymore.
Do you want shoes or life?
Shoes for keeping life.
Alright.
Wait for me here.
Be quick.
I’m waiting here for you.
I can go now.
You fool!
This is Pingting!
You are alone!
You can’t live here!
I can’t live if I trust you.
This is a letter from my daughter.
How come all of you can read it?
Silly girl.
You’ve grown up.
You’d rather cheat me to Pingting
than taking me to Zhaodu.
Do you think
I can’t protect you anymore?
To be Goddess
is really more important than me?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Chief Priest!
Why are you in such a hurry?
Goddess asked you
to meet her at Tianqi Cemetery.
Tianqi Cemetery?
What to do?
Goddess said,
it’s time to hold a funeral for Fozhuan.
Your Majesty.
Fei Tian,
what do you want to do?
I know as much
as you do.
Goddess.
What does she want to do?
She said,
if she can’t bury Fozhuan
in Tianqi Cemetery,
She’ll make the same platform
to burn herself.
Goddess,
you can’t do that.
Don’t you want to witness
Goddess’ power?
Fozhuan died for his faith.
He gave his life
to Goddess.
This is
the ceremony Goddess welcomes him.
Fozhuan gave his life
to Goddess.
Immortals will give him
the equal glory.
Chief Priest.
This is the sign of Goddess.
Now,
can we bury Master Fozhuan
as a God servant in Tianqi Cemetery?
Yes!
Good.
I agree to hold the Ritual of Eternity.
But
if you can’t prove you're Goddess
at the Ritual of Eternity,
it means you’re a liar,
and you’ll be sentenced to death.
Do you agree?
I agree.
Your aim is perfect!
It’s nothing,
just one of my required skills.
What do you think?
Want to learn?
I can teach you.
Watch carefully.
Like this?
I underrated you.
It’s nothing.
It is just
one of my required skills.
How about
we play a game?
How?
Your turn!
Come on!
Don’t shoot me!
Why don’t you do it by rules?
Rules don’t say I can’t hold it.
Let’s begin!
I’ll see how you shoot.
Would you like me to move closer?
What are you doing?
You break the rules.
Rules don’t say
I can’t move closer.
You are shameless.
You did it first.
Take the apple out.
I
will
not!
Take out or not?
I won’t take out!
Alright. I give up.
You mean it?
A bet is a bet.
What do you want?
Well...
I have to think it over.
It’s a promise from
the Emperor of Suchuan.
I’ll use it at critical moment.
Linglong...
Will you abandon me?
Ling...
I’ve slept for so long.
Little girl.
What... What’s wrong?
I... I’m not cold.
Take it. Take it.
Alright, alright.
Thank you.
By the way,
do
you know the way to Zhaodu?
It doesn’t matter.
This is Pingting.
Sir.
What do you think of this?
My chicken is big and fat.
Come have a look.
Come help me.
I’m coming.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Come on, this way.
Don’t run.
Wait for me.
What are you doing?
Are you blind?
Sorry.
Look at this.
These birds
are good.
Idiot!
Be careful.
You nearly break it!
It's you again, little girl.
You
are looking for me?
Well...
Alright.
I should return this to you.
You take it. Take it.
I…
Alright.
Thank you.
I
have something to do.
I can’t play with you.
You come back
to your father and mother.
Come on.
Well...
What... What’s wrong?
Little girl.
Where is your family?
Did you get lost?
Where is your father?
Died.
Well... Where is your mother?
You...
Don’t cry.
Don’t...
Don’t cry. Don’t cry.
Alright, alright.
Come on.
I’ll give you a twirl.
It’s alright.
Stop crying.
My daughter Linglong
is like you in her childhood.
When she’s crying,
I’d pick her up and hold her high,
and she’ll be fine after a twirl.
Am I right?
Well...
Little girl.
Do you know the way to your home?
What should I do then?
Bun!
Steaming hot buns!
Wear it. Wear it.
I’m not cold.
Wear it.
Here.
Done.
Where are we going?
You are hungry, aren’t you?
I haven’t eaten anything for two days.
Here, sir.
Your buns!
Thank you.
Wait for a moment.
Boss.
Sir.
What do you want?
Your buns
are bought with money, right?
You must be joking.
At my stall,
five coins can buy
two meat buns
or six vegetable buns.
See?
What do you want?
I
don’t have money.
But
here.
What do you mean?
Give me ten buns.
Take this blood stone as proof.
According to the rule of our Fire Tribe,
I will return ten buns
within ten days
and take back my blood stone.
Let’s go.
I know
ten buns don’t worth
my blood stone,
but
it's a special situation.
I have no other idea.
It's done!
Go!
You beggar!
You fool!
Don’t beat him! Don’t!
Go!
You can refuse the deal.
Why you beat her?
You bastard!
Don’t beat me!
You even beat a kid. Are you a man?
You bastard!
You beat a kid!
Your food
doesn’t match my blood stone.
We won’t eat it.
Let’s go.
In the future,
don’t eat anything
given by such kind of people.
Do you know?
Is this yours?
What is it?
Is this a picture?
It is a person.
It looks like me.
Look, the hair is like mine.
Look,
is it like me?
You still don’t think so.
The eyebrow is like mine, too.
It is drawn by you?
Did you know me long ago?
Look,
the hairstyle is rare in
Pingting.
Wanted Reward: Ten coins.
Reward:
Ten coins.
I am wanted.
It’s hunting.
Make way!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Little girl.
Remember,
life is more important than money.
Little girl.
Come here.
Go buy medicines for your mother.
Don’t you leave?
Want my help?
Who are you?
In Pingting,
don’t believe anyone,
including kids and dogs.
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪