Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 3
So,
the light in the Palace of Flames
is because of me?
Only when the power of the Goddess
is felt,
the Pillar of Eternity
gives out light like that
to show the existence of the Goddess.
Sixteen years ago, when you were born,
it gave out light once.
When you transformed,
it proved again that you’re the Goddess.
If you are really the king of Suchuan,
why did you conceal it?
Simply speaking,
the current situation
of Suchuan is complicated.
Many people want to replace me.
That’s why you need me.
But that’s not the only reason.
If you are the king,
where is your queen?
I don’t have one yet.
Not yet?
Besides,
did I look beautiful
when I transformed?
Yes.
That’s the prettiest thing
I’ve ever seen.
Thing?
No.
The prettiest person.
Well,
did I look better than
what I look like now?
What you look like now
is the most beautiful.
Stop!
What?
Don’t you want to find your daughter?
Who on earth are you?
What do you want?
To find your daughter.
She’s not here.
Yeah.
But so long as you’re my hostage,
she is sure to come here for you.
Linglong,
do you believe
all that I say?
Em.
That’s why I take you here.
To see the Glory Rock.
Only when standing here and
looking at it,
do I know if I’m really
willing to leave here.
Every time I stand here,
I can hear it whispering.
It’s the echo of the strikes that
Earth Fire did on it
in the past five hundred years.
It’s the memory that lights up
the life of people in Fire Tribe.
I only saw records
on the Flame Chilling Wall
in the old scrolls.
But the shock I feel when I see it
is more vivid than when I read
the words in the scrolls.
That’s not the real Flame Chilling Wall.
This is.
Every name on it
is a wall that prevents
the Earth Fire from going further.
Here is the real
Flame Chilling Wall of Fire Tribe.
Only warriors who have
fought with the Earth Fire
are qualified to engrave their names
on the Glory Rock.
But do you know?
On the rock,
there will no longer exist
my father’s name.
Maybe there won’t be mine.
If I’m really the Goddess,
then
can I put out the Earth Fire?
I don’t know.
But there must be a way.
All the time,
to find the Fire Demon,
put out Earth Fire,
and carve my name on Glory Rock
are the biggest wishes
of my life.
But I want to thank you.
If you hadn’t come here
and tell them I was the Goddess,
maybe I
would have been treated as
a monster like my mother,
or even
would have been killed.
No. You wouldn’t.
You are the Goddess
who will not be hurt by mortals.
Yes.
My father
won’t let anyone hurt me.
In Zhaodu, your imperial city,
is there a Glory Rock, too?
If I’m really the Goddess
who can save Suchuan,
will my name
be engraved on it, too?
There isn’t a Glory Rock in Zhaodu.
But
I’ll build one for you.
I’ll build a Glory Rock
that only belongs to you.
I believe you.
I’ll let everyone know
I’m not a monster.
Next,
the most difficult thing is
to persuade my father.
Let’s go.
Linglong.
Tanmiao?
Are you here alone?
You got better?
Who is he?
He...
He is my savior.
Don’t tell anyone
that you saw us.
Remember?
Yes.
Hush.
Just stay here
and wait for my father...
Come in.
When my father comes back,
I’ll explain to him.
Come.
Sit down.
You must be hungry.
If your father doesn’t agree,
will you go with me?
He will agree.
There is no room for me here.
He won’t let me be wronged.
It’s because your people
don’t really know about you.
Soon
they will get to know you again.
I think so, too.
Why don’t you sit down?
You must be tired these days.
Would you like to...?
Who made my bed this messy?
I... I’m not like this usually.
It must be my father.
Hold on.
Wait a minute.
It’s done.
Don’t worry.
It is messy
but clean.
It’s fine.
I had a good rest.
I’m not tired.
Well, it’s up to you.
Are...
Are you uncomfortable?
I.. I’m okay.
I just...
just...
It’s the first time...
the first time...
The first time what?
It’s the first time
I go into the Goddess’s room.
Yes.
I used to believe that
the Goddess should be worshipped
in Tianqi Temple.
Isn’t it surprising?
I used to believe that
the emperor should be worshipped
on the throne.
But I didn’t expect
to see an emperor
in a room of a country girl.
Yes.
Did you sleep well?
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
What are you afraid of?
I’m not a bad guy.
I won’t hurt you.
Don’t come over!
What if I must?
What do you want to do?
You can’t do it.
What do you want?
There must be a misunderstanding.
Well...
Who are you?
I’m here to help you
and your daughter.
I don’t believe you.
Don’t be a stingy man.
If I don’t coax you,
will you go with me?
Trust me.
Don’t go back to Fire Tribe.
It’s for your own good.
At present, Fire Tribe,
is the most dangerous place
for you and your daughter in Suchuan.
The Leader of your tribe believes
Linglong is a monster.
He won’t let you go.
Maybe Linglong
has already been locked up.
No need to care about our tribe.
Fine.
Even if you’re not afraid of them,
I’m telling you
the men of Marquis Pingjiang
will be here soon.
What monkeys?
It’s a praise to you Fire Tribe members
to say you’re ignorant.
You only know Earth Fire.
Let’s just say
Zhu Xi, Marquis Pingjiang,
is the “Earth fire” of Suchuan.
Besides,
in this world,
there is no Flame Chilling Wall
to stop him.
What will he do?
Take your daughter away.
Why does he do this?
Why?
Don’t ask why.
Are you going to reason with him?
Tell me something useful,
such as the conversation
between only you two,
so Linglong can believe me.
I’ll bring her here for you.
I don’t buy your words.
Okay.
Then go and see yourself.
Why is there no food?
Yuan Yi.
♪Together with you I want♪
♪To see the end of the world
and the shore♪
♪Know each other heart to heart♪
♪That doesn’t seem too hard♪
Thank you
for finding me.
♪How long the time is♪
♪My look and my heart♪
♪Listen♪
♪I’m so lonely without his love♪
Don’t move.
I’ll go for a look.
Go and search!
Leader?
Take Linglong away.
Leader, listen to me.
Take them away!
I...
Chi Fang.
Listen to me.
It’s not what you think.
Chi Fang.
Linglong.
It’s Leader’s order.
Well...
Close the gate.
Be at ease.
My father will find me
at the cost of ruining the tribe.
Uncle Xin!
Tanmiao.
Uncle Xin.
What happened?
Linglong...
Linglong was taken away by Leader.
Where are they taking her to?
I don’t know.
Leader and his men
were very fierce.
And,
there is also a man.
That bastard!
Who are they?
The men of Marquis Pingjiang
will be here soon.
Their purpose
is to take your daughter away.
Tanmiao,
go back and tell Leader that
strangers are coming
to take Linglong away.
Let him hide Linglong quickly.
Do you hear it?
Go now.
Okay.
It is the territory of Fire Tribe.
No matter who you are,
we don’t welcome strangers.
Are people of Fire Tribe
all rude to guests?
It’s really impolite
to come here rashly.
Okay.
I’ll give you
a gift.
I’ll repeat it.
Fire Tribe
doesn’t welcome any stranger.
Is it the Fire Spear?
I don’t seem
to know how to use it.
I still like to use
a knife.
You’ll be my gift of greeting.
Let’s go.
Take us to Fire Tribe.
Don’t leave anyone.
Women and children, go into the wall.
Bring enough food.
Don’t come out without my order.
Don’t be careless.
Leader.
Is it all done?
Yes.
They are locked in a deserted mine
of the ancestors.
No one can find them.
There is enough food and water.
Don’t worry.
It’s just these few days.
They will be able to survive.
Leader.
You’re making a big deal out of it.
What are you afraid of?
I don’t know.
Maybe I worry too much.
Did you find Huotu Xin?
No.
Who are they? Why are they here?
Let go of me.
Mother.
Mother!
Help me!
Tanmiao. Tanmiao.
-Madam. Don’t go. Don’t go.
-Mother!
-Stop her!
-Who are you?
What do you want?
Help me!
Mother!
Who are you?
Why do you hurt my people?
Are you the leader?
Yes.
I’m here for someone on behalf of
Zhu Xi, Marquis Pingjiang.
As long as you don’t seek troubles,
I’ll just take the person away.
I won’t cause you any trouble.
Otherwise...
Huotu Xin, what are you...?
I only want the person I want.
Take her to me,
and everyone will be fine.
Who do you want?
I don’t know.
If there is such a person,
I’ll release her.
Okay.
Tell me.
Who lit up the Pillar of Eternity?
The Pillar of Eternity?
What’s that?
I don’t know.
Do you know what it is?
I don’t know. I don’t know.
Who made that light?
Or
among your people,
does someone feel
something wrong in his body recently?
Bring the person to me.
You see?
All our people are here.
Is there the one you are looking for?
They are looking for
a girl named Linglong.
Why are you so slow?
She must have gone.
I’m fast enough.
You didn’t watch her carefully.
Don’t blame me.
You are here to arrest someone.
If you don’t catch her,
go to explain to Marquis Pingjiang
yourself.
Did you hear that?
A girl named Linglong.
If you have any
news about her,
tell me.
Or you will
end up like him.
Be polite
to these people.
If it’s not them,
your grandparents would have been
burned to death by Earth Fire.
Are you okay?
Don’t be afraid.
You have me.
You won’t die.
Just look for the person you want.
Don’t cause troubles
and ruin the reputation of
Marquis Pingjiang.
The girl you are talking about
is also the one we are looking for.
We don’t know where she went.
I swear.
Okay.
I believe you.
Then I’ll wait here.
You’ll help me get her back.
Everyone.
Go get Linglong back.
Wait.
The men go to find Linglong while
women and children stay here.
Stay with me.
Are you okay?
How do you feel?
What happened?
Leader.
They can’t move.
Father.
Help me!
I can’t move.
Don’t hurt them.
I rushed here
and I’m already exhausted.
If I fall down,
I can’t protect them.
So,
you must
be quick.
Okay.
Look for her!
Take Linglong back for me!
Don’t worry.
You lit up the Pillar of Eternity.
Zhaodu must have got the news.
The Chief Priest knows I’m here.
They will come soon to help us.
I’m not worried.
I am recalling.
Recalling what?
How did I become the Goddess?
Or
how do I use the power of the Goddess?
Do you know it?
In fact,
being chosen by Goddess
is only one condition.
To complete
the fusion with Goddess
is not easy.
Do you believe in Goddess?
I...
I even don’t know what Goddess is.
It’s okay.
When we go back to Zhaodu,
I’ll explain it to you.
But I can’t wait for that time.
My father hasn’t come to rescue me.
Something must have happened to him.
Do you know
why I transformed that night?
It may be because
you were burned by Earth Fire,
and you lost consciousness.
Then Goddess could temporarily
take over your body
and protect you.
I lost consciousness, and then
Goddess came to protect me.
Knock me out,
and the power of Goddess
can be activated.
Then we can go out.
No way.
I can’t do that.
Why?
You said that
your bloodline of the Yuan family
is linked to the mind of the Goddess.
You are the only one
who can communicate with Goddess.
Are you afraid that I’ll hurt you?
No.
I don’t.
I can’t do something
offensive to Goddess.
Absolutely not.
Fine.
You can’t.
Then I’ll knock myself out.
Linglong.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Let go.
Calm down.
Linglong.
Leader?
Don’t cry.
It’s fine. There, there.
Now you trust me?
Why didn’t you tell on me?
You still don’t believe me?
I went to your house
and got the clothes.
I like it.
Change it.
Look at the blood stains.
I care about you so much.
What are you doing?
When your daughter is here,
you won’t want her
to see you being like this.
Where is Linglong?
Where is she?
I don’t know.
But
as long as you are here,
she will definitely come.
Can your wound be cured
by your daughter?
She doesn’t know medicine.
How can she cure me?
What are you doing?
I have a crush on him.
Be nice to him.
Leader.
It isn’t the way back to the city.
Where are you taking us to?
We won’t go back.
And you can’t go back.
Tomorrow
there is a boat from Weisheng
in Pingting.
It’s right by White Forest Lake.
I did the Flammable Stone business
with them.
I intended to
ask your father to help me.
But it seems that he can’t.
I’ll try to get you on board.
Never come back.
Why?
Where’s my father?
What happened?
A group of terrible strangers came
and asked to take you away.
The women and children
in the tribe become hostages.
Your father
is also in their hands.
Linglong.
You know.
Your father never wants to
see you have any accident.
So,
you have to leave quickly.
Go as far as possible.
Who are those strangers?
It is said that they are
the men of Marquis Pingjiang.
Marquis Pingjiang, Zhu Xi?
Do you know him?
Will he obey your orders?
Who are you?
If it’s really Zhu Xi,
I’m afraid it won’t be easy
for you to escape.
No way.
I must go back to rescue my father.
Linglong.
Will you be of any help?
Leader.
You haven’t seen their means.
It’s not a game for kids.
Linglong.
You know your father’s temper.
If you don’t go,
when it’s late,
I can’t help you.
As for your father,
I will find another way to save him.
Listen to me.
Kid.
If you don’t say,
I won’t force you.
I treated you that way before
is because I had to protect
our people.
Please forgive me.
But from today,
please
protect Linglong well.
Can you promise me?
I respect Linglong’s wish.
I can’t go.
Linglong.
If you let me go first,
and then save my father,
even if you succeed,
our men are still here.
They will come back to revenge.
Linglong.
You...
Anyway, I’m half an outsider.
What I do
has nothing to do with Fire Tribe.
So,
my father
will be saved by myself.
From now on,
I’m no more a member of Fire Tribe.
No matter what you do,
I’ll support you.
Leader.
Tell me
what means they used.
It’s her.
Release them all.
Release them.
Great!
Go home with Mother.
Hurry up.
Are you okay? Go quickly.
Go home.
Go fast.
And him.
Him?
Someone of us has a crush on him.
So...
He can’t go.
Bring the girl here.
Okay.
Who are you?
Why were you looking for me?
Who dares to be rude to me?
Little girl.
Don’t be presumptuous in front of me.
Since you came to me,
you should have known who I am.
If I’m not willing to come here,
can the people of Fire Tribe
catch me?
Your name.
Is that all?
That’s all.
Here is my silver bullet!
Linglong!
If I let him control me,
it means I’m unconscious.
If I’m in danger,
the power of the Goddess will
protect me.
Right?
Theoretically
it is.
Okay.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪