Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 6
Master.
It smells so good.
Thank you.
It’s okay.
Xiao.
It’s really delicious.
Linglong.
You didn’t lie to me.
It’s really good.
Father.
Mother was like
Yin Zhuang, right?
What?
If her brother hears this,
he’ll freak out again.
Father.
You didn’t like anyone
in the tribe,
and you couldn’t do that.
But now you’re out,
have you ever thought of
finding me a mother?
You...
What about your mother?
I’m sure she would wish us happiness.
I think
you should think about it.
She’s going to get married.
What?!
Did you get it wrong?
Intentional, I said.
Well...
The ship owner was intentional.
I didn’t mention Yin Zhuang.
Why are you nervous?
Leave me alone.
Yin Zhuang.
You really go to Pingting
to get married?
Yes.
My future husband
is waiting for me in Pingting.
Have you
seen him?
Do you like him?
No.
Then why do you want to marry him?
Because
he is the richest man
in Suchuan.
Rich...
Then you’ll marry him?
What’s the money for?
You’ll see
when you’re out.
Money can
do a lot of good.
Don’t worry.
I’m here.
You don’t need money.
Guy.
I told you.
We’re
not going to Zhaodu.
Father.
No one mentioned this.
I’m afraid of his bad memory.
So tell me.
If we don’t go to Zhaodu,
where should we go?
Suchuan is so big.
There are so many places to go.
Linglong will return to Zhaodu with me.
No.
I’m afraid of death.
She must go with me.
Just stop that.
Come on, sit down.
After this meal,
we can go wherever we want.
Merry meet, merry part.
As a man,
how can you only care
about your own safety?
Is it wrong for me
to fear death?
Who will take care of my daughter
if I’m gone?
You’re right.
We all know that.
But please stop fighting
and just eat.
She must
go with me.
She is my daughter.
It’s not up to you.
Xiao.
Huotu Xin.
Your soup is really delicious.
I want to have another bowl,
okay?
Your Majesty.
Don’t worry.
What’s the difference
between you and
those who come to grab her?
You’ll scare them.
It’s no use arguing.
I still have to decide
my own business.
Linglong.
Don’t worry, Father.
No matter what,
you are the most important.
You’re my top priority.
Linglong.
You told me...
Just stop.
I can’t see my father get hurt anymore.
Yeah, that’s
what a daughter should say.
The rabbit is okay.
Delicacy
must be cherished.
God gave it to us.
We can discuss everything
after the meal,
right?
Try it.
No.
Have a bite.
Try it.
-Here it is, Father.
-Here it is.
-The master baked it.
-Eat more.
After all these work,
you’re not full, right?
Only when you are full
can you protect Linglong,
right?
Thank you, Master.
Your Majesty.
No.
I’ll eat the rest.
Try it.
It’s delicious.
If you are sleepy, go to sleep.
I’ll be watching.
I’m not sleepy.
I have to watch my daughter.
As the saying goes,
the concern of the thief is even worse.
Right?
You’re awake?
Master.
You said to look at me,
but you slept deeper than me.
Yin Xiao.
Have you been here all night?
We can’t let up.
Yes.
Sleep in the wild
for the first time, right?
I never thought that
I could fall asleep out of my bed.
Yin Zhuang also slept so soundly.
She’s nothing like a squeamish girl.
Her suffering
doesn’t show on her face.
Is that why
she wants to marry the rich guy?
You’re too young.
You don’t understand.
I want to see the Evil.
I’ll take you there.
Master.
What’s on the other side?
It’s the guard ring,
the barrier guarding Zhaodu.
So what’s down here?
Maybe
only Evil Soul
knows that.
Master Fozhuan.
What’s
Goddess?
The Goddess
is the guardian sent by the Immortals
to Suchuan.
What’s
her power?
Can she put out the Earth Fire?
So
why does Suchuan need Goddess?
Even if you could put out
the Earth Fire,
of all the sufferings in this world,
could only one Goddess save them?
So the power of the Goddess
is not important.
Yesterday,
you saw me rise from the dead
and scatter enemies with Fire, right?
What do you feel?
I...
Hope.
Because I think
you can save my father.
Yeah.
At that time,
you didn’t know where your father was,
whether he was alive
or dead.
But
you’ll keep looking for him.
Because you believe in a power
and see hope.
Hope
is the power of Goddess.
I think
I got it.
Oh.
Come here.
I’ll tell you a secret.
You know what.
It’s all a lie.
Shh.
Keep your voice down.
Look.
The knife
goes in here
and out here.
I had already
shrunk down to this side.
The blood is fake.
Well...
Then...
What about the Fire?
I secretly sprinkled
fire powder on him.
Only
a little spark...
So
you can’t spell at all.
I’m an ordinary person,
so there are no spells.
But if you believe it,
it’s true.
Over the years,
with these little tricks,
I’ve really saved
a lot of lost people.
Oh, yeah,
and this.
Look at it.
Yuan Yi’s Star Map.
You...
Look at this.
What you saw before
was all the phantom it projected.
It’s made by
the descendants of Li,
the only one in Suchuan.
Even Yuan Yi was cheated by you.
His Majesty can do it.
But only on the Calculator,
that’s the real miracle.
Master.
You got kicked out of
Tianqi Sect
because of these heresy?
How can you believe these rumors?
I...
I really left on my own will.
And,
Fei Tian and I
are in love.
I think
I understand your words.
You are a smart girl.
Oh, and
I’ll keep the secret.
You learned so fast.
Remember.
Mystery
is the first rule of
being a Goddess.
Linglong.
Is my father awake?
Yuan Yi and my brother went
to find Linglong.
Aren’t you worried?
What to worry about?
Didn’t you hear her words?
I’m her
first priority.
And I tell you.
Linglong,
whatever she decides,
no one could change it.
Aren’t you afraid
she’ll change her mind?
I tell you.
Kid.
You can’t force her,
the more you force her,
the more she’ll turn against you.
So,
you need to give her some space.
Oh, you know how to raise a kid.
When you have kids,
you’ll understand.
I want to
have a daughter
like Linglong.
Have you considered it?
I’ve been thinking your words.
As a Goddess,
I have no choice,
but I can’t let my father
get hurt again.
Linglong.
I’m here.
You’ll be safe.
I mean,
I’m leaving my father.
As long as he’s with me,
he’s in danger.
Only on the way to Zhaodu,
there are so many blockers.
In Zhaodu,
it’ll be more dangerous.
I’ll go to Zhaodu with you,
but my father
can’t go.
Yin Xiao.
Can you grant me a request?
Before I truly become the Goddess,
please protect my father
and don’t let him get hurt.
Okay.
What’s your plan?
I...
I have an idea.
How dare he come here!
Don’t worry.
He can help us.
How long have they been there?
Why haven’t they come back?
The radishes are all boiled to a pulp.
They’ll be back soon.
It’s not far from here.
Again?
Yin Zhuang.
Wait here for me.
I’ll go find them.
I’ll go with you.
Father.
Get up here.
The trackers are here again.
How did you get up there?
Don’t get on their boat.
If you don’t come up, it’s too late.
The trackers are over there.
Right?
Well...
Get up here.
We’ll talk about it up here.
Get up first.
OK, let’s go.
Where is Linglong?
Don’t worry.
They’re safe.
Come with me.
Hurry up.
Wait a moment.
I’ll go get them.
I’m sorry.
Father.
He’ll be furious.
With Yin Xiao there,
he’ll be fine.
You left him a letter.
Your father will understand you.
When you see him again,
he’ll know
you are right.
Yes,
definitely.
I worked hard
to get her here,
and you let her go?
She’ll be much helpful in Zhaodu
than in Pingting.
What’s your plan?
Weisheng Yan.
As the richest man in Suchuan,
why don’t you spend more money
to buy a good smoke?
As a girl,
why don’t you bring a handkerchief?
She’s your bride?
Beautiful?
But her brother is fierce.
Yeah.
If her brother knows that
you are Weisheng Yan,
happy event will also become a funeral.
Since he would marry his sister to me,
he would never ruin his career
over such a trifle.
He is now in favor of His Majesty,
will he care about you?
Yin and Yuan teamed up again.
Even you didn’t expect it, right?
Or,
when I followed him,
you knew he was His Majesty?
I don’t know everything.
Remember?
This time, even I
almost got killed.
Now that you’ve let her go,
what about what you promised me?
She’s no use to you now.
Only if she’s recognized by Zhaodu
can she be valuable.
How do I explain to Zhu Xi
when I go back?
Her father is here.
This Fire Tribe man
is your answer to Marquis Pingjiang.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Linglong.
Are you okay?
I don’t know if
my father’s used to
Pingting’s food.
If you regret it,
I’ll send someone to take him to Zhaodu.
No.
Thank you.
When you go through a real separation,
you’ll grow up.
And then,
you’ll find that
all the gatherings and separations
are wonderful.
Fei Tian is coming soon.
Master, are you nervous?
Why me?
Ah.
I never
thought of seeing her again.
Has she told you about me?
I only heard your name
mentioned by the Chief Priest
when he was teaching the little ones.
He still remembers me.
Tell me
your story.
My story
is very old-fashioned.
We
fought and fought
and finally fell in love.
For her,
I almost
broke
all the rules.
Although Fei Tian
is a woman,
she has great ambitions.
At that time, she had just
found her footing in the court.
Tianqi couldn’t tolerate
her Moon Tribe growing stronger.
My relationship with her
has become more of an obstacle.
Later, I realized that
only by leaving her
can I make her.
And then?
And here we are.
Over the past ten years,
I’ve been traveling in Suchuan
and preaching.
She
became the first Moon Prime Minister
of Suchuan.
No wonder Fei Tian
has never considered
marriage.
I thought she was all about politics.
Fozhuan.
I’ll preside over your marriage
back to Zhaodu.
After so many years,
I don’t expect this.
Have you never thought about
marrying her?
As long as
I can
see her wings one more time,
falling from the sky
to my side,
I’ll be satisfied.
Run.
Run!
Master Fozhuan.
Fozhuan.
You...
You’re lying again?!
Master, you know spells, right?
Stand up.
Master.
Go.
What about your spells?
Stand up quickly.
I can.
Fozhuan said...
How can you play tricks?
Kill the man.
Take the woman.
Stop.
Fei Tian.
Seeing His Majesty,
kneel down.
His Majesty.
Your Majesty.
It’s you again.
What are you doing?
Where is Linglong?
She has gone.
Gone?
You...
Where did you get her?
Don’t be angry
and allow me to make something clear.
Your daughter left
on her own will.
And,
she begged me to do her a favor.
Look.
Fire Tribe script.
Linglong’s handwriting.
I can’t imitate this, right?
Oh, by the way,
the Yin siblings did their part.
Is that clear?
A show
of solidarity with you,
it must be hard for them.
Linglong.
Daughters are all like this.
Go out.
Get married.
They’ll leave their parents
sooner or later.
Let it go.
Where is Yin Xiao?
Get him over here.
He’s not awake yet.
I can’t believe
you guys
are stronger.
OK.
I believe you.
You
untie me first.
I can’t do that.
You’d better put the letter away,
in case Marquis Pingjiang gets it.
What do you mean?
We’re almost at Pingting.
What are you doing?
I warn you.
I know who you are.
Weisheng Yan.
You...
I’m not scaring you.
If you do anything to me,
I tell you,
you’ll come to a bad end.
Believe it or not.
I tell you,
I’m not scaring you.
How do you tell?
I know now.
Then I can’t tolerate you.
Are you awake?
Where are we?
It seems
we’ve arrived.
-Here is...
-Shh...
You’re awake.
You’ve been waiting at the door?
Yes.
I don’t dare to bother you.
Why stun us?
I’m really sorry.
I’m afraid that the Fire Tribe man
learned that his daughter had left him
and gone to Zhaodu,
he would make trouble on the boat.
In order to avoid
collateral damage to you,
I made this move.
Linglong has gone to Zhaodu?
As a servant,
you’re too bold.
That’s why
I’m fighting for my life.
You
hated me so badly,
and were forced to board the ship.
I’m afraid that
if something happened on the way,
I can’t safely bring you to Pingting
to meet my host.
Excuse me.
Is this the home of Weisheng Yan?
Yes.
My host has been detained on the road.
Please forgive.
Where is Huotu Xin?
He’s in the guest room.
Don’t worry.
Take me to see him.
Okay.
Follow me.
I’ll be back soon.
Take care of Miss Yin Zhuang.
-Yes.
Please.
Right here.
Where’s he?
Help.
Help me.
Lord.
Marquis is waiting for you.
Help.
What happened?
Where’s he?
I...
I don’t know.
Well...
He was just screaming for food.
Damn.
Go find him.
Yes.
I’m really sorry.
I didn’t know he was in such a hurry.
What for?
I gave him Linglong’s letter.
This Fire Tribe man
is very brutal,
not as good as you.
You saw what he did to me.
I can’t bear the guilt of
stealing his daughter.
But don’t worry.
As long as he’s in Pingting,
my host would
find him.
We’ll get him back sooner or later.
Of course you can find him.
It’s your place,
right,
Weisheng Yan?
I dare not deceive you.
You condescend
along the way,
pretending to be the ship owner,
pretending to be humble,
for what?
You’re joking.
Even if I don’t pretend,
you’re still honorable.
I’m still humble.
To observe us.
You’re so wise.
What’s your conclusion?
Yin Zhuang is worth marrying,
and Yin Xiao
is worthy of support.
Do you think
I’ll marry my sister
to you?
Please come with me.
Please see.
That’s
our vault,
and this key
is the only way into it.
Then you have to put it away.
Even a man
can disappear in your house,
let alone
the little key.
You’re joking.
Even if an outsider gets this key,
it is useless.
Because the lock of the vault
is bound to my blood,
and cannot be opened
by the key alone.
And I’m
the only Weisheng
in this world.
So,
my child will be
the second person in this world
who can use this key.
Weisheng Yan.
Your most precious thing
is hanging on the mountain,
and mine
should be living in freedom.
You trade it for Yin Zhuang,
then you’re underestimating her.
In three days,
bring Huotu Xin here.
I’ll take her out of Pingting.
Live in freedom?
That’s what Yin Zhuang wants?
What’s that golden thing?
Miss.
That’s host’s vault.
Vault?
Yes.
Weisheng Yan...
Yin Zhuang’s expectation
of marrying Weisheng Yan,
as the ship owner,
is clear to me.
Is she expecting me?
Of course not.
She hasn’t even seen me.
So,
what does she want?
If you insult Yin Zhuang one more time,
I’ll cut your tongue.
Our marriage
was appointed by your father
before he died.
As her brother,
in spite of your father’s will,
you ruined the life she desires
just for your own selfishness.
Who insults Yin Zhuang?
Have you ever wondered
what is her happiness?
Yin Xiao’s sister for a lifetime?
Mrs. Weisheng?
Or
both?
I’ll treat her well.
Weisheng Yan.
Why do you want to marry her?
To
keep it for my child.
I built the vault there,
holding the only key
in my hand.
You think it’s foolproof?
Of course not.
If Marquis Pingjiang
wants what’s inside,
he doesn’t need the key.
You’re right.
No matter how much money
I hide in there,
it’s not on me.
I’m always
a humble civilian.
The only reason I still own it
is because
he needs me
to generate more money for him
until I’m not useful
anymore.
When that day comes,
I’m afraid my blood
will be mixed
in the roadside mud.
So
I need your surname.
My fortune
can help the Yins
return to the top of Suchuan.
In this world,
the strongest bond
is mutual need.
Her child
will have the most wealth
in Suchuan.
At that time,
only you can protect him.
But what you said,
I don’t care at all.
Yin Zhuang.
Mr. Yin.
This way, please.
Yin Zhuang.
Xiao.
Look over there.
Do you know what that is?
Weisheng Yan’s vault.
You already know that?
Then guess
how much money is there?
Is that
important?
He’d have to be rich
to build
a vault like this.
I never thought
his home
would be like this.
Xiao.
You wanted to
tell me something?
No.
You met Weisheng Yan, right?
I thought
you had a falling out
with him.
Xiao.
Please get along well with him.
Or I’ll be caught
between my husband and you.
By the way.
Where’s Huotu Xin?
He has left.
Left?
To Zhaodu?
I’m not sure about this,
but I’ll find out.
Linglong entrusted us.
We can’t ignore him.
Xiao.
You helped Linglong leave?
If Linglong
is the Goddess,
then going to Zhaodu
is her only choice.
Linglong
is really a great child.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪