♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 13=
You think
I’ll beat you just for this?
I’m this mean
in your mind?
Of course not!
Look at me.
I’m being childish again.
You’re the generous
Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
You’ll forgive me, right?
Now,
it’s my turn to draw.
I thought you would let me go.
It turns out to be
an idiotic idea again.
Come on.
Narrow-minded Lord
will definitely make me ugly
and take me out to the street.
How will I keep my image
if anyone recognizes me?
Or, I should just ask him
to make it as ugly as he can
until I can’t even recognize myself.
My Lord, I think…
Shut up.
Done.
Open your eyes.
Time to watch the dragon boat racing.
Have a look.
Sachet.
Sachet, pendant.
Mother, I want a cake.
Mother.
Okay.
Ayu,
you are selling flowers instead of fish.
Baldhead,
will you buy some flowers
for Yuxiang?
Young Master Zhiyong died.
You can take this chance to get her.
Am I that bad?
Zhiyong died not long ago.
You ask me to do this?
If I buy flowers,
I should send them to Zhiyong’s grave.
Go away. No flower for you.
Then you can’t sell them to others.
Move.
-Stop.
-Ruin them.
Don’t!
-Raining flowers.
-Stop.
What are you doing?
-I’ll ruin all of them.
-Come on.
Stop doing it!
You can sell nothing.
What were you doing?
Caterpillars you’re most afraid of.
Caterpillars…
Baldhead.
Longhair, come to help me.
Okay.
I can’t take them out.
-Baldhead.
-Scratch my legs.
-Take off your pants.
-My legs are itching, too.
Take off my pants in public?
Well...
Make a way out. Stop fooling me.
Here, beat him with this.
Okay.
Why beat me?
I’m beating the caterpillars.
Do you feel better?
Yes.
Good.
Come on.
You’ll pay for this!
Be gentle!
Well, don’t run.
Here, here.
Be gentle!
I’ll buy all of these flowers.
They’re not worth so much.
I know you!
You know me?
You know I am...
You’re Yuchi who saved me.
It must be you!
Although I didn’t see you clearly,
I won’t make it wrong.
These flowers are ruined.
I can’t take your money.
If you want flowers,
I’ll bring you some fresh ones.
It doesn’t matter.
Ayu,
can I take you to a place?
Where?
You’ll know it.
Okay.
I haven’t been here for a long time.
It hasn’t changed at all.
Yuchi, look.
Fireworks.
How beautiful!
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
At this moment,
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
how I wish to embrace you.
♪I meet you in every dream♪
But I can only watch you like this.
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
Yuchi, do you like fireworks?
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
I also like fireflies all over the sky,
and flowers all over the ground.
I love stars after the rain the most.
I like what you mentioned, too.
There is none.
What’s wrong?
I just recall that Zhiyong and I
came here to watch the stars
and we inscribed characters on the wall.
I’ll find them.
Look, they are still here.
(Beauty Jun)
This Beauty Jun is me.
(Brave Wise Man)
This Brave Wise Man is Zhiyong.
I don’t know
what we were thinking then.
This city wall was built by the court.
He shouldn’t have
inscribed characters with you.
It’s damage to public property.
We were young then.
A man and a woman
shouldn’t stay together alone.
From now on,
you can only come here with me.
But you’re a man, too.
I’m Qingqing’s brother,
of course yours, too.
It’s cold here.
Don’t stay for long.
“It’s cold here. Don’t stay for long.”
I heard this somewhere else.
It’s cold here.
Don’t stay for long.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Let’s go.
(Beauty Jun Brave Wise Man)
(Beauty Jun)
Yuchi,
this way is not to your home.
I...
I’ll send you home.
What if that Baldhead
makes trouble for you again?
I’m not afraid of him.
Moreover,
you can’t protect me at all time.
And I’m not so fragile.
This is for you.
What’s this? So beautiful.
These are fireflies I trained.
Fireflies can be trained?
Once you release one firefly out,
it will come to me
and lead me to you.
Then,
I can see you at any time.
Yes, any time.
Thank you, Yuchi.
Remember to release the firefly.
What’s wrong with me?
I can’t fall sleep and keep missing him.
What am I thinking?
I haven’t finished the embroidery
on the handkerchief.
Is a scholar too gentle?
It’s not good
if there is a fight.
No.
I shouldn’t tackle the hooligans
with this,
or I’ll be laughed at.
This suit is good.
Where is Qingqing?
When did you come?
When you wore the armor.
What are you doing this for?
I’m waiting for Ayu’s calling.
Calling?
Once Ayu releases a firefly to call me,
I’ll be right there by her side.
But dressing is not that important.
What do you mean?
Women love gifts the most.
If she wants to see you,
will you meet her with nothing?
You’re right.
You haven’t told me where Qingqing is.
What about flowers?
Ayu is a florist.
You send her flowers?
What’s this?
The Empress’s phoenix hairpin.
It’s delicate and unique.
It’s the Empress’s?
You want Ayu to be killed?
You want her to ride it in a war?
These silk fabrics are too pompous.
The Night Pearl is too precious.
You send her this to
scrape the scales of fish?
I see.
You’re jealous of me.
So you disagree with me
for whatever I do.
Why should I be jealous of you?
I’m much closer to Ayu.
While you and Qingqing are still
playing hide and seek.
Much closer?
Qingqing follows my family name now,
while Ayu
hasn’t called you till now.
I can go to meet her.
You keep it.
-Stop!
-Miss Yuxiang...
Listen to me,
yesterday, Longhair and I
made great damage to
Ayu’s flower stall.
All the flowers were ruined,
and the petals were all over the ground.
It doesn’t matter you have no hair,
but can you think with your brain?
It’s not what I want.
Well...
It’s far from enough.
I see.
I will make a bigger trouble for her.
Leave it to me.
Don’t be too upset.
Qingqing,
why do you come to help me today?
It’s a fair day. I’ll give you a hand.
Help me cry my goods.
Okay.
Flowers!
Fresh flowers! Ayu’s flowers!
Anyone wants flowers?
-Fresh flowers.
-It’s good she didn’t call me.
It means she’s safe.
Flowers!
-Flowers! Fresh flowers!
-Chestnuts roasted with brown sugar!
-Ayu’s flower!
It tastes
like what I had in the capital.
Flowers!
-I’ll send you
-Fresh flowers!
chestnuts roasted with brown sugar.
Ruan Ayu!
You profiteer!
I won’t forgive you.
Mrs. Sun, what’s the matter?
Mrs. Sun’s grandson Fuwang
ate the fish you sold
and got serious diarrhoea.
He’s so sick that
he nearly mistook me as Longhair.
How do you want to deal with it?
How to deal with it?
Report to the government.
-Yes.
-Arrest her.
-That’s right.
-Come here, everyone.
This profiteer Ayu
-sold stale fish
-Come here, everyone.
-and made the buyers sick.
-Come have a look.
Come here, everyone.
-What nonsense! Nonsense!
-Come here.
You’re venomously slandering her.
Don’t worry.
My fish is fresh.
It’s nothing to worry.
That’s right.
Ayu,
Fuwang is so sick now.
Tell me, what should I do?
Mrs. Sun,
how exactly is Fuwang now?
We visited a physician.
The physician said,
it’s because he ate the soup
made by your stale fish.
How will you deal with it?
Everyone, what should we do now?
Report to the government.
Yes, report to the government.
Compensate money.
Report to the government.
Don’t talk nonsense.
Call me.
Report to the government.
Ayu,
Fuwang ate your fish.
He not only has diarrhea,
but also a sore throat.
Sore throat?
Is he slobbering?
Yes, he keeps slobbering.
You profiteer Ayu.
Don’t talk endlessly here.
You should talk at the court.
Yes.
It’s a bawbee.
Why should we go to the court?
We can solve it by ourselves.
Bawbee?
How to solve it? With money?
Do you have money?
You!
Diarrhea, sore throat and slobbering.
Mrs. Sun, I can cure Fuwang.
Really?
Well, don’t boast.
Are you a physician?
Mrs. Sun, let’s not waste time,
or Fuwang will suffer more.
Okay. I’ll trust you for the last time.
-Let’s go now.
-Okay.
Miss Yuxiang, just ignore her.
Why didn’t she call me?
You must cure my grandson, Fuwang.
Mrs. Sun, don’t worry.
Let me check Fuwang first.
You do take yourself as a physician?
Yeah.
I said long ago,
it’s because Fuwang ate the soup
made by stale fish.
Ayu,
don’t delay the treatment of Fuwang.
Leave him to us, okay?
You can’t solve the problem by this.
Admit your fault,
admit you’re a profiteer,
report to the government by yourself,
and admit your fault,
okay? Am I right, everyone?
Yes. Yes.
-Water is coming.
-That’s right!
It’s hot. Baldhead, have some water.
Physician Jia, have some.
-Yuxiang, do you want some?
-No.
No!
When I became a physician,
you were younger than Fuwang is now.
How dare you doubt my medical skill?
That’s right. Physician Jia
is well-known among the neighbors.
You’re playing sword before...
before...
Wait.
-Well, I have to go to the toilet.
-Give me.
Wait a moment. Give way.
Physician Jia,
as far as I know,
stale fish or shrimps
may lead to diarrhea and erythema.
Why there is no erythema
on Fuwang’s body?
What a joke! You know nothing.
The soup Fuwang ate contains nothing
except the fish and some ginger slices.
If it’s not the fish’s problem,
it’s the ginger slices’?
I’ll go to the toilet first.
Let’s talk later.
-Physician Jia, be quick.
-Physician Jia.
Physician Jia, be quick.
Ayu, Ayu, Ayu, Yu.
-I’m here.
-Ayu.
It’s...
the fish’s problem. It’s the fish.
Baldhead, why are you slobbering?
Am I?
I don’t know.
I... I have to go to the toilet again.
I’ll go again.
His... His symptoms
are similar to Fuwang’s.
With erythema or not,
it’s the fish’s problem, anyway.
Diarrhea, sore throat and slobbering.
-It’s obviously...
-It’s obviously...!
I’ll be back...
Physician Jia.
So weird!
They didn’t eat Ayu’s fish.
Why they have the same symptoms
as Fuwang?
Why?
They didn’t eat the fish soup.
It’s so strange.
Come on.
You please!
You please! Please!
Physician Jia.
Do you both have diarrhoea?
What diarrhoea?
Diarrhoea,
sore throat,
and slobbering.
It’s obviously being poisoned.
Tell me, did you
add croton seeds in our tea?
It’s because of croton seed?
Croton seed!
Croton seed?
It’s croton seed.
No, no.
No, listen to me.
It’s croton seed.
No, no, no.
You, no, you...
Physician Jia, your symptoms
are the same as Fuwang’s,
because you ate croton seed.
But you said Fuwang had diarrhea.
Don’t you delay his treatment?
Yes, that’s right. It’s a delay.
No, no, it’s not like this.
-No, no.
-Baldhead.
Your money.
No.
It’s you who made the trouble.
You solve it.
What? What money is this?
Baldhead,
why did he give you money?
I... I don’t know.
Mrs. Sun, obviously,
the truth is Baldhead and Yuxiang
colluded with Physician Jia
by money to frame Ayu.
I bet the croton seeds
were put by them, too.
-You mean me...
-It’s definitely you.
No, no, no.
It has nothing to do with me.
Who did it then?
I... don’t know.
Physician Jia.
His medical kit was left behind.
What a forgetful man!
I’ll send it to him.
You!
Ayu,
what... what should we do
about Fuwang?
Mrs. Sun, don’t worry.
I have some medicine made
of goldthread root and golden cypress.
It can detoxify the croton seed.
It’s so risky.
Here you are.
Thank you!
Ayu,
I’m so sorry that
I misunderstood you just now.
That’s all right.
Miss Ayu is so generous.
Yes. Ayu has both
a beautiful face and a beautiful heart.
Yes. What a good girl! She’s kind.
See? I told you,
the fish Ayu sells
has no problem at all.
Welcome to buy fish again.
Okay. Okay. I will. I will.
-Bye.
-It’s done.
Go back to your work.
Ayu.
How did you know
Fuwang ate croton seed?
I was piggish and had no mom.
I ate stale fish and
croton seed before.
My experience tells me the difference.
Qingqing,
when I was treating my wound,
how did you look after Ayu?
I didn’t do it intentionally.
I didn’t know human kids
can’t eat those.
Have a seat.
Qingqing, you have more experience.
Can you teach me
how to make lifelike embroidery?
What pattern do you like?
I’ll find a master for you.
I like dragon.
Dragon?
Dragon King, did you hear it?
Ayu has you in her mind now.
If I can complete the other half dragon
on Yuchi’s handkerchief,
he must be happy.
Qingqing, is this yours?
Why is it still here?
You people...
What does it mean if a man
sends a sachet to a woman?
Generally, it’s
love.
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
Impossible!
Stop pretending. It’s silly.
Why it’s you again?
Me again?
You must be disappointed
when seeing me.
Yes.
It seems you didn’t see her.
No, I saw her.
But she didn’t call you.
It means Ayu is safe and sound.
No.
She met some difficulties,
but she never thought
to call me from the very beginning.
So, the noble Dragon King
thinks he’s not needed.
What about you?
You’ve been waiting from dawn to night,
but she hasn’t come to you.
This is her home.
It’s late. She’ll be home soon.
It’s past 7:00 PM.
As her brother in the human world,
you don’t care about where she is?
When she was Long Qingqing,
I was her brother.
Now she’s Xue Qingqing.
I have nothing to do with her.
Where do you think she could go?
Is it possible she’s at Ayu’s home?
Will you go to find her?
No.
Then you keep waiting here.
Why didn’t you call me?
Where is your firefly jar?
Is it
you lost it?
Yuchi.
Why haven’t you called me?
Is it you lost the jar?
You must’ve lost the jar.
So you can’t call me.
Wine is really a good thing.
I have an illusion again.
It’s not an illusion.
I also have phonism?
You don’t have phonism.
You are really Ayu?
Who are you?
Who are you?!
I’m the real Ayu.
She’s fake!
How could you say that?
How am I fake?
Dragon King, she’s fake.
I’m the real one.
Yuchi, I’m the real one.
She’s fake.
I’m real!
She’s fake!
-She’s fake!
-No.
I’m real!
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪