♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 14=
I’m the real Ayu.
She’s fake!
How could you say that?
How am I fake?
Dragon King, she’s fake.
I’m the real one.
Yuchi, I’m the real one.
She’s fake.
I’m real!
She’s fake!
-No!
-I’m real!
I’m real!
-Stop! Stop!
-I’m real…!
You both say you’re Ayu.
Then, let me ask you.
Why can Ayu come to Dragon Pool?
Say it!
Or, don’t blame me for being rude.
-It’s you?
-It’s you two?
Why did you pretend to be Ayu?
That’s what I should ask you!
Lately, Dragon King always drowns
his sorrows in wine.
The trouble should be ended
by the one that started it.
No matter what we say,
it can’t value more than a word
from the girl he loves.
But, how to let Ayu tell him?
Star Halo!
Yuchi said
he liked to see it.
Little firefly,
bring Yuchi here. Hurry up.
It’s the daytime.
Can Yuchi see the firefly?
Will the Star Halo still be there
when he comes?
So what?
Did your heart beat fast
when you touched my forehead?
Don’t talk nonsense.
Xue Qianxun!
How dare you!
I just hit this bug.
Then let me hit the bug for you.
Seriously? Can you be reasonable?
Why should I?
Guys.
Guys!
It’s not a bug. It’s a firefly.
Ayu is in trouble!
Ayu.
Yuchi! Finally you’re here!
What happened?
You… What happened to your clothes?
A small accident.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
What about you? What happened?
Look!
I remember you said
Star Halo is the thing you want to
see the most.
So beautiful.
Yuchi.
I cherish these
precious fireflies a lot.
But the Star Halo is so rare
and beautiful.
So, I called you here
to enjoy it together.
There are many fireflies.
As long as you like,
you can use it anytime.
Really?
Then
I can see Yuchi anytime I want.
Sugar-roasted chestnuts!
And they are peeled!
Let’s eat together.
It tastes good.
Weird. Star Halo
only appears after rain.
But there was no rain.
Yuchi.
You can take off your clothes.
Take off my clothes?
We…
That’s not so appropriate.
There’s nobody else here.
It’s OK.
Right here?
No. No, we can’t.
We can’t do it even not here.
No?
Why not?
Your sleeve is torn.
Let me sew it for you.
I brought needle and thread.
I’m real!
She’s fake!
Immortal of Fate and Xue Qianxun
should take the blame.
They made me look so embarrassed
in front of Ayu.
It’s OK. I can do it myself.
Yuchi, you think I can’t do it well?
I always help my father sew clothes.
Trust me.
No, thanks.
Sorry.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
Look!
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
Did I just take a nap?
I have done this much!
I’m pretty talented!
The tea today is good.
It was boiled just right.
You…
My Lord,
don’t you have anything to work on
in Luofeng Pavilion?
You just always come and ask me
to make you tea.
Because my maid hasn’t returned.
You have so many people there.
Anyone can replace me.
I think Bingxing is better than me.
I decide
who is better.
Alright, I accept it.
My Lord, may I have a request?
Can you give me back my power?
With my power, I can get things done.
At least,
I can protect myself and Ayu.
If I meet an injustice again
on the road,
I can give a helping hand…
OK.
Wait.
What did you say?
OK?
Stand still.
Yes.
Turn around three times and
laugh three times.
Laugh happily.
Two.
Three.
My Lord, when you sealed my power,
you just clapped once.
Why did it need so many moves
when you unsealed it?
You tricked me again!
You didn’t want to give me back
my power at the beginning, did you?
Your power was already unsealed
when I patted you on your shoulder.
The moves after that
were just a test of
how much you want your power back.
Why do you keep changing
into your real body?
I also want to ask you.
I wanted to get an osmanthus cake
for the first time.
And for the second time, I wanted to
freeze…
Forget it.
But when I used my power,
I could only change into my real body.
Is it
because my power has been sealed
for a long time
and it lost efficiency?
The seal has been altered.
I can’t unseal it.
Then, I’ve been working for nothing?
Oh, no.
As a bird demon, without my power,
I’m done!
Who altered the seal?
It doesn’t matter who did it now.
What matters is
I can’t get my power back.
It’s all your blame!
It’s all your fault!
All this wouldn’t have happened
if you hadn’t sealed my power!
What are you doing?
Stand up!
I’m wrong!
Look at you!
I have given you so many chances!
But you just disappointed me
every time.
Good of you.
Can you give me another chance?
OK.
I don’t want to see her again.
Who?
You want Ayu…
to die?
I…
So what?
You don’t dare to do it or you can’t?
I dare.
And I can do it.
But, can you grant me a small request?
How dare you have a request?
Yes.
Yuxiang, it’s been so many years.
I have always been following you.
I think
you must know
my feelings for you.
I like you.
Can I kiss you?
In your dream!
I knew it!
I knew that the girl I like
is not easy to get.
Don’t worry! Your business is mine.
Just count on me!
I’m going!
I’m going?
Go!
Sure.
Qingqing is not here?
Did you do anything to the seal
of Qingqing’s power?
I changed the time limit of it.
Why?
I intended to unseal it.
But I failed.
It was sealed by me.
But you wanted to unseal it?
It should be me to do it.
How could I know you…
Forget it.
Next time when we have a drink,
I’ll punish myself by three cups.
Don’t bother. Just tell me
why I can’t unseal it.
You tried?
Yes.
Oh, no!
What do you mean?
If anyone tries to
break the seal I altered,
everything will start all over again.
You mean
Qingqing will be sealed for another
99 years?
I think I forgot to
tell Ayu something.
See you.
Seriously?
Why don’t you try not to get together
with Liuying for another 100 years?
That’s different.
How about I protect Qingqing
for you for the next 99 years?
I knew you were up to something!
You took Qingqing away
from Luofeng Pavilion,
and then you altered the seal.
And you even let her live
together with you.
Now you want to protect her
for 99 years!
What are you jealous of?
You know I have only Liuying in my heart
and I have no feeling for Qingqing.
She and I just have one common goal,
to protect Liuying.
You only have Liuying in heart?
But now you also have Ayu.
You’re being so sensitive because
you can’t get Qingqing.
I can’t get her?
It’s impossible between you and Ayu.
Why impossible?
Ayu and I are getting on well.
Now she calls me all the time.
What about Qingqing?
She just wants to escape from you.
You need reflect on yourself.
She is my maid.
Where can she escape to?
She managed to escape
from Luofeng Pavilion.
What do you think?
She will always be mine
no matter where she goes.
Ridiculous!
She only thinks she’s your maid.
But after next life,
Ayu will be my wife!
Dragon King…
You…
Go on. Go on.
I’ll go back to my room.
Go on.
What?
How about we help each other
to apply the ointment?
OK.
Why should I help you first?
You have the ointment in hand.
Hurry up.
The Dragon King is afraid of pain?
Alright, your turn now.
Where are you going?
Going back to my Dragon Pool
to take a bath, of course.
You haven’t helped me yet!
Why do I feel so dizzy suddenly?
Did I get a heat stroke during the day?
That’s weird.
Why do I always feel dizzy recently?
Let me out!
Take off your clothes.
My pool can cure wounds.
Shouldn’t you help me to apply
the ointment first?
Why don’t you go to Qingqing?
Isn’t she your maid?
That’s right.
You just don’t want to ruin
your image in her mind, do you?
Not like that.
Don’t deny.
Human’s love needs you to spend
more time together.
But I have wounds on my body.
That will scare Qingqing.
That’s true.
Girls are all timid.
But it’s something
you have to experience.
Trust me.
Qingqing is not timid at all.
She doesn’t care about what I say
to her every time.
She can only remember it when I
order her or threaten her.
Then, have you ever thought
not to get along with her with your
identity as Lord?
I’m not the Lord?
What do you mean?
You are really dull.
In front of our beloved,
we are not the Dragon King or Lord.
You should put these thoughts aside
and simply get along with her
equally in the way a man
treats a woman.
How could it be equal
between her and me?
You will understand it gradually.
I need to put on my clothes now.
I have the feelings
that Ayu will call me soon.
You cast the power
of Connection on Ayu?
I don’t need to use power.
Love makes the connection.
Just enjoy your bath.
What is this?
Baldhead?
Why do you tie me up?
Let me go!
How do you know it’s me?
I’ve watched your head
since childhood. Of course I know it.
Where are you taking me to?
No more questions. Just tell me
what it is!
It’s mine!
Cut the crap.
Now even you are mine.
You’ve been kidnapped by me!
Just tell me what it is!
It’s mine! Don’t touch it!
I touched it. I touched it.
I want to…
How dared you bite me!
Just have some sleep now.
Come on. Sleep.
Close your eyes. Sleep.
Didn’t you say you’d be called soon?
What are you waiting for?
Are my clothes too plain for me?
Becoming silly is also what we
have to experience?
What did you say?
Nothing.
I can’t deal with you?
Where is Ayu?
Did I allow you to leave?
Sorry!
Where did you plan to take Ayu to?
I… I… I…
Say it!
No! No! It’s not me! It’s Yuxiang!
No! It’s not! It’s not Yuxiang either!
I… I wanted to sell her to…
Yuchi?
Why are you here?
Everything is fine now.
Where is my firefly jar?
Here.
What about Baldhead?
I have already punished him for you.
Baldhead
is usually no match for me.
But I don’t know why
I’ve been a little weak recently.
Let’s see how I will punish him
next time I see him.
No more talking.
Go to sleep now.
Yuchi,
can you leave after I fall asleep?
Sure.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪