Stop right there.
Mr. Cassano.
Are you guys okay?
Why didn't you go?
I took care of it in another way.
And I forgot to feed Inzaghi as well.
Anyway, stand back.
Do you happen to be Vincenzo Cassano?
That's none of your business.
I'll make you pay
in less than five minutes.
Go bring her to me.
Damn it!
Shit!
Oh, no. Stop it! Stop!
-Stop!
What the hell?
CHUNGJU OWL GANG LIGHTNING SCISSORS
NATIONAL SPORTS FESTIVAL
GOLD MEDAL WRESTLER
GOLD MEDAL WEIGHTLIFTER
FLYWEIGHT BOXING CHAMPION IN ASIA
LOADING MIDDLE SCHOOL BOXING CLUB
STREET FIGHTER TURNED DANCER
SSIREUM CHAMPION FROM CHUNGCHEONGBUK-DO
PRESIDENT OF VINCENZO'S FANCLUB,
"OH MY CONSIGLIERE"
GEUMGA-DONG SPIRAEA
FORMER GEUMGA-DONG'S ANGEL IN WHITE
NOW, NUTRIA
I have underestimated you.
Mr. Cho, who is this guy?
He's candidate Park Seung-jun's
right-hand man.
I see.
Then Mr. Park is about to lose
his right hand today.
Let's talk.
-I have nothing to say to you.
-I can help you with that.
By the way, I'm really curious now.
Was there really gold here?
How dare he talk such bullshit?
What was he saying when he was hit?
I don't know. Did he say something?
-She came out of nowhere.
-That was fast.
My goodness.
She's the best. Way to go.
EPISODE 19
Everyone.
Are you all okay?
Of course. We're as good as new.
You guys sure can fight.
How have you been holding back?
We didn't have a good reason to fight.
And it usually bites us in the ass.
But we have a legitimate reason
to fight now.
And you are the ones who gave us
a legitimate reason to fight.
And you also got us together
as a community.
Let me say something fancy, too.
"If you walk alone, you reach quickly.
But if we go together, we can go far."
I wrote your name when I was asked
who my role model is at school.
-Good.
-That's great.
Thanks to you, I learned a thing
or two about the importance of power.
Thank you.
Merciful Buddha…
Hey, Nutria.
The only thing you could do was to bite.
Gosh, you know nothing.
That's an advanced skill.
I bite, chew, taste, and savor.
There's four levels.
Nutria, can you open this for me?
Don't do it!
-Did you see that?
-Are you okay?
-Blood. Is he bleeding?
-His tooth…
-I think he chipped his tooth.
-Nutria.
Mr. Cho.
You didn't answer my calls,
so I was worried.
I was ambushed.
I'm sorry.
By the way,
how did you secretly move the gold?
It must have attracted some attention.
-Mr. Cassano.
-Yes?
I've wanted to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
Just what is…
under here?
I kept getting electing shocks
whenever I meditated here,
so I opened it.
Wait, sir. My finger!
One, two, three.
And we saw something
that looked like a door to a vault.
I couldn't stop shouting during meditation
because of the electricity.
Seeing how the light was on,
there must have been an electric leakage.
This is…
where the gold is stored…
isn't it?
Is the window open?
Right?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell the other tenants?
We didn't want there to be
a dispute over it.
So we waited for the owner.
I see.
Since you know now,
please help me.
But how do you open the vault?
Ms. Seo.
It's time now.
Let's open the vault tomorrow.
At last!
-By the way, Mr. Cassano,
-Yes?
I will open the vault for you, but…
You'll get a fair share of your cut.
You trust me, right?
What are you…
Of course. I will open it right away!
Okay.
-Got that?
-Got it.
Got it.
-It's tomorrow.
-Yes.
Nice!
-Great!
-Yes.
-It hurts?
-Where?
We're almost there.
One, two…
Mr. Nam, pull it harder.
Please move the gold
little by little every day.
NANYAK TEMPLE
Then where is the gold?
Someone might hear us from outside.
Let me whisper it to you.
Yes.
Then, is the Guillotine file
with the gold?
No.
I hid the Guillotine file
somewhere only I know about.
He didn't even tell me.
Obviously, he didn't--
I know.
Mr. Cho.
I will tell you when the time is right.
GEUMGA PLAZA
Did you come back because of me?
Your Italian family needs you, too.
I took care of it.
How did you take care of it that quickly?
You didn't even leave Korea.
Eighty million euros.
Pardon?
I promised to give them 80 million euros
for leaving my family alone.
By the way, 80 million euros is about…
a bit over 100 billion won.
Did they agree to that?
Yes. I sent over the contract.
My contract is credible
in the Mafia world.
Then I'm relieved.
Thank you.
And…
I'm so happy…
that you are back in one piece.
You look cool today just like that day.
The day we had the party.
You looked great in a Booralro suit
that I'd only heard about.
I was glad to meet…
someone who recognized
a Booralro suit that day.
What the…
Damn it.
I couldn't hug you earlier
because Mr. Cho was here.
Finally…
Mr. Cassano.
You've been hugging him
for over 20 seconds.
People say you barely notice newcomers,
but you notice people's absences.
Your absence left a hole
with a 30m diameter in my heart.
Okay.
Please stop hugging me now.
That hole has been filled in now.
Let him go, please.
-We should teach Park Seung-jun a lesson.
-Yes.
Right.
I don't care if he's running
for President. He needs a lesson.
You startled me.
Come on, my dear Guillotine file.
How many bribes did he take?
How corrupt is he?
CANDIDATE PARK SEUNG-JUN ACCUSED
OF BUYING LAND FOR SPECULATION
CANDIDATE PARK'S BROTHER-IN-LAW
COLLUDED AS THE HEAD OF IUDC
The article about Park Seung-jun is up.
What? I can't believe
he's running for president.
The whole family is corrupted.
Our country is doomed.
CANDIDATE PARK PROFITED OFF
LAND SPECULATION
I don't get it. What is wrong with you?
If only you got rid of Vincenzo
from the get-go…
With all due respect, sir,
I think you acted rashly.
What?
Did you tell Mr. Park
that you went after Vincenzo?
It's none of your business.
You should never underestimate him.
He has definite evidence to bring us down
but he's just spreading them as rumors.
He's toying with us.
It's likely he will use the evidence
during the Babel Tower trial.
All the videos of people
involved in the tower
as well as Mr. Park's involvement.
You two must be in that video too, right?
Then we'll all be arrested
if things go south.
-Yes.
-Mr. Kim.
There is a way to stop the trial.
But…
Mr. Park has to set something up for me.
Oh, right.
When will Mr. Jung get promoted?
He wants to take the promotion
after this case.
Just promote him.
He needs more authority
to make this go away.
Yes, sir.
Accept the promotion.
Yes, Mr. Kim.
Let me offer my congratulations
in advance, Mr. Jung.
Gosh.
Does he think he runs this place, too?
You little…
Why are you even here
if you're going to act that way?
Did I offend you in any way?
No, not at all.
Why are you in a bad mood then?
Just because.
I see.
People can just be in a bad mood.
That happens.
Hey, over there!
Move!
Out of the way!
Stop him!
-Stop him now!
-My ear!
He still has his ear.
Come here.
Come here, you asshole!
Let go of me!
Ms. Hong.
Have this.
It'll help relieve stress.
I need these when I'm working.
They wake me up.
Come on!
What's wrong?
This is from
the Seoul Namdongbu District Court.
You should read this.
"The court finds it highly likely
that the Babel Tower trial
could be used by the press
and the opposition
to smear the name
of a specific presidential candidate.
Therefore, after much discussion,
the court has reached a ruling
that the trial will be postponed
until the election is over."
It looks like Mr. Park
pulled some strings.
Unbelievable. Gosh. This is just…
I mean, how could they stoop so low?
Since it was them who stooped this low,
we should do the same.
How?
It looks like
the trial won't be happening.
We have a magic lamp.
The Guillotine file?
THE JUDICIAL BRANCH
Everything from here.
-Namdongbu office.
Right there.
Gosh.
Damn it.
I just read this on the anonymous
chat room for lawyers.
Prosecutor Jung In-kuk was
the one who postponed the trial.
What's more annoying is
that he finally got promoted.
That darned traitor.
Let's give him a present
for the promotion then.
There we go.
You were right, Ms. Hong…
about how everyone here is
as crooked as the Mafia.
They group together
as government officials…
in finance, transport, taxes,
and even as alumni…
There are so many.
"It's okay to be corrupt
when you're competent."
This is what many of us believe.
But…
how can you be competent
when you're corrupt?
Competent in looking after oneself, maybe.
But never when looking after others.
I see.
That makes sense looking at it
from a villain's point of view.
When you leave
after everything goes as planned,
you won't be able to come back, right?
But, to me,
Vincenzo Cassano will not be
remembered just as a memory.
Ms. Hong
I never make promises
unless it's for business purposes.
But I promise you this.
I will come back.
"Further discussion
on the aforementioned trial was necessary,
and the court has reached a new decision.
The aforementioned trial is
unlikely to be abused
as a false propaganda
in the next presidential election,
and the suffering of the plaintiffs
from Babel Tower's development is greater.
Therefore, you are notified that the trial
will proceed as previously scheduled."
I'm sorry.
Mr. Jung.
You said you could handle it.
What is this?
They used the Guillotine file as leverage.
You should have seen that coming!
Since you saw it coming,
why don't you and Mr. Han handle this?
What did you say? Hey!
It's so cold. Gosh, it's freezing.
-It's so cold.
-Going home, sir?
Who are you?
It's Judge Heo.
Your Honor. Hey, man.
Listen. Ung-jin.
You are our last defender in this game.
Okay? You're the sweeper.
Yes.
So listen carefully. Focus!
Gosh. You startled. I almost punched you.
All right.
So whatever happens during the trial,
you must back us up at the end.
I got it, sir.
Get home safely, Mr. Chief Prosecutor.
Gosh. Don't be so formal with me.
-I'll get going.
-Wait, your car is here.
We have the same cars!
Gosh.
Don't be like that. Don't do that.
Treat me like your friend.
I'm so sleepy. I'm going to sleep now.
Bye.
See you.
Sweeper, my ass.
I know that he's just using me.
That jerk.
Open the door.
Let's go.
Hey.
Drive me home. Why did you stop here?
You…
You're Vincenzo Casanova.
Get out.
Get out of the car.
What do you want from me?
-I'll tell you a story.
-What story?
King Cambyses of Ancient Persia
punished corrupt judges severely.
He once skinned a corrupt judge alive.
Oh, my.
-Do you know what happened next?
-No.
The corrupt judge's son was also a judge.
When he presided over trials,
the king made the son sit
on his father's skin.
So he could come to his senses
and give a fair trial.
Why are you telling me that?
I'm saying
you could have ended up like that
if we were in those times.
Gosh.
You're presiding over
Chairman Jang's trial, right?
Yes.
Do what you always have done
so that he can get out early.
Even if I try to get him out
as soon as possible,
it will take two months at least.
Then don't extend his imprisonment.
If you refuse…
you'll be getting
more than a wasp this time.
Goodbye.
DAY OF THE TRIAL
The law is like a spiderweb.
It has limited durability.
Strong wasps will tear it apart
and fly away,
but weak flies end up dead
on the spiderweb.
But the flies in this plaza
joined forces together
and are biting off everything
whether it's a wasp or a spiderweb.
And you'll see the result yourself today.
Watch carefully
what happens to the wasps.
Let's do this!
Let's go.
One, two, three.
-Let's go!
Where's the file I've prepared?
Where is the file?
I told you ten times already!
I told you 1,000 times!
This way, sir.
Sit down.
We're in the sacred court.
All right.
All rise for the honorable Judge.
PLAINTIFF
DEFENDANT
Please be seated.
CHIEF PROSECUTOR HAN SEUNG-HYUK
We will now begin
the trial for case number 2021-30184,
Babel Group
versus the tenants of Geumga Plaza,
to settle the compensation
for damages caused
by Babel Group's illegal activities.
We will begin by
questioning the plaintiff's witness.
Plaintiff's counsel,
you may question your witness.
Our witness is Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
Please come forward.
Your tie.
Fix your hair.
Good luck!
WITNESS BOX
I solemnly swear…
-Your Honor.
-Yes?
My honorable judge.
Yes?
My testimony will be
about why Babel Group committed
the illegal activities.
And I will testify with video evidence.
Your Honor.
His video evidence has nothing
to do with this trial.
We might find something important in it.
So I will decide whether it's relevant
or not after watching it.
Sit down.
Play the video.
Gosh.
-What's that?
-Goodness.
-Oh, my.
-What's he holding?
-A gold toad?
-No way!
-Come on.
-Is that really gold?
-That's gold.
-Look at that.
A gold toad?
DEFENDANT
What's with the blur?
Why are only our faces blurred?
Why…
Quiet down.
Please quiet down!
Stay away.
Don't…
Good to see you again, friend.
I warned you, didn't I?
To do whatever you like.
That I'll come back for you
when you have everything you want.
Did you?
I don't seem to recall.
But you got your promotion
and tried to stop the hearing.
Congratulations.
You've ignored my warning
and chose to die.
Right.
You can't kill a prosecutor
in the court of law.
Don't push yourself.
Show me how humble you can be
in the next two days and I'll spare you.
I'm being generous.
You Mafia prick.
You can't toy with a prosecutor like this.
I'm not toying with you.
I'm giving you a chance
to redeem yourself.
Gosh. This doesn't feel right.
Why on earth did they blur only our faces?
Why do you think? He wants to kill us.
It'll be hard to do that
if we're in prison.
I know. I know that, too.
By the way,
all of us are about to get killed.
Why do you look so calm?
What do you suggest I do, then?
Should I go somewhere and weep?
We need to figure out a way
to get out of this.
Why don't you find your own way out,
Mr. Chief Prosecutor?
What?
This is our farewell drink.
This is the perfect place.
You recruited me here.
Why would you say something like that?
Come on.
We need to close ranks even more
at times like this.
Close ranks, my ass.
You coaxed Jang Han-seo
to save your own ass
and even begged Park Seung-jun
for you to become the chief prosecutor.
I should rip your mouth to pieces.
You're hurting my feelings!
Think about it.
Who helped you live in luxury like this?
Look at your face. It's glowing!
I bet you forgot how you started. Gosh.
Thank you so much, you slithering snake.
Snake?
If you get in the way of Chairman Jang
and me to save your own skin,
I will kill you myself. Got that?
I enjoyed the drink.
Fine. We should part our ways now.
Go. Leave, Myung-hee!
Don't you come back to me and beg!
I'm the chief prosecutor!
The Babel Tower scandal has come
as a huge shock to the public.
The illegal activities and corruption
in the prosecution, the police,
the National Assembly, the media,
and local organizations
have appalled the public.
Moreover, the constant assaults on
and attempted murder of the tenants
of Geumga Plaza in the process
of illegally acquiring the land
for the Babel Tower
have angered the public.
Babel Group's ownership of Geumga Plaza
will be nullified
due to corruption and illegal activities
committed when acquiring
the permit for the construction.
Yes. Stop the production of RDU-90.
Yes. Cancel the order of raw materials.
No. It's okay.
It's fine, just do as I say.
Okay. Good day.
Sorry.
I have a lot of urgent matters to handle.
You…
really look like a real chairman now.
I'm so proud of you.
Why would you be? You're not my mom.
Oh, right.
What did you want to talk about?
You watched the video at the trial
yesterday, right?
Only our faces were blurred.
He did it so he could kill us.
So you and I should join hands again--
No. I'll join hands with Vincenzo.
Pardon?
Vincenzo's in a different league
from you.
I'll team up with a pro.
But still,
you can't just toss me out like this.
Don't forget who introduced you to him.
It was me!
-Oh, right.
-Yes.
You're right.
-Sorry. I forgot about that.
-Exactly.
-Thank you so much. I mean it.
-I understand.
It's okay.
But you're on your own now.
What do you mean?
-Mr. Chief Prosecutor…
-Let me join you.
-you're on your own now.
-Sir.
Sir?
Mr. Han is leaving now.
Get his car now. He's in a hurry.
No, I'm not. Can I join you?
Inmate 6723. Visitor.
What is it? Are you here to gloat?
That you won?
If you just hear the news,
you might not actually feel it.
Sorry I broke into your place.
But what a relief.
It wasn't the real tower.
Now that Babel Tower
has been brought down,
you must know what's next.
I'm a hungry cat now.
Fine. See if you can eat me.
Try to eat me whole.
I will when you get out.
Right after my celebration.
When I get out of here,
it won't be as Chairman Jang Han-seok.
Is that so?
I will be the Jang Han-seok
that I was in my childhood.
A monster that had no inhibitions.
You won't be going up against
the chairman of Babel.
You'll be up against just plain old me.
That'll be interesting.
You know my past very well.
What I did to my friends when I was young.
I think your watch…
will end up in my walk-in closet.
Suit yourself.
I have a knack
for straightening up delinquent kids.
Mr. Jung.
I have an urgent favor to ask you.
Let me…
stay in prison just for three months.
Pardon?
I'm sure you know why I'm asking you this.
Vincenzo…
Listen.
Just come up with a charge
and lock me up just for three months.
And get me out if Vincenzo dies
during those three months.
But still. I cannot--
Gosh. Just do it. Do it for me.
If you do it for me, I will give you
all the privileged information
on Wusang's clients
including Jang Han-seok.
It'll be as good as
having the Guillotine file.
With that information,
you will climb up the ladder smoothly.
Come on. Just do it.
You think this is pizza?
Yes, Korean-style pizza.
Vincenzo.
Are you really going to leave Korea
once everything is over?
Yes.
Can't you just stay here?
I can hire you as a legal advisor
for Babel Group.
-You'll be a director.
-I'm good.
Then don't leave without saying goodbye.
Okay?
That's what the Mafia does in the movies.
Some Mafia members have
week-long farewell parties.
Seriously.
Your party has to last a week, too. Okay?
Have you heard from Jang Han-seok?
No. He's been quiet.
He'll get what he deserves
if we provide all the evidence, right?
We don't know that yet.
Then could he be released
after two months?
Listen.
Go abroad for now, just for a few months.
Okay?
Once he gets out…
you'll be his first target.
I'll recommend a few safe places.
I'm good.
When I started this…
I knew I'd have to risk my life
at some point.
Besides, I made a promise to you.
You can keep your promise later.
I want you to reconsider.
No. I'll fight.
I have 20 bodyguards.
It won't be that easy to get to me.
And more importantly…
I have you.
You know everything,
keep me safe,
and beat up all the bad guys.
That's you. Goodness.
Why are you so cool?
Hey, that's soy sauce. Don't drink it.
That's salty.
You should have told me sooner.
What should I do to get Mr. Jang out?
What should I do?
Mr. Cassano,
once Jang Han-seok is released,
we'll do as planned, right?
Ms. Hong.
You really don't have to join me
to finish off Jang Han-seok.
So far, we've been like vigilantes.
But after this,
we'll be monsters.
And I want to protect
your virtue.
To be honest, everything we did
was so cruel
that it was hard for me to endure.
But do you know why I supported you?
There's no law that can punish
a monster like Jang Han-seok.
And there are no other options.
That's why I supported your method,
the lesser evil.
I thought that was the right thing to do.
NAM JU-SUNG
EVERYONE IN THE VIDEO WE PROVIDED
WAS RELEASED
Unbelievable.
What is it?
Prosecutor Jung In-kuk released everyone.
Everyone in the video
that was taken at Jang Han-seok's house.
That means he turned down
my last act of generosity.
How could you ask for help
after screwing this up
in every possible way?
We can put an end to everything
for good this time.
Including Vincenzo
and the Guillotine file.
Forget it.
We'll take care of Vincenzo
and the Guillotine file ourselves.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Mr. Park is in the middle of his campaign.
What if your attempt to get rid of him
goes south and affects the campaign?
That will be another scandal.
For Mr. Park's safety,
let me take care of this problem.
So how will you do that?
Please do whatever it takes
to get Mr. Jang out of prison.
He's the biggest problem right now.
Getting him out is next to impossible.
Mr. Kim.
-Give me that.
-How does it look?
-Did you get it?
-This one.
I already fabricated evidence
that I'd incited, threatened,
and pressured Babel
for my own benefit
since when I was working as a prosecutor.
No judge or prosecutor
will be able to tear down my claim.
With my evidence,
it'll look like
Mr. Jang was no more than my puppet.
Are you saying that you'll…
Yes.
I'll take the fall for everything
and go to prison.
Mr. Jang is the only one
who can put an end
to Mr. Park's Babel Tower scandal
and bring down Vincenzo.
Mr. Jung!
Many congratulations on your promotion!
-Congratulations!
-Mr. Jung!
-Yes!
We are the prosecutors of this country.
Do not cave in or lose,
especially to those rich assholes.
If they challenge our authority,
stomp them out.
Got it?
-Yes, sir!
Raise your glasses.
Cheers to Namdongbu Prosecutors' Office!
-Cheers!
Go, Namdongbu!
-Congrats.
-Drink!
Congratulations, Mr. Jung!
-Congratulations!
You…
Vincenzo.
Hey!
You bastard…
It's rare for me to be so generous,
but you won't accept.
Shut up, you Mafia prick.
You sure talk big for a lowlife criminal.
I may be a criminal,
but I'm aware of the things I did.
Why aren't you?
I haven't done anything wrong.
I live by the law and its principles.
All right.
Since you won't acknowledge what
you've done, I'll free you from your sins.
That which has no life has no sin.
-Hey, isn't that a person?
-What?
What the…
I finished one.
And I must take care of the rest
one by one.
For me…
and for Ms. Hong.
The fabricated evidence is ironclad.
You didn't have to go that far.
It's all right.
I'll humiliate myself once
and go down for all the charges
to make it all go away.
Once you get out, recuperate,
and get me out later.
When you get out,
you will be the vice chairwoman…
of the Babel Group.
Thank you.
You told me to keep an eye
on Mr. Jang Han-seo.
He's definitely with Vincenzo now.
He makes it so obvious.
Did you hear that
Mr. Jung committed suicide?
Yes.
He should've at least
let him enjoy his party.
He's so cruel.
Vincenzo is…
making his moves now.
I'll do as you say on one condition.
I want to be released quickly
without anyone knowing.
Don't let anyone know.
It'll be just me.
One, two. One, two, three, four.
That's it.
Ms. Choi.
We're from Namdongbu Prosecutors' Office.
You're under arrest for instigating
and abetting tax evasion and murder.
Is that true?
Give me two minutes.
Just two minutes.
You don't have to read me
the Miranda rights.
Choi Myung-hee was arrested?
Yes. And the charges against her
are just huge.
Her subordinate must have reported her.
Then, I'm sure it was Mr. Yoon.
I mean, she must've made
his life a living hell.
That happens
when you fail to protect your family.
SEOUL NAMDONGBU DETENTION CENTER
Are you going somewhere?
A judicial training reunion.
Why do you ask?
I see. I thought
you were going to ask me out.
Gosh. You were totally off.
But why? You said you weren't
on good terms with them.
I'm not going there for fun.
I need to check
if they're badmouthing me or not.
I see. When will it be over?
I'll have to see.
By the way, if you're going home,
you should go up that way.
I'm going somewhere, too.
As if.
I'm leaving. Don't skip your meal.
-When will it be over?
-No idea!
-Are you going to drink?
-A lot!
-Should I pick you up later?
-No.
Is that for women only?
There are men, too.
Hello, sir.
Yes, our merciful Buddha.
Did you eat?
I see. You're fasting.
No. I'm sorry. Bye.
Okay, bye.
Hey, Mi-gyeong.
I'm in the parking lot.
Yes. Hye-won and Hye-ju are there, right?
Yes. Okay. I'll be there in a bit.
Mr. Kim? I thought you went home.
Mr. Kim?
I came out quietly
to surprise you, brother.
What's the point of hiring bodyguards?
When I offered money,
they all took it and left.
CEO JANG HAN-SEO
You incompetent traitor.
I didn't betray you.
I was trying to run the company properly.
I brought your gun.
I couldn't get one at such short notice.
Okay.
I see.
Now I really can't keep you alive.
I'm sure you understand that.
Yes.
I was bound to suffer
the same fate as Father.
I will accept it.
HONG CHA-YOUNG
The person you have reached
cannot come to the phone right now.
Please leave a message…
Han-seo.
Are you okay?
I didn't think you would abduct me,
but you did.
This makes you such a cheap villain.
What's the difference?
All villains are the same.
No matter how hard I think about it,
you are not a human being.
Don't you know how much I love you?
That makes me human.
Abducting a woman you love
is not love, but a crime,
you crazy asshole.
Sorry, Cha-young.
But to me, my principle comes before love.
Your principle?
Killing everyone you don't like?
What a load of bull.
Han-seok.
Someone like you
shouldn't have been born at all.
That hurts a lot.
I shouldn't have been born?
Isn't it harsh, Han-seo?
Kill me already.
Don't be stupid and call Mr. Cassano.
I can't do that.
That's the reason I abducted you.
Hey!
Don't use me to harm him. Just kill me!
INCOMING CALL
JANG HAN-SEOK
ACCEPT
Where is Ms. Hong?
Shouldn't you ask me how I am first?
I just got out.
I don't care.
Where is Ms. Hong?
Come to where I am now.
She's alive.
Please bear with me.
I heard from my fellow inmates
that this trick works the best
when you need to lure
someone who owes you something.
If anything happens to her, I'll kill you.
If you don't hurry,
something will happen to her.
The bloody necklace…
It was shocking, right?
It was pig's blood.
I tried your method.
You're worse than I thought.
You abducted your brother
and a woman too?
A rat who's about to be devoured by a cat
has no rules.
Do you think you'll live
if you kill everyone here?
Right.
The Mafia always has backup.
Think carefully.
Whatever you do, you'll die.
Even if I do,
I want to see you die first.
Pick it up, Han-seo.
Pick it up!
Chairman Jang.
Beat him to death with it,
and I'll spare you.
What?
Not only will I spare your life,
but I'll also give you all of Babel.
You crazy asshole!
You really are mad, aren't you?
Cha-young, be quiet.
If you keep talking,
I'm really going to kill you.
Do it then.
Stop this ridiculous joke.
Do as he says.
If I kill Vincenzo…
will you really let me live?
Of course.
You're my brother, after all.
I'm sorry…
Mr. Cassano.
It's okay.
You have no other choice.
Okay.
I'll make a decision I won't regret.
Please, stop!
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son