♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and let's count down
to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 32=
Here.
Yan Yan, something happened to Gu Chuan!
You're awake.
Why did you bring her here?
I've told her everything.
You swore
you wouldn't tell anyone.
Yes.
I did say
that if I were to tell anyone,
I would be struck by lightning.
But Yan Yan isn't anyone.
She's my wife.
Right?
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
Also,
I wanted to visit you as well.
Did you get me here?
Yes, there is a low battery alarm.
Did you forget to charge again?
If you keep doing this,
that'll be suicide.
It was my negligence.
Earlier,
I thought
my time was up
and that I was going to die.
Thank you
for making it here timely and saving me.
Knock it off.
It's good to have you.
Gu Chuan, I'm sorry.
I misunderstood you.
I kept telling Xiao Ning
that you were a jerk
to treat her that way.
But after hearing your condition from
Xu Cheng Ran,
what you did for Xiao Ning
was really noble.
In this world,
you're the man who loves Xiao Ning the most.
I apologize to you.
Thank you
for using your own way
to love Xiao Ning.
Here's your wedding gift.
What is it?
It's a painting.
I painted it a long time ago.
But I didn't have the chance to give it to you.
Thank you, Xiao Ning.
Wen Wen.
How long will you be there this time?
I think I'll be there for quite some time.
Otherwise,
I wouldn't have asked you out
to say goodbye to you.
After we're married,
we don't intend to settle down in one place.
So we plan to travel first
and think about where to live later on.
I'm so envious of you. Such a perfect couple.
What's there to envy?
There are different
types of happiness in life.
Speaking of which,
you don't look so great.
Are you too exhausted?
Do I?
There are things
that haven't been taken care of.
How are you and Gu Chuan?
Mr. Xu said he went on a vacation.
I haven't seen him for quite some time.
This is my own business.
You can just leave me alone.
I know.
I'm being meddlesome.
I just hope you and Jiang Xiao Ning
can be happy.
If you just let her pass you by like this,
I will feel sad for you.
I'm the one who feels the saddest.
Do you know
about his mechanical heart?
He told me.
And he saved me in the car accident
ten years ago.
I didn't know you two
had such a story.
Xiao Ning.
I can't comment
on your relationship.
But I think
Gu Chuan is the kind of person
who keeps
everything to himself.
So if you don't want
to give up on him just yet,
I think
you need to try a little harder.
Don't just believe what you hear
and what you see.
Feel with your heart.
Whatever your decision is,
I'll have your back.
All the best.
See you.
(When I First Met You)
(I'm grateful to have met you.)
(May your days with him)
(be filled with laughter and smile.)
(Gu Chuan is the kind of person)
(who keeps)
(everything to himself.)
(So if you don't want)
(to give up on him just yet,)
(I think)
(you need to try a little harder.)
(Don't just believe what you hear)
(and what you see.)
(Feel with your heart.)
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
(Gu Chuan, where are you?)
(Are you going to just leave me like this?)
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
♪We are total strangers meeting
for the first time♪
♪Why does my heart beat so fiercely♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪People who think alike♪
♪Are pushing the gears♪
♪Ah~Ah~♪
♪Turn around♪
♪Thankfully, faith allows people to♪
♪Defend their fates♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Come on~♪
♪The destined one♪
Hello?
All right. I'll be right there.
♪It's you♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪
(Ai-Bi Pet Hospital)
Hi, doctor.
Hi.
Why did you give me a refund?
Didn't you bring the cat
to the vet the other day?
You have paid for
the euthanasia drug.
But we didn't give it the injection.
Of course,
we have to get you the refund.
No injection?
That's right.
Didn't he sign
the consent form?
Didn't he tell you?
He did sign the form.
But he couldn't bear to do it.
After much deliberation,
he changed his mind.
Here is the money.
Please put it in the car.
Thank you.
All right.
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
Sir, the cement's here.
Okay.
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
Speed up.
Thank you.
(Xiao Ning, what's the matter?)
Do you remember
what I told you about Ice Cream?
I thought Gu Chuan
signed the consent form for euthanasia.
But today the pet hospital called
and told me to get the refund.
The vet told me that Gu Chuan changed his mind
about the euthanasia injection
and took Ice Cream back.
I wanted to ask him
what actually happened.
But I called him twice
and there was no answer.
Could you ask Mr. Xu for me
if he knew
where Gu Chuan had gone to?
I didn't hear him talk about it.
Sister Yan Yan.
I'm so confused now.
I can't help thinking
like things aren't that simple.
Could you ask Mr. Xu for me
if he knew
where Gu Chuan had gone to?
Do you really want to know?
Of course.
Sister Yan Yan.
Do you know something?
Tell me, please.
Gu Chuan took Ice Cream back
and accompanied Ice Cream
during its final hours.
He didn't tell you
because he was afraid
the pain would be too much to you.
(Xiao Ning, Gu Chuan was trying to protect you.)
What do you mean?
Did he tell you these
or it was just a wild guess?
Xiao Ning, stop asking questions.
Did it cross your mind
Gu Chuan's current situation
is similar
to Ice Cream's?
What are you talking about?
What is similar?
Sister Yan Yan, just tell me, please.
(Xiao Ning, ask no more.)
Think about your wish.
Think with your heart.
You'll know where he is.
(Sorry, the number you have dialed)
(cannot be reached temporarily.)
Gu Chuan.
You shouldn't be here.
So you hiding here and rebuilding my family house
is what you should do?
I just want to help you
rebuild your family home.
Who are you to help me?
You don't even want me.
What's the point
of you fulfilling my dream?
I'm such a fool.
I was with you all the time.
I should have known
you weren't feeling well.
that you were lying to me.
Regardless,
we can't be together anymore.
Why?
I don't want
to tie you down with me.
You can have a better future.
I don't want you to regret it in the future.
That's right.
Gu Chuan.
I have no right
to tell you how to live your life.
And you can't dictate
how my life will be.
Did you think
breaking up was doing me any good?
Have you forgotten
what we've been through together ten years ago?
I met you again ten years later
and I fell for you.
I fell in love with you.
Even if you left me
or refused to see me now,
did you think I could forget you?
It doesn't matter when you leave me.
To me,
it still hurts as much.
It doesn't make it any less painful.
But...
if you are willing to be with me,
no matter how long we can go,
every single day in the future
will be a blessing to me.
All you're trying to do now
is just
to fulfill my dream
so that
I could live a good life.
If so,
why can't you do it in a simpler way?
We can do these things
together.
As you already know,
I don't have
much time left.
What would you do
if you were me?
If one day, I'm gone
all of a sudden,
how are you going to face it?
Ten years ago,
you held my hand
and encouraged me to persevere.
Why wouldn't I have the courage
to face it?
Gu Chuan.
If you were to leave now,
would I not have any regrets?
I respect your decision about your life.
But you, too,
have to respect mine.
Even if there's no tomorrow,
I still want to be with you.
♪The bell tolls over the castle♪
♪The fireworks are shining brightly♪
♪Your passing in the dark♪
♪No matter what, there's no skipping it♪
♪Growing up makes the fairy tale come to an end♪
♪Love is silently playing tricks♪
♪Encourage us to wait patiently for destiny♪
♪Take me away like the magnificent fireworks♪
♪Take me away, endlessly, no explanation needed♪
♪Take me away to our air space♪
♪Take me away, fairy tales are different
because of you♪
Stop walking around.
It puts me on edge.
I'm nervous.
So am I.
Look who's talking.
It's all because
you told her.
I thought I was the worse
secret keeper ever.
You're even worse than me.
Don't tell me if you have the guts!
Besides,
I didn't say anything.
I merely
gave her some hint.
Hint?
The only thing you didn't do
was to send her the location.
What now?
What do you think
the two of them
will talk about when they meet?
What will happen?
Will Gu Chuan pass out
if he gets agitated?
His heart is...
Call her now.
No.
You call her if you want.
There's no warning alert on my phone.
But the index is fluctuating.
I think it should be fine.
Perhaps,
they've made up already.
But if the two of them
get back together,
we are the ones who make it happen.
That's a good thing, Wifey.
How about going into our room
and celebrating it?
I'll take a shower first.
I didn't even know
there was a nice hotel
around here.
Once our resort project
is completed,
it will be the best hotel in town.
Of course.
No one's design
can beat my boss's.
They should know their place.
Being a bootlicker again.
Our reporting relationship
can only last
because of that, right?
Is that so?
I always thought
it was your intelligence and talents.
Flattering my boss
is part of my job too.
Fine.
I'm going to get the key card.
No.
I won't run away.
Who knows?
Please swipe the card.
Thank you.
Sorry, Mr. Gu.
A moment, please.
Our system
is rebooting.
All right.
In the past two days,
the power system's
been a little unstable.
The breaker trips
occasionally.
We have upgraded the system.
If there's any problem,
feel free to contact us.
Sorry about that.
Thank you.
Don't worry. It's our mistake.
It's done.
Okay. Thank you.
Does the lady
want to check in as well?
Are you sharing the room?
Yes, thank you.
Are we not?
Don't waste your money.
I can sleep on the floor.
Please give me another room.
No.
I'll take the bed and you take the floor then.
My ID. Thank you.
Let's go.
I never thought we would check in to a hotel
under such circumstances.
You called this checking-in to a hotel?
Instead of going home, we stay in the hotel.
What else could it be if it's not
checking-in to a hotel?
You're right.
By the way,
did you tell your aunt you are not
going home tonight?
I...
Get on the bed.
It feels a little far to talk like that.
Get on the bed?
Do you feel unsafe with me?
How is that
even possible?
Come on then.
Here.
I will definitely
control myself.
What were you saying?
I was saying
did you tell your aunt that you are staying out?
I lied to her and said that I am working overtime.
Oh, no.
She'll not spare me.
If she knew
that you didn't want me,
she wouldn't spare you for sure.
Did you tell your aunt
everything?
Well, no.
But I had to keep it a secret and it was so hard.
Actually, after the accident,
I tried looking for you.
My parents' deaths
were a huge blow to me.
But I remember everything.
I told my aunt that I wanted to find you
and say thanks to you.
What then?
Then,
my aunt said she couldn't find you.
To me,
you're my life savior.
But to you,
they weren't good memories.
My aunt told me
not to live in the past
and that I had to step out of it and start afresh.
I never thought
we ended up meeting each other again.
Actually, I kind of regret it.
If you didn't meet me again,
your heart
wouldn't have had frequent glitches.
You could continue
living your life based on
your previous lifestyle
and live all the way to 80 years old.
And you wouldn't have so much worry
and trouble.
If I didn't meet you again,
I would have left this world
after winning the award.
I never regret meeting you,
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Forget it.
If we get too intimate,
your heart rate
will keep rising.
I don't want to send you
to the emergency room
while we're dating.
We are the most special couple
in the world.
I should just sleep on the floor.
It's too cold on the floor.
I should go instead.
Hold on.
I've thought about it.
We need to set our own rules
of getting along together.
Ensure it's strictly enforced.
And we should keep your heart rate
within a safe range.
Not only will it
be good for your heart,
but also make us
less alienated.
This is not something
within my abilities.
I'll leave it to you.
All right.
Go to bed.
I'll do the thinking.
Go on and sleep.
We can share the same bed.
But we can't kiss.
We can hug each other.
But that depends.
Is this okay for you?
Whatever you say.
Good night.
(I can kiss him on the cheek when he's asleep.)
(We can look into each other's eyes,
but have to keep it short.)
(When he's angry, I can behave
in a coquette-ish manner.)
(I can help dry his hair. Wear matching couple
T-shirts and exchange roles for one day.)
Jia Jia, here's your coffee.
What's wrong?
What's on your mind?
I don't know.
My mind is blank.
Look, even the office is empty.
It's so desolate.
You have me.
Knock it off.
Su Man Lin is gone.
I don't really like her,
but listening to her bossing me around
actually livened up the place
a little.
And now, Jiang Xiao Ning is gone too.
She used to jump around the place
like a rabbit,
always helping us out with a smile on her face.
But now that I don't see her.
The office
seems so lifeless.
Have a cup of coffee.
It helps improve your mood.
Jia Jia.
Here are the materials that you asked for.
Thank you, Dong Dong.
Now, it feels like
the atmosphere here
is much better now.
Was the atmosphere bad?
I was so down before you came back.
You should avoid
going out so often.
If not,
I'll have no one
to talk to in the office.
Sure. No problem.
Go now. Get back to your work.
Why are you still laughing?
Hello?
Were you laughing earlier?
No.
You...
Just now,
you were pulling a long face.
But
you were all smiles
as soon as you saw him.
You rolled your eyes at me.
Are you...
What are you talking about?
You...
I'm saying...
Oh, no.
This is bad.
What happened?
The landmark project.
Mr. Gu's previous plan
was not detailed enough.
So during this time,
we've been making adjustments
based on the opinions
of the project expert group.
Here comes the final feedback.
There are many things that require amendments.
But Mr. Gu isn't around. What do we do?
I'm sure all of you are aware of the amendments
needed for the project, right?
Mr. Xu, we were just talking about it.
Mr. Xu, what do we do?
Cheng Dong, why don't you go?
You have experience in it after all.
Brother Kai, you need to be mindful.
How could you randomly assign
someone to deal with it?
Su Man Lin was the first assistant director.
It'll not be a problem if she's around.
And she's familiar with Mr. Gu's style.
But you expect me to take over at the last moment.
Aren't you ruining
the previous design concept?
We should wait for Mr. Gu to come back.
Mr. Gu hasn't been here
for so long.
He should be back soon.
No.
Definitely not.
No one is allowed to contact Gu Chuan.
You hear me?
If anyone dares to breathe a word of this
to Gu Chuan,
I won't go easy on you.
Mr. Xu.
How do we solve this then?
I'm here, aren't I?
Wait to hear from me.
It's been a while.
Not really. Does it feel that long?
Perhaps I've been missing you.
That's why
it felt like it's been a while.
Knock it off. I know you.
Stop beating around the bush.
Just put your cards on the table.
There's been a minor problem with the design
for the landmark project.
It requires some amendments.
Gu Chuan got something to deal with
and he couldn't take time off.
You're the only one I can think of.
Are you asking me
to go back and amend the design?
After all, you were the first assistant director
of this project.
No one's a better candidate.
But do you think
I could still bring myself to go back there again?
Everyone in the company
must hate me to the core.
I don't know what they think
and I don't care.
All I know is that
you have put a lot of effort
into this project too.
You can't just let it
fall apart.
I would love to help.
But I've booked
a flight ticket for tomorrow.
Where to?
I applied for a position
at a foreign design company
and I'm going to report to work.
So this city's
iconic architectural design plan
and the control and guide...
Actually...
Hey, are you guys
even listening?
Cheng Dong, they think
your proposal
doesn't match Mr. Gu's style.
This makes no difference at all.
What can I do?
Mr. Gu isn't here.
I can only voice out my opinion
and discuss it with you guys!
What's the point of asking all of you here?
Calm down. Let's discuss it.
We'll find a way.
Hear me out.
There have been some changes in the project.
So I've invited Su Man Lin
to help us out.
She was supposed
to report to work at a
design company in Italy.
But I managed to persuade her
to stay and help us out.
She'll leave after completing the project.
Welcome back.
Aren't you going to welcome her?
Save it.
Our top priority is the design.
Nothing else matters.
Cheng Dong.
Tell me the feedback.
What are the problems?
This is the report from the project team.
Take a look.
Sister Man Lin.
It's the previous design.
♪Colorful rays of light♪
♪I can see everything♪
♪So empty♪
♪The people around♪
♪Their feelings♪
♪One, two, three, count with me♪
♪If the youth is precious, then cheers♪
♪Those blazing dreams, follow my command♪
♪Four, five, six♪
♪Chase recklessly, long live the young♪
♪You are the most perfect when full of vitality♪
Man Lin.
Welcome back.
The studio is having some difficulties
and Gu Chuan isn't around.
I need to come back.
Thank you.
Less sugar.
♪You are the most perfect when full of vitality♪
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪