(The Penthouse brought a sensation
all over Korea.)
(They're back.)
(Stories that'll leave you
speechless)
(Don't kill your husband.)
(More extreme stories)
(Stories to draw you right in)
(Stories with plot twists)
(Their own awards ceremony,
Hidden Awards)
(And...)
(a mysterious woman is
at the studio.)
(Even stronger temptations are
coming.)
(A heated villain contest to leave
everyone fuming)
(The story that hasn't ended yet.)
(Aren't you excited?)
(We will begin now.)
The Penthouse 2,
Hidden Room, is now open!
(The Penthouse 2 Special,
Hidden Room: Unfinished Story)
(Um Ki Joon as Joo Dan Tae)
Right.
The first season was sensational,
but the second season gained
even more popularity.
- I love this.
- What?
When I start a show
and there's an empty seat.
It's so obvious that
someone is missing.
I like it real.
- Indeed.
- That is Lee Ji Ah's seat.
Ji Ah is currently filming, right?
Yes.
By the time we were filming this,
all the filming for the drama was...
supposed to be finished,
but with dramas, filming schedules
always get behind.
Right.
By the time the show airs,
the last episode of The Penthouse 2
would've aired.
But we haven't...
watched the last episode...
as we're sitting here.
I'm so frustrated.
(Eugene as Oh Yoon Hee)
- You know what I mean, right?
- Yes.
I'm dying to find out
what happens in the last episode.
But our viewers would've
already watched it.
Yes, they'd have watched
the last episode by now.
Indeed.
We've prepared a video...
of how sensational
The Penthouse 2 was like,
so let's go ahead
and watch that first.
You made it sound as if you prepared
the video.
Our crew has prepared it.
"Our story inside The Penthouse".
Splendor from which you can't
take your eyes off of.
- 1.5 million dollars!
- 2 million dollars!
- 3 million!
- 4 million!
- How much?
- 5 million.
In The Penthouse,
everyone has millions of dollars.
(To these people,
a 5-million-dollar home is nothing.)
I want to live
somewhere like this too.
While watching the drama,
did you ever feel...
like the life in the drama was
so different from yours?
However,
that is very much not the case.
That is, when you look closely.
My desire for money...
(Her desire has been filled?)
(But it's in human nature
to have endless desires.)
(Even if it means they must sell
their souls...)
Even if it means they must sell
their souls,
A return on investment
of 250 percent.
they want more.
What I want is
the grand prize trophy.
With people, there are things
that we want to take,
I'll do whatever it takes
to erase your memory.
and there are others
that we want to protect.
Are you sure
you can protect Eun Byeol?
I'm going to protect her
with my life.
When you see it
from that perspective,
you'll realize that these people
in the drama are just like us.
Even if that means you have
to kill Bae Ro Na?
Except that how they get things is
not exactly right.
Every human has desires.
I think The Penthouse is
a dramatized example...
of what happens when people try
to fill their desires...
in the wrong ways.
There's another human instinct...
that this drama alludes to.
Let's look
at each character in the drama...
to examine this closely.
Pull yourself together, Oh Yoon Hee.
Seo Jin.
That is, humans aren't
single-faced,
but have multiple faces.
In other words,
the good and the bad,
and...
Hello,
I'm Director Cheon Seo Jin.
the strong...
and the weak coexist in us.
(Opposing traits coexist in us.)
Shim Su Ryeon was almost the only
"good" character in the drama.
I'm sorry, Yoon Hee.
I'm going to use you for a bit.
Even she uses others...
to get her revenge on someone.
You're my winning lottery ticket...
Oh Yoon Hee was the same.
(Yoon Hee is someone who knew
how to appreciate her people.)
She...
(Get rid of Shim Su Ryeon.)
repaid goodness with bad.
And in the first season,
Cheon Seo Jin did every bad thing
you could possibly imagine.
I feel like a monster.
I feel like it's all my fault.
It's driving me crazy.
Even she was a human
who has regrets.
(Even she has her weak side.)
Like this, The Penthouse...
narrates that humans don't change,
but with each situation,
different sides of them
are brought out.
Oh Yoon Hee is a great example
of this.
(Yoon Hee suddenly jumped
into the rich people's world.)
After she moves into Hera Palace,
Is this really our house?
her suppressed desires...
start to come out.
They become more extreme.
(Moving into Hera Palace
triggered her greed.)
So, in other words, anyone can be
like Shim Su Ryeon,
Cheon Seo Jin, and Oh Yoon Hee.
With that said,
do you remember
the character keywords last season?
(Sickly sexy)
In season one, this man has...
coined the term, "sickly sexy."
(The sickly sexy man, Ha Yoon Chul)
I warned you.
I won't stay still if you hurt
my wife.
Ha Yoon Chul showed
his macho side...
and even a chokeslam,
becoming a strong sexy man.
Strong sexy!
People change after all.
(Eugene's keyword fit her
perfectly.)
And back in season one,
Oh Yoon Hee was described...
as someone who's always fighting,
crying, or drinking.
I quit drinking in season two.
That's not easy to do.
(She didn't drink a single sip
of alcohol in season two.)
(She doesn't even have
a glass in front of her.)
I didn't want people
to get mad at me...
for still drinking
after killing someone while drunk,
so I quit drinking.
Then, who's taking...
this "fighting, crying, or drinking"
keyword?
(Cheon Seo Jin)
Open the door, Oh Yoon Hee!
(She fights with Yoon Hee,)
(with Yoon Chul,)
You jerk!
(and with Joo Dan Tae,
who she got along great with.)
You're the stupid one!
You jerk.
Get out!
(As if that's not enough,
she fights with her daughter too.)
You fought so much.
Do you know what we've done
for you?
When did I ever ask for that?
- Ha Eun Byeol!
- What?
Like mother like daughter.
(She cries because of her daughter.)
I think I might go crazy
if my daughter was like that.
(She cries because of her father.)
She cried so much.
I'm sorry.
The way she cries...
Don't go to Oh Yoon Hee.
(And she cries even more
because of men.)
(Why don't I drink some soju
to feel better?)
(Maybe some hard liquor this time.)
She drank a lot.
(But her favorite is wine.)
You took my keyword.
Drinking by the bottle, I see.
(It's delicious)
(Drinking by the bottle is
the best way to drink.)
This drama is...
filled with quite strong characters.
That was a whole bottle of wine.
There has been another
big change in keywords.
Back in season one,
with just one wig,
Gu Ho Dong went from Gu Ho Dong
to Logan Lee.
(Logan Lee's
ultimate disguise was his wig.)
Hair, hair!
This keyword now goes to...
Shim Su Ryeon.
At this point, wigs seem to be
their couple item, don't you think?
(Are wigs their couple item?)
That's a wrap-up of
"Our story inside The Penthouse".
Did you root for the same people
you did in season one...
in season two?
I'm a real fan of The Penthouse,
and I used to detest Cheon Seo Jin
in season one,
but in season two,
I started to feel bad for her.
Who will I start rooting for...
and start hating in the next season?
I'm Jo Jung Sik,
SBS' favorite news anchor.
That was great.
- I just thought of something.
- What is it?
You know how at the start,
we're talking in millions?
- That's right.
- As we kept filming,
20 million dollars started
sounding like nothing.
I see.
Dan Tae, Yoon Chul, and I invest
in real estate,
- and that's 70 million.
- Right.
The three of us decided
that that's too little,
so I think we changed it
to 160 million.
We made the numbers
higher like that.
You lose your touch with reality.
It's not even our money.
- We don't even have 30 dollars.
- Exactly.
(Yoon Joo Hee as Ko Sang A)
You lose your touch with reality.
In the clip, we saw...
a lot of crying from So Yeon.
I thought about how exhausting
all of that would've been.
Whenever I was shooting for days,
I'd lose some weight...
and that really stressed me out.
For season two, I'd eat a lot
to prepare myself,
but even just after one scene,
I'd lose it all.
Every scene...
required a lot of energy to film.
I just realized how much I screamed.
I'd like to thank my vocal cords
for not giving out.
And a big change we saw
in season two is...
- Yoon Jong Hun.
- in Ha Yoon Chul.
The emphasis was on "sickly"
in season one,
but now, the emphasis seems
to be on "sexy"...
in the second season.
Sickly sexy.
I feel so awkward now.
Why are you so anxious?
Right.
- Could you keep your hands still?
- Sorry.
He keeps wiping his hands...
- after we called him sexy.
- Are you trying to show off?
(He's blushing.)
Is that what you were doing?
To appeal your sexy charm?
What a sly man you are.
The kids...
also played a huge role
in the drama.
They're the best.
The Penthouse kids...
have sent video greetings
to the cast.
(Video greetings
from The Penthouse kids)
Let's go and watch.
Mom and Dad, I miss you!
Hello, Jong Hun and So Yeon!
Have a great shoot today.
I hope that we'll get
to meet again...
as a happy family.
Cheers!
Mom and Dad, Dan Tae
and Su Ryeon.
Thank you for filming with us
in season two.
It was an honor to be acting
on the set with you.
I look forward to filming with you
in Season Three as well.
I miss you.
Have fun with the shoot today!
Cheers!
Mom, Yoon Hee, and Yoon Chul,
who turned out to be my dad,
I'm a little sad...
that I'm not there with you today,
but have fun!
(Dear Oh Yoon Hee and Ha Yoon Chul)
My mom, Ma Ri, who I respect
and love so much,
I'm a little sad that I'm not there
with you right now.
But I'll be rooting for you
from afar.
And Mom, I have a dad now!
(Dear Kang Ma Ri)
Let's make a happy family...
in Season Three.
Mom and Dad, I'm so lonely
without you two here.
I'd love to be with you next time.
Good luck with the shoot today.
And Eun Seok,
it's been so long since we last saw
each other.
We're always rooting for you.
- Good luck with the shoot today.
- Good luck!
Good luck!
- We love you!
- Logan, you keep meeting my mom.
Right!
- That's right.
- They've got something to say.
You better watch out for me.
- Good luck.
- You're my son!
Cheers, everyone!
- I have a son now too.
- It's weird, seeing them like this.
- They are adorable!
- You could be their new dad.
Seok Hoon Lee!
That was a strong comment
at the end.
Seok Kyung and Seok Hoon have...
"You keep meeting my mom."
sent Logan a warning.
- That was a big blow.
- They're warning me.
So,
you're going to get back
with her, right?
I don't know.
I can see from the clip...
that they have so much love...
for their moms and dads
in the drama.
You have a huge fandom.
Let's check out the clips...
that The Penthouse kids have
picked out.
(They also gathered again.)
(An adorable and hilarious talk)
(The best scenes,
chosen by The Penthouse kids)
When I got the script
for the first episode,
the first thing I read was,
"A girl is dead on the ground."
Right. Ro Na.
(A long-haired girl is dead
on the ground!)
They said a girl was lying, dead.
I wondered who it would be.
Who would it be?
I never imagined it would be me.
(You're wrong, Bae Ro Na.)
Later on, when I read the script,
it said that Ro Na was dead.
"'Ro Na's dead.'
What, Ro Na's dead?"
"Eun Byeol killed her?"
I was so surprised.
"Then what happens to me?"
- My only connection...
- They all worry about their share.
- Yes. Ro Na is all he has.
- She's my only plot line...
and she dies?
- I did worry about my share.
- See?
I was very shocked and very upset.
(It's okay, Ro Na.)
But I had this slight...
This strong feeling that
she'd come back.
And when the script confirmed it,
I thought, "Okay, great."
Yoon Hee says to Ro Na,
"Ro Na, get up."
"Mom's so scared."
There's that line in a scene.
Ro Na.
Ro Na. Open your eyes.
(Emotional)
Mom's scared. Open your eyes, Ro Na!
I was supposed to be dead then.
Eugene acted out her part
so emotionally.
She was like a real mom.
- It was a really cold day.
- I was dead and a tear fell.
I remember that.
(Ro Na's most shocking
and emotional scene)
My dad.
Mr. Bong really helped me a lot
with my acting.
In the last episode,
he objects to the sentencing,
and he jumps up and...
Is it called the hammer?
He grabs that and climbs up...
- and jumps.
- That was hilarious.
- Joo Dan Tae!
- That was funny.
- I missed it.
- A flying squirrel.
(Kyu Jin the flying squirrel
stood out in this scene.)
Do you know who I am?
I couldn't stop laughing
when he shot that scene.
What would you have done without me?
I will show you!
Kyu Jin even shot some footage
on his own.
- That clip is worth keeping.
- If there were a Korean Joker,
wouldn't that be Bong Tae Gyu?
That's what I think.
What a compliment.
I believed my mom was dead,
and I get to see her again.
(He's reunited with Ro Na and
Su Ryeon whom he thought were dead.)
(Seok Hoon...)
(Mom?)
It's so sad
if you just see the highlights.
I almost cried here.
My gosh.
(Mom.)
(I missed you, Seok Hoon.)
Mom.
(I missed you so much.)
From Seok Hoon's standpoint,
people he thought were dead
suddenly reappeared.
So I wasn't sure...
- how to portray my feelings.
- That's true.
"Am I dead?"
- I thought I'd be really surprised.
- "Am I dead?"
"I go up to Seo Jin..."
"and do that?"
The last scene of episode four.
I can't...
This was a famous scene.
(Seok Kyung blackmails Seo Jin.)
That's why I'm being shameless
and asking you for this favor.
- That scene alone.
- Her Eun Byeol impression's funny.
I thought, "How am I to do this?"
(She pulled it off with
lots of thought and hard work.)
(Look at her act...)
Why did you just run away?
Instead of saving your dad?
(That's a perfect high act!)
I was so surprised that scene
was the episode's finale.
Shall we restart our discussion?
I imitated Eun Byeol.
She did so well.
- Right? I was surprised.
- The hair thing.
(Her Eun Byeol impression
was talk of the town.)
My dad asked you.
That was so funny,
I kept rewatching that part.
No!
- It was funny.
- It was.
(Let's watch it.)
No, no.
- No, no.
- Please.
Do it just once.
(Shudder of embarrassment)
- She's so embarrassed.
- Let's watch.
(Channeling Ha Eun Byeol)
(Ha Eun Byeol carbon copy)
Don't make jokes.
My dad asked you.
Just let me compete.
You're the director...
- She did pretty good.
- That was good.
She nailed the details.
Eun Byeol's so sweet.
You're not teasing me,
are you? I'm sorry.
The scene that got me emotional...
was where I confess my baldness.
That was so sad.
(Jenny was bullied so much,
the stress caused hair loss.)
- What... What happened?
- This was so sad.
When did this happen?
Jenny had been through a lot...
in season two.
(She was bullied
throughout the season.)
She'd wanted to tell her mom,
but she held back
and then it all came out at once.
Ms. Shin said, "Who did this?"
I crumbled when she said that.
Who was it?
Who did this to my daughter?
Tell me now!
That was so moving.
I watched the episode as a viewer,
and tears kept welling up.
Jenny's acting
alongside Ms. Shin's...
I felt the maternal love
and connection,
and I also felt
just how hard it must've been...
for Jenny and I felt bad for her.
Min Hyuk doesn't think or care,
and he just enjoyed what happened.
I think he's
the worst of all the bullies.
I'm so stressed out
because of my character.
(Stressful headache)
On my personal social media account,
I apologized to
all the Min Hyuks nationwide.
Whenever the drama airs,
all the Min Hyuks get chewed out,
and I felt terrible.
In the bathtub in our home,
- I help my mom bathe.
- That scene...
(Jenny found out
what her mom does for a living.)
- Keep still.
- That scene was really...
I'm so grateful towards Ms. Shin.
That day, I had a lot of trouble
getting into the right mindset.
I heard Ms. Shin's voice
where she's emotional and choked up,
and I could feel her trembling
through her back.
That suddenly got me emotional.
Even after we'd finished the scene,
even after we were done,
we both kept crying.
Even after the scene.
(It made us think when
we last saw our parents' backs.)
(Which scene
do you remember the most?)
(Every scene in
The Penthouse 2 was special.)
That was lovely.
We were watching the clips
and Eugene...
- She cried.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- Ro Na's death.
We were talking about
your crying scene...
- and you cried again.
- I worried when I got the script.
"I won't be able to stop crying."
That's what I thought.
Because I have a daughter
in real life,
- My gosh.
- It felt...
- Oh, no.
- Yes, right.
To be honest, in my acting career,
I really never wanted to...
play a role in which my child dies.
No one knew that Ro Na would die.
So when I got the script...
"I really have to do this."
It's really an emotion
you don't want to experience.
Talking about it set her off again.
(She got emotional again.)
(They feel how she felt
during the shoot.)
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
- Talking about it made her cry.
- Excuse me.
Who are you?
It's Leon!
- Leon.
- It's Leon.
- A bag instead of a plant.
- The greatest scene for me...
- Yes?
is where Kim So Yeon...
takes out a phone's SIM card
and chews it.
(The phone contained a video
that incriminated her.)
The script said...
I flush the SIM card
down the toilet.
The director said, "So Yeon."
"We prepared a SIM card
made with chewing gum."
"You can chew that
and pretend to swallow it."
So I said, "Okay, I'll do that."
But there was no chewing gum.
- My gosh.
- What?
So I had no choice but to...
actually put the SIM card
in my mouth...
and then pretend to chew it.
The chewing was a mime.
They didn't have the chewing gum.
I was so surprised
when I saw that episode.
- The script...
- It didn't say that.
Right. There was no mention of
chewing a SIM card.
I wondered how it came about.
- It was the director's idea.
- It came from our director's head.
We've heard people talk about
acting as if one's possessed,
- but our director's possessed too.
- So...
Jong Hun coined a term for
our director's directing.
- "Direction of blessing".
Whatever the scene,
he just says something...
- and it becomes a great scene.
- Yes.
- He lets the actors shine.
- He gives us an upgrade.
But he's gruff too.
- He gives us all the credit.
- Yes.
But even if he asked
the actor to chew a SIM card,
if the actor refuses,
we wouldn't have had that scene.
- She willingly...
- Yes.
The director could say,
"How about you chew and swallow?"
- You could refuse. "No."
- Right.
"I'll suck on it instead."
(Laughing)
- Sucking on it is weird.
- It is a bit.
- She willingly...
- Yes.
- Chew, chew, gulp.
- That's amazing.
- But...
- Oh. Finally.
- My gosh.
- She's here.
Are you Shim Su Ryeon
or Na Ae Gyo?
- Hang on. Her hair...
- Na Ae Gyo?
Shim Su Ryeon.
- Good job.
- Take a seat.
Well done.
She finished her scene.
- Good job.
- Are you done?
- Give her some applause.
- Thanks.
The shoot's officially done, then.
Like Eun Kyung just said,
- is it really now...
- It's really over.
Did you run over?
I ran fast. I was in such a hurry.
- I wanted to get here fast.
- People who haven't watched...
think you're just Na Ae Gyo.
- But... Yes.
- Oh...
My top half is Su Ryeon...
- and my bottom half...
- Na Ae Gyo.
- It's a collaboration.
- I see that.
It's a collaboration.
This was intentional.
You wouldn't know,
but we were talking about
the greatest scenes.
Right now, all I see is
the meat right in front of my eyes.
- Oh, the meat.
- What is that doing there?
- You were looking at the meat?
- Yes.
I thought you were looking at Logan.
I found that quite pleasing.
- That's hilarious.
- But you were looking at the meat.
She doesn't care about me.
I'm invisible.
What scene
personally stuck with you?
I'd say the one
where I played two roles.
It was the first time I'd done so,
and it was really hard.
You talked about playing two roles,
but she actually played four roles.
She was Na Ae Gyo, Shim Su Ryeon,
Su Ryeon pretending to be Ae Gyo,
and Ae Gyo
pretending to be Su Ryeon.
There seem to be
some minute details.
When I play opposite myself,
what Ae Gyo will say and do,
I must take that into consideration
when I play Su Ryeon.
And when I play Ae Gyo,
I have to think about
what Su Ryeon will say and do.
When we act, we usually have
someone else to bounce off of.
But I didn't have that this time.
I had to think about everything...
and calculate what to do.
That was quite hard,
but it was fun too.
Would you play a double role again?
No.
(Is this the first and last time?)
You must've read the script...
where it says that
Joo Dan Tae's arrested.
How did you feel when you read that?
You need an outlet like that
if Season Three is to work.
(It's a must for Season Three!)
Oh, so we were all
dressed like prisoners.
We'd gathered around wearing that,
and we talked about how
it was a first and so fascinating.
Yoon Chul said...
"I'm used to it."
He had lots of experience.
So did I.
I even went on the run.
- That's right.
- They all wore handcuffs...
and what's that rope called?
They were tied up in a rope.
It was so funny to
see them all like that.
- That day was the day...
- You were relaxed.
we took the most photos
during filming.
- All of us.
- We were all there.
Including the whole shoot...
So now,
we wanted to thank all the actors...
for giving us
all these twists and surprises.
- We prepared an award ceremony.
- That's right.
I want to thank the crew...
that put together this special show.
- They prepared gifts.
- Oh.
The item caught Ji Ah's eye
as soon as she entered.
- Is that the real thing?
- It's real.
You didn't get much rest
since the first season.
You've been working hard.
Right now, a healthy
immune system is a must.
To boost your immune system,
we prepared a full set of
nutritious Korean beef.
We all get it?
- If you win.
- First place only.
- Only one gets it.
- Is there a dud?
- Some get nothing?
If you don't, you must try harder.
(I want it so bad.)
Are you messing with us?
And also, from the set,
the limited edition goods
that you used in Hera Palace.
Look, the Hera Palace goods.
- Hera Palace goods...
- That's crazy.
- and nutritious beef.
- No wonder it looked familiar.
Shall we give out the first award?
The first award is called...
A for Effort.
Shall we check out the nominees?
(Hidden Awards: A for Effort)
A for Effort.
Joo Dan Tae.
"Dooly the Little Dinosaur".
Looking over here
And over there
You ruined many childhoods.
- But I still can't see
- Carrying a dagger.
Yoon Hee
Kang Ma Ri, Oh Yoon Hee.
"I Am Not Alone".
(Giggling)
After heavy rain and strong winds
- The sun will shine again
Good!
When it hurts too much
- Give a loud shout
- She was in S.E.S.
Lee Kyu Jin, Ko Sang A.
"Morning Dew".
All together!
On the leaves
- "Hee".
- Hee
- Please look at me
- I laughed so much at this.
- You used to
- like me
- What a dreadful harmony.
The kind that I love.
- Hee
You're so serious.
(A for Effort)
Isn't this stiff competition?
- A for Effort.
- Yes.
I can't pick one.
The nominees are all so great.
I think Dooly's a tough one to beat.
Oh... Joo Dan Tae.
It was such an unexpected
song choice.
How did you end up singing that?
- It was improvised.
- Oh, really?
The director wanted me to
sing something...
while I was looking for Yoon Hee.
He wanted me to sing
the hide and seek song.
"That might be boring."
"Dooly might be fun."
And he went with it.
How did you think of that song?
"Looking over here and there".
- To that...
- Not to mention that...
- Dan Tae sings it so very well.
- Yes.
- He's a musical actor.
- Exactly.
- It was like...
- Yes.
- It made it a good scene.
- It did.
He's a good singer,
- so it made it extra chilling.
- Right.
And then you two
singing "Morning Dew".
That's a tough candidate too.
- Was that in the script?
- No.
- That too?
- Really?
I came up with the idea.
A for Effort...
- is very close.
- Right.
- I'll announce the winner.
- Go ahead.
(Why is this so tense?)
The Penthouse Hidden Awards.
A for Effort goes to...
Oh, gosh.
These people got it.
Lee Kyu Jin, Ko Sang A.
Congratulations.
(Congratulations)
(Placid)
- Wow, that's so cool.
- What is this?
All of these? Not just one?
It's really all here.
- Of course, it is.
- Is this real?
(I'm so jealous.)
(Flustered)
Thank you so much.
The goods are beautiful.
- That's worth it.
- Yes.
Us singing "Hee" was improvised too.
We deserve this.
- What a nice wrap-up.
- Kyu Jin!
- Well said.
I married the right guy.
That's so funny.
You must all wonder why...
Kyu Jin and Sang A won.
They're the only people
who sang two songs,
and their singing...
took up 46 seconds,
the longest of anyone.
That's where the effort comes from,
so we gave them
the A for Effort award.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
Our next award...
is the Fragmented Memory Award.
I know it's unclear what
the award is for,
so let's take a look
at the nominees first.
(Hidden Awards:
Fragmented Memory Award)
The Fragmented Memory Award.
Cheon Seo Jin.
(I'm not going to beg you for it.)
(Cheon Seo Jin: Says this and that
and changes her mind constantly)
Yoon Hee! Please...
(Bursting into laughter)
(Begging her desperately)
That's so funny.
Please save me, Yoon Hee.
She's very quick to adapt
to her circumstances.
(Says this and that
and changes her mind constantly)
(I'll never go back to you.)
(Bursting into laughter)
(Please stay with me.)
- That was so fast.
- This could only be you.
- Why don't we put those flowers...
- She changed her mind so quickly.
Ma Doo Ki.
- Whoever even touches...
- He is one formidable competitor.
(Ma Doo Ki: There are so many
different mes inside of me.)
(I completely agree with Seok Hoon.)
- That was really funny.
- Guys, how can you be so cold?
Your classmate is dead. How come
no one seems to genuinely grieve?
Seok Hoon, where are you going?
Oh, you're leaving early today?
(Be careful on your way.)
("I will.")
(That's my boy.)
- He's so good at this.
- What are you looking at?
Ha Yoon Chul.
(Ha Yoon Chul:
Different from moment to moment)
(You're not alone anymore.)
(I can't leave you alone here.)
(I can't even watch.)
What did I do to deserve you?
At least he's sincere at the moment.
He's so easy.
He just changes from moment
to moment.
Get your hands off of my daughter!
(Can't even lift his head)
- The editing is amazing.
- He's an impressive dad to Ro Na.
(Ha Yoon Chul:
Different from moment to moment)
(I'll protect you, Ha Eun Byeol.)
Now he's an impressive
dad to Eun Byeol.
This is amazing, really.
(You're not the same
Ha Yoon Chul of old.)
(Hidden Awards:
Fragmented Memory Award)
I vote for Ha Yoon Chul.
This is so hilarious.
You're trash.
- The nominees are neck and neck.
- They are.
But to be honest,
we don't know who the winner is
before opening the envelope too.
But this is really tough.
- Yes, everyone's a good nominee.
- It's a close call.
Ha Yoon Chul.
- Ha Yoon Chul?
- That piece of trash.
- Oh, the piece of trash.
- He's a strong candidate.
Ji Ah, who do you think
will win this one?
- I vote for the trash too.
- Another vote for the trash.
Another vote for the trash...
Now I hope someone else gets it,
instead of the obvious choice.
I think it will be me.
Jong Hun votes for himself.
- He votes for himself too.
- That's right.
Will there be an upset?
The Penthouse Hidden Awards.
Fragmented Memory Award...
goes to...
the piece of trash. Congratulations.
(Congratulations.)
So this is how it turns out.
Wow, this is great.
Thank you.
This is so funny.
Jong Hun, can you tell us
how you feel, winning this award?
I think I deserve it.
We're getting a lot of
famous lines out of this.
This award is for your extraordinary
fragmented memory.
Now let's present the next award.
The next award...
is the Sudden Injury Award.
(Hidden Awards:
Sudden Injury Award)
Sudden Injury Award.
- Did you forget something?
- Ha Yoon Chul.
(Ha Yoon Chul: Suddenly injured
out of nowhere)
Oh, that kind of injury.
- Our relationship...
- Lee Kyu Jin.
- Ma Ri. Don't do this.
- We chose the wording carefully.
(Lee Kyu Jin: Sudden sudden injury)
- What are you saying?
- Lee Min Hyuk.
(Lee Min Hyuk: Unexpected
self-injury)
Oh, that time.
Hey.
Guys, I think I broke my arm.
Logan Lee.
(Logan Lee: An explosive,
sudden injury)
You haven't seen this yet.
- This is episode 13?
- Yes, this is on episode 13.
(Logan Lee: An explosive,
sudden injury)
- Right next to him.
- Right next to him...
- No one's seen this yet, right?
- No, no one saw this yet.
So that's how it exploded.
(Hidden Awards:
Sudden Injury Award)
- That was so entertaining.
- Wow, look.
- That final scene was shocking.
- Look forward to Season Three!
You take this.
It's yours.
This is yours.
I'll even give you mine.
I feel like they're
giving me a gift in advance.
So is Logan Lee returning
in Season Three?
No one knows.
Didn't we say the same thing
during the season one special?
- This sounds familiar.
- I know.
That's right. The ending...
We talked about if Shim Su Ryeon
would be coming back.
It always ends in a cliffhanger.
Logan himself doesn't know yet.
I heard a rumor that I'm not
going to be in it?
So you heard through
a rumor yourself?
That's so hurtful.
- The suspense is killing me.
- Let's announce the winner.
The Penthouse Hidden Awards.
The Sudden Injury Award...
goes to...
Logan Lee. Congratulations.
(Congratulations.)
My long-time friend
- That I've known for ages
(Solemn)
- But still...
- You should relax.
- I'm sure we'll meet again.
- I'm sure.
- He has to come out again.
- He's like a phoenix.
- That's right.
- I wanted one of these so badly.
What time is it now?
Logan Lee received this award...
because his injuries appeared
the most severe.
He is the winner
of the Sudden Injury Award.
Next we have
the Exercise is Life Award.
Let's meet our nominees.
(Hidden Awards:
Exercise is Life Award)
Exercise is Life Award.
Joo Dan Tae.
(Joo Dan Tae: Everyday exercise)
With bottles of water.
You filmed a lot of this.
Su Ryeon, Su Ryeon.
Oh Yoon Hee.
- She ran for so long here.
- She ran for a long time.
(Oh Yoon Hee: Athlete)
- She wanted to chase down a car.
- What's this music?
I thought you were Forest Gump.
(Oh Yoon Hee: Athlete)
Wow.
Cheon Seo Jin.
(Cheon Seo Jin: Special training
befitting "Iris")
- She's a witch.
- Look at that.
(Applauding herself)
It's like you're training for all
the parts of an Ironman.
(Cheon Seo Jin: Special training
befitting "Iris")
I feel so bad about that.
Shim Su Ryeon.
(Shim Su Ryeon: Pool)
This was really impressive.
You must be good at pool
in real life.
- I know, right?
- You can tell she's good.
(Shim Su Ryeon: Pool)
(Shim Su Ryeon:
Pool and Mixed Martial Arts)
- Wow.
- What a surprise.
- She's so good at that.
- I know.
(Shim Su Ryeon:
Pool and Mixed Martial Arts)
She's even good at martial arts.
(Shim Su Ryeon: Pool and
Mixed Martial Arts and Shooting)
(Hidden Awards
Exercise is Life Award)
You are the hard-working type.
You exercise, drink,
then exercise some more.
He's working hard so he can
go drinking healthily.
(He takes care of his health
so he can go drinking.)
He's younger than I am,
but I have a lot of respect for him.
And he even films, on top of that.
- Exactly.
- I know.
From the viewers' perspective,
they might think you just ran
for a little bit,
- but you shot the scene many times.
- Yes, we filmed several times.
And you were wearing heels.
I drew on my experience
dancing in heels.
- I see.
- Of course.
I should win that award.
I'm in multiple categories.
- That's true.
- You should get it.
So now you're all getting
a bit more ambitious.
The meat has been right in front
of my eyes this whole time.
She was really looking
at the meat the whole time.
As someone who really loves
to shoot pool himself,
- How did you see it?
- we usually shoot like this.
Usually, we use that pose
when there's really no other way.
In my point of view,
She could've just...
(Was this necessary?)
But she had to do it like that.
(Dong Yeob's tiny but
meaningful analysis)
You're so sharp.
Now, who will win?
I'll announce the winner.
The Penthouse Hidden Awards,
Exercise is Life Award.
The award goes to...
the queen of pool, Shim Su Ryeon.
Congratulations.
(Exercise is Life Award winner,
queen of pool Shim Su Ryeon)
(Congratulations.)
- Finally.
- Thank you.
She couldn't tear her eyes away
from this Korean beef set.
- It does look really tasty.
- It does.
Later on, when you eat the beef,
don't just eat it normally,
but go like this.
(She is happy even though
she's being teased.)
That's good.
Of all the nominees,
Shim Su Ryeon...
was active in the greatest
number of different activities,
making her the winner
of the Exercise is Life Award.
Congratulations.
Next, we have what
many might consider...
the flower of award ceremonies.
This is an award to celebrate
one's hard work.
But as you know,
there's usually only ever
one nominee for this category.
- Now for the award.
- Let's find out who the nominee is.
(Hidden Awards: Special Award)
- Special Award.
- Special Award?
- It's not an achievement award?
- It's a special award.
(Joo Dan Tae)
(A unique existence
in the world of villains)
(Captivated)
(In order to fulfill
his ambitions...)
I love you.
(he'll use any means,
and any method necessary.)
(You can't escape from
the evil forest around him.)
How dare you.
(Violence is his everyday.)
- Violence is his everyday?
- Wow.
Don't waste time and get out.
(Threats are his hobby.)
(Equipped with a home
detention cell.)
Joo Dan Tae.
Please call my mom.
(If you get in his way,)
(he's even willing to kill.)
I really love my daughter...
(A character full
of resentment and rage)
(The genius villain who made
the public quake at his atrocities)
It's the Atrocities Award
for best atrocities committed?
(Joo Dan Tae)
No one else can compare.
(We present this award to you.)
Now for the person who will
receive this award,
(The Atrocities Award)
the Atrocities Award...
This is too funny.
It goes to Um Ki Joon.
Congratulations.
(The Atrocities Award goes to
Joo Dan Tae.)
Congratulations.
(Delivering the Korean beef set
and other prizes)
The beef for the Atrocities Award...
was prepared for you
since last summer.
Please tell us how you feel.
I think I deserve this award.
(I deserve this award.)
(I made that catch phrase.)
He did deserve it.
There's even a new slang term
that arose from this.
"Andante" means slow,
"forte" means strong,
and "Joo Dan Tae" means...
do you know what it is, So Yeon?
To be cruel?
- Yes, that's it.
- Yes, that's correct.
Right now, only Eun Kyung,
Eugene, and So Yeon...
didn't receive any beef sets,
but we only have one category left.
So there's only one award left?
Yes, we only have one left.
But you have two beef sets left,
if you count the producer's.
(The winners are relaxed.)
The final award...
is the Ratings Improvement Award.
Let's see our picks for this award.
(Hidden Awards:
Ratings Improvement Award)
The Ratings Improvement Award.
The helicopter.
- This is a famous scene.
- It really is.
(Helicopter: Made The Penthouse 2
a blockbuster)
Was it really rotating?
That day, the scene was so fun.
Really?
- They had three strong fans.
- I was watching from above.
Oh, this was done with fans.
- With a real helicopter.
- There was a real helicopter too.
- I see.
- Wow.
- That was a great scene.
- That feels great.
The Ma Ri Sauna.
- That's right.
- Clip my toenails too.
- That was a famous line.
- For the ladies with me too.
Who dares to insult Ms. Jincheon?
- Wow, so scary.
- Who was it?
I won't use the same water
as political sewer rats.
Replace the water in the tubs.
Drain the tubs!
- That was so refreshing.
- Wow.
The first appearance.
(Shim Su Ryeon? Na Ae Gyo?)
Who are you?
So impressive.
Shim Su Ryeon?
She kisses him at first sight.
- It was a strong first appearance.
- There's this rumor saying that...
Um Ki Joon directed
this drama himself.
How have you been?
It's been a while,
Joo Dan Tae.
Shadow singer.
(Shadow singer: The perfect high F)
(Perfectly memorized)
I don't believe this.
That was a perfect high F.
(Hidden Awards:
Ratings Improvement Award)
Our nominees are all impressive.
I wonder which it will be?
Furthermore, for our nominees,
we combined the ratings,
the VOD searches, and scenes
chosen by viewers...
to come up with our nominees.
Now,
the winner is...
(The Ratings Improvement Award
goes to...)
The production crew is amazing.
Truly amazing.
Are they going to give it
to everyone?
I saw everything from the front.
Now, the winner is...
There is no winner.
(There is no winner of
the Ratings Improvement Award.)
Instead of choosing a winner,
they're saying everyone is a winner.
We can't leave anyone out
when we talk about...
- improving the ratings.
- That's true.
Is that the Korean beef?
We need one more.
- Thank you.
(They bring the last one
to the stage as well.)
Oh, my gosh.
Wait, who is it?
- What is this?
- It's writer Kim Soon Ok.
Really?
- Wow.
- What is this?
What is this?
Wow, really?
(It's the real Kim Soon Ok.)
- Nice to see you.
- Wow.
(It's the real Kim Soon Ok.)
- My gosh, it's true.
- Where are you going? Catch her.
Catch her.
You have to catch her.
That was so moving.
(Writer Kim Soon Ok surprise visits
the actors to show her support.)
Thank you for all of your
hard work, everyone.
(Everyone, thank you
for all your hard work.)
You're the best, Ms. Kim.
Thank you so much.
I was so surprised.
She came herself because
of the circumstances.
Because of COVID-19,
we couldn't do readings together,
- or drink tea or anything.
- Or gather together.
- Everyone wanted to see her.
- That's right.
But for her to show up so suddenly,
I doubted my own eyes.
- I was so surprised.
- Right.
That's so touching.
In order to alleviate
some of those regrets,
- we decided to have this event.
- That's right.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Bringing writer Ms. Kim here
was the ultimate gift for us.
- That's true.
- It really was.
- Season Three...
- I have no idea.
I'm also really curious about
where Eun Byeol went.
But...
Ms. Jin has a line
where she says to me,
"Mom will..."
- So maybe it's my real mother.
- What?
Or not.
- Since it's the last season,
- You're really shocked.
- He looks like Ahn Yeon Hong.
- a lot will happen.
Evil will be overcome.
- New faces will appear.
- Then who am I?
Jenny's father will appear.
My father and Joo Dan Tae's
relationship.
These things might be
further developed...
in the story.
My father will come out
no matter what.
Whether that's through
a prison break,
- or through bribes.
- Bingo.
- She's right on the nose.
- No matter what.
If there's something I hope for,
I hope Yoon Hee...
accepts her punishment,
and even if they don't have
much money,
I hope she lives happily
ever after with Ro Na.
Ro Na should be happy now.
Instead of always wondering
if she's dead or alive,
I hope she has more
enjoyable, fun scenes.
I want to be friends
with Ro Na again,
and clear up the misunderstandings
that have arisen so far.
Both of our moms are in jail,
so it would be nice
if we could lean on each other.
(How sharp of her)
- That's my personal opinion.
- Even though her mom's in jail,
- she looks pretty happy.
- How about me?
- But you betrayed her first!
- She's my daughter.
Oh, no.
I thought I'd get married to him
in Season Three.
(Giggling)
I heard through some rumors...
that Min Hyuk would grow up.
(Totally interested)
What did you say?
Min Hyuk would grow up.
Min Hyuk's growing up?
Wow, finally.
(Hooray.)
- That's great.
- Applause.
I really hope so.
I'm so stressed out
because of my character.
- Oh, no. So sad.
- I guess he saw the comments.
The kids have told us
what they're hoping for...
on the next season.
But Jin Bun Hong...
At first,
I thought she was just someone...
- who came because Logan called.
- Right.
But her attitude towards
Eun Byeol is really...
- That's right.
- And there is...
a theory that she's Eun Byeol's
real mother.
What did you say?
(They love her fake acting.)
There's no way.
Yoon Chul did it again?
My, Yoon Jong Hun.
What kind of a jerk are you?
That will end up being
a totally new story.
No one knows anything
about Season Three.
I want Kyu Jin to change a bit.
- In what way?
- In season one,
he was the comic foil,
somewhere between fun and evil,
and in season two, he was mostly
just a comic character.
I'm not sure if I can say this,
but I've run out of
funny things to do.
Personally, I'd like to see..
some change in Kyu Jin's character.
Our family was the most solid
and harmonious...
through season two.
I'm wondering if that will
continue in Season Three.
You're getting anxious.
Is Min Hyuk really my son?
- Yes, exactly.
- That gave me goosebumps.
- Every kids...
- It was Yoon Chul.
It was Yoon Chul again.
Ha Yoon Chul, really.
What are you going around doing?
I had a dream from long ago.
Now that we're heading
to Season Three,
when we saw the kids' interview,
I realized how much...
those children had grown
over the course of a year.
I imagined for a moment...
how their kids might look like...
in season 10.
If we could film 2 seasons
in 1 year...
Just as Eun Kyung said,
if we could have The Penthouse
continue on SBS...
like "Country Diaries"...
We grew up with Bok Gil,
and followed his character
as it grew up too.
My dream has really come true.
I'm really very happy.
But on top of that, to have
so much love from viewers...
That's true. There is always
something like that.
It ends when you think
you're finally getting along.
Elders used to say, "You run out of
rice when you have appetite".
(She loves his jokes.)
Did people say that
back in the days?
You run out of rice
when you have appetite.
- That's very sad.
- Yes. It's very sad.
It's very sad.
And you appease your hunger...
- through season 2 and 3.
- Yes.
What about you, Dan Tae?
He will somehow crawl out of prison.
He'll somehow escape from there
and find the penthouse back.
And he'll take revenge on her.
Su Ryeon...
lived as Ae Gyo.
So I'm expecting Su Ryeon...
to upgrade...
with Na Ae Gyo's attitude.
She thought her revenge was over,
but it starts again...
with Logan's death.
I want her to take bigger revenge.
"Bigger revenge".
- You're not satisfied yet?
- No.
What's supposed to happen to me?
Eugene. What about you?
As of now, all my problems
are solved.
I've paid for my crime
that I suffocated me.
I went to prison.
I thought Su Ryeon was dead,
but she came back alive.
Now I know that
my daughter is alive.
I feel like...
I can really enjoy my time
in prison.
So I'm really curious...
what I can do in the drama.
Right. Is there anything...
you expect to happen?
Maybe a relationship with anyone?
Should I look in Tae Gyu's eyes?
(Interested)
- What about me?
- But Ki Joon...
- She's surprised.
- We were the perfect couple for...
two seasons in a row.
What's happening to me?
Honestly, I think Yoon Hee's
sick of men.
- No more?
- No more. Go away.
(Cutting off her ties
with Ha Yoon Chul)
Ha Yoon Chul's nickname is
the Korean Charlie Chaplin.
Charlie Chaplin had
dozens of children.
So in the next seaon,
we have to focus on
how many children Ha Yoon Chul has.
Okay.
- Just kidding.
- Yes.
Do you want a happy ending
with Cheon Seo Jin...
or Oh Yoon Hee?
Who do you have in your heart?
Let's say it for fun.
- For fun?
- Of course.
She said she doesn't need me,
so I choose her.
He carried it inside himself.
- I don't need you.
- He's hurt.
You take him.
Come to charming Kyu Jin.
(Kyu Jin doesn't miss his chance.)
Call me when you're lonely.
This is crazy.
- Logan Lee.
- Yes.
- In Season Three?
As you saw...
- Are you dead or live?
- I know.
If I return,
I'd probably take revenge.
He went after me this time.
So it's going to get
a little more personal.
That's what I expect.
If not,
I'll enjoy watching
Season Three at home.
You go back to being a viewer.
He said those things,
but what he desperately wants is
that he wants to live.
(What Logan Lee really wants
is to survive.)
- The last episode was a bit...
- He wishes he didn't die.
I hope you return
by all means necessary.
Yes. Thank you.
The production crew mentioned...
about Season Three...
that neither the actors...
- nor we know.
- Right.
Really?
They said...
- the actors are very curious...
- Yes.
and they'll like it too.
But it's not about what we expect...
or what the rumors say.
We got the script.
- What?
- It's shocking.
- This is real.
- Not even the actors know.
- You've never seen it before.
- We haven't received it yet.
I'm getting goosebumps.
The script is so thick.
- He must be really curious.
- I'm utterly shocked.
- I can't wait to read it.
- It's so shocking.
Has it been printed?
Only two scripts have been printed.
Only Writer Kim Soon Ok,
- Director Ju Dong Min...
- I should read that before I go.
and the two of us know
what it's about.
I can't believe it.
Season Three.
(The script won't be shared
for security.)
Episode One.
(Surprised)
Seriously.
- Why did I close my eyes?
- Take it away!
- Take it, So Yeon.
Can you read one, please?
Should I check if Eun Seok's in it?
I don't quite like...
acting childish.
- But...
- You're going to act childish.
I'm serious.
(Reading the script)
- I'm curious.
- What does it say?
- Joo Dan Tae!
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Seriously.
If you have anything sharp,
give it to me.
Joo Dan Tae! Seriously, Joo Dan Tae.
He's really annoying.
Look. This is what happens.
- This is what happens.
- I'm not curious.
Look what happens here.
- I'm curious.
- What?
(What's Season 3 Episode 1 about?)
- That's intense.
- My goodness.
This episode...
is the most shocking...
- first episode so far.
- Right.
- As an incident occurs,
- Again?
Season Three begins.
Something amazing is going to happen
in here.
Will Seol A come back alive?
That's not a statue.
- It wasn't a statue.
- It's been watching all along.
- A person in body painting?
- Yes.
- "Body painting".
- Is it an actor?
It's Seo Jang Hoon in disguise.
That's possible.
- The statue comes alive?
- If the statue moves...
Is there a dead body
inside the statue?
(Surprised)
- That's a reasonable doubt.
- Oh, I know.
Does it start
with Joo Dan Tae's death?
- What?
- I think it's me.
Because I killed Min Seol A.
- Oh, that's right.
- You read it.
- You're right.
- You read the script.
Don't act like you didn't read it.
No.
Logan Lee said no.
I think there's a dead body
inside it.
I was thinking...
where the dead body could be.
When you break it,
a woman lies inside just like that.
In that shape?
My goodness. In that shape?
Let me give you a heads up.
Let's not air this.
Let's just share it with actors.
- No. We can't.
- It's okay.
No, we can't.
As the statue breaks,
a man who looks just like it
walks out.
(She got fooled.)
That's actually a man.
(She didn't get fooled.)
- Gosh.
- Oh, that's the secret.
It wasn't a woman. It was a man.
It's not the statue of Hera,
- but Hercules.
- Is it the statue of Zeus?
- "Hercules".
- Is that true?
- It says in here.
- What a shocking twist.
As the statue of Hera breaks,
Hercules comes out.
My goodness. I can't wait to say it.
The Penthouse 3...
will begin in early June.
When it starts to get hot,
watch The Penthouse 3
and cool things off.
Do we get to meet again
for The Penthouse 3 Special?
See you in The Penthouse 3.
- Thank you.
I don't think I have a chance
to say this...
unless I say it now.
The Penthouse production crew
worked really hard.
Including Director Ju
and Writer Kim,
directing team, filming team,
lighting team,
audio team,
props team and arts team.
As the shoot continued
for over a year,
all actors really pulled it off.
I hope the viewers know that.
And please give us
a lot of compliments.
I thought...
it'd make my day if I could say it.
You won't edit it out, will you?
Please air it.
- Please air it. Promise.
- Thank you.
(Please look forward to
The Penthouse 3.)