DO YOU REMEMBER...
THE SHOCKING ENDING TO SEASON 1?
The end of your revenge
is your death.
Goodbye.
SU RYEON'S DEATH
Kill me. Kill me right now.
Ro Na.
I'm sorry.
YOON HEE'S DOWNFALL
SEO JIN'S WORLD
Everything is okay now.
After a storm comes a calm.
Everything she was
getting framed for gets resolved,
and everyone that she wanted
to leave has been taken care of.
The real story starts now.
WE'LL TELL YOU THE REAL STORY NOW.
THE PENTHOUSE 2...
WILL BECOME MORE FUN.
THE PENTHOUSE 2 SPECIAL,
HIDDEN ROOM
A SECRET STORY
The Penthouse Season One
ended with the shocking death...
of Su Ryeon.
However, it's not over
until it's over.
There are still many stories
that we have left to tell.
Today, Hidden Room will assume
the role of a bridge...
that connects Season 1 to Season 2.
If you miss out on today's episode,
you may end up regretting it.
Shall we get started on
The Penthouse 2 Special,
Hidden Room: A Secret Story?
"THE DIVINE COMEDY"
IF "THE DA VINCI CODE" HAD
THE LOUVRE,
THE PENTHOUSE HAS
THE HEPAL'S CODE.
"The Divine Comedy" by Dante.
IT'S NOT A SIMPLE STORY.
IT'S TIME TO GET A PROPER TASTE
OF THE INFERNO NOW.
IT'S A PREDICTION.
- Look at her.
- Let us out!
THE DOOR TO THE INFERNO
IS OPENING UP.
A MYSTERIOUS SYMBOL
HIDDEN BEHIND NAMES
IF YOU FOLLOW THE CAUSE OF DEATH,
YOU CAN FIND THE ANSWER.
ORIGINAL SIN
No!
That's right.
Please save me.
A MYRIAD OF CODES THAT ARE
INTERTWINED LIKE A PUZZLE
Oh my gosh.
THAT'S INCREDIBLE.
IF YOU DID SOMETHING WRONG,
OF COURSE YOU SHOULD GET PUNISHED.
Punishment.
You're so evil.
PUNITIVE JUSTICE
THE SINS THAT YOU'VE COMMITTED...
WILL END UP COMING BACK TO YOU.
HOW DARE YOU COVET HIM?
LOOK AT YOU ACTING LIKE
YOU'RE HIS ACTUAL WIFE.
ALL OF THE CLUES
HAVE ALREADY BEEN GIVEN.
SHE WAS WEARING A RUBY RING
ON HER HAND.
WHO IS IT?
REVEAL THE HIDDEN CODE
INSIDE HERA PALACE.
HEPAL'S CODE
As you saw through the video,
I intend to find all the things that
are hidden inside...
The Penthouse
through HePal's Code.
There are a lot of stories
that are floating around already.
There are.
There are a lot of guesses too.
I wondered if the premise
of this drama...
has a special code.
That's what I thought.
- The premise.
- Yes, the premise.
I believe the HePal's Code
to the premise...
is "The Divine Comedy".
- "The Divine Comedy"?
- "The Divine Comedy".
What comes to mind when you
think of "The Divine Comedy"?
What comes to mind when I think
about "The Divine Comedy"?
- Dante?
- Yes, that's right.
- Dante.
THE POET, DANTE, CREATED
THE INFERNO IN "THE DIVINE COMEDY".
Who created Hera Palace?
It was Joo Dan Tae.
Hera Palace.
JOO DAN TAE IS THE CREATOR...
AND THE RULER OF HERA PALACE.
And what is Dan Tae's last name?
I'M JOO DAN TAE.
DAN TAE'S LAST NAME IS JOO.
Who is the king of the gods
in Greek mythology?
- Zeus.
Another name for Zeus is...
IN GREEK MYTHOLOGY,
HIS NAME IS ZEUS.
- It's Jupiter.
- It's Jupiter. Bingo.
- So that's why he's Joo Dan Tae?
- Right.
I see.
I didn't hear anything about that.
That might be how he got
his name, but I'm not aware of it.
Right. Zeus.
That's why we wondered...
if Dan Tae was Zeus
among ourselves.
- Is that so?
- Tell us about that.
- That's a good story.
- It happened so long ago.
We talked about it at the beginning
of Season One, so I don't remember.
And...
in Korean, it was translated as
"The Divine Music".
In other words,
it's the music of divine beings.
In the drama, they do vocal music.
The music of divine beings,
vocal music.
A BIG PREMISE IN THE PENTHOUSE
IS VOCAL MUSIC.
IS THE PREMISE OF VOCAL MUSIC TAKEN
FROM DANTE'S "THE DIVINE COMEDY"?
And there's something that
Joo Dan Tae says often.
IF YOU DID SOMETHING WRONG,
OF COURSE YOU SHOULD GET PUNISHED.
If you're finished enjoying yourself
like a reckless brat,
it's time to be punished.
A woman like you must be punished.
PUNISHMENT
- He acts like a divine being...
- Right.
and says that he will punish people.
That's right. In mythology,
Zeus' wife is Hera.
- Hera.
- Is that why it's Hera Palace?
- Then it connects to Hera.
- I know.
Hera is the goddess of family,
- but she's also extremely jealous.
- That's right.
Let's think about the people
who live in Hera Palace.
They always fight...
and conspire against each other,
but none of them have a goal.
- Come to think of it, you're right.
- They don't have a goal.
That person may not have done
anything to me,
but for some reason,
I don't like them.
I have no reason to dislike them,
but I do.
I think it might be an extension
of those feelings.
He's just someone who's hated
within Hera Palace.
IF YOU LOOK INTO THOSE FEELINGS...
He's just someone you can't
relate to. It could be that.
It's just jealousy.
You just don't want to see
that person succeed.
They're just fighting.
It's like a dog fight.
But the most representative person
is Cheon Seo Jin.
- Cheon Seo Jin.
The reason why Cheon Seo Jin
stole Ha Yoon Chul away...
wasn't because she loved him.
It was simply because she was
jealous he was dating Oh Yoon Hee.
- Right. That was all.
- Right.
Furthermore, the reason why she
had an affair with Joo Dan Tae...
was because...
she wanted to take Shim Su Ryeon's
husband from her.
It was like that.
- Not because she loved him.
- Right.
ALL MEN ARE THE SAME.
Shim Su Ryeon.
DO YOU THINK THE PENTHOUSE
WILL BE YOURS FOREVER?
THE CODE THAT PENETRATES THE DRAMA,
HERA'S JEALOUSY
DANTE'S "THE DIVINE COMEDY",
DIVINE BEINGS,
JUPITER, HERA, HERA PALACE
I agree. Now that I made...
the connection between
jealousy and Hera Palace,
the story seems to fall into place.
However, I still don't understand
why Dan Tae is Dante.
The notion that Dante, the author
of "The Divine Comedy",
has been absorbed into
this premise...
- can be defined by this.
- What is it?
Joo Dan Tae...
- is obsessed with Shim Su Ryeon.
- Right.
He murdered her previous husband.
AFTER MURDERING
HER PREVIOUS HUSBAND,
THE REASON WHY HE INSISTED
ON CUTTING OFF HIS FINGER IS...
THE MOMENT I SAW THE WEDDING RING
ON HIS FINGER,
I TOTALLY LOST MY MIND.
How dare he steal you from me?
The fact that you were pregnant
with his baby...
made me want to tear his heart
into pieces.
DAN TAE EXHIBITS A MAD OBSESSION.
That's right.
Dan Tae is extremely obsessive.
Actually, Dante was
a very obsessive man too.
He met his first love
when he was nine.
His obsession with her continued
into adulthood...
even after they both got married.
Her name is Beatrice.
Dante's obsession with her
was persistent.
"DANTE WOULDN'T HAVE LONGED FOR
BEATRICE ALL HIS LIFE..."
"IF HE'D LIVED WITH HER."
DANTE'S WIFE, GEMMA DONATI
Let's just forget about everything.
DAN TAE OBSESSES OVER THINGS
THAT HE DOESN'T HAVE.
I'm going to take your silence
as a yes.
WAS THE CHARACTER INSPIRED
BY DANTE'S OBSESSION?
It doesn't end there.
After Dante was expelled
from Florence for political reasons,
he stayed...
in an Italian city called Verona.
- Verona?
- Verona.
- Yoon Hee's daughter is Bae Ro Na.
- Bae Ro Na.
- Exactly.
Ro Na!
Bae Ro Na!
THE NAME BAE RO NA IS
JUST AS RARE AS JOO DAN TAE.
DOES THE NAME BAE RO NA
CONTAIN HEPAL'S CODE?
BUT...
"Romeo and Juliet" by Shakespeare...
is also set in Verona.
- That's another connection.
- Exactly.
What is "Romeo and Juliet" about?
- The two are in love, but...
- They can't stay together.
- Their families are enemies.
- That's right.
What does that remind you of?
Seok Hoon and Ro Na.
- Seok Hoon and Ro Na.
- Yes.
THE TWO START DEVELOPING
FEELINGS FOR EACH OTHER.
BUT...
SU RYEON DIES BECAUSE OF YOON HEE.
IN THE END, SEOK HOON AND RO NA'S
FAMILIES BECOME ENEMIES.
WAS BAE RO NA INSPIRED BY
DANTE AND "ROMEO AND JULIET"?
THEN...
They probably don't end up together.
Will they die?
Exactly. Not ending up together
isn't the real problem.
Both Romeo and Juliet die
in the end.
I hope we don't have a tragic end.
Every time I receive a new script,
I'm scared that I'll die.
That's interesting.
- Even Ro Na has many implications.
- Right?
If the writer really did intend it,
I'd get goosebumps.
This is incredible.
- There's another interesting name.
- Another?
Shim Su Ryeon.
What does her name mean?
Su Ryeon means water lilies,
which grow in the mud.
- You didn't know?
- You could say...
the Hera Palace people are
always fighting in the mud.
Su Ryeon must be a water lily
that grows in that mud.
- Shim Su Ryeon.
- She's an elegant water lily.
She rarely wears colorful clothes.
- She often wears white.
- Like you today.
It's the Shim Su Ryeon style.
I thought it was
the Jung Won Kwan style.
"Last night, I started hating you."
- All right.
- Okay.
I've prepared so much
about names.
- Do you have any?
- I do.
Do you remember
Min Seol A's English name?
- I do.
- What is it?
- It's Anna Lee.
- Yes.
Anna means grace in Hebrew.
- You're talking about Hebrew now?
- Yes, I did some research.
Starting today, your name is Anna.
Anna Lee.
HER ADOPTIVE PARENTS
NAMED HER ANNA LEE.
From her adoptive
parents' perspective,
Min Seol A is the person
who can save their son.
That's why her name means grace.
That's where her name, Anna,
comes from.
- Don't you think it's far-fetched?
- I guess it is.
But who knows? The writer
may have really thought that way.
- Then I have another one.
- Go ahead.
- Gu Ho Dong.
- Logan Lee.
- Yes, Logan Lee.
The name Gu Ho Dong was
inspired by Kang Ho Dong.
GU HO DONG WAS
INSPIRED BY KANG HO DONG.
- Cut it out.
- Okay.
- I mean...
- What are you doing?
There's evidence. I wouldn't have
brought it up otherwise.
One of the things that
Gu Ho Dong says most often is,
"Nice to meet you."
He even said,
"Nice to meet you, brother" once.
That's right.
HE REALLY SAID,
"NICE TO MEET YOU, BROTHER."
And the name Kang Ho Dong was
even mentioned in the show.
- I don't remember hearing it.
- It was.
LOGAN LEE WAS ABDUCTED BY DAN TAE
IN SEASON 1, EPISODE 21.
That came out wrong.
Kang Ho Dong, no,
Gu Ho Dong, right?
DID YOU GET THAT?
ONE MORE TIME
That came out wrong.
Kang Ho Dong, no,
Gu Ho Dong, right?
WAS THE NAME GU HO DONG REALLY
INSPIRED BY KANG HO DONG?
That was my ad-lib.
The original line was,
"Gu Ho Dong, no. Logan Lee, right?"
But I changed it to Kang Ho Dong.
THIS HEPAL'S CODE WAS
BASED ON HIS AD-LIB.
But the director just went with it.
But this one is...
too hard to catch.
Don't you agree? It was too fast.
Dan Tae didn't say it
clearly either.
"Kang Ho Dong, no..."
He corrected himself right away.
I never make ungrounded claims.
- All right. It's accepted.
- Okay.
The next HePal's Code is...
- original sin.
- Original sin.
Original sin.
- You're good at English.
- No, I'm not.
Are you talking about "sin"...
- Original sin.
- Yes.
Or are you talking about "scene",
like in movies and dramas?
The meaning would depend on that.
- Do you want me to answer?
- Yes.
Both.
BOTH
It's both.
Both?
It's both original sin
and the original scene.
- Both?
- Both.
- It means both.
- Yes.
Let's talk about
the forbidden fruit first.
Min Seol A was wearing
a necklace when she died.
- Do you remember its pendant?
- An apple.
But it wasn't just an apple.
It was the forbidden fruit.
- That sounds far-fetched.
- No, it isn't.
It makes sense.
Do you remember
when that necklace first appeared?
It was during her interview
with Cheon Seo Jin.
Exactly. During her interview.
They sell this apple necklace
at that store.
Do you remember?
During the interview,
they showed a close-up
of the necklace.
And there must be a reason.
The necklace must hold a meaning.
The director must have
received an order.
There must have been an order.
"Please shoot an insert."
An insert.
We know...
- Every TV person knows that...
- Yes.
- if there's an insert...
- It's something important.
A close-up means
it's something really important.
It's extremely important.
But why is that the forbidden fruit?
What does
the forbidden fruit symbolize?
- Original sin.
In addition,
it symbolizes temptation.
Temptation. That's right.
Yoon Hee resists temptation
many times,
but in the end, she gives in.
She ends up killing Min Seol A.
It was as if she picked
the forbidden fruit.
HER MURDER LOOKED LIKE SHE WAS
PICKING THE FORBIDDEN FRUIT.
AFTER PICKING
THE FORBIDDEN FRUIT...
As long as you die,
Ro Na can be accepted.
YOON HEE COMMITS THE ORIGINAL SIN
THAT CAN'T BE WASHED AWAY.
IS THE APPLE NECKLACE REALLY
THE FORBIDDEN FRUIT?
Now that I think of it,
- the necklace was left in her hand.
- Yes.
It symbolizes her original sin
that can't be washed away.
- That's right.
- That was the intention.
Exactly.
Even if she gets cleared of
the accusation of killing Su Ryeon,
she still has to carry
her sin around all her life.
- That's incredible.
- Right?
If you look at it that way,
it sure is incredible.
I'd love to ask the writer about it.
- Right?
- Yes.
Were there any scenes...
that imply who the killer is?
Then let's look at a code...
- that already gave us the answer.
- Okay.
There were scenes that tell us
who killed Min Seol A.
It's the original scene.
Really? They tell us
who killed Min Seol A?
There were many of them.
I watched the show really carefully,
but I missed that.
- Did you watch Episode 3 carefully?
- Episode 3?
YOON HEE AND SEO JIN'S
DIALOGUE IN SEASON 1, EPISODE 3.
INSTEAD OF BEGGING ME...
Why don't you kill
one of the students...
who was accepted...
SEO JIN SUGGESTED YOON HEE'S
FUTURE MURDER.
Obviously, you didn't pay
enough attention.
- Probably not.
- But there was a scene that was...
even more obvious.
What is it?
Do you remember Seol A's dog?
Sugar!
SUGAR KNOWS.
SEOL A AND SUGAR
HAVE RELIED ON EACH OTHER.
Focus on your operation
and getting better.
GENTLE
- The thing about Sugar is,
- Okay.
she never barks at anyone...
- Right.
- except for one person.
Who?
IT'S YOU.
THE ONLY PERSON SUGAR BARKS AT.
What's the matter?
Stop it. That's enough.
SHE EVEN BITES YOON HEE.
That's huge.
- Right?
- Just like the close-up.
In dramas,
animals usually play
an important role.
Right? They're important.
- Especially when they bark.
- It implies something.
Why didn't I remember that scene?
But the next scene
will shock you even more.
When are you going to stop
giving me the chills?
I'll continue until you get sick.
When are you going to stop
giving me the chills?
LAUGHING
Do you want to become
my fellow comedian?
- Sorry.
- Do you want to work with me?
I apologize.
Many people say that this scene is
the best scene...
of The Penthouse Season One.
- Among all scenes...
- Oh, I know.
I agree with you.
Who is that?
- It's Cheon Seo Jin.
- Are you sure?
- That's how she plays.
- It doesn't look right.
LAUGHING
THIS IS THE ACTUAL SCENE.
It was raining,
and her father fell down the stairs.
She thought no one was watching.
- But there was.
- She gets blackmailed later.
But you can see that...
already in the scene
where her father dies.
Is that so?
Dad.
EUN BYEOL.
I was really curious
after I saw that scene.
That wasn't in my script.
I'm still really curious.
I want to ask him
if I get a chance to meet him.
MR. JUNG SUNG MO. IF YOU SEE THIS,
PLEASE GIVE ME A CALL.
It was already revealed then.
He saw Eun Byeol filming everything.
Right. Her father saw her.
How can she hear him
if he calls her so softly?
But it would be weird if he shouted
out "Eun Byeol" at that moment.
Then Cheon Seo Jin wouldn't have
played the piano...
- and done something different.
- Then the scene wouldn't exist.
They show Eun Byeol
filming it later.
I see. There are a lot of
interesting elements...
- hidden in the scenes.
- There are.
I thought that...
I saw through everything as
I watched Season One,
- but there are many hidden scenes.
- This is fun.
The HePal's Code that I prepared...
is Contrapasso.
"Contrapasso"?
What is "contrapasso"?
It means that if you commit a sin,
your punishment
will correspond to it.
Then it's like
"An eye for a tooth"...
- Did I say "An eye for a tooth"?
- That's not right.
I'm sorry.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- Do you take a tooth for an eye?
No. That would hurt though.
- In any case...
- It's punitive justice.
- Punitive justice. Right.
- It means punitive justice.
You mentioned earlier that...
Dante's "The Divine Comedy"...
and Dante's breath is absorbed
into The Penthouse.
In "Inferno" which is a part of
Dante's "The Divine Comedy",
- "Inferno".
- the term "contrapasso" comes out.
CONTRAPASSO APPEARS IN DANTE'S
"THE DIVINE COMEDY" IN "INFERNO".
It makes sense.
Yes. If I start talking about it,
you might end up slapping your knee.
- Okay. Let's see if I do.
- Don't let your pride stop you.
- No, I won't.
- If I'm right, do it.
- If you're right, I will.
- Okay.
We'll start with your favorite,
"An eye for an eye,
and a tooth for a tooth."
- Okay.
- I'll make it easy.
- "Fire, fire, fire, fire".
- "Fire, fire, fire, fire"?
Yes. "A fire for a fire,
and a fire for a fire."
In Episode 2 of Season 1,
do you remember the scene...
where Min Seol A gets bullied
by the kids in The Penthouse?
Yes, I do. They were so mean.
That fool.
I think something caught on fire.
IN THIS SCENE, THE CAR CAUGHT ON
FIRE WHEN SHE WAS LOCKED INSIDE.
They were so mean,
and they started a fire.
Right. In the van.
There was a similar scene,
and I'm sure you remember it.
It's with the adults
in The Penthouse.
THE PARENTS
WERE ALSO LOCKED IN A BUS,
AS THEIR LIVES WERE THREATENED
BY A FIRE.
THEY EVEN RECREATED
THE EXPLOSION.
I'm sorry!
- I'm sorry!
- I apologize.
I was also wrong.
Are you going to slap your knee
or not?
LAUGHING
- Does it make you slap your knee?
- Yes, it does.
That isn't all.
- You slapped your knee too hard.
- Right. It really hurts.
But it was worth it.
The next is "Between affairs".
There are a lot of things
that in between.
When Cheon Seo Jin was trying to
steal Ha Yoon Chul away,
- Right.
- she had a drink with him.
- Through the window,
- Right. Yoon Hee sees them.
she sees Yoon Hee
and gives him a kiss.
Yoon Hee sees that happening.
There was such a scene,
and it repeats itself.
Where does it repeat?
Are you okay?
I shouldn't have called you
like this.
SHE FALLS INTO YOON CHUL'S ARMS
WHILE SEO JIN WATCHES.
FURTHERMORE, SHE EVEN LOOKS
AT HER THROUGH THE WINDOW.
Gosh.
- My knees will hurt so much later.
- It isn't over yet.
- There's more?
- Yes, it's "Between knees".
That's dangerous.
Is it okay to talk about
"Between the Knees"?
- It's not that.
- I enjoyed watching it.
It's not Rated R.
What I mean by this is
they get on their knees.
They get on their knees?
When do they do that?
First, it's because of
Yoon Hee's daughter, Ro Na.
Seo Jin.
YOON HEE GETS ON HER KNEES
IN FRONT OF HER NEMESIS, SEO JIN,
FOR THE SAKE OF HER DAUGHTER.
Are you asking me...
to use my connections
to let her in illegally?
If you want, I can even
clean your house. Seo Jin.
This repeats itself.
Cheon Seo Jin gets on her knees
in front of Shim Su Ryeon.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
SEO JIN GETS ON HER KNEES IN FRONT
OF HER RIVAL IN LOVE, SU RYEON,
FOR THE SAKE OF HER DAUGHTER.
Please save her.
THEY EVEN FILMED THE SCENES
IN THE SAME EXACT ANGLE.
One.
THEY BEGIN TO SLAP THEIR KNEES
CONTINUOUSLY.
Our knees will be so sore.
- It is incredible.
- Yes. It makes you slap your knee.
Contrapasso means punitive justice,
but it also means repetition.
It means repetition?
Were there scenes that
were repeated in The Penthouse?
There was quite a lot.
During the Cheong A Art Festival,
after the awards were given
and everything had ended,
Cheon Seo Jin and Oh Yoon Hee
have a fight in the dressing room.
Go on and try if you want.
AFTER THE CHUNG A ART FESTIVAL,
SEO JIN AND YOON HEE HAVE A FIGHT.
That was the standard of
a dog fight.
- Right.
- Yes.
Do you remember the line
that was said then?
YOU'RE JUST A DARNED THIEF.
You're just a darned thief.
SCARED
Oh Yoon Hee said that
to Cheon Seo Jin, and later on...
THE SAME LINE IS REPEATED LATER
IN A CONTRAPASSO SCENE.
- Ro Na says it to Eun Byeol.
- To Eun Byeol.
Go ahead and deny it if you can.
YOU'RE JUST A DARNED THIEF.
You're just a darned thief.
IT'S FUN TO IMITATE IT.
- It's repeated.
- Since we're talking about lines,
there's another line that
is repeated.
What is it?
SEOL A WAS POOR BUT DIGNIFIED.
I PITY YOU GUYS.
I pity you guys.
- Do you remember it?
- Yes, I do.
But... Why?
There's someone who says
the line that Min Seol A says.
- There is.
- It's Bae Ro Na.
RO NA IS THE TYPE TO SAY WHAT'S
ON HER MIND LIKE SEOL A.
I PITY YOU GUYS.
EVEN THE PEOPLE WHOM SHE SAYS IT TO
ARE THE SAME.
While we were talking,
I realized that we could
talk about it all night.
- Right.
- I feel like we shouldn't...
let each scene pass us in vain.
If you keep in mind the codes
that we mentioned here today...
- as you watch Season Two,
- Right.
I think you will enjoy Season Two
a lot more.
That's nice.
JUST WAIT A BIT LONGER.
I haven't...
I HAVEN'T EVEN GOTTEN STARTED YET.
THE PENTHOUSE 2
PREMIERES FEBRUARY 19.
Okay.
You have all waited a long time.
It's finally time for us to start
talking about...
- The Penthouse Season Two.
- Right.
We asked a few questions
in advance...
through SBS Catch,
and a lot of people participated.
I heard.
We will start
The Penthouse Exploration...
- with our viewers right now.
- Okay.
Please give us the first question.
THE PENTHOUSE EXPLORATION
MADE WITH THE VIEWERS
THE FIRST QUESTION
WHO IS THE GREATEST VILLAIN
IN THE PENTHOUSE SEASON 1?
NUMBER 1, JOO DAN TAE
CONTRACTING ASSAULT
ARSON AND DESTRUCTION OF EVIDENCE
ABDUCTION
FURTHERMORE
ATTEMPTED MURDER
CONTRACTING MURDER
AND MURDER ITSELF
NUMBER 1, A COMPLETE SET
OF EVIL DEEDS, JOO DAN TAE
NUMBER 2, CHEON SEO JIN
SHE COMMITTED MANY EVIL DEEDS,
BUT THIS ONE EXPLAINS EVERYTHING.
A REPROBATE DAUGHTER
WHO BETRAYED FILIAL PIETY.
ALSO, SHE IS THE DEFINITION OF
ADMISSIONS CORRUPTION IN THE DRAMA.
Die!
Hello, Seo Young.
It's me.
NUMBER 2, I'M THE EVIL WOMAN
AROUND HERE, CHEON SEO JIN
NUMBER 3, OH YOON HEE
THE REAL CULPRIT BEHIND
MIN SEOL A'S MURDER
As long as you're gone...
Let's be friends forever.
Let's never fight
or betray each other.
SHE BETRAYED THE PERSON
WHO GAVE HER...
FULL MATERIAL
AND EMOTIONAL SUPPORT.
DESPITE IT ALL, SHE'S SHAMELESS
AND REFUSES TO ADMIT IT.
NUMBER 3, SHE RUINED
A MOTHER AND DAUGHTER, OH YOON HEE
NUMBER 4, LEE KYU JIN
Why are you letting her go?
You can't let them walk off before
we tell our side of the story!
A TWISTED GUARDIAN OF THE LAW
WHO DEFENDS BAD PEOPLE.
In general...
HE ALSO HAS
DEEP-ROOTED CLASS PREJUDICE.
Like a fly.
The tax we pay...
makes the world go round.
HE DOESN'T HAVE ANY FRIENDS
OR ALLIES.
NUMBER 4, THE THOROUGH OPPORTUNIST,
LEE KYU JIN
NUMBER 5, HA YOON CHUL
IN REALITY, HE HAS MORE
WORLDLY DESIRES THAN ANYONE ELSE.
AFTER DOING WRONG THINGS TOGETHER,
HE HYPOCRITICALLY PRETENDS
TO BE INNOCENT.
I really hate hypocrites like you
who love money...
but act all kind on the outside.
HE EVEN DUMPS HIS DEVOTED
GIRLFRIEND TO BECOME SUCCESSFUL.
NUMBER 5, THE HYPOCRITE,
HA YOON CHUL
WHO IS THE WORST VILLAIN
OF THE PENTHOUSE SEASON 1?
The first question is
more of a warm-up.
Nearly 300,000 people...
- answered this question.
- That's a lot.
Jung Sik, who do you think...
is the worst villain of Season One?
I'd say Lee Kyu Jin is.
He's not exactly a bad person,
- but he's sly.
- Exactly.
- It's not like he has ambitions...
- He's sly.
or goals.
Kyu Jin's goal in life is...
WHAT IS KYU JIN'S GOAL IN LIFE?
It's to be the best son.
Isn't that awful?
To be the best son.
It's not to be a good son.
He's Wang Mi Ja's son.
Whatever happens,
he forgets the same day.
He doesn't remember things
longer than a minute.
A minute and a half at most.
I'm sure many people would...
- agree with my choice.
- Okay.
It's Joo Dan Tae.
He's not just a bad person.
He's evil.
- I can't wait to see the result.
- Right?
Let's see who our viewers think
is the worst villain.
Here we go.
Joo Dan Tae, by any standards.
I'd say Joo Dan Tae.
- Joo Dan Tae.
- Joo Dan Tae, right?
Joo Dan Tae won by far, didn't he?
Everyone knows that. It's no secret.
Right?
I guess it's me.
JOO DAN TAE WAS CHOSEN
AS THE WORST VILLAIN BY FAR.
After Season Two, more than
80 percent would answer so.
That became clear
after yesterday's shooting.
WHAT TERRIBLE THINGS
DID HE DO NOW?
I don't understand
why Oh Yoon Hee came in second.
It's not right.
It's unfair.
I guess it's because I killed
Min Seol A.
I actually committed murder.
I'll have to accept the result.
I expected that Cheon Seo Jin
would come in second.
Me?
I'm an awful person.
I deserve to be hated
and am unreasonably mean.
But from a legal perspective,
I didn't...
directly commit murder.
It's so weird that I'm saying this
while smiling.
Even though I'd love to beat
Oh Yoon Hee at everything...
SHE WANTS TO BEAT
OH YOON HEE AT EVERYTHING.
This is such a disgrace,
so I'll give up.
Yoon Hee can have it.
What made the viewers
think this way?
- Let's find out.
- Great.
Here are comments from
those who chose Joo Dan Tae.
"One, Joo Dan Tae killed a person."
That's right.
- He did.
- It's clear.
"Two, he tries to solve everything
with money."
Gosh, that's right.
"Three, he hits children."
- Yes, he hits his children.
- He's such a jerk.
- He's trash.
- Going over all these things...
- There's a funny reason too.
- Okay.
"He has too many kissing scenes."
He makes me wonder,
"How can he kiss in that situation?"
He had many passionate
kissing scenes.
Let me read some of the comments...
from those who chose Oh Yoon Hee.
"Joo Dan Tae's evilness is
on another level,"
"so it feels like he lives
in another world."
"Oh Yoon Hee is scarier
because people like her do exist."
- She feels more real.
- Do you agree?
"Joo Dan Tae and Cheon Seo Jin
have always been mean."
"But Oh Yoon Hee pretended
to be nice in the beginning..."
"but then betrayed people
and turned into trash."
You get more hurt by betrayers...
- than those who've always been bad.
- You're right.
"The worst villain is the person
who started all this."
"The veterinarian".
- He ripped off Seol A.
- I know.
I got the money. Operate on her now.
It's 2,000 dollars, right?
IS THE VET A HIDDEN VILLAIN
WHO CAUSED THE WHOLE TRAGEDY?
That much?
Your dog might die
if you wait too long.
I'll get the money somehow.
THERE ARE NO WARMHEARTED GROWN-UPS
IN THE WORLD OF THE PENTHOUSE.
- If he hadn't ripped her off,
- Exactly.
Seol In Ah wouldn't...
- Seol...
- Seol In Ah?
- I mean Min Seol A.
- Come on, Jung Seok.
EMBARRASSED
You too? Me too.
LAUGHING
- Seol A wouldn't have died.
- Min Seol A.
She needed money.
This comment isn't funny.
- It makes sense.
- It does.
Here comes the real fun part.
The Penthouse Season Two.
It's time to guess.
Let's get started.
THE PENTHOUSE EXPLORATION WAS BORN
THROUGH THE VIEWERS' PARTICIPATION.
THE SECOND QUESTION
THE BIGGEST MYSTERY OF SEASON 1
The butterfly tattoo.
There's something suspicious
about that picture.
Their mother died right after
giving birth due to septicemia.
But...
THE WOMAN TURNS OUT TO BE ALIVE.
THE WOMAN WITH A BUTTERFLY TATTOO
HOLDS THE KEY. WHO IS SHE?
NUMBER 1, SHIM SU RYEON
DID SHE SUFFER
SERIOUS PSYCHOLOGICAL TRAUMA...
AND LOSE THE MEMORY...
OF GIVING BIRTH TO THE TWINS?
WHO IS THE WOMAN
WITH A BUTTERFLY TATTOO...
WHO GAVE BIRTH TO THE TWINS?
SHIM SU RYEON!
NUMBER 1, SHIM SU RYEON,
WHO LOST HER MEMORY
NUMBER 2, SU RYEON'S TWIN SISTER
Her twin sister?
That's a possibility.
NOTHING IS KNOWN ABOUT HER PAST
EXCEPT HAVING WEALTHY PARENTS.
EVEN THOUGH SHE IS MISSING
FROM HER CHILDHOOD PICTURES,
DOES SU RYEON HAVE A TWIN SISTER?
TWINS ARE MORE LIKELY
TO GIVE BIRTH TO TWINS.
IS THE WOMAN WITH
A BUTTERFLY TATTOO A TWIN HERSELF?
IS THE WOMAN WITH A TATTOO
SU RYEON'S TWIN SISTER?
Oh, right. Reporter Kim.
Reporter Kim.
REPORTER KIM POPPED UP
OUT OF NOWHERE.
SHE IS THE ONLY PERSON THAT
SU RYEON CAN TURN TO FOR HELP.
THE RELATIONSHIP OF THE TWO
SEEMS EXTRAORDINARY.
And you even paid for my tuition.
THERE'S SOMETHING MYSTERIOUS
ABOUT HER.
IS REPORTER KIM, WHO IS
CLOSE TO SU RYEON, THE MOTHER?
- They seem very close.
- Right.
I'm so curious about her.
Why won't anyone pick up?
FROM THE BEGINNING, SHE SEEMED
UNCOMFORTABLE AROUND SU RYEON.
She seems to feel attached
to the twins too.
Don't worry.
- That photo too.
- It was weird.
SHE ALWAYS SEEMS TO WANT TO TAKE
SU RYEON'S PLACE.
That left me with an uneasy feeling.
SHE WAS DESPERATE
TO STAY AT THE PENTHOUSE.
IS MS. YANG, WHO IS DEVOTED
TO DAN TAE, THE TWINS' MOTHER?
NUMBER 5, SOMEONE ELSE
It could be someone else.
THE PENTHOUSE EXPLORATION
I have no clue.
WHO HAS THE BUTTERFLY TATTOO,
WHICH WILL BE REVEALED IN SEASON 2?
This is the biggest mystery
of Season One.
- I agree.
- It has to be solved...
- in Season Two.
- It makes me uncomfortable.
Right? Joo Seok Hoon
and Joo Seok Kyung.
Who do you think is the woman...
with the butterfly tattoo
who gave birth to the twins?
I loved watching
one of Kim Soon Ok's previous works,
"Temptation of Wife".
In that show,
- Min So Hee comes back with a mole.
- Yes.
Just like that, I think
Shim Su Ryeon is the mother.
Her death was quite suspicious.
Everyone who has died
in The Penthouse so far...
- fell to their deaths.
- They fell to their deaths.
Including Min Seol A.
FALL
- She fell to her death.
- She fell.
So did Cheon Seo Jin's father.
FALL
Mr. Yoon is the same.
This is my final act of loyalty.
FALL
- That's right.
- Mr. Yoon too.
But that's not true.
Director Min hung himself.
Oh, right.
Please ignore what I said.
SHE CHANGES HER POSITION
AS FAST AS LEE KYU JIN.
- I like that about you.
- It wasn't 100 percent.
- You admit your mistakes.
- Of course.
You should take it back fast.
- What do you think?
- I suspect Ms. Yang.
Ms. Yang.
From editing herself
into the photo...
to her desperation
to stay at the Penthouse...
despite all the bad things
that happen to her,
everything makes her suspicious.
- You think she's their mother.
- Exactly.
- She's desperate to stay with them.
- Right.
That's why I suspect Ms. Yang.
- That makes sense.
- Right?
Let's find out
what the viewers think.
THE PENTHOUSE EXPLORATION
SU RYEON'S TWIN SISTER, 61 PERCENT
This time too,
more than half answered...
the woman would be
Su Ryeon's missing twin sister.
You're right. In Season One,
Logan Lee and Su Ryeon were
surprised by a picture.
Don't be surprised.
SURPRISED
She was probably surprised because
the woman looks just like her.
That's right. Otherwise,
why would she be so surprised?
Let's see who came in second.
They agree with you.
They chose Ms. Yang.
The thing is,
in the photos that show up,
the shoulder...
Who always poses like that?
But from her hairstyle...
to her silhouette,
she looks a lot like Ms. Yang.
That's right.
The viewers chose her...
mostly because...
the woman in the photo has
a similar hairstyle to Ms. Yang's.
That's why, if you think about it,
the butterfly on her shoulder...
- means it's Ms. Yang.
- Yes.
It's only fair that
we tell the truth right about now.
- We know absolutely nothing.
- Right.
- But we heard something earlier.
- Yes.
The producer of this very show...
My gosh, seriously, you know...
- It was the biggest shock today.
- I know.
Our producer
already saw eight episodes.
Honestly, that's...
They're the one person
I envy the most right now.
Seriously. It feels like
the producer has everything I want.
They're loaded, like Mansour.
"Did you watch
the first eight episodes?"
So arrogantly, they said,
- "There were blanks in-between."
- "There were blanks."
They could've said "empty scenes",
- but they said "blanks".
- "There were blanks."
- Shall we ask just one thing?
- What?
Do you know who has
the butterfly tattoo?
- but they said "blanks".
- "There were blanks."
- Shall we ask just one thing?
- What?
Do you know who has
the butterfly tattoo?
THE WOMAN WITH
THE BUTTERFLY TATTOO.
WE'LL TELL YOU
WHAT IT WAS LIKE ON SET.
In the photo taken at Seok Hoon
and Seok Kyung's first birthday,
that's when the tattoo
first appears.
When I posed for that photo...
was when I realized
someone else was the kids' mom.
The woman I posed with...
was an extra.
GIGGLING
EVEN THE ACTORS DON'T KNOW
WHO THE WOMAN IS.
We're destined to watch the drama
at the same time as everyone else.
- Yes.
- That's our conclusion.
Some people named someone
who wasn't even an option.
Ma Doo Ki.
MA DOO KI?
It's because
we brought up Ms. Yang's hair.
Ma Doo Ki's hairstyle...
- He has a bob cut too.
- He does.
And he does speak with
a feminine tone.
His gestures and things...
Considering Kim Soon Ok's style,
couldn't Ma Doo Ki
have been a woman?
MA DOO KI COULD'VE BEEN A WOMAN.
HA DO KWON, PLAYS MA DOO KI
I was a woman?
LOST FOR WORDS
Season One had an open ending.
I guess I could be a woman.
I promise to read
the future scripts carefully.
Ma Doo Ki appeared as
one of the possibilities.
It can't be that. I just laughed.
- That's nonsense.
- But Yoon Hee...
didn't know she was the killer.
I wish it were me.
I'm against it. I object.
- I see why.
- You two as a couple?
You don't know whose kids you are.
YOU DON'T KNOW YOUR PARENTAGE.
Is Ma Doo Ki...
not the woman but the man
with the butterfly tattoo?
We'll find out in Season Two.
Let's move on to
the last question of...
- The Penthouse Exploration.
- Yes.
WE ALWAYS WANT TO
KNOW MORE ABOUT THIS.
THE LOVERS
In The Penthouse,
amid all the madness, love blooms.
Babies are born even during a war.
You're so sexy.
WHAT COUPLES DO THE VIEWERS
LOOK FORWARD TO IN SEASON 2?
Cheon Seo Jin and Joo Dan Tae.
CHEON SEO JIN... JOO DAN TAE...
THE WORST COMBINATION.
I HATE THEM.
SHUDDERING
THE PENTHOUSE'S
OFFICIAL COUPLE OF EVIL!
NEITHER OF THEM WILL REST
UNTIL THEY GET WHAT THEY WANT.
KISSING
ARE THEY A NECESSARY EVIL
TO GIVE US THE KISS QUOTA?
FOR MANY REASONS, WON'T THEY
MAINTAIN THEIR RELATIONSHIP?
THE WORST COMBINATION,
SEO JIN AND DAN TAE
This couple was popular.
They got together
at the end of Season One.
IT WAS SPECIAL FROM THE START.
I wanted a chance
to live a decent life.
THE BEGINNING:
THEY MISUNDERSTOOD EACH OTHER
She stabbed him and still...
That was Cupid's arrow.
THE DEVELOPMENT: PRINCE CHARMING
COMES TO THE RESCUE
THE CLIMAX:
THEIR FEELINGS GROW DEEPER
They comfort each other.
There weren't any scenes...
where either of them
openly showed their affection.
No. But I found myself
rooting for them.
I think they'll be happy.
WILL WE SEE THE CONCLUSION
THIS SEASON?
THE EPITOME OF ROMANCE,
SU RYEON AND LOGAN LEE
YOON HEE AND YOON CHUL
Oh Yoon Hee and Ha Yoon Chul.
- The old lovers reconcile.
- Yes.
The look in Yoon Chul's eyes
suddenly changed one day.
- And he's divorced now.
- Yes.
IF I DIDN'T LEAVE YOU BACK THEN,
WOULD THINGS HAVE BEEN DIFFERENT?
THE PROBLEMATIC MEETING
OF THE EXES.
That was a close-up shot.
- Did you see it?
- It means something.
HE THINKS OF HER WHEN IN PAIN.
They inserted the perfect song.
It's like a music video.
HE'S ALWAYS WORRIED ABOUT HER.
She's always on his mind.
- Let me go.
- Affix your seal.
I won't!
It's really like a music video.
HE WANTS TO HELP HER
WHEN SHE'S IN NEED.
YOON CHUL'S DIVORCE INCREASED
THEIR CHANCES FOR A RECONCILIATION!
WILL THE OLD LOVERS
GET TOGETHER IN SEASON 2?
THE FIRST LOVES,
YOON HEE AND YOON CHUL
- The Yoon-Yoon couple.
Like this?
SEOK HOON AND RO NA
Their love is young and cute.
Romeo and Juliet.
INSTEAD OF BEING LATE FOR SCHOOL,
THEY FELL IN LOVE ON DAY ONE.
SHE HAS A PRETTY FACE.
A TYPICAL CHEERFUL LEAD
Her eyes get bigger when she sings.
A TYPICAL COOL LEAD
It's a lot like "Boys Over Flowers".
Their characters...
RULE 2: THE BOY
NONCHALANTLY HELPS THE GIRL.
RULE 3: THE GIRL IS MOCKED BY
HIS RICH FRIENDS.
RULE 4: THE BOY MUST NONCHALANTLY
CARE FOR THE GIRL AGAIN.
Hey. Seok Hoon eats
someone else's cooking?
RULE 5: THE BOY NEVER FAILS TO
APPEAR WHEN THE GIRL IS IN DANGER.
- Are you okay?
- Move.
RULE 6: IT'S TIME FOR
A MISUNDERSTANDING.
It's going bad.
RULE 7: THE GIRL ACTS OUT
AND THE BOY SUFFERS.
STRIFE IS A MUST.
That's a lot of emotion
from Seok Hoon's perspective.
Didn't you get it?
He's so cold.
RULE 8: THE TREND DEMANDS
THAT THE GIRL TURN BRAZEN.
Where's my seat?
RULE 9: HAPPINESS IS FLEETING...
AND SUFFERING IS LONG-LASTING.
How can nothing change?
THE KEY IS THAT THE SUFFERING
MUST BE TOO HARD TO BEAR.
We're missing the last rule.
WHAT IS RULE 10?
WON'T IT COME UP
IN THE NEXT SEASON?
They're so sweet here.
The Seok-Ro couple.
THE HIGH-TEEN ROMANCE,
SEOK HOON AND RO NA
IT'S NONE OF THESE COUPLES!
There are others?
DAN TAE'S OBSESSION
ISN'T OVER UNTIL IT'S OVER.
Joo Dan Tae and...
- Shim Su Ryeon?
- Her again?
- Only if he's mad.
- That's the movie "Ghost".
"Love and War".
It can't be them. She's dead.
IF NOT THEM...
Eun Byeol.
THE DOTING DAD
They reconcile for their daughter?
THESE TWO...
They might get back together?
- That is a possibility.
- It is.
Our Eun Byeol.
OR COULD IT BE...
THE BEGINNING OF A COUPLE
THAT'S OUT OF THIS WORLD?
THE OTHER COUPLES
I love him.
WHICH COUPLE DO YOU
LOOK FORWARD TO SEEING THE MOST?
Wow, seeing separate footage
of them as couples...
It feels different.
The viewers love it so much...
- that they even gave nicknames.
- I know.
Dan-Seo couple.
Su-Gan couple. Yoon-Yoon couple.
And Seok-Ro couple.
They support...
their favorite couple.
Who's your favorite?
- I like the Su-Gan couple.
- Oh, Su-Gan.
Right. Those two are...
They receive...
the most attention in the drama.
They also didn't express
their feelings...
- in Season One.
- That's right.
As you saw earlier, she tabbed him
in the chest with a pen.
Let's say...
- you're in love with someone.
- Okay.
She stabbed you in your chest
with a pen.
- Can you still love her?
- I'm going to sue her.
Oh, right.
Let's find out...
- what the viewers think.
- Yes.
THE PENTHOUSE EXPLORATION
As expected, many people support
Su Ryeon and Logan.
- I was right.
- To return the favor,
Su Ryeon must not die.
- The writer needs to know this.
- I know.
Su Ryeon should survive...
- and fall in love with Logan.
- I hope so.
- I'm saying it as a fan.
- As a fan.
The next one is unexpected.
Seok Hoon and Ro Na placed second.
First place?
What did I place?
2nd? That's a shame.
I thought I placed 1st.
What a shame.
Thank you.
I'm dying to find out too.
WILL SEOK HOON AND RO NA WORK OUT?
I hope they work it out.
I'm hoping they do.
The biggest obstacle?
The obstacle?
- It's me. So what?
- We just had eye contact.
My father is standing over there.
I think it's my father.
Seok Kyung? Maybe?
It is true that Seok Kyung...
hates Ro Na.
And Seok Hoon cares so much
about Seok Kyung.
I'm not saying I own my brother,
but he keeps spending time...
with the person I don't like.
I'll set them apart.
Everything upsets me.
Also, quite a lot of people want...
Seo Jin and Yoon Chul
to get back together.
Maybe because they lived together...
for 17 years?
She wants to steal everything
of Yoon Hee.
KIM SO YEON AS CHEON SEO JIN
But she also wants to take
Ha Yoon Chul away from her...
because she still has feelings
left for him.
At least that's what I thought
as I was acting.
We call it love and hatred.
I'm pretty sure...
that's how they felt
when they fought.
They also have Eun Byeol.
I think that's why...
people want them
to get back together.
Not only the questions
and answers...
but from the comments,
I can tell that
we only have true fans with us.
- You can feel their love.
- Right.
Above all,
we're going to find it out together.
So I'm very excited.
It will be fun to find out...
- what we got right and wrong.
- Yes.
People will be like, "See?"
- "I was right."
- Yes.
That's what people
are going to talk about.
Now, it's the highlight...
of The Penthouse 2 Special,
Hidden Room: A Secret Story.
It's the generous preview
of Season Two.
I can't believe we're doing this.
First, we prepared how members
of Hera Palace are doing.
Let's watch.
THE PENTHOUSE 2
2 YEARS LATER
HOW DO THE MEMBERS
OF HERA PALACE LOOK?
CHEON SEO JIN IS STILL
KOREA'S BEST PRIMA DONNA.
AND JOO DAN TAE IS STILL RICH.
How's the construction going?
Of course.
You may look forward to it.
Aside from being busy
with expanding my business,
I'm having
the most peaceful time in life.
My relationship with Seo Jin is
going very smoothly too.
I'm going back to Seoul
on the first flight tomorrow.
Okay. See you at home. Love you.
I love you too, sweetie.
He's very nice to me.
People say I shine.
I think it's the love I never
received before.
HOW'S KANG MA RI DOING?
It couldn't be any better.
Only good things have been
happening to me lately.
CONGRESSMAN LEE KYU JIN?
Oh, haven't you heard?
Kyu Jin is now in politics.
Not only the legal circle but
the political circle wants him too.
HA YOON CHUL RETURNS TO HERA CLUB
AFTER A LONG TIME.
I was in the States.
I studied and stuff.
WE'LL GET STARTED RIGHT AWAY.
LOGAN LEE IS UP TO SOMETHING.
I'm back to square one.
I will never give up that easily.
HOW DID OH YOON HEE SURVIVE?
Well... It's a long story.
People think I've lost everything,
but it has only begun.
THE PENTHOUSE 2
IT BEGINS...
AGAIN.
You could die.
Find everything that will choke him.
What are you telling me that now?
You jerk.
The more dangerous they are,
keep them close to you.
- This is insane.
- A Gangnam Congressman's son.
I'm thinking about placing
a pushover in the game.
Then I'll never forgive you.
So did you kill me?
My goodness.
Stop talking insanity.
INSANE TWIST
How am I supposed to find it?
Do all it takes to bring him
in front of me.
You remember.
Don't worry.
Use the back door.
You're lying?
Admit it.
You don't have to try so hard.
Isn't it fun?
I'll kill you.
There will be fierce winds again.
THE PENTHOUSE 2
I have...
someone on my mind.
THE PENTHOUSE 2,
PREMIERES FEBRUARY 19
HOLDING HER LAUGHTER BACK
Isn't that too much?
As a viewer who's waiting
for The Penthouse 2,
it was nice.
Is it okay to reveal that much?
I'm worried about our producer.
He's the one who'll get fired.
He looks like a good guy.
- This might be our last time.
- I know.
I feel bad for him.
They revealed so much of it.
I might as well reveal
something I know.
- I picked up something huge.
- Do you know something?
I watched
the producer editing earlier.
I could see it.
In Season Two, the producer changes.
- In Season One, the producer was...
- It was Joo Dan Tae.
- But in Season Two...
- Who is it?
WHAT DID HE SEE?
- I also have a secret card.
- Really?
But it's... I'm not sure
if it's okay to say it.
Are you sure we're doing
what's best for the drama?
I don't know. I don't know
what will happen to us either.
- I acquired it.
- What did you acquire?
The script.
- Come on.
- Not Comedy Big League's script.
- No way.
- Don't be surprised.
- Does your chair have back support?
- No.
Stand tight. You'll fall back.
TA-DA
My goodness.
Hey.
- Are you okay?
- I'm doing my best.
I'm learning a lot from you.
I'm SBS' representative anchor.
These are the scripts
for The Penthouse.
- They're real.
- For Seasons 1 and 2. They're real.
It's not just the cover. It's real.
- I think it says Jang Do Yeon.
- No.
It's real.
The viewers are going to hate us.
This is real. It's a real script.
There's slapping.
My goodness. There's splashing.
Autopsy.
- Autopsy.
- Wait. What's this?
Fritters and tteokbokki?
What's this?
Why does it say
fritters and tteokbokki?
If we keep going,
- people will hate us.
- I agree.
We should do something.
Why don't we reveal a bit...
that it wouldn't spoil the drama?
Where shall we start?
- Episode 1.
- Episode 1?
I feel like an actress
to read the script.
Let's pick a random scene.
Like Scene 43
or something like that.
Sound good. Scene 43.
It's Scene 43.
We'll read just what it says...
without changing a word of it.
- Episode 1, Scene 43.
- We aren't good at acting.
Even if we do it,
people wouldn't know.
- I'll start.
- Read it. Read the text too.
THE PENTHOUSE 2,
EPISODE 1, SCENE 43
FALLS AFTER BEING SLAPPED.
GETS UP WITH A CHANGED EXPRESSION.
LOOKS STRAIGHT AT SEO JIN.
The person who has to leave
is you, not me.
What?
That was...
I'm sorry, writer.
We could do the whole episode
if we do it like this.
Even if we keep going,
it wouldn't affect the drama.
- That was Episode 1, Scene 43.
- Now, Episode 2.
You must check Scene 43
in Episode 1. It's there.
I wonder how it will look.
- Episode Two. Which one?
- Scene Four.
- Yes.
Scene Four. Okay.
THE PENTHOUSE 2,
EPISODE 2, SCENE 4
- Read it please.
- Me? Okay.
THE PENTHOUSE 2,
EPISODE 2, SCENE 4
I stopped by. I was in the area.
It wasn't intentional,
but if I interrupted you, I'm sorry.
See you later.
We'd never.
Was that "Pokemon"?
SUDDENLY, IT TURNS INTO "POKEMON".
- That was on SBS.
- Okay.
I think...
- people wouldn't notice.
- We can do the whole episode.
- People wouldn't know at all.
- Let's try Scene 29.
THE PENTHOUSE 2,
EPISODE 2, SCENE 29
No. It's too risky.
HIS DESIRE TO BE FUNNY
RESULTS IN DISASTER.
Apologize to the writer.
I'm sorry, Ms. Kim.
Let's move on.
Do as I say. It's not impossible.
It was just never brought
to the surface.
Okay, that was like...
"I'm Jessie. I'm James. I'm Meowth."
It...
- It keeps going.
- Just like in "Pokemon".
I'm sure there are people who want
to watch our spoiler.
Are there?
- We must continue.
- Okay.
- Let's try Scene 53.
- Let's be serious.
Sure. Here we go.
THE PENTHOUSE 2,
EPISODE 2, SCENE 53
I can't guarantee...
that it will be restored perfectly.
That doesn't matter.
Why did you act old?
In case I spoil it.
We just read the script.
I bet some people feel refreshed.
You think?
What if it was frustrating?
Like eating sweet potatoes.
- You think?
- Now that we've done it,
you should watch how the actors...
- actually deliver those lines.
- I don't ask for anything else,
but can you compare our rendition
with the drama after Season Two?
- Right.
- I'd like to see it.
Let's be humiliated big time.
After reading the script,
I want to see the actors...
bring these lines to life.
- Do you want to see it?
- Is there more?
Of course.
We have a producer
who only lives today.
Let's say goodbye to the producer
before we go.
This time,
let's watch The Penthouse 2
by theme.
THE PENTHOUSE 2 PREVIEW BY THEME
THEME 1, DIFFERENT THOUGHTS
IN ONE SCENE
FROM SEASON 1, EPISODE 21
What's important is that we got rid
of the thorns on our sides.
THEY GOT RID OF ALL OBSTACLES.
Bye, bye.
WILL THERE BE A NEW FAMILY?
DAN TAE'S FAMILY AND SEO JIN'S
FAMILY ARE HAVING DINNER TOGETHER.
HOW DO THEY FEEL TO BE
IN ONE PLACE TOGETHER?
Something I have to get.
It's not love.
It's a certain something.
Why can't we be well together?
If Seok Kyung becomes family,
I... No, I don't have to pretend
that we're close.
We don't have to be close.
But once Seok Hoon becomes family,
our love can't be achieved.
I must avoid it
by all means necessary.
Do you want to say anything?
No.
There is a possibility...
that Eun Byeol's family
and my family would unite.
Since I can't ignore it,
it will become a big obstacle
between me and Ro Na.
If you excuse me.
Sit down.
The adults are still eating.
I'd be upset.
Oh, I mean, Seok Kyung.
The situation itself is
already upsetting.
And on top of that,
she'll have to live with...
that annoying Ha Eun Byeol.
Then she'd explode
and break everything.
Mom. His lemon charlotte was
really good.
Did you like it?
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO UNITE?
THEME 2, OBSERVATION POINTS
OF SEASON 2 FROM THE ACTORS
One word?
Chaos?
THE CHAOTIC STORY OF SEASON 2
WHAT COULD IT BE?
I'd say "hashtag regret".
REGRET
TEARS OF REGRET?
I think it's change.
CHANGE IN PERSON?
CHANGE IN RELATIONSHIPS?
It's the matter of
Ma Doo Ki's appearance.
HIS APPEARANCE ALONE
MAKES IT FUNNY.
Jenny changes.
She's no longer the Jenny
you knew from Season One.
IT'S FRUSTRATING TO WAIT
AND FIND OUT.
She rebels in a different way.
ARE YOU SURPRISED
BY THE NEW WAY OF REBELLION?
All relationships change.
WHY DO THE RELATIONSHIPS CHANGE?
I'M NOT TELLING YOU.
I realized the power of family
is great.
ASKING MOM FOR HELP
A series of twists.
A TWIST IS COMING SOON
I don't know what to focus on.
WHAT SHOULD WE FOCUS ON?
Twist after twist after twist.
THE EFFECT OF THE TWISTS
IS CLEAR.
It's a big twist.
It won't be on TV anyway.
SECRET STORY
A TWIST THAT CAN'T BE ON TV
IT'S A HUGE TWIST.
I didn't expect it either.
What a twist. Don't you agree?
I think it's the biggest twist
in Season Two.
What do you think is going on?
THERE ARE BETRAYAL,
CONSPIRACY,
AND UNEXPECTED TWISTS.
THE PENTHOUSE 2,
PREMIERES FEBRUARY 19
The Penthouse 2.
We've seen a lot,
- but I don't know what I saw.
- I know.
- I'm getting even more curious.
- That's right.
Even though I've seen a lot,
I'm still curious.
I guess...
the quantity doesn't matter.
So when is Season Two starting?
You must not miss it.
It premieres on Friday,
February 19 at 10 p.m.
Don't miss The Penthouse 2.
We'll now leave discreetly.
Sounds good.
- Thank you.
Hello, viewers of The Penthouse.
Did you enjoy watching Season One?
Season One received so much love.
The Penthouse 2...
Will premiere on February 19.
We're surprised...
to read the script every time.
We'll come back with a brutal...
Even more spectacular...
And shocking story.
Please continue to support us.
As much as you waited...
We worked hard to shoot the show.
We're doing great.
Please look forward to it.
Please support us.
If you don't watch...
You'll be punished.
That was weird.