[English subtitles are available]
Hey…
It's dangerous here…
Fly away…
To somewhere… far away…
Falco!
Eh? Brother… what's wrong?
Good! If you can still talk, then you're all okay!
Colt!
I'm running! Hold on tight!
Falco!
Colt, how's the situation?!
The Eldian unit on the front line…
took a direct shell hit and was blown away…
And the trenches?
It's impossible to dig any further!
Impossible?
Is that an order?
You, an Eldian, is giving me order?
Hey! You!
Watch your mouth in front of Commander Magath!
But… at this rate…
Falco, are you drunk?
He must've hit his head.
We've been at war for four years, do you remember?
Who are… you guys…?
Or more like… eh?
Wasn't there a group of people jumping
around wielding a sword?
Like, swoosh…They took down a Titan
Looks like we need to
explain the operation to you again.
Just listen to me, Falco.
This war that has consumed our last four years…
It's finally going to an end.
All we have to do is to take control of Fort Slava.
Well, to be precise,
we have to sink the Mid-East Allied Forces' fleet
in the naval station below it.
Once we do that, we, the Marley, will win this war.
But to do that, we must take control Fort Slava
that defends the high ground.
Otherwise, we can't attack the station.
Can't the Marley navy attack them
from the sea for us?
Zofia?! Do you really think we can count
on that Navy to do something for us?!
They're the cesspool of incompetence
that took four whole years
to take control of the seas!
That hurts!
It took them half of the battleships
we have for them
to accomplish that!
Yet, they have the nerve to tell us
to capture a fort for them
before they can do a thing!
Those bastards! Do you understand?!!!
Udo, you're going to rip Falco's head off.
Ah! Sorry, sorry!
So,
why did they send warrior cadets like us
to the frontline?
It's to test us.
To see who is it among us…
that will become the next Warrior.
The "time" is near.
Commander Magath has decided this
to be our final exam.
In preparation for what's coming next,
he will choose who gets to play an important role
on the plan to suppress the Paradis island.
The heir to the Armored Titan.
[Attack on Titan]
♫Let's start a new life from the darkness♫
♫Until the light reveals the end♫
♫Sinister faces, growing curses♫
♫This is my last war♫
♫Angels playing disguised with devil's faces♫
♫Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom♫
♫Angels planning disguised with devil's faces♫
♫Children cling on to their very last coins♫
♫Destruction and regeneration♫
♫You are the real enemy♫
[#60 The Other Side of the Sea]
The Armored Titan…
Who will get chosen, I wonder.
Well, Gabi.
You made it sound like no one but you
could possibly be chosen.
I mean, who else?
True, we're not much compared to Gabi.
Considering the grades, yeah.
No, it's not about the grades, Udo.
Aren't I always telling you that?
The thing that separates me from you guys…
it's my resolve.
The resolve to shoulder the fate of all Eldian
and kill every demon living in that island
who've caused us so much suffering.
To prove that
the only remaining Eldians are the good ones,
I will win this fight
and show it to the rest of the world.
I won't lose.
I will free everyone from the internment zone.
So…
What have you been fiddling with all this time?
This? Cool, right?
Why, Commander Magath?!
It's impossible for infantry like us
to destroy the tracks
behind that machine gun on our own.
They have eyes all along that trench,
there isn't a single crack in their defenses…
On top of that,
they have artillery supporting them from the fort.
If we stay here,
they will just start raining shells down our heads.
Sounds like you have an idea, Colt.
Let's have Jaws and Cart go loose here.
Galliard and Pieck should be able to do it.
They'd be able to wipe out the enemies
in the pillbox and the trench in an instant.
No.
We’ll lose if we play our cards in the wrong order.
Commander Magath. It's here.
What is it?
It.
The Armored Train.
It has total four guns on its front and back cars.
The allies' new weapon;
the Anti-Titan Artillery.
The 100mm armor-piercing shells they fire
would stop a titan in one shot.
Even one of the Nine.
But, both of our titans are quick.
It couldn't possibly hit their nape.
But what if it does?
We… will lose the power of a Titan,
as well as a Warrior
and there's no guarantee
that we'll be able to regain it.
That's right.
Just like how our plan to regain the Founder
launched nine years ago failed
and we lost the Colossal and the Female
as a result.
Our enemies perceived it
as a blow to our military strength,
and it becomes the trigger to the war
that continues to this day,
thus delaying our Paradis operation.
What is it that makes our homeland Marley
the great empire it is today?
It's the power of the Titan.
That's right.
If we lose any more of it, this country
won't be able to sustain itself any longer.
The power of the Titans is absolute.
That is our axiom.
Prepare the Eldian unit to charge.
Roger.
Commander Magath! That's…!
What is it, Eldian?
Aren't you all Warriors
who have pledged your loyalty to Marley?
This is your chance to be honored
by our motherland.
All eight hundred Eldians here.
Stand, all of you! Prepare to charge!
Come on, stand up!
Now, you Eldian unit
will charge straight at enemy's tracks
and crush them!
The death squad will jump into the enemy's bunker
and neutralize their machine guns!
Listen well!
This is a chance for you disgusting descendant
of devil to clear your name!
A wonderful opportunity for you
to be honored by our motherland Marley!
Give it your best!
Roger!
You warrior cadets stand by here.
The Eldian unit's charge must destroy
those tracks no matter what.
As long that
Armored Train prowls around the fort,
neither the Armored nor the Beast
can be called upon here.
But still…
Colt. If you would inherit the Beast,
you should show that you're prepared to be a leader.
Nice.
It's a chance to blow the tracks along
with the train.
Can you let me do it?
Tadaa!
I can neutralize the Armored Train all by myself.
Hey, Gabi…
Do you have any idea how much it
cost the country to train you bunch?
Denied.
True, I am a gifted talent,
unlike the rest of them.
And I doubt you will find another warrior
as exceptional as me.
I'm super cute, too.
However, if I succeed,
we can get through this
without losing eight hundred Eldian soldiers.
And if you fail?
You will lose one exceptional warrior cadet
and seven hand grenades.
But, if you consider me to worth more
than eight hundred Eldian soldiers
it can't be helped.
If you're willing to sacrifice
eight hundred soldiers
because you love me so much, then I--
Fine.
Go.
No. - Gabi…
I promise! I will prove you that I'm a warrior
worthy of inheriting the Armored Titan!
What are you doing?
It's for the plan to work.
Please allow me to take off my armband,
just for now.
You may.
Hey. Someone is coming. Alone.
It's a girl… a young one at that.
Seems like she's coming to surrender.
No, wait.
She could be an Eldian.
But still, she looks strange.
It looks like she's dragging a pair
of shackles on her leg.
She's close. She must be an Eldian.
Shoot her before she turns into a Titan.
Don't be silly. Your rifle should do the trick.
Shit.
What is it?
Not yet…
Not yet…!
She's moving.
Don't mind her, just shoot.
Now…!!!
She did it!
Galliard! Get ready!
Dammit… those Marley cowards!
This is why… we must…
not let you get with what you want!
Gabi!
Falco, no!
Galliard!
We have confirmed that the Armored Train
is out of commission.
The airborne operation will now begin.
Be sure to stick to the plan.
Zeke will be our spear,
and Reiner will be our shield.
[Known Information Military Power Marley Led by Helos who ended the war Marley becomes a rejuvenated super power. With seven titans of the Nine as their warriors, it keeps invading other countries. In addition, it also has the Army, the Navy and Air Force made up of airships. So it’s stronger than any other country.]
That hurts!
Why is a Marley like me getting shot?
-What are you doing, Falco?
-Eldian should be at the forefront!
Can't you tell?
He can't fight anymore, he's our prisoner.
Udo, give me the tourniquet.
Here.
Damn kids, forget about him. He's an enemy.
Is that supposed to be your strong suit?
You're trying to overshadow me
by adhering to the international law,
believing it will get you chosen
to inherent the Armored?
It doesn't seem to be working, though.
Hell if I care.
Weirdo.
He's saying something.
Can you translate for me, Udo?
Tell him his bleeding is settling down,
so he can just relax.
"Don't touch me."
"You filthy."
"Devil."
That's what he said.
Retreat!
Hurry up!
Get away from the fortress!
Don't get caught in it!
It started.
No! Stop it!
They truly are… devils.
So our Marleyan ancestors…
were eaten up that way, too, huh.
By you Eldians.
Fire!
The kinetic bombardment was sufficient.
But due to excessive altitude,
about half of them died from falling.
Many of the Anti-Titan artillery
are still functional.
Twenty eight… twenty nine…
Location and number confirmed.
But still…
A wall again?
I'm sick of walls already!
It's the Armored!
Kill him!
Fire!
The Anti-Titan shells…
So it can even pierce my armor?
What? What just hit me?
Armored Train?
There's still more of it?
Fire
Galliard!
You descendants of whore!
Good.
So, you've subdued them all…
Our defeat caused this war, Reiner.
Isn’t war a terrible thing?
Now, at last… this war will end.
With the annihilation of their fleet,
the Mid-East Allied Forces
signed a peace treaty with Marley.
The four-year long war
ended with Marley's victory.
♫In an instant ♫
However, the world learns that
the age ruled by Titan is coming to an end.
♫In an abandoned world♫
Marley must soon acquire
the power of the Founding Titan
as soon as possible.
♫If you can fly♫
No way…
Thanks to the excellent
work of our courageous brave Marleyan army,
♫Please tell him♫
the Fort Slava has fallen!
♫Many birds with burnt wings♫
Awesome!
As expected from our Marleyan army!
♫Scattering ashes and smiling♫
♫I wish someone♫
♫Spreading the proof of my existence♫
♫Even if my body turns into dusts♫
♫I will be immortal♫
[Next episode]
The power of the Titans is not absolute.
It's the fact faced by the Marleyan army.
With a fleeting joy of victory,
the warriors return to their homeland; Liberio.
Next episode: Midnight Train
[Midnight Train]