Sub by kisscambodai
♪Our entangled fate♪
♪Love doesn’t need any logical thinking♪
♪Instead of right pace♪
♪Baby You’re my only remedy♪
♪I’m willing to be
treated by you all my life♪
♪On my heart you knock knock knock♪
♪There comes your exclusive summons♪
♪Your eyes are engraved on my mind♪
♪I want you to belong to me♪
♪A sure and happy future♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
♪Needs your frown
smile and glance♪
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪A lifetime of hug♪
My Little Happiness
Episode 27
Rong.
Make sure you lock the door.
Our main task these days
is to distribute supplies
to the victims.
There is a list on this paper.
Please familiarize yourself with it.
Everybody, hold the intercom,
and act in unison.
Hand in Hand, Earthquake Relief
Earthquake Relief
Hello.
We’re volunteers in support.
Thank you.
We brought relief supplies
in the trucks.
Great.
Get down and move the supplies.
Come on.
Boys.
Disaster Relief Supplies
Saline and anti-inflammatory drugs
brought by the volunteers arrived.
Please help
Medical Team of Puhua Hospital
and move them inside quickly.
-Coming. -Coming.
Distribution Stop
Water. Water.
Here you are. Take it.
Here you are.
There’s hot water over there.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank her.
This is for you.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
-Water.
-Thank you.
Hand in Hand, Earthquake Relief
Volunteer
Febuxostat
This part of the blood vessel
is too thin.
Can you do it?
Why not wait a moment?
Boss.
The patient’s bleeding out. Do it now.
Go on.
Earthquake Relief Medical Team
of Yun Ji Hospital
Operating Room
Earthquake Relief
China Health
Distribution Stop
-Hello.
We’re volunteers.
Come on.
Come down and gather.
Then you two go there to move supplies.
Be careful.
Come and take a look.
Go over there quickly.
Anyone?
Let’s go over there.
You check the back room.
Okay.
Be careful.
Anyone? Anyone?
Anyone?
Help me.
Help me, please.
Here is someone.
Kid, can you move?
How old are you? What’s your name?
My name is Xiaolang.
I’m five years old. It hurts.
Okay, don’t move.
Don’t move. I’ll get a stretcher.
Remember. Don’t move.
A five-year-old boy, conscious,
but the cabinet hit his lower body.
I don’t know if his spine was injured.
Be careful. Slowly. Slowly.
It hurts.
Slow down.
It’s okay. Boy, don’t be afraid.
It hurts.
Slow down.
I’ll get you out first.
It hurts.
Be careful. Be careful.
Don’t move.
Be careful. How is he?
Fortunately, the spine and nerves
were not injured.
It’s too dangerous here. Let’s go out.
Okay.
Be careful.
How are you? Does it hurt?
I’m fine. Go out.
Okay.
Be quick.
Come on. Be careful. His leg is hurt.
Okay.
Are you leaving today?
Not sure. Are you okay?
I’m fine. Don’t worry about me.
A doctor, please.
Go ahead.
When the surgery’s over,
if you’re still here, wait for me here.
I have something to tell you.
Looking at his back again,
I suddenly understand that
he is just a man.
But once he puts on that white coat,
he is like a man in armor.
And I’m willing to follow him
and do my best to protect his mission.
Notice.
Because of the aftershock,
the road ahead is blocked.
Today we’re here on standby,
waiting for the road to be cleared.
Roger that.
Disaster Relief Supplies
It’s snowing.
I told you I’d take care of myself.
I never break my promise.
Why did you get here?
I come to see you. Isn’t it okay?
I thought I might see you.
Then we meet here.
That means we’re meant
to meet each other.
Rong...
You...
What are you doing? Don’t shout.
How can you be so blind?
Go, go, go. Don’t look.
I wanted to go back
and find another chance to tell you.
Now that you’re here, I won’t wait.
What are these?
There are nothing on them.
Give me a second.
Disaster Relief Supplies
Three love letters for you.
Hello, Cong Rong from Class 11,
I’m Wen Shaoqing from Class 9.
Can I like you?
Pink.
The little girls
all like this color, right?
The little boys
all wrote love letters like this, right?
I studied regular script at that time.
You said you were Cong Rong
from Class 11.
But before I could tell you that
I was Wen Shaoqing in Class 9,
you transferred to another school.
White.
The college girls
all like this color, right?
Girls’ white skirts, boys’ white shirts.
When I was in college,
I studied running script.
If we met in college,
Cong, the book says gentle and calm,
years of quietness.
I would be your senior.
We’re the perfect couple.
There’s love in school.
In college, I read a few books,
so even my confession is full of books.
Silver gray.
Mature and stable.
As a doctor, I wrote too many cases,
Frown, smile, glance, a couple always.
so I used the doctors’ usual font, cursive script.
At this age,
if I write love letters,
I won’t
write about love.
A responsible man should
give a woman a lifetime commitment.
Disaster Relief Supplies
When did you prepare these?
Last time you said you wanted
a love letter from the boy you liked.
I used to think that
a love letter from the boy I like
would be very romantic.
♪I’m with you♪
Don’t look at it.
So yes?
♪The light with you♪
Why do you like me?
Because I like you.
It’s not logical reasoning,
so it can’t be calculated step by step.
♪Being simple♪
Take your time.
♪Being stable♪
Let me know when you figure it out.
♪Begin to stop♪
Road is cleared.
Notice.
Road is cleared. Let’s go.
♪About the future Being brave together♪
♪Comparing with each other♪
♪Being attractive to each other♪
♪It is like fate♪
Be careful.
♪Walk easily towards across all others♪
♪With you♪
♪I’m with you♪
See you around.
♪Being with you♪
♪The light with you♪
♪Only if I’m with you♪
♪I have the brightest night♪
Today,
Dijing City held a post-disaster
reconstruction oath conference.
The first rescue teams
have returned to the provinces
and cities.
One in Trouble
Volunteers will receive honor.
All Others Come to Help
Comrades, we won!
Take photos.
Get ready.
Okay, left hand up.
Don’t move.
Earthquake Relief
Commendation Conference
Thank you.
Earthquake Relief
Commendation Conference
I’m already downstairs.
When can I see you?
Wait a moment.
Rong, I missed you so much.
Why are you here?
He dropped me off,
and he wanted to see you.
Come with me, Cousin.
Anyway, you have a lot of time.
Just give me a few minutes.
Rong.
New Year’s gift I grabbed.
What’s this?
Take a look.
2019 Yun Ji Hospital
What’s this? Medical Guide?
Look here.
Do you like it?
These 12 people
were elected by the whole hospital.
Boss is so handsome, right?
Not bad. I’ve seen him.
It’s not for everyone.
I raffled it off.
I gave up selling in high prices
to honor you.
Thank you for
your talk with my mother.
I don’t have to listen to her nagging
about the rescue.
You’re old enough
to pay me back.
Yeah, of course.
So, give me a big bonus
for the New Year.
Okay, I’ll leave you alone.
Bye! Bye, Boss!
You keep looking at it.
Better than real me?
I didn’t know
you could be so sexy.
More than that. I’m also emotional.
Oh.
Oh, sorry to interrupt you.
Rangyirang.
Why not give way?
It’s your dog. It’s certainly like you.
You look fine.
The rescue must go well.
Yeah, yeah, thanks to you.
Why don’t you get back to it?
Let’s go. Rangyirang.
Go home.
This way.
Go to my house.
What are you up to?
Rangyirang. You can go to my house.
I’ll bring something.
You have a third wheel…
In your room.
Rong, you’re back…?
What are you doing here?
I watch your house, so I’m here.
Ah, it’s not a good time.
No.
But that’s okay.
I’ve done my part,
so I’ll leave you two alone.
Bye.
We won’t bother you. Have fun.
How about staying for dinner?
Be real.
You can eat it all by yourself.
Your grandpa asked me to remind you
to buy the Blue Phalaenopsis
for your grandma
when New Year comes.
Why don’t we start with the cake?
What?
I just think it’s so great that
we can live and die together,
and be so close
even if we can’t see each other.
I guess this is what you’d call
a romantic love. Right?
You’re jealous?
Well, do you know
the point of a romantic love?
Never give up?
It’s two people, one pair.
And we’re special.
We’re just two people.
Oh, I see.
You mean I haven’t said yes, right?
So much nonsense.
So?
I thought I’d already say yes.
That’s in your heart. I don’t know.
I didn’t know you cared so much.
You like me so much?
Yeah, of course.
So when are we going out?
My boyfriend.
What?
You promised me last time.
I wrote it all down on my phone.
Where did I promise to go?
I have proof.
Street Park, right?
Zhou Chengcheng made many dishes.
She’s so sweet.
I haven’t had a good meal
for a long time.
I’m sick of crunchy crackers.
Why aren’t you eating?
I can be full watching you eat.
Cong Rong.
Come to my house for the New Year.
My parents are coming back this year.
You can meet my parents.
What did you say?
I’m serious.
All of a sudden?
But can I?
Of course, you’re the girl I like.
I mean, am I their type?
How is my hair?
How are my clothes?
Should I change my look?
No, they like everything about you.
I’ll take that as a yes.
I want to say...
No?
No, my shirt got grease on it.
It won’t come out.
Leave it to me.
You just leave yourself to me.
Mom, I have some bad news.
No, you’re scaring me.
Is everything okay?
I’m fine.
I can’t go home for New Year this year.
Will you spend the New Year at Shaoqing’s?
That’s great.
That’s good news, not bad news.
You won’t see your lovely daughter.
That’s okay.
After you get married,
you go home together for the New Year.
I’ll be so happy.
So, what’s the plan?
Not yet.
Why?
Then why are you blushing?
Come on, tell me.
How’s it going? How far have you gone?
Has he asked you to marry him?
So, when can I have a grandchild?
Oh.
You have so much free time.
Take good care of Dad Jiang,
and cook delicious meals for him.
Meet Parents
Blessing
Happy New Year!
Let’s go.
Happy New Year
This...
Is this the Phalaenopsis
that Grandma likes?
Yeah.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Are you nervous?
I’m fine.
Deep breathing is
a subconscious activation of
the parasympathetic nervous system
to release pressure.
What should I do? I’m so nervous that
I can’t walk well.
It’s okay. Just do as usual.
We’ll just have dinner.
My family is very easygoing.
We’re almost there.
Here, hold your bonus items.
Okay.
Grandma.
Take your time. Slow down.
Hello, Grandma, I’m Cong Rong.
Grandma.
This is the girl
I was telling you about.
Good. You are pretty.
Better than the picture.
You look good, too.
I’m what you call
a fashion old lady.
Oh, I almost forgot.
This is a gift for you.
Yeah. Grandma.
She knows you like Phalaenopsis.
So she found it specially.
That’s very kind of you.
The color is rare.
His grandpa asked me to look for it
for a long time,
but I couldn’t find it.
Thank you so much.
You’re welcome.
So nice.
She’s usually better,
but she’s a little nervous today.
That’s good.
It means she cares about you.
Come on. Come on in.
Let’s go.
I’ll prepare some dumpling stuffing.
You take her to meet Grandpa.
Where’s he?
He’s doing municipal construction.
Municipal construction?
It’s a good spot. I’ll take it.
Let me get the floor for you.
Okay, your turn.
3,500 points.
Here you are.
Not enough.
Five.
I told you.
I’ll stay in the jail today.
What’s the fun in that?
It teaches you to buy houses and land
when you have money.
-That’s interesting.
Grandpa, just ignore him.
He’s envious of your young mentality.
Rong, you’re here.
Uncle, this is Cong Rong.
I told you.
This is my best friend.
Uncle…
Grandpa. Happy New Year!
Happy New Year! Happy New Year!
Sit down.
Wen Rang, make some tea.
Go.
Okay, I’ll go.
Sit down.
Grandpa, let me introduce her for you.
Cong Rong.
Your girlfriend, a lawyer.
She fought a lawsuit for you and
just got back from the rescue with you.
You were after her, right?
Grandpa, you’re the Oracle.
Chengcheng muttered from time to time,
so I remembered that.
You’re always bragging about me.
Uncle, we’ve got a live one.
What do you think of her?
Good.
She’s just too skinny.
Come on, show me.
Smell it. Is it okay?
What did you say?
That’s not enough for you?
You can’t drink strong tea.
Smell it. Is it okay?
Okay.
All right. You said it’s okay.
Learn from her. Eat and drink well.
I don’t eat that much.
Don’t you?
You’re the No.1 omnivore.
Drink tea.
Rangyirang made the tea.
Rangyirang can make the tea?
Yeah, it can bite you.
Get away from my seat.
Be good. Pour the tea, Rangyirang.
We never interfere
with these kids.
But Shaoqing
never brought girls home.
It’s different this time.
He brings you to our home.
And he must be serious.
We talked it over with his parents and
we got you a welcome gift.
Grandpa, it’s too much.
I can’t take it.
Take it.
It’s a gift from the elders. Take it.
Open it.
This looks like blue amber,
a kind of amber.
I don’t know what the print is.
Pi Xiu?
Bi An.
It’s the seventh son of the Dragon.
It’s on the gate of Yamen.
It’s said to judge cases impartially.
Good point.
Then it’s for you.
Thanks, Grandpa. I’ll collect it well.
Great.
Dragon has nine sons.
Does he love the youngest the most?
You like it?
I’ll give one to you.
It’s perfect for you.
Okay.
Let’s make dumplings.
Dumplings. Go.
Help Grandma make dumplings.
Okay.
Coming, Mom.
Let’s go help, too.
Go.
Grandpa, we’re going.
Go, go.
Darling. Slow down.
It’s good to be at home.
Professor Wen, Professor Lin.
May I help you with your luggage?
No, we’ll do it ourselves.
The Dean arranged everything well.
Thank him for us.
Yes.
Okay.
It’s our appreciation. Take it.
You don’t have to do this. It’s my job.
Take it.
It’s New Year today.
You’ve worked so hard to pick us up.
Just take it.
Take it.
I wish you a happy new year
and a happy family.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Bye.
Mom, Dad.
Let’s go.
Son.
You must be tired after
flying for over ten hours.
I’m not tired when I see you.
This is Cong Rong, right?
Hello, Uncle and Aunt, I’m Cong Rong.
Come into the room. It’s cold outside.
I’ll get the luggage.
No, no, no. Go.
I’ll take it.
Come on, son.
Grandma and Grandpa are waiting for you.
The food is ready.
All right. Come on.
It must be hard on you, Aunt.
Are you okay?
I’m okay.
-Happy New Year.
-Good health to Mom and Dad.
-Good health to Grandma and Grandpa.
Thank you. Good luck to the kids.
Happy New Year, Aunt and Uncle.
All right, drink.
Drink.
Eat. Don’t wait for us.
-Come on.
-Eat.
You have a good appetite, so eat more.
Wen Rang. Shaoqing.
Take care of your girlfriends.
Did you hear that?
Aunt asked you to take care of me.
Yeah. I heard it.
It’s not the time yet.
I’ll get you some pepto-bismol
after dinner.
I can do it myself.
It’s the mission Grandma gave us.
Thank you.
How long can you stay here?
We’re not
going anywhere.
That’s right.
Really?
Yeah.
After all, that’s not our home abroad.
There is a sense of wandering.
So it’s better to go home.
That’s nice.
Chinese medical technology is good,
and investment funds are sufficient.
So we discussed it carefully and
transferred the personnel relationship
back to Yun Ji Hospital.
Dad, you’re back in Neurosurgery?
Yeah.
Your mom’s back in Thoracic Surgery.
Next year,
we
can meet at the hospital.
Don’t you welcome us?
Come on.
Congratulations.
Dr. Wen, you’ve made it this far.
You’re not young,
so you’d better go home.
Nothing is important
but family.
Family’s good.
-Poverty doesn’t matter.
That’s true.
Yeah, I agree with old...
No old.
Dad’s words.
Congratulations.
Brother and sister-in-law.
From now on, your father watches you.
And mine watches me.
That’s a lot of balance right there.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
Eat the dishes.
Dumplings.
Eat.
Just eat your food.
Food’s getting cold.
Who made the dumpling? Eat it.
This one, this pig-like one is mine.
I know it.
Oh, it’s leaking.
It’s leaking.
The pig’s alive.
Try my mom’s egg dumplings.
Dad, eat.
Okay. Let me eat.
Cong Rong.
Thank you, Aunt.
Eat more.
You eat more.
Okay, Dad.
This is good.
Come on.
Stop talking and eat.
Eat this.
This is good.
This is you, not obedient at all.
What?!
How obedient I am.
That bets I made with you.
Open my own bookstore
and get a girlfriend.
I’ve done them all.
Go and play.
Go, go.
Go play.
Look at that. Three stars.
On the left is the Longevity Star,
the middle is the Prosperity star,
and the right is the Luck Star.
Good, huh?
Yeah.
Aunt, I thought it was Wen Shaoqing.
Put this on.
You put it on. I wear more.
How is it? Are you used to it?
Good. It’s a good family.
Is this your first time outside
on New Year?
Yes.
But I do video chat with them.
I don’t want them to think
they’re empty nesters.
Shaoqing told me
the story of you two
about a banyan tree.
He told you that?
He loved school so much
because he was waiting for you.
He really likes you.
You like him a lot, too?
I like him as a boyfriend,
and
as a doctor.
His integrity, detachment,
discipline and empathy
are all good.
Aunt, look.
That’s a lot of fireworks.
Look, come here.
Look, it’s beautiful.
Fireworks.
This is beautiful. This is big.
So big.
Dad, look at that. Look at that.
That’s beautiful.
Here. Here.
What?
I can’t see it.
Come on, I’ll take you somewhere.
It’s beautiful.
Beautiful, isn’t it?
What about over there?
It was this lantern last year.
Can you see clearly from here?
It’s a nice view.
When I was a kid, I used to
do my homework on this balcony.
They would call me to eat in the yard.
You had a happy childhood.
I’m happier now.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪How to separate♪
What’s wrong?
Nothing.
I just think your family’s nice to me.
You’re nice, too.
Because they believe in me.
Someone I like must be nice.
♪Your smile is killing my healing♪
Time is almost up.
Let’s count it down.
Okay.
♪Say all the good night♪
♪Needs your frown smile and glance♪
Wen Shaoqing.
♪Let me stay with you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you
in our song♪
Happy New Year!
♪We look into each other’s eyes♪
♪The whispers of wind
sound like lovers’ words♪
Happy New Year!
♪They’re saying happiness comes♪
♪We hold each other’s hands♪
♪We embrace each other♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Finally we hold hands♪
♪Intimacy is assurance
of your tenderness♪
♪The unforgettable smile♪
♪I want to remember it each second♪
♪Partly hidden Your shyness♪
♪A postcard filled with memories♪
♪Favorite milk tea Firework in the park♪
♪Each word memorized deeply in heart♪
♪I want us to travel through space♪
♪Feelings grow during this summer♪
♪The moment you left temporarily♪
♪I was in the clouds♪
♪Sunset glow has cleared my eyes♪
♪The subtle realness of dream♪
♪You aren’t aware of your beauty♪
♪Thanks to what the time has made♪
♪Intimacy is
when looking into your eyes♪
♪Turns out happiness can stay longer♪
♪You are my little happiness♪
♪How romantic it has been♪
♪How vivid the sweetness has been♪