♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 3=
Add a few more herbs,
it will be more effective.
I’ll look for them.
Are you okay, kitten?
You put yourself in such a mess
to save a wild cat?
You again?
Stay away from me.
It’s the law of jungle.
Death and life are destined.
Why do you ask for trouble?
No trouble at all!
I can cure it.
Animals always
get injured in the mountain.
Can you cure them all?
Since I came across it,
I will cure it.
Father said that doctors can’t cure
all the people in the world,
but they can cure the ones they meet.
I’m not arguing with you.
If you have to save this cat,
I can help you.
Don’t bother.
I can do it myself. Thank you.
Fine.
Then go by yourself.
Houttuynia cordata...
Houttuynia cordata!
The last is golden-leaf chrysanthemum.
Golden-leaf chrysanthemum!
What are you thinking about?
You can talk?
Are you worried about me?
Is anybody there?
Who is it?
Thank you.
(Bingxing)
I’m Bingxing from Luofeng Pavilion.
Thank you for helping us
kill the fleeing demons.
May I ask your name?
Yuchi Longyan.
Luofeng Pavilion can’t
even control the demons.
You are the Dragon King.
Luofeng Pavilion owes you a favor.
It’ll pay you back some day.
I’m leaving.
You got hurt?
Just small injury.
No, it must be treated now.
I’ll treat you.
What a grand library!
Who are you?
How can
there be such an attractive,
elegant
and handsome person?
In the human world...
No, no. In the elf world,
I’ve never seen anyone
as handsome as you.
You don’t treat yourself as an outsider.
I haven’t asked you who you are
and what you’re doing here.
But you asked me first.
I... I’m the bird elf Qingqing.
You... You are Immortal of Fate?
Exactly.
Oh my.
I always thought
you were an old man.
I didn’t expect you to be such
a young and handsome immortal.
I have to tell
my friends on earth and in heaven.
I can’t let rumors ruin your reputation.
Look how handsome you are.
You are so talkative.
You shouldn’t come here.
I will not punish you today.
Get out of here.
No.
Please allow me to read the books here.
As soon as I find a solution,
I’ll leave.
Please.
Meteor mark.
Take your clothes off.
I’ll apply medicine to you.
Now?
Don’t think too much.
I just wanna apply medicine to you.
Here we go.
This medicine may make you painful.
Hang in there.
Thank you for saving me.
I’m not used to
you talking to me this way.
Why does my face burn
when she is close to me?
It’s done.
Spotty, it’s your turn.
So,
do you fall in love with a mortal
and want to find the books
to see what you should do?
Fall in love with a mortal?
How is it possible?
I have only one friend
in the human world.
She is Liuying from Xiahou’s Mansion.
She’s my savior,
not my love.
Liuying from Xiahou’s Mansion.
You’re really interesting.
I’ll make an exception today.
Tell me.
What can I do for you?
Really?
Sir,
you’re not only handsome, but fine.
You’re unique in heaven and earth.
I...
I want to find out
this scar on my forehead.
I was the most beautiful bird elf.
But this scar
becomes a hindrance to my beauty.
And I think it is weird.
It’s always on my forehead
no matter what I become.
So I went here and wanted to...
It’s meteor mark.
You know it?
Have a look.
(Book of Reincarnation)
It is the symbol of the soul.
If you want to remove it,
you have to go to Luofeng Pavilion.
Thank you so much.
(Book of Reincarnation)
You are so nice.
Spotty, it’s your turn.
(The Legend of the White Snake)
Spotty?
I just named it.
Do you randomly name
all the animals you save?
Not all of them.
Just special ones.
Who is the most special?
The most special?
Of course, it’s...
In that case,
call it Marble.
Marble.
It sounds good.
Then your name is Marble, okay?
Marble.
(The Legend of the White Snake)
The white snake
is also to repay the favor.
According to this book...
(The white snake repays the favor)
(Love in West Lake
in a rainy spring day)
It’s raining.
Bad weather.
Suddenly it began to rain.
Here you are.
Thank you.
Don’t you share the umbrella with me?
You just hold it.
Okay.
It’s not the same as in the book,
but we walk together under one umbrella.
It stops raining.
Your wound gets wet.
Are you worried about me?
I’ll bind it up for you later.
Okay.
According to the story of
“Borrowing the Umbrella” in the book,
her attitude is really different.
It seems that the methods in this book
are effective.
This is Luofeng Pavilion.
It’s too depressing.
The new-born souls
have to go to Luofeng Pavilion
before they go to the human world.
For the sake of our six hundred years
of friendship,
please don’t let us drink the Lethe Tea.
Drink the Lethe Tea
given by the Grief Purger
in the River of Tears.
Forget the past and
descend to the human world.
It’s so stupid to be punished for love.
It would be better for you
not to see each other again.
No need to thank me.
Xue Qianxun, master of Luofeng Pavilion,
(Xue Qianxun)
is cold-blooded and impartial.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
-Look at that man.
-So handsome.
-If only I could marry him.
-He’s so handsome.
Sir, could you give me a hand?
Sir.
What’s wrong with me?
Don’t get me wrong, Dragon King.
I didn’t mean that.
I think you did right just now.
I can return the favor.
Dragon King, have you heard that
men and women should keep distance?
I know.
Men and women should keep distance.
Xu Xian said the same thing
when he lent Bai Suzhen an umbrella.
But Bai Suzhen...
Let me say it again.
You don’t have to return the favor.
I know.
It was wrong to make a commitment.
It’s all the fault of this book.
(An Evilly Charming Emperor's Requite )
You did that
because you read this?
This is a bad book. You can’t read it.
If you read this book,
people would think you are a bad man.
There are books in the human world
that teach people to be bad.
You don’t read bad books, do you?
Of course not.
It seems that
I have to finish reading
how the white snake returns the favor.
(The Legend of the White Snake)
Xue Qianxun has a Fleeting Pipa.
But he never plays it.
It can remove the meteor mark
on your forehead.
Just get the string, grind it
and apply the powder to your forehead,
and the mark will disappear.
This is the Fleeting Pipa.
Immortal of Fate didn’t cheat me.
It seems that my mark can be removed.
Hold on.
Is it too obvious?
Immortal of Fate said
I just need to get the string.
How dare you!
Catch her.
Yes.
Go.
My Lord.
She entered your room
without permission.
How to deal with her?
Kill her.
Yes.
Sir. Your Highness.
No, no.
My Lord, please spare my life.
I’m just an elf.
It’s my fault
to enter your room without permission.
But I don’t want to steal any secret.
I just want to get...
to borrow your Fleeting Pipa.
You don’t play it anyway.
How dare you!
How dare you look at him like that.
Fleeting Pipa is his greatest treasure.
I can’t believe you want to borrow it.
I’m afraid you want to steal it.
No, no.
As an old saying goes,
goes...
Well...
The desire to look attractive
is universal.
I came to steal the string just to...
to remove the scar on my forehead.
No, no, the meteor mark on my soul.
Remove the scar on the soul
with the string?
I’ve never heard of it.
You’re obviously lying.
Take her away.
Yes.
-No!
-Wait.
For thousands of years,
no one dares to borrow my pipa.
She is so weird.
I’ll punish you
by being my maid for a hundred years.
I...
I’ll find out
what you really want to do.
Why did you take my power?
Take her away.
Go.
I’m a bird elf. I can’t be a maid.
-Go.
-Let me go. I can’t be a maid.
And I can’t do anything.
I only care about beauty.
You’ll regret
making me a maid.
Marble, you’ll sleep here tonight.
I understand.
What?
Bai Suzhen,
a thousand-year-old snake demon,
comes down to repay Xu Xian.
In order to return the favor,
she marries her savior.
If you like this way,
I can marry you.
Marry me?
Would you marry a dragon?
I... I can’t afford it.
Why?
Because...
Because I have no money.
It doesn’t matter.
I have a Dragon Pool
and a thousand years of spirit power.
You don’t have to worry about money.
And I don’t eat much.
You should be able to afford me.
No.
What? You still won’t?
I don’t mean it.
Actually,
I didn’t save you.
My lady saved you.
If you want to return the favor,
you should go to my lady.
But I clearly remember
the smell of your body.
I have a good intuition.
Or you don’t want to marry me
because I’m not a human being.
Of course not.
Or you don’t think I’m good-looking.
It doesn’t matter.
No matter what you like,
I can become what you like.
You like scholars?
Or generals?
(Dadu Baochao)
Or you like the rich?
I don’t think you’re not good-looking.
I walked all day today.
I’m a bit tired.
You are right.
It’s really late.
Have a rest.
You’re not leaving?
Don’t we
have a rest together?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪