♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 4=
It’s getting late.
I should go to bed.
You are right.
It’s really late.
Have a rest.
You’re not leaving?
Don’t we
have a rest together?
Didn’t I tell you
men and women should keep distance?
A woman who says that
usually ends up with a gentleman.
So, you’ll marry me in the end.
I really can’t marry you.
Do you
detest me?
No.
Perhaps I don’t understand mortal love
or I don’t know how to please you.
But I’ll give it a good try.
Only people who love each other
can get married.
Forget about the operas and novels.
They’re not real.
Anyway, unmarried men and women
cannot share a bedroom
in the mortal world.
But this is the only room left
of the inn.
Where could I sleep?
You are the Dragon King.
Why sleep in the inn with me?
Go back to your Dragon Pool.
Go now.
Get out of here.
Come on.
Unmarried men and women
cannot share a bedroom
in the mortal world.
We shared a bed before.
Didn’t that make us a married couple?
Good girl, Marble.
Go to sleep.
If sharing a bed means we’re married,
why did she refuse me to return favor
and not marry me?
Hard to follow.
She smells cool
and fragrant.
I didn’t lose sleep in a strange room,
and woke up naturally.
Marble,
Dragon King may go back to his pool.
You’re still here.
You slept well last night, didn’t you?
Yes, great.
How about you?
It was great,
but later a silly pig
crawled on me
and I was almost suffocated.
There are pigs in Dragon Pool?
Well, can the pigs
get in your bed as they wish?
Let’s go.
Good girl.
-Don’t cry.
-Look.
Look what I got here.
Let me take it.
Good girl.
Let’s go.
We’re going home.
Listen. Is it beautiful?
What?
What do you mean?
Your arm hurts?
(Luofeng Pavilion)
I’m sorry. I’m sorry.
Forgive me.
That’s the silk handkerchief
Immortal Fox gave me.
Immortal Fox?
Qingqing.
Yes.
Fire, there’s a fire.
Why not perform the extinguishing spell?
That’s because you sealed
my power.
Of course I couldn’t perform the spell,
or conjure water.
Otherwise,
I could have transformed to Blue Bird
and flap the fire out with my wings
even if I’m bad with spells.
So you shouldn’t have...
I’ll get you a new robe.
Three days.
No food for you for three days.
I...I didn’t mean to.
You...you...
You’re the cruelest man in the world.
Why did I smile?
Marble, your wound will be healed soon.
When you fully recover,
I’ll send you home.
Marble,
where did the Dragon King
go?
He isn’t coming back, is he?
You’re back.
Here.
Roasted chestnuts.
You haven't been so happy for some time.
Enjoy it.
It tastes
just like those I had in the capital.
I thought there wouldn’t be
such tasty roasted chestnuts
in the town.
They are the chestnuts from the capital.
Sure they taste the same.
You went back to the capital
to buy the roasted chestnuts?
Just some chestnuts.
No big deal.
Thank you.
You’re welcome.
I’m requiting your kindness.
In fact, you don’t need to do that.
Your company along the way
has made me very happy.
Are you alright?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
Let me check it.
Your pulse is irregular.
Is it because of your old wound?
Does it hurt?
Get up. Let me see it.
I’m fine.
Are you afraid of pain?
Are you kidding me?
My wound is healed.
Are you sure?
Not even a scar.
Right.
You are the Dragon King.
You’re blushing.
Are you having a fever?
I’m fine.
It’s stuffy here. I...
I need to
get some fresh air.
Then I’ll be fine.
Vulnerable people shouldn’t go out.
Why am I so hot all over
and why is my heart racing?
(The Garden)
Take a look, gentlemen.
The two most beautiful girls
are going to perform
the new White Snake and Green Snake.
Gentlemen, hurry up.
It begins soon.
You don’t want to miss it.
(The New White Snake and Green Snake)
Men, come in quickly.
The performance begins soon.
You don’t want to miss it.
Come on, gentlemen, come in please.
(The Garden)
Sir, come in please.
Come and take a look.
(The Garden)
A play by the two most beautiful girls.
It begins soon.
Qing, you and I
have cultivated for thousands of years.
Don’t be fooled by Fahai.
Suzhen, what is good about Xu Xian?
What is love?
About love, I don’t know how to put it.
All I know is he’s always in my mind.
From dawn to dusk, I miss him.
Racing heart
is a symbol of love.
That’s mortal love.
So you’re not requiting his kindness,
but have fallen in love with him.
I think I should just take him here.
I don’t believe
he won’t fall for your beauty.
That’s right.
Qing, mortal love is disciplined.
People in love care about each other,
but they keep it quiet
from others.
When the tokens of love are exchanged,
they can hold a wedding ceremony
and be happy together
for their lifetime.
I see.
Once the tokens of love are given,
direct contact is allowed
between men and women.
Qing, when you and I
cultivated in Mount Emei,
our cave was high and cold.
We were buried in clouds every day.
No company, mister?
Your chestnut cake tastes special.
Pack some for two, please.
This is our specialty.
You can enjoy here, but can’t take away.
Then get them ready.
I’ll come back.
…enjoy the landscape.
Where have you been? Do you feel better?
Much better.
What brings you out?
Did you also
have a racing heart like mine?
I came out to look for you.
I think maybe the pig hurt
your heart last night,
so I booked two rooms for tonight
and you can have a good sleep.
You’re looking for me?
Do you care about me?
Sure I do.
People in love care about each other.
I heard only people in love
care about each other.
No.
Um...
Friends also care about each other.
I know. I know.
Keep it from others.
When the tokens of love are exchanged...
You can’t say it.
By the way,
I know a place where
great chestnut cakes are served.
You’ll like them. Go.
You didn’t eat any at all.
Delicious.
Sir, you paid a precious pearl.
I’m Peony. Thank you.
Never mind.
My chamber is cozy.
Would you like to come with me?
No thanks.
Let’s go.
Sir.
Miss, you’re not alone here.
Give yourself some honor.
Young lady, you must be joking.
Which girl who has honor
would come to The Garden?
The Garden?
Yes.
Allow me.
Sir.
You mean
this is a pleasure house?
Yes, miss. Don’t be so surprised.
When I served the young master,
he quite enjoyed it
and he paid a great deal.
It was great.
You brought me to a pleasure house?
And this woman and you...
What is a pleasure house?
Liuying.
Don’t touch me.
Liuying, what’s wrong?
Didn’t you like the chestnut cakes?
I was worried about you
and looked for you everywhere at night.
Yet you went to the pleasure house
and had fun with Peony.
And you brought me there too.
Seeing you angry
pains me in the chest.
It feels more terrible
than heart racing.
I didn’t know The Garden
is a pleasure house.
But if you don’t like the place,
we won’t go there anymore.
Well, how
did you get to know Peony?
I went to watch
The Legend of White Snake
and found the chestnut cakes delicious,
so, I brought you there.
It seems
I misunderstood you.
Don’t ever go to
the pleasure house again, alright?
Alright.
My lord, the Heaven is now in peace.
♪Autumn orchid
green leaves and violet stem♪
♪In the hall of beauties I’m Qingqing♪
♪Autumn orchid
green leaves and violet stem♪
♪In the hall of beauties I’m Qingqing♪
-Qingqing.
-I...
Yes, my lord.
Bingxing,
take her to the River of Tears
to practice.
If she’s genuinely tone deaf,
give her the post of Grief Purger.
Yes.
I don’t want to be the Grief Purger.
It’s cold and damp
by the River of Tears.
Without feathers, I could catch a cold.
What’s up?
What brings you here?
I heard you’re in danger.
I stung my finger. It’s nothing.
Why put the finger in your mouth?
Because
it relieves the pain.
So like cats, you lick
the wound to get cured.
Why are you still up
and sewing at this hour?
I can’t sleep in a strange bed.
Strange bed?
I mean
I’m used to my bed
with my quilts and pillow.
In a different bed, I can’t fall asleep.
Like now.
But I slept well
last night.
Don’t worry about me.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
(Love with Dragon)
Love with Dragon.
The bed isn’t the problem.
I am.
Bravo! Bravo!
There is an opera on.
Raccoon for A Prince.
I watched it before.
Lord Bao delivered justice
and proved Concubine Li’s innocence.
Delivered justice?
Nothing but people in power
speak louder.
I think
there’s justice in the mortal world.
There may not be justice even in Heaven.
Why did you say that?
What’s wrong?
Did you
learn it by experience?
What could you do even if I tell you?
What’s wrong with you?
Are you bothered by something?
You can talk to me.
It will make you feel better.
If you’d like to share,
I’ll be glad to hear it.
So,
what is the injustice
you suffered from?
The Stone of Goddess Nuwa?
Guards of the terrace?
Anybody here?
Refreshing.
The purifying Stone of Goddess Nuwa
cures the wound.
Amazing.
Insolent man!
(Immortal Ziyang)
How dare you steal the Stone?
You get me wrong.
I’m not stealing it.
We have evidence.
Stop justifying yourself.
Guards, seize him!
-Yes.
God,
this is the dragon demon
who attempted to steal the Stone.
Why did you try to steal the Stone?
I fell onto the Terrace of Nuwa
and basked in its radiance.
Absurd.
The Stone is a heavenly object
and the Terrace is heavily guarded.
How could you possibly see its radiance?
When I fell onto it, no one was there.
It’s impossible.
Thirty-six heavenly guards
keep watching in turns.
It must be guarded.
Then you should ask
why the guards weren’t there.
God, we should look into
the guards if they quit their posts.
Find it out.
Yes, my lord.
The demon tried to steal the Stone.
How should we punish him?
Thunder strike for a thousand years.
Return to his original form
and start over again.
Granted.
This is unfair.
I don’t accept it.
Thunder strike for a thousand years?
Those guards quit their posts!
How could they pass the buck to you?
This is outrageous.
So when Lady Xiahou and I
found you in the garden,
you were just struck by thunder, right?
It’s really heartbreaking.
Yes.
It hurt a lot.
It pains here
and here too.
So at a moment like this,
she doesn’t care about that men and
women shouldn’t have direct contact.
What’s that sound?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪