(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
So?
Did the talk with your father go well?
How dare you. Eyes down!
(Statement)
You made and distributed illegal propaganda leaflets.
You admit to planning the whole thing on your own, right?
Yes.
(Letter of Withdrawal)
(Kim Myeong Hee)
I never thought you, of all people, would decide to drop out.
Are you sure you won't regret this decision?
Yes.
For real. Just ask her. It's okay.
Myeong Hee.
Something came up with my family.
Can you cover my Saturday shift?
Sure.
You want me...
to get engaged to Lee Soo Ryeon?
Yes.
(Episode 5: A Good Woman)
Why do you want me to get engaged?
I heard your family...
is now involved in her family's business.
If the factory doesn't get built...
I'm not asking about Soo Ryeon. What's your reason?
Did you invest in Changhwa Pharmaceuticals?
Then I'll understand.
To me, Soo Ryeon is...
as important as Kyung Soo is to you.
I encouraged her...
when I should've stopped her if anything.
That's why things got all messed up.
If...
If anything bad happens to her family,
I'll beat myself up for it for the rest of my life.
Are you sure you'll be okay...
if I get engaged?
Yes.
All right.
- Bye. - Wait.
Hold on.
What?
Do you have something else to say?
Oh, this?
My dad asked me to pick up some flowers.
Goodnight then.
(Emergency Room)
Gosh, I'm late.
What?
Hey, Soo Ryeon.
You're still here?
What's going on?
I wanted to see you even for just a moment.
I was actually wondering if I should call you...
and see you tonight even if it's late.
Why? Do you have to talk to me about something?
The thing is...
I'm going to start seeing Hee Tae.
I thought I should tell you first.
Hey, Soo Ryeon.
Are you all right? What's wrong?
What do I do?
My family is in trouble.
Myeong Hee.
Can you please try to persuade Hee Tae?
You told me that he already said no.
How can I...
He may change his mind if you ask him to do it.
Help me just this once.
Ask him for me. Please?
If I can't get engaged,
both my father and brother...
will suffer because of me.
Please, Myeong Hee.
Please.
("Kyungsoo Daily")
(Detained Students to Be Released Immediately)
Isn't it too early to be interested in political affairs?
- Good morning. - Hwang Hee Tae.
What brings you here?
I'm here to speak with your father in person.
What do you need to talk to my father about?
You know what it's about.
- I can come in, right? - No, you can't.
I told you I'd take care of it. Can't you just...
Look at you lovebirds bickering with each other again.
You two have so much energy even though it's still early.
Let's go inside. Have breakfast with us.
It's okay.
I'm here to speak with your father.
I'm sorry for stopping by unannounced at this early hour.
I figured I should tell you...
as soon as possible to sort out the situation.
Okay, what is it about?
This all began because of Soo Ryeon,
so I was waiting for her to tell you and Soo Chan herself,
but it doesn't look like it'll happen anytime soon.
So I'm here to do it myself.
Hwang Hee Tae, are you seriously...
We'd like to get engaged.
A little bit to the right.
A little more.
Pull down your chin a little.
No, not that much.
Are you sure you can do this?
Do you not trust me? Oh, that's it!
Yes, stay still. I'll take it now.
Hey, smile a little.
No, not a smirk.
As if you're thinking about someone you love.
You know what I mean.
Lucky you for having a friend like me.
It would've taken you at least two days...
even if you had gone to every photo studio downtown.
Thanks a bunch!
Hold on. If you're applying for a passport...
I suppose you can afford a plane ticket now?
Soo Ryeon.
Lee Soo Ryeon? Did she lend you the money?
I thought you didn't want to ask for a favor.
Well, that's how it turned out.
I guess she has a conscience.
I'm glad.
Don't even think of paying it back and just use it.
Think of it as compensation.
Compensation for what?
You know, for what happened in high school.
If you hadn't taken all the blame,
you wouldn't have to be making a passport like this.
You would've gone to a nice university here...
and lived a proud life like her.
Why do you keep mentioning that?
Soo Ryeon had nothing to do with that.
Okay, whatever you say.
Lady Soo Ryeon had nothing to do with it whatsoever...
and it was all voluntary?
Hey, Sun Min.
Whatever. Just take this.
(Kim Myeong Hee)
It's just because I'm so frustrated.
You always pretend to be strong and unfazed...
but eventually end up taking all the blame...
and giving everything away.
Don't you have any pride?
You're not even saying hi now?
I didn't have time to.
I'm too busy preparing for the engagement ceremony.
Hello.
I heard.
That you're getting engaged.
Thank you.
Instead of thanking me,
don't you have anything else to say?
I'm sorry...
for forcing you to do this.
Instead of saying "thank you" or "I'm sorry",
I'm asking you how you really feel.
Like whether you feel happy or sad.
If you tell me to stop, I will.
I'll stop right away.
I'm going to leave soon anyway.
And you and Soo Ryeon...
will have to stay.
I don't want to cause trouble just to be happy for a short while.
So this is how you hold yourself back.
What?
I'd better get going then.
I have a lesson.
Hee Tae. I already chose...
the song we'll listen to today.
I don't listen to music when I study.
(1979 TBC's Songs of Youth)
Come on. Music is what?
Sit down. We have a lot of work to do.
Come on.
You said I was destined to be good at math.
Why don't we enjoy some nice music...
Gosh.
"Enjoy?"
Have you ever seen anyone enjoy doing push-ups?
Math is like strengthening your muscles.
There is no shortcut. Got it?
The results depend on how much effort you put in.
- Show me your homework then. - Yes, sir.
(May 10, 6pm, Gwangju Park Hotel)
This week?
Gosh, isn't this a bit too soon?
And why did you reserve such a fancy place?
It's not even a wedding.
Hey. Are you okay with this?
Anyhow, the decision has been made,
so place an announcement in the local paper.
And make some calls to our relatives in advance.
- Go on then. - Okay.
[VIU Ver] KBS E09 'Youth of May'
"Myeong Hee's Trip to Seoul"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
(List of Contacts)
You're coming home now?
You surprised me.
Are you testing me?
I really quit.
Lighter.
Here.
Where's the lighter I gave you last time?
Oh, it must be here somewhere...
This will work just as fine. Shall I light you up?
(Music Cafe Hee Hee Nak Rak)
Music Cafe...
I guess you have it in your blood too.
You know how my mom was.
I take after her, you know.
That may not be true, seeing what you did today.
I'm glad you decided to get engaged. Good job.
It was nothing.
Then...
You can continue to see other women even after you get married.
What I mean is, don't mess up a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity...
just because of some petty emotions.
Just like my mother?
Good night, Father.
(Music Cafe Hee Hee Nak Rak)
(Cheongja Cigarettes)
(Kim Myeong Hee)
(Ministry of Foreign Affairs, Jongno-gu, Seoul)
What's taking her so long?
Oh, gosh. You surprised me.
- Hee Tae. - Hello.
Why are you standing here? You should wait inside.
Soo Ryeon's going to need some time.
It's okay.
Are you going somewhere?
Oh, I'm going to Seoul today.
Oh, I heard you're going shopping for wedding gifts and your outfits.
Yes.
I'm sending someone who'll take good care of you,
so you don't have to worry.
"Take good care of us?"
Gosh, this is it.
Take a look at this baby. How pretty.
Gosh, Auntie.
Did you excavate that from the ground or what?
Can't we just choose something simple?
That's nonsense.
An engagement gift should be this fancy at least.
Hee Tae? Take a look.
What do you think?
I think I saw that in an ancient tomb...
I mean, she looks like someone from a royal family.
Do you really think so? Good.
Let's choose yours now.
- What? - This bracelet.
Oh, that's...
What do you think?
I feel like I've become Buddha...
The thing is, my family is Christian.
This is truly unbelievable.
Even your picky tastes...
are exactly alike. You know?
Auntie. Why don't you go home now?
We'll pick out some nice gifts on our own.
Yes. You need to pick out your hanbok too.
You must be busy.
I don't need a new hanbok.
I'm going to wear the one I already have.
Goodness, that's not okay.
Go and pick out a new one.
You should. We already let the store know.
Let's go.
Then let me take a look at just one more.
Excuse me.
Can you show us the one with the rubies over there?
Sure.
- Auntie. Come on. - Hold on.
This necklace would be perfect.
What do you think? Doesn't it look nice?
- It does. - Right?
I'll get going now.
- Is this true? - How could this be possible?
- No way. - I'm sure it's true.
Seriously?
- Gosh. - Unbelievable.
What's wrong? Did something happen again?
(We urge the media to report facts!)
(Engagement, Hwang Hee Tae and Lee Soo Ryeon)
Soo Ryeon is getting engaged to Hee Tae?
Hwang Ki Nam, the guy's father,
is the Head of Anti-communist Investigation, right?
I knew something was wrong...
when the elusive Won Seok got arrested.
Lee Soo Ryeon was a mole.
Watch your mouth.
That's a groundless accusation.
Are you still defending Lee Soo Ryeon?
Even after seeing this?
You never liked Soo Ryeon anyway.
What?
Put your personal feelings aside.
It looks like you're excited to have an excuse to hate her.
No one is more excited than Lee Soo Ryeon right now.
I just saw her picking out jewelry, looking all happy.
Jewelry? Where?
Gosh. I'm going to go over there and see for myself.
- That sounds good. - We should do that.
- Calm down, guys. - Let's go.
What? 1 to 2 months?
But I have to leave the country next month.
You probably didn't know,
but it's not so easy to get a passport.
A waiting time of 1 to 2 months is just an average.
It often takes even longer.
Is there any way to speed up the process?
Do you know anyone in the Ministry of Foreign Affairs?
Then there's nothing you can do.
Next.
What if I fail to leave the country...
because I can't get a passport after all the fuss?
I'm such an idiot.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
Here.
Wait. Myeong Hee.
Hold on. Soo Chan?
What are you doing here?
I came to apply for a passport.
What about you?
I had something to do at the Medicines Agency...
and thought I'd visit my friend who works here.
You have a friend who works here?
Yes, at the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
You can find men's suits here on the first floor...
and women's dresses on the second floor.
Feel free to look around...
and let me know if you'd like to try something on.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm looking at clothes.
Go pick out a dress for yourself instead.
Don't tell me...
you think we're going to pick out clothes for each other.
Well, fine.
Go and ask Myeong Hee to persuade me again.
Who knows if I'll go along with it again?
Don't be ridiculous.
Why would I want to do that with you?
Then go on upstairs.
You're a jerk.
I'll come back tomorrow with my brother.
Okay, sure.
Congratulations on your engagement.
Did you find any jewelry you like?
So you joined hands with the dog of the military dictatorship?
You, Lee Soo Ryeon,
of all people?
I don't know what to say.
- But... - Forget it.
Did you rat on Won Seok?
I never did anything like that.
Do you expect us to believe you?
You were the only person who was in touch with him.
There you are.
I'm sorry to interrupt the people's court,
but we have more to prepare before our engagement.
Hey.
Can I take her away?
Who are you?
Me? I'm her fiance...
and the son of the Head of Anti-communist Investigation,
the puppy of the military dictatorship.
If you haven't found a job yet,
why not consider the Defense Security Command?
What?
It's just that I think you're really cut out for it.
You find a target, cook up a hypothesis,
and pretend it's a fact.
That's what my father does all the time.
What did you just say, punk?
There you go. I knew you'd grab me by the collar.
Come here.
What? What are you doing?
Pretend we're friends.
If it looks like we're fighting... You see the two cars over there?
You guys might get arrested.
Hey, let's go. Come on.
What? You're leaving?
Listen, fighters.
Come over on the weekend if you have time.
I'll prepare a really nice dinner!
Are we really being watched?
I don't know.
They want you to pick out your dress today.
The fitting takes time.
Come on.
What are the odds of us running into each other in Seoul?
At the Ministry of Foreign Affairs at that?
I know.
Without your help,
I would've had to forget about studying abroad.
Is that so? Then I shouldn't have helped.
Anyway, your passport will be ready soon.
Just apply for your visa in time.
I don't have any friends at the embassy.
Okay.
Squid, peanuts, and eggs!
Myeong Hee, would you like something to eat?
We won't arrive until well past lunchtime.
Let me get you something.
Hold on. Are you trying to humiliate me?
Come on. Forget it.
I mean it. It's my treat.
Seriously. Don't do this.
This isn't enough.
Buy me something more expensive sometime.
- Fine. - Here.
- Excuse me. - Yes, sir?
Can I get you something?
Let me see. Some bread,
butter cookies, soda...
Here's your soda.
- I'll take eggs too. - Sure.
Squid, peanuts, and eggs!
I shall peel an egg for Grandpa Myeong Hee.
What? "Grandpa Myeong Hee"?
Myeong Hee.
Thank you.
Squid, peanuts, and eggs!
No.
It says here that Y is a natural number.
X is greater than 36,
and Y is a natural number. So which quadrant is it?
The first quadrant.
Right, the first quadrant.
- Here. - Hold on.
Where is the third quadrant?
Jin A, didn't you learn this in middle school?
I don't know!
My brain isn't functioning...
as we've been doing this for three hours.
Sit up.
Come on.
At this rate, you can't go to Seoul during your school break.
You said you wanted to check out TBC.
I should've just gone to Seoul with Myeong Hee.
Seoul?
What's she doing in Seoul?
She went to the Capitol building to get her passport made.
I should've tagged along...
to see Gyeongbok Palace and check out Seoul.
Are you going somewhere?
Oh, I have to go to Seoul.
How will you solve functions when you don't even know quadrants?
Open your book.
Thank you for the ride.
You helped me out so much all day today.
Come on. Your place is on my way home anyway.
Thank you so much again. I'll be sure to return the favor.
Get home safely.
All right. Good night.
Myeong Hee.
If you have some time tomorrow,
can you help me with something?
Hee Tae, what are you doing here?
Did you go to Seoul earlier?
- Yes. - With Soo Chan?
How did you know?
You could've asked me to go with you.
How could I do that knowing you're getting engaged?
Why not?
All you had to do was ask me, but you didn't.
Look, this is...
All you had to do was ask.
You know that I'm waiting for you to say...
Exactly. So how can I, knowing that?
If we went to Seoul together, what about your engagement?
What will you say to your family as well as to Soo Ryeon's?
What do you expect me to do...
when there's nothing I can do?
Why do you say there's nothing you can do?
Do they have something on you?
Is someone threatening you?
- Hee Tae. - No, right?
You just don't want to be a bad person.
Do you think I'm not afraid of anything?
You probably think I don't even care what people think of me.
I'm trying to hold back every single moment.
Because it's you.
Because I believed you felt the same way about me.
We only have a month.
I don't even want to let a day pass by like this.
I thought you were holding back too.
But I guess you're...
I guess you're okay.
I'm done writing letters to someone who won't write me back.
Sorry. Did I wake you up?
What brings you by so late?
Well, here.
Can you give this to Soo Ryeon?
What is this?
You can give it to her yourself.
Well, I'm not invited to her engagement ceremony.
Plus...
She won't want to see me because it'll be awkward.
(Declaration for Democracy)
Soo Ryeon wrote it.
She worked so hard on it,
so she should see how it turned out.
Make sure she gets it.
Hey.
So? What can I help you with today?
I need to borrow your fine taste. Let's go.
We have many places to check out.
What about this? This will go with everything.
Myeong Hee, Myeong Hee.
What's your shoe size?
230mm. Why do you ask?
Oh, these happen to be 230mm.
Here. Try them on.
Why should I? We're here to buy your shoes.
Well, this is just...
Just try them on.
Come on.
Here.
How pretty.
Myeong Hee, Myeong Hee.
This one. This too.
And this one too. Go try them on.
Why do you keep doing this? Pick out things for yourself.
Goodness. Just go try them on.
Go on. We don't have time.
Hurry. Go.
- I'm really okay... - Go on!
- Watch out. - My gosh!
Oh, no!
What's going on?
- Goodness. - My gosh.
(Watch Repair)
My goodness.
Those punks.
Are you all right?
- Gosh. - Yes, I'm okay.
Goodness.
What's going on though?
Obviously,
they're trying to catch the kids who protested.
What a mess.
Goodness.
I see your daughter is having a lot of fun lately.
Keep a good eye on your daughter.
She's not a kid anymore.
I thought we came to pick out your clothes,
but these are all for me.
You're making me uncomfortable.
Just consider it as a gift for your help.
I'm choosing mine now.
I came to return a favor,
but I'm receiving more in return.
Come on, it's just a dress. There's no need to say that.
Myeong Hee, you're like a sister to Soo Ryeon.
It's natural for siblings to receive gifts...
when their sister or brother gets engaged.
How does this look?
It looks like a suit for a groom.
What about this? This will look good on you.
I like it. It's nice and neat.
Ma'am, can I try this on?
Oh, there's someone in the dressing room right now.
- Can you wait for a second? - Sure.
Hey, future brother-in-law!
Hello, Soo Chan.
Did you come to get your suit fitted?
Gosh, what a great choice.
You look like a prince.
Are you going to try that on?
Yes. I'll go try this on.
Okay.
Hey, look at this.
It's so tight that I can't even breathe...
Myeong Hee.
What are you doing here?
Oh, Soo Chan asked me to help him pick out a suit.
Gosh, that looks perfect on you.
I wonder what the groom thinks about it.
It looks nice.
It's as if it were her own dress.
I told you it would look good.
Soo Ryeon!
I never imagined seeing you in a dress.
Goodness, you both look amazing.
The perfect bride and groom.
Oh, my. You're both tall too.
You look like foreign actors.
Don't you think?
Yes, they do.
Hee Tae.
You look like you could be an actor.
No way.
You look great too.
Oh, this? Myeong Hee chose this for me.
By the way, where are you two headed?
I'll give you a ride.
It's okay. We can take a cab.
We need to drop by a few places.
- Hey, Soo Ryeon. - You do? I can give you a lift.
Do you have time later?
- It's okay. - Today?
Yes. I have something to give you.
I'm a bit busy today.
Myeong Hee.
Can we talk after the engagement ceremony?
Soo Ryeon.
Okay then.
We'll be off then. Drive safely.
Okay. I'll see you guys later.
Why is it pouring so suddenly? My goodness.
Is anyone home?
Who is it?
Hello.
Is Myeong Hee here by any chance?
May I ask who you are?
What are you doing here?
I'm asking what you're doing here.
Do you still do this kind of stuff?
Give it to me. It's not what you think.
Give it to me!
What are you...
You still haven't come to your senses...
even after what happened?
Why do you care?
Why do you care if I protest...
or set myself on fire?
Kim Myeong Hee!
I'm living just the way you want.
[VIU Ver] KBS E10 'Youth of May'
"The Engagement Ceremony"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Father.
Father, something's wrong with this place.
All the others were released. Why am I...
No matter what,
just say "yes".
Father, I really didn't do anything wrong.
How can I take the blame for something I didn't do?
Just say yes to everything.
Say that everything is your fault.
Father.
They've agreed to punish you...
by making you drop out of school.
So live gratefully from now on...
Don't even breathe too loudly.
Live quietly.
Father.
Just like you wanted,
I'm living quietly, saying yes to everything.
I gave up everything in my life.
What more do you want me to do?
What more do you want from me?
By the way, how is an engagement ceremony...
different from a wedding?
Don't they just...
promise to get married at an engagement ceremony?
I thought that's what you do at a wedding.
I think an engagement ceremony is like a preview of a wedding.
Anyway, only rich people seem to do it.
Right?
Whatever. Just go back to sleep.
Hey. Can you bring back some good food for us?
Yes, you should.
What? Are you out of your minds?
How can I possibly bring back food from the ceremony?
Hold on.
At least bring back some rice cakes in this bag.
Are you beggars? Don't be ridiculous.
Get him!
- Stop it! - Are you going to do it or not?
- Bring back some food! - Get off me!
Are you going to do it?
- Promise that you will! - Answer!
Are you okay?
You have a fever.
You should've taken the afternoon off.
I'm fine.
I'm getting off work soon anyway.
Thanks.
(From Assemblyman Han Seok Joong)
(Congratulations on Your Engagement, Hwang Hee Tae and Lee Soo Ryeon)
This way, please.
(From President Yoon Soon Young of Gyeongju Gas)
Make way please. This way, sir.
Hello.
Congratulations.
Couldn't your wife make it?
- She's helping out at the church. - I see.
Please.
Thank you.
There you are.
Myeong Hee.
Come on. Don't cry.
You'll ruin your makeup.
By the way...
Here.
I'm sorry.
I should've taken better care of it. It's all in pieces.
This is...
It's from Hye Gun.
He said you should see the result of your hard work.
The ceremony is starting soon. Please get ready.
See you out there.
It's starting!
The engagement ceremony...
of Hwang Hee Tae and Lee Soo Ryeon will begin shortly.
Please be seated.
Myeong Hee, sit here.
We're honored...
to have you all as our guests...
on this happy day.
We will now begin the engagement ceremony...
of Mr. Hwang Ki Nam's eldest son, Hwang Hee Tae,
and Mr. Lee Chang Geun's eldest daughter,
Lee Soo Ryeon.
First,
the parents of the couple will thank the guests.
Please give them a big hand.
Auntie.
Why are you...
(Congratulations)
Thank you all for coming.
Now,
- it's time to welcome the couple. - What was that?
Please give a warm round of applause...
for the soon-to-be bride and groom!
You want me to get engaged to Lee Soo Ryeon?
Yes.
Are you sure you'll be okay...
if I get engaged?
Yes.
Now, the soon-to-be bride and groom...
will bow to the guests to show their gratitude.
Sir, my son would like to thank you.
- Congratulations. - Thank you very much.
She's the daughter of Changhwa Industrial.
- I see. - Enjoy your meal, sir.
Come this way.
Hello.
Thank you for coming.
Do you like the food?
I love it. You should thank him.
I must be distracting you from your meal.
I shouldn't have made you sit next to me.
Don't...
Don't worry.
Do you want some more water?
- Excuse... - It's fine. I'll get it myself.
Go and talk to your guests.
Gosh, why am I doing this?
I'm sorry.
No. I shouldn't have popped up from behind.
Don't worry.
It's really fine.
Go and eat some more.
My, the groom is so good-looking.
She wouldn't need any wedding gifts!
I know.
Soo Ryeon is such a lucky girl.
He's handsome, and he's a doctor on top of that.
It's a mystery that he didn't get snatched up sooner, you know?
- It is a mystery indeed. - Right?
- He's so good-looking. - Come on. Hurry.
Oh, dear.
- What a fine young man. - I know. He's very handsome.
He really is.
Even the grasshoppers aren't helping me today.
I look forward to May every year.
On a May night, even if you sing badly,
the grasshoppers help you out.
The grasshoppers?
Whenever I think of you, Myeong Hee,
I can't help but sing.
Myeong Hee.
Do you want to go out with me just until the end of May?
Are you okay?
No.
I'm not okay.
I don't want this May...
to pass by without you.
(Youth of May)
Do you think you can beat me now that you're grown up?
What would you have done if your family had seen it?
Why are you so angry?
You can't say that when you ran away from your engagement ceremony.
Why did he drink so much?
I'm off today and tomorrow.
Then let's hang out the whole time.
What a coincidence.
I can't believe Hee Tae's brother is your roommate, Myeong Soo.
What is your relationship?
Joint management?
It's so the investors can put their worries to rest.
Call off the engagement.
Hwang Hee Tae is seeing someone.