VINCENZO
Goodness. Oh, my.
I've seen this somewhere before.
Why aren't they locked up?
They beat us up first!
I was just passing by
when they suddenly assaulted me.
Look here.
Do you see how they tore my dress?
Hey, this is sexual harassment.
-Yes, you.
-"Sexual harassment"?
This was a brand-new dress.
Had I been determined
to teach them a lesson,
I would've broken all of their bones.
Gosh.
-Hey!
-What are you looking at?
I'm sure you've never seen a monk
commit assault.
Gosh, that stupid monk.
I was just talking,
and he flew in and kicked me.
He flipped me over and hit me with a flag.
Where's that flag?
That one. That's a weapon!
Mr. Lee, you know me.
I'm dressed in white.
I wouldn't have worn this
if we were attacking them.
Come on, you know me.
-Be quiet!
-That's a load of bull!
-It was them!
-Be quiet!
He hit me right here.
What is it this time?
I'm their lawyer.
Me too.
Why would they hire two lawyers?
See?
This is how well-prepared we are legally.
They assaulted him first.
The others came to help him,
but they were assaulted too.
That's not true! They hit us first!
Kim Yeong-ho.
-Kim Yeong-ho--
-Coming!
Hey, why are you here?
Could you show the detectives
what you filmed?
Sure.
But what's with the tone of your voice?
Just go.
-What is this?
-Let's see.
-What's that?
-All right.
That's…
See? We have proof!
-See? Here's the proof.
-We have proof.
He filmed it.
-Wait!
-Hey.
That's me. I'm wearing the same clothing.
We did get what we wanted.
You're indeed a Mafia.
-Stop that.
-Ma…
Don't.
-I'm on cloud nine.
-We'd like more kimchi.
More kimchi, please.
-Kimchi.
-All right.
-That's right.
-And one more soju, please.
-Hold on. Stop.
-Me too.
-Hear me out.
-A cold one, please!
You all did well.
Especially Gi-seok here.
Unlike his appearance,
he could hold his own.
Could it be because you're my apprentice?
You held out well today.
I didn't tell you this before,
but I'm no average Joe.
Tell me about it.
We should've fought them
from the beginning.
Taking them down was a cakewalk.
That's how gangsters are.
They go around in groups
because they're weak, right?
Those bastards were no match for us.
-Exactly.
-Right?
Larry, you really hung in there well.
-That's right.
-You have my respect.
I didn't tell you this before,
but dancing and martial arts
go hand in hand.
I grew up tough in a slum
so I can take down
three or four of them at a time.
Oh, really?
I learned martial arts at a temple before,
so I'm not so bad either.
-I see.
-You're incredible.
I see.
If we're to talk about our pasts,
I have a lot to talk about.
-When I was younger…
-Yes.
I'll stop right there.
Come on.
-Hey, you little bastard.
-What?
Why weren't you at the academy?
Mr. Cassano told me to take a video.
What? He did?
-Mr. Cassano.
-Yes?
Thank you.
Thanks to you, we came to our senses
and stood our ground.
I don't understand.
He's right. Thanks to you,
we finally realized that Park Seok-do,
that bastard, is no match for us.
He's also stimulated me
to make better dishes.
In that sense, let's give him an applause.
-Yes!
-Applaud!
-Everyone, give him a round of applause!
-Applause!
-Vincenzo!
Vincenzo!
Park Seok-do may seem like a loser,
but you should never provoke
or assault him first.
-We got it.
-Don't you worry.
Gosh, we're not him.
You're right.
And feel free to ask for our help anytime.
If it's regarding you two,
I can always turn off my iron
and run over.
We should do the same.
Check this out. It got 200,000 views.
-What?
-Two hundred thousand?
Look at us!
Why do I look so ugly?
Why is my face so big?
Is this photoshopped?
It looks just fine.
He did a good job. It's like a movie.
-He's talented.
-It looks amazing.
I've never mixed soju and beer before.
-Here.
-Try it.
I finally realized why these people
remained here and stood their ground.
They were inspired by Vincenzo's strength
and excellent leadership.
That means Vincenzo isn't a Mafia.
He's Che Guevara.
Here.
Thank you for agreeing
to meet with us, sir.
Since we've come to this,
let's try to get along.
We'll set up a meeting with Chairman Jang
right away.
Right, Myung-hee.
About what I told you last time…
About my colleague, Chief Kim's scandal.
-Take care of that, will you?
-Well…
What? Don't you want to?
I generously agreed to your favor.
You should do that much for us.
You're right.
We'll take care of it immediately.
We will, so don't worry.
I believe she's already working on it.
Aren't you?
What should I ask first?
EPISODE 8
Why did you join the Mafia?
How do you become a Mafia lawyer?
How much does a Mafia lawyer make a year?
I have so many questions.
Don't ask me anything.
How could I not now that I know?
I already have over 80 questions to ask.
Fine. I'll answer two of them tonight.
First, how did you become their lawyer?
They're not any different.
It's just business.
Then do people really get killed
like they do in movies?
You have to pay the price
for your actions.
That's what the Mafia believes.
They're really no joke.
-Next question.
-Enough.
You've already asked two.
Then I'll ask the other 78 questions
next time.
The number may increase.
Go in.
Thank you so much for saving me
from ending up behind bars.
Make sure to pay me back.
You always have to return the favor
when dealing with the Mafia.
Okay. I'll pay you back
one way or another.
Good night.
MERCHANTS IN CRISIS
FIGHTS OFF HIRED THUGS
Darkness cannot defeat light.
1,2 MILLION VIEWS IN A DAY
WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?
There are still 13 of us left.
Come back again, and I will teach you
a lesson with this iron.
There's no occupation that caters
to people more than cooks do.
All I want to be is the light and salt
of the world for the people.
Sir, can you move back a bit?
You're too close.
My face shouldn't look so big.
You know that.
Let's cut that out and do it again.
Lastly, let's meet the monks.
We are monks who carry on
the patriotic spirit of Buddhism.
It is also our duty to fight against
those demons who are blinded by greed.
WE WILL FIGHT AGAINST
THE DEMONS WHO ARE BLINDED BY GREED
We've won over
the Namdongbu prosecution service.
Great job.
Not at all, sir.
We only did what was necessary.
It wasn't you. It was Vincenzo.
It was him, wasn't it?
Actually, we just received
the slightest bit of help.
Do you even know how he convinced him?
He sent the chief prosecutor's son,
who is a terrible soccer player,
to Italy's BC Milano.
It's obvious how
you former prosecutors handle things.
Seeing how you keep failing,
shouldn't you just quit by now?
Sir.
What?
Do you know why I'm still here
even after you've locked me in a car,
bashed it, and humiliated me?
-Ms. Choi.
-Stay still!
If I were to give up like this,
I'd die mortified from the shame.
If I quit, I'll end up hanging myself
in the mountains.
Like you,
I myself have never lost twice in a row.
I'll pay him back a hundredfold
and then quit with a sense of closure.
And what?
It's obvious how I handle things?
You're right. That's the only way
I handle things,
and I'm going to win no matter what
using this method!
Yes! This is it!
This is exactly what I wanted!
I don't need a lawyer.
I need someone who can be
the devil himself for me.
I can be a mean devil too, sir.
Use this devilish spirit of yours
to keep the Namdongbu prosecution service
under control.
As long as you support me,
I'll do my best.
You do know Babel was humiliated
and lost its funds
because of Geumga Plaza, right?
Yes, I saw it on TV this morning.
Think of a way to secure
our funding again.
Devil's spirit
I read over the compensation proposal
you sent us regarding
the victims of Babel Chemicals.
Do you think this is the lottery?
"Lottery"?
We were being pretty generous, right?
Even though Babel's chairman bowed
and apologized for that incident,
you're still asking for too much.
Then we'll file a criminal suit.
We were willing
to end this with compensations.
There is no way Babel will agree to this.
You can file your suit.
Wait.
Don't you think the chairman
will agree to this?
Is that what you think?
Why don't you just listen to him?
You become smarter day by day.
Then I'll review it
and discuss it with Babel.
Be honest with me here.
Do you have more cards against Babel?
There's no need to.
There's no point
in piercing more holes
into a sinking ship.
-Don't you think so?
-I agree.
You and Mr. Han can play the violin
on the deck of the sinking ship.
I regret having let you out of the cell
much too soon.
We'll wait and see
whether this will be the Titanic
or a nuclear submarine.
I have this one favorite Korean saying.
You told me about it.
-Oh, that?
-Yes.
-Looks like you need a good beating.
So you're saying,
there's no way to convince
the banks as of now?
No, sir. Not for now.
The banks are refusing
to negotiate with us.
Senior Managing Director,
Junior Managing Director,
and Director.
You've been directors
since my father was alive.
Why are you so incompetent?
What is it that you do?
I'm sorry, sir.
But this isn't our fault.
It's because of the lawsuit
with Babel Pharmaceuticals and Chemicals.
Not to mention the Babel Tower incident
a few days ago.
Things are getting worse--
You're all fired.
Stay out of my sight from now on.
Damn it.
Sir, the product you ordered has arrived.
It's next to you.
Did you take care of those bastards
who humiliated Babel E&C?
I'm cold.
Stop saying you're cold.
I think my blood vessels are frozen.
I'm in huge trouble. What should I do?
I just did what I was told to do.
I'm only an accountant.
Why am I here?
I told you not to come to the office.
Why did you have to come?
I had to report surtaxes.
Stop talking about surtaxes.
Gosh. Get closer.
Scoot over.
-Today's the due date.
-We're going to live.
I need to report it by today.
-Hey, are they dead?
-What?
Hey, wake up. Dong-sik, wake up! Dong-sik…
Dong-sik… I'm cold.
-Come closer.
-He's dead.
-No, he opened his eyes.
No, he's dead.
-I'm dying.
-Hey.
-Get closer. I feel warmer.
-Please save me.
SHINKWANG BANK MAIN BRANCH
PROSECUTOR CHOI MYUNG-HEE
Hello, Prosecutor Choi.
Goodness. I'm working for Wusang now.
Haven't you heard?
I forgot.
Congratulations on your fresh start.
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
Can we meet?
Sure, when?
We're her lawyers.
All that we can do now
is administer painkillers.
How long does she have?
It depends on her will to live,
but I'd say a few days.
If she has a family, you should tell them
as soon as possible.
We should request a stay of execution.
They'll grant it if we submit
her medical report.
Mr. Nam is looking into it,
but he hasn't found any family members.
Are you okay, Ms. Oh?
I'm Lawyer Hong Yu-chan's daughter,
Lawyer Hong Cha-young.
Hello.
I thought
I'd never see you again.
You should've told them
if it was this bad.
I didn't say anything
because it was bearable.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
We're going to request
a stay of execution.
Once they grant it,
you should get treated right away.
I have
no money to receive treatment.
I'll take care of that.
I don't want to be indebted to anyone.
Ms. Oh!
Just do as I say!
Are you serious?
You want me to invest in a heinous company
like the Babel Group?
That's rich coming from you,
don't you think so?
Hasn't your bank been known
for being heinous
since your father was the president?
Let me count how many cases
I've dealt with.
Gosh, there's way too many.
I'm not asking you
to actually invest in them.
Just pretend you are.
You'll receive a fake application form
from Babel
and Shinkwang will give them a fake loan.
It's simple.
If you give us a pass,
receiving loans from other banks
will be a cakewalk.
-Our bank is--
-I know.
Your bank is infamous
when it comes to loan assessments
and you have the best credit
in this line of business.
But…
isn't your safety more important
than your bank's reputation?
You do know
that I still have your case, right?
Would you like me to take it out
and bring it into the limelight?
I'm Jang Han-seo.
Hello, sir.
I hope this relationship
will benefit both of you.
-Why don't you have a seat?
-Sure.
How about a drink?
Ms. Hong.
Ms. Oh Gyeong-ja's stay of execution
has been granted.
I'm glad that it didn't take too long.
We should move her to another room.
Would you like to come?
You can take care of it.
I have somewhere to be.
Are you running away?
A new method?
-Without demolishing it?
-Yes.
We'll use iris recognition.
But Wang Shaolin is dead.
We can't get his iris.
I received information
that he owns a museum in Hangzhou.
And the relic storage room has
an iris recognition system.
Then his iris must be registered there.
Correct. Unless they deleted it,
it will still be there.
But how can we get the data?
There's this group of hackers in Shanghai.
I'm planning
to take them to Hangzhou myself.
I hope it all works out.
It will.
GEUMGA PLAZA
What is all this?
What? This?
They're…
They're for my hobby.
For my collection.
I'm a collector.
-You collect these things?
-How should I put it?
Don't you feel stronger
just looking at them?
You're right.
By the way, if you're ever interested
in learning self-defense,
let me know anytime.
I'll teach you a few moves.
Toto must be waiting for you.
Go on.
Wait.
What?
Why is he here?
Who is that?
He used to own the plaza
before Babel took over.
He looks familiar.
I think I've seen him before.
I've just arrived.
Come on, Mom. Stop grilling me.
I understand.
Okay. I'll make sure to say that.
Gosh, I'm busy as is.
Ma'am.
It's been a long time.
I heard they granted
your stay of execution.
Why are you here?
We were once like family.
I ought to visit.
Did the chairman tell you
to check on me and see when I'd die?
That's enough for you to spend
on yourself and pay for the funeral.
Don't waste your breath
on stupid ideas like a retrial.
What's going on here?
Who are you?
He's the son of Chairman Hwang Deok-bae
who died while sexually assaulting me.
Watch what you say.
You're President Hwang Min-seong
of Shinkwang Bank.
-Right?
-And who are you?
I'm Ms. Oh's lawyer.
I see.
Then you must be the daughter
of the crooked lawyer who died, right?
I'm warning you.
Don't provoke her
and cause a headache.
I think you're the one
who's causing a headache.
What?
Are you okay?
I have something to tell him.
Come here.
Come closer.
Closer.
-You scumbag!
-What are you doing?
You wretched son of a…
Damn you!
-You made me rot in prison.
-Let me go!
-How dare you visit me on my deathbed?
You shameless bastard!
-Let go!
-Ms. Oh, you shouldn't do this!
-Let go of me!
-Let go!
-Don't!
I'm going to let this pass.
but you better not do anything foolish.
Or I'll kill you all!
Shinkwang Bank's decision
to invest in Babel Group
will help the latter, who has been
labeled as an evil company,
get back on their feet.
Since Shinkwang Bank is known
to have high standards in investment,
this decision has caught
the attention of the financial world.
This is absurd.
I thought we finally destroyed them!
That bank refused to give us a loan
three times already.
I'm sure something fishy is going on.
Of course.
Everyone knows that Babel
is hanging on by a thread.
Had I known this,
I would've pulled out more of his hair.
What are you talking about?
President Hwang Min-seong
visited Ms. Oh at the hospital.
-What?
-Right.
He's the son of Chairman Hwang Deok-bae
of Shinkwang Finance.
They're the ones who framed her.
I see.
Why did he visit her?
He knew her stay of execution was granted,
so he threatened her
with an envelope full of money.
He told her not to request a retrial.
He must be no different from his father.
Like father, like son.
Gosh, those petty scumbags.
We have to stop this investment
at all costs.
Both the Babel Group and Shinkwang Bank.
We need to screw Shinkwang Bank over
big time for Ms. Oh's sake.
It was really hard sneaking this out.
The security is extremely tight
these days.
You're going to let me work
for that lawyer from Boston, right?
Of course.
If this pans out, I'll transfer you
to their law firm immediately.
Hurry up.
After that company dinner,
Ms. Choi keeps making me do impressions.
She won't let me be.
She'd call me drunk and tell me to do it.
She's so annoying.
What does she take you for? A comedian?
-Hey.
-Yes?
Can you do Lee Sun-kyun
from Parasite again?
I've missed it so much.
"This isn't a test,
so drive like you normally do.
-Where can I have some ribs?"
-Goodness.
"I'm craving some ribs.
One thing she was good at
was making delicious ribs."
You sound exactly like him!
Hello, Mr. Lee!
"I've been craving some."
PERSONAL INFORMATION
HWANG MIN-SEONG
That's personal information
on President Hwang Min-seong.
He's been sued for dating abuse
four times.
Dating abuse?
But they're all young men.
Right.
That's just his personal preference.
But what's important is that
dating abuse is a form of violence
no matter the victims' gender.
How did it happen?
He'd approach his fellow club members
to date them.
If they refused to do as he said,
he'd assault them.
One man even went blind.
His victims couldn't
go public with the incident
as they were afraid of being outed.
And he wasn't indicted
thanks to Wusang, right?
Yes. Choi Myung-hee
was the prosecutor in charge.
It must have been her and Seung-hyuk.
I see. So…
Ms. Choi used this against him
and made Shinkwang save Babel.
However…
this won't be enough
to stop their investment.
I know.
But there is a way to stop the investment
and bring down the president.
Is there another way?
We'll use an homme fatale.
A charismatic man who'll bring him down.
-I've looked into it.
-Okay.
President Hwang has an ideal type.
They need to have a pale face
and glistening eyes.
They should look young, handsome,
and naturally exude
intelligence.
And lastly--
Stop.
Don't you dare.
A soothing voice
and a composed manner of speech.
What are you looking at?
What are you implying?
I won't do it! I can't!
-Just think about it.
-Don't get mad.
Just think about it.
Don't be ridiculous. This is absurd.
Mr. Nam, block the door!
Get out. I said, get out.
I can't do it! This isn't right!
You'll just be acting.
And you're doing this for justice.
I don't care about justice.
I just can't do it.
You don't need to do anything.
He'll just fall for you. Right, Mr. Nam?
I just never told you this,
but, speaking as a man,
you are indeed attractive--
That's enough.
This will work for sure.
We should stop the investment
and avenge Ms. Oh.
Still, I can't.
I can't do this. I can't.
It's ridiculous.
I'll give you instructions
following you around
so that you won't be too flustered.
You can do it.
No. I can't do it!
This just isn't right.
Don't!
No, I can't do it!
SHINKWANG BANK
He's an elite who has studied abroad,
but he lacks social skills.
According to Ms. Oh,
he never trusts anyone
and spends most of his time alone.
He's also a hardcore mama's boy
and only listens to his mom, the current
chairwoman of Shinkwang Finance.
Right. He loves horseback riding.
He goes horseback riding once a week.
Nearsen.
Please, listen to me today, will you?
Please.
He must be a stubborn one.
-What's his name?
-Hwang Min-seong.
It's Nearsen.
I see. Nearsen.
He must be Nearco's descendant.
Is he related to Northern Dancer?
Correct.
It takes quite some time
to gain their trust.
They're highly distrustful,
so you need patience.
You're very knowledgeable.
There was a straw.
-May I ride him?
-Sure.
Be as rough as you want.
You startled me. What's wrong?
There was something on you.
He wants to drink tonight.
I don't think I can do it.
Just the thought of it makes me shudder.
That's because it's cold. Gosh, it's cold.
You might as well have a drink then.
It'll be easier to win his heart
once he's relaxed.
Forget about…
Forget about winning his heart.
I just can't do this.
You're the Mafia's lawyer.
You're strong and cool-headed.
You never let go of your target.
That's your charm, Vincenzo Cassano.
Forget it.
I can do it.
You can do it, Vincenzo Cassano.
You are so handsome.
It's dangerous to startle a horse
from behind.
It could kick you. Be careful.
Cheers.
Right.
There are a few things he's fond of,
one of which are one-syllable first names.
TAE HO
ATTORNEY
"Tae Ho"?
-You're a lawyer.
-Yes.
I'm running a small law firm called
"Only…
You."
Do you know how it feels
to meet a complete stranger
and feel like you've met your soulmate?
Yes. I actually…
feel the same way.
You seem older than me.
Brother.
Can I call you that?
No.
Just call me by my name.
Your name?
Okay.
Tae Ho.
I have a condition.
Let's not be business partners.
I want us to just be friends,
Mr. President.
Let's not talk about work.
It feels like
you can see right through me.
That's what I want as well.
-Would you like some?
-Sure.
Let me.
You know what?
I envy you.
How could you become the president
of the great Shinkwang Bank
at such a young age?
-Tae Ho.
-Yes?
Do you want to know how?
Yes.
When my father was the chairman
of Shinkwang Finance,
he was against me becoming
the president of the bank.
But he was a despicable womanizer.
Whether they be his employees
or housekeepers,
he'd be all over them. Gosh, that geezer.
Then one day,
he was sexually harassing
one of his housekeepers.
She said no and fought back, and…
She pushed him.
My mom was secretly watching it happen.
Through a chink in the door.
She was watching?
Yes.
But my dad couldn't get back up.
Do you know what's funnier?
She didn't even bother to call 911.
She let him die.
Would he have lived
had she called?
Yes.
The doctor said he could have operated
on him had he come ten minutes sooner.
Why did she
let him die?
My mom had always wanted
to lead Shinkwang Finance.
Her wish came true.
What happened to that housekeeper then?
She took the blame and went to jail
for murdering my dad.
Tae Ho.
Yes?
We couldn't let the world know the truth.
After all, my family has
a reputation to uphold, right?
Right.
Your family's reputation.
Min-seong.
Are you free this weekend?
Should we spend it together?
This weekend?
I'm totally free.
NANYAK TEMPLE
I don't think there's gold here.
People hide it
in the most unexpected places.
Knock on the wall.
I got mold on my hand.
I think it's right here.
It's either behind this wall,
or through that back door.
Let's check it out.
-Honey.
-Yes?
I think there could be bats in here.
Open it first.
-Honey, turn that off!
-Why?
Turn it off! Hide!
-Lock the door.
-Right.
-You scared me.
-What is this?
-Goodness. Hi.
-Goodness.
Goodness. Fancy seeing you here.
What brings you here?
Me?
I come here all the time.
What about you two?
We had a late-night snack,
-so we were exercising.
-Right.
Why would you exercise here?
Do it somewhere spacious.
-Right.
-Let's go.
Hey, isn't that what they use
at the airport to scan your body?
-A metal detector?
-No.
-It's a massager.
-It…
doesn't look like one.
It's the latest model.
It's an AI massager.
It emits anions
and also works as an antioxidant.
-Goodness.
-Gosh!
Toto.
-Oh, my God.
-What are you doing?
Well, the building is too dirty.
This is a special type of vacuum.
A vacuum?
Isn't that a metal detector?
No, it isn't.
It's the latest model.
These magnets attract all the metals
around them.
Toto, didn't you serve at the GOP
and look for mines in the DMZ?
No, you got it wrong.
I just played Minesweeper.
-Honey.
-Yes?
Should we go home
now that we're done working out?
-Should we?
-Goodbye, then.
-Goodbye.
I've been massaging myself quite a bit.
I feel more relaxed now. Good night, then.
-Good night.
-Get home safe.
I'm done cleaning as well.
Okay.
MUMU LAND
Hello.
I haven't been this happy in a while.
The weather's wonderful,
there's a cool breeze,
and you're here with me.
It's been ages
since I came to one of these places.
-Tae Ho?
-Yes?
Let's act like we're kids again
and have a blast.
Okay.
Didn't I tell you that he'd fall
head over heels for him?
But the two of them together look like
Beauty and the Beast.
-Tae ho?
-Yes?
Let's run!
Here we go!
Let's go, Spaceship Victory!
What is that?
Hello!
Hi!
-Thank you.
-Hello.
You guys seem so close.
People might think you're lovers!
Oh, come on!
Hello.
I'm so happy. I'm having a blast.
Me too.
Oh, no.
I'll hold onto you.
Let me hold you a little.
Hold on.
This is fun.
-It is, right?
-Yes.
What's wrong?
Tae Ho, there's one thing I'm scared of.
Zombies.
I watched a zombie movie
for the first time in seventh grade.
I was so traumatized that I had to see
a psychiatrist for a week.
Go away!
I'm sorry.
HAUNTED HOUSE
-Then let's go elsewhere.
-Did he leave?
Yes. Let's go.
Let me go. You can let go.
I haven't had such a blast in years.
Why do you look so down?
Did I do something to upset you?
No. I'll drive. Give me the keys.
What's wrong? Tell me.
It's nothing. Give me the keys.
We're not going anywhere
unless you tell me.
Go on.
I saw on the news
that your bank agreed to invest
in the Babel Group.
Yes, it's true. But what about it?
You know very well how evil they are,
so why would you do that?
You could get hurt because of this…
I'm sorry. I crossed the line.
I had no other choice.
Tae Ho. You don't have to apologize.
I really don't want you to get hurt.
I'm truly thankful
that you're worried about me.
I don't think I can see you anymore.
I broke our promise. I talked about work.
I'll leave.
No. No!
Tae Ho.
It's okay. You were just worried about me.
No. A promise is a promise.
Don't follow me
or visit my law firm!
-Tae Ho!
-Don't follow me!
Don't.
-Hong Cha-young, you…
-Tae Ho…
LAW FIRM ONLY YOU
ATTORNEY, TAE HO
OBNOXIOUS
I NEED YOU BACK IN MY LIFE, TAE HO
INCOMING CALL
OBNOXIOUS
IT'S RAINING BECAUSE OF YOU
MY HEART HAS FROZEN STILL
TAE HO, PLEASE THAW MY HEART
Let's eat!
Thank you.
We need some snacks
when watching something entertaining.
He's determined to wait until I see him.
-How long has he been out there?
-For about five hours.
You should give in now.
Maybe after two more hours.
You know how to play hard to get
like a true Mafia.
I guess love is to blame.
You're responsible for this.
And villains don't deserve to love.
Why not?
Not everyone deserves to love.
Those who harm or hurt others
don't deserve to love.
For them, love is nothing
but an accessory.
Then do you deserve to love?
Are you finally willing to see me, Tae Ho?
A bank president shouldn't be doing this.
I'm not here as a president,
but as a friend.
And I've made a decision.
Business-related advice?
I'm willing to hear them out.
Because I know
you sincerely care about me.
Thank you for understanding me.
Tae Ho, give me advice
regarding the signing ceremony.
I'll take everything you tell me
into consideration.
Min-seong.
-Yes?
-How about holding the ceremony
at an opera house?
It'll be very dramatic.
Tae Ho.
How do you always come up
with such great ideas?
Min-seong.
There's something else I really want.
Don't mess it up today.
Don't just sign the agreement.
Exude your charisma.
-Got that?
-Yes, sir.
Right.
I heard you fired
three directorate members
without my consent.
Well…
I was too enraged.
I fired them
because they were incompetent.
Well done.
I was going to fire them anyway.
But you see,
make sure you ask for my permission
next time.
You're giving me the impression
that you have a lot on your mind.
No, sir. There's not
a single thought in here.
That's why I got emotional.
Right?
Don't disappoint me.
Of course not, sir.
INVESTMENT AGREEMENT SIGNING CEREMONY
Here you go.
-Hi, Boss.
-Hi.
Did you get a haircut?
Yes.
-Let's go.
-Sure.
SHINKWANG BANK
Oh, my. This is grand.
It's nice.
Isn't that Hong Cha-young?
Who?
Hello.
What's she doing here?
Hey! Cha-young!
What are you doing there?
Cha-young, why are you here?
-Keep an eye on her.
-Why are you here?
She looks suspicious.
I'm here to witness the power of love.
"Love"?
I have a bad feeling about this.
What should I do with her?
He really is one of a kind.
He had his back turned for that.
You're dead meat.
We will now begin
the investment signing ceremony between
Shinkwang Bank and the Babel Group.
Chairman Jang Han-seo of the Babel Group
and President Hwang Min-seong
of Shinkwang Bank will sign the agreement.
BABEL GROUP
CHAIRMAN JANG HAN-SEO
SHINKWANG BANK
PRESIDENT HWANG MIN-SEONG
Show me how sincere you are
with your action.
Tae Ho.
I LOVE YOU
TAE HO BELIEVES IN YOU
INVESTMENT AGREEMENT
I won't sign this.
What?
My reason is simple.
Babel Group is immoral and unreliable.
What do you…
Bravo!
The power of love!
Damn it.
I'll be leaving now.
Thank you for coming.
-Don't go.
-Wait!
Who is that?
-Mom.
-You idiot.
How dare you ruin this?
Were you aware of this?
As the chairwoman,
I will sign the agreement myself.
Surprise!
Mom, let me take care of this.
Be quiet.
Stop disgracing our family name and leave.
Go on!
Damn it.
Your son has many weaknesses,
so he may fall into a trap.
Just to be safe,
I would like you to lead the ceremony.
Why should I listen to you?
Issues related to your son
and your deceased husband…
I have many stories to tell about them.
It's humorous to see a lowly wench
blabbering just because she studied law.
Then should this lowly wench
keep her stories to herself
or bring them out in the open?
Devil's spirit.
Why are you still here?
NOT BAD
"Not bad"? What an impudent jerk.
-What? Who are you?
-Be quiet.
Who are you? What are you doing?
Let me go! Let me go right now! No!
Goodness.
-Oh, no.
-Tae Ho!
Damn it!
Let go of me! Let go!
Do you want to die?
How dare you? Let me go right now!
What's going on?
-One, two, three.
Wait!
DRESSING ROOM
-Scream!
-Open up!
-Open the door!
-Raise your voice!
-Scream!
Please open the door.
Mister?
I'm scared.
Mister!
What's the most heartless way
to take revenge on someone?
Using what they fear the most.
It could be more painful
than death itself for some.
-Wait.
-This is difficult.
We'll be filming tomorrow.
You'll get fired
if you don't put more soul into it.
But zombies don't have souls
to begin with.
As extras, we won't even get paid
that much.
Why do you expect so much from us?
Sir, I think I truly know what acting is.
I feel electricity
flowing through my body.
-Really?
-Yes.
If it's that electrifying,
keep practicing.
Five, six. Look in the mirror.
Like this.
I have an even more electrifying offer.
Are you interested?
Excuse me.
Ma'am.
Ma'am?
Excuse me.
What?
I'm so pretty.
Tteokbokki.
-Hey, dig in.
-No!
Don't!
REHEARSING
DO NOT ENTER OR KNOCK! SILENCE!
Help me!
Good work. Let's go.
-They're Welsh corgis. Alkong and Dalkong.
-I see.
Hi, Alkong. You too, Dalkong.
-Thank you for everything, ma'am.
-My pleasure.
I hope we continue this friendship.
We should have a meal together.
Sure. I'll set a date soon.
You looked gorgeous today.
When I saw you enter,
I was totally mesmerized.
Thank you. I hope we get along.
We'll set a date for that meal.
He scared me.
What's wrong with him?
You darn brat! What are you doing?
That's your son.
-What's going on?
-Sir.
I'm scared. It was so scary.
Tae Ho?
Tae Ho…
Tae Ho.
I'm so scared.
-Move aside!
-I'm so scared.
I said, move aside.
Mr. Hwang Min-seong.
You're under arrest for assault
and blackmail.
-What? On what grounds?
-What?
We received a tip-off from a man
named Vincenzo Cassano.
"Vincenzo Casanova"?
What kind of name is that?
-Why aren't you taking him?
-What?
-Get over here!
-You can't do this, ma'am.
You can't arrest him.
He's done nothing wrong.
-Do you even know who I am?
-Vincenzo Cassano.
That's me.
-I said, let go.
-This is an obstruction of justice.
I believe I grabbed you by the hair
like this.
How dare you touch my son?
Please, stay still.
Tae Ho.
-This is wrong.
-How dare you cuff him?
Hurry up and take him!
Move aside!
Tae Ho!
Lawyer Choi!
Yes, ma'am.
I'll take care of it right away.
I'll go first. Take care of this
and bring him home!
Tae Ho!
-Don't worry about your son.
-Goodbye, ma'am.
What's going on?
There weren't enough reporters,
so I called some more.
Come here.
Who do you think you're messing with?
Sir. Calm down.
Sir.
You looked way smarter
when you were working out.
Why you little…
Sir. Calm down. Okay?
I should've known that something was up.
I guess you learned something
through your consecutive losses.
We were going easy on you
not to trample your hopes and dreams.
You should be grateful.
Aren't you being a bit too cocky
for winning this one round?
Next time you get an investment,
keep your wallet safe.
Because I'll be robbing you soon.
Be my guest. Before that happens,
I'll rip you all apart.
You should really watch out.
I've sharpened up my blade just for you.
Don't even bother
with that crusty old thing.
Just play the violin on the Titanic.
We've already escaped on a lifeboat.
Sad news for you.
Yes. The rich people
were the first to escape.
It might be better if you stayed on board.
There might be sharks.
Then it'll be Jaws, and not Titanic.
That's it.
Gosh, she's unbelievable.
Your father…
If you don't want to end up like him,
you should keep quiet and lie low.
Ms. Hong.
Reporters! Gather around!
I am…
the daughter of the late Hong Yu-chan,
a lawyer who died in vain
while fighting against Babel.
I'm Lawyer Hong Cha-young.
Jipuragi Law Firm will expose
every single corrupt deed
that the Babel Group has committed.
Including Babel's connection
with the prosecution.
Reporters, this small-scale law firm
is spreading false rumors
just to storm up some controversy.
-Whatever.
-Kim Seong-il from CBN here.
Could you elaborate
what you mean by "corrupt deeds"?
Do you mean they did something illegal?
Are you saying the Babel Group
and the prosecution have colluded?
-What kinds of deeds?
-Please elaborate.
Write to us if you have any questions.
If you ask any more questions,
I'll regard that as a form of assault.
Please make way. Let's go.
Mr. Han.
VINCENZO
SPECIAL THANKS TO KIM SUNG-CHEOL
AND LIM CHAE-MOO
Director Gil knows who it is.
They're bound to leave traces
even if they're invisible.
That's our chance.
Don't worry about me.
Who do you think gave the orders?
It's someone who was working alone.
I just have to promise
not to kill you, right?
I'll change things to the way it once was
starting today.
And I'll show them
what they're up against.
Surprise.
I won't make him pay for it.
I'll kill him right away when I find him.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs