VINCENZO
Ms. Hong.
Do you even want to win?
Definitely. Desperately.
Let's come up with a new witness.
We're already struggling as it is.
Where will we find a new one?
Me. Bring me in as a witness.
You?
To be a witness,
you must have direct ties to the case.
Just get me in the ring first.
If you do, I'll do the rest.
A while ago,
you promised to take my advice
if a situation demands it, right?
I did?
Yes, you did.
Now is the time.
Just do exactly what I tell you.
This is Vincenzo Cassano,
my surprise witness.
Vincenzo Cassano?
To be more exact,
he's a witness as well as an assailant.
What? An assailant?
That came out of nowhere.
He's the assailant that assaulted
employees of Babel Chemicals,
and the assault case is
relevant to this case.
You and I are the only ones
who know about the illegal activities
between Babel Chemicals
and Haemun Medical Center.
So you can get into the ring
as a surprise witness.
It won't work if the defendant
rejects your request.
Right. So we do need another plan.
Then, I must be a witness
that they cannot reject.
An assailant who has his hands on
a vital piece of evidence.
I'm so sick of those victims' families.
Tell me about it.
They should've accepted the deal.
Those goddamn bastards are trying
to get more money out of this.
Hey!
You're the head of
the New Materials Development.
You're the team leader and
the associate team leader, right?
Who are you?
You blamed the researchers
for their illnesses,
but BLSD was leaked because of
the poor sewage disposal system.
What are you talking about?
Are you a reporter?
Do you know that guy?
-No.
-Me, neither.
-I'm going to beat you up.
-You bastard.
Hey! Damn it.
He's an advisor to the plaintiff
and assaulted the employees.
I refuse to let him testify.
Babel Chemicals did not equip their lab
with the proper sewage disposal system
for the toxic agent, BLSD, to cut costs.
As a result, the researchers
were exposed to BLSD.
-Your Honor.
-However, the company
distorted the truth, blaming
the researchers' past health problems.
The court has not allowed you to testify.
And you weren't even sworn in.
What are you doing?
Your Honor.
I present to you this critical evidence.
What's that?
This cell phone belongs to the head
of the research team I assaulted.
The text messages saved here
clearly show that the company
covered up the incident
and threatened the victims.
-Gosh. What's that?
-Please, stop.
-What's that?
-Wait.
What is this?
Put your heads up.
-Freeze!
-Stop right now.
Did you call the police?
-Did you assault them?
-I did.
BABEL CHEMICALS
Goodness.
That almost gave me a heart attack.
My goodness.
After the commotion,
an employee of Babel Chemicals
picked up this cell phone.
When he went through it
to see whose phone it was,
he accidentally read the text messages.
And the employee gave us the phone
for public interest.
DEFENDANT
It's possible that he plotted this
with an accomplice
to illegally read the text messages.
We can ask the witness to elaborate.
WITNESS
PLAINTIFF
I'd like to submit the evidence.
Yes, sir. Stop them.
Well…
Your Honor.
-Please call an ambulance.
-Pardon?
When the trial is over,
I plan to beat the witness,
Director Gil Jong-moon, to a pulp.
Me?
If you make another threat,
you will be escorted out of my court.
Director Gil Jong-moon
gave the victims false information
about the cause of their sickness
when he was aware of the correlation
between BLSD and blood cancer.
Your Honor. The witness,
Vincenzo Cassano, is speaking
without any medical knowledge.
As a result, he is tarnishing
Director Gil's reputation severely.
Sustained.
I will only take opinions from experts
into consideration.
-Exactly.
-There she goes again.
That's why I call forth a medical expert
as my new surprise witness.
Another one?
A new surprise witness?
Witness, please come in.
-Honey.
-Is that your wife?
-Why…
-Hey.
Hey, there.
This is our expert witness.
She's Professor Kim Yeo-won, the director
of the Pediatric Cancer Center
at Sungwon University Hospital
and an expert in the field of leukemia.
Your Honor.
I'd like to reject this person
from speaking as a witness!
Our expert witness has
a very important piece of evidence
that can prove Director Gil
has committed perjury.
I will…
allow it.
Honey!
You may stay out during her testimony!
Why are you doing this, honey?
Honey! Hey, let go of me.
-Honey!
-This way, please.
Honey.
Witness, you may take the oath.
I swear.
Befriend the enemy of my enemy.
Our enemy, who is also a key witness,
is Director Gil Jong-moon.
Who could be his enemy?
His subordinates
or other doctors at the hospital?
It'll be hard to persuade them
since their job is at stake.
But he wouldn't have enemies
outside the hospital.
There is someone. The most intimate enemy
that you share secrets with.
The enemy he fears the most.
Gosh, isn't it obvious who that is?
Once you lose their heart,
you become their worst enemy.
Look into Gil Jong-moon's personal life.
Someone once said
that one should look at art and war
from a distance.
You'll appreciate the painting more
if you take a few steps back.
The colors held by Liberty represent
freedom, equality, and fraternity.
Delacroix used these colors
in three different places.
One is in Liberty's hand.
The colors show up again
in that man's red belt,
white undershirt, and blue shirt.
And lastly,
it's also at the top
of Notre Dame Cathedral.
And the dress she's wearing doesn't
look like a regular French dress, either.
That's a Greek dress.
That's why she also symbolizes Libertas,
the goddess of freedom in mythology.
She reminds me of you
in how you've pushed forward with
the Pediatric Cancer Center
against the board of directors.
Do you know me?
It's an honor to meet you.
I'm Lawyer Vincenzo Cassano.
DIRECTOR GIL'S SLUSH FUND RECORDS
PERSONAL TRANSACTIONS
I knew that he was having an affair
and was secretly preparing to divorce me.
But…
I didn't know
he had hidden this much money.
More than anything,
I am furious that
he downplayed your intelligence.
What do you want from me?
I want you to be our expert witness
and refute Director Gil's claims.
When all you did was expose his secrets,
isn't this too much?
No, it's not.
Because our law firm will take care
of your divorce suit,
and Director Gil will lose
all of his assets to you.
-I have one more condition.
-Please.
Do you like opera?
Opera gives me
the biggest comfort in my life.
Then, take me to see an opera.
Cheers to your beautiful
and alluring eyes.
This contains Director Gil Jong-moon's
personal correspondence
with Dr. Ramos of the UCLA Medical Center
regarding how to treat BLSD.
Here, he admits that improper
sewage disposal was what caused the leak
and identifies BLSD as the direct cause
of the blood cancer.
The emails clearly show he was
discussing the leak with Dr. Ramos.
Reading your spouse's emails
without consent
is a violation
of the telecommunications act.
Hence, this evidence
cannot be used in court.
She didn't read Director Gil's emails.
Dr. Ramos sent them to her.
-What?
-That's right.
Dr. Ramos is an old friend of mine.
He asked me about
what my husband had asked him.
And during this inquiry,
Dr. Ramos shared these emails with me.
What? Then why didn't you
talk to your husband about this?
I didn't want to hurt
my poor husband's pride.
If he had known it came from me,
his fragile ego would have been hurt.
In order to verify the witness' testimony
and to compare their medical opinions,
I will call the defendant's witness…
What's his name?
-Gil Jong-moon.
-I will call Gil Jong-moon to the stand.
So we can go over this one more time.
Honey!
Go to the witness stand.
Darling, what's wrong with you?
Right.
I almost forgot.
Here's a bonus from your "darling."
I found this in the corner
of my husband's desk drawer.
I thought this was salt
that you have with sundae.
It turned out it was methamphetamine.
He's a doctor.
How could he be so reckless?
I suspect the defendant's witness
is a habitual drug user.
I find it difficult to accept
his expert opinion.
That's not mine! It's not!
Then is this mine?
-You junkie.
-What?
Let's roll up his sleeve.
It has been brought
to the court's attention
that Director Gil might have injected
Lee U-yeong with methamphetamines.
Lee U-yeong is hospitalized now,
but once his innocence is proven,
his testimony as a witness
must be also admissible.
That's right.
Components that make up a drug may differ
depending on who has manufactured it.
Your Honor!
I am sure that the components
that make up the drug found in
Lee U-yeong's blood will be identical
to that of Director Gil's.
You in the gallery. Be quiet!
Okay.
How dare you do this to
your own husband? My goodness!
Fine. I get that you're smart.
But how dare you destroy
the head of a family
who is brilliant and levelheaded?
Witness!
You're not allowed to speak
unless it's relevant to the case.
Be quiet and go back to your seat.
What are you doing?
Go back to your hussy, you prick.
And you know what?
You're dirt poor now, you asshole.
Please, refrain from using profanity
in the sacred court of law.
I get that you are pissed at me,
but how dare you tarnish our family's
reputation in this sacred courtroom?
You're going down anyway.
Do you want some more?
What?
-Hey.
-Calm down.
Let go of me. You come here.
Stop fighting.
What was his name?
Vinsingzo.
I've seen him before.
I think it was about two weeks ago.
He came to me when I was working out.
He talked about some strange things
and left.
Then he probably figured out
how stupid you are.
What?
I didn't respond to him at all.
I sensed that something was off.
Forget it.
Hold a press conference tomorrow.
A press conference?
Admit to everything
and announce we'll get rid of BLSD.
Punish everyone who's involved,
and tell the victims
we'll compensate them.
And don't forget to bow respectfully.
Okay.
How is Babel Tower going?
I think the supervising department
is experiencing some hiccups.
Just shut up and demolish it.
We're not building it for our own good.
Don't you know
it's for the prosecutors, the judges,
politicians, and government officials?
I'll personally see to it
as soon as I get back to the company.
I get that you're a fake,
but you still must do your best.
Yes, sir.
Bye.
Damn it!
If Babel is smart, they'll want to settle.
I agree. They'll try to settle this,
so it doesn't turn into a criminal case.
What's your plan?
Of course, victims should be compensated.
I'll sue them in criminal court.
This could've taken 5 to 6 years,
but we finished it in 2 weeks.
Good work.
Gosh, there's no need for that between us.
Right. Do you need anything?
Do I need anything?
Yes. You played a huge role
in winning this case.
As the CEO, I want to reward you.
Anything I want?
Yes. You name it.
Okay.
I'll show you how it's done!
Do you know how much
Babel will lose today?
Seven hundred and sixty million dollars!
I'm already past 200km per hour.
Should we jump over there
-to see what happens?
-Please, don't.
Even if it's a Booralro suit,
you can't wear it all year round.
And more importantly,
it makes you look out of style.
So I've been making up for that
with my good looks.
So annoying.
So how many suits do you want?
We'll start with ten suits.
That many?
Let's leave now if you're not up for it.
No. Go ahead.
-Let's go.
-Get them.
By the way, you have such a great body.
I almost thought
I was measuring a mannequin.
Should I hold my breath for three seconds
like a real mannequin?
Then, can you hold your breath
for three seconds?
That would be an interesting experience.
I have some sample suits in your size.
-Would you like to try them on?
-Sure.
Okay.
Ms. Hong, what do you think?
Are you okay with a sample suit?
This is perfect for me. Thanks.
Here.
-What is it?
-Open it.
This is to celebrate our partnership.
I don't like the font,
-but I appreciate it.
-Such a smart-ass, aren't you?
You're so annoying. Just give it back.
Give it back. Give that to me.
Let's go.
We should get out of here.
-Wait.
-Stay in the car!
Stay here? Okay. I got it.
I…
Boss. Boss?
I will do my best, okay?
Calm down.
What's he doing? I mean, boss.
Hey. My gosh.
That crazy asshole.
Get out.
All right, I got it.
Okay. I got it.
Am I dreaming?
I never lost twice in a row
in my life. Never.
This isn't real.
What is this?
Well, I'm very sorry.
Never in a million years did I think
they'd go after
Director Gil's wife. Never.
I let my guard down
and failed to assess my enemy.
It's not that
you failed to assess your enemy.
It's that your method is old-fashioned.
You guys have no creativity.
-In Korean, it's--
-We know.
-Yes, you know.
-Yes.
We will start working creatively
from now on.
Are you kidding me?
Creativity is something you're born with,
just like Vincenzo Cassano!
Sir, do you know anything about Vincenzo?
Isn't he the perfect lawyer?
He's spotless
to the point of being invisible.
First, go after Hong Cha-young.
Take her for everything she has.
Money, her license, everything.
I'll take care of Vincenzo.
And I will also take care of
-buying the Namdongbu office.
-No, I'll do it.
-Are you serious?
-Give me a chance to redeem myself.
A chance
is reserved for only those who are worthy.
I will prove myself to be worthy
of that chance again.
You have three days.
Three days.
You want me to win
with this useless intel?
Tell me the truth. You assholes are trying
to destroy me, aren't you?
-I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
Will you say that at my funeral too?
I'm sorry.
All of you, stop whatever you are doing
and get me everything on Cha-young.
Including her call history,
everything she ate and drank,
whatever she printed,
and the snacks she ate at the lounge.
Get me everything. Got it?
-Yes, ma'am.
Don't stand there. Get out!
Hello, sir.
It's me.
Thank you so much for your help.
Thank you.
Our wishes and wisdom from Buddha
must have reached your hearts.
This is amazing.
There's no other way to describe this.
-You finished them in one blow.
-But I prepared all the files.
Okay. You love taking the credit.
This man defeated Goliath.
Now, I can't even guess
the things he's able to accomplish.
You should come have dinner.
I'd like to serve
the new dishes I developed to you two.
Maybe I'll offer you
a nice cup of coffee instead.
Let's have a meeting tomorrow.
What meeting, Mr. Cassano?
A meeting about the plaza.
I am sure you will be happy
to hear the news.
He said it's good news.
Why are you all so silent?
-That's great. Awesome.
-Yes. Nice.
-Tomorrow? Tomorrow is great.
-Yes.
-Good.
Let's meet at 11 a.m. tomorrow.
-At 11 a.m.
-I see.
-Around that time…
-Then…
Didn't we have an appointment?
-I think we did.
-Right.
-I'm sure we had plans at that time.
TEAM LEADER NA OF BABEL E&C
I did everything I could,
but I cannot stall this project anymore.
Make it happen.
I really can't.
The order came directly from the chairman.
If I don't demolish it in a week,
he'll fire me and take over the project.
-A week?
-Yes. A week.
Seven days. One week.
And, for your information,
I ended it with my mistress.
I'm devoted to my family now.
I've been going camping with an RV
with my wife every weekend.
And we make gambas by the bonfire.
We also play the guitar.
So what should I do?
Keep going camping with your wife.
If you cheat on her again,
you'll be dead for real.
-Gosh.
-Yes, Mr. Cho.
We went to Eurwangni last week.
Are you sure?
Yes.
He's a Korean-Japanese
architecture professor in Tokyo.
He said there might be a way to get into
the basement while minimizing the impact.
Does he know about the plaza's condition?
Of course. He's done it before
on buildings that are over 100 years old.
-And you can trust him?
-Yes.
I can vouch for him.
When will he be in Korea?
As this is urgent,
I asked him to come by tonight.
Great.
Good work. Bye.
What?
How dare you?
You think I'm a joke because
you have a few judges on your payroll?
That's a misunderstanding.
I know that I can't move you with money.
We are here because we would like to
help your future in politics.
What is it?
Will Babel help me become the president?
Gosh. As long as we have you,
anything is possible.
Shut your mouth.
Why would assholes like you
care about my future?
Babel is unbelievable.
Sir.
Our chairman truly respects you.
Hey!
I told you to shut up.
If you call me again
for something like this…
I don't care if it's Wusang or Babel.
I'll throw all of you in jail! Got it?
Don't forget that.
Sir.
Myung-hee, you should know your place.
You can't leave like this.
It was a bust, right?
Damn it.
BEAUTY SALON
FOR RENT OR SALE
Gosh, this is crazy.
No! Get away!
-Don't come near!
-I'm Yeong-ho!
It's me, Yeong-ho.
-No, you're not!
-I'm Yeong-ho.
-You're not him!
-What's wrong?
I'm Yeong-ho.
-My gosh.
-Yeong-ho?
Yes.
What's wrong with your face?
I started my own bizarre comedy channel.
What?
What are you talking about?
If you liked today's video, please
subscribe and press the like button.
And I'll be back with a better video
next week. Bye.
Why this, of all things?
I'm being productive. I even quit smoking.
Then you should focus on your studies!
I'm better suited for this than studying.
So let me be.
You get scared so easily.
This is so cool.
Coach Giuseppe Rossi of BC Milano,
a world-renowned Italian football team,
has started his four-day visit in Korea.
Coach Rossi who landed in Korea
this morning
watched the matches
between youth soccer teams in person
and announced that he's looking
for the next Son Heung-min.
According to a source from BC Milano,
they plan to scout promising players,
put them through
a one-month tryout in Milan,
and train the selected players.
This has grabbed the attention of
soccer fans worldwide
who are looking forward to
the discovery of the next Son Heung-min.
Yes, Mr. Cho.
The architecture professor
has arrived at the airport now.
Should we meet tomorrow?
No, let's meet now.
Mr. Cho.
Yes?
Why did you want to meet this late?
I wanted to see the moonlight
reflected on your heads.
Pardon?
I was joking.
I'm sorry.
Actually,
I wanted to ask you a few questions.
Come to our temple, then.
No!
I've become allergic
to basements recently,
so I can't even take the subway now.
-Let us talk here, then.
-Yes.
So what are your questions?
What should people who want
to be vegetarian be careful with?
And…
if you forget the words of the scriptures
while reciting them,
do you improvise?
Girls like guys who go to church,
but how come they don't fall for monks?
I wanted to ask these three questions.
What do you think?
My gosh. I didn't know it'd be this bad.
The workers did a shoddy job.
The beams and columns are the worst.
Then, is it impossible
to get into the basement?
I'm afraid so.
Drilling 30cm will be enough
to bring down the whole building.
All right. More.
-Drink some more.
-Yes, sir.
Gosh.
There's no need for that. We're brothers.
Okay.
Thank you.
Are you ready?
There will be a storm tomorrow.
Yes. I'm ready.
I'm as ready as I'll ever be.
It's just you and me now.
You got the company,
and I got the legal world, okay?
Yes.
I thought our old man was wrong,
but he was right.
Don't ever put your trust in anyone else
or give out compliments.
Yes, I don't trust anyone but you.
I won't listen to anyone but you.
Gosh, my little brother.
If you were just a tad bit smarter,
I would've adored you infinitely.
I have a question.
If I keep disappointing you,
will you do me in like you did with Dad?
What?
Like what you did to Dad that day.
This is what you told me
when I entered middle school.
"To become a successful businessman,
live a life that cannot end up
in a biography."
I'll do exactly that, Dad.
Die already.
Apologize to Mom when you…
You wouldn't be able to see Mom,
because you'll dive head-first into hell.
Come on in. He's gone.
You knew?
That I sent him away?
Yes. Of course, I knew.
You aren't that stupid after all.
You're quite smart, actually.
I'm so proud of you, Han-seo.
Gosh, I was so wrong about my brother.
Thank you
for acknowledging that.
By the way, Han-seo.
I don't like your eyes these days.
They remind me of Dad.
No, actually…
It's because I didn't get
much sleep lately.
It's just that my eyes are tired.
I was just joking, you fool.
You're his son.
Of course, you resemble him.
Here.
Eat it.
Eat it. Okay?
We've run out of options.
And the plaza will be demolished
in a week.
We don't have any other ways
to get into the basement.
But we can't keep throwing parties.
How about we demolish it at a random time?
Unless the police and the city office
are on our side, it's impossible.
I guess the only thing we can do now
is to stall for time.
Do you have any other ideas?
There's a card I can't help but play.
It's the most common method.
Gosh, it's burnt!.
TO NOT HAVE IS TO HAVE
4 DAYS AGO
By the way,
did you live abroad?
Why is your name Gilbert?
It's not actually a name. It's gilbeot,
Korean for "a friend on the road."
-My goodness.
-I see.
So it means, "a friend on the street"?
I thought you were from the US.
We gave you food. Now tell us.
You said you'd tell us
something important.
Right. There's gold inside this building.
A lot of it.
A lot of gold.
It's true.
-I saw it.
-What did you see?
What was left behind by the people
who moved the gold when they died.
What do you mean they died?
Was it three years ago?
I was hiding in a bar
to get some free food.
And the people
who moved gold into this plaza…
were drinking there.
And they said
that they moved
12 billion won's worth of gold bars
to this plaza.
-Good work.
-Good job.
Hello.
So, you're saying
that someone killed the workers
who moved the gold?
Yes. It was to keep it secret.
The person who hid the gold bars--
That's a load of crap.
What a load of bull.
Do you take us for fools?
I'm telling the truth.
Hey, do you think I'm a joke? Seriously.
-All right.
-My goodness.
Let me see.
This phone belonged to one of the workers
who died that night.
Gosh. Isn't that real gold behind him?
Right. What are they called?
They're gold bars, aren't they?
The gold bars are inside this building.
Fine. Let's say they are.
Where did they hide them then?
I didn't hear where.
If I knew, I would've gotten it myself.
Come on. Goodness.
Gosh, this is ridiculous.
Why are you taking him so seriously?
I mean, he even has the photo
of the gold bars. Look.
There are a lot of studios
that take photos like that.
Right. That makes no sense.
How can there be
12 billion won's worth of gold here?
I believe it's just a rumor.
Probably, right?
What a funny rumor that is.
You're quite a character, Gilbert.
I'm telling the truth. Damn it.
Next on the news.
Chairman Jang Han-seo of Babel
issued an apology
to the victims of Babel Chemicals,
promised to compensate them
and to immediately start working on
preventive measures starting today.
We were at the scene where he
issued his heart-felt apology.
This was what he said.
I would like to express
my deepest regret and apologies
to all those who are concerned.
The Babel Group
feels a great sense of responsibility
for the recent incidents.
-I would like to personally…
-He's an awful actor.
I agree. He should have taken
acting lessons.
He doesn't sound sincere at all.
That's not for the victims anyway.
It's to lighten the sentence
in case he's charged with anything.
My goodness. How embarrassing!
This post was just uploaded
to the anonymous forum for lawyers.
It's about Choi Myung-hee.
She tried to bribe Chief Prosecutor
Hwang Jin-tae and failed.
How can such a secretive story
spread this fast?
If you make a fool of yourself
in our industry,
you get burnt twice with these rumors.
She must've offered him a hefty sum,
but he didn't bite.
He's been on the Josam Group's payroll
for the last 20 years.
He has a lot of money
and has no interest in bribes.
He just wants to set up his own cartel
to move up the ladder.
It's 11 a.m. It's time
for our meeting with the tenants.
Right. Let's go.
I'm sure you've heard already.
Mr. Cassano is trying
to make good on his promise.
He'll purchase a building in Sangchi-dong
and will relocate you there.
That's right.
I will do my best to find a building
where you can
work as well as live.
That's great. Awesome.
Aren't you happy?
-Great.
-Sounds great.
Good.
Oh, my. I've never seen
such a peaceful crowd.
All you need are some doves flying around.
Are you the delivery man?
You come here daily.
If he was delivering something,
we'd at least be excited.
The same goes for your face!
Stop cutting me off and move. Come on.
I'm sorry.
The sight of him makes me lose my temper.
I heard that you are all moving
to a nice place. Where?
-Sangchi-dong.
-That's right.
How…
How did you know that?
Nothing gets past by me
in this neighborhood.
Well, I wish you all the best.
But before you go,
don't forget to sign the agreement.
But we're not moving out.
My gosh.
Why not?
You're not?
How should I put it?
This building is our home
and a resting place for us.
We must protect it.
This place is stained
with the sweat from our brows.
You know what?
This plaza is
like the heart of Geumga-dong.
It's a sacred place!
What's wrong with you?
Sangchi-dong is a much better place.
And that's not my turf,
so I promise I won't even go near there.
We're still not moving out!
We will fight to our deaths
to protect this place.
-What? Why?
-We'll never leave!
-What do you think happened?
-Why all of a sudden?
-We'll never leave here!
-You said you'd sign it!
-Come on. Hong-sik.
-Never!
Everyone!
Guys.
Until now,
we have been too weak.
It's time for us to join hands
and fight.
We are Geumga Plaza!
Geumga Plaza is what we are!
Let's fight!
Let's protect this place
with everything we've got!
Fight!
-We will fight.
-Fight!
-We will fight!
-Let's go!
-Fight!
-Geumga!
They've got to be kidding.
Why do they always end up chanting
and trying to fight us?
I really don't get it.
What else are they going to do? Sing?
Here comes the bird
Sing a song?
That was so lame.
-My pride is hurt.
-I'll kill him.
-Stop him.
-Sir, please.
Let go of me. Come on. Stop it.
I'm getting a call.
Yes, sir.
Really?
Then we can raid this place, right?
Why are they so fickle?
What's gotten into them?
They said they'd go!
Why are they doing this to me? Why?
-He's still handsome when he gets angry.
-Damn it!
Show me your angry face, Mr. Nam.
You should stick to smiling.
Ms. Hong Cha-young.
What is it now?
You're under arrest
for malpractice, embezzlement,
violating the attorney-at-law act,
making threats and forgery.
-Let's go.
-What?
She's not some professional criminal.
Those charges are ridiculous.
Step back.
Do you even have evidence?
She'll find out at the station.
Gosh, Choi Myung-hee.
She must've launched
one of her vendetta operations.
-You startled me.
-What was that?
You're very cooperative today.
Let's go. Come with us.
Aren't these colorful?
It's like the Olympic flag.
We have evidence
of your illegal activities
in these five flash drives.
People at Wusang are so diligent.
They worked so hard to fabricate evidence.
We object to the validity of the evidence.
Hey!
Object all you want.
These are irrefutable.
Hey. It's this one.
-Is that right?
-Yes.
Just in case
I end up taking the fall
for all of those charges…
Let me see.
I'll be released from prison
after three Olympic Games.
The flash drives in the Olympic
flag colors meant something.
This isn't the time for that.
This is way more serious than last time.
I can laugh because I know
you'll get me out of here.
It won't be easy.
Their evidence seems to be
impenetrable this time.
Then do something…
Mr. Mafia Lawyer.
Handle this matter
like a member of the Mafia.
Do it.
I'm not in the Mafia.
Enough with your act.
It's getting difficult playing dumb.
I mean, what I meant was…
How did you know?
You stabbed Jang's pillow with syringes,
burnt down their warehouse,
fired guns, and found out
confidential information.
How can an ordinary lawyer do all that?
Do you think I'm a fool?
You always brought up the Mafia
every chance you had.
So how could I not know?
Hurry.
In 48 hours, I will be transferred
to a detention center
and be in a prison uniform.
Okay. I'll handle it.
I'll do it my way.
Great. That's what I wanted to hear.
Don't come back
until you make this go away.
It's about Choi Myung-hee.
She tried to bribe Chief Prosecutor
Hwang Jin-tae and failed.
-I'm going all-in.
-Going all-in.
No more bets, please.
Player. Banker. Player. Banker.
Player's card
Banker's card.
The banker stays at seven.
Player, six. Banker wins.
Bet on the player.
I don't want to.
I will keep betting on the banker.
You're not good at games of chance.
People who are good at games of chance
are con artists.
No more bets, please.
Player. Banker. Player. Banker.
Player's card
Banker's card.
Banker, let's play.
Player, open.
Player, a natural line.
The player wins.
Damn it.
I wonder why you're here.
Right, Cha-young will be thrown in jail
in two days.
Don't you dare try to cut a deal with me
to get her out.
You've got nothing I want.
But I'm sure you do.
How about Chief Prosecutor Hwang Jin-tae?
I guess word travels fast.
I'll deal with him for you.
Release Ms. Hong.
This is a contract.
It states that you will release Ms. Hong
if I help you with Chief Prosecutor Hwang.
CONTRACT
Do you want a fountain pen?
Are you pulling my leg?
I guess I haven't made
enough of an impression on you yet.
Should we go and do some laundry?
Why? Don't you believe me?
I guess
you have no problem
trusting someone who tried to kill you.
Sometimes, trusting your enemy
can bring you luck.
Of course,
it's not an easy decision to make.
-That's it.
-Over here.
-Be faster when you pass.
-Go.
Go.
There you go.
Great. Keep going.
-Pass it.
-Pass.
-Goal!
-Good.That was great.
Put some distance there.
-Good.
-Pass it over.
Did you know?
Pardon?
Coach Giuseppe Rossi
of BC Milano is in Korea now.
Gosh. I know.
I also know that he visited
all the other youth teams except ours.
Goodness. This soccer club
can't do anything right.
Number 21 is your son, isn't he?
What? You know my son?
He's good.
He is, right?
Are you a family too?
I'm here because I need to talk to you,
Chief Prosecutor Hwang.
Who are you?
I'm an acquaintance of Choi Myung-hee.
You must be out of your mind.
How dare you come here?
Hey. Leave.
Just give me one minute.
I can't even give you a second.
If you accept Choi Myung-hee's offer,
I'll give you the thing you want the most.
What is it that I want the most?
Isn't it your dream
to send your son to the European league?
I can make that happen
within 24 hours.
What kind of crap is that?
Who the hell are you?
Wait.
Isn't that…
Sir, I didn't know that
Coach Rossi of BC Milano
was going to visit our club.
Number 21.
-Him?
-Me?
That's my son.
Vincenzo!
Giuseppe!
-How are you?
-Very good. Thanks.
Is this the guy? Number 21?
Yes.
He's the worst player here.
Yes, it's him.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
-I'm so jealous.
We're friends.
Yes!
SNAKE HWANG
ATTORNEY CHOI MYUNG-HEE
Hello, Chief Hwang.
About the discussion we had the other day…
Let's try that again.
Do you really mean it?
Yes.
Okay. I got it.
Thank you, sir.
How on earth did you do it? How?
Let's talk outside.
I hope we'll never see each other again.
I should be saying that to you.
Come on.
Let's go.
Come on. How did you do it?
I cut a deal with Choi Myung-hee.
What deal?
I got her to release you in exchange
for convincing Chief Prosecutor Hwang.
So…
you cut a deal with Choi Myung-hee
who I despise the most.
As if that wasn't enough, you gave
Chief Hwang to her on a silver platter?
Just to get me out?
I'm sorry.
I had no choice.
Good job.
Well done. That's what I'm talking about!
That's so Mafia-like.
You made an offer
she couldn't resist, right?
You really are Mr. Mafia Lawyer.
I knew you could do it.
Well done.
Be quiet and let's go. Come on.
Police officers, he's in the Mafia.
Isn't that fascinating?
It fascinates me, too.
I'm taking her to the hospital.
How is this possible in Korea?
-Honey, this is heavy.
-Okay.
-Take this for me.
-Here.
What's all that?
Oh, this? The protesters
at the next building used these.
We'll need these if we're going to fight.
It all comes down to
what you equip yourself with.
They make me want to fight even more.
My goodness. I see.
Gosh. You look beautiful.
You look like a goddess.
Goodness.
It's my birthday today,
so I gave myself a present.
I didn't know it was your birthday today.
It's all right.
Everyone, close your businesses early
and let's drink until we drop
at my snack bar.
-Are we having a party?
-I love it.
You look pretty.
-Hello.
-Stop it. That's enough.
Okay. This order is
from the team leader at Babel.
Only an elite group of us will go
without any machinery.
-Are the guys ready?
-Yes, sir.
-Okay, and
the protesters will be
wearing red jackets.
Only beat up the ones
wearing red jackets, okay?
-Yes, sir.
All right. If you have your tools ready,
let's go!
Excuse me.
I have to report surtaxes today.
I need receipts from your meal.
Do we really have to do that right now?
The deadline is tomorrow.
Give me the receipts.
Come on. She has to report surtaxes.
So just give her the receipts. Now.
Who has the receipt for jjolmyeon
from yesterday?
-That's it. Yes. That's it.
-This is it?
Who ordered extra rice?
WE OPPOSE DEMOLITION
FIGHT
Slow down.
We need to hurry. It's almost time.
Time for what?
-Park Seok-do will raid the plaza soon.
-What?
We should come up with a plan
before we just rush there.
Don't worry.
I'm the one who made Park Seok-do
raid the plaza.
I'll make Park Seok-do and his men
assault the tenants
and expose that to the public.
It will cause quite a scandal
on social media.
They'll have to postpone
once people start condemning them.
But the business owners may get hurt.
You're right.
That's why we can't hurt them.
Get me some sturdy men
and make them look like protesters.
Let them get beaten up a little.
They can retreat once we get the footage.
How will I know
if they can take a few punches?
Yeong-ho.
I want you to film something
and post it on social media right away.
No, I don't want to. I'm busy.
What do I need to film?
Order Park Seok-do to raid Geumga Plaza.
He's really dangerous.
What if someone gets hurt or dies?
They won't.
Have him attack
people wearing red jackets.
You are indeed in the Mafia.
Your plan is thorough and original.
Can you stop mentioning
that I'm in the Mafia?
But that's what you are.
Should I call you a yakuza instead?
Mafia
Yes.
The health center?
What?
I was in contact with a carrier?
Thank you.
I want to bury my face
In your chest
And cry today
-What's taking him so long?
-Sailing across
-Where are the drinks?
-The river of time
Hey!
Don't you work at the pasta place?
Yes.
-What is it?
-How dare you talk back?
Hey, it's a red jacket!
-Hey, he's wearing red!
-Hello.
-What? Get him!
-Hey! Get him!
In our dreams
-That's it. Go.
-Let's go!
-How long
-How long?
Must I wait
To see you?
Mom!
Mom, come on!
You brat. How dare you interrupt
your mom when she's singing?
You know those thugs that come here?
They are beating up Mr. An.
-What?
-Damn it.
Those assholes have
really asked for it now.
There will be blood!
They brought this upon themselves.
I'll kill them all.
-Let's go.
-Let's do this!
-Wait.
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
-Let's teach them a lesson!
-Let's go get them.
-Let's go.
-Are you wearing shoes?
-Go!
Are you wearing shoes?
-Let's go!
-We'll get them!
What's this?
Are they fighting?
Mr. Cho.
Yes. It's going very smoothly.
What?
No. That can't be.
One of the people I hired
came in contact with an infected person.
They were afraid they might
end up infecting the others
so they all went to get tested.
Then who are these people fighting here?
My goodness. Oh, my.
I've seen this somewhere before.
VINCENZO
SPECIAL THANKS TO CHA SOON-BAE
AND KIM BYUNG-JI
We have to stop this investment
at all costs.
You do know
that I still have your case, right?
Don't waste your breath.
Is there another way?
There is a way to stop the investment
and bring down the president.
And villains don't deserve to love.
Not everyone deserves to love.
I need someone who can be
the devil himself for me.
This is it! This is exactly what I wanted!
Looks like I'll have to
break the promise I made
that I wouldn't hurt anyone.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs