THIS IS BASED ON THE TALE OF ON DAL
IN CHRONICLES OF THE THREE STATES.
CHARACTERS, INCIDENTS, AND DATES
DO NOT MATCH HISTORICAL FACTS.
Do you know what happens...
when you drink poison hemlock?
Your body turns to stone,
but your mind remains clear.
In other words,
I am telling you to watch...
as I carve up your son, alive,
piece by piece.
EPISODE 14
What are you doing here?
I was told to leave the shrine
for fear of bringing evil.
Step aside.
He commanded that no one be allowed in.
Move!
Princess!
Do you remember me?
Over ten years ago,
for you and for Goguryeo, right here,
I used to help serve the rites.
One word from you and I
lost my wife and child,
and I became a spirit that wanders the world.
Each time I inhale and exhale,
I suffer from a gut-wrenching pain.
You have no idea that my
life is endless torture.
To make you feel just one-hundredth
of the pain I went through,
I took in your daughter...
and raised her to be an assassin.
She failed to kill you at the ceremony,
but I will show you today.
The pain of...
losing a family member in front of your eyes.
Ga Jin. You have changed beyond
recognition in the meantime.
You are a monster.
Have you forgotten already?
- I am your chief.
- Shut your mouth!
Escort the King out!
Bring death to that man, Pyeongwon.
Ga Jin.
Everyone is safe.
It is all over.
Is the King safe?
His physician gave him an
antidote for the poison.
And the Crown Prince?
Fortunately, he is well.
The Princess and her husband went to see him.
How did this happen?
I deserve death for this.
He lived with the goal of getting revenge.
He created Cheonjubang...
and manipulated my memory...
to make me a killer.
It was all to get to my father.
I almost lost my brother too.
I never imagined he would enter
the palace as a fortune-teller.
He is a good trickster.
Calm down.
Everyone is safe.
It is not over yet.
What do you mean it is not over?
I am sorry, Dal.
Go to Ghost Valley on your own.
- Ga Jin.
- Who is behind Du Jung Seo,
and who threatened my
father. I must find out.
Okay. Do that with me.
You have a lot to do with the chief.
The sooner your tribe
settles in Pyeongyang Castle,
the more you can help me.
Please, Dal.
My wife has no time for rest.
Enemies abound in your vicinity.
If you give a woman that look,
you are bound to give the wrong impression.
You can misunderstand all you want.
I will willingly put up with any ridicule.
The sun is rising already.
Does love wither away because
the sun shines brighter?
I do not want to let you go.
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
What happened last night.
Do not think of it.
If I can help you in any way, just ask.
I will ask for help if I need it.
Are you talking about work?
Love shared over one night...
will be forgotten in time.
Helping each other...
is more important than our feelings.
As it was until now.
I cannot do that now.
That might have been so until now.
But Lady Hae, from now on,
you are closer to me...
than any woman.
I need to go.
Okay.
General.
What is it?
Gochuga hurriedly went to the palace.
At this hour?
What happened?
There was an unfortunate incident.
An unfortunate incident?
As soon as the King woke,
he summoned me and Royal Consort Hyeon.
He will question me about
admitting the fortune-teller.
What should I do?
If he punishes you, accept the punishment.
How could you say that?
If I am thrown out of the palace,
what will happen to Geon Mu?
Geon Mu.
Yes.
I cannot let my son live without a mother.
So...
tell me what to do to survive.
If word were to get out,
it will damage our reputation. So...
I summoned you in secret.
I know nothing.
I heard of a skilled fortune-teller...
and requested an impregnation ceremony.
I did not know who he was.
He saved you when you were
bedridden from sickness.
Why would I suspect him?
I was deceived also.
Do not deny your involvement.
The Crown Prince almost died.
Please excuse us.
Your Majesty...
Sit down.
You saved Goguryeo from Northern Zhou,
and this time you saved
me and the Crown Prince.
You flatter me.
Your husband. Did he not come with you?
He left with the Sunno Tribe
people to take care of things.
She invited a fortune-teller in
for an impregnation ceremony.
The Royal Consort had no ill will,
so you can show her mercy on this issue.
However,
it is different for you, Your Highness.
Are you saying I had ill will?
He asked to see the King
and Crown Prince in private.
Did you not suspect anything at all?
He said any other company
would jinx the ceremony.
"I did not know. I was deceived."
Do you try to avoid punishment with excuses?
As Queen,
you cannot avoid responsibility
for what happened.
I understand.
If I must be penalized for not knowing,
you should punish the Princess also.
Leave us.
You brandished a sword to
take your father's life.
At the bid of the very same man,
did you not try to go
against all earthy morals?
Who are you?
Just because you had no memory...
does not excuse you for...
what you did at the ceremony.
If you wish to punish me,
punish the Princess also.
I had no choice.
As did I.
I was duped, just like you.
Then we should inform the subjects
and have them decide who is worse.
That is a good idea.
Shut your mouths.
If word of the past ceremony...
or this incident were to get out,
it would do us no good.
- Father.
- Queen.
And Princess.
Do not bring up the past again.
How did you find out?
About what?
What happened at the ceremony.
Who told you about it?
In the palace,
even the walls have ears.
If you live here,
you will get used to it.
By the way,
your husband does not know
proper palace etiquette.
Instead of getting involved
in what does not concern you,
you should teach him that first.
Who are you?
Tell me who you are.
They knocked out the guards...
and took him before anyone noticed.
How could someone escape within the Capital?
Did you find out who they were?
Is it not obvious?
The killers got involved...
to save their chief.
Arrest them quickly.
Yes, sir.
I have men searching the Capital.
Do not...
try to bring him in alive.
As soon as he is found,
have him beheaded.
I will do as you command.
Your Majesty. About who
brought him into the Palace...
As of this day,
no one is to speak of him or that incident.
Whoever says so much as a word...
will be punished severely.
Dal...
What is it?
It is nothing.
Who is there?
I said it is nothing.
You got me!
You startled me.
How have you been?
You are as light as a feather.
Why are you home without notice?
I came because I missed you.
I am here to see you.
This is a welcome surprise.
It has been a long time.
I heard you came to Pyeongsa Plain...
but turned back with your men.
The battle was already ending.
I had no business there.
You and your husband gained victory.
That is enough for me.
Right. I will soon arrest
the man that got away.
Goodbye.
Master Go.
I heard that my father trusts you.
I do my duty.
You also trained the Crown Prince.
Thank you.
You flatter me.
Why are you so stubborn?
Ga Jin and I are leaving,
and so are the chief and most
of the Ghost Valley people.
How can you remain here alone?
I will not be alone. I will live with Weol.
She is saying she will
stay only because of you.
We will not live in a thatched hut.
We will live in a huge tiled house...
I will not listen to any more.
Just the thought of the
clustered city suffocates me.
I do not wish for riches or honor at my age.
If you insist on staying here,
would Ga Jin and I be able to rest?
Do I have to suffer just so
that you two do not feel bad?
Forget it.
I am not interested in
feasts and silk sheets.
I am better off with simple
meals and cotton sheets.
- Mother.
- What?
General Dal.
Do as she says.
I will think of her as my own
mother and take good care of her.
Goodness.
Gosh, be careful.
Should we load that chest
over there onto the cart too?
That is for those moving
to Pyeongyang to decide.
Be careful.
Yes.
Why are you not helping out?
We are leaving first thing in the morning.
I sprained my back.
That is too bad. Is it serious?
I will be fine after
sleeping on a heated floor.
You are in a rush. Do not mind me.
This is not good.
There will be much housework to
do once we arrive in Pyeongyang.
What shall we do if you sprained your back?
Housework?
The entire Sunno Tribe
will be living together.
Who else will be up to
the task if not for you?
Do you mean...
I am coming with you?
Do not make me repeat myself.
My goodness. Chief!
My dear. Come on.
Pack up your things.
Why are you not packing up?
Chief.
I am not sure if I should
follow you to Pyeongyang.
What are you talking about?
The Princess's stepfather
should, of course, come.
I am destined to shave salt
in Ghost Valley all my life.
None of us belong in Pyeongyang.
But without Dal,
we would have continued to
wander around aimlessly.
We are only coming with him to repay him.
We are almost done loading the carts.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
The Princess will need you there.
Deuk, we all are just as worried as you.
But it does not matter whether you
are in Ghost Valley or Pyeongyang.
After some getting used to,
you will feel at home.
I know that. I do understand all of that.
But it just does not feel right.
Why are you taking it out on me?
- I am sorry.
- Stop it.
Let it go.
Shall we get going?
Fine, let us go.
- Are you coming?
- I am.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, let us go!
So you are coming!
Do not be like that.
I am not coming.
I mean it.
Why are you two fighting?
Should you not be busy packing up?
I am telling her to come with
us, but she will not listen.
Where would I be going with
San buried in the field?
Fine, stay then.
I do not care.
If you are going to say the same thing,
I do not want to hear it.
I do not want to move to Pyeongyang either.
It is unfamiliar...
and somehow suffocating.
Still, I could not leave Ga Jin there alone.
She is surrounded by evil people everywhere.
Your chief got caught recently.
While trying to harm the King.
And the man he was with...
died by my sword.
It is not your fault.
He would have...
even covered himself in oil
and jumped into the fire...
if the chief had told him to.
That is exactly what Ga Jin said.
With San gone and you far away,
Ga Jin will have no one to turn to.
You will be there for her.
That is different.
She needs her friend as well as her husband.
So?
You must see but not look,
and hear but not listen...
for your family to be at peace.
What happened at the ceremony.
Who told you about it?
In the palace, even the walls have ears.
I assume that he has not been found yet.
He must either have run far away...
or hidden himself somewhere.
Or maybe...
someone is harboring him.
Either way, I will find him as soon as I can.
Of course.
By the way,
have you heard?
General Yeon of the Jeollo Tribe...
is returning to the Five Tribe Council.
It is said to have been the
Princess's desperate request.
Dealing with barbarians all her life,
she must have gotten bored.
He is a close relative of the late Queen.
He is a relative to the Princess.
What are you trying to say?
The Sunno Tribe and Jeollo Tribe.
The two vacancies...
at the Five Tribe Council have been filled.
It is obvious...
that they will side with His
Majesty and obey the Princess.
They are nothing to be afraid of.
At the center of all this is the Princess.
Are you lecturing me on politics?
I am just concerned.
Before they settle in and gain a foothold,
we must nip them in the bud.
I have told you this before.
Did you already forget?
Violence without a cause
is a house built on sand.
It is that lax attitude of yours...
HOUSE ON SAND: SOMETHING WITHOUT
A STRONG BASE AND LIKELY TO FAIL
that got you in this situation.
Watch your mouth.
I must say this.
Do not underestimate the Princess.
The son of General On Hyeop
may cause trouble as well.
- Leave.
- Let me take care of it.
I will take charge.
I said, leave!
Sure.
This medicine will boost your energy.
Take it twice a day.
What you wish for is my wish as well.
Everything will go as planned.
Do not worry too much.
Do not get too close to Go Geon.
Father, what are you talking about?
I have eyes to see...
and ears to hear.
Did you think I did not know...
you were getting close to him?
The Princess and the Gyeru
Tribe are in fierce conflict.
If you get involved with
General Go at times like this,
you may get hurt...
or put the entire Sono Tribe in danger.
If that is the reason,
I will not keep a distance from him.
Mo Yong.
He cares for me sincerely.
I also accepted him without calculating.
I will never cause trouble for our family.
Please do not say anything more.
Father.
You are forbidden to go
out for the time being.
Gosh.
Chief!
- The Princess is here!
- Gosh.
- What? The Princess?
- She is here.
Goodness.
You are here.
The journey here must have been tough.
Tough? No.
My son-in-law took good care of
me. I was comfortable on a wagon.
Thank you for taking care
of him. What about Mother?
Her stubbornness has won.
I will go see her later and
make sure I bring her here.
She is a stubborn old lady
who loves crossing people.
Why would you want to bring
such a lady? Forget it.
Do not just stand here.
Everyone, let us go back to work.
- Okay.
Thank you for your hard work, Lord Sa.
Thank you.
The exclusive rights to sell salt?
Right now, the Five Tribes have exclusivity.
Originally, it belonged to the royal family.
Of course.
That jerk, Go Won Pyo, stole everything.
We must take it back even
if it has been too long.
Moreover, it was a wish of my late mother.
Chief, Ga Jin has been
planning this for a long time.
I mean, please help us, Lord Sa.
There will be a huge backlash.
Even so, what could they do?
The King has given his order. And
the Sunno Tribe will agree to it.
The Jeollo Tribe will join our cause soon.
The first thing we must do is...
to check the size of the salt ponds
and the yield of salt accurately.
Can you guys find that out?
Father, I would like your help too.
Say no more.
It is not just a task for the empire...
but a favor for my daughter.
Do not worry, My Princess.
Please do not worry.
When I used to work as a peddler,
I visited every nook and
corner of this empire.
- She does not need to hear that.
- You should talk less.
Thank you.
You have a visitor from the palace.
Our attendance is required at the palace.
- We have to go to the palace?
- The palace?
Obey the King and accept
your official position.
General On Dal, the King has
assigned you with Eighth Rank.
Moreover, the King has appointed
you the Head of Capital Defense.
Do your best to achieve
peace within the capital.
I will.
Accept your duties wholeheartedly
as General On Hyeop had done.
I will do my best, unto death.
Next. Generals from the
Sunno Tribe, come forward.
So tell me. How tall was
the general of our enemy?
Here.
He was about the same
height as me. Oh, right.
But his ax was something else.
Whenever he swung it, I could
feel the breeze from it.
Do not kid with me.
My son-in-law turns out to be a jokester.
Gosh. I am not joking, Sire.
- All right. Pour me a drink.
- Okay.
He shows no class.
All right.
Take it back.
That is way too greasy for my father.
Right.
- All right. Let us drink.
- Okay.
Their get-together must be running long.
It is his first time having
drinks with his son-in-law.
The evening is too early for
it to end. Do you not agree?
General On has a low tolerance
for alcohol. So it will end soon.
What good will come from getting drunk?
Gosh, men.
Escort the Prince to his chambers.
Yes, Your Highness.
Is he going to sleep now?
Once you are done with the
refreshments, you may leave.
She is such a snob. She must
think she is better than everyone.
She is the one who brought such
a dangerous man to the shrine!
Please do not speak of that again.
See? The King has let it slide again.
This is why I must give birth to a prince.
Or I must write him love letters diligently.
Love letters?
Gosh. How beautiful.
You did not even knock first.
Is that for the King?
Do not ask me such a question.
Gosh, this is beautiful.
You put this beautiful flower
on the love letter, right?
Should I write one too?
I tried to write one as well.
But I am not good with words.
So she wrote a love letter?
Yes. Why do you ask?
Gosh, the robe was suffocating.
It really was.
Dal, drink this.
That hits the spot.
Leave us be.
Come here, my wife.
You must be drunk.
Where are you going?
Go to sleep first. I need
time to think about something.
- About what?
- Go to sleep already.
By myself?
You are acting like a baby. Just go to sleep.
- Ga Jin.
- Yes?
It is nothing.
I am going to sleep now.
What are you doing?
You have greatly angered...
Lord Kim Cha Seung.
- Tie her up.
- Yes.
JANGBAEK
Are you serious?
She just disappeared without a trace!
What do you mean you know nothing about this?
We are searching inside
and outside the store,
- but we have not found her yet.
- Did she say...
she was going somewhere?
No, I have not heard anything.
- Oh, no.
- Lord Hae.
Send a message to General Go.
- What are you doing? Do it now!
- Yes, my lord.
What on earth happened?
What do you mean she disappeared?
If this incident was caused
by affection between you two,
this is enough.
I will not tell your father about this.
What are you talking about?
Do not tell me you did not know about this.
I am sure someone has kidnapped her.
We must find her first.
Oh, no. She...
What did you do with Lady Hae?
I am sure your subordinates are behind this.
Never.
However, she does have
enemies all around her.
She only has herself to blame.
I kept you alive to give you
one last chance to survive.
If I find out that you were involved in this,
I will tear you to pieces.
- Keep him locked up.
- As you wish.
One last chance?
What do you mean, Your Highness?
You think Gochuga and the
Queen are having an affair?
I still remember clearly how I ran into him.
I remember the face Go Won Pyo
put on when he threatened me.
If they kept their inappropriate
relationship until now...
Please do not say that.
What if someone hears us?
Why are you so startled?
I only asked if you knew something.
I do not know anything, and
I have not heard anything.
Nanny, how do I look?
Today is my first day of work.
I see.
What happened?
It is nothing.
You are not telling me again.
Ever since we came here, you
have been keeping things from me.
When we were in Ghost Valley,
we told each other everything.
Dal.
Anyway, I wonder how Weol is
doing with Mother's nagging.
- Weol.
- Yes?
What on earth are you doing?
I am only blind. It is not
like I do not have hands.
My goodness.
Just get used to being
comfortable, and have your meal.
If I wanted to be comfortable,
I would have gone to Pyeongyang with my son.
I would not have made you serve me.
You must be sad now that
Dal is not here anymore.
No matter how cozy the nest
is, if their wings get too big,
they should find another tree and fly away.
That is the way of the world.
And you, Weol.
Do not behave like this, as if you
are walking on eggshells around me.
I did not take you in to make you my servant.
I am not going to live as your servant.
I will run away if you make me.
My goodness. Where would you go?
Are you going to fly away
to Baekje or something?
Wait. I did not mean that.
I am fine. Let us have our meal.
- Put it on my spoon one last time.
- Sure.
This will be the last time, okay?
- Go ahead and have your meal.
- Okay.
What is this?
Get on. It is the horse for
the Head of Capital Defense.
I prepared it for you.
Forget it. I do not need a horse.
It is better for me to walk to
look around the capital carefully.
Get rid of it.
Troops, march.
- Just let me go in.
- I cannot do that.
- Why do you not understand me?
- You cannot go in.
- Pil Gu.
- You are here right on time.
What is happening, Father?
We lost the pass to enter the capital.
We have an important
message for the Princess,
but they are just treating
us like a bunch of beggars.
Maybe we smell like salt
because we have been...
checking the salt ponds.
He is the Princess' step-father,
and they belong to the Sunno Tribe.
We cannot let a man without
a pass in the capital...
just with a few words.
- How dare you. What did you say?
- He is right.
You are doing well by following the rules.
I will tell them to be careful,
so please let them in for now.
Yes, My Lord.
There you go.
Dal is indeed amazing.
Our flag needs to be fluttering
even when seen from far away.
That is one of the rules too.
Yes, My Lord!
- Let us go in.
- Sure. You are practically flying.
He is my son-in-law! You heard me?
- Dal is the best.
- He is my son-in-law!
What is this nonsense?
You want us to give you the
exclusive rights to salt?
The exclusive rights to salt...
belong to the royal household.
You are not giving them to us.
You are only returning them.
Lord Hae! Why are you not saying anything?
It is not a matter worth our time to discuss.
The King has given us the
rights a long time ago.
Anyway, we are looking into
the status of the salt ponds,
so as soon as General Yeon
from the Jeollo Tribe arrives,
let us all take a vote.
A vote? It is 2 against 3.
Is it not useless to take a vote?
The Five Tribe council is a
coalition among five tribes...
where they come together to lead Goguryeo.
It took your tribe a long time to return.
Do you really want to spend your
time cleaning up after the Princess?
I will bear your advice in mind.
How dare he!
We must get back the
exclusive rights to salt.
Since Lord Sa has told the
other lords of the Five Tribes,
you two must keep an eye
on the Five Tribe council.
Do you think they will back off easily?
We need to find a way to make them.
I know you have a lot on your plate,
but do not be too inattentive to Dal.
What do you mean?
It is okay for us since we live together,
but Dal is all alone in the palace.
If you do not look after him,
he will remain an outcast.
You are worrying too much.
He is not a child. I do not
need to follow him around...
and take care of him.
Do not forget for whom
he fought in the war...
and for whom he is living in the palace.
Dal. I am sorry.
For what?
I could not pay attention to you
because I was immersed in my work.
We are married. You do not
need to worry about that.
I am okay.
This is what has been keeping me busy.
What is this?
It looks like a letter.
It is a love letter that the
Queen sent to Go Won Pyo.
The Queen...
sent this to Go Won Pyo?
It is the evidence that proves
they are having an affair.
I will clean this up right away.
What did you say?
How did the Princess lay her hands on it?
I am not sure about that.
I am...
not telling you this for
you and the Queen's sake.
If that love letter causes trouble,
the Crown Prince and Prince Geon Mu...
will be deeply scarred.
I understand.
Then you must know what
you should do about it.
That is impossible.
The letters have never
fallen into anyone's hands.
Are you smiling right now?
Maybe the Princess is playing tricks on us.
- Pardon?
- Maybe she is trying to...
set us up using a fake letter.
Just like how her mother was tricked.
Hide this in the queen's chambers
after she leaves on patrol.
What is this?
A talisman that will make you queen.
But what if she really has our letter?
We have no time for this. We
need to find the letter first.
Ja Gyeong.
What...
did you just call me?
Jin Ja Gyeong.
I am calling my longtime lover's name.
Also, I already know...
that Geon Mu is not my son.
You...
already knew?
If you could make your son
the king of this empire,
you would have done anything.
I loved your avarice,
which is why I willingly fell for your lie.
Please...
forgive me.
Forgive?
I admired you for you resembled me.
So how would I forgive you?
We only need to get rid of
the letter if there is one.
Do not be afraid.
Are you deeply moved...
to be back on Silla land again?
You must have had no idea that
you would return this way.
My Lord.
I did not punish you when
Silla was destructed.
But you...
made a false report on
Goguryeo and the Northern Zhou.
Have you forgotten who you are...
and what your duty is?
That is not true.
- Please give me another chance.
- Shut it!
Since I am the one who saved
you, I will kill you myself.
My Lord!
What is it?
SILLA, SEORABEOL
KING JINHEUNG, 24TH KING OF SILLA
I, Kim Cha Seung, am here as I was
granted an audience to Your Majesty.
Get up.
Lift your head.
Are you Hae Mo Yong?
Yes, Your Majesty.
King Wideok of Baekje...
is a dishonorable man, so I do
not need to worry about him.
DISHONORABLE: A PERSON WHO BRINGS
SHAME OR DISGRACE ON THEMSELVES
King Pyeongwon of Goguryeo...
has been busy looking after himself.
So...
do you know what gets in the way...
of my great cause to unite the three empires?
How dare I assume anything?
It is Princess Pyeonggang, the
daughter of King Pyeongwon.
Whose son is the man...
Princess Pyeonggang got married to?
The former chief of the Sunno
Tribe, General On Hyeop.
He defended the border against us.
That is right.
She took in the son of a tiger
and made him into a general.
And she helped her powerless father...
to defend her country
against the Northern Zhou.
I am concerned about...
what she will do next.
That means...
For the great cause of the three empires,
I want you to return to Goguryeo.
And...
kill...
Princess Pyeonggang.
It is nice to be gathered together.
Princess, you are here.
Hi, you are here.
I thought it was an urgent call.
We wanted you to get some fresh air...
outside Magnolia Hall.
The Queen suggested that we gather for tea.
All of us have gathered after a long time.
Do not think much of it and have a seat.
The Crown Prince has been
remarkable with his studies.
You are too kind.
Please continue to teach your brother well.
Yes.
Pyeonggang, do you want to see my book?
Show it to me too. I want
to see it, Your Highness.
What else have you learned?
Wow, that is amazing.
I checked the ferry Lady Hae uses...
and all the big herb stores in the capital,
but no one has seen her.
Did she soar up to the sky...
or did she sink into the ground?
Lord Hae.
I will go farther outside the
capital to look for her tomorrow.
- Lord Hae.
- Yes?
Lady Hae is back.
What? She is back?
Lady Hae!
Mo Yong!
- General Go.
- What happened?
Mo Yong! Mo Yong...
Get up.
You found it?
I told you not to be afraid.
It is the grace of the skies.
The skies must have helped.
No, they did not do anything.
It is because you called the
Princess out of Magnolia Hall.
That is not true.
You and I did this together.
Wait. This is not my handwriting.
Are you here to exchange love letters?
That looks like my letter though.
What do you think you are doing, Princess?
What about you two?
What is this discreet meeting
at this time of night?
What do you mean? Watch what you say.
The Princess must have gotten us wrong.
Stop right there, Go Won Pyo.
RIVER WHERE THE MOON RISES
Are you going to keep deceiving me?
You can stop pretending
to be a loyal subject.
I will go against your will...
and get rid of everyone who is corrupt.
You need to give it up.
Do not try so hard. Just do one at a time.
Do one at a time, enough for you to bear.
So why do you not take a break?
I cannot afford to be idle.
The general of Hwangju Castle
raised hundreds of soldiers.
I will go.
That is the only way the
Princess will be at ease.
Trust me.