(Episode 9)
Are you finally awake, Na Ae Gyo?
Who are you?
Where is this?
I saved your life.
Don't you think you should be
a little more grateful?
I guess you only look like Su Ryeon.
Who are you?
I'm Logan Lee.
We've met two years ago.
Logan Lee? I don't know you.
Stop this nonsense and piss off!
Hold on!
I'm not trying to hurt you.
I just want to hear...
what you're about to say back then.
If you don't want to die,
get your hands off me.
I can finish you in seconds.
Until Su Ryeon died,
you pretended to be Joo Dan Tae's
wife because you look like her.
I know that you got
insider information by lobbying...
Party Leader Jung Doo Man
and others at Happy Future Party,
and you made a whole lot
of money from that.
But two years ago,
you certainly decided...
that you'll separate ways
from Joo Dan Tae.
That's why you wanted to meet me.
Stop speaking nonsense.
I've never made such a decision.
Joo Dan Tae is
the only person that I trust.
This voice!
I know it's you!
I'm Na Ae Gyo.
I have something to tell you
before I leave.
I know what Joo Dan Tae did
to Shim Su Ryeon...
and what kind of a person he is.
I might never get to tell you
if I don't tell you today.
I know...
that you meant what you said.
You were desperate!
I must've...
had a fight with him or something.
Don't you think that I could've
done that on a whim?
I'm not very good
with anger management.
Does that mean that it's fine
if I play this for Joo Dan Tae?
Yes. Go ahead.
Are you trying to threaten me
with a mere voice recording?
I'm sorry,
but the relationship
between Dan Tae and I...
is much stronger than whatever
you think it is.
We had children together.
You think a voice recording can
change anything?
Stop snooping and don't you
ever try to find me again.
We meet again.
What are you doing?
Did you approach me
because you two are a team?
I don't know what you're thinking,
but I'm Dan Tae's woman.
I'm the birth mother of the twins.
Joo Dan Tae tried to kill you.
You almost died today!
You...
don't know when you'll be abandoned
like Su Ryeon.
And yet, you want to stand by him...
just to be loyal?
What do you know about Dan Tae?
Because I've been betrayed.
I've had to flee and almost died
because of him.
You're not any different from me.
You know better...
about how he deals with people
who are of no use to him.
I'm giving you a chance
to abandon him...
before he abandons you.
Work with us, Na Ae Gyo.
What do you two think you are?
(Seok Hoon)
Hello?
Hello, Seok Hoon. It's me, Ms. Oh.
Everything is good, right?
I called because I was worried.
I'm fine. How are you?
My dad didn't try to do anything
to you again, did he?
No, I'm fine.
Good to hear that you're fine.
Bye now.
Don't you want to meet
your children?
I'll let you meet Seok Hoon
and Seok Kyung.
You two are adorable!
You think you can
win me over with just that?
If I had any
maternal attachment to my kids,
do you think I would've run away
when they were infants?
Being a mother?
That's certainly not my thing.
Do you know what Joo Dan Tae
did to the kids?
Your kids are being abused.
They're living in a nightmare!
And you're okay with
that lunatic raising them?
Watch what you say
about other people's families.
Let her go.
We can't let her go like this.
What if she tells Joo Dan Tae?
We can't stop her.
So? You'll give up?
I can't.
She may say that,
but I saw the look in her eyes.
We'll have to hope she has at least
an ounce of motherly love left.
Where were you?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Did you get a new man?
Who are you to complain?
You're the one who tried to kill me.
Why did you try to kill me,
you jerk?
Now that we sold the building,
you had no use for me
so you wanted to kill me?
I couldn't understand
why you did that two years ago,
so I was just verifying it.
What couldn't you understand?
I went to Thailand quietly
as you told me to!
I meant...
leave for a short while
because Su Ryeon was dead.
Since people can't see you.
So why did you avoid me?
You wouldn't take my calls,
you wouldn't come back...
and you ignored me.
How was I supposed to take that?
Babe. We're ideal partners.
We've been one forever.
As long as you don't betray me,
I will never betray you.
But once is enough.
Try that garbage with me again,
and there will be a bullet
in your skull.
Got that?
Finally,
I feel like Ae Gyo is back.
To be honest,
you were kind of sexy earlier.
You made my heart race a little.
How about a drink
to celebrate our making up?
I was nervous because I thought
you were straying.
You know what you mean to me.
We need to score big with
Cheonsoo District's redevelopment.
I won't stray at least until then.
Their relationship seems to be...
more solid than we anticipated.
No. I just saw a crack.
She didn't tell him that she met us.
Let me know
if you ever change your mind.
I'll let you meet Seok Hoon
and Seok Kyung.
What brings you by?
The chairman isn't home yet.
I stopped by because of the tux
for the wedding.
I need to check his size.
Go back to work.
Yes, ma'am.
This necklace belongs
to your daughter, correct?
We found her DNA...
and the victim's blood on it.
Where is it?
What are you doing?
Why are you snooping around
in an empty office?
Looking for this?
Give it to me.
You don't need it anymore.
I did everything you asked.
I sent out the invitations
and ordered my dress.
I'll show up at the wedding
as promised,
so give me the necklace.
That won't be hard,
but you don't think this is...
my only ace in the hole, do you?
What do you mean by that?
I heard Eun Byeol got an IV.
So? Did it cleanly erase her memory?
How could Dr. Ha test a drug
still in clinical studies...
on his own daughter?
He's still a licensed doctor.
He shouldn't do that.
What if there's a bad side effect?
His daughter's life
would be ruined for sure,
and he'd end up in jail.
Ms. Cheon Seo Jin.
Why are you so dense?
I told you. You can't be free of me.
It's time to accept your fate...
unless you want your daughter
to get back the memory she lost.
Do you understand now,
my dear Seo Jin?
(Yoon Chul)
(Fate)
What are you thinking?
You're marrying Chairman Joo?
You said you wouldn't marry him
for Eun Byeol's sake.
You know what kind of a jerk he is.
I do. But what about it?
What man wouldn't lose his temper...
if his fiancee fools around
with her ex-husband?
What's gotten into you?
Something happened
with him, didn't it?
Why did you suddenly
change your mind?
You don't love him!
I'm not a 20-year-old child...
crying for love.
Marriage is the biggest business
in a person's life.
That's why I chose Dan Tae.
What about our daughter?
Do you think Eun Byeol
can accept this marriage?
It's for me.
You dumped Yoon Hee.
That's enough for me.
I refuse to see you and Yoon Hee
live happily.
What?
Why?
Didn't you know? This is who I am.
I've been using you.
I had to bury Eun Byeol's crime,
so I needed your blind
fatherly love.
I wanted to get revenge on Yoon Hee,
so I acted like I wanted
to go back to you.
You're lying.
No matter how low you may be,
you wouldn't do this to me.
Stop being so clingy,
and get away from me.
I never wanted to go back to you...
from the start.
The type of man
who's right for me...
is someone who is insanely rich
and gentle...
like Dan Tae.
Seo Jin.
So take Eun Byeol and leave.
Go to the US or anywhere.
I don't care.
Now, you'll even dump our daughter?
My life is more important...
than my daughter's.
It's better for her too.
So...
make sure...
to leave before the wedding!
I...
I'm done talking.
You really are...
the absolute worst.
Please...
I need you to protect Eun Byeol.
That's the only way left now.
What's all this?
They're gifts from Chairman Joo.
Some of them are for you.
Do you want to have a look?
He sent a dress and shoes that you
will be wearing to their wedding.
Are they really going ahead
with this ridiculous wedding?
Seok Hoon, where are you?
That's hilarious.
Oh, wait. Ms. Kang!
Ms. Kang!
What are all these?
Why did you buy
so many designer handbags?
They're gifts from the Three Queens.
My birthday is coming up.
Isn't it so sweet of them?
Oh, my. They bought you all these?
Were all the new bags
you've been carrying...
also gifts from the Three Queens?
I knew it.
They must think of you
as their family.
They look heavy. Let me help.
Forget it.
I don't want people to think
that I boss you around.
Who would think that?
My obedience to you is
completely voluntary.
Come on.
I'm great at carrying bags.
I'm the greatest gentleman
of the 21st National Assembly.
Let's go.
A gentleman, my foot.
- You don't have to do that!
- Let's go, Ms. Kang.
- My goodness.
- Be careful.
- You're an important person.
- Stop it.
What's going on here?
It's okay. They were
going to find out sooner or later.
Let's go.
Their friendship is beautiful.
They're siblings!
Which floor did they start from?
What did you say?
Their mom and dad are
getting married soon.
How can Seok Hoon
and Eun Byeol be dating?
But they're quite cute together.
It made my heart flutter.
Chairman Joo, what if
your wedding gets called off?
Word will spread
among the neighbors in no time.
That's not going to happen
as long as you keep quiet.
You know I'm good
at keeping secrets.
Oh, I almost forgot about Ma Ri.
If she spreads the word
at the bathhouse, you're doomed.
Seok Hoon knows better than that.
I'm sure Eun Byeol came up
with the idea to stop our wedding.
If I react,
it'll only encourage the immature
kids to act up even more.
I ask you to stay
out of our family matters.
The door is that way.
Chairman Joo,
you can be honest with me.
Why are you so determined
to go ahead with this wedding?
I mean, your fiancee
cheated on you with Yoon Chul.
I doubt that you're
still in love with her.
I guess what you're in love with
is your share in Cheong A Group.
My wedding is coming up.
I really don't want to use violence
so early in the morning.
Also, you're
an assemblyman, after all.
I root for you.
That's true love right there.
You're pursuing love
despite your children's opposition.
I'm very touched indeed.
Hey, I have an aide too.
He was the best fighter
in all of Beolgyo.
You got up to something
very cute, Son.
You've been rebellious lately,
so I thought you were all grown up,
but you're apparently
still a little kid.
You're my baby...
who I need to shelter and care for.
I heard that Ms. Cheon is
stepping down as the director.
We'll finally get to see
how good Eun Byeol really is.
It'll be her first test
without her mom's influence!
She's way too timid
to do well on the test.
I heard that Mr. Ma even got rid of
her private bathroom.
She'll also be eating
the same food as we do.
She went from being the princess
to a commoner overnight.
Mr. Ma sure acts faster than anyone.
- Let's run.
- Hurry.
Is this really necessary?
Why did you have to show up
at school in this situation?
You don't care about me at all.
Whether it's your wedding or school,
you want everything your way.
Don't waste your energy
taking a taxi in the morning.
If you want to avoid me,
I'll get you a separate car.
I hate you.
You unloving egoist.
What is it?
Why are you doing this? Let go!
What are you up to these days?
Are you advertising
that you're dating my brother?
Is that your silly way...
of protesting against the wedding?
I'm not just protesting.
It's for real.
Seok Hoon and I are in love.
Do you think
that can stop the wedding?
What's going to happen is, Seok Hoon
is going to get beaten to death.
He may literally die.
He may die?
Do you want to know
how scary my dad is?
- Do you see that?
- What happened to your arm?
No way.
This is who your future stepdad is.
So forget about convincing my dad.
It'd be faster
to try and stop your mom.
If anything happens
to my poor brother,
I won't forgive you.
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
All right.
It seems like everyone's here.
We're here to take a vote
on the dismissal...
of the director
of Cheong A Foundation.
Before that,
I have something to say.
Cheong A Foundation is...
the country's most prestigious
private school foundation.
The previous directors
donated their immense wealth...
and dedicated themselves
to this cradle of education.
But Director Cheon
damaged the school's reputation...
with her incompetence and arrogance.
I strongly demand that
Director Cheon be dismissed.
Director Cheon,
do you have something to say?
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
I admit that I made
a crucial mistake.
I am deeply ashamed.
However, this is
no time for division,
but we need to work
closely together.
I will put things right
by all means.
I can easily give up
my reputation as a singer,
but Cheong A Foundation...
is my life.
I can put everything back
the way it is.
Please give me a chance.
Let's take a vote.
(Against)
(Vote on Dismissal
of Director Cheon Seo Jin)
All right.
Let me announce the result.
(For: 5, Against: 6)
Five are in favor of her dismissal.
Six are against it.
What happened? I can't believe this.
It's been tampered with.
- What's going on?
- Unbelievable.
I announce that the motion
to dismiss Director Cheon...
has been rejected.
Thank you.
Thank you so much
for trusting me.
To repay your support,
I will do my best...
to make you proud
of Cheong A Foundation again.
(Notice of Board Meeting)
I don't know what you did
to manipulate the board members,
but I can never accept this result.
Of course not. We'll appeal
and take a vote again.
Let's go, Mom.
Your father asked us a favor
before he passed away.
What favor?
My first daughter
still has a long way to go.
She is ambitious
but lacks in many ways.
Once she becomes the director,
her mom will make up excuses
to bring her down.
Seo Young will
cause trouble as well.
Just believe in Seo Jin...
and support her...
so that she can keep her place
as Director.
Father...
So, no need to thank us.
Think of your father
and work harder.
We'll have your back.
(Vote on Dismissal
of Director Cheon Seo Jin)
Father!
Father...
(Vote on Dismissal
of Director Cheon Seo Jin)
Father!
I'm sorry.
You were here?
Were you looking for me?
Director Cheon isn't dismissed.
Did you hear?
No, I don't care.
I don't understand why she's
so attached to the foundation.
She doesn't even look ashamed
to see the students.
I'm so ashamed of her.
Don't mind what others are saying.
People will forget over time.
Keep your chin up.
Seok Hoon,
you can count on me
if you need a shoulder.
I can lend an ear to you anytime.
You know how much I like you, right?
Are your memories back?
Do you remember what I told you?
No, I can't remember anything.
Can't you just tell me?
Just keep thinking.
Don't you remember
who you met with by the stairs?
Me? Who else other than you?
You have to get your memory back.
You might've seen the murderer
who killed Ro Na.
What do you mean?
Are you saying that Mr. Park
wasn't the murderer?
You know how kind Mr. Park is.
I'm confident that he's being
falsely accused.
I couldn't believe it either.
He's not a man who'd kill anyone.
If you get your memory back,
we could find the murderer...
and prove Mr. Park's innocence.
If you remember anything, tell me...
and tell me only.
You can promise that, right?
Wait.
Are you still thinking of Ro Na?
It's not about Ro Na.
I just feel so bad for Mr. Park.
You'll help me, right?
Yes, I will.
I'll do anything for you.
- I'll get my memory back.
- This peaceful afternoon,
I'll end off with a song...
that'll wake everyone up.
What's wrong?
How did you say Ro Na died?
Someone stabbed her in the head
with the Arts Festival trophy.
Trophy?
(Golden Real Estate)
Hello, I'm Hwang Geum Bong.
I'd like to look into properties
in the Cheonsoo District.
The Cheonsoo District, you say?
That area doesn't have
any development plans yet.
If you'd like to invest,
I'd recommend the Opyeong District.
Please hold on.
I'll ask my investor.
Are you sure
about the information...
that Cheong A Group is going
to invest in Cheonsoo District?
Of course. I heard it directly
from Mr. Joo himself.
But, do be careful about it,
because the official announcement
hasn't been made yet.
Okay. So, how much property
are you looking for?
Everything you can
get your hands on.
There's going to be a massive
increase in value soon.
Okay.
Do you know Joo Dan Tae?
Sounds like Chairman Joo directly
made this recommendation.
My client wants Cheonsoo District
and nowhere else.
Okay.
Cheonsoo District, you say?
(Golden Real Estate)
Chairman Song, it's me,
Hwang Geum Bong.
How have you been?
I just heard
of a new redevelopment plan,
so I had to call you.
Is that right?
All right, then.
Do some research and send it
to my assistant's office.
All right.
Ms. Jincheon,
- Yes?
- Did you like my present?
I put a lot of thought into it.
Of course!
You ladies have the best eye
for everything.
Does that nasty lady
not bother you anymore?
You said that she lives with you
at Hera Palace, right?
After you ladies taught her
not to mess with me,
she can't even say a word to me.
Don't worry about it.
If she ever tries to mess
with you again, tell us.
How dare an assemblyman's wife
look down on my Ms. Jincheon?
Why don't you just move?
- Move?
- I just got a call,
and I hear that they're going
to build a multiplex condo...
that's 130 floors high
in Cheonsoo District.
You heard about that rumor too?
Hearing that Chairman Joo is
getting involved too,
it sounds like they'll announce
a redevelopment plan soon.
Chairman Joo?
He's so quick when it comes
to things like that.
Ms. Jincheon, you should
get a place there too.
That area will become
an even richer area than Hera.
Really?
That's some amazing
insider information!
Since it hasn't been announced yet,
the prices will go soaring
once it does!
That's why you need to hurry.
I hear that Chairman Joo bought
all the good areas already.
Honey!
Honey! Kyu Jin!
You need to dress me
so that I can go to work,
and take care of... Nevermind!
Why are you going around like that?
You look like you're crazy.
Did you visit
Kang Ma Ri's bathhouse again?
Why don't you just get a job there?
Did you save the country
in your previous life?
How did you find a woman like me?
I probably met a woman like you
because I didn't save the country.
How will you get your funds
for the election without me?
What? Did you hear something?
Cheonsoo District is going to be
redeveloped soon!
That rumor is already
about 200 years old!
I've been looking at properties
with my mother since a pre-teen.
I'm serious.
I've heard the Three Queens
say so themselves.
You know who they are?
They're the ultimate insiders
to real estate!
Not only that, Chairman Joo...
has been buying up properties there!
He didn't even tell me anything!
He's trying to take
all the gold alone!
How much money do you have
on hand right now?
No, I must call my mom.
That's right.
I am...
going to hold
a little talent show...
to get some cash on me.
Good morning, ma'am.
Here I go.
This is really expensive.
In just 2 years,
it'll be 100 years old.
You didn't have to.
Here you go.
This must be so expensive.
Here.
Please take a look over this.
(Real Estate Sales Contract)
Here.
Here as well.
All good.
What's this?
It's just a meal.
This is going to be worth
50 million dollars.
- Sorry?
- I said 50 million dollars.
Okay.
Let's stamp the last one together.
All right. Hold it.
(Real Estate Sales Contract)
Congratulations.
All there's left to do is get rich.
You're good at your job!
Sure I am.
I don't know
how the information leaked,
but sales in the Cheonsoo District
has gone up sharply today.
Who smelled the money?
I couldn't find who it was.
You idiot!
You used so much money for this.
How can you not know?
Find out as soon as possible!
Look into who bought the properties
and who's behind these deals.
No. First, purchase
all the properties...
that I've been eyeing on.
- Get out!
- Yes, Chairman.
That incompetent jerk!
It can't be...
Oh Yoon Hee? You again?
My goal has changed.
I want to become extremely wealthy.
I'll do whatever it takes
to accumulate wealth...
so that I can own this penthouse.
That witch!
How dare she even dream
of taking my penthouse?
Honey, it's me.
Could I ask you a favor?
I need you to take care
of this witch.
That's my expertise.
We'll talk later when we meet.
Thanks for calling me, Ms. Na.
I didn't expect you to call so fast.
No need to thank me.
I'm just here to check
how great you are...
at keeping your promise.
Are you sure you just need
to see them from here?
What else?
Should I hug them
and cry tears of joy or something?
They're here.
- You're early.
- Hello.
What is it? I thought you wanted
to talk. Why is she here?
Don't be rude.
She has something to tell us.
What do you want to drink?
It's on me.
The strawberry milkshake is
good here.
It's really sweet.
All done, right?
I'm not all that generous...
that I can sit across from the woman
who killed my mom for long.
Sit, Seok Kyung.
It's about your mom.
Mom?
Your birth mother.
- She's alive.
- What do you mean, birth mother?
I'm sorry,
but our birth mother died
as soon as she gave birth.
If you're going to try to fool us,
you need to get the facts right.
Do I need to stay any longer
for this nonsense?
Your father lied to you.
Your birth mother is alive.
She's your birth mother.
Have you gone insane?
Is this a joke? This is our mom
that just died.
No, she's your birth mother.
The resemblance between her
and Su Ryeon is uncanny.
I know it's hard to believe,
but it's true.
I've met her and checked myself.
Is this real? Where is she now?
You trust this woman?
She's trying to mess with us
because I bullied Ro Na.
Photoshopping photos like this is
a piece of cake.
We can ask Dad ourselves.
You still trust him?
After all of that, you still don't
know what kind of a man he is?
He's the man who abuses...
and controls us.
How do you expect him
to tell us anything truthful?
Just stay quiet.
Ms. Oh is trying to help us.
She's very close to you.
If you want to see her,
I'll let you.
Did I ever ask for my birth mother?
How dare she try to act
as if she's our mom now?
I only have one mom.
A fake mom? I don't need one.
Be honest with me.
You know something, don't you?
What is it? Tell me!
The person who killed our mom...
might be Dad.
Have you gone insane?
Why would Dad do that?
What would he do that for?
Why?
Because he no longer
needed our mom.
That's the kind of a man he is.
He abandons everyone useless to him.
We don't know...
when we'll be abandoned.
So, we can't trust Dad anymore.
Do you understand?
It's just you and me.
I'll never abandon you.
Even if I have to die,
I'm going to protect you from Dad.
If...
Dad really killed Mom,
I won't just let him be.
I'll never forgive him.
What is it?
What threats are you
making to Seo Jin?
Call the wedding off right now.
Seo Jin doesn't deserve
a trashy husband like you.
Stop fooling around.
You think you'll have a chance
to patch things back up...
if I don't marry her?
Let's be honest here.
Aren't you back because
you want her money too?
I guess this is the only use
your hand has now.
I should've completely crushed it
when I had the chance,
but I got too soft.
You lunatic!
I'm going to stop this wedding,
whatever it takes.
Even if it means that I'll have
to risk my life.
I love this
ambitious attitude of yours.
But I guess you haven't heard
anything from her.
That's disappointing.
She's your daughter too, after all.
The birth father should know.
What are you saying?
I found out...
that your daughter killed Bae Ro Na.
What can you do?
Parents need to be responsible
for their kids' mistakes.
Seo Jin is going to bear it all.
She loves her daughter quite a lot,
as you know.
Wow.
I wish someone else was here
to see that look on your face.
Go on. Hit me.
If you can handle
what I'll say, hit me.
I said to hit me.
Take your daughter
and get out of my sight...
before I turn her into the police.
I'll... I'll kill you.
I'll kill you, Joo Dan Tae!
Good luck with that.
I'll kill you.
I will kill you!
(Restricted Area)
I can't figure out
what Na Ae Gyo is thinking.
Even seeing her kids
didn't have much effect.
She won't readily show her emotions.
We'll have to wait and see.
What about Cheonsoo District?
Has there been progress?
As expected, it reached Kang Ma Ri
and Lee Kyu Jin too.
The tip we leaked
to the Three Queens worked.
Then it's time to make our move.
Hello, Mr. Hwang. It's Oh Yoon Hee.
I'll sell lot 27 in Cheonsoo.
Yes. Please find out
if there are any buyers.
As soon as possible please.
Thank you.
Joo Dan Tae should be arriving
at his vacation house.
Did you want to meet
to give me this stupid invitation?
This is so annoying!
If Cheon Seo Jin won't divorce you,
will you live with her
for the rest of your life?
Am I stupid?
And she's marrying me
only because I am blackmailing her.
It means nothing to me.
- He's blackmailing her?
- This is just for the stock.
Then put all the land
you bought in Cheonsoo District...
in my name.
Let's go with half.
70 percent. I won't go any lower.
In exchange, I'll get the land
in Oh Yoon Hee's name.
Even still, 70 percent
is excessive.
70 percent is excessive?
Really?
Fine. But...
it's only until I divorce Seo Jin.
When will you end that marriage?
Once we register our marriage,
I'll be Cheong A Group's
largest shareholder.
As soon as I get the shares,
I'll chop up the company
and sell them off.
I'll bring up the stock price...
to the max and bow out.
- Don't you trust me?
- The man who tried to kill me?
How could I trust you?
Would you, if you were me?
I already explained that.
How would I know?
I may disappear quietly one day...
as Shim Su Ryeon did.
Get lost.
I'm not in the mood
to drink with you.
We're not done talking!
Seriously.
She has such a nasty temper.
What happened to your face?
Who did this?
Call off the wedding.
It's lunacy.
Is Joo Dan Tae blackmailing you?
Don't be afraid.
He has no way to prove
Eun Byeol killed her.
How did you know?
Did he tell you?
No matter what
he threatens you with, stand firm.
I'll deal with
Eun Byeol's treatment.
Say you know nothing.
He has evidence.
Eun Byeol's necklace.
It has her DNA and Ro Na's blood.
And a recording of my confession.
Why didn't you tell me that sooner?
You can't handle this on your own.
Don't underestimate me.
I can control Dan Tae easily.
If you'd take care of Eun Byeol,
I'll handle the rest.
Please leave quietly.
This is my final request.
I didn't do it, did I?
No, I couldn't have.
There's no way.
Then why do I keep
remembering the trophy?
It's time to take your medicine.
Your mom said
to make sure to take it.
Will this make my headache go away?
Does it hurt a lot?
Oh no. You reviewed this...
only three times.
I feel like my head is
about to explode.
I'm solving the math problems,
and numbers keep
crawling around in my head.
What if I really end up going crazy?
You've been doing well until now.
Ro Na's gone now.
Forget this.
Stop studying and go to sleep.
I'll wake you up early tomorrow.
How's Eun Byeol doing?
She's having a really tough time.
Her mom's wedding is coming up,
and something's wrong
with her memory.
What about the drug she's taking?
That's hindering her from getting
her memory back, isn't it?
I've swapped them out with vitamins,
so it won't have any effect.
She'll remember soon...
what she did.
No matter how much she struggles,
she's back where she started.
Poor girl.
(Seok Hoon)
Why did you want to see me?
I know that someone else...
killed Ro Na.
What?
Was it...
Eun Byeol?
I do suspect her, but...
I'm not positive.
I don't have evidence.
I think my father was involved
in Ro Na's death.
He has the necklace
that Eun Byeol wore...
during her performance.
Joo Dan Tae knew
that Eun Byeol was the killer.
He's blackmailing Seo Jin with it...
into marrying him.
(Golden Real Estate)
A good lot just became available
in Cheonsoo District.
Then naturally, I should buy it.
I'll pay 50,000 dollars more
than the highest bidder...
No. 100,000 dollars more.
I'm relying on you, Mr. Hwang.
Awesome. A good lot
became available already?
Mr. Hwang was worth every dollar
we bribed him with.
If that land becomes mine,
my life will be set for life.
A 130-floor apartment complex...
is being built on that land.
This lame Hera Palace
is nothing in comparison.
My gosh. The Three Queens
have incredible sources.
Hurray. Hurray.
What did I tell you?
I told you...
that Kang Ma Ri's bathhouse
was like a secret conference room.
Who would've thought I'd benefit
from a bathhouse scrubber?
Send Jenny's mom a few boxes
of the fanciest Italian towels.
I know, right? Honey.
We totally struck gold.
Kang Ma Ri's bathhouse?
Bathhouse scrubber?
Let's hurry.
I love you!
Hey, Jenny.
Are you aware that candy costs
100 dollars a piece?
If you have a sore throat,
just get normal candy
at the supermarket.
Mind your own business.
Don't pick a fight and go away.
Isn't that humidifier
from Switzerland?
I'm impressed.
And all your clothes are
from designer brands.
Jenny, this is not okay.
Did you buy them for me?
Did I steal them from you?
I use them because I can
afford them. What do you care?
Get lost so I can study.
Still, it's unacceptable.
Think about how many people's
backs your mom has to scrub...
to earn all that money.
Shouldn't you be more thrifty?
What? My mom does what?
Hey, you really didn't know?
After hearing...
how your mom works her bottom off,
I was really touched.
That's why I prepared
a little something for you.
Guys, what are you waiting for?
It's time to give her our gifts.
Ta-da!
- Here you go.
- It's pretty.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Why is my wrist aching so much?
I still have to work
many more years.
Ma'am! This is insane!
What if Jenny sees this?
Why would you dry these
in the living room?
Ma'am!
I did it.
Jenny. Well...
The thing is... I can explain.
When were you going to tell me?
If you're so ashamed of your job,
why do you even do it?
Just quit already.
How did you find out?
I wasn't trying to keep it
from you...
- I'm sorry, Jenny.
- For what?
Did you steal?
Did you hit people
and take their money?
No, it's not like that.
Then why were you
hiding it from me?
I've never done anything
I should be ashamed of.
Even if you were ashamed of me,
I can't quit.
What did I do wrong?
I've pampered you
more than any other parent,
and I've done everything
I can for you.
Isn't that enough?
If you don't dry them completely,
they'll smell.
If you don't satisfy your customers,
they'll leave.
Then we'll starve.
What?
After what happened to Ro Na,
I'm not ashamed
or scared of anything.
I don't care if the kids tease me.
And I don't care if I don't
get into Seoul National University.
The only thing
that scares me is that...
someone close to me may leave me
and never come back.
With Dad gone,
we only have each other to rely on.
Why would you keep secrets from me?
I'm your daughter.
How could you let me find out
about your job through Min Hyuk?
Jenny.
I've run us a bath.
Come in when you're ready.
I want to see how good you are.
Don't forget banana-flavored milk.
My princess is all grown up.
Now that she's found out,
should I tell her
about her dad too? Or no?
Mom, hurry up!
The bath is getting cold!
Okay, I'm coming!
Here we go!
Come on. Let me scrub your back.
Stay still.
Your mom is a professional
with 25 years of experience.
There's a long line of chairmen...
waiting to be scrubbed by me.
You don't trust me?
Gosh, look how dirty your back is.
Were you too busy scrubbing
other people's backs?
Gosh, this is seriously gross.
What are you talking about?
I wash myself every day.
Have some milk. I want to pick up
some scrubbing skills.
Why should you?
You'll go to Seoul
National University...
and live a comfortable life.
That's why I'm working so hard.
Are you listening to me?
Gosh, you talk too much.
You don't have to pay me.
Just stay still.
Just for today.
Mom.
Have some snacks and study.
Did you tell Dad to take me
to the US? Is that right?
Dad has to visit the headquarters.
Follow him and get some fresh air.
It's your vacation soon.
You're lying.
You're only sending me away
to have a wedding.
How can you do this
if you're my mom?
Mom. Can't you cancel the wedding?
I can't live without you.
Please don't abandon me.
I'm scared.
Eun Byeol.
You're my everything.
So please don't get married.
If I have to go to the US,
I want you to come with me.
As long as I have you,
I can give up on everything,
even college. I mean it.
Why would you give up on college?
After all this hard work?
Don't be so weak. Just do as I say.
I'm only staying behind
to protect you.
To protect you from that monster.
Why?
I said, I'm not angry.
Forget it.
Just focus on planning
your wedding with Seo Jin.
Are you sure you're coming
in a few days?
Of course.
I'll come as soon as I sort things
out at the company and foundation.
Don't worry.
Stay with your dad until I come.
I'm not sure
if this is the best idea.
Eun Byeol can't know.
Don't say anything about me.
This is not right.
I can't leave you alone here.
Let's just kill Joo Dan Tae
and run away.
Stop this nonsense and leave.
Right now.
Seo Jin.
Goodbye.
Don't get weak, Seo Jin.
You're getting married today,
but you sent your daughter away
without letting her see the wedding?
I guess Joo Dan Tae doesn't make
a very good stepdad.
Stay out of my family's affairs...
and leave this place.
Your child and husband are gone.
Why are you still here by yourself?
I like...
this place.
I also like the fact
that you're dying to get rid of me.
And I'm curious to see...
how happily in love
you and Joo Dan Tae will be.
- What?
- That's why...
I plan to sincerely wish you
a happy marriage.
See you later.
Can't wait to see
the happy bride, Cheon Seo Jin.
Why is a bride's skin so dry?
Were you up all night
from the excitement?
If you couldn't wait,
you should've said
let's have it sooner.
(Cheon Seo Jin)
This is what you need, right?
You can register
the marriage yourself.
I wanted to rent out
an entire hotel...
and make you
the greatest bride in the world.
But your reputation is a bit...
You know.
Please understand why we're having
a small one at Hera Palace.
Even so, you're becoming
the owner of the penthouse.
Enjoy it.
So, did Eun Byeol leave?
The weather in California
must be incredible right now.
Don't say her name.
Even if I marry you,
Eun Byeol is not your child.
She'll have
nothing to do with you. Ever.
Gosh. What a shame.
I was so happy
to get another daughter.
I think
they're really getting married.
Eun Byeol left for California.
She left? She did?
Where are you going?
(Seok Hoon)
Don't answer...
anyone's calls.
(Seok Hoon)
Pull over. Pull over now!
(Police)
Don't come out.
Ha Yoon Chul, correct?
Yes, I am. What is this about?
You are under arrest for
the murder of Bae Ro Na.
What?
What are you talking about?
Dad. What's going on?
What are you doing to my dad?
Park Jung Shik, who is locked up
for murder confessed everything.
That you bribed him to lie
and confess.
Come to the station with us.
Wait. Wait a second.
Something's not right. Wait!
Wait!
It's not true! Wait.
- Dad.
- I need to talk to my daughter.
Eun Byeol. Get in a cab
and go to the airport now.
- Got that?
- Dad!
I'll be fine, so don't worry.
You have to go.
- Dad!
- Did you hear me?
Let go of me!
Dad!
Dad.
Dad... Dad...
Dad!
Dad...
He was just arrested
and is being taken in.
(He was just arrested
and is being taken in.)
Good work.
(Good work.)
(Eun Byeol)
(Power off)
What happened? What's going on?
Seok Hoon... What do I do?
Thank you, everyone.
We're finally getting married.
You've succeeded.
You two make a good couple.
Look. Here's the bride.
Hi.
You're wrong, Ro Na.
I will not lose...
anything to you.
Not my dad,
not Seok Hoon,
not the grand prize trophy.
What's wrong?
Ro Na... It was Ro Na.
I killed her.
Smile.
Smile as if you're so happy,
you can't keep it in.
I'm sorry for realizing it so late.
I loved you, Ha Yoon Chul.
(The Penthouse 2)
Welcome to your nightmare.
I need to learn from you.
I killed her.
I'll make you regret so much
that your heart will tear apart.
I keep getting a feeling
that you're not a bad person.
Whatever the reason is, use me.
I remember everything now.
- There was someone else?
- Why did Ro Na die?
There's a trap here.
I need you in order to find
Ro Na's real murderer.
I'm going to find out everything,
even if I have to kill you.