Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow
that fills up the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing,
please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth,
flying towards fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness
that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and
let's count down to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 20=
This uninvited guest
comes like a tornado.
Don't talk about him.
How old is he?
What are you insinuating?
Nothing.
How does he look like?
I bet he has quite the look
since it bothers you so much.
You may leave now.
Don't keep trying
to chase me away.
With such a nice atmosphere,
if I were you,
I would have confessed.
And you have to wait
for another three months?
Three months later,
there's no telling whose girlfriend
Jiang Xiao Ning will be.
How did it go for you today?
Well, things went well
and were under control, of course.
So, Zhao Yan
is still not your girlfriend,
right?
Want to grab a drink?
(Mr. Huang: The address is 189, Guang'an Hutong.)
Dude.
Do you know me?
Of course.
You don't look familiar to me.
What is it?
Anything I can do for you?
You don't remember me?
I don't think
we have met.
Ten years ago,
I asked for your favor.
But you just disappeared.
Do you mean Chen Yun?
That's my brother.
He's dead long ago.
Your brother?
Forget it then.
Hold on.
I can do
whatever Chen Yun could.
Pay me
and I'll do the job for you.
Really?
Director Xu.
He is here.
I've been watching Chen Ao lately
and I discovered something.
Go on.
Someone came to see him today.
Who was it?
Gu Chuan.
How could you go and see him yourself?
It's dangerous.
I was looking for an opportunity
to get near him
and see
if I could worm something out of him.
It's too much of a coincidence.
He actually has a twin brother.
His brother hit me with a car
and Jiang Xiao Ning's family
and he assaulted you not long ago.
Don't you think
there could be
a link?
How would I know?
Which is why
I asked for his number
on the pretext of needing his help
to see
if I could get anything from him.
I'll go to meet him with you.
Call him
and set a date.
All right.
(Hi.)
(The number you have dialed)
(is busy.)
No answer?
(Please try again later.)
Try again.
How is it?
Have you prepared the money?
Looks like he's avoiding you.
(Gu Chuan, missed calls)
Assistant Liu.
Going somewhere?
Cheng Ran.
Anything?
Do you know this guy?
Yes.
Why?
Why did he come to see you?
Our company's new project is launching.
He was a nail house owner there.
Not only did he refuse to vacate his home,
he even brought people to cause a ruckus.
We couldn't reach an agreement
even after I had a discussion
with him here in the office.
He insisted on meeting Director Xu.
Later on, our company
secretly gave him more compensation.
Only then, he moved out.
I think this photo
was taken when he came to get the money.
That explains why
he came after me.
He went to see you?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I thought he was just saying it.
I didn't expect he would do it for real.
That's outrageous.
But worry not.
Since he has taken our money,
I bet he won't be coming here anymore.
Okay, I get it now.
Later.
Director Xu.
Cheng Ran came asking about it
and I've replied to him as you told.
Also,
Chen Ao has been taken care of.
He won't show up ever again.
Mr. Gu.
Is there anything else?
Nothing, you can get off work now.
Okay.
Boss.
May I take a day off?
I can't send you home.
Why?
I have a date with my friends.
They're waiting for me.
Sure, go ahead then.
Thank you, Boss.
I'll send you home then.
It's fine.
I have a design to work on.
You may go now.
All right then.
Don't stay too late.
Okay.
Over here!
Would you like something to eat?
I have no appetite.
Don't be upset.
If this goes on,
I'll be in a bad mood too.
It's not that.
Look.
Seriously?
It would take days
to tell you the whole story.
I'll tell you everything later.
How about this?
Come over.
What do you think?
That works.
You sure you don't want to eat?
No, I have no appetite.
Let's talk while we walk.
All right.
Coming.
Hello.
A new friend.
Let me do the introduction.
Chen Chen.
This is my best friend.
Sister Yan Yan.
Hi, Sister Yan Yan.
How could you? Jiang Xiao Ning.
You never told me
you know such a handsome guy.
And you called me your best friend?
She didn't tell me either
about her pretty girlfriend.
Slick.
Of course.
But you're not really
my type.
Do you know whose house you are in?
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Before you brought him here,
didn't you tell him
how my temper is like?
You come to my place...
All right now.
Stop fighting.
I've bought a lot of food
and some self-heating hotpots too.
I'm starving. Let's eat, all right?
All right then.
Get me one.
I've been craving fish with Sichuan pickles.
It drives me crazy.
Here, this is for you.
(Self-heating hot pot)
I don't get you.
Your family can do more than support you
but you insist on depending on your own.
Why?
I'm not a three-year-old.
Why do they
interfere with my life?
In the eyes of parents,
their children never grow up.
I'm really envious of you.
If my parents were still alive,
I would let them
even if they kept doing that.
Let's drink.
Here.
What's with the sigh?
Let's go racing when we have time.
If this was the only thing,
I wouldn't be so depressed.
Look.
Don't get all emotional here.
I hate guys who cry.
Leave if you're going to cry.
Don't. Ignore her.
Tell me.
What is it?
Xiao Ning, I got my heart broken.
I was dumped.
I thought it was something serious.
Out with the old,
in with the new.
As simple as that.
That's right.
Yan Yan knows many people.
All kinds of physiques.
Take your pick.
You two girls have quite a special way
to cheer people up.
Sister Yan Yan.
I want the type of girls
with big eyes, double eyelids,
and nice body shape.
That's picky.
But I think...
if I were you,
I would take action
and show them my determination.
You're right.
Prove myself with my actions.
You have to help me then.
How?
What is it?
Let's take a picture.
What does this have anything
to do with determination?
I'll post it on Moments.
That's right.
Post it on Moments.
This would give the impression
that I'm doing just fine
as if I wasn't hurt at all.
I think that's a good idea.
Sure it is.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
(A small gathering of three. How delightful.)
Chuan.
Have you seen the post on Moments?
What post?
This one.
Is this the pretty boy
that you talked about?
A heart hand gesture really? Look.
This is nothing.
It's just a normal
friend gathering.
We, too, have had
many gatherings with them.
But I've never seen them
posting it on Moments.
At times like this,
you can't remain so calm.
You just told me
that you like Jiang Xiao Ning.
This is the first time
you ever like someone.
You can't just sit here and do nothing.
No.
I haven't confessed to her.
Jiang Xiao Ning and I
are simply
boss and employee.
Still trying to act tough?
But
as a future designer,
she's too shallow.
You're right.
She is.
He has the look
but not that good looking.
Compared
to you and me,
he's still far from it.
Bad aesthetic judgments.
Poor taste.
That's right.
Look at his hairstyle.
Unbelievable.
The hair quality is just average.
Not only that,
they made the heart hand gesture.
It's fine if he did it
with Jiang Xiao Ning.
Why did he drag Yan Yan along?
Why is it fine to do it
with Jiang Xiao Ning
but shouldn't get Zhao Yan involved?
Neither is acceptable.
We have to win this round.
How about...
you confess
to Jiang Xiao Ning tomorrow?
No way.
What if Dr. Peer
couldn't come up with a solution
three months later?
What do I do then?
If Jiang Xiao Ning
and I are together,
and I end up like a waste of space.
It's bad for her.
That's a really lame excuse.
Just be honest.
Are you afraid
of being rejected by Jiang Xiao Ning
and that it's going to put you on the spot?
Look.
If you keep this going,
Jiang Xiao Ning
is going to be with someone else.
If a wimpy kid got her before you did,
that would be a real shame.
You come up with a way
to get this man out of the picture quickly.
Don't let him
revolve around Jiang Xiao Ning
and give him the opportunity
to become a part
of Yan Yan's social circle.
No matter what,
in these three months,
you can't let Jiang Xiao Ning
be with this guy.
You have to be with her
at all times
and protect her.
Wait.
Are you being concerned about me
or are you worried about Zhao Yan?
That's not the point.
The point is that
we can't just sit back and do nothing.
We have to take the lead
and get to the bottom of things.
Are you coming or not?
Are you sure this is the place?
Yes.
Why isn't he here yet?
You're right.
That's him.
Him?
Can he do it?
It'll be fine.
Hurry.
Cover me.
Hit the dragon.
Hurry.
You two go on.
Coming!
(Food Delivery)
Hi.
Are you Miss Zhao,
the Super Invincible Conquering Palms?
Here's your delivery.
Did you guys order a takeaway?
No.
Thank you.
A hangover soup?
Sir.
A moment, please.
What is it, sir?
Who accepted
the food delivery just now?
Are you a cop?
No.
If that's the case,
I can't disclose
the customer's personal information.
I'm a very professional
food delivery man.
What if I'm to tell you
that I am the one who placed the order
and that I can give you a bad rating?
What? Is this a threat?
How about this?
I won't ask you anything
and you don't have to answer me.
Just a nod or a headshake will do.
Was it a girl
who signed the receipt for the food?
Her last name is Zhao.
She's about
this tall.
She's not pretty
and has buck teeth, crossed eyes,
and big nostrils.
Says who?
She's gorgeous.
There are another girl
and a guy in the house, right?
I can't tell you that. No comment.
Fine.
You're quite tight-lipped.
How about this?
Let's talk.
I'll place a few more orders.
Make it ten.
I can tell you don't usually
order online food delivery.
What do you mean?
The orders are randomly assigned.
I'll make a remark
to have you deliver the food.
How about that?
That will do.
The customer is king.
King, huh?
If that's the case,
can I make a few more requirements?
I'm a...
Don't worry.
I know
you're a very professional
food delivery man.
I won't give you a hard time.
Coming.
Didn't you just leave?
Why are you here again?
May I know
if this is Miss Jiang's house,
the gentlest and cutest pretty girl
in the universe?
She's in bed already.
I didn't order any food delivery.
I'm not sure about that.
The address is correct.
If she's asleep, you can accept these for her.
Well, I'll accept them on her behalf then.
They're pretty heavy.
You're a girl.
You can't handle them.
Why don't you ask
your boyfriend
or husband
to get them?
I am a single young woman.
I have no boyfriend.
Let alone a husband.
Shall I bring them in for you?
Thank you.
Where should I put them?
In the house.
Sir.
If he keeps delaying,
all the following orders will be canceled.
Ignore him.
As for me,
I'll place
another 100 orders.
Well, 100 is a little exaggerating.
I'm a professional
food delivery man.
Fifty will do.
Fifty, huh?
All right.
Fifty it is. Whatever makes you happy.
I'm going up for a bit.
Wait here for me.
Boss?
Why are you here?
I'm here to look for Xu Cheng Ran.
He didn't answer my calls.
Is he here?
Chuan, help me! Chuan.
Chuan!
Boss, don't get us wrong.
I had a drink earlier
and slept for a while.
When I woke up,
I saw Director Xu came to find Sister Yan Yan
dressed up as a food delivery man.
And he said he was playing
a cosplay game.
A game?
Mr. Gu.
Would you like to join us?
I'll pass.
This game
doesn't look like my type.
I still have plenty of
design drafts to revise.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Are you going home?
I can give you a ride.
It's fine, Boss.
I'm crashing here tonight.
All right then. Well, I...
I'll leave you be. Later.
Chuan!
Wait for me!
Perfect.
Delightful.
Xiao Ning.
Let's go to bed.
Why did those two
seem so weird?
Gu Chuan, what a loyal friend you are.
If I hadn't escaped,
would you have
left me there?
Was I that bad?
Yes!
Your look, your body,
and your words have betrayed you!
You were going to leave me there.
How is that possible? You're overthinking it.
Thank you, brother.
You're my real brother.
Unlike some people.
I'll place another 100 orders
for you tomorrow.
Brother, that's so generous of you.
I'm a professional
food delivery man.
Feel free to ask me for anything.
Remember, 100 orders.
Actually, you can't blame me.
You offered
to deliver the food.
So?
Did you see anyone else?
Why should I tell you?
I risked my life going up there
yet you didn't care about me.
Ungrateful!
Actually, I already knew.
After you left,
that guy
left from the side entrance.
So nothing could possibly
happen up there.
Not possible?
That's because I was smart enough to escape.
If not, I would be screwed.
That's perfect, isn't it?
You could spend more time
with Zhao Yan.
You're right.
Why don't you send me up again?
Sure.
Hell no.
Drive.
Boss.
I would like to take a day off.
Having a meal with your friend again?
Yesterday was an exception.
I hope you don't mind.
Not at all.
Tell me.
Why do you need a day off?
The school-leaving examination is coming soon.
If I can't get the credits required
in time,
I won't get the graduation certificate
and the degree.
So I've registered for
an evening cram school
to make some progress in a short time.
I may not be able to take you home
on Wednesday, Thursday, and Friday nights.
Is that all right?
Of course.
But are there any buses available
so late at night after class?
It's fine.
After class, if it's too late,
I can ask Chen Chen to send me home.
If there's nothing else, I'll get back to my work.
Hold on.
Are there any spots left
in the cram class?
I don't know.
Why?
I'm thinking
to attend the class
or something.
Are you kidding me?
You're more than qualified to be a lecturer there.
I've worked for so long.
It's inevitable for my designs
to be too commercial.
It's time to be back in class
to feel the vibe again.
I can help you evaluate
if the cram school
is up to standard.
What's the matter?
No... Nothing.
Nothing?
It's settled then.
Get back to work.
Under normal circumstances,
a residential building
can be divided into many floors.
However, the architectural standard,
the coverage, and the layout
of each floor
are completely different.
Well, what is a building
with three floors or less called?
It's called a low-rise residential building.
Four to six floors...
(Her boss is here.)
multi-story residential building.
Seven to nine floors,
mid-rise residential building.
As for high-rise buildings,
the ones with ten or more than ten floors
are called high-rise residential buildings.
To be specific,
(Dinner tonight?)
low-rise residential buildings
refer to the ones of ten meters
or less in height,
They usually have
one to three floors,
such as bungalows and villas.
Generally, low-rise residential buildings
feature simple building structure,
a short construction period,
and low construction cost.
They give people a sense of familiarity
and tranquility.
They stand right on land
and not many floors are built upon it.
They offer better coziness, convenience,
and spatial scale
than those of high-rise buildings.
Therefore, people love to have them
as a residence.
However, low-rise residences occupy a lot of lands
and the land utilization rate is low.
In cities,
the land is extremely expensive.
which makes it difficult
to develop this type of residence extensively.
(I don't believe you can stop me.)
Generally,
people call buildings
with eight to twelve or thirteen floors
as small high-rise buildings.
Small high-rise residential buildings
generally adopt
the reinforced concrete structure
with elevators.
There are multiple stories in a small high-rise.
It gives people a sense of familiarity
and tranquility.
The house type is preferable
with a higher building efficiency ratio.
It also boasts high resilience
and high durability
as the ordinary high-rise structure.
(You Si Design School)
Both of the two young men.
What are you doing?
Stand up.
Get out if you don't want to attend this class.
Don't disrupt the order
of the classroom.
Those who weren't listening
should be the ones to leave.
So you were listening then?
Well, tell me then.
What is spatial sequence?
The latecomer should answer first.
OK, you tell us.
About that.
Spatial sequence...
It's actually very simple.
It's...
Well...
In this space...
I...
Spatial sequence.
A construction
is a tridimensional entity.
People can't see all of it
at a glance.
Therefore, in the process
of continuously moving
from one place
to another,
people can see its parts
little by little
and form
an overall impression.
That's the meaning of spatial sequence
in architecture.
Did you see that?
It's indeed very simple.
Not bad.
Tell us
what the elements of green buildings are.
There are many elements
of green buildings,
like source economy,
lower cost,
whole-life design,
people-oriented design,
design flexibility,
unity of traditional
and modern architecture,
unity of architectural theory
and environmental science.
Not bad.
You may sit down.
Thank you, sir.
Unfortunately,
you need to leave the classroom.
Let's not let them
interrupt the lesson.
So he's Gu Chuan?
That's right.
He is the Gu Chuan
who won the Jin An Award.
He's so handsome.
Let's move on to detached houses.
So handsome.
Pay attention.
Where were we?
A detached house
is a single residential building
for one family only.
Feeling hungry already?
It was fun going to class with you.
I had fun.
You left the lecturer dumbfounded.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Why are you still here?
Since I have nothing to do,
I might as well wait for you
to finish the class.
Wanna grab something to eat?
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Buy me a bottle of water.
Sure.
Look at you.
Instead of focusing in class,
why do you keep pestering Jiang Xiao Ning?
I think
something charming about her.
It makes you feel better
as soon as you see her.
If I can work
with her every day,
I don't mind working for free.
You won't get the chance.
Why?
Do you like her?
It's none of your business.
Well...
if you don't like
Jiang Xiao Ning
and this goes on,
she might not be yours.
If not mine,
whose will she be?
Mine, perhaps.
Where does your confidence come from?
Myself.
I know Jiang Xiao Ning
better than you do.
Boss, here's the water your want.
Okay.
Come on. I'll send you home.
Let's go.
Drive safely.
Study local culture
and bring modern art and historical traces...
If you don't like
Jiang Xiao Ning,
she might not be yours.
If not mine,
whose will she be?
Mine, perhaps.
I know Jiang Xiao Ning
better than you do.
So...
this is my rough idea.
What do you think?
Mr. Gu?
Go on, please.
I... I'm finished.
Shall I repeat it?
It's fine.
You may go now.
I'll come to you later.
Okay.
Brother Dong.
Boss.
Are you going to cram school today?
Yes.
Until before the exam.
I'll send you.
It's fine.
There are a lot of projects lately.
I'll just go there by bus.
It's too slow.
I'll send you.
End of discussion.
You may go now.
Well, thank you, Boss.
I've asked my lecturer.
He said you can't join the class.
It was fine last time.
Look who's talking.
The lecturer said you came to show off.
All right then.
Boss.
Are you going to drive back
by yourself?
Shall I call you a designated driver?
It's fine.
I'll take a walk nearby.
After that,
I'll drive back
on my own.
Can you?
Why don't you wait
until my class is over
and I'll send you home?
It's all right.
Go to class now
or you'll be late.
Well, I'll get going then.
The load-bearing structure
is very easy to remember.
Three types.
Two, thirteen.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Your boss really cares about you.
It's the load-bearing wall.
My boss always cares about me
and he's been very supportive of
me finishing my studies.
The load-bearing structure
is divided into 13 categories.
Could your boss
be in love with you?
I hope so.
Take a look in detail.
Do you like him?
I confessed to him before.
Then? What happened?
I guess he rejected me.
I don't stand a chance.
That's not for sure.
Before I came to class,
I saw him standing at the door.
Do you need my help?
Stop it.
Don't upset my boss.
Even if he rejected me,
I think we are good now.
Give it a try.
Just try it out.
Pay attention.
Don't distract me.
Have you learned
the things taught in class today?
Have you?
Of course.
Tell me
what you have learned today.
Let's have supper later.
No, thanks.
Boss.
You haven't left.
I just came back from a walk.
You're really something, Boss.
You could even take a walk for two hours.
Good for you!
I'll drive you home, okay?
Since your boss is here,
shall we
go for a late-night snack together?
I'm not hungry.
No?
What a coincidence.
Xiao Ning said she was hungry
and we were planning to have hotpot.
Well.
You may leave first.
I said...
Let's have hotpot.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Yes!
Drive.
I feel like having it now.
I'll lead the way. Follow me.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
What would you like to eat?
My boss can only
take food that is less oily,
less salty, and not spicy.
He's so picky.
I'm not picky.
It depends on my mood.
So you can eat anything?
No, he can't.
I can.
Boss.
You can't take this.
I'll order porridge for you.
It's fine.
Give me a glass of water.
How about beer?
I need to drive Jiang Xiao Ning home.
All right, then.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Get a big jug of water
and make sure it's cold.
Go.
Go on.
Pleasant to the eye.
Stop looking.
Looking at what?
Nothing.
Do you like her?
It's none of your business.
It is.
You can't.
Do you dare to?
It's boiling.
Here comes the water.
All right, you two.
It's not spicy.
Feels great!
Excuse me.
I'm going to the gents.
Afraid?
Who's afraid?
The oil got on my hands.
I'm going to wash it off.
I'm squeamish.
Give me water.
Water.
Serves you right.
Are you out of your mind?
If anything happens to him,
I'm going to kill you.
Jiang Xiao Ning,
I give it all out for you.
Why did the power go out?
Waiter!
The power went out!
Boss!
How are we going to eat?
(Don't worry.)
(I'm fine, really.)
(Boss.)
(It was my fault.)
(I shouldn't have made you wait for me)
(and let you have hotpot.)
(It's not your fault.)
(I was being gluttonous.)
(I promise)
(you won't see Chen Chen again.)
(He's too awful.)
(I used to be good at eating spicy food.)
(If it weren't for the power outage
at the hotpot restaurant,)
(we would have battled it out.)
(Why was there a power outage at the restaurant?)
(It's nothing.)
(Rest early.)
(I'm going to take a shower and rest.)
(See you tomorrow.)
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪