Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 19=
Help me put this pot
above the microwave,
I'll take care of the rest.
Thank you, Boss.
Okay.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
When we were eating,
I heard your aunt said
that your family was involved
in a car accident ten years ago?
Was that ten years ago today?
Yes.
Where was it?
It was on the way to the geopark.
It was my birthday that day.
My dad finally had time
to take me to Grandma's place.
But on the way there...
Dad! A car!
Do you remember
I told you that
I have
a big brother whom I miss a lot?
Actually,
that big brother was hit
and fell off the cliff with us.
It was really cold that night.
He was holding my hand
and encouraging me to stay alive.
He even sang the birthday song for me.
Although he sang in a really low voice,
I heard everything.
Make a wish.
The wishes
made on birthdays
always come true.
Happy birthday to you.
Hope you're happy every day.
Actually,
the birthday song you sang today
was a little special.
Boss,
what's wrong?
Nothing.
Have all the dishes been washed?
Let's go to the living room if everything's done.
We'll be leaving then.
Have a safe trip home.
Be happy!
Bye-bye.
Then...I'm leaving.
You go upstairs first.
You go first.
You first.
I'll wait till you get in the car.
When I get in the car,
you're going back up.
Hold on,
don't turn around yet.
♪July, summer♪
May I hug you for a while?
♪A scalding wave of heat♪
Today is the saddest day of my life,
but also the happiest.
In the past years,
I always spent this day by myself.
But today,
I celebrated my first birthday
in ten years.
Thank you for being with me.
♪Endless dreams♪
♪Pink rose, Diana♪
♪Heart wavering like green grass blades♪
It's me who should be saying "thank you".
Thank you
for letting me feel the warmth of a family.
Did you know?
I haven't been
in such an atmosphere
in ten years.
It feels
very warm and nostalgic.
♪You say hello as you smile♪
Are you really not sensitive to pain?
It's an after effect from
that car crash ten years ago.
Boss,
I'll work hard to be happy every day.
-I...
-Go ahead.
I just wanted to thank you
for accompanying me to the hospital today.
Actually,
I didn't mean to not tell you
my dad is Xu Guo Xiang.
He is your dad
whether you choose to tell me or not.
Relax,
I won't tell anyone.
That's not what I mean.
Anyway,
thank you for making me feel better.
You don't have to say it.
I know that you must hate me
even more now.
But I really didn't mean to
hide it from you.
You didn't give me a chance
to let me introduce myself to you.
It's unfair.
But now I know you,
Mr. Xu from Xun Lu Group.
Yes! That's me.
But please, I beg you.
Yan Yan, listen to me.
I beg you
to give me another chance.
Just one.
I'll prove that
I'm serious about you.
Please.
There is no need to beg.
Sure.
I'm saying...
yes.
No.
You said yes.
Did… did you agree?
Yan Yan,
you agreed!
Yan Yan!
Okay, calm down.
Sorry, I got too excited.
I'm telling you.
I'm warning you!
This chance is offered to Xu Cheng Ran,
not Mr. Xu from Xun Lu Group.
I know, I know.
I am Xu Cheng Ran.
Xu Cheng Ran is me.
Why don't you just
stay for the night.
Sure.
Drive safely on the way home.
Remember to think about me.
Yan Yan, I love you.
Are you sure you want to
drink coffee this time of the day?
I'm afraid that you won't be able to sleep.
If it's not for Gu Chuan,
this brat who doesn't care about his life at all,
(Mechanical heart valve)
I won't be working this hard.
If I don't make these improvements possible
for his mechanical heart,
I'm afraid that the world
will lose a top-tier architect
in the near future.
But...
you haven't had a breakthrough
in a long time.
This is the nature of my job.
Maybe I won't make any progress in ten years,
or
I will make a
major breakthrough.
You still have to rest when you need to.
You have to alternate work with rest.
Alright.
Let's call it a day.
Breakthrough.
This is the breakthrough!
Right when I needed it.
Charging completed.
Hello?
Hi, Gu Chuan.
I'm going to tell you something.
Promise me you will
control your emotions.
Don't get so excited
that you destroy your own house.
Go on.
I'm in the charging station right now.
It's safe.
Since the last episode
of your excessive electric discharge,
I've been doing different calculations
in the lab
to try to find a solution to that whole series of
errors.
However,
nothing happened.
But,
just now,
a moment ago,
the moment that I turned off my computer,
everything changed!
So you're saying that...
All of the side effects
of your mechanical heart,
the noise, the electric discharge,
and everything else
have been solved!
There are only a couple of issues left.
Give me some time
and I'll be able to fix everything.
From then on,
you can start
living
like a normal person again.
No way.
Are you serious?
I swear to god
with my whole career,
my assets,
and my thesis,
this is true.
How long would that take?
Three months.
Maximally three months.
I'm here.
I just got home when you called me.
What's up?
I'm coming in now.
No way, what a coincidence.
What if you mistook her for someone else
and everything just isn't true?
Today is Jiang Xiao Ning's birthday.
Ten years ago today,
we were both
in the car accident.
Are you sure
it was the same car accident?
Yes.
So you're saying
the girl you saved
ten years go...
is Jiang Xiao Ning.
It's such a small world.
I know, right?
I couldn't believe it either.
And you two just
ran into each other like this.
Not just running into each other.
What else?
Don't leave yet.
Go on.
I don't want to keep running away.
I…
-So you like her?
I knew it.
Why didn't you tell her?
Who would accept a boyfriend
with a mechanical heart
that can discharge electricity at any time?
How long do you
plan to wait?
Three months.
The doctor said that
he will fix
every single problem
that the mechanical heart has.
At that time,
I can live
just like a normal person.
Really?
You're saying
after three months,
I won't have to drive you,
help you drink,
or stare at my phone all day
worrying about your heart rate?
Yes.
And that I won't have to worry about
you fainting because the battery is running low.
And that I don't need to worry about
seeing your suicide note
your organ donation card,
or you just disappear suddenly?
You're right.
That's great!
This is so sudden.
I don't even know
how we should celebrate this.
Let's do this.
We're telling Jiang Xiao Ning
that you like her, now.
How can I do that now?
I should wait for
three more months.
Look at you, so patient.
If I were you,
I must be running towards her now.
Destiny decided that
you two will come back to each other.
This means
she is the one for you.
To be honest,
I felt different
when I
first saw her.
Ten years ago,
I had a new chance
for life.
And when the day
all problems of the mechanical heart are fixed
and can work perfectly
finally comes,
it will be
another chance for me to start  afresh.
I have never
looked forward to that day this much
like I am
right now.
The destiny of you two
is just magical.
Oh, right.
The car accident that you just mentioned
has reminded me of something.
Does it mean that
Jiang Xiao Ning's father
was the one involved in
the Dong Jiang corruption case?
Jiang Guang Da?
How did you know about this?
My dad worked for Dong Jiang too.
After the corruption case,
the whole company
was in a chaotic situation.
My dad quit
and started his own business.
He also adopted
his colleague's son.
Tang Xu.
Tang Xu and Jiang Xiao Ning
grew up together.
Your dad adopted Tang Xu.
Does that mean
the three of them knew each other?
Maybe.
The world is just so small.
I'll ask my dad if I get a chance.
Okay, ask your dad when you get a chance.
Now,
do you want to go grab a drink?
Now?
Let's wait till your heart is totally fixed.
I really want to drink now.
If you aren't there to watch me,
I'll probably end up
like I did last time.
Okay.
I'll get to decide how much you drink.
Sure.
♪Woke up feel like a superstar♪
♪You know what you are♪
♪Fireflies all around♪
♪The smile will never cease♪
♪Like feeling the stars♪
♪Believe that good things will happen even without luck♪
♪The journey is on and I'm running to you ♪
♪I saw it all♪
♪So empty♪
♪The people around♪
♪Their feelings♪
Good morning, Boss.
Morning.
♪One, two, three, count with me♪
♪If youth is precious, then cheers♪
Boss,
am I not the one driving?
I'm in a good mood today.
I'll drive.
But driving
is a part of my job.
I said I'm in a good mood.
Are you trying to destroy that?
♪One, two, three, count with me♪
What's wrong, Boss?
Why aren't you wearing the hairpin?
I was in a rush this morning
and forgot to use it.
I'll put it on now.
♪You are the most perfect when full of vitality♪
♪One, two, three♪
Does it look good?
♪Those blazing dreams, follow my command♪
Let's go.
♪Four, five, six♪
♪Chase recklessly, long live the young♪
♪You are the most perfect when full of vitality♪
Boss looks different today.
Nothing's different.
Just like every other day.
You guys never notice anything.
Out of all these years,
have you seen Boss like this before?
Of course, I see him every day.
Right,
there must be something going on!
Boss was like autumn before.
Today's Boss
feels more like spring.
Spring?
(Chuan Design Studio)
Are you playing Landlords?
I think you're just overthinking this.
(Chuan Design Studio)
Don't you think that
Boss is
(Chuan Design Studio)
surprisingly different today?
Not really.
It's odder to think all day
that some rich guy
wants to date you.
Qi Hong.
Miss Su.
Did you keep the profiles
of all the job applicants?
Here.
It's here.
Okay.
(Jiang Guang Da's Corruption Case News)
Miss Su.
Miss Su, are you okay?
Qi Hong.
How can you be so careless
as an HR?
What did I do?
Did something happen?
Jiang Guang Da.
Who is that?
Do you not know Jiang Guang Da?
The architect from
Dong Jiang Architecture ten years ago.
The one that smuggled...
Lower your voice.
smuggled millions of money?
Is that the one?
He's Jiang Xiao Ning's dad.
This case
had such a bad impact
on the entire construction industry.
How could you not have done
any background checks
and just let her in?
Not to mention that
she's Mr. Gu's assistant.
If our peers
find out that
we've hired someone
with a background like this,
how would they see us?
What if it gets posted online?
Have you ever thought about what the media would say?
I apologize, Miss Su.
It was my problem indeed.
But Jiang Xiao Ning
was here because you...
What did I do?
You referred her.
I didn't think there would be a problem
because
you were the one who referred her.
So I didn't do any background checks.
Alright.
I'll see what we can do.
Oh, my god.
Jiang Guang Da.
(Jiang Guang Da related news)
Oh, my god.
(Dong Jiang Group's Criminal Corruption Case)
What?
You're saying
Jiang Xiao Ning is the daughter of an embezzler.
Keep it low.
Are you trying to get me fired?
Why did no one find out about it earlier?
I'm an HR,
not a spy.
But this event
had a great impact
on the entire industry.
It was your fault too.
How can you lie about this?
Jiang Xiao Ning
did cover herself up well though.
No wonder why
she never talked about her family.
She rode such a fancy car
on her first day of work.
That guy
is still giving her rides.
It takes some effort to be able to do that.
You're right.
Kids do grow up a little faster
in families like this.
You're right.
I grew up with him.
He's like my own brother.
It's not like what you think.
Xiao Ning, don't get us wrong.
We just heard it
so we were
gossiping about it for a bit.
My dad is not a criminal.
Please apologize.
Xiao Ning.
It is definitely our fault
to talk behind your back.
But your dad's case
is already decided on a verdict.
We're not making things up.
Plus,
if your dad didn't do all those things,
Dong Jiang Group
would not have ended up like that.
The company went bankrupt.
The money that
your dad embezzled
was mostly pension
and compensation
for those who left their jobs.
Do you have any idea
the number of people who were affected?
Many of them couldn't even afford a meal.
I did not wrong him.
I'm repeating this one more time.
My dad is not a criminal.
Xiao Ning,
it was such a big event.
You could look it up
anywhere online.
I didn't make things up.
Chill, chill.
Let's not talk about this
in the workspace.
We're all colleagues, don't…
I'm speaking the truth.
That isn't the truth.
My dad is not a criminal.
You must apologize.
There's no need to talk anymore.
Apologize.
Jiang Xiao Ning, what do you want now?
Let's not do this.
Let go.
Apologize.
I told you to let go, did you not hear me?
Let go!
Calm down, calm down.
Let's all calm down.
Apologize.
Jiang Xiao Ning, are you crazy?
What are you all doing?
-You pushed me?!
-Mr. Gu.
Mr. Gu.
Qi Hong,
we've worked together
for so many years.
What's wrong with you today?
Why did you disclose
the confidential information of our employees?
If I knew earlier
that my HR manager
is someone like this,
should I
think this through
and see if
I can find a better fit?
Mr. Gu,
I made a mistake today.
This will be the last
and the only time.
Sorry, Mr. Gu.
I'm not the one you should apologize to.
Apologize to Jiang Xiao Ning.
I'm sorry, Xiao Ning.
I made a mistake today.
I'm sorry.
Alright, alright.
Don't be angry with me.
Xiao Ning,
I was just gossiping around.
You know
what kind of person I am.
Don't take it personally.
Mr. Gu,
what caused the
style change recently?
I'm talking about your clothes.
Did I change?
To be more accurate,
you changed back to what you were like before.
Before?
Don't tell me you are changing the style
of your architecture design as well.
Can't say for sure.
You really have changed a lot.
You got so mad in the meeting room
and now you're so relaxed and laughing.
You look like a different person.
Isn't this better?
Is there anything else?
No.
If so, I'll get back to my work.
Boss,
let me drive.
Don't worry,
I'm okay.
Promise I'll drive safely.
Get in the car.
(Parking lot)
(Tomorrow is the weekend.)
(Let me take you somewhere.)
(I'll pick you up at 10.)
(Sure, Boss.)
(A date tomorrow.)
(Sure.)
Yes, yes!
Charging.
I got this.
I got this tomorrow.
Let's go!
Boss,
did something happen recently?
Is there any good news?
Why do you say that?
Your vibe
got much more charismatic,
like way more!
Have you had breakfast yet?
Not yet.
I knew it.
I got you breakfast.
And I knew that
you would have something prepared for me.
Would you like to have some before we leave?
I'll eat later.
Let's go, I'm driving today as well.
Sure.
Where are we going?
You'll know when we get there.
Where are you heading, girl?
I can give you a ride.
You're late.
No,
I got here a while ago.
I was watching you from upstairs.
If you are late again,
don't come anymore.
I was stuck in traffic.
Don't be mad.
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
You asked me out
and now you want to say where we're going?
Are you doing this or not?
I just want to know
if you have
a specific place in mind.
Of course,
my house.
Get in the car, let's go.
I'll take you to wherever I decide.
That sounds better.
She likes the dominating style.
Boss, Boss, Boss.
Is this a prank?
I can't believe you're taking me here
knowing that I'm so unlucky.
You said
you were absolutely horrible at this, didn't you?
You can catch
as many as you want today.
You remembered everything I said?
You're thinking too much.
You speak too much.
No one can remember all of them.
Stop trying, Boss.
That is mission impossible.
The exhibition will end by the end of this month.
Thank god we're here today.
I know.
I've always wanted to come.
I know that too.
How do you know?
You posted on both
Weibo and WeChat.
You did your homework.
Of course.
Are you trying to please me
by taking me here?
Not really.
I work in
an art-related field.
Me being here for appreciating aesthetics
should be completely normal.
Also,
I'm your boyfriend.
It's my job
to make my girlfriend happy.
I'm not your girlfriend.
Not again.
I thought we talked about this that day?
I said to give you a chance
to prove yourself.
I didn't say that
you're my boyfriend.
What?
Great.
I think so too.
Would you like to try that?
That one.
-Try this.
-This one?
Move to the right a little bit.
Forward, forward, forward.
Right, right.
Too much, too much.
Go lighter.
To the right.
Move it little by little.
I told you to go right a little bit.
It's all your fault.
I couldn't focus.
My fault?
No way.
How can I blame my boss?
Talk.
You told me to shut up.
Look at you.
I'm just sad.
Don't try to act cute.
May I talk?
Yes.
Yesterday, you agreed that...
You could say anything except for that.
Then I'll stop talking again.
Why didn't I realize
you are this compliant?
I was trying to irritate you.
Why?
I like you but you always ignored me.
So I just wanted
to get your attention.
Take a picture for me.
Come here.
Smile.
Let me help.
It's okay, Boss.
It's okay.
Why don't you try that one?
That one is easier.
(It will all be good luck
after we get through those bad days)
Boss,
maybe I should just give up.
Give it a try.
Come on.
Give it another try.
It's just a picture.
Am I
your boyfriend now?
No.
Then what am I now?
Candidate.
How can I pass the test?
It depends on your performance.
How should I perform to pass?
I don't know.
There has to be a standard.
My standard is...
There is none.
Just following my feelings.
What do you mean?
You don't have to if you don't want to.
Don't want to? Impossible.
Whatever my baby says.
Don't call me baby.
Whatever my darling says.
Not darling either.
My queen.
Whatever you say.
Okay.
Drive me home now.
Of course!
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Chen Chen.
Why are you here?
If I say
this is because
I can connect with you
and came by following your vibes,
would you believe me?
No.
Is this your friend?
This is Chen Chen.
You've met each other
at the convenience store.
We studied the same major in university.
I remember now.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Boyfriend?
No, this is my boss.
Mr. Gu.
Boss.
Her boss.
Hello.
Try again.
Xiao Ning,
are you still studying architectural design?
I've been studying by myself.
I've registered for this class.
It's in the evenings.
Shall we be study buddies?
Let me think about it.
A little to the right.
It's all your fault!
You kept talking to me.
Let me do this.
I can't even watch.
Watch carefully.
What happened?
The power is out.
I almost got it.
I was this close.
(It will all be good luck
after we get through those bad days)
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night~~♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪