[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 13]
By the way,
come over to my house for dinner tomorrow.
I will invite a few friends over
for a welcome back party.
Fine, stop dilly-dallying.
Can you please hurry up?
Put on your shoes and go.
Go, go.
Such a small world, Ms Ma!
Come on in, Shan Shan.
Yes, come in, come in.
Hi.
Ma...
Ms Ma, I hope you didn't pinch your feet.
Come in and have a seat.
I remember you like
to drink hot chocolate.
Here you go, your earphones.
Thank you.
So how have you been?
I'm good.
You attended the homecoming?
How was it?
The students were enthusiastic.
Speaking of which, Mr Qin spoke of you.
He said you were his best student.
I should go back
to see him sometime.
I will come with you.
I mean, did you see him
when you were there?
I hadn't noticed.
I should go now. I have some things to do.
So soon? Don't you
want to stay a bit longer?
I'm on the clock.
Let me walk you out.
Ms Ma!
Ms Ma, Ms Ma.
Are you going home alone?
Yes, obviously.
Ms Ma, I mean...
It's the weekend, and it isn't
easy to order a taxi.
So?
So I was wondering if
you could give me a lift?
My home isn't very far from here.
I...
Get in the car, Ms Ma.
Get in.
I'd never imagine that
you and Orange were classmates.
If she had told me earlier,
wouldn't we have met already?
Have you ever heard about the
six-dimensional space theory?
Also known as six degrees
of separation theory?
It's a theory that anyone on the planet
can be connected to anyone else
through just five intermediaries.
So...
To sum it up,
I think we can become
close friends.
As...
As the saying goes,
the more friends you have,
the more options you'll have in life.
When we were acting together last time,
we were quite a team.
Am I right, Ms Ma?
[Radio broadcast.]
[Traffic broadcast.]
[Let's hear the power of love.]
By the way,
Orange and the other guys
are coming over to my
place for dinner tomorrow.
Feel free to join us if you have time.
It's just us friends.
I...
This...
Officer,
were you calling me?
Your identity card, please.
So you're Sun Bin Yu?
Yes, that's me.
What's going on?
Did you book a taxi?
Are police nowadays driving taxis too?
Not only do we provide hire car service,
we also offer day trips
to the police station.
Are you serious?
Here's the thing.
The taxi driver couldn't
get through to you.
And he saw that you were
moving fast on the GPS.
He called the cops because he
thought you might be in danger.
This is all a misunderstanding.
I was in my friend's car.
I thought it was a prank call.
Be more mindful next time.
The taxi driver wasn't
worried about his business,
he was worried about your safety.
Yes, yes.
The taxi driver
is truly a caring citizen.
I will send him a silk banner later.
You look kind of familiar.
Have we met before?
As humble as I am,
I'm actually a famous actor.
Really?
Yes, I'm the real deal.
Then that's all the more reason
you should lead by example
and pay attention to your public image.
Right, right.
I have to set a good example
for all my fans.
I think your friend is leaving.
Ms Ma!
Ms Ma! Ms Ma!
Don't leave me here.
Ms Ma!
We haven't set a deal for tomorrow!
Ms Ma! Ms Ma! Ms Ma...
It's truly my honour.
Thank you, officers.
Thank you for giving me a ride home.
You're welcome. It's our
duty to serve the people.
You should be careful not
to repeat such actions again.
Don't mislead your viewers.
Got it.
Officers,
why don't I take a picture with you?
I shouldn't let you come
all this way for nothing.
Come on.
Officer, take the phone.
You do it.
Maybe you should do it.
Lu Jing,
come here, help us take a photo.
Here.
Make sure we look nice.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Nice.
Okay, we should go now.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
Are you going in
or did you just come out?
Watch it!
Liang Chen is coming to
my place for dinner tomorrow.
I might just tell her
embarrassing stories about you.
Jing.
Jing, what are you doing?
I say, Jing,
stop playing with Uncle, okay?
If you keep doing that,
you're going to pull out all its hairs.
You hear me?
Give it to me, give it to me.
Come here, come here.
Jing, you're always either
reading books
or playing with my baby.
Shouldn't you go get yourself a girlfriend
and start dating?
I...
I'm working on it.
Working on it?
I want to see you take action.
Let's go, good boy.
[This is my house.]
[I certainly can't let you cook.]
[Let's wait for Ding.]
[We will wait to try Jing's cooking then.]
What are you looking at?
Why didn't you go in?
Nothing.
How is it, Ding?
The brisket today is going to impress you.
It smells so nice.
It will taste even better
with some coriander.
Authentic.
I'll serve this up first.
Ding, hurry up and come out.
Not only do Jia Yun's dishes taste great,
they're presented well, too.
Here comes the last dish.
Where is the coriander?
Didn't I put some in just now?
If you add coriander,
that's the end of our friendship.
Okay, come on.
Thank you all for coming
to my humble abode today.
We have fine food,
fine wine, a beauty
and handsome guys like us...
That's enough.
Can we eat already?
-Cheers.
Here we go.
Jing,
I'm making three-ingredient
dumplings today.
Eat more of this later.
Do we have any vinegar?
Your grandfather has
used up the vinegar.
We don't need vinegar for
three-ingredient dumplings.
Vinegar will drown out the savory taste.
I'm craving vinegar today.
Okay, I'll ask your grandpa to buy one.
Grandma,
I will go.
Okay, go on then.
It's superb.
Isn't it?
I'll go and check it out.
You guys dig in.
-It's delicious.
-How is it?
This pork ribs with glutinous
rice taste really good.
What do you want?
I need to borrow some vinegar.
It's in the kitchen. Help yourself.
Jia Yun, you haven't
gotten rusty at all.
It's really delicious.
Have some more.
Orange,
my little brother is handsome, isn't he?
What are you talking about?
He's just a young boy.
Right, Director He?
Yes, yes, just a young boy.
Young boy.
Here, Ding.
Here, have some shrimp.
Close the door on your way out.
That boy
is really strong.
Here.
Director He,
here's a toast to you.
Without you,
we wouldn't have been able to
finish the film so smoothly.
I've known you for so many years,
you are still as superficial
as you used to be.
By the way, that boy just now...
I'll go.
What do you want this time?
My grandma asked me to borrow some garlic.
Go on, go on.
It's in the refrigerator. Help yourself.
Have some greens.
Sorry about that.
It's okay, it's okay.
Cheers, Director He.
Thank you, Jia Yun.
I can manage.
Okay, sorry.
What's wrong with him?
Come on, eat some dishes.
Your door is very solid.
So is my refrigerator.
Come on, cheers.
Cheers.
Interesting.
Here comes my chance.
Beware, you guys.
Hurry up.
That little brat.
Your grandma hasn't finished cooking?
It's 9 p.m. now, man.
She's making a midnight snack.
What do you want to borrow this time?
-A pan.
-A pan?
You're telling me you
want to borrow a pan?
Any problem with that?
My grandma is getting old.
She forgot where she put her pan.
Unless your grandma
put her pan in the closet,
there was no way she couldn't find it.
Fine. Come in.
It's in the kitchen. Go help yourself.
Come on, let's carry on.
A pair of sixes.
-A pair of sevens.
-Hold on.
Let her play the cards.
Hold on, no.
Let her play it.
No.
Play it.
Think before you play.
What's there to think about?
Here you go.
Triple plus one.
Don't touch it, don't touch it!
You can't take it back.
It's on the table now.
I made a mistake.
Don't touch it. I got you. Four jacks!
Triple plus one? Game over.
This...
You lost. It's still your treat tomorrow.
It's getting late now.
I have another date.
-I have to go now.
-Okay.
Okay, bye-bye.
Hey, are you leaving just like this?
Goodbye.
I can't believe I lost.
Ding, now that he's left,
let's play two more
rounds with just the three of us.
Two more rounds. Come on.
Jing,
why did you bring back a pan?
It's a gift from the
washed-up actor next door.
I think it's used.
Look, it's oily inside.
They are having
braised beef brisket
with potatoes tonight.
I'm going to return
this stupid pot to him.
What a coincidence, Liang Chen.
Indeed. Do you live here?
Let's go.
How are you getting home?
I'm going to book a taxi.
What about your chauffeur?
I gave him the day off.
Let me give you a ride home then.
My house is nearby.
All the more reason I should take
you home and save you the trouble.
You're done with the pan so soon?
My grandma found her pan.
Congratulations.
Would you like to
borrow anything else then?
How come you've stopped borrowing stuff
since Liang Chen left?
You're nuts.
Who's nuts?
You've knocked on my
door several times tonight.
Get real.
That is Liang Chen.
What's that look on your face?
You're not really thinking
of courting her, are you?
She's surrounded by popular celebrities.
Aren't you cold? You're wearing so little.
I'm fine.
Put some warm clothes on, Liang Chen.
You're not as strong and healthy
as young people, after all.
He is your fan, isn't he?
Probably.
Young fanboys these
days can be really bold.
The more people adore us,
the greater our responsibility.
But even if they idolise a celebrity,
young people should still have
their priorities straight.
It'd be improper if they
have some unrealistic expectations.
I used to have unrealistic
expectations too.
For example,
I wanted to be a singer.
Our ride is here.
[Put some warm clothes on, Liang Chen.]
[You're not as strong and healthy
as young people, after all.]
Check.
Was that
Ding Jia Yun last night?
Yes.
He and Liang Chen seemed close.
They are close.
I mean,
one of them is an actor,
the other one is a singer.
Why are they so close?
When it comes to a man and a woman, it's
either because they have much in common
or...
No, I made a wrong move.
Let me take it back.
Finish your sentence first.
Or they
have feelings for each other.
Yes, this is the right move.
Checkmate.
[Orange]
Hey, what are you doing right now?
I'm busy. What do you want?
Are you at home?
Yes, just tell me what you want.
Nothing.
I'm hanging up, bye-bye.
What was that about?
[What are you doing right now?]
[Playing with my dog at home.]
Hurry up.
You gave me a fright!
Why are you here?
I just stopped by to see you.
Stopped by?
I'm busy now. I don't have time for you.
Wait. Since I'm here already,
just let me inside.
I'm here to return something.
Return what?
Is this mine?
I don't remember giving you this stuff.
It's your neighbour's.
That young boy lent this to me last night.
He went to see you off yesterday?
No, the wind was strong last night.
So he lent me his coat.
The wind was strong, was it?
What's with that weird look on your face?
What's wrong with that?
Let me tell you, I'm pretty
and I have a sweet voice.
What's wrong with lending me a coat?
He probably wanted to give me
a big hug too.
I have stuff to do. I should go now.
Since you've come all this way,
why don't you sit down for a while?
Come on.
I don't want to.
Just for a while. It's not like
you haven't met him before.
You just told me that
he probably wanted to give you...
What was it again?
A big...
Here you go.
What were you guys doing just now?
It's such a coincidence.
You came after we had just
finished two rounds of chess.
Carry on with your game then.
I should go now.
Liang Chen,
didn't you say you came
to return something?
Yes, yes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You shouldn't have, Liang Chen.
You should keep it.
I should keep it?
[How can I keep it?]
I'd better keep your
token of appreciation then.
[Token of appreciation?]
[What does that mean?]
You are indeed pretty and your voice
is indeed sweet.
I was just joking.
Do you like to joke, Liang Chen?
I do.
That's what friends do among themselves.
Right, Taro?
But I tend to take things seriously.
Then I'll joke less in the future.
Aren't you guys tired
from all this talking?
It's like you're doing a stand-up comedy.
Have a seat and drink some water.
I've got some stuff to do.
I'm leaving.
Okay, bye.
I will walk her out.
Let me walk you out.
Help me throw the garbage
away on your way out then.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
Liang Chen,
are you fantasising about an
elevator malfunction scenario?
No.
Good.
You've been staring at the
alarm for quite some time.
What? Should I be staring at you instead?
Sure.
[How did he manage to say such things]
[without blushing?]
Thank you for walking me out.
Bye-bye.
Liang Chen,
do you want a...
No, no.
Ms Qing,
what brings you here?
I've approved Ke Ke's
annual leave this week.
Finally.
What did you bring me?
I brought you Doubendou Soymilk.
Have a bottle to replenish your nutrients.
Thanks.
The live stream of Beautiful Soul
is going to kick off soon.
Are you ready for it?
Honestly,
my gaming ability
isn't good.
If you really can't handle it,
ask Sun Bin Yu to lead you in the game.
I can do that?
The organisers intended to find someone
to team up with you.
They even asked me for recommendations.
I have an immature little suggestion.
Hello.
[Hello.]
I am Liang Chen's manager, Liu Yi Qing.
Is this Mr Herman?
Yes, how can I help you?
Here's the thing.
I would like to invite you to join
the live stream promotion of
Beautiful Soul with Liang Chen.
I wonder if you would
be interested in joining?
I need to discuss this
with someone very important to me.
[Can I reply later?]
Sure, I'll wait for your call. Thank you.
Someone important?
It's 3 p.m. now. I have a phone meeting.
Someone very important?
Who?
So it's me.
[Liang Chen's manager called me just now.]
[She invited me to join Liang Chen in
the live stream of Beautiful Soul.]
[Say yes then.]
Trying to get me to lead you
by using another account?
Nice try.
[Doesn't it bother you that
I'm leading another girl?]
Should I tell him that
I am Liang Chen?
No, no.
I can't tell him.
[I don't mind. Go right ahead.]
[But it bothers me.]
[You're my only pupil.]
[How can I simply team up with others?]
[So]
[I'd better reject Liang Chen's offer.]
[Sadako, Sadako!]
[Goodness, Sadako!]
[You're so well nourished.
How can you die?]
[Sadako...]
[There are socks in the
house I haven't washed.]
[Can you wash it for me?]
[Sure. I will wash it all.]
[As long as you don't die.
Please don't die.]
[Don't die. Hang it there.]
[Hang in there.]
[Don't die now. Not now.]
Hello.
Do the live stream with me.
You don't even bother to start the
conversation with a greeting now?
I'm in no mood for this. Yes or no?
No.
I have a reputation to keep.
Taro, you disappointed me.
Are you that upset?
Let me give you a solution.
Talk to my little brother.
[He'd be happy to help.]
He turned me down.
[What?]
He turned you down?
That shouldn't be.
Why?
Isn't he your fan?
Being in the same room with his idol
is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
How could he not appreciate it?
[You're my only pupil.]
[How can I simply team up with others?]
[So]
[I'd better reject Liang Chen's offer.]
It's a complicated story.
I've got to go.
I'll figure this out on my own. Bye.
I wonder what Ding is doing.
He's probably really free.
Ding,
our girl Liang Chen
is having a big problem right now.
Don't you think we should
give her a little help?
[Ding Jia Yun]
Hello, Jia Yun.
Hello, Liang Chen.
Do you need my help with the live stream?
What a coincidence, Lu Jing.
Have you eaten?
No.
You actually turned down your
idol's invitation to do the live stream.
I'm waiting for her to beg me
when she fails to find anybody.
Young boy, you're still too young.
Do you really think Liang Chen won't
be able to find someone to help her?
She invited you?
No.
She's going to invite the
more capable one, of course.
Ding Jia Yun?
You may be terrible at making choices,
but you're pretty good at guessing.
Jia Yun,
it is just an ordinary live stream.
I don't want to trouble you.
It's fine. I've got time.
It really is no big deal.
I don't want to trouble you.
Chen Chen.
Jia Yun, hold on.
-What's the matter?
-Herman called.
He said he wants to do
the live stream with you.
He said yes?
Really?
Okay, one moment.
[Hello, Jia Yun.]
Hello.
[Ms Qing has settled it for me.]
But thank you anyway.
No worries.
That settles it, then.
Bye-bye.
He said yes!