[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 14]
Jia Yun. It's just an ordinary
live stream.
I really shouldn't bother you.
It's fine. I happen to be free.
But it's really just a small matter.
I shouldn't drag you in it.
Chen Chen.
Jia Yun.
Hold on a second.
What's the matter?
Herman called.
He agreed to go live with you.
He agreed?
Really?
Give me a second.
[Hello? Jia Yun.]
Hello?
[Ms Qing has arranged everything.]
Thank you anyway.
You're welcome.
Talk to you next time.
Bye.
He finally agreed.
Team up with others?
In your dreams.
This way, Ms Liang.
This way.
Ms Liang.
That is our control room.
This is the streaming room
we specially prepared for you.
Let us know if you need anything else.
Everything looks good.
You can have a seat here.
Get yourself familiar with the computer.
What about this table?
This is for the player
you're teaming up with today.
Don't worry.
The camera will only be facing you.
He won't be on screen.
Wait a minute.
He's sitting in the same room?
Yes.
He can see me?
You have a pretty face.
Why are you afraid to be seen?
You're free to relax in here.
I'll continue with my work now.
Thank you.
What's the schedule today?
We're now going to the location
for the commercial shoot.
The journey takes two hours.
We will head back right after the shoot.
Is there a problem, boss?
No.
Give me the tablet.
Are you going to watch
Ms Liang's live stream?
When we contacted you,
you said you weren't available.
The world is always changing.
Who knows what can happen
in a month?
Ms Liang...
Ms Liang Chen.
You're here.
Hello. Hi.
I'm the commentator today.
Hello.
Liu Shun, it's about time.
We're going to start now.
Good luck on the game later.
Good luck.
Senior.
We meet again.
Yes.
Are you nervous?
No, I'm not.
Don't worry.
I'll back you up later.
I won't embarrass you.
Are you two ready?
We can start now.
Aren't you giving me a game account?
Game account?
I forgot, Ms Liang.
Please give me a minute.
You are not planning to use
your own game account?
Are you afraid people would recognise you?
What do you mean?
I mean
your fans.
Are you afraid they'd know it's you?
Yes.
[Streaming Room]
[On Air]
Alright. Ready.
Three, two, one.
Start.
Hello, everybody.
I'm Liu Liu Da Shun,
the hottest commentator in town.
The mission begins.
Let's see what Liang Chen is doing.
Hello, everyone.
I'm Liang Chen.
I'm Herman.
[What can I do
so that he won't figure out]
[I'm Little Box?]
Sorry for interrupting.
Follow me closely.
Looks like Liang Chen
is pulling a Leeroy Jenkins.
Don't be affected.
He's clueless.
What we're doing is a strategic retreat.
Go.
There are too many robots
on this level.
Do you have a strategy?
Go in and blow them up.
We're low on grenades.
Take this submachine gun.
It's the King of Close Combat.
Then we'll go in
and put up a good fight.
I'll follow your command.
[This is the hardest part of the mission.]
[Can Herman and Liang Chen
withstand the pressure]
and complete this test?
Let's watch and see.
Don't worry.
Three, two, one.
Why are you looking at me?
The way you shoot was cool just now.
I would like to learn from you.
Well, maybe I can teach you.
[Overall Assessment]
[Task Completion Time, 28 mins 41 secs]
[Number of robots eliminated, 38]
Don't you find them weird during the game?
Were they flirting?
[Streaming Room]
[On Air]
Lu Jing.
What's up with you two?
You looked like love birds.
Hello.
That was perfect.
Looks like inviting Ms Liang Chen
to this game streaming session
was a very smart choice.
Today's views have hit the roof.
I believe
through today's live stream,
many more people will understand
our world ladder tournament.
Our gaming industry
will be given a boost.
Thank you, Mr Lin.
I owe it to everyone here.
Herman.
He is outstanding.
Of course, our commentator did great too.
Thank you for the praise, senior.
You know each other?
He's my junior from school.
We met at our school's
anniversary celebration.
What a coincidence.
Your chemistry was great.
Viewers might think
you play with each other regularly.
No, this was our first time.
It's our first collaboration, right?
Yes, I was surprised too.
It almost felt like
we've been teaming up
everyday.
[I didn't expect Herman and Liang Chen]
[would complete the mission so quickly.]
[Congratulations to them.]
The collaboration between Ms Liang
and that guy seems good.
The streaming seems to be a success.
Sorry for keeping everyone waiting.
Today,
I want to thank everyone here.
I've prepared an after-party
to celebrate this success.
I hope everyone here can join.
Are you going?
It would be great if you can join.
Since I'm free, why not.
Alright.
I'll join too.
What was that?
You knew your schedule is tight.
Can we put work aside for a while?
I want to relax a little.
Alright.
I still have work.
I'll head back to the office now.
You can have the car.
Oh, right.
What's up with Herman?
I kept getting a weird feeling
about the way he looks at you.
Really?
It feels like you two are close.
You must be mistaken.
Well, maybe I am.
I'm going now.
Be safe. Bye.
Alright.
[We thank Liang Chen and Herman]
[for an exciting streaming session.]
[At the same time,
we hope you can give your support]
[to the Beautiful Soul.]
[But do remember.]
[Reasonable gaming boosts your brain,
excessive gaming burns your body.]
[Make sure you manage your time wisely]
[so you can enjoy a healthy life.]
[This is the end of the live stream.]
[Goodbye, everyone.]
Lu Jing took a short cut to meet his idol?
Totally shameless.
I've asked Ms Ma so many times
but she kept ignoring me.
[Want to play a game?
Two-player mission.]
[No.]
[Come on.]
[Are you bored?]
I'm not bored. I'm dogged.
I'm so funny.
[Only one game.]
[If I beat you,]
[don't ever bother me again.]
[Game on.]
Ms Ma is so naive.
It's time to flex those skills.
A robot is coming.
[Don't panic, Ms Ma.]
I'll go finish him now.
He's dead.
Ms Ma, lady luck is on your side.
Another one is coming.
Let's go there.
A troop is closing in.
Be careful, Ms Ma.
They're all dead.
This is boring.
I'm not playing anymore.
The mission is not over yet.
The scores are not out yet.
Why are you stopping?
There are 50 robots.
I killed 26.
You'll never beat me.
What?
Ms Ma. You logged out?
She...
She keeps track of the body counts
as she plays?
Ms Ma is so smart.
You played well today, senior.
Do you practise a lot?
My...my work takes up a lot of time.
I don't get to practise so much.
Then you must be
a gifted player.
That's all.
Mr Lin.
Who else is coming tonight?
You'll know later.
He is the bridge of our collaboration.
Ding.
Sorry I'm late.
-Take a seat.
-Sit, sit.
Ding recommended you to us.
You have a good eye.
It's nothing.
Liang Chen is indeed the right choice.
I've been following
your live stream today.
You played well.
Thank you for recommending me.
Come. Let's toast.
Thank you all for your wonderful effort.
Cheers.
[Ms Ma, let's play another game.]
[Ms Ma, are you there?]
Wait. What is this?
She blocked me?
[Hello.]
[The number you have dialled
is not available.]
[Please call again later.]
She...
She really blocked me.
Charismatic. I like it.
Liang Chen.
Not only is your singing amazing,
your gaming skills are awesome too.
So...
Let's collaborate more.
Great.
Cheers.
I got it.
Alright.
Ding.
How did it go?
Liang Chen is right for you, isn't she?
Yes, she is.
Come. Let's drink.
Cheers.
Here.
Mr Lin.
I don't want any payment for today.
I want something else instead.
What do you want?
Little Fire Dragon.
Now I remember.
That was a prop
introduced during the launch
of Beautiful Soul.
But the company decided to
cancel it.
They don't feature it anymore.
But if you really want it,
I can give it to you.
Since you're not afraid of
attracting firepower anyway, right?
Thank you, Mr Lin.
But it's not for me.
I plan to give it to someone.
Really? Who?
Some noob player.
So that she can play with it
when she's bored.
Are you alright?
Since she's a noob,
keeping a little fire dragon
is practically suicide.
It's alright.
She is with me almost everyday.
I'll deal with the firepower.
She can just play with
the little fire dragon.
I...I'll go get something to eat.
Thank you, Mr Lin.
No problem.
I'll get something to eat too.
Alright.
Don't catch a cold.
I'm not cold.
Can you do me a favour?
What favour?
Just a tiny favour.
It won't take up too much of your time.
Why don't we
go to the corridor to talk about it?
Alright.
Boss.
If you really like her,
you need to do take the first step.
Senior.
Your button popped out.
Let me get it.
Alright.
Thanks.
Liang Chen.
Jia Yun. Are you looking for me?
Nothing.
It's cold tonight.
I'm just afraid you'll catch a cold.
Put this on.
Here.
Thank you, Jia Yun.
My friend's movie is premiering.
I want to invite you...
Jia Yun.
What is it?
I...I've been a long time fan.
I grew up watching your movies.
Can I have your autograph?
Alright.
Thank you.
You're really kind.
Is there anything else?
Ms Liang Chen.
Can I also have your autograph?
Sure.
Thank you.
-Thank you, Ms Liang Chen.
-Thank you.
Let's go.
Ding.
I have asked the driver
to get the car ready
to send everyone back.
Don't worry about me.
My assistant drove his car here.
My driver is here too.
Then the two of you
can ride in my driver's car.
That's great.
Thanks, Mr Lin.
Don't worry about me, Mr Lin.
I'll find my way back.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you free this Sunday?
It's my friend's movie premiere.
Do you want to go with me?
I have a recording this Sunday.
Then forget it.
I'm off now.
What a great weather today.
Senior, where do you live?
Bocui Tianchen. Why?
I'm on that route too.
Give me a ride.
Where are you going?
Sun Bin Yu's place?
Hop on then.
I'll go now.
-Alright.
-Bye.
Bye.
Boss.
If I'm not mistaken,
Ms Liang and Mr Sun's place
are not in the same direction.
I know.
Buckle up.
I don't know how.
Can you help me?
[Are your arms broken?]
[Just because you buttoned my top,]
[you expect me put on
the seat belt for you?]
I'm just kidding.
Did you
talk about me secretly?
No, of course not.
All done now.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Senior.
Do you want to come up?
No. No, thanks.
Alright then.
Goodbye, senior.
Goodbye.
[You cold-hearted woman.]
[You kept trampling on my heart.]
[I'll never forgive you.]
Come in.
Great.
That's what I like you about you, Ding.
When I need a drink,
you are here.
It's like you read my mind.
Here.
About Liang Chen's live stream today,
do you know who was playing with her?
Who?
Your neighbour.
Lu Jing?
What happened?
That puppy came on quite strong.
How did Liang Chen know him?
It's through mutual friends, I think.
What friends?
Introduce them to me.
I don't know them.
I wonder who they are too, right?
Do you know
what kind of relationship they're in?
Only one kind of course.
Ordinary online friends.
Ding.
I've been wanting to ask you something.
Do you have feelings for Orange?
Yes.
Oh my goodness.
You really do?
Are you serious?
[You two are my buddies.]
[Now you're fighting over a woman?]
[What do you want me to do?]
Oh, man.
This is a mad, mad world.
So this is Little Fire Dragon.
[Pet System]
[Pet Name: Little Fire Dragon]
Cute.
[Are you free? Log on now.]
So soon?
[Coming.]
Do you have something to tell me?
No.
Have you heard of Little Fire Dragon?
It circles around the person
spitting fire.
That kind of little fire dragon.
I know that. It's fun.
Do you want it?
Yes, I do.
But they are not featured anymore.
You lost your chance.
But you...
[I should have strangled you
with the seatbelt today.]
It's late.
I got to go.
Wait.
It's so cute.
Were you waiting for this the whole night?