ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
I told you not to put that dress on her.
Who cares?
She'll beat you up
even when you saved her life,
so you have to be careful. Okay?
Hey, are you all right?
You shouldn't move around.
She's a nursing major.
She got you medicine
and sutured your wounds.
You should go to the hospital right away.
Where am I?
This is my place.
Where are you going? You can barely walk.
Too much time has passed.
Tae-sul must've been caught.
No.
-Mr. Han!
-Give us a statement!
This has been on the news since yesterday.
QUANTUM & TIME'S CEO HAN TAE-SUL
EXPECTED TO RETURN TO OFFICE SOON
He seems to be doing fine.
The number you have dialed
cannot be reached…
-Move.
-She said you shouldn't move around.
At least say thank you
for saving your life.
Thanks. Out of my way.
Here, have a taste. Come closer.
-Mom!
-Seo-hae! You're home.
I smell something delicious.
What are you making?
Are you hungry?
-Yes.
-Stir-fried sausage with vegetables!
Try it.
It's good, right?
-Don't eat too much of it.
-Okay.
Oh, you woke up. You should eat something.
Come on. Have a seat.
You guys too. Sit over there.
SISYPHUS
I think my brother likes you a lot.
He looked after you the whole time.
He's not the type of jerk to do that.
Gosh, you brat.
You just eat and never help me.
Don't get married. I don't want
someone's precious son to suffer.
Seriously, Mom? Are you really my mom?
Don't worry. I'm a misogamist.
I won't get married.
I'll just live with you forever.
What is a misogamist?
It means I don't believe in marriage.
Are you a misogamist too?
See? No one wants to get married
these days.
Hey, you can't get married.
It's not by choice.
Look who's talking.
Enough! Let's eat.
Mom, you'll cook for me every day, right?
You think I'm your chef or something?
Goodness.
Come on! Everything you make
is so delicious.
-Please?
-It's the cooking app.
You can delete it. Just cook for me.
-Gosh. No way.
-How can I help you? Mom!
-Who are you? Go away.
-The dishes?
Mom! I'll help you a lot.
-Gosh.
-So cook for me every day.
-Please?
-Goodness, hey!
Take good care of our little girl.
Mom! No!
Mom!
Here.
Should I have gotten lemon tea instead?
Are you feeling better?
-Yes, thanks.
-You're welcome.
Oh, I won the lottery
with the numbers you gave me.
Darn it.
That day,
you suddenly disappeared like that.
So I had no choice
but to just come home on foot.
And I found out that Mr. Muk died.
He's the owner of the restaurant.
They said he took his own life,
but he'd never do that.
I got a bad hunch.
That's when I saw
the jerks who broke into my room.
The men from the Control Bureau.
I could tell instinctively.
-They were looking for me.
-Damn it.
They were going to kill me.
QUANTUM & TIME'S CEO HAN TAE-SUL
EXPECTED TO RETURN TO OFFICE SOON
If Han Tae-sul opened the suitcase,
they'll kill him.
So I went to a crowded place and hid,
crouching on the ground.
I resented you a lot back then.
I thought about
how I crossed paths with you
and let you ruin my life.
I thought I was screwed.
But that moment,
I found the lottery numbers
you had marked.
-I was scared of the Control Bureau.
-Okay.
So I hesitated for a moment.
But I went to buy a lottery ticket.
I figured I had nothing to lose.
MU MART
Huh? I'm sorry, sir.
-Our machine is broken.
-What?
Is your lottery machine working?
-Yes.
-Thank goodness!
Darn it. This can't be true.
Here! I got it!
Okay, that's 1,000 won.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
The funds raised will be used
for various welfare
and public service projects
for low-income families
and the underprivileged.
I see the balls tumbling.
The first lucky number. What will it be?
It's 21.
Let's find out the second number
that will come after 21.
It's 16.
The next lucky numbers are 27 and 37.
Now, the fifth…
Number one.
-Wow.
-What will the sixth number be?
THE 913TH DRAW
Number seven.
Please let it be seven.
-Seven!
-Oh, it's seven.
"Seven"?
Now, we'll draw the bonus ball
for our second prize.
That's how I won the lottery.
I won 2,8 billion won.
I paid off my debt.
Then I bought a house and a car.
But it didn't feel right.
It's been over a week
since CEO Han Tae-sul
of Quantum & Time got shot,
but the police haven't even been able
-to identify the suspect yet.
-I thought you'd come back to find him
if they didn't have the suspect
in custody yet.
So I went to the hospital
where Han Tae-sul was staying.
I camped out there for about three days.
But no one came.
Wow, look at this huge mansion.
Damn, they're not at the hospital
nor at his place.
Darn it! Where are they?
Starting that day,
I waited in front of his house
except when I went to the bathroom.
Huh?
What are they doing?
Damn it.
You and Han Tae-sul
seemed all lovey-dovey together,
so I didn't want to help you,
but I thought I should return the favor.
That's why I followed you.
Get in!
Cool car, wasn't it?
It can go from zero to a hundred
in 4,4 seconds.
We outran them like this!
Oh, here. I didn't feel comfortable
returning this to you at home.
Are you an NIS agent?
No.
How did you know the lottery numbers?
Is it really rigged as they say?
You don't need to know.
What about Han Tae-sul?
What happened to him?
You don't need to know.
Gosh, you say that all the time.
I need to know what's going on
to be able to help you.
It's okay. I don't need your help.
You see, I know nothing about you.
So your name is Gang Seo-hae?
That's a pretty name.
Can I call you Seo-hae?
No.
Then I'll just call you "Sis."
-Why?
-Well, you're older than me.
I was born in 1997.
I was born in 2012.
What?
Never mind. Don't call me anything.
-Why not?
-Because you'll never see me again anyway.
Hey, why so serious?
You don't need to bear it on your own.
I don't want to put anyone in danger.
They say only those who can accept help
can help others.
-You know that saying, right?
-No, I don't.
Gosh, you can't even walk properly.
I'm going to help you.
-Hey.
-Let's say you were right.
If Han Tae-sul got caught,
how will you save him on your own?
I'll figure it out.
I'm heading back in.
Hey, even if you keep refusing my help,
I'm going to help you.
Okay, Sis?
-Hey.
-Oh, right. Here.
I saw the scar on your wrist.
Use that to cover it
and think of me when you see it.
Thank you so much for saving my family.
I'll return the favor for all my life.
SEPTEMBER 9, WEDNESDAY
Save my number.
Call me if anything happens, okay?
Okay.
Hello?
Mom?
Sorry? Hello?
Speak up, please.
Was it a prank call?
Wrong number, I guess.
Mom, why are you crying?
What? Did something get in my eye?
That's odd. What's wrong with me?
Daddy's home!
Dad!
My gosh, Seo-hae.
-You're late.
-I know.
Dad, look at this.
I drew this.
Let's see. Wow, this is impressive!
-Isn't it great?
-It looks awesome, doesn't it?
This is you. This is me, and this is Mom.
Why is your mom as tall as I am?
I'm much taller.
-Run.
-What?
Exchange all of your money
and go abroad with your family.
What are you talking about?
A war will break out on October 31.
Everyone will die.
I'm from the future.
There's a time machine.
We call it the uploader.
Han Tae-sul invented…
I mean, he will invent it.
Some people came here
through the uploader to kill him.
It'll lead to a nuclear war
that will kill everyone.
So I must stop it.
You saw it, remember?
I flickered and almost disappeared.
It's a side effect of time travel.
It means I don't have much time left here.
What are you talking about?
This is so random.
Is this a hidden camera prank
or something?
I'm serious.
So you knew the winning numbers
because you're from the future?
Yes.
For real? You're not lying?
Then what should I do?
I can't just pack up
and leave the country.
Follow me.
-Be quiet.
-Why did you bring such a small bag?
-It's in the trunk. Quiet!
-Gosh, this is so sudden.
-You should've listened to me.
-Okay! Be quiet, please.
My goodness.
What about the valuables?
Did you pack them all?
Where are we going out of the blue?
I'll tell you later.
Where do we go now?
Don't move.
I'm faster than you.
I'm sure you know that.
Go get your boss.
Where's your boyfriend?
Keep talking if you want to get shot.
Goodness!
Look who's here. It's good to see you.
My gosh.
By the way, where's Mr. Han?
Did you two break up?
Oh, dear.
Have a seat.
Had I known you'd come here voluntarily,
we would've quit looking for you two
and just watched the store.
These kids went everywhere
to track the two of you down.
Do me a favor, and I'll give you the key.
Well, what's this key for?
Don't annoy me. I won't repeat myself.
It's the one you're after,
the key to the safe.
I'm not like Tae-sul. I don't lie.
I thought you were a close-minded loner,
but you know how to negotiate.
All right. Tell me what you need
and give me some time to think it over.
What do you need?
First,
help three people
leave the country safely.
Who are they?
You don't need to know.
The Control Bureau might come after them.
Help them leave the country safely
as soon as possible.
Can you do that?
Okay.
What else?
Next…
I can't reach Tae-sul.
Goodness, why are you telling me this?
Maybe he doesn't want to talk to you.
He got caught.
QUANTUM & TIME'S CEO HAN TAE-SUL
EXPECTED TO RETURN TO OFFICE SOON
He's doing fine.
That's not him.
Have you ever seen this jerk
voluntarily thanking anyone?
The one you saw on TV is fake.
You're right.
That jerk certainly isn't the type
to thank anyone. Gosh.
Help me save Tae-sul.
She's right. They've blocked everything.
No phone or Internet.
The weird thing is,
it's not blocked from the inside.
It's blocked from the outside.
Looks like he's locked in there.
Hey.
So?
Apparently,
he hasn't left the house for days.
It's surrounded by security guards.
A guy's in there. What was his name?
Ed?
-Eddy Kim.
-Yes.
Only he is allowed to go in.
Really?
Then there's nothing we can do, right?
Forget it.
But you promised.
I never get involved in dangerous stuff.
Safety comes first.
Fine.
Hey! You impatient little brat.
-You said you couldn't do it.
-When did I say that?
I just said safety comes first.
Then how about this?
We'll help him out a little
to escape from the house.
After that, you can rescue him
or do whatever the heck you want.
What do you say? Good?
-But how?
-Is it a good plan or not?
Okay.
All right. Hey, that thing.
What thing?
The thing we can shoot!
-For real?
-Won't it be dangerous?
If we go ahead and use it,
the higher-ups will flip out.
She'll hand over the key!
Even if we do all sorts of crazy things,
nothing will change anyway.
Hey.
We can upload items to his house
from the future.
What? How?
Things he'd need, for example.
We can send it to a safe PO box and
store it until sometime in the future.
-We'll send it back to the present.
-To the exact location?
Yes, up to one gallon,
which equals approximately 3,7 liters.
It's 100 percent accurate up to the size
of the smallest mailing box.
The accuracy rate is inversely
proportional to the amount of data,
so the accuracy rate drops
when you transport people.
Complicated colors or structures
increase the failure rate.
Hey, that's enough.
Look here.
If you have anything to send to Mr. Han,
hand it over.
Anything that can help him
escape from the house.
If you don't have anything,
we'll send things like guns or grenades.
Goodness. What is this?
Isn't this an EMP?
Why are you even carrying this around?
Not this.
Do you have a picture
of the two of you together?
Something memorable.
-Why?
-So he can know who the sender is, okay?
When he sees this,
he'll know that it's from you.
Look. Hey, look at this.
How lovely.
Got a death wish?
Hey, if there's something to tell him,
write it on the back.
I'M A MISOGAMIST TOO
I used to be a misogamist too.
-That's mine!
-Let go! You don't own this.
We have to enclose an object like this.
When the cup breaks,
we'll know that it has arrived.
Take this to the post office.
Make sure it arrives at his house
by 10 p.m.
-Okay.
-Hurry up.
Yes, sir.
It'll arrive at 22:00,
so I'll start downloading now.
If all goes well, the cup will fall
at his house at 22:00 sharp.
The rest will arrive five seconds later.
By the way,
who's holding him captive there?
Sigma.
I'm just curious.
Let me ask you something.
Why on earth are you doing this?
What? To stop them
from inventing the uploader?
Is that it?
Then why do it the hard way?
If I were you, I'd just kill Han Tae-sul.
Then it'd all be over, right?
What?
You think you can change the future?
You know that you can't change anything,
don't you?
Nothing will change,
no matter what you do.
The package will arrive in 15 seconds.
Then why do you want the key so much?
We can change the future.
Sure, I hope that's the case.
I can change it.
Downloading now.
Four, three,
two, one.
It has arrived.
This isn't mine.
I'M A MISOGAMIST TOO
What?
-Get him!
-What? Turn the lights on!
Tae-sul!
Han Tae-sul!
Darn it!
NO CALLER ID
Han Tae-sul got out.
He's headed to the tool market.
The tool market.
-Hey.
-Yes?
About Han Tae-sul…
Gosh, this will make me
sound like a loser.
What's your relationship with him?
Nothing.
Then be my girlfriend.
Why should I?
Let's leave the country together.
There will be a war. Why stay here?
-Ask that man to get another ticket.
-No.
Why not? Because of your family?
No.
Then what's the reason?
Because of that jerk, Han Tae-sul?
Do you like him?
-Is that a real rifle?
-No, it has rubber bullets.
Can it kill someone?
-Do you want to try?
-No, I'm good.
Hey, Sis!
I'll wait for you here.
CEO HAN TAE-SUL'S RETURN
TO MANAGEMENT POSITION UNCLEAR
How did things get so messed up?
Spread out and find him.
Damn it.
Darn it. Where did he go?
What is he doing?
Darn it.
UNKNOWN CALLER
-Hello?
-Hello? Is it you, Seo-hae?
-Is that you?
-Yes.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Did you manage to escape that day?
Yes. I saw the news.
You seemed to be doing fine.
Me?
I'm telling you this because you should
adjust to the modern society.
You shouldn't believe everything
the media says.
The world isn't that honest.
-What's going on?
-Seo-hae, listen carefully.
You're the only person I can trust
whether from the past, present, or future.
I ran away from home,
and I'm in huge trouble right now.
-Can you help me?
-Where are you?
I'm at Hannam Tool Market.
I'm a bit busy right now, though.
What? What are you doing?
I'm just busy.
You can't do this to me!
-Get down.
-What?
-I said, get down.
Hello? Seo-hae?
What the heck?
What was that?
Why are you here? You said you were busy.
What can I do? You said
I was the only one you could trust.
What happened to you?
And what are you wearing?
Oh, this?
-Forget it. Come on, let's go.
-Hey, wait.
Are you really Seo-hae?
-What are you talking about?
-Well…
For the past few days,
they kept telling me that you're fake.
So I don't know who to trust anymore.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry,
but I can't tell what's real
and what's fake anymore.
What if you're…
It is me. I'm here.
Look. It's me, right?
Let's go.
Hey, you're back. Here.
Hop in. Wait!
She has to sit in the front.
-What do you want?
-Darn it. You sit in the front then.
By the way, where are we going?
To Asia Mart.
Why?
I need to hand over the key.
-What?
-I had to get you out of there.
Still, we can't give him the key.
You got another idea?
They helped us get you out.
I get that, but still…
We can't hand it over to those jerks.
Jeez.
It's cold. Turn on the heater.
Don't touch it. I'll do it.
Where is it?
It's right here. The fan button.
What is this car?
I see. A discontinued model.
Did you buy it secondhand?
Gosh, this seat is so uncomfortable.
Jeez. Why are you dropping the honorifics?
Who is this guy?
Me? The person who saved you.
When did you save me?
If you have a problem, get out.
-How old are you?
-Be quiet, both of you.
Darn it.
It's cold in here.
-Go inside.
-Wait…
Thanks for everything. Get going now.
Send your mom and sister my regards.
Come with us.
You can't keep living like this.
Get going. Your family is waiting.
-No, I'll help you.
-I said, go.
This isn't your fight.
If you stay with me, you'll die.
-How do you know that?
-This isn't something you can do.
Go.
WARNING
TOP SECRET
Goodness.
Welcome.
Hey, give me the key.
Hey, is this really okay?
Goodness.
I met your brother.
What?
You're putting Tae-sul in danger.
This is my last warning.
If I ever see you again,
I'll kill you.
You don't care whether he dies or not
if you can save the world,
but it's the opposite for me.
As long as I can save Tae-sul,
I don't care what happens to the world.
I always thought it was odd.
Why did he put the blueprint
in the safe and lose the key,
knowing how dangerous it is?
If someone manages to open the safe
and obtains the blueprint,
you'll become useless and face danger.
I'll tell you what's in this safe.
At some point in the future,
Mr. Han will invent the uploader,
which will save all of us.
And the original blueprint
is in this safe.
If I were Han Tae-san,
I'd never keep something so important
in a safe.
Then what?
If the blueprint is gone,
you'll be the only person
who can build the uploader.
No one will be able to kill you.
If I were your brother,
I'd keep it with me,
even if I have to be on the run forever.
There's nothing inside the safe.
What the…
TO TAE-SUL
"To Tae-sul."
Tae-san.
It's his handwriting.
To Tae-sul,
if you're reading this letter,
it means you've opened the safe.
The blueprint is safe with me.
You'll be safe
as long as I keep this with me.
No one can harm you.
I'm doing fine. For real.
So don't worry about me.
If you're still beating yourself up
for what happened that day, don't.
Brothers fight all the time.
I'm really okay.
But I really miss you
from time to time.
I want to sit down with you
and laugh and chat with you
like the old days.
Is the future
really unchangeable?
If everyone is going to die,
and if that means you could die too,
what should I do?
I made up my mind.
I'm going to save you.
Tae-sul, I hope you make a choice
that you won't regret.
I believe the outcome will be good
when good choices are accumulated.
As you know, I'm not that smart.
That's the only way I can look at it.
You'll do better than I did.
Live your life to the fullest
with no regrets.
And don't look for me.
We'll meet again someday.
I believe that we will.
I miss you, Tae-sul.
I love you.
I figured out who Sigma is.
He was right next to us all along.
HAN TAE-SAN
DON'T LOOK FOR YOUR BROTHER
IF YOU DO, YOU'LL DIE
Tae-san wasn't hiding after all,
nor was he on the run.
Hey.
Those photos
weren't photos of me.
He was looking for Sigma.
Mr. Han,
what the hell are you talking about?
Guys.
Where's the blueprint?
My brother has it.
What? I kept my promise.
I gave you the key.
Be honest if you want to strike a deal.
If you want to trick me,
you should be smarter about it.
You brats, how dare you try to dupe me?
Hold on! What's that sound?
The Control Bureau is here!
I called them.
Hey, go lock the door!
Hurry up, you punks!
What? You told me to be smarter.
Turn around.
You too. Now!
Well, you're pretty smart after all.
Put your hands up!
-Put your hands up!
Arrest them.
-Start searching.
-Yes, sir.
Where's the back door?
-Where is it?
-Outside and to your left.
-You brat.
-Don't follow us. Let's go.
Hey, you're so cool.
I know.
Make sure you never run into me again
in this lifetime, both of you.
Will do. Stay healthy, Mr. Park.
All right, thanks.
Bingbing, is the generator on?
You stay here.
Keep the doors locked, okay?
What about you?
Those jerks from the Control Bureau
will leave quietly once they catch me.
Hey.
You must not turn off the downloader.
Okay?
Do you understand?
-Boss, wait!
-Let go!
Lock the doors.
Do not leave this room, no matter what.
Okay?
Yes.
All right.
Goodness.
I have to go back in there.
Don't come out.
Jeez, you guys are so loud!
Goodness.
Here! I'm right here. My goodness.
Must you cause all this ruckus?
What a crowd.
Okay, all right. My goodness.
I have my hands up.
Jae-sun, you know which gate it is, right?
Yes.
I think it's that way.
Jae-sun, why are you standing there?
Come on.
Sorry, Mom. Go without me.
Go-eun, take good care of Mom.
And take this.
-Jae-sun.
-Jae-sun!
Son!
-Good morning.
-Hi. How are you feeling?
Good.
Breakfast is ready. Come and eat.
Okay.
Tae-sul.
There's a sniper,
so don't try anything funny. Sit down.
You seem to be doing well.
I already cut that wire.
You can't make calls,
and there are no security guards.
I just have some questions for you.
That's why I'm here.
Who is Sigma?
If you refuse to answer,
I will take away everything you have,
one by one.
Then I'll rip them to shreds,
so you'd better answer.
Who is Sigma?
As of this moment,
you're removed from the Quantum & Time
board of directors.
Tae-sul, that is not something
you can decide on your…
By the time this is over,
Tae-sul won't be able to recover
because of the drugs.
-I got a locked ward prepared for him.
-What about Eddy?
He thinks it's just a treatment.
The only thing on his mind
is taking over the management rights.
It's a short conversation,
but three counts of legal violation
are mentioned.
Instigating unlawful confinement.
Violating the Medical Law
and the Capital Markets Act.
How did I record this?
Well, when I almost died here that day,
I put my earpiece on the floor.
I'll ask you one last time.
If you refuse to answer again,
Seo-jin will go to jail.
Who is Sigma?
When and how did Sigma approach you?
From the very beginning.
Do you remember the day we first met?
What?
The investment briefing?
Sigma came to see me a month before that.
He had this medicine
that could cure my wife,
who was on the verge of death.
I thought it was complete nonsense.
However,
she really woke up.
And he told me to invest in your company.
What about Tae-san?
What happened to my brother?
He said Tae-san was getting in his way,
-so he should be put in a mental ward.
-Darn it!
Where is this jerk now?
No idea. I really don't know.
I had no choice.
You must have a way of contacting him!
He contacts me only when he needs me.
Tae-sul.
I'm sorry.
Where is the chairman?
He said he'd be here.
I can't reach him.
We're short on time, so let's begin.
We asked all of you to be here today
because we have
an important announcement to make.
Is it about Mr. Han Tae-sul?
Is it true that something happened to him
last night?
You can ask questions later.
I'll read this aloud first.
"Due to CEO Han Tae-sul's absence,
his position has practically been
left vacant for a while now,
which is weakening
the company's competitiveness
and making our shareholders anxious.
Hence, we have decided to appoint
a new leader.
The board has come to the conclusion
that I will fill in
Mr. Han's virtually vacant position…"
-It's Han Tae-sul!
-What's going on?
-What?
-He's here.
-It's Han Tae-sul.
Jeez.
You're the CEO now?
That's cool. Congratulations.
Tae-sul.
Just a moment.
I have an important announcement as well.
This is being broadcast live, right?
I have something to say.
Well,
Tae-san.
Han Tae-san.
You're watching this, right?
I know we'll meet again.
Stay safe until that day, okay?
I miss you.
And the other person who's watching this.
Yes, you. Sigma, you jerk.
Don't hide like a coward.
Show yourself, you wimp.
Actually, never mind.
You just stay put,
because I will find you.
Now, it's getting interesting.
Hello?
I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused.
Honey.
I'm sorry.
This happened because I'm incompetent.
Come on.
All this fuss over just one death?
What will they do
when 50 million people die?
I can't understand
why she has to go through all this
just to save someone like you.
How do you know Tae-sul?
He has to make something for me.
I said I'd help you find your brother,
not Sigma.
I have to risk my life.
I have to tell Han Tae-sul
not to meet him.
You wanted to know
what the future looks like, right?
Enjoy it when you can.
Everything's going to burn down soon.
"Sigma." Now I know what it means.
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs