ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
AUGUST 6, 2001
Sir, it's dangerous to be here.
The train is going to come soon.
Sir!
Hey! Get up. Are you okay?
You shouldn't be…
What? Why does he have
a photo of Tae-sul and me?
Hey.
Who are you? How do you know Tae-sul?
Who are you?
What?
Hey, you!
Who are you?
SISYPHUS
Oh, my gosh!
RESIDENT ID CARD
DONGMYEONGJANG INN
-One room.
-How long are you going to stay?
Three days.
YEARS 2001 - 2010
Korean athletes won first and second place
for the first time
in a major golf championship.
August 6.
AUGUST 2001
HORSE RACING NEWS
Why are your hands trembling?
-It's Number Two!
-Oh, gosh!
His hands are trembling so much!
Three months. A room with a window.
AUGUST 15, 2001
STOCK PRICES
With conflicts in the Middle East,
KOSDAQ has been fluctuating.
Only nuclear power-related stocks
have been rising.
AUGUST 25, 2001
STOCK PRICES
SEPTEMBER 11, 2001
HORSE RACING NEWS
Number Three is in the lead!
Number Three finishes the race!
It won the race!
WINNER IS HORSE NUMBER 3, HIM-CHAN!
Yes, sir. I checked the account.
All right.
How may I help you? Investments or--
Make an account.
Buy these now
and sell them the day after tomorrow.
FOMECT
HUISANG A&T
Why don't we discuss details…
The prices went up again.
The Financial Supervisory Service
might inspect us at this rate.
It's been a month,
but your earnings rate is 1,000%.
Sell everything
at the closing price tomorrow.
And open a futures account.
-You want to trade futures?
-Buy put options.
How much?
Everything.
Why? They're doing well these days.
KIM DONG-HYEON
FOREIGN FUTURES OPTION PURCHASE ORDER
FINANCIAL INVESTMENT CLIENT LIST
BANKBOOK COPY
CORPORATE SAVINGS ACCOUNT
KIM DONG-HYEON, MANAGER
MD INVESTMENT
Kim Dong-hyeon! Have you lost your mind?
-What's that sound?
-What's wrong with you?
Buying put options in a bull market?
Have you gone nuts?
If you want to die,
don't drag others with you!
-What happened?
-Why did you do that?
Why did you do it?
I see you've become reckless just because
you've been doing well these days.
What will you do tomorrow?
The higher-ups will sue you
for breach of duty!
What will you do, you jerk?
-What is it?
-Sir, look at the news!
The strongest country in the world,
the United States, has been attacked.
Korea's stock market is at risk as well.
The composite stock price index
dropped by 12,01% today.
It's the biggest drop ever.
-As many as 621 sectors of stocks dropped.
-What happened?
-Another 591 sectors dropped in KOSDAQ.
-What's going on?
-Only 11 sectors have risen in the market.
-What should we do?
-This is insane.
-It's complete chaos.
This is perfect!
I hope things will continue like this!
It's a day to celebrate.
Sir.
I really respect you, sir.
I'm really grateful that I met you.
You're my savior.
I promise
to serve you well from now on.
-Help me meet someone.
-Who?
Kim Han-yong. He's an IT investor.
IT?
That bubble burst already.
There's nothing to gain from it.
It burns easily.
Money burns easily.
But people don't.
What?
Hello, Mr. Kim.
I'm Kim Dong-hyeon. Please have a seat.
I don't know what this is about,
but I came here
because you kept begging me to meet you.
I'm busy.
If you have something to say,
make it quick.
Sir!
He's a bit picky about food.
What are you doing?
I heard your wife is sick.
Was it ALS or something like that?
-What is it?
-Medicine.
She could die any moment.
There's nothing to lose.
Who the hell are you?
Mr. Kim, is this some kind of a joke?
No, of course not.
Sir, there's no cure for ALS.
-It's incurable.
-Not yet.
Try it and contact me if you need more.
Let's go.
That crazy jerk.
-Hey, Dad.
-Hey.
You must be tired.
You should've just gone home.
-Mom.
-Honey.
Mom!
Honey!
Mom, can you recognize me?
It's me, Seo-jin.
Oh, my gosh.
Honey!
I don't know how I can ever repay you.
Han Tae-sul.
Invest in him.
Invest in your name with my money.
Why do you want to invest in him?
He has to make something for me.
The medicine will lose its effect
in about a month.
If you obey me, I'll give you more.
-Keep in touch.
-I will.
CONGRATULATIONS
QUANTUM & TIME LISTED ON NASDAQ
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Tae-sul!
-Hold on.
-You can't go in.
Tae-sul!
Hold on.
-Excuse me.
-I'm his brother. Just a second.
Take it.
This isn't about money, you know.
It won't take long.
Just spare me five minutes.
I know you went through a lot,
but must I put up with this forever?
-I'm just--
-I'll repay you for everything, so--
I'm just so worried about you.
What if something happens--
Tae-san! If you really care about me,
drop this and just go home.
-Hey, let's step out for a moment.
-Seriously, enough!
-I'll explain outside.
-I'll call you!
-No, our phones are tapped!
-For God's sake!
Jeez.
Tae-sul.
Wait, Tae-sul. Tae-sul!
Tae-sul, wait.
Darn it.
You. It's you, right?
You!
It's you, right?
Who are you?
What have you done to Tae-sul? Huh?
You!
Let go of me!
Let me go!
What have you done to Tae-sul?
Let go of me!
It's been listed now, so you'll earn
at least ten times the investment.
Gosh!
This is amazing.
Aren't you happy?
Come to think of it,
I've never seen you smile.
My life has been so successful
since I met you.
Thank you.
The CEO recruitment will go well.
By the way,
my wife is pregnant.
They said it's a boy.
I've always wanted to ask.
How do you know all this?
Gosh, the view is amazing.
Enjoy it when you can.
Everything's going to burn down soon.
What?
Everyone's going to die soon.
Everyone.
SEPTEMBER 20, 2020, PRESENT DAY
QUANTUM & TIME'S CEO HAN TAE-SUL
YOUNG FOUNDER, RICHEST STOCK MILLIONAIRE
Hello? Honey.
Listen to me carefully.
Go to the airport right now
and leave the country.
Take Seo-u with you.
I don't have time to explain. Hurry.
I'll leave soon too.
I have to tell Han Tae-sul
not to meet him.
Okay.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
-Let's talk for a minute.
-Okay. Hang on.
This is a facial recognition program.
It was made for the military.
It can even find faces from 20 years ago.
But I can't find him.
Who in the world is he?
A millionaire? A politician?
I'm sure he's some kind of big shot.
Why can't I find him?
I got it.
Tae-san took a bad photo.
Look, it's totally out of focus.
That's why I can't find him.
Would he be in his Forties? His fifties?
Or his thirties?
-He's definitely a man, right?
-Tae-sul.
Hey. How tall does he look to you?
How would I know that?
Let's say he's about 175cm.
Go over there.
The PEXCO conference hall,
the second-floor maintenance room,
the bathrooms and the lobby.
There are 317 security cameras in total.
Even if I only check the day
of the shooting, it's 24 hours.
What is it? Are you worried
about the Control Bureau?
Let those jerks come.
Didn't you say
you have something to tell me?
What is it?
What's the matter?
Stop this. It's too dangerous.
If the Control Bureau comes, stay hidden.
I'm pretty influential,
so they can't harm me that easily.
That's why I was so confident.
We'll be safe for now.
-It's not that.
-Then what?
I meant looking for Sigma.
-What about it?
-You almost died last time.
Me? When?
Come on.
What's with you?
You said you wanted to stop the war.
We must catch him then.
If you don't make the uploader,
there won't be a war.
That's why they're after you.
Just don't do anything.
Okay. Fine.
Speaking of the uploader,
where is it?
You used that to come here.
We can just go find it.
-I don't know.
-Try to remember.
Don't change the subject.
I'm going to find Sigma
even if I have to risk my life.
If we fail, there will be a war again.
Then everyone is going to die.
Don't you care about that?
No.
How can you be so selfish?
I didn't do anything.
If I were you, I'd stay hidden
until everything is resolved.
I told you I'd protect you.
Don't you feel guilty?
Why would I feel guilty?
Everyone will die because of you,
even my mom--
I didn't do anything yet!
That jerk's been hovering around me
the whole time.
He mocked me behind my back.
He's fooled me and my brother
all this time.
So how can I forgive him?
I'll catch him and--
This is exactly what he wants you to do.
I said I'd help you find your brother,
not Sigma.
-It's the same thing.
-No, it's not!
If you keep going after Sigma…
You'll die if you do.
October 31.
It's the day you die.
There's a lot of time left.
I got him!
HUGE HEDGE FUND INVESTMENT LOSS
DUE TO U.S. TERROR ATTACK
Your fan's here. Give him a wave.
Sis!
My mom and Go-eun arrived safely.
Are you going somewhere?
I'll give you a ride.
You said the war breaks out
on October 31, right?
What do I do now?
-I told you to leave.
-Come on.
-I can't just leave, you know.
-Leave.
Hang on.
Be careful, okay?
You could've died last time
if I hadn't saved you.
So be careful.
What?
Jeez, that lunatic.
Right. Here.
It's the man who was with Sigma.
His name's Kim Dong-hyeon.
He started as a fund manager
and became a millionaire.
He's a legend in the field.
Remember the 9/11 attacks in 2001?
He made it big with put options back then.
Put options…
To put it simply,
he already knew
that something huge was going to happen.
So you're going to find him
and ask who Sigma is?
No, he died in an accident last week.
Be quiet!
Just remember one thing
when you question them.
"Everything they say is a lie."
How are illegal entrants
different from us?
They have information.
They're from the future.
-Right.
-If they say it'll rain tomorrow,
you can't tell if it's true or not.
That's their weapon.
You can't tell if they're lying.
I see.
What happened?
He was making such a fuss
that we had to tie him up.
It's an honor to have such a famous person
here with us.
You've grown a lot.
You too.
He's grown a lot.
Park Hyeong-do.
You were in a holding cell
after getting arrested for murder,
and avoided a nuclear war.
How lucky.
As for your family…
Wow.
She's pretty.
Should we pay her a visit?
If you cooperate with us,
we won't play any cheap tricks.
Jeez.
We're working in the same field, you know.
Cut me some slack.
Hey.
You.
I can
find your family too.
You jerk!
What about Han Tae-sul?
He's poking around here and there.
He drew a bit of attention
at the press conference.
If we act rashly,
people will start talking.
That's what he intended.
-What about the girl?
-She's still with Han Tae-sul.
We're still keeping an eye on them.
Leave Han Tae-sul alone for now.
What?
Nothing, sir.
I repeat. Leave Han Tae-sul alone.
We'll only keep an eye on him for now.
Get the girl instead.
Grab her when she's away from Han Tae-sul
and take her into custody.
That'll be all.
What?
I'm sorry I asked you to meet me
so suddenly.
It's all right.
Do you know who this person is?
He came to our house twice,
when we first moved here
and again last week.
-Last week?
-Yes.
Right there.
He sat there and argued with my husband.
After he left, my husband left saying
he needed to go somewhere.
And then…
Do you remember his name
or any other details about him?
Anything is fine.
No, I don't.
My husband didn't say anything about him.
It's all right. Take your time to think.
The painting.
"The painting"?
He gave us a painting
as a present when we moved in.
He said he painted it himself.
I covered it up because it looked awful.
That crazy jerk.
You wanted to know
what the future looks like, right?
He killed my husband, didn't he?
Why did we come here?
The painting.
It'll take at least a month
to draw such a huge painting.
He wouldn't have gone wandering around
when he's in hiding.
I'm sure he drew it where he was staying.
You can find where it is
with that painting?
See the Trade Tower over there?
And those four red lights?
That's the Finance Center.
From here, those two buildings
are the same height.
They're 229 meters and 206 meters.
He was looking up,
so the angle would be eight degrees…
Nine degrees?
Are you sure it's this building?
It's here.
Are you sure?
Probably.
Promise me one thing.
Don't do anything dangerous.
If you think something's going to happen,
hide behind me. Okay?
Hey. I'm good at that.
Don't joke around.
All right.
What? Hang on.
What is it?
It looks like it was never even touched.
No way.
That's the smell of oil paint.
Over there.
This is the right place.
He drew the painting here.
Hang on.
"Sigma."
Now I know what it means.
Sisyphus.
He is an eternal sinner
in Greek mythology.
He pushes a boulder up a mountain
only to see it roll down.
Then he pushes it up the mountain again,
and it rolls back down. Again and again.
He receives eternal punishment. Forever.
What was he punished for?
-That jerk!
-Darn it!
You jerk!
Hey!
You.
Hi.
You came to find me yourself?
You were taking too long.
Run, Tae-sul!
You jerk!
Seo-hae!
Hang in there.
What happened to Sis?
Why aren't you answering me?
She cut her palm.
And she has bruises here and there.
I gave her first aid,
and she's asleep now.
What are you doing?
I'm upset as well right now.
I can't understand
why she has to go through all this
just to save someone like you.
If you can't, don't.
You jerk.
-Stop.
-You stop.
She keeps getting injured because of you!
Hey. She risked her life to come here
to save her mother.
Do you think she'll even listen to me?
And talk to her yourself
instead of doing this to me like a coward!
You tell her.
I want to tell her too,
but she won't listen to me.
You don't know what that means.
I guess she doesn't want to listen to you.
Darn it.
HUGE HEDGE FUND INVESTMENT LOSS
DUE TO U.S. TERROR ATTACK
"Gang Seo-hae."
Look forward. Good.
Hold the handles tightly.
Good.
Seo-hae, you're doing great!
-Don't let go, Dad.
-I won't. I'm holding you.
-Don't let go.
-Okay. I won't.
Dad, you're lying, right? Come on.
No, I'm still holding on.
-Really?
-Of course.
I'm going to look back.
-Don't look back!
-You should've caught her!
-My goodness.
-Are you okay?
-You should keep looking forward.
-Does that hurt?
-Are you okay?
-It's okay.
I'm going to let go now.
-Okay.
-I'll let go now.
Good job.
You're doing great!
You're the best!
-Seo-hae, you're so good!
-She did it.
-You're doing great, Seo-hae!
-You're doing great!
Happy birthday, Seo-hae.
-My present?
-Yes.
Thanks, Mom.
Open it.
-It's a cell phone!
-Do you like it?
September 30.
SEPTEMBER 30, SUNDAY
It's her birthday today.
Happy birthday, Seo-hae.
Giddyup!
What a nice view.
I came here with my parents
when I was little.
I think the last time I came
was when I was nine.
I didn't get to ride this
because I was less than 140cm tall.
People had to wait two hours to ride this.
But now there's nobody here.
Shoot, Gang Seo-hae.
Shoot it.
Darn it.
What took you so long?
I went hunting.
Are you okay, Dad?
Yes, I'm fine.
You don't look okay.
Let me see.
It's fine.
-Let me see.
-Come on.
When did you get hurt?
Is it the gunshot wound from before?
Did you take antibiotics?
It's okay. I don't need it.
It's late. Where are you going?
To the hospital.
No!
It's too dangerous.
You can't go there on your own.
If I don't go and you die,
I'll be on my own anyway.
Seo-hae.
Wait. Gang Seo-hae!
One, two…
"Antibiotics."
Hands up!
Turn around!
No! Don't move!
You told me to turn around.
Should I turn around or not?
Turn around.
Hands up.
Where are the antibiotics?
My dad's hurt.
I'll leave quietly with the medicine.
Please.
The fridge behind you.
The second shelf.
Three pills a day.
Inject it into his vein.
Thank you.
No!
No…
Darn it.
Catch her!
Stop!
Pull back.
Gosh, that startled me.
My back hurts.
I slept all day.
What is this?
"Dear Seo-hae,
Happy birthday."
By the time you read this, I'll be dead.
Don't be surprised.
What you're looking at right now
is yourself.
Listen carefully.
There is something we must do.
Take the uploader and go to the past.
Save Han Tae-sul.
If he lives, the war can be stopped.
Only you can do this.
Protect him from Sigma.
Han Tae-sul?
Don't ever lose him.
Whatever happens, overcome it.
You can do it.
Please protect the person I love.
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi
-You said you hate amusement parks.
-But it's your birthday.
Are you Sigma?
What will you do with Sigma?
I'll fix it since I ruined everything.
The girl or the world?
I'll walk out of here tomorrow afternoon.
You're not the CEO anymore.
You're nothing.
It seems like a normal hospital.
Basement Level Four.
Seo-hae is here right now.
I hear this shot makes you disappear
like a ghost.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs