♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 19
Mu Jin, thank you for
helping me carry water today.
Do you feel better about your foot?
I made some lamb bone soup for
you, do you want to drink it?
Mu Jin?
I'm coming in, may I?
Mu Jin.
Mu Jin, what's wrong?
Are you okay? Wake up!
Gosh.
It's so hot.
No.
Right, alcohol, any alcohol?
Alcohol.
Be careful.
Does it work?
Once the fever is brought
down, it would be okay.
I will go to find the witch doctor.
I'd take more alcohol.
Okay.
You must get better soon!
You can't die.
Why are you here?
You are awake!
Why did you take off all of my clothes?
The fever is brought down.
Lie down, quickly.
You must be dead if you get the fever again.
Bah bah!
How can you curse me death?
You...
You stepped on the rusty pin for helping me.
If you die, I...
My mom have got the similar experience
of stepping on a rusty pin.
Her fever lasted for many days.
When I figured out this method,
it's too late.
Fortunately, you survived.
Mimi, don't feel sad.
I'm very strong. I won't die easily.
I'm one of the warriors from the grasslands.
Your look now is not that persuasive.
Stop flaunting your manhood.
I didn't.
I'm a great man, indeed.
You are if you're alive,
or else you're just a dead man!
So, did you take care of me for the whole night?
Of course.
Lie down.
It's a little bit cold.
Why are you laughing?
It's itchy, itchy.
Go.
Stop.
The northwest region is on the
left, much more away from Luoyang.
Her Highness can't be there.
Jizhou is in the middle.
Cangzhou is on the right.
Princess, if you left
Yunzhou, where would you go?
This is from you,
hope it can tell me about your trace.
Jizhou on the front, Cangzhou on the reverse.
Go.
Sun.
Did I tell you to take a good rest?
Why do you come? You're just cured.
I've been recovered long before.
Well, our provisions are running out, right?
I want to purchase some with Mimi Guli.
Why? Still suspect her?
Only taking her with you can make you convinced?
No! No!
It's not what I mean!
Well, I think this girl is smart.
I can get better bargain with her.
Besides, I want to show my appreciation to her
for taking care of me that day.
Okay.
Great.
Look at your lambs, all of them look like you!
They are white!
Mimi.
Wait a minute.
Look, Mu Jin is here again.
Right.
What's wrong?
I want to ask you that if you're willing
to purchase goods in Yunzhou with me?
Me?
Don't be overthinking.
Just because a woman is better
at bargaining than a man.
Although Yunzhou is not comparable to
Changan, it's bustling enough.
You must haven't seen it before.
I will tell Military Counsellor Li later.
Just go with me.
Okay.
See you later!
Changge, what are you embroidering?
It's quite ugly.
This is the only pattern I'm able to embroider.
If you don't like it,
just use the package.
Yes!
I like it.
Who said she didn't like?
Go on.
This money bag is indeed ugly.
It's not, it looks good.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Yes.
I didn't mean that.
Anyone who said it's ugly shows no appreciation.
You said it, too.
I think each one you embroider is pretty.
Changge, how about telling
me something interesting
or delicious in the markets
of the central plain?
Or tell me what do you want? I will buy for you.
Do you have money?
I can borrow from Mu Jin.
I can be his servant for
some days as the payment.
I don't allow you to be the servant of others.
Changge, you like rabbits very much, do you?
I liked them.
What about now?
[Rabbit.]
It's done.
Here.
Is this for me?
I've got some payment as military counsellor.
Just buy anything you want.
No need to save money for me.
I haven't been treated so well for so long.
Thank you, Changge.
I will buy anything you want for you.
When you arrive in Yunzhou,
it woulld be the Mid-autumn Festival.
In my hometown, we'd eat moon cakes
and stay with our family in this festival.
Besides, we'd light the sky lanterns as well.
There is no mooncake in the grasslands.
You may taste it in Yunzhou.
Are you homesick?
Be assured, I'd definitely
buy many mooncakes for you.
The stitch is not tight enough.
It's still the problem of the warping.
Lack of practice.
This is a completed fabric.
Send it to the cloth shop, they must be happy.
Bad news!
The purchasing manager said that
due to the constant heavy
rain and their dead stock,
so they wanted withdraw this cloth order.
We tried every method to persuade
but
they insisted on cancelling the order.
Luckily, they didn't ask
for the front moeny back.
- What should we do?
- Right.
The front money is useless.
It seems that we might suffer a heavy loss.
Ms. Chai, I've got an idea.
We can take our cloth products
to the market for selling.
This idea is practical.
Right.
It's a good idea.
Okay.
Let's follow Yan's advice and
sell the cloth at the market.
Get ready now, let's go to sell our cloth.
- Okay.
Hurry.
Be careful.
Okay.
This is good.
Right, let's come again later.
Waiter.
Waiter!
How many days does it take to Cangzhou?
Sir, it isn't far away.
It would take one or two days if you speed up.
Thank you.
What a coincidence.
What's wrong? Got ill?
Not serious.
I was caught in a rain and got a cold.
You must take care,
or else you may get worse
before finding the princess.
It's nothing comparing to Leyan's safety.
Don't worry, I can stick it out.
Let's deal with her Highness's business later.
His Majesty has decreed to call
you back to Changao for reporting.
You will be appointed as Supervisory Censor.
What?
How do you know?
It's no doubt that I always keep in
contact
with the people in Changan.
But...
Stop it.
Do you want to resist the decree of his Majesty?
Leyan hasn't been found, how can I just leave?
I hope to atone for my fault.
I won't shrink from my responsibility.
I must find Leyan back.
Look at your current condition.
If you don't get treatment in time,
you can hardly see her Highness in the future,
not to mention working for his Majesty.
You should think twice which
one is the most important.
I can go back to report.
However, Hao,
Leyan is just like my sister.
Please remember...
I will try my best.
Boss, do you really think this
kerchief can sell well in Cangzhou?
Yunzhou is famous for handicraft industry.
Most of the people there are weavers.
What about Cangzhou?
Look, this delicate skill and
stitch looks like royal style.
If we bring this to Cangzhou,
the royal ladies must treasure it!
Look, I embroidered a rabbit.
Other people always embroider
the rabbit's eyes in red
but I embroidered it in green.
Because there are meadows in the rabbit's
eyes, that means freedom.
I think the girl who embroidered
this must be sophisticate.
What are you doing?
Where is this kerchief from?
Do you want to be my competitor?
I'm not interested in the business.
I'm asking you again.
Where did you get the kerchief?
I've been a merchant for decades
but never been afraid of threat.
Let me tell you,
a business man only cares about profit.
Is this enough?
Boss?
Weaving workshop of western suburb in Yunzhou,
It's made by a young lady.
Your Highness, it turns out
that you are still in Yunzhou.
I'm too careless.
He left so quickly!
Today is the Mid-autumn Festival,
a festival for families to gather together.
However,
I have something sad to tell you.
What's that?
Actually, it can't be called as a sad story.
It's a good news.
Because of the military havoc,
the government notes door to door
that if anyone in the border
who
wants to go back to the central plain
can go with their army to the south.
At that time, a new identity will be registered.
It's said that they also distributes lands.
Really?
That means I can go back home!
Perfect!
We have the fate to meet each other,
how about we selling Ms.
Chai's cloth before we leave?
Okay.
Of course!
Whatever, the weaving workshop of
western suburb is always our home.
It will be here forever.
Okay, go to sell the cloth now.
Nobody can go if she sells even a penny less.
- Yes.
- Okay.
Let's go.
- Yan
- Here.
- This one.
- Yan.
Just stay, you're homeless.
I won't make you hungry once I've got any food.
Thank you, Ms. Chai.
Ms. Chai, may I ask where is
the troop to the south going?
They will go straight to the south.
I think they may pass by many places.
Will they go to Luoyang?
Do you want to go to Luoyang?
One of my houses is located in Luoyang.
Ms. Chai, please let me go with
them to sell the cloth for you.
I want to pay your favor back as much as I can.
Don't you worry about the
manhunt of local authority?
I think it is fine.
Didn't you say that no one
is asking about me now?
Okay.
Go with them.
It's good to get more experience.
Here.
Go.
Thank you, mom.
Good.
Come here.
[Yunzhou.]
Let's go.
I bet you'd like here.
There!
There're more!
Looks nice!
How much is it?
Hurry, hurry up!
Coming!
Taste this, is it yummy?
Yes.
Mimi, how is it?
Did you enjoy it?
Should we go purchasing now?
Don't rush.
This is my first time to see
so many people and goods!
What's more, they look so happy!
Today is the Mid-autumn Festival.
Of course it is bustling.
Mid-autumn Festival?
The Mid-autumn Festival is also
called as the festival of moon.
Every year, the people in the central plain
gather together to appreciate
the moon on this day.
And...
Eat the mooncake.
How do you know?
Do you think you're the only
one who is knowledgable?
Mimi.
Did I say anything wrong?
No.
So the Mid-autumn Festival
should be spent with family?
Actually, it's not that interesting.
Just see the moon with the family members.
Nothing special.
Look there!
Let's go!
Candid haws on sell!
This cloth looks good.
Mimi, look.
It's suitable for you.
Come on!
This color?
I think it's more like auntie Su Yili's style.
How about this?
This color is special.
This is suitable for Su Yishe.
Let's go.
Lady.
Look, lady.
Do you like this pattern?
Unfortunately,
the cloth with embroidery was sold out,
if not, you must look great in that pattern.
You should show this earlier.
This is really good.
Today is a festival, I want to buy it as a gift.
Today is the Mid-autumn Festival.
If you like,
you can pick more for your family.
They must feel happy to see it.
No need.
Lady.
Did I say anything wrong?
Don't badger with me.
I won't buy.
Lady.
I didn't mean to let you buy my cloth.
When I mentioned about your family, you...
Mimi.
Get away from me.
That girl said without thinking just now.
Don't mind it.
You shouldn't talk about it, either.
Well, I've got bad temper just now.
I'm sorry.
No need to say sorry.
It's fine once you feel happy.
Shall we go on shopping?
Do you want to eat this?
- Yes.
- Sachet, come and have a look.
Be careful to hold it.
Mooncake.
Mooncake on sell.
This looks tasty.
How about I buying you one?
As my apology.
Okay, I accept that.
Mooncakes.
Mooncakes on sell.
Hello.
How much for a mooncake?
Three coins for five, reasonable price.
Okay.
They're all just ready.
What's wrong?
Do you keep Changge's money bag?
No.
I don't keep it.
No good.
It seems I've lost Changge's money bag.
Just lost some money, I've got enough.
It's not a matter of money.
This is a money bag made by Changge.
Just a bag.
I will buy ten for her later.
She won't blame you.
No.
I can never lose the gift from Changge!
I have to find it back!
I'll go back now.
Mimi.
Where are you going?
Don't be anxious.
Let's recall which stalls we've been to.
You might leave it behind
in one of those stalls.
Right.
Trust me, I'll help you find it out.
You can look for it in this market.
I will go back to the previous
stalls to have a look.
Let's meet here later.
Okay, go now.
The stalls just now.
One hundred and sixty-one.
One hundred and sixty-two.
One hundred and sixty-three.
Finally I can pay Ms.
Chai's favor back this time.
But I feel so sorry for that lady.
She might think of something
grievous by my words.
I should apologize to her
if I can see her again.
Don't move!
You're back.
Certainly I should.
I knew it!
Lady, you must like this cloth.
Let me give you this as a gift for apology.
What? Do you want to end this
by giving me a roll of cloth?
What do you think?
I certainly want you return me
the money bag you've stolen.
What are you doing?
This is my bag!
How could it be yours!
What a coincidence?
This is exactly the same as the one I lost.
Even the ugly rabbit on it is the same.
Give it back to me!
You must recognize it
wrongly, this is really mine.
Thief!
You stole my bag but deny it!
- How dare you grab it?
- Give it to me.
What are you doing?
I said it was my money bag,
how can you behave so rudely?
I..
Unreasonable.
I didn't!
I discussed with you in nice manner and tone.
But you refused to return it to me.
Give it back to me,
or else I'd take it by myself.
You're so unreasonable.
Fine.
You want to be reasonable, right?
Tell me, can you prove
this is your money bag?
There is one hundred and
sixty-three coins in the bag.
I earned it by selling the cloth roll by roll.
The bag is at your hand,
of course you know how many coins in it.
Fine.
Show me your proof if you think this is yours.
This rabbit.
I used the ugly but cute
colors of white and green.
Besides, the stitch has been
repeatedly removed and sewed.
The most important is,
there is a twisted character
of "rabbit" sewed in the bag.
[Rabbit]
How do you know that?
This is my money bag!
See? I'm telling the truth.
Really.
See?
This thief stole my bag but said it was hers.
She's a liar!
Listen, I won't take
any one of your coin.
I'm in a hurry today,
or else I would not let you go.
Thief!
Stop there!
Shame on her.
How could she steal from others?
Right.
Let's go.
What a bad girl.
What happened?
Forget it.
If you didn't sell it well, it's okay.
This is your first time to sell at the market,
you must be shy to cry your wares.
If you sincerely want to go to
Luoyang, I won't deduct your money.
It's okay.
You earned so much money!
Leyan, you're amazing!
I looked down upon you.
Leyan, have you decided to go back to Luoyang?
Give me your hand.
Take this money.
You need lots of money on you way.
Don't tell them.
I will pay you all wages later.
This is my secret reward to you.
This is our fate.
But there would be hardness
and evil conditions on the way.
It won't be as cosy as Yunzhou.
Can you stand it?
I had never gone out of my home alone before.
Even though I were driven out
I would not be able to know how to go back home.
But now I've learned a lot
from you and the ladies.
I can even sell the cloth at the market.
I think...
I can find the way back home.
I will never forget you.
Okay, okay.
Mimi.
I found it!
How can you be so careless?
You left it in the previous shop.
Check it.
Anything missed?
Well...
Oh no.
This is embroidered by Changge.
So the thief just now...
What thief?
The girl...
Mimi, where are you going?
The market is off.
The gate of the city is closing.
We made some money these days.
I will distribute the
money to each of you.
Now that you've decided to leave,
we should say goodbye in harmony.
In a word,
hope you all be safe and sound.
There are some flapjacks in the kitchen.
Take some with you.
When you leave Yunzhou,
it would be hard to eat
something warm on the way.
Here.
I'm worried about you the most!
You've been here just for a few days,
learning only some brief skills.
But at least you've got a
craftsmanship for living.
You should be diligent on your
way so that you can survive.
Why are you crying?
Everyone has its destiny.
I'm still here to weave.
Everybody, promise me you will live a good life.
Someday we might meet each other in the future.
Come on.
Go and pack up.
Go with the troop before
the city gate is closed.
Go and pack up.
Go.
Mimi, it's getting dark,
who are you looking for?
No.
She's left.
The girl who sells the cloth,
this money bag is really hers.
I grabbed it from her just now.
Look, although the bags are nearly the
same, one is brand new,
the other has been used for some time.
Maybe they are both made by Changge.
The only difference is the
time Changge embroidered it.
They are exactly the same.
How could it be such a coincident.
I don't know it, either.
Maybe only Changge knows the true story.
Let's go back and ask her.
I've blamed you frequently these days,
but that is for helping
you to improve your skill.
Don't be mad at me.
Remember to follow them closely later.
The weather is cold,
remember to put on more
clothes in case having a cold.
Ms. Chai, are you sure you won't go with us?
All generations of my family live in Yunzhou.
This is my home.
Thank you for taking care of me these days.
Leyan can't give you anything else
but a bag made by myself as a souvenir.
Come on, time to go!
When you meet with a trouble
alone, don't be anxious or scared.
Learn to ask for help if necessary.
Just stay away from the danger.
Don't get injured.
I believe that you can protect yourself well.
By the way,
I packed many flapjacks in your bag.
You can eat them for a long while.
Don't let them see it.
The gate is closing.
Go.
Ms. Chai, take care.
Stand up.
Be careful on the way.
[Yunzhou]
We can't go out?
Let's go back tomorrow.
It's all my fault.
I lost the bag so we are late.
It's impossible for us to go
back to Eagle Division today.
It's not a big deal.
Every year I purchase in the border market,
I'd stay for one or two nights.
Nobody would worry about this.
What should we do tonight?
Go with me.
Brother Mu Jin will take you
to live in the post house.
I...
Wait me.
I've asked Mu Jin to buy
the cloth and herb we need.
[August 15th of lunar calendar.]
What's wrong?
Today is August 15th of lunar calendar.
Right, the winter is coming.
August 15th of lunar calendar,
it is the Mid-autumn Festival
of your hometown, right?
I heard that in the central plain,
people would appreciate the moon and lights,
and eat mooncakes every Mid-autumn Festival.
Can Ms. Su Yili make moon cakes?
I will let her have a try.
No need to bother.
The meaning of this festival is not about these.
Once the home and the family is with you,
it can be called as Mid-autumn Festival.
Tegin Sun, if you have no
more command I'm leaving now.
Wait.
I've got something for you.
Here you are.
How can this stone shine?
Look at the light.
Is it like the glowworm we saw that night?
Why do you give this to me?
I just want to tell you
that once you sincerely
pursue the beautiful things,
they can surely be saved.
Likewise,
the place with family is home
while the place makes you feel
secure can be called as home as well.
There is also happy reunion in the grasslands.
Actually, I hope peace and happiness
would last forever both in the
grasslands and the central plain.
Hope there will be no more war.
Thanks for your gift, Tegin Sun.
Goodbye.
Mimi.
You scared me.
Haven't you gone to bed?
What are you doing here?
I'm watching them spend the festival here.
The boy over there held a pile of moon
cakes, staying with his family.
They are happy and harmonious.
Try it.
Where did you buy it?
When I searched the money bag for you,
the mooncake stall hasn't been off.
And you were not back, so I bought one there.
Have a taste, it's still warm.
It's been a long time,
how could it be still warm?
I kept it in my arms, warming it by my body.
How is it?
It tastes good.
How about having a taste as well?
Don't tear it.
Mooncakes should look like the moon,
if you tear it up,
the meaning of reunion would be ruined.
Really?
Absolutely.
The is the local custom.
Well...
It tastes just so so,
and may hurt my teeth.
Anyway, I think it tastes good.
Let me take one more bite,
I didn't get the flavor.
How is it?
Very tasty.
Great.
♫ You're in my sight. ♫
♫ My heartbeat is fast. ♫
♫ Sneaking in my hairs. ♫
Mimi, are you homesick?
No.
You can tell me about your past.
I won't tell anyone else, I swear.
I have been kidnapped as a
servant since my childhood.
So I can remember little about my hometown.
What a coincidence.
I was a servant, too.
You?
I'm a servant born in the Khan's Tent,
so I haven't been to my hometown at all.
If so, how can you...
Became the military
counsellor of Eagle Division,
admired and followed by ten thousands of people?
Stop the narcissism.
Actually these are all because of Sun's help.
When I was a child,
I was nearly beaten to death.
Sun saved me.
Later, he was titled as "Great
Warrior" by the Great Khan.
He took me to the Eagle Division.
Later, Eagle Division became my home.
Mimi.
Actually, Eagle Division is a nice place.
Look at Li Changge.
She also lives well there, doesn't she?
I hope someday,
Eagle Division can be your home as well.
It's too late.
Go back and have a good rest.
Okay, you should go to bed early, too.
We'll set off tomorrow.
Changge.
Where did you get this?
Kind of grabbed by me.
Yesterday, I carelessly lost the
money bag you gave me in the market.
And a girl's bag was exactly the same as yours.
I though mine is stolen by her.
So..
However, Changge,
I saw you embroider this money bag here.
How could she get the same one?
I made one to a friend of mine as well.
Mimi, what does the girl look like?
She is not tall,
but her appearance is comely.
And she's timid.
I didn't say anything harsh while
she dared not to speak more.
It's really Leyan.
Why is Leyan in Yunzhou?
Leyan?
She is a best friend of mine before.
Mimi.
Where did you meet her?
At Yunzhou's market.
She took a bamboo basket with
her to sell cloth at the market.
There must be something wrong.
How could Leyan be in Yunzhou?
A girl like her who has never
worked should do business now.
No.
I have to go to find her.
Mimi.
Thank you.
Changge, where are you going?
Yunzhou.
Do you need... my company?
- Great Khan decided to set
off now?
- Lower your voice.
There is no sign before.
Great Khan has planned about this long before.
Tegin Sun, the military
counselor made me inform you
that she went to Yunzhou for some business.
Does she really want to inform you?
Let her be this time.
Mu Jin, do not tell her
about my military expedition.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad