sub by kisscambodia
Official movie site: kisskh.me
YIN YANG MASTERS USE
THE DOCTRINE OF FIVE ELEMENTS
TO DISTINGUISH MEN FROM MONSTERS.
RIGHTEOUS MEN GATHER
IN THE YIN YANG BUREAU
TO TRAIN AND CAPTURE EVIL SPIRITS.
Qingming.
What have you done?
Cimu…
was killed.
Cimu.
What did you do to Cimu?
It's not me.
A monster broke out of the Subduing Cell.
It stole the Scale Stone.
So many people are dead.
Why are you the only one alive?
It wasn't me.
-I didn't do it.
-You will never change.
You are the true monster.
No…
No, I'm not!
Baini.
What happened?
Qingming killed Cimu
and tried to steal the Scale Stone.
That's impossible.
-It can't be him.
-He has already fled.
You can't be the chief
if you can't tell right from wrong.
The bellflower bracelet.
SEVEN YEARS LATER
PINGJING CITY
When Pangu opened the heavens
men and monsters coexisted in harmony.
But the evil monster, Xiangliu,
claimed to be the Monster Emperor.
This nine-headed serpent
hypnotized other monsters
and ravaged human lands.
Fortunately, Yin Yang Masters fought back
and created a powerful weapon,
the Tushan Sword.
They decapitated Xiangliu
and drove back the monsters.
From then on, the worlds of men
and monsters were separated.
Humans lived within the city,
while monsters lived in the Monster Realm.
Each side kept to its own.
Any monster that crossed the border
would be seen as a remnant
of the Monster Emperor.
They would be captured immediately
and imprisoned in the Subduing Cell.
Move aside.
Capital Guards are under orders
to escort tributes out of the city.
Move aside.
Capital Guards are under orders
to escort tributes out of the city.
MONSTER REALM IS DANGEROUS
LEAVE AT YOUR OWN RISK
It's the ghost festival period now.
Yet our Captain volunteered
to deliver the offerings.
This is simply
looking for trouble.
I agree. Why must we do this errand?
It's the Yin Yang Bureau's job.
There's something in the forest.
Who is it?
Go!
Look here.
If you dare to mess
with the Capital Guards,
this is what will happen to you.
Good!
Sword!
Give me the sword!
Those are imperial tributes.
How dare you!
I'm just a passerby.
Let's help each other.
Good sir.
You're welcome.
Hey!
What are you doing?
I helped to get rid of the monsters.
It's nothing.
I'm not asking for payoffs.
I'll just pick a few things here.
No one is paying you.
Who…
Sir.
You are in the wrong here.
Those who escaped monsters' fangs
usually show their gratitude.
This took me a while, but you
are being stingy.
These are imperial tributes.
We can't give them away.
The three ferret monsters knew you.
Perhaps,
you are a monster in human guise.
Sir.
You are being small-minded.
No more excuses.
Judgment awaits you.
Sir, if you keep pestering,
you will fall
as soon as you take a step.
You are with the Yin Yang Bureau.
You dare knowingly break the law?
Evil thief!
What's your rank in the Yin Yang Bureau?
Tell me your name!
My name
is Qingming.
Qingming?
I'll never forget you.
I feel bad to see you fall.
That will be all
for today.
The Capital Guards,
where the hell are they?
Master doesn't like us
to keep things for ourselves.
Will we get busted for stealing this much?
Don't say a word.
Don't mess around.
There are more here?
YIN YANG BUREAU
SCALE STONE WARD
Something is wrong in the Subduing Cell.
SUBDUING CELL
Move aside.
Return to purity,
seal!
-Monsters have broken in.
-Chief.
Who is guarding the Scale Stone?
-Sunless day, moonless night.
-All laws unravel, all gods retreat.
-Order to break.
Return to the right path,
purity inside out.
Order to seal.
About nine li
to the northeastern direction.
Take it out.
What is that?
The Scale Stone.
It's so shiny.
It's precious.
Don't touch the Scale Stone.
I got you.
-It's mine.
-I saw it first.
Let go!
Ferret monster.
Put it down!
Stop!
What happened to you?
I have failed and should be punished.
I took the Scale Stone
from the Yin Yang Bureau,
but I ran into three ferret monsters.
I don't know whose order they followed,
but they took the Scale Stone and fled.
"Three ferret monsters"?
Those must have been Qingming's.
He saw through my plan.
How could you ruin
something so simple?
The Raven Hound twins.
The best fighters in the Monster Realm.
Everyone says you both are invincible.
But it seems like
both of you are unremarkable.
The Scale Stone has been removed
from the Ward.
Raven Hound, your trip was worth it.
You can rest now.
Do it again.
Don't stop.
Lift it higher.
Stab forward.
Stab sideward.
Taking the tribute isn't enough.
Master expects greater things from you.
Lift it higher.
We practice
and train for the battle
to prepare for the future.
Lift your arms.
Use your strength.
Where are you aiming at?
If it wasn't for Master who took you in
as familiars,
each and every one of you
would still be strays
and bullied by all.
Come.
Stab forward.
Again.
Where did you go?
What's the matter?
Stop.
Someone fell. Who fell?
He ate something.
And you hit someone.
We meet again,
Qingming.
The Scale Stone has finally left
the Yin Yang Bureau's control.
You must help me return to the world.
This is your destiny.
Do you understand?
Qingming.
Light of the North Star,
order to seal.
Did something go wrong?
Look after the Ferrets.
It's about the Scale Stone.
I'm going to the Monster Realm.
The bureau lost the Scale Stone
and Subduing Cell has been
in chaos ever since.
The Protectors used spells
to contain them.
It took them all night.
I refuse to believe it is a coincidence.
Qingming's monsters
stole the Scale Stone.
Evidently,
he failed seven years ago
and now he wants payback.
The loss of the Scale Stone is a disaster.
It's hard to guard
against traitors from within.
If there was no traitor within the bureau,
how else could
the Raven Hound break the seal
and use our spells to destroy the Tower?
The Scale Stone was just stolen,
but the ferret monsters acted right away.
The bureau should have captured
that traitor years ago,
but Chief is softhearted.
Xican.
The thief now leaves unpunished.
Elder, you don't need to worry
about my past with Qingming.
-It's a reminder--
-Elder Xican.
Please mind your words.
I will handle this issue.
A hundred years ago,
the elders at the bureau
sacrificed their lives
one after another
to cut off the head
of the monster named Xiangliu.
But the serpent has nine heads
and its power was great.
Although its body was destroyed,
its power was not so easily dispersed,
so it was refined into
the Scale Stone in the end.
The Scale Stone was sealed
within this Tower.
Hence, defending the Tower
and keeping the Scale Stone safe
is the Yin Yang Bureau's
greatest responsibility.
It will be up to you in the future.
You can never be careless in your duties.
Cimu.
Please lead everyone
in the protection spell chant.
Yes, Elder.
Black Turtle holds the north,
Vermilion Bird calms the south.
-Black Turtle holds the north,
-Vermilion Bird calms the south.
Return to the right path,
purity inside out.
-Return to the right path,
-purity inside out.
Qingming.
-Don't chant along with them.
-Order to seal.
-You are a monster,
a monster with my blood.
-Release me
-Black Turtle holds the north,
-and join me.
-Vermilion Bird calms the south.
-No!
What's wrong?
Qingming.
-Qingming.
-Qingming, stop playing around.
-This is the Scale Stone Ward.
-Qingming.
He's a half-monster.
He carries the blood of monsters.
Did it call out to you?
What did Xiangliu say to you?
That's nonsense.
Qingming will be a Yin Yang Master.
He was an abandoned infant
who came from nowhere.
The bureau only kept him
-to check on him.
-Silence, all of you!
-That's an order.
-Baini, you are not the chief yet.
-You can't order--
-Shut up.
Sit down.
-Yes, Cimu.
Qingming.
Qingming!
Return to the right path,
purity inside out.
Order to seal.
Qingming.
Do not speak
of what happened today.
-Yes, Cimu.
Whether you are a man or a monster,
you must control yourself.
Otherwise,
you will destroy yourself.
TOMB OF CIMU
Cimu.
I won't let you die in vain.
Qingming didn't leave us with any choice.
Yin Yang Bureau should be ashamed
for not capturing the traitor
for the past seven years.
We will scour the entire Monster Realm
to bring him in.
COURT OF THE GUARDS
Give us the order.
What order?
For us to go to the Yin Yang Bureau,
arrest the monster thief,
and retrieve the tributes.
There was an emergency
at the Yin Yang Bureau last night.
How would they have time
to bother about the tributes?
I hereby order
Seventh-Rank captain Yuan Boya
to be suspended for investigations.
If he does not return
the tributes within three days,
confiscate his possessions.
You tried hard to think of ways
to achieve your ambitions.
See what happens now.
You don't know your limits.
I'll bring that monster back here.
You'll see.
Sir, I'll be honest with you.
I have always received
my goods from Yanyan Le.
What? Who is he?
A mystic and an expert on monsters.
-"Expert on monsters"?
-Yes.
-Come.
-Take a look!
His tent is over there.
Ask him about Qingming if you want.
Quit wasting your breath.
Hurry up and talk.
There is no road to the Monster Realm.
-Will you talk or not?
-That's painful!
No.
You who are in there.
I'm Yuan Boya of the Capital Guard.
I'm here on court orders.
Where are your manners?
The burning big incense stick outside
means we have guests.
You can't just barge in here.
Are you that mystic named Yan Lele?
I'm here to ask you about someone
called Qingming.
Do you know where he lives?
The one you are asking about
is the Yin Yang Master, Qingming.
That's him. I fought with him last night.
He fled in defeat,
-so I must bring him in.
-Liar!
Don't hide back there.
Come out here and talk!
How dare you
attack an imperial official!
I'm going to take you in.
If you can't even beat me,
why would Qingming flee then?
Are you Yan Lele?
I'm the only one who gets to talk here.
I'm here to find Yan Lele. Hurry--
Shut up!
His name is Yanyan Le.
Isn't that what I just said?
You are not very smart
for a Capital Guard.
That's why I need you.
Are you going to tell me? Or should I
-No.
-use my umbrella again?
It's right behind me,
inside that pile of fur.
If you had said this earlier,
I wouldn't have hurt you like this.
Not just anyone can enter
the Monster Realm.
The map won't help you.
How does Qingming get in and out then?
Qingming is a half-monster.
-"A half-monster"?
-And he has the bureau's spells.
"Spells"?
I have a spell.
You have a spell?
I…
-Where is it?
-You…
Untie me.
My young captain,
I can see that you're something special
and not ordinary at all.
Stand back!
This is it.
Sir.
I, Shenle, am willing to help you
get into the Monster Realm
and arrest Qingming.
If I get to the Monster Realm,
will I be able to find Qingming?
I knew right from the start
that he was a bad guy.
But he turns out to be
the son of a man and a monster?
What do you know?
Qingming's bloodline is rare.
Only he can command monsters.
All right.
He chose to be a monster
when he could be a man.
The next time I see him,
I'll kill him immediately.
Here. Check the map.
Just how much farther is it?
How can I check when I'm tied up?
I tied you up to protect you.
The map says to walk
about 35 li past the Temple of Earth
and we'll see the statues at the entrance.
CRUMBLING CLIFF
See, we are here.
This…
It looks like we found the entrance.
The problem is…
How can we cross?
Hey, you.
Give me the spell.
Hurry up.
A halo of golden light engulfs me.
Flying within and beyond the three realms.
The sun travels and the shadow changes.
A halo of golden light engulfs me.
Flying within and beyond the three realms.
The sun travels and the shadow changes.
The spell. Why…
Why did it burn away? You…
You are a liar!
-Come--
-You are the liar.
You don't even have a badge.
Behave yourself.
-Stop messing around.
-Let me go!
Isn't this a path?
It takes some time, you know.
Don't make a fuss if you know nothing.
Are you coming or not?
The bridge will disappear
if you don't come now.
"Disappear"?
There is no way you knew this was here.
What is that?
Plum leaf water.
It covers the human scent.
Why didn't you do it earlier?
I was so excited, I forgot about it.
Give me some.
Here we are.
The Red Tower.
The one in charge of the Monster Realm,
the Port Master, lives here.
Qingming does business with him.
Fish-eye earrings.
How much is it?
Can you focus here?
How does it look?
It's horrible.
Qingming won't show up at this time.
Go to the bridge and check
if you are worried.
Hey!
Take a bite.
It's all right.
What is it made from?
-Jeez. You--
-Go away.
All right.
Here. Try putting this belt on.
What is this?
A present.
You look handsome.
I like it.
We have serious things to do
-and you are confessing--
-Master!
Master, I'm Shenle!
The thief?
Master.
Master, I've finally found you.
This is a gift I bought for you.
Please accept it.
I can finally capture you, thief.
Go away.
Stay away from my master.
Master, this Capital Guard
is trying to harm you.
I came to warn you.
Remember my contribution.
You monster thief
and freak.
I, Yuan Boya, am taking you in.
What's your name again?
Yuan Boya.
I'm a Seventh-Rank captain. Hey!
-Give it back…
-Is your name written like this?
Let go.
Are you using monster magic again?
It's familiar spell.
-What spell?
-Familiar spell is cast on you.
What spell?
Master, cast it on me too.
-I'm willing to give my life to you.
-I can't control my limbs.
-Free me from it!
-Master!
Master.
Master…
What are you doing?
Hey, stop it!
-Thieving monster!
-Master!
Master!
Master.
Thieving monster, remove it!
Let go of me, Yuan Boya!
An honored guest has arrived.
I'm honored to welcome you.
We were apart for one day,
but it feels like forever.
Your familiars sent me two carts
of tributes just yesterday,
and you are here in person today.
Could it be
that you have brought me another treasure?
This time,
I have come to get something.
Everything changes
and change brings opportunity.
So tell me, what do you want?
The Tushan Sword.
Mentioning it is taboo here.
How can I have it?
Think twice before you answer.
My precious treasures!
Back then, you swore your loyalty
to the Yin Yang Bureau.
They lent you the sword
to lead the monsters,
but you have only made it your own.
Stop playing dumb.
It's a trivial matter.
I'm surprised you remember it.
The Tushan Sword killed
the Monster Emperor a hundred years ago.
The Monster Realm has never recovered.
The Monster Emperor is dead
so everyone has forgotten about the sword.
What would you need it for?
The monster's body may be dead,
but its soul still lives.
It doesn't hurt to be prepared.
I can't offend the Yin Yang Bureau.
I'm warning you.
Don't overstep your bounds.
You are in the Monster Realm,
which is my domain.
I have the final say.
Don't break anything.
You have to negotiate to do business.
You can't leave me at a loss.
I'll give you two live humans.
"Two live humans"?
Would you be more amenable
about the deal?
Master!
Master, look here!
Hey!
Help!
Where did this come from?
It doesn't look like a monster at all.
Yuan Boya, be careful!
What are you doing?
-Let her go!
-You should worry about yourself!
My fellow monsters.
This is an unprecedented fight
between a man and a monster.
A fight until death.
It is an amazing sight to behold.
Hurry and place your bets!
You are a capital guard, right?
Fight with all you got,
or your friend will pay the price.
I present to you the Evil Red Ghost.
He has never left the arena since birth
and he has never lost a fight.
Only one of you
may leave this arena alive.
The more Red Ghost gets hit,
the bigger he becomes.
That is his ultimate tactic.
It's no wonder why he never loses.
The Tushan Sword's energy is too great.
I won't be going in.
You came here quickly.
Who knew the Yin Yang Bureau
was so capable?
The light shines.
Open.
Master's spell?
Three Thousand Miles of Universe, break!
I hope you're doing well.
I'm not here to reminisce.
Return the things
that do not belong to you.
Freeze!
So, you want this sword too?
Stop playing dumb.
I want the Scale Stone.
"The Scale Stone"?
What does that have to do with me?
Stop pretending.
Talk to your Ferrets.
"My Ferrets"?
Although they are mischievous,
they won't steal the Scale Stone.
Do you trust your monsters that much?
Of course.
I've made them my familiars.
They are not hateful monsters.
Familiars go through life and death
with their masters
and never betray them.
That's what you taught me.
Its nose!
Hit its nose!
Nicely hit!
What kind of fight is this?
It's a scam!
End it!
Loser!
Kill it!
Finish it!
The rules state
that only the winner can leave.
Let's go!
Stop them!
Don't let them escape!
Be careful!
This guy is hard to fight against!
Where are you going?
Don't move!
Be careful!
-The Tushan Sword!
-Why is it here?
This monster is helping you!
I don't need its help!
Whoever brings back the sword
will be rewarded.
Monster thief!
You are walking into your own trap.
Capital Guard.
That thing you are carrying
is worth more than your life.
Give it to me.
-Is it yours?
-It is mine.
You lost something
and now you are worried?
Hurry up and give it to me.
Come with me to the Court of the Guards
and prove my innocence.
All right.
Yin Yang Bureau is here!
Chief.
Baini!
Baini.
Follow them quickly!
Why did it follow us?
This…
What is this place?
This is Master's home.
The stolen tributes
are definitely here then.
No, we are on the same side.
Don't hurt each other.
Although you followed Master,
we are not friends.
I don't want to be your friend.
I recognize all your faces for sure.
You are the filthy monster thieves
who stole my tributes.
Who are you calling a thief?
I'll rip your mouth!
Shut up.
Pretty monster,
please forgive this fool.
They are guests.
Let them in.
All right.
Thank you, miss.
We will just look around.
We won't cause any trouble.
Baini.
Is there still a place for me
in the bureau?
What is this?
It's a token of my trust.
These are for girls. I don't want it.
This bellflower bracelet
makes you my familiar.
This spell is to be used on monsters.
I'm human.
You are a half-monster. That counts too.
I'm not a monster!
I'll never be a monster!
Qingming, it's all right to be a monster.
Be my familiar, and I'll be your master.
Don't you know?
If a monster has a master,
it has a home,
so it will never turn evil.
In that case,
I,
Qingming,
from this day forward
will be the familiar of Baini.
Our alliance is sealed.
Let's live and die as one,
and never betray each other.
Never betray each other.
Be careful with your wound.
I promise
that I'll help you find the truth.
Your promises
are worthless.
If you don't believe me,
why did you save me?
I'm looking for the Scale Stone.
Everyone knows you and your monsters
are stealing everywhere.
You must be involved.
All the monsters here
are like me.
They can't enter Pingjing City
and they don't belong
in the Monster Realm.
They don't have a home.
Theft and robbery
are for survival.
-We have no choice.
-So now you stand with the monsters.
You and I made an oath together long ago.
You chose to go astray
and ruined everything.
I left the Yin Yang Bureau
as a last resort.
That night, seven years ago,
it was my turn to guard
the Scale Stone seal.
I ran into Cimu.
Qingming.
As always,
he showed concern for my situation.
Cimu.
Are you still bothered by Xiangliu?
The ghost festival
brings extra discomfort.
Thank you for teaching me
the protection spell.
I often chant it recently.
Stay away from trouble.
If you truly lose control one day,
it would be better
to reverse the spell and self-destruct
than to let Xiangliu possess you.
"Reverse the spell"?
I'll guard the Ward
instead of you tonight.
But unexpectedly,
the monster's voice that night
was especially powerful.
I knew
that something had happened.
The Tower.
My comrades' bodies were everywhere.
I tried to find Cimu,
but the Tower had already melted.
The evil in the Scale Stone
drove me insane.
Is anyone there?
Poor Qingming.
You are treated as an outcast
in the human world,
but little do you know
that you belong to a rare
and treasured bloodline.
Purity inside out.
Order to seal.
Don't bother with that useless spell.
You are a monster,
a monster with my blood.
Yet another thief for the Scale Stone.
It was the Snow Lady.
She should be locked in the Subduing Cell.
How did she get into this place?
Cimu.
-Cimu!
-Qingming, go!
That was the last time I saw Cimu.
I was forced to act in defense,
but I ended up watching Cimu
being shattered into pieces by me.
The Snow Lady also disappeared.
I desperately tried to find the Snow Lady
in the past seven years.
"The Snow Lady"?
Who else besides you
could send monsters to get past the seal?
Cimu died because of you seven years ago.
Now, seven years later,
more tombstones have been raised
because of you.
You are not innocent.
If you are so sure,
why do you still have this token?
It's this thing again.
Something is wrong.
Don't touch anything in the courtyard.
I just did.
Maybe the stolen tributes are inside.
It's not your turn.
Qingming.
The Tushan Sword!
The Ferret has mutated.
Stab him!
What more do you have to say?
If the Yin Yang Bureau had done its job,
the Ferret wouldn't have
ended up like this.
I won't pester you today.
I'll let your monsters have
a few more days of peace.
But when I return,
I'll destroy this courtyard.
My brother.
This token of you and Master,
I'll leave it with you.
You were Master's familiar
until death.
Every monster needs a master
in its life.
If it has a home,
it will never turn evil.
But back then,
my fellow monster sisters
didn't even get a proper burial.
"Your monster sisters"?
I was an orphan.
I had to beg for food.
One time,
I was chased by a dog.
In the end,
I passed out in front of a house.
I remember how good it smelled.
It filled me with energy
and my wounds didn't hurt at all.
You must have been dreaming.
It was better than a dream.
That place was called the Courtyard.
"The Courtyard"?
Isn't that a famous brothel?
How could a brothel be good?
It was great
because they treated me well.
When I was seven years old,
the Yin Yang Bureau came.
Those people said my sisters
were monsters lurking in the city,
and they must leave Pingjing City.
Those who cooperated were sealed away.
And those who fought
were killed.
But among them,
there was this young man.
He was also trembling.
He was a Yin Yang Master,
but he didn't harm my sisters.
Instead, he picked me up.
He also picked up my sisters' umbrellas.
Since that day,
I saw him as my master.
Wherever my master goes
will be my home.
I'm no one's master.
Must you interrupt now?
You are the problem.
If you are a monster,
why are you acting like a Yin Yang Master?
If you are a human,
why would you keep all these monsters?
-It's ridiculous.
-We were both abandoned.
Why must we insult each other?
How can you compare me to you?
Aren't we both
oddballs that got expelled?
I…
Come.
Let's drink.
What's the matter?
Are you afraid that I've poisoned it?
-I'm not afraid of you.
-Yuan Boya.
Stop it.
Let's drink.
I'm not afraid.
Stop getting into trouble.
The chief left with serious wounds.
I've already cast a spell to stop her.
The Scale Stone must not be returned
to the Yin Yang Bureau.
After this round,
I'll take you back
and close the case.
Even the person closest to me
said that I betrayed her,
yet you still believe
that I'll keep my promise.
You promised me.
Are you going to break it?
If you have any gratitude,
you should toast to my master now.
Did you think you can defeat Red Ghost?
It was my master's spell that helped you.
Hurry up and take off this spell.
A grown man wearing a red thread
is embarrassing.
Don't be an ingrate.
Master, I want it.
That's not a familiar spell.
That red thread
is just the master's joke on him.
So, you fooled me?
-It isn't a spell?
-Only monsters can be familiars.
It's impossible for humans.
-That's all right.
-We, humans,
don't even qualify to be familiars?
The human heart changes easily.
A sealing alliance that lasts until death,
how could a human manage that?
Don't look down on humans.
If you say we are mean,
then your master is half-mean.
And if I say monsters are fools,
then your master is half a fool.
He is that
mean and foolish
freak.
Well said.
I really am a freak.
From one freak to another, let's toast.
I'm a freak as well.
I should have a drink too.
Foolish monster.
You little monster.
Would you like a drink?
-You are a fool.
-Little monster.
Why am I here?
-Chief.
Chief.
We rushed here once we had located you.
Chief, are you all right?
It is dangerous here.
We shouldn't stay.
Take this.
It's the Scale Stone.
Return it to the bureau.
Watch out!
Behind you!
The Scale Stone is important.
Chief, please go.
Baini!
It's you again.
What a misfortune to see you.
If you can kill her
and retrieve the Scale Stone for Master,
you'll surely be rewarded.
The grudges from seven years ago.
Let's…
settle them today.
Come with me if you want your revenge.
It's my fault for not trusting you.
The Scale Stone is still here.
We can still win this.
Snow Lady mentioned a master.
-I'll investigate it.
-Qingming.
When this is over,
this bellflower bracelet
will be yours once again.
Without this bracelet,
you are still my master.
Let's live and die as one,
and never betray each other.
I'll be back.
Where is your master?
There is no need to rush.
You will bow to him soon.
The entire world will bow to him.
Who is it?
The Scale Stone doesn't belong to humans.
It should be returned to where it belongs.
Where does it belong to then?
To the world's
most powerful monster, of course.
Whoever your master is,
today, the old debts must be paid.
You fool.
The master took good care of you
in the bureau.
Weren't you always
grateful for this?
Cimu.
I joined the bureau at the age of nine.
At the age of 30,
I became the youngest Protector.
But what did it matter?
My future
at the Yin Yang Bureau meant nothing.
The mundane attachments,
in my eyes,
are mere distractions.
I know you are obsessed with Qingming,
but I have my own obsessions.
That scorned monster only exists
to show the greatness
of the monsters' power.
If the young Qingming had such power,
then with Xiangliu's aid,
what could possibly be out of reach?
What I need
is…
the Scale Stone's power.
Cimu.
Master Cimu
is our savior.
Do you hear my master's call?
Nonsense.
That night,
Cimu died
right in front of me.
It was a simple illusion.
Master.
SNOW LADY
I, Snow Lady, hereby vow
that I will serve
Master Cimu forever.
He has succeeded.
I…
I cannot live
until the day I witness
my master rule over all.
Mother.
Mother, I'm so scared.
Mother, hurry up. I want to go home.
I long for a world
under the Monster Emperor's rule,
but I was born at the wrong time
and became the bureau's lackey.
If the Monster Emperor returns,
I will sacrifice my life for him.
Where is my wine?
Wine…
-Why are you still lying there?
-Wine…
Hurry up
if you don't want to be barbecued.
-Hurry up.
-Wine…
-He is heavy.
-Barbecue?
Where is the barbecue?
Let's go.
What…
What is going on?
What happened?
What are you distributing?
Attach the spell to your nostrils
to avoid mutation.
-Give me one.
-Humans don't need it.
Why?
Again, you are excluding us.
An evil monster
has obtained the Scale Stone
and opened the gates to Monster Realm.
The monsters are going to invade us.
Invade?
Why are they invading?
Master didn't forget his responsibilities.
He prepared you for war.
In the face of this danger,
we must protect Pingjing City
on Master's behalf.
"Pingjing City"?
Who will invade Pingjing City?
Today is the day.
-Guard the Spirit Bridge.
-"Guard the Spirit Bridge"?
Familiars,
fight with your lives.
The courtyard is destroyed.
There's no way out.
Hey!
Shenle! Where are you all going?
They are using this excuse to flee.
You are not one of us.
Go back to the Capital Guards.
You're right.
I'm not one of them.
What?
What do you mean?
Keep an eye on them?
I should do that.
Hurry up.
Cimu,
I have a question for you.
We are not at the Yin Yang Bureau.
Addressing me like that
is inappropriate.
Seven years ago,
as a Protector at the Yin Yang Bureau,
you colluded with Snow Lady
and killed other Protectors
to steal the Scale Stone.
Order to break!
Master.
Humans can't handle the Scale Stone.
It must be a monster.
-Let me do it.
-Back off.
Master, let go.
Let go!
You will die!
Master.
The alarm has sounded.
Let's retreat.
Yet another thief for the Scale Stone.
I lost an arm,
but I got this strange arm.
It was worth it.
You showed me
the wonder of monsters' power.
You failed to follow your nature
and that's why
you have ended up so pitiful.
Actually, I'm the one
who finds you
far more pitiful.
You are now a monster with nowhere to go.
Maybe my courtyard
can take you in.
Take me in?
I heard Xiangliu's call.
I tortured myself
to create this monstrous body,
and now I have the Scale Stone's power.
You, right now,
are only the mud under my feet.
Xiangliu summoned you?
He said it was my destiny.
I'll become the strongest in the world.
Both men and monsters
must bow to me,
or they will die.
A trick of disguise.
I never expected
to use this sword to kill you.
The Scale Stone
has been refined
over the hundreds of years.
What can this Tushan Sword
do to me?
You should know
you will never see Baini again.
Your beloved,
your master,
is gone.
How is it at this timing
that the freak is missing?
Move aside.
Looks like it's up to me
to handle the situation now.
Will this work?
They are chewing like there's no tomorrow.
-This…
-Chew harder!
Don't let them cross the bridge!
What is happening?
It's terrifying.
A cloud is coming from Monster Realm.
-It's a monster cloud!
-Monster cloud?
Is it poisonous?
Are the monsters attacking?
Shenle!
I'm here!
If we survive this,
give me that belt.
What? A bell?
What bell are you talking about?
I said Red Ghost is indeed my familiar.
He's faster than a bell ring.
Why did everyone stop?
Watch out for tricks.
What is that?
It's Master.
Master.
Master!
Master…
Master told me
that if he dies,
all of you
have to go your own way.
You shouldn't die with him.
It doesn't make a difference if I go back.
I might as well die fighting here.
You can't defend the city without me.
I love watching useless struggles.
It's so much fun.
The bridge is going to break. Retreat!
Shenle.
I will remember you.
I hope you will remember me too.
Yuan Boya!
Destroy the bridge!
Stop them from crossing the bridge!
Qingming.
Baini?
What is this place?
You are awake.
I have been waiting for you.
You finally made it here.
Forget about your familiars.
Forget about the Yin Yang Bureau
and Pingjing City.
Just the two of us,
we can be together forever.
Isn't this
what we have always wanted?
You are not Baini.
Baini would never turn her back
on the world.
-Are you sure of that?
Evil monster.
You must replace Cimu
and join me.
"Replace Cimu"?
You were the one controlling Cimu,
driving him insane.
You kept denying your nature
and refusing my call.
Now, Cimu has struck you
through the heart.
You and I are finally connected.
This is the perfect time to merge with me.
Why does it have to be me?
Cimu has not inherited my blood.
Only you
can truly bring me back to life.
No.
I would rather reverse the spell
and destroy myself
than become your puppet.
But what about them?
Must they be destroyed too?
I made a pact with Baini
to never become an evil monster.
Baini's life is also in your hands.
No.
No!
Cimu has the Scale Stone's power.
I am no match for him.
Join me
and become a real monster.
Acknowledge me as your master
and you still have a chance.
Acknowledge you as my master?
Will you be a weak human
or a monster that can save the world?
Which one would you choose?
Yuan Boya!
Red Ghost!
The bridge is broken.
We'll protect the city
with our lives.
Do you think you can stop me?
I, Seventh-Rank captain Yuan Boya,
will fight alongside you
and die without regret!
Freak.
You pretended to be dead.
How did you…
I was supposed to control both worlds
and rule over all.
Your heart is hollow
and you have no respect for the world
nor attachment to anything.
How could you be worthy enough
to rule the world?
The Scale Stone
cannot be yours.
Chief,
we defended the bridge
and saved the city, thanks to Master.
Take the Scale Stone
and return to the bureau with me.
Master.
Qingming.
You have promised
to go through life and death with me
and to never betray me.
Have you forgotten?
Freak!
That stupid familiar spell of yours,
I thought it was real.
And all of them could make it until now
because they are your familiars.
Which one would you choose?
You actually used
Cimu to threaten me.
You let him cause chaos in both worlds
just to force me under your control.
Are you really reversing
the protection spell?
You will destroy yourself!
Both my body and spirit
will be destroyed.
And you
will be trapped
within Cimu's body forever.
What are you thinking?
If you want me to free you,
you should be the one to call me Master
and listen to my orders.
Stop now!
Will you obey or not?
Answer me!
Qingming.
If I become your familiar,
you will continue my evil work,
cut off all feelings,
and forever become an enemy of mankind.
I'm asking you,
will you obey or not?
I, Xiangliu,
will be the familiar of Qingming
from this day onward.
Live and die as one
and never betray each other.
The familiar spells
have been revoked.
Master!
As of now, we are no longer connected.
In the seventh month of Gengxu year,
a disaster struck Pingjing City.
There were hurricanes
and tornadoes.
The above was what the historians wrote.
It was completely different
from my report.
The battle at Spirit Bridge
decided the fate of the world.
Qingming and his familiars
fought with their lives,
but somehow I was seen
as the great hero.
Qingming.
What had happened to you?
I'm still not sure.
But to see you so determined
to cut off your familiars,
I'm sure it wasn't what you wanted.
Your sacrifice
brought peace to the people,
but the familiars were cast to the winds.
I, too, no longer have a home.
Qingming.
No matter who is the master
and who is the familiar,
we all hope for your return.
We are willing to share all your burdens.
Isn't the purpose of the familiar spell
to go through joy and sorrow as one,
live and die as one,
and never betray each other?
Qingming’s New Year divination
is about to begin.
It seems that the story is not over yet.
Subtitle translation by:
Michael Jon Crossman and Charlotte Ou