(Episode 1)
(Daeguk Hospital)
(Emergency Room)
Now.
Hyung Sik.
Hey, get up.
Is it over? Is the spirit gone?
(Daeguk Hospital)
Homes where you feel a chill
at the height of summer.
Homes where you see spirits
during sleep paralysis.
Homes in which every resident...
goes either mad or dead.
In other words,
even if it is a haunted house,
we don't care.
Daebak Realty will work
quickly and accurately...
to sell your house
at a satisfactory price.
We promise a one-stop-shop
for services.
By "satisfactory price", you mean...
Of course, it's the market price.
So to conclude,
you're saying that you hear
footsteps every night at midnight...
on a deserted rooftop, yes?
Yes, it gives me goosebumps.
Did anyone die in the building
recently?
She is the CEO of Daebak Realty,
Ms. Hong Ji A.
I see.
Have you ever killed anyone before?
Excuse me?
It's a standard question
for our process.
When we perform an exorcism,
the most important thing is...
is to confirm the identity
of the unrested spirit.
To be honest,
there was one new tenant
who was evicted last year.
Whom I heard was...
killed in a car accident.
But how does an exorcism work?
Should I prepare food and such
like for a rite?
What's the point of giving food
to bodiless spirits?
To mock them?
Let's go.
What?
You're going right now
to do the exorcism?
Before that, I need to confirm
there really is an unrested spirit.
Even the sound of a cat...
can sound like a vengeful spirit...
to a guilty person.
Our CEO tends to be impatient.
She doesn't like to waste time.
(Daebak Realty)
(Sell Your Haunted House)
Who are you?
Why are you taking photos
of someone else's house?
I'm sorry.
Why are you hiding what you took?
What is this?
Are you perhaps the owner
of this house?
Yes.
Recently, have you noticed
electronic appliances flickering...
or turning off for no reason?
That's true.
Just a week ago,
there was a blackout for no reason.
With this much energy,
I'm sure you heard
some strange noises as well.
Every night, I hear a man weeping.
I'm too terrified to sleep,
and I can't tell anyone about it
because the house price may drop.
Let's go inside.
It's more serious than I thought.
Do you have any idea
whose spirit it could be?
Right.
The former landlord...
committed suicide
after this house was auctioned off.
I knew it.
So you're saying his spirit
lives here.
I've only read about these cases
in research papers.
It's amazing.
Research papers?
Actually,
I'm a researcher
from Stanford University,
studying scalar energy.
I'm sure you've heard
that there's a close connection...
between electromagnetic field
and health.
I'm studying the correlation
between that theory...
and spiritual phenomena.
Simply put,
I emit energy into places like this
where spirits lurk,
to cast them away.
So you'll cast the spirits away?
Correct. However,
we must install
the equipment we've developed.
- How much is it?
- No, we should pay you instead.
After all, you're offering a place
for us to do our research.
For 2 days, how about 500...
Excuse me.
What do you say to 500 dollars?
You'll cast the spirit away
and pay me as well?
(Daebak Realty)
Let's see.
Gosh.
Many people consume red ginseng
for their health.
We have a limited amount.
Red ginseng.
It's more expensive
than when I bought it.
(6-year-old red ginseng)
It was a great deal.
This will be the only live deal
you'll get, so don't miss out.
For a price of one cup of coffee...
These black, cowhide boots are
great for everyday wear.
No way.
This is a unique brand.
There's one downside, though.
I shouldn't pass up
this opportunity.
But today, we're having a sale.
While this is being aired...
Hello? I'd like the black boots
that are being aired right now.
I'd like them in a wide 235mm.
Hello?
They're going to be sold out soon.
They'll sell out soon.
You must hurry.
[Kocowa Ver] KBS2 E01 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"Ji A Looks for a Psychic"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Mom.
Do you always have to make a mess?
It's not like you'll clean up
after yourself.
You're unbelievable.
Come on.
They may look the same,
but if you look closely...
If you look closely,
the designs are all different.
You know nothing about fashion.
Gosh, she keeps flickering
the lights.
Gosh, I can't stand it.
What's so wrong...
about buying some shoes
with my own money?
Gosh!
You scared me.
Why are you standing there
like a ghost?
Why are you still here at this hour?
How late is it?
When did the sun go down?
Oh, my gosh.
The most recent unrested spirit
must've been a heavy smoker.
I've picked up his habit
of chain-smoking.
Why did it have to be this habit?
It'll go away in a few days anyway.
Come to your senses.
The psychics are outside right now.
Was the interview today?
Hurry up. Move.
Move.
Hurry up.
Welcome to our psychic interview.
- Hyung Sik, you're back.
- I am.
Excuse me. Psychic?
I thought you were just hiring
a new assistant.
Right, you're a newbie.
Oh, dear.
You sleepwalk,
suffer from night terrors,
and are a virgin.
You have the basic qualifications.
First, let me explain what we do.
Daebak Realty...
only handles haunted houses
and performs exorcisms.
Psychics are absolutely needed
when exorcists are doing their work.
Unrested spirits don't have bodies,
so they can only be exorcized...
after they enter a psychic's body.
We've invited you here today
because we need a psychic...
who'll do something
a bit more unique.
Understood?
She is our CEO and also an exorcist.
She's Ms. Hong Ji A.
Excuse me.
Is it not dangerous?
Such as...
side effects?
If it wasn't, I wouldn't pay you
1,000 dollars per hour.
If you have no more questions,
we'll begin the test.
What's the best ingredient
worldwide...
for casting away spirits?
Salt.
Please step over the salt.
What a pity.
You've used up your energy already.
Those whose salt has changed color
may stay.
The rest of you, please leave.
I'll wire you the interview fee.
Goodbye.
Nice.
All right.
This is the last test.
Climbing all the way
up the stairs is...
your final test.
Really?
I'll be paid 1,000 dollars
for just going up these stairs?
You bet. You'll be paid extra
for succeeding.
Extra?
Hyung Sik, you're next.
Okay.
I can do it.
Who's going to get rid of them?
We both will.
I guess the psychic
we're looking for isn't here today.
I wonder if there is such a psychic.
That didn't get rid of
the spirit for good?
As I told you the other day,
the device only emits energy
to cast away the spirits.
I see. It can only cast them away.
I was happy the spirits went away
with the device.
But without the device,
the spirit will come back, right?
Unfortunately, probably.
Leave it here.
I'll let you collect data
from my place for free.
Well, as I explained before,
this is for my research.
So I need data
from a wide array of locations.
I am very sorry.
Doctor, I'll disassemble it now.
Wait!
Sir.
Doctor.
Okay.
All right.
- Bye.
- How trustworthy.
Ta-da!
Gosh. He mobilizes thugs...
to buy properties at a cheap price
from the poor,
and yet he's scared of spirits.
He's terrified because he's done
a lot of shady stuff.
Why don't we go
and spend our hard-earned cash?
Okay.
(Joeun Bank)
Oh, my.
How much is the daily rental fee?
Is that important right now?
Think about how happy
this baby can make me for the day.
That's important.
You are born to be a fraud.
You are born to be an average Joe.
- Come on.
- You are the only fraud...
who saves money in a bank.
You never know how happy it is
to see your money pile up.
- I don't.
- Gosh.
Get in.
- Please get in.
- Thank you.
- I'll close the door for you.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's go!
This is it.
Put your hands up!
Come on!
Hey, hop in!
Hey, there's an empty seat. Get in!
- This is nice.
- Oh, my.
Who is this?
(Kim Tae Jin)
Come on.
What is it?
It's Mr. Kim from Taejin Nightclub.
He's being so petty
over 50,000 dollars. Gosh.
I didn't even like his face
to begin with.
He ruined my mood.
(Taejin Nightclub)
What?
- What is it?
- In Bum!
In Bum, answer your phone!
Answer your phone, please!
- Oh In Bum!
- What do we do?
- In Bum!
- I don't know.
What? Look at that punk.
- Act cool.
- Block his car!
Come on, step on it!
Hey, step on it! Faster!
If you miss him,
you're not going home tonight.
Go!
Darn it.
Hey, what do we do now?
- Hold tight.
- Okay.
Step on it. Come on, man.
- Hey.
- We got him.
Hey! Watch out!
- Hey! My goodness.
- Come on!
Hey, pull over! Pull over now.
Hey! No!
In Bum!
Oh In Bum!
I'll see you again.
Oh, my. Goodness.
Amazing!
Gosh. I told you to buy it
at the convenience store earlier.
You always drink
that expensive stuff.
Come on.
That won't look cool, you know.
This is it.
"Carpe diem." Seize the day.
What's the point of tomorrow's
dream car or dream house?
I might not even survive the night.
That's life.
Seriously.
Kids these days are so weak.
I understand
that their spiritual energy is weak.
But how come
no one can climb up the staircase?
Why are you sighing
as if it's the end of the world?
Hang in there.
We've always had trouble
finding the right psychic.
We are running out of time.
They will redevelop
this neighborhood pretty soon.
We can't stay here forever.
And I can't leave
my mom here all alone.
Did the thugs come back again?
Please don't tell me...
that you lost your temper
and beat them up.
- Ms. Joo.
- Right.
You are old enough.
You wouldn't be so reckless now.
What if there isn't any psychic
that can send my mom away,
What do I do?
Staying in this world...
as a spirit without a body is...
equivalent to standing outside
only in underwear...
when there's a snowstorm
in the middle of winter.
If it's that cold,
why wouldn't they just leave?
That sounds foolish.
They are so upset
and were unfairly treated...
that they couldn't leave.
We can help them forget
about their grudges,
so they can be happy
in a warm place.
Mom, you must be cold.
I'm sorry.
Gosh.
I'm really good at sending away
poltergeists in other houses.
But I can't seem to help you, Mom.
Sorry.
But don't forget that...
I'm Hong Ji A.
The daughter
of the great Hong Mi Jin.
I...
I will find the strongest psychic
and help you leave here.
You trust me, right?
I promise.
Gosh, I'm sleepy.
Gosh, you scared me.
This is so embarrassing.
Was it a dream?
A nightmare.
In Bum.
Never take this off.
Do you understand?
No, my poor son.
No.
There's no way our Sung Sik
committed suicide.
There's something wrong here.
Sung Sik!
Is that your goal?
I'm not even close yet.
I'm sure you're not.
There's no way to buy a house
in Korea without a loan,
no matter how hard you save.
Besides, there's no one...
who would lend us money
except for loan sharks.
I see.
Just go back to sleep.
Keep on sleeping
and having nightmares.
Why are you ruining my healing time?
So for our hardworking Chief Heo
to buy his house soon,
I found a big job.
- A big one?
- Yes.
- How big?
- This big.
Dream Officetel.
Last year, the construction company
building it went bankrupt,
so it is unfinished.
Two victims who had bought
lots in the building...
committed suicide...
from the roof of that building.
I said I'll give you
a discount on your rent.
The current building owner
bought the building...
- and finished the construction.
- Can you even say that?
But there are rumors
that everyone who moves in...
either goes mad or gets killed
by a spirit.
It's perfect for our work.
This is our goal.
This is the room purchased
by the investors who died.
Room 401.
Okay.
(Commercial Space for Rent)
Fourth floor.
You said you were coming,
why aren't you here?
What is it?
What? A spirit?
Fine, tell him not to bother.
I told you we should request
an exorcism from Professor Oh.
As soon as they install
the device invented in the U.S...
You think spirits
are like mosquitos?
How can you catch them
with an electronic device?
My goodness.
- Where are you going?
- To take a dump.
All this worthless chatter is
giving me a stomachache.
Great, we've now set the mood.
Once the building owner is out,
let's add the sound and wrap it up.
Okay.
An exorcism, of all things.
Where does my wife think
I'll get the money for that?
What's going on now?
The maintenance is terrible.
They haven't even
replaced the lights properly.
What?
Who's there?
Honey?
- What's wrong with him?
- He's not supposed to be out yet.
Honey?
What?
What did you do?
- I didn't do anything.
- Then what's going on?
This was the important part.
- This shouldn't be happening.
- Fix it, quickly.
Honey, what's wrong?
Honey, what are you doing there?
- What's going on? What's happening?
- Honey...
What happened?
Get down from there.
- Are you insane?
- What just happened?
I wasn't trying to die.
Then why were you up there?
I don't know why I ended up there.
What's going on.
It's working.
What happened?
Did you deploy the hologram?
I don't think so.
Gosh.
It's the owner's wife.
Yes, hello.
It's not difficult to install
those devices, no,
but you said your husband
was opposed to them earlier.
It doesn't matter.
Please install them right away.
All right. Okay.
It's an okay.
All right.
What do you mean, an exorcism?
Isn't that just a ploy to scam me?
The exorcism is free.
Like other realty firms,
we ask only for a commission
once the sale has been completed.
You're telling the truth, right?
You'd better not say something else
later on.
Did you see the spirit yourself?
No.
Wait, I think I did.
Did you?
I suddenly saw my wife...
throwing herself off the building.
But when I came to,
I was the one standing on the edge.
It was like I was possessed
by a spirit.
You were possessed.
Right?
Is there anything suspicious
about the building?
Honestly, I bought it at auction.
Later, I found out that two
investors fell to their deaths.
If you don't buy this,
you'd be a fool.
I've never seen such a good site
for sale in my entire career.
I don't have the money to buy
a commercial building.
It's not a matter of money.
No one uses their own money
to invest these days.
Everyone gets a loan.
A loan?
But what about the interest?
You're so frustrating.
If you get a year's worth
of commercial rent,
you can make back your money
with extra more.
Remember that naive kid, Jae Hoon?
Everyone said he was a fool
when he bought his house.
But look what's happened now.
It rose 300,000 dollars in a year.
The Korean real estate market is
invincible.
They said I can pay back interest
and the original investment...
after getting just a year's rent
from the commercial spaces.
If it were that easy to make money,
everyone in the world would be rich.
Father, this is how everyone
makes money these days.
If they all decide to die,
will you do the same?
Why are you swayed by others?
Is it wrong to want to live
like others?
I...
While my friends in university
didn't worry about their tuition...
and focused on their study,
I worked three part-time jobs.
Had you given me just as much
as the other parents did...
Young Do, what's going on?
- Bankrupt?
- I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry!
- I don't know. I'm a victim too.
Oh, gosh! I'm done for!
Goodness!
What should I do?
- No!
- What should I do?
- Goodness.
- What about my money?
Goodness!
Selling your soul, being in debt,
a negative account,
and panic buying.
Believing that Korean real estate
was invincible,
what made these two youngsters
commit suicide?
This happened last year.
(Dream Officetel Case)
The construction industry
went bankrupt,
leaving the two victims
to lose ownership.
They jumped off
the half-built building together.
They were Yang Woo Jin
and Nam Young Do.
These 30-year-olds were friends.
If they jumped to their deaths,
then it's similar to how...
the building owners attempted to do
the same when they were possessed.
The police concluded
that they had committed suicide...
because they couldn't pay
the interest...
after selling their souls
to the devil to get a loan.
Selling souls to the devil?
They have no idea
what that even means.
It just means
that they were that desperate.
What's important is identifying...
whose unrested spirit
is wandering around.
Let me check his face.
(Commercial Space for Rent)
Fourth floor.
How long will you keep this up?
I know you're still roaming around
because you feel resentment.
I'm sure you hate
the person responsible...
for your death
and those who ridiculed you.
You can kill everyone on this earth,
and still, nothing will change.
You'll be the only one in pain.
Two revengeful spirits are
tied to each other.
Secretary Joo, I've checked.
We'll get to work tomorrow midnight,
so look for a buyer.
What's her deal?
Is she insane?
You were here already.
I inspected the device
before disassembling it.
What? Disassemble?
Thanks to your device,
I could get a good night's sleep.
How much is it? I'll buy it.
This is why I called you.
It's for research only, so...
- What are you doing here?
- Honey.
This is Doctor Oh In Bum.
Remember him?
He's the researcher
from Stanford University.
Hello, I'm Oh In Bum,
a Doctor of the Paranormal.
Hello.
Honey. Come here.
I've put this building
on the market already.
They're going to get rid
of all the spirits.
What kind of realty performs
exorcisms?
You got scammed.
How much more do they want?
What do you take me for?
They've confirmed that
they'll only get the commission.
Let them do whatever they want
to get rid of the spirits.
They promised to sell it
at the same price...
as other buildings in this area,
so let's wait.
Same...
- Same price?
- That's right.
Doctor.
Have you disassembled everything?
Sure.
I'm happy for you.
Thank you.
- You heard, right?
- They'll sell it at market price?
That realty is great at their job.
They're not selling anything.
They'll probably bail after
receiving a heavy pre-payment.
There are way too many scammers
in this world.
Check all nearby CCTVs.
- I think I know who it is.
- Did you see them?
It's her.
She's pretty.
Pretty?
I thought she was insane.
But she's a scammer?
(Daebak Realty)
Daebak Realty. Hong Ji A is the CEO.
Simply put, they perform exorcism
in haunted houses and sell them.
Isn't that brilliant?
They close during the day
and open at night.
Are you sure they're even open
at night?
No one has seen her perform
an exorcism.
Even her clients aren't allowed
to see.
She performs it in secret.
Of course.
Having witnesses will only blow
her cover.
Where are you going?
I should know exactly
whom I'm dealing with...
to attack them properly.
Here I go.
(Daebak Realty)
Construction industry, agency,
and home shopping? All right.
(Daebak Realty)
She buys
her daily necessities online.
Judging by her items,
I'm certain she's living alone.
Investigation 101.
Start with their garbage.
(From sunset to sunrise)
Excuse me.
- Hello, I'm...
- Where are you from?
Construction? Service? Union?
Are you here alone?
I think there's a misunderstanding.
I'm...
Of course.
You wouldn't come here all alone.
I'm not with them.
In that case, leave.
Before you get hurt.
Kim Tae Jin?
You seem busy, so I'll just leave.
(Taejin Service)
Gosh, this is pitiful.
Ms. Hong.
Come on. You won't solve anything
by being stubborn.
You could get evicted
without getting paid...
half the market price.
I hope you make the right decision.
I've already made my decision.
I'm not selling.
So quit being a nuisance
and get lost.
Why? Why won't you sell it?
Chief Heo.
In Bum, I don't see you.
Are you hiding well?
How much?
- How much do you need?
- I told you already.
My mom's spirit lives here,
so I can't leave her behind.
You're pulling that card again?
If you don't believe me,
then so be it.
It was quite original at first,
but not anymore.
- Go on.
- Yes, sir.
Why won't you listen
when we're being nice?
Turn the police siren on right now.
Siren? Why?
- Hurry up!
- Don't go easy on her.
Sex discrimination is bad.
[Kocowa Ver] KBS2 E02 'Sell Your Haunted House'
"Dream Officetel"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
What's this?
What's going on?
What?
(Daebak Realty)
I'm scared.
Stop it.
I'm sorry.
What?
Why are they like that?
- Ji Chul. Hurry.
- Don't rush me.
Hey, be patient. Gosh.
Oh, my.
Nice.
I didn't think
it would scare them this much.
Who knew the police siren
would scare them out of their wits?
I was able to think on my feet.
Oh, right. I just did what's right.
No need to thank me.
Are you from the borough office?
Have you ever seen
an impeccably dressed civil servant?
Actually, I'm studying
paranormal events.
I came here because I could feel
strong energy from here.
I know it may sound absurd.
But there is
an unrested spirit here.
And the spirit resents you.
The unrested spirit is here...
because it resents me?
If you don't take action,
the resentment will grow...
and might kill you.
Have you obtained
a listing recently?
That's where the spirit is from.
Luckily, it latched onto you
not long ago.
I can get rid of it...
You are a fraud, aren't you?
You must have worked out.
My agility is above average,
you know.
But you are super fast.
Let go so we can talk.
Of course, I can get out of this,
but I don't want to hurt you.
Fine! I'm a fraud!
But...
you are a fraud too.
I know everything.
Dream Officetel.
I've been working on it for a month.
So butt out.
- Frauds have a code of ethics too.
- A code of ethics?
Unless you want an untimely death,
find a different career.
If you keep scamming people
by using spirits,
you might face a sudden death.
Darn it.
Hey, are you okay?
Hey, why did she attack you?
Exactly. I helped her!
How dare she treat me like this?
Let's go to Dream Officetel.
Now? Why?
Set it up again with our best stuff.
Let's see which one of us ends up
looking for a new career.
I told you to order your own
if you were going to eat.
I just want a slice.
Why would I order a whole pizza?
I must eat the whole thing.
I must stuff myself,
so I feel less cold
during the exorcism later.
Ms. Hong.
Eating a lot will not solve
the source of the problem.
Why the serious face?
During the exorcism,
your body temperature...
it drops because...
you're not strong enough.
That's why I can have a slice.
Did you come up with a plan
for the tied-up spirits?
It will be hard to separate them
before they take up bodies.
So after I put both of them
into Hyung Sik's body,
I need to stab him
twice consecutively.
Will you tell him
that you will stab him twice?
Why would I?
Right.
He would be scared if he knew.
- Hello.
- You're here, Hyung Sik.
Hi.
Our valuable psychic, Hyung Sik.
Before we set out, make sure
no one can get into the building.
There can't be any outsiders
even by mistake.
The building owner promised
the fourth floor will be empty.
The elevators and staircases will...
be sealed off
from 11:30 p.m. to 1 a.m.
Okay. Looking good.
Let's make sure
the sounds come out on time.
(Yang Woo Jin)
(Nam Young Do)
Should I pack extra rock salt?
I already did.
Let's go.
Okay.
Don't salt the door.
The spirits must enter.
Gosh. I've been doing this
for six months now.
I salted all over here
except for the door.
- Okay.
- What are they doing?
Gosh.
Are they trying to catch a raccoon?
Oh, my. No one is watching.
They even lit an incense.
And she's got
a cool incense burner too.
Hey, be quiet.
Let's start with the sounds first.
I told you to start with the sounds.
Why are you changing the lights?
Chief Heo.
Mr. Oh, In Bum.
Why isn't he answering?
What? What's wrong with this now?
What is he doing?
Hey. Ji Chul!
Can't you hear me?
Why is it so chilly in here?
Fourth floor.
There's no point in struggling.
Let's not drag this out
and end it quickly.
Hyung Sik, take it off.
You.
What was that?
Why are they fighting
all of a sudden?
Hey.
Stay still, you crazy fool.
I'll kill them all.
Young Do.
Please stop this now.
Don't try to stop me.
I'll burn this building down,
and then I'll kill myself.
Don't you feel how unfair it is?
Unfair?
How can you say that to me?
If it weren't for you,
I wouldn't be in this mess.
Darn it!
You and I were both too greedy
for our own good.
We didn't invest, we gambled.
But why are you blaming others?
I'm going to quit now
and start over.
You should come to your senses too.
Shut up.
You're the one who needs to wake up.
No matter how hard I struggle,
I'll end up repaying my debts
for the rest of my life.
You might be happy working
in manual labor forever,
but not me.
I'd rather die...
than live like that.
Nam Young Do.
You're so pitiful.
Pitiful?
Do you think I'm pitiful?
Who do you think you are,
calling me pitiful?
Darn.
What?
Hey.
You're not dead, right?
Woo Jin?
Hey, Woo Jin.
Woo Jin, Woo Jin!
I didn't do anything wrong.
I don't know anything.
You came here alone,
all by yourself.
Then you drank alone...
and fell off.
(To my father, from Woo Jin.)
Young Do.
Let go.
You're going to make me fall too.
Young Do, please.
- Let go!
- Please, Young Do.
Please save me.
- Please, save me.
- No.
Please.
No!
It's so unfair.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I...
This is why I hate this work.
Ms. Hong! It's me.
Where did Yang Woo Jin go?
Hey Fraud.
You were a psychic?
(Sell Your Haunted House)
What, a psychic?
That's what we call people
easily possessed by spirits.
I knew I got a bad feeling
from that woman. She's insane.
Is something wrong?
I keep thinking of
that fraud psychic.
Did you fall for him?
The biggest private art museum
in Korea.
They had a new construction
planned in Yongin,
but it isn't proceeding because
of rumors of a spirit appearing.
I hate people saying
stuff about spirits.
It's that ghost.
It disappeared into the museum,
but I'll need to come back
during the day to confirm.
Installation complete.
Oh In Bum.
Don't move a single step
until I say it's all right.
It'll cause me more trouble
if something happens to you already.