Ms. Hong! It's me.
Where did Yang Woo Jin go?
Hey Fraud.
You were a psychic?
It's all over now.
Just go.
No.
Please.
(To my father, from Woo Jin.)
What was that?
What did I just see?
What are you talking about?
Did you see something?
What?
You just said you saw something.
Ms. Hong, help me.
(Episode 2)
Are you this patient's guardian?
No, she's the perpetrator.
I see.
Just stop by the admin desk
before you leave.
Thank you.
Oh In Bum, we need to talk.
I don't have anything
to talk to you about.
Just pay for my treatment.
I did everything they asked for,
- so it's not on me.
- Of course.
Ms. Hong, it's all over now, right?
You're going to sell the building
at full price, right?
Yes.
How's Hyung Sik?
Thankfully, he doesn't need surgery.
He only needs to wear a cast
for six weeks.
But who is this
and why was he at the scene?
I'm a researcher
at Stanford University.
- I have a doctorate...
- He's a lead shaman.
My wife called him.
I see, a lead shaman.
No, I'm a doctor.
Gosh, when are they coming out?
Oh In Bum.
- Oh In Bum?
- I'll just ask you one thing.
When you came to the roof,
you said you saw something.
What did you see?
What was that?
What did I just see?
What are you talking about?
You keep asking if I saw something.
Should I have?
When I exorcise spirits,
I see a part of their consciousness.
The regrets, obsessions, and things
they couldn't let go of...
right up until their death.
- Just a moment. Out of the way!
- That's why...
- Hurry!
- Will he be okay?
This time, those memories
didn't come to me.
They went to you, didn't they?
Memories? What are you talking...
(To my father, from Woo Jin)
I'm sorry, Father.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Do you want me to explain again?
Usually, when I exorcise spirits...
Stop it, I get it.
But I didn't see anything.
Is that true?
You can choose to believe me or not.
Oh, right.
This time, it's my turn.
Before...
This is so embarrassing to say
out loud.
You did something to me earlier,
didn't you?
I remember dragging
that big guy up with you,
but when I came to,
that guy had a broken leg,
and I was on the ground.
You wouldn't understand
even if I told you.
Wow, you're looking down at me.
I didn't want to brag about this,
but I was even accepted
to Seoul University.
Don't worry about whether
I'll understand or not...
and just explain
why my memory is gone.
Because you're a psychic.
What? A psychic?
That's what we call people
easily possessed by spirits.
I exorcise spirits
by trapping them...
inside the body of a psychic,
then release them onwards.
Yesterday, you were my psychic.
That's all.
I was wondering what kind
of excuse you'd come up with.
But this is absurd.
You really are a psychic.
The fact that your memory is gone
is proof of that.
A psychic cannot remember
the events while possessed.
That's enough.
I'm not a psychic
or anything like that.
You're the one who should stop lying
to yourself.
If you were born a psychic,
this must've happened often.
Why are you feigning ignorance?
Whatever.
Let's never see each other again.
Okay?
What were you two talking about
for so long?
I have no idea.
I knew I got a bad feeling
from that woman.
She's insane.
Gosh, that stings.
What? My necklace.
It's gone.
Your necklace?
The one your uncle gave you?
Search carefully.
Check your pockets.
Ji Chul. Turn the car around.
- Hurry!
- Okay.
I'm sure I dropped it somewhere
around here.
In Bum, I found it.
Really?
Is it there?
It's totally smashed.
Did the ambulance run over it?
Darn it!
That woman is just bad luck!
(Commercial Space for Rent)
This way.
Fourth floor.
This is 165m².
As you can see,
this place gets a lot of sunlight.
Many of our customers are...
very much content with this place.
As you can see,
this place gets a lot of sunlight.
There's great energy here as well.
This building is
conveniently located too...
I feel great.
Thank you.
(Office Name: Daebak Realty)
(Woo Yeon Ho, Lee Kyung Ae)
(From sunset to sunrise)
I'll go now. Thank you.
We wish all the best for you both!
How much do you want?
(Changhwa Restaurant)
- Just leave.
- This won't get you more money.
- We're done talking here.
- Let's go.
- Let me take care of this, boss.
- Just leave.
- I said, let's go.
- How much do you need?
- I have no more business with you.
- Why won't you sell your building?
- How much do you need?
- Let's go!
Let's go, you scumbags!
- Let's just leave!
- What's wrong?
- Just go! Please!
- Let's go.
What's wrong?
What's his deal?
(Changhwa Restaurant)
The realty that won't budge...
How's it going?
She's still...
Still?
She refuses to sell the place.
She doesn't want any money.
So?
Well...
What will you do?
I think we saw something there.
- Perhaps, a spirit.
- A spirit?
Well, the boys said they saw one.
Sir.
You see,
I hate people saying
stuff about spirits...
more than parasites
who try to leech off of you.
They're not in their right minds
to begin with.
You're right, sir.
You're right.
(Dohak Construction)
Mr. Kim.
Don't send the boys there.
Take care of it yourself.
I'll...
I'll take care of it myself, sir.
(Daebak Realty)
(2021 Dream Officetel)
Good evening.
We've settled the balance
for Dream Officetel.
The mortgage has been settled too.
I've sent the register too.
It's all done.
You know that old man?
He begged me
to take out the commission fee...
and caused a scene.
It was unbelievable.
Ms. Hong.
Is something wrong?
I keep thinking of
that fraud psychic.
Oh, dear.
Are you in love?
What?
Never mind.
He was handsome, that's all.
Then why is he on your mind?
Come to think of it,
I even took off my coat that night.
You know I never take it off...
during an exorcism
because of hypothermia.
But I never put it back on again
that night...
because I didn't feel cold.
So you're saying that the fraud...
absorbed
the unrested spirit's memory...
and raised your body temperature
as well?
Yes, but I'm not completely sure.
I didn't know
such a powerful psychic existed.
With that much power,
I can't help but think
that he could put my mom to rest.
I should've dragged him here
against his will.
I'll ask a cop that I know.
Since he's a fraud,
he must have a record.
Was his name Oh In Bum?
No.
I should've beat him up
and brought him here.
(Hong Mi Jin, Hong Ji A)
(Record of Exorcism)
Instant coffee is the best.
Have you eaten dinner yet,
my dear baby?
What are you thinking about?
Didn't you say Yongdoori coffee
tastes best when it's still hot?
This doesn't feel right.
The coffee?
I'm also drinking Yongdoori coffee.
I'll brew some for you next time.
When I exorcise spirits,
I see a part of their consciousness.
The regrets, obsessions, and things
they couldn't let go of...
right up until their death.
They went to you, didn't they?
Coffee. Yes.
(To my father, from Woo Jin)
I'm sorry, Father.
- What is it?
- I'm here right now.
What?
I'll burn this building down,
and then I'll kill myself.
Young... Nam Young Do.
What?
Where am I?
Ji Chul.
Ji Chul...
(To my father, from Woo Jin)
What? It...
It wasn't a dream?
You heartless brat.
(Our condolences for your loss.)
Where are we?
- Ji Chul.
- Yes?
When a family member
commits suicide...
Yes?
Do you know what happens
to the rest of the family?
That came out of nowhere.
Why do you ask?
Did you dream about your uncle?
Whatever.
Why should I care?
(Personal Information on Oh In Bum)
As you can see,
I found two ex-convicts...
under the name of Oh In Bum.
One of them is in his 60s.
And the other one is a teenager.
The age doesn't match.
They'll look into reports
regarding shamanic scams.
So we have to be a bit more patient.
I shouldn't have let him
go that day. Gosh.
Please stop drinking.
What do you mean?
(With This Alcohol)
Darn this habit
of the unrested spirit.
Last time, you were a chain smoker.
This time, you're an alcoholic.
I'll book an appointment
for your health checkup.
I think I know where Oh In Bum is.
How?
When you absorb
the memories of unrested spirits,
their habits remain with you too.
I'll be able to find him
once I check places...
where Yang Woo Jin would go.
Don't drive. Take a cab.
Okay?
Gosh.
Here again?
- Why is that woman here?
- Who is it?
You are Yang Woo Jin's father,
right?
Didn't a strange man come to you
and do weird things recently?
A strange man?
He has a face of a sly fraud,
but he might have behaved
just like your late son.
Like coming into your yard
and sitting there.
Did you lend money to Woo Jin too?
Pardon?
If that's why you are here,
you wasted your time.
I don't know
how much money you lent him,
but I don't have the means
to pay it back.
And he broke my heart...
when he took his own life.
So please go back home.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Your son...
didn't commit suicide.
Is it wrong to want to live
like others?
I...
While my friends in university
didn't worry about their tuition...
and focused on their study,
I worked three part-time jobs.
Had you given me just as much
as the other parents did...
Darn it.
And throw out those glasses
and buy a new pair.
I'll make a lot of money
and buy you an expensive pair.
(To my father, from Woo Jin)
Dad, this is Woo Jin.
I'm writing this letter
because I am ashamed to face you.
I wanted to make you proud of me.
I am sorry that I disappointed you.
I didn't mean it
when I talked back to you.
Wanting to live like other people...
Hey, hurry up!
Not worrying about money
when choosing what to eat...
- Come here.
- Or when meeting my friends...
I would be lying
if I didn't want that.
But I never resented you.
- Hey. Didn't you eat?
- Dad.
I'm going to start over.
Please believe in me
and be patient one last time.
I'll come see you
on your birthday this year.
Let's go and have pork ribs,
your favorite.
Your son...
didn't commit suicide.
I'm sorry.
You scared me!
I got you.
You said
you didn't absorb his memories.
But how did you find this place?
Who were you again?
Hey.
Hey. Oh In Bum.
Hey, let's talk. Hey!
Hey!
- Why is she following me?
- Hey.
I need to talk to you.
Get out of the van.
Hey!
Hey! Get over here!
- What?
- What's wrong?
Another nightmare?
What is that? Isn't that Ms. Hong?
- Why is she chasing us?
- I don't know.
It will be a headache
if she gets to us.
Hey, what's up with her?
Why won't she stop?
- Look where you're going.
- Pipe down a second.
Hey!
We're good, right?
But In Bum, why did she do that?
I don't know.
Did you lose him?
I almost had him.
Calm down.
No need to worry.
He's a fraud exorcist.
We're bound to meet sooner or later.
Either when he's sued or arrested.
I hope he doesn't go clean
and stop with his scams.
Shoot.
(Open Temple Free Offerings Event)
Thank you for the food.
There's not much to temple food
but it's so tasty anyway.
Maybe because it's all natural?
It's just because you're hungry.
It would be weirder
if it didn't taste good...
- after this hike up the mountain.
- Is that so?
Lee Eun Hye.
Director of Britium, the biggest
private art museum in Korea.
They had a new construction
planned in Yongin.
But it isn't proceeding...
because of rumors
of a spirit appearing.
Why would such educated people
believe in spirits?
Of course, people like us are
grateful if they do.
According to rumors
in the stock exchange,
they say that Director Lee
poisoned her husband.
Her husband was in a coma
for a whole week,
but she didn't show up
at the hospital even once.
Publicly, she said it was...
because she was preparing
for an exhibit by a famous artist.
So that's why there are rumors...
that the museum is haunted
by Kwon Moo Jin.
That's right.
But do you think Director Lee
even believes in spirits?
She will when her husband's spirit
appears right in front of her.
We're great at making them
look real.
That's true.
But if that still doesn't work,
there is a Plan B.
Honestly, I think this one
might be more effective.
So Kwon Moo Jin's wife is
the museum director.
A sibling from a different mother,
a nephew,
and a cousin.
They are all executives
of the Britium Museum Board.
I'm sure the rumor
of the spirit was...
fabricated by Kwon,
the sibling from a different mother.
Why? Because if they ruined
an important exhibit...
and caused significant damage
to Britium,
Director Lee's position
would be endangered.
Giving Deputy Director Kwon
a shot at Lee's position.
And then what?
If we can find evidence...
that Deputy Director Kwon
started those rumors,
we can use that to blackmail him...
or hand over the evidence
to Director Lee.
Either way, we win the lotto.
Nice one, In Bum.
- Would you marry me?
- I really don't want to.
Don't abandon me.
- Really.
- This is a winning lottery ticket.
This used to be a factory,
but it doesn't smell at all.
See how big the windows are?
There's great ventilation,
and it gets a lot of light.
It's a quiet neighborhood,
so it's perfect for work.
What do you do again?
We're reporters.
This place would be perfect!
This is the bathroom
on the first floor.
The second floor is...
being used by an artist.
Even that artist loves
this building so much,
that they've been using it
for several years now.
What's wrong?
Wasn't someone there just now?
What?
What's this smell?
What's wrong?
What was it he saw?
Excuse me, I'm the landlord.
My gosh, the smell...
Goodness.
What's going on?
It's a wandering spirit.
A wandering spirit? People who die
away from home turn into them.
Why would someone who died
inside his house turn into one?
He probably didn't consider
this place as home.
Or a wandering spirit
from another area...
could've moved
into this vacant spot.
I think I'll find a lead
once I follow him.
Yes, check that once more.
Isn't this better?
- Please set the lights soon.
- Yes, ma'am.
It's done.
Check. I can see now.
Let's wrap it up.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Wait.
Yes?
Please turn off the ceiling lights
before you go.
Oh, sure.
Okay.
I swear I saw a spirit downstairs.
What are you talking about?
I'll go check.
(Exhibit Hall 4)
Nice. I'll be leaving now.
Why aren't the lights turning on?
Good work.
Did you check?
It disappeared into the museum,
but I'll need to come back
during the day to confirm.
Let's see.
Nice.
You startled me.
What? What is it? Don't come out.
Go back inside.
This isn't new.
I bought it on sale last year.
Unbelievable.
She always knows
when I buy new clothes.
New trainers?
New shoes as well?
They're not new.
At least take the price tag off.
You know wandering spirits are
hard to track and locate.
I needed activewear.
I never asked.
After all, you bought them
with your own money.
Exactly.
I'll be off.
Goodbye.
(Britium)
Oh In Bum
Who were you again?
What was that for?
Don't move a single step
until I say it's all right.
It'll cause me more trouble
if something happens to you already.
How dare you keep trying
to scam a fraud?
What was that?
(Self-portrait, Marvin Gaye)
I couldn't see his face
because of you!
What a feisty way of expressing
your gratitude.
What?
Come on.
Gosh.
Excuse me.
Excuse me!
Do you know...
that you look like a pervert
right now?
Gosh.
Check the pieces.
- Who are you?
- This isn't good.
I'm Hong Ji A from Daebak Realty.
Ms. Hong?
I'll give you the chance to explain
before we check the CCTV.
You won't find anything
on the CCTV anyway.
Whenever there's an unrested spirit,
most electrical devices malfunction.
Unrested spirit?
Are you talking about ghosts?
Let me explain.
I hate to break it to you,
but there's an unrested spirit
full of resent in your museum.
You're an exorcist?
Ghost Story Cleaner is
a start-up company...
that has patented the technology
of using electromagnetic waves...
to cast out unrested spirits.
- Are you his partner?
- No.
Excuse me.
- Oh In Bum speaking.
- It is your real number.
Please leave.
Call me if you change your mind.
And be careful of this woman.
She can be very violent...
and is nowhere near sane.
I'll show myself out.
Ms. Hong.
I'd like to talk to you about
selling my art museum, Britium.
Ms. Hong, I'll wait for you outside.
Talk to her well for me.
Right after my husband's funeral,
a rumor
that my art museum is haunted...
started to spread.
And there's another rumor
that I poisoned my husband too.
Did you murder your husband?
You are straightforward,
just as I heard.
You know Chairman Han of
the investment firm in Masan, right?
He told me that you handled
the sale of the building...
that gave him headaches.
I'm sure you saw it on the news.
My art museum, Britium, will move
to a bigger place.
I already bought the land
for the new location.
The negotiation to sell
this building was in place.
But I was offered
a ridiculous price...
because of the rumor
that the museum is haunted.
I apologize, but if this regards
the sale of the building...
I already have a case,
so I cannot accept another client.
I ended up here today...
because I was following
the unrested spirit of that case.
An unrested spirit.
You don't believe me.
If so, why are you asking me
for my help?
The most important job
for me as the director is finding...
the best solution
that can keep our image intact...
and minimize our monetary losses.
Deputy Director Kwon is here.
Unless you demand...
the client to believe in exorcisms,
please call me as soon as
you are done with your current case.
Call me directly.
Hey, hurry up. Hurry.
Hey, that's crooked.
Level it properly. Okay?
Hey, let's get the angle right.
That's it.
Look at this mess, Eun Hye.
There was a minor commotion.
It's nothing.
It's nothing?
You are the director. But obviously,
you don't act like one.
So even tabloids think...
they can belittle us
and get away with it.
You're diminishing our class.
Responding to such tabloids...
would diminish our class even more.
Is that so?
I wonder
if the board will agree with you.
There are rumors
of how you poisoned my brother...
and that the museum is haunted.
Gosh.
Will they reappoint you
as the director...
when you are
the root of all these rumors?
Why did you run into her here again?
Are you guys ill-fated or something?
What do we do? Should we give up?
Why would we give up?
We can't let her steal
two cases in a row.
Hey, she's coming. Bye.
What should I say?
He'll turn me down again
without giving it a second thought.
Gosh. What should I say?
She'll really beat me up
if I don't sound sincere.
"Not being intimidated
by the mighty Lee Eun Hye."
"I learned something new today."
No.
If I cave in right away,
it won't look cool.
"Be my psychic just once."
That sounded so selfish.
"You can't steal two of my cases
which I worked hard on."
"Let me take this one."
As if. She would never.
Why am I racking my brains for this?
He's a fraud. He'd say yes to money.
Right. Not looking cool isn't
important right now.
Money is.
- We...
- Let's do a case together.
- No, I...
- I don't mean it permanently.
Just one case. That's it.
Hold on.
I did it.
Okay.
Let's do that then.
We keep running into each other.
So we must be destined
to cross paths.
I'm going to Ms. Hong's place.
No way. Is she interested in you?
Otherwise,
she wouldn't bring you to her house.
I'm not going to her house.
I'm going to her office.
She said I had to take a test
or something.
That's an excuse.
She lives alone on the second floor
of the same building.
Gosh.
I see.
What?
Nothing.
I saved her life earlier.
That must have been it.
Even I thought I was pretty amazing.
When did you save her life?
When there was a commotion
in the gallery earlier.
A commotion in the gallery?
What do you mean? When?
So this is how it looks inside.
It's just a regular office.
What is it?
Nothing.
Go to the second floor.
- What's up there?
- My room.
She's making it too obvious.
If this is about work,
let's talk here.
Go upstairs. That's the test.
Okay.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Isn't your heart beating fast?
Aren't you experiencing
shortness of breath?
Or do you feel dizzy?
I'm not climbing Mount Everest.
Why would I be out of breath
for climbing up a few steps?
I might not look like it,
but I've been working out regularly.
As long as you're okay,
keep going up.
Okay.
He really climbed all the way up.
Why is it so dark in here?
Are you allergic to sunlight?
Gosh, it's cold in here.
What's that?
Stay right there
until I tell you it's okay to move.
Isn't this what you did
at Dream Officetel the other night?
- Isn't it?
- Yes.
The smoke from the incense burner
calls a vengeful spirit.
I see. A vengeful spirit.
I bet it does.
It's my mother.
She's quite beautiful.
She passed away 20 years ago.
Mom!
Now, she's here.
She's been haunting
this house for 20 years.
I see.
So she's not a fraud,
she's just delusional?
The one exorcism I asked for...
is for my mother.
I think you might have
misunderstood.
I only came thinking
we were going to work on Britium.
I'll give you 10,000 dollars.
- Money's not the problem.
- 20,000.
Last time, you had a strong-looking
man working with you.
Why are you asking me?
My mother is a special case.
She can't be exorcised
by an ordinary psychic.
Then what about me?
You're special.
(Hong Mi Jin)
Step outside the circle.
Should I run away now?
Step outside.
No, if I just do as she says,
I'll get 20,000 bucks
and the Britium job to boot.
I'll give it a go.
Mom?
Oh In Bum?
Oh In Bum.
Oh In Bum!
Help me.
I'm... I'm sorry...
Die.
Die!
You should die too!
Uncle.
Have you come around?
Isn't that something you use
when your heart stops?
Did I...
die just now?
I prepared this
in case of emergency,
but thankfully
your heart didn't stop.
Thankfully?
Are you saying
that I was supposed to die,
but thankfully didn't?
Why...
Why is Ms. Hong's mother
in my memories?
Why did Ms. Hong's mother...
try to kill my uncle?
I'm sorry.
I thought it would work with you.
Take this.
- This...
- If you wear this,
you won't be possessed
by most spirits from now on.
It's like a bulletproof vest,
so never take it off.
You can...
never take this off.
Do you understand?
What? What is this?
I'll pay you what I promised,
so don't worry.
Your mother.
You said she died 20 years ago?
How...
did she pass away?
Because of me.
Just go now. I'm tired.
Save me.
I'm sorry.
Twenty years ago,
my uncle and I came here.
Something happened then.
There's no way our Sung Sik
committed suicide.
Did my uncle really commit suicide?
You said I was special earlier.
Why don't you team up...
with this special psychic?
(Sell Your Haunted House)
I said I would never work
with a fraud.
No partners start off
on the right foot.
Ms. Hong, you need me.
You need this special psychic.
We need a psychic right now.
You said he even helps
get your temperature up.
Staying pure?
They didn't sleep together.
Why does Ms. Hong have
the same one as your uncle?
That's what I'm trying to find out.
What the relationship between
Daebak Realty and my uncle was.
On the outside, it looks
just like a regular realty office.
- Ji Chul, let's form a plan.
- A plan?
It's by the writer Cho Yeon Seo,
the "Artist of Mullae-dong."
You believe me now, right?
That you're a psychic.
So being possessed by spirits
was real after all.