♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend of
the four-leaf clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage
and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 25=
Are you in a bad mood?
No.
Don't worry about me.
Are you worried about the exam?
You can read my mind
even with a computer monitor in the way?
I've been busy with detailed issues
of the art gallery recently.
Haven't had time to tutor you in a while.
Why don't we finish working early today
and head home to study?
Okay.
Thank you, Boss.
Here.
Didn't you say that
you have to pass
the general exam this year,
complete the credit requirements,
and there is no make-up exam?
So I've prepared
these study plans for you.
I have to go through all of these?
Not only do you have to go through these,
but you also have to master everything.
Okay.
I'll pull myself together
and not let Boss down.
Right now we're off work.
Don't call me Boss.
I won't let my
handsome and outstanding boyfriend down.
Be serious.
Hello.
Are you Mr. Gu?
Yes.
This is your package.
Please sign for it.
Okay.
Sorry.
I forgot to bring my pen.
Could I borrow yours?
Sure, wait a second.
Thank you.
Going to use your pen for a bit.
What package?
Your learning materials.
There's more?
You...
These...
These are only part of it.
Oh my god.
What?
You don't want to study?
You can't imagine how much I want to study.
If you can let me
go out and take a break,
I'll be even happier.
Sir.
Your cat ran away.
Ran away?
Ice Cream.
Why are you here?
You scared me.
Ice Cream is here.
Where did you go?
You scared me.
I got so anxious.
Ice Cream.
Do you feel the same way I do?
Tired of being stuck at home
and wanted to go out
to relax?
How come you're tired of being stuck at home?
I've been studying
all afternoon.
I got a headache because of it.
Studying for one afternoon
gave you a headache?
I need to balance studying and resting.
I want to take a break and go outside.
Yes,
there should be a balance between
studying and resting.
Look, you've been
taking a break for a while.
Shouldn't you go back
to studying now?
I just...
Coming.
Come in, come in.
Take a seat.
Dishes are ready.
Dumplings will be ready soon.
Take a seat.
Look.
My timing is spot-on.
Dishes are done and dumplings are ready.
You're here too.
Here.
Delicious dumplings.
What do you need?
Nothing.
I just wanted you to come home to eat with me.
Try some of my dishes.
I've been really busy recently.
It's okay.
You should eat no matter how busy you are.
You can leave after eating.
I won't ask you to stay. Okay?
Here.
I made these myself.
Try one.
See if
it still has the taste from your childhood.
Hello?
Okay, I'll be there soon.
What?
Finish eating before you leave?
I have to take care of things at the company.
I need to go.
Also,
don't call if there is nothing.
Don't contact Director Xu either.
Dad, I'm tired.
Tired? Do you want Dad to carry you?
Yes.
Let's go.
(We heard your father is an embezzler.)
(How much did he embezzle?)
Give some money to us
to buy something to eat and drink.
You idiot.
Your dad is an embezzler.
Don't play the victim.
I won't give money to you guys.
The teacher is coming.
Let's go.
Someday,
I'll stop being bullied by others.
When that day comes,
you won't be bullied either.
I'll protect you.
♪I can't help♪
♪But feel a little happy♪
♪But feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that♪
♪Fills up the black and white♪
♪An apple falls from a tree♪
♪And hits me♪
♪Newton's laws come true♪
♪After I fall in love with you♪
Thanks, everybody.
Thank you for all your support.
Thank you.
Drink some water first.
You were almost hysterical.
Please pay attention to your wording.
What do you mean by hysterical?
This is being crazy for love
and making the tune linger in the room.
I want some water.
Your idea of relaxation is singing karaoke?
I don't think that was relaxing.
You're tired from singing and I'm tired
after listening to your singing.
You mean I suck at singing?
I brought you here
precisely because I suck at singing.
Your turn.
I'll pass.
Please sing.
To make up for your mistake.
Are you really asking me to sing?
Yes.
What do you want to sing?
Whatever. There's no difference.
Then this song.
Here.
If you don't know how, I can help you.
♪I can't help♪
♪But feel a little happy♪
♪But feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow♪
♪That fills up the black and white♪
♪An apple falls from a tree♪
♪And hits me♪
♪Newton's laws come true♪
♪After I fall in love with you♪
♪The God of Love has a lot of arrows♪
♪One of them hits me♪
♪Don't you try to escape♪
♪Unless you disobey Cupid♪
♪I was once obsessed♪
♪With the legend of the four-leaf clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage♪
♪And you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing♪
♪Please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
You come here often.
It looks like you have a lot to worry about.
The usual.
I'm an idiot.
Turned down everyone
for one person.
And ended up with nothing.
It looks like
we're
the same type of people.
We're obsessed with our feelings towards someone,
but we don't want to let them know.
In the end, we're so hurt on the inside,
but we're still pretending to be okay.
You sound like you know everything.
But you didn't get
Jiang Xiao Ning either, did you?
We might not become friends,
but at least, we won't become enemies.
I don't have many friends,
but I think we
get along pretty well.
If either of us wants to chat about
our failing relationships in the future,
we can drink together.
(Reindeer Group) (Tang Xu)
(Deputy General Manager)
You're quite a catch.
Why don't you try pursuing
Jiang Xiao Ning again?
I'm not very confident.
I got it.
Your cowardness
has done harm to both of us.
My apologies.
I'm just saying.
In Gu Chuan's words,
I didn't lose to Jiang Xiao Ning,
I just chose the wrong person.
In other words,
Gu Chuan
has never liked me.
Do you hate him now?
Hate?
Not quite.
It's despair.
There's nothing worse than apathy.
Some people come into your life
just to teach you a lesson
and they will just leave after that.
You're right.
I need to thank him.
Thank him for teaching me a lesson
that overwhelmed me
with pain and sorrow.
Still lots of whiskeys left.
I'm willing to listen to you for a while.
Cheers.
So when we're having
the team-building event last time,
you sang horribly on purpose
because of me?
I choose to be the one inflicting pain,
rather than bearing the pain.
Then you should be the one who sings
and I'll listen.
Okay.
Only sing for me.
Would that be too much to ask?
That's...
not too much to ask at all.
You're too nice.
I really want to kiss you.
Here.
The seat belt is stuck.
Let's go home first.
Come in.
Boss.
You have a guest.
Sorry.
I didn't make an appointment in advance.
We can call each other friends.
Get straight to the point.
You guys talk.
I'll go make some coffee.
Mr. Gu.
This is a proposal.
(Procurement Proposal)
(Reindeer Group)
(Coordinator: Tang Xu)
Reindeer Group plans to
construct a new office building
in the New District.
The goal is
to make it become the city's new landmark.
We want to ask your company to be in charge of
designing the building.
Who is the coordinator
for this procurement?
Look,
the board has not finished
the review and approval process.
I'm not the formal CEO
of our company yet.
However, I've been in charge of
all the projects
so far.
I really hope Mr. Gu
can participate in our project.
I'm also looking forward to your designs.
After all,
you are a designer who has won the Jin An Award.
I'll take a look at the proposal first.
I'll contact you after I'm done.
Okay.
I won't keep you any longer.
Brother Xu.
Are you guys done talking?
Oh right, Xiao Ning.
This is for you.
What's this?
A gift card.
I can't take it.
This is for Aunty.
Remember,
this is the best way
to make elders happy.
Brother Xu.
Okay, I have to get going.
He's so attentive.
Showing off how caring he is
after showing off his power.
He said it's for Aunty.
I'll look for a chance
to return it to Brother Xu.
Okay.
My Chuan, you finally remembered me.
Do you know about
Reindeer Group's new landmark project?
How could I know?
Reindeer Group gave this project
to us.
Maybe my father intentionally gave this to us
to prove that I can't live
without his protection?
Turn it down.
Tang Xu just handed the
proposal to me personally.
He also said
he is going to be the CEO.
Tang Xu?
Something feels a bit strange.
That's my father's style.
Making me have crisis awareness.
You should go back and ask him.
But don't have a quarrel with him.
Okay.
The landmark project.
I'm turning down the collaboration
on behalf of my company.
We won't do it.
Why?
First,
I don't need you
intentionally taking care of my company.
You walk your own path.
I walk my own path.
Second,
this is the largest project
of the group so far.
A new landmark of the entire city.
I beg you
to take care of it yourself.
Don't let outsiders take advantage of it, alright?
Who is the outsider?
Tang Xu.
How can Tang Xu be an outsider?
He's your brother.
Brother.
How can he not be your brother?
He is doing his filial duty for you.
Besides that.
The board of directors knows that
Tang Xu has the ability.
You're not on this project.
Are there any problems for me
to hand the project to him?
You mean
he's more capable than I am?
I'm worse than him, right?
Mark my words.
If he's in charge of this project,
he won't give me an advantage
during the procurement process, right?
We'll play a fair game.
I'll show you
if my tiny company
is capable to win.
Sure.
I'll wait and see, boy.
Don't look down on me.
I'm not.
I'm not bidding for your money.
I'm bidding for my pride.
So sudden.
Did your old wounds hurt again?
Or are you cured?
I just want to express my gratitude.
Not necessary at all.
Thanks for taking care of me yesterday.
You're a gentleman.
You mean
I don't look like a gentleman?
And almost made you misunderstand me?
I was joking.
I simply want to say thank you.
Although you're very pretty,
I have self-control.
I won't
take advantage of you.
You're good at chatting with people.
Chatting with me feels
better than chatting with Gu Chuan, right?
I was just starting to feel better.
Can you not mention him?
If you dislike him that much,
why not quit your job
and come work at my company?
I don't want to leave.
Not resigned?
If I were you,
I wouldn't be resigned either.
You must remember that
you need to make him realize
how important you are.
For him,
you are the irreplaceable woman.
If he didn't have you,
he wouldn't have become who he is today.
That's impossible.
He'll never think in that way.
That's because
everything is going well for him nowadays
and he won't know how important you are.
What are you trying to say?
You know what I mean.
I don't want revenge.
It's not revenge.
You need to let him
suffer a setback.
I'm telling you.
A man
will only know which woman is true to him
when he is at a low ebb.
Of course,
I just want to help you.
I don't have other intentions.
It could be
hard for you to hurt him
given his prestige
in the field.
However,
if you don't let him
suffer a setback,
you'll never have a place
in his heart.
Are you giving me advice?
What's in it for you?
This is not advice.
In other words, this is
a collaboration.
If the collaboration goes well,
I can get my Jiang Xiao Ning back,
and
you can win back your Gu Chuan,
right?
A win-win resolution.
(Sustainability)
(Thanks for watching.)
In recent years,
I haven't been coming to the office often.
But I remember all
your names.
I also know everything that
goes on in the company well.
Okay, maybe not that well.
I made an agreement with Chuan.
I would take care of
the initial funding of the company
and he would handle all the technical aspects.
I promised not to intervene.
However, this time,
I'm going to assign tasks to everyone.
We have to win
this bid.
I've never participated in this type of
bidding before.
But it's different this time.
We can't let Mr. Xu down.
From now on,
take a break from your current projects
and focus on this bid.
I only ask for one thing.
We must win.
We've got this!
Come on.
One, two.
We've got this!
Now, I'm going to announce
the project team members.
Coordinator.
Me.
First assistant, Su Man Lin.
Second assistant, Cheng Dong.
Graphics, Qiao Meng Jia.
♪You are the most perfect when full of vitality♪
Hey, everyone.
You guys have been working hard.
I appreciate your efforts.
Keep it up
and the victory is ahead of us.
Brother Kai.
Everyone hasn't eaten anything yet.
I'll go buy some food.
Great idea.
I'll reimburse you.
Okay.
(It seems we can get started.)
Welcome to Lai Yi Fen.
We have a lot of snacks for you to pick.
Thank you.
Hello, please choose whatever you like.
Do you have any discounts today?
Yes.
Buy one get one free for those nuts.
Okay, I'll take some.
Hi. I'll pay the bill.
Okay.
Can I pay with my phone?
Sure.
Where did everybody go?
Where did you go?
I went downstairs to buy food for everyone
since no one had eaten anything.
They're not lucky enough to eat these.
Where are you going?
Work.
I'm back.
You're back.
You haven't gone to bed?
How dare I?
Sister Zhao Yan dined out
with her good-looking colleague.
Seems like you're tired from having a great meal.
Do you want to pick a fight?
I put a lot of effort into
making all these dishes,
waiting for you to come back.
I didn't call you
or send you a WeChat message
because I was afraid of interrupting you.
Didn't I say
I was having dinner with my colleagues?
I just want to know
how attractive
this colleague is
that could make you
leave your handsome boyfriend
at home alone.
Why do you sound like a grumbling woman?
What do you mean sound like?
I am a grumbling woman.
Leave me at home all by myself.
I'm so scared.
Xu Cheng Ran, you.
It's a waste if you don't become an actor.
Be serious. Don't laugh.
Okay, I'll be serious.
Come on.
Say what you want to say.
Start your performance.
I'm not performing. I'm serious.
Are you jealous?
I'm seriously jealous.
Am I not important to you?
Of course you're important.
You
are the most important one.
I'm going to take a shower.
Do you mean it?
Did you lie?
I'm taking a shower.
Every floor
has a certain capacity.
This way,
it can put together more people.
What do you think?
I brought some Meco Fruit Juice for everyone.
Help yourself.
Thank you.
Thank you, Xiao Ning.
Sister Man Lin.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
I'm here.
Go to Wu Yi Street to
take some photos of the street for me.
The more, the better.
Okay, I'll go right now.
Wait.
Traffic is heavy on that street.
Take care of yourself.
Okay. Thank you, Boss.
Your phone is ringing.
Okay, I'll answer it.
Don't call me
during work.
Okay, I'll call back at another time.
Has the design come out?
I need to have them
in advance to prepare.
Should be soon.
I'll contact you in advance.
Okay. Remember.
You're not doing this for me.
You're doing this for yourself.
Are you sure
you can do what you've promised me?
Don't worry.
As long as Gu Chuan
got knocked off his pedestal,
Xiao Ning will no longer
admire him blindly.
At that time, I'll just need to give it a little push
and she'll let go.
Hurry up.
Empty an office
for me first.
We'll discuss other things
in detail later.
Don't mess around with those right now.
You should handle other things first.
Do what's important first.
Zheng.
Mr. Tang.
What do you think?
Is my pace alright?
Yes.
When you said you wanted to start a company,
I got your
business license,
office space,
and staff ready immediately.
You're one step away from opening.
Zheng.
I'm giving you an opportunity
to make money.
This is a huge bid.
If other people get it,
they would be too happy to fall asleep.
Actually,
I feel happy but also worried.
Are you sure I can win
this huge bid?
Rest assured.
You'll know soon.
I'll give my plan to you later.
But you must ask your
design team
to make revisions based on my plan.
I need the plans to be similar
but not exactly the same.
If you can do this,
the bid is yours of course.
It's simply copying.
No problem.
You're paying for it anyway.
You are the boss.
(Zhi Mu Architectural Design Company)
Hey, you two.
(Zhi Mu Architectural Design Company )
What are you doing?
(Zhi Mu Architectural Design Company)
Leave that.
(Zhi Mu Architectural Design Company )
Focus on priorities.
Okay, okay.
Look at them.
(Zhi Mu Architectural Design Company )
I know what the problem is.
Look here.
Like this.
If you look at it from a different angle,
the problem is resolved.
Here.
The visual focal point changed.
It's like this every time.
When it looks like
we've hit a dead end,
you can always think of a workaround
to shift the way of thinking.
Maybe this is
the talent that a designer should have.
Sister Man Ning.
Boss.
Juice.
Xiao Ning.
Go buy a sandwich for me.
I'm starving.
But...
it's raining outside.
I have an umbrella at my desk.
I'll go.
It's okay. I have an umbrella.
I can do it.
What's wrong with her?
She encountered something unpleasant
on a rainy day.
So she doesn't want to go out
when it rains.
True.
Being trapped in such a high place.
Anyone would have trauma.
How long do we need to wait?
Don't get anxious.
Wait a little longer.
I'm confident.
You guys worked hard these days.
Take a break.
I'll treat you all to dinner later.
Great.
Mr. Gu.
You guys go first.
Qiao Meng Jia, Cheng Dong, and I
can stay here
until the file finishes rendering.
Okay, thank you, guys.
Xiao Ning.
Okay.
I'll clean up.
You guys...
(Downloading)
Jia Jia.
Come.
Sit here.
I'm starving.
I got everything ready for you.
Be quick.
Look.
Come.
Use this.
Eat.
I saw everyone's hard work
when working on this bid.
Let's take
a half-day off tomorrow.
Great!
Come on, make a toast.
But Boss,
don't say that.
We have to rely on you for making money
to buy food.
It looks like you've eaten a lot
to look the way you are today.
Good for money-making.
Come on.
(I'm here.)
Yes.
Where is the restroom?
On the left.
I'm going to the restroom.
Eat this.
Give it to me.
We've come this far.
Why are you still hesitating?
Nothing.
I disgust myself.
That's better than
always losing.
Be quick.
Eat more.
This is so yummy.
Don't drink too much.
Cheng Dong.
Come on.
You've worked hard.
It's what I should do.
How's the food?
Very good.
The food tastes so good.
Boss.
Thank you.
See you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, Boss.
Bye-bye.
Rest well.
Take care.
Bye-bye.
I'm so happy.
I haven't been in
such a good mood in a long time.
Feeling fulfilled and looking forward to it.
Look forward to what?
Our bidding result.
Do you have confidence
in our design?
Let's go.
Mr. Tang.
I'm a layman.
But I think
your previous design
is very well done.
You...
It's none of your business.
The point is
whether your team can meet my requirements.
I want a design that looks similar
but not exactly the same.
No problem.
These are not people
randomly picked off of the street.
I chose and poached
them one by one
from other companies.
They're super experienced.
Also,
the base is very strong.
Doing a little
copying is not a problem for them.
Come and take a look.
Take a look.
Look.
What do you think?
(Smart workplace)
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪