♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and let's count down
to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 26=
Hello, Brother Xu?
All right.
Give me a moment. I'll come right away.
These are for you.
Brother Xu.
You need to stop buying me gifts.
I'm running out of space at home.
Don't worry.
I can support myself
and I can take care of my family.
This is the gift card you gave me.
I'm giving it back.
It's for you, Xiao Ning.
I insist.
I don't want to rely on others.
Xiao Ning.
I just joined
a design company.
Would you
like to work for me?
This is my second time asking you.
Brother Xu.
Don't put me in a bad spot.
I like my current workplace.
But Gu Chuan
will never be like me.
I'll give you
all the space you want.
You should know.
I'm starting to take over
the operation of Reindeer Group.
When I become the CEO,
you can come.
I'll set up the best
design studio
for you alone.
Brother Xu.
I'm glad to see
that you're doing well now.
But
I want to follow my own path.
It's more down-to-earth
and more practical.
Do I not sound practical?
Don't get me wrong.
That's not what I meant.
Everyone wants success.
This is the ultimate goal
for most people.
But I'm well aware
of the path that a designer has to go through.
This profession
is like architecture itself.
It needs a solid foundation.
If the foundation is not strong,
one day, it'll collapse
no matter how gorgeous the design is.
So, in order to lay a good foundation,
I have to take things one day at a time.
That's the path that most people
have to take.
But not you.
Because you have me.
Have we not had enough misfortune
over the years?
We've endured a lot of pain
that people at our age couldn't.
Only you and I
know this pain, isn't it?
Xiao Ning.
Don't be silly.
This is a rare opportunity.
Seize it.
Also, you have to trust me.
I swear to you
I can keep my words.
I can't digest
so much information now.
I want to focus on my exam now.
Let's talk about it next time.
Sure.
I won't bother you then.
But I want you to know this.
No matter where and when,
I'll always be by your side.
Thank you, Brother Xu.
Well, I'll get going.
Let's talk again.
Drive safe.
Did you catch a cold?
How about a cup of 666?
Thank you, Xiao Ning.
What I need now
isn't a cold remedy.
What I need is sleep.
Cold remedies can treat colds.
But look at the dark circles.
I sleep until noon
every Saturday.
I finally had two days
of beauty sleep.
Working overtime
is simply destroying my youth.
I really miss my bed.
I'm currently at the site of the
architectural scheme bidding meeting
of the Reindeer Group
in Jiangdong City Business North District.
I'm bringing you live news
from caijing.com.
(Reindeer Group) (Jiangdong City Business)
The companies
(North District Architectural Scheme Bidding Meeting)
participating in
the bid today include Chuan Design Studio,
Zhi Mu Group, et cetera.
Please wait for a moment.
I will notify you in advance
when you're up next.
Thank you.
It's just a bidding meeting.
Can't it be done in the company
conference room?
Instead, they're doing it here.
How ostentatious.
Such a waste of our money.
If it were you,
it would be way more than this.
That's for sure.
I just couldn't stand him.
Chuan.
The ball is in your court now.
Trust me.
Boss, drink some water.
Thank you.
Sister Man Lin.
Sister Man Lin?
What is it?
Drink some water.
Sorry, Sister Man Lin.
Man Lin, what's wrong?
Are you nervous?
You're not going on the stage.
Gu Chuan will be there.
I'm fine.
Hi, Mr. Gu.
Please come with me.
Sure.
Chuan.
This is similar to ours.
This is not just similarity.
Even a layman
can tell the degree of similarity.
What happened to the design?
We're screwed.
Did someone
plot against our company?
There are so many journalists.
What do we do?
Why would this happen?
Chuan.
To leave or to stay?
You call the shots.
What's the matter?
Is this plan on the screen
made by the company
that just left?
That's right.
Is there a problem?
It's none of your business.
This is our own internal affairs.
We'll take care of it.
Right.
I'm only here to remind you.
Time is running out.
Every company
has a fixed duration.
Could you give us more time?
We'll be quick.
We can't
use this plan.
An identical plan is taboo.
We'll become a laughing stock.
It's obvious they copied ours.
What's there to be afraid of?
Mind your words.
We need evidence
to prove that they plagiarized.
That's enough. Stop arguing.
The journalists are taking pictures.
Chuan.
Wang Kai.
Give this
to them.
Understood.
Take your seats.
Let's go.
Coming up next is Chuan Design Studio.
Let's welcome the designer, Gu Chuan.
I apologize
for the delay
because we made
some minor changes
to our design plan.
Let's take a look at the screen.
This time, our design plan
is based on warm colors.
We mainly use glass
for the exterior design
which makes it
look more modern.
It may not be the same
as the ordinary design scheme.
Usually,
construction using glass material...
This isn't our initial design.
That's Gu Chuan
who recently won the Jin An Award.
In addition to the sense of simplicity,
it also gives people
a sense of coldness and distance.
In order to break out of
rigid thinking patterns,
we use
the reflection principle of glass
to convert the blue basic cold light
into warm light.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Do you know what's going on?
Boss.
(A few days ago)
Here.
Take a look.
What do you think?
It's beautiful.
So this is how
your initial design looks like.
I didn't say it was mine.
It's not?
But it's very similar to your style.
It's far from it.
It is at first glance.
But your current style
is more avant-garde,
technological, and futuristic.
I've seen some of your work.
It's all grotesque and variegated.
But at first glance,
this design is bright and radiant.
There's hope.
There are similarities between the two.
Really?
My dad always said
that the outer shell of one's works will change,
but not the inner core.
Many ideas
have been formed
in childhood.
Even if the building is different,
the style on the inside
will not change.
Even if your current work
is avant-garde,
there is a warm
and bright side of it.
This was
my work when I just went to college.
I did some modifications.
That explains it.
There are some differences.
But this is a really cool design.
Do you think
it's suitable for this plan
if it's based on this?
This design
looks really warm.
But don't we already
have a plan for...
We'll go with this as the foundation.
Here.
You're in charge now.
Can I?
Of course.
If there's anything you don't understand,
just come ask me.
♪In my memory♪
♪Who is that♪
♪No, I can't sleep♪
♪Pieces piece together our encounter♪
So...
the two of you
did it anew.
We haven't slept much this week.
It is possible
if he has a good foundation.
But this
is an impossible task.
Also, this design is really beautiful.
It's even better than the previous one.
I like it.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
You two are my life saviors.
And so
this is the design
from Chuan Design Studio.
Feel free
to give us your valuable feedback.
You can't do this.
This wasn't the plan you submitted.
What's going on?
Does it violate the rules?
You...
It's not a problem.
We appreciate
and are willing to accept
better design plans,
even if
it is your momentary inspiration.
It's good enough to prove your brilliance.
Gu Chuan.
You're good.
Thank you.
(Thanks for watching)
Mr. Gu.
Why did you suddenly
change your design?
I heard you discussing
in the conference room
that someone has copied
your original design plan.
Is it true
that it's the same as Zhi Mu's?
Who's plagiarizing?
I have no comments
about this.
All I want to say is that
works with vitality in it
can never be plagiarized.
The life
everyone desires is different.
I love this beautiful world.
Thank you.
All right. Thank you.
Stop taking pictures.
Thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
Stop taking pictures.
Thank you.
(Chuan Design Studio)
You make me proud.
You are the most talented
and the coolest
designer team I know.
Although the results aren't out yet,
I believe that today's work
is enough
to take Chuan Design Studio
to another level.
Anyway,
we won
a handsome victory.
Thank you, Director Xu.
Allow me to update you.
The final plan was actually made
by Mr. Gu and Jiang Xiao Ning
who pulled all-nighters
in the final week.
So the credit goes to them.
We just benefited from them.
Cheng Dong.
We're a team.
The credit goes to everyone.
Everyone has made contributions.
Jiang Xiao Ning and I
used it as a backup plan.
We were worried
there would be a clash of designs.
It was a coincidence
that it came in handy.
Mr. Gu, you're being so modest.
It's a huge change in style.
How could you say
it was just a backup plan?
That's what makes a boss.
That explains why I'm poor.
That's for sure.
In fact, this time,
the inspiration came from Jiang Xiao Ning.
Although she hasn't been in the industry
for a long time,
she quickly perceives
the concepts and value of designs.
If a designer
does not have the ability to perceive things,
it's as good as losing everything.
So we have to thank
Jiang Xiao Ning for that.
Here.
A toast to Jiang Xiao Ning.
A toast to Xiao Ning.
Cheers!
What's wrong?
I'm just too happy.
This is
the first time I gain recognition from someone.
I couldn't believe it.
When you become a famous designer,
you'll be sick of listening to these.
Xiao Ning.
This time,
you're our hero.
That's right, Xiao Ning.
If it hadn't been for you,
I would be so embarrassed.
But
how did our design
leak out?
We can just check the CCTVs.
The CCTVs
are only available in the lobby
and the elevator of the office building.
The reason why I don't install
surveillance cameras
is that
we are a design company.
I hope
everyone can work more freely.
So there's no way
to find out who's the culprit.
There were people
keeping an eye on it the whole time.
Qiao Meng Jia,
Cheng Dong, and I have been keeping an eye on it
throughout the time.
We didn't see anyone coming in.
Forget it.
Just call the police and let them investigate it.
The process was precarious.
But it turned out well.
Chuan.
I've made a decision for you.
Everyone has been working hard lately.
How about a three-day break?
Thank you, Director Xu!
Thank you, Director Xu.
We can use this opportunity
to find out how did our design get plagiarized.
No need for that.
It being an outsider is very unlikely.
If it was someone from our company,
I hope
that person would come to me personally.
We've worked together for a long time.
I won't be ruthless.
Why were you so careless?
Why didn't you stay until the last minute
before giving me the design?
Don't you understand?
I've told you.
They pulled all-nighters to work on it.
They being
lovey-dovey isn't news.
I can't
be keeping an eye on them at all times.
You must have done something
that raised their suspicion.
I didn't.
I didn't say anything.
Everything was normal.
The hell with it then.
Knock it off, will you?
Do you think I enjoy this?
I haven't been able to sleep or eat lately.
I actually fell for your words
and did something like this.
You willingly worked with me.
Okay?
Fine. I made my own bed.
I love Gu Chuan so much,
but I ended up
doing something to hurt him.
It was so foolish of me.
Look, Su Man Lin.
Don't think you're the victim here.
My situation
might be way worse than yours.
What's on your mind?
Don't you want to find out who did it?
I couldn't think of anyone.
Actually, I know who did it.
I just wanted
that person to come to me
and come clean with me.
So it was someone from our company?
It was Su Man Lin.
Sister Man Lin?
It's fine. I have an umbrella.
I can do it.
What happened to her?
She encountered something unpleasant
on a rainy day.
So she doesn't like
going out on rainy days.
True.
Anyone who was trapped
in such a high place would have trauma.
(I've never told Su Man Lin)
(about you on the rooftop the other day.)
(Why would she know about it?)
(That caught my attention.)
(The surveillance footage)
(showed Su Man Lin)
(followed you and Chen Wen Wen in.)
(That night,)
(the one who locked you)
(on the rooftop was Su Man Lin.)
(I never thought)
(Su Man Lin would do such a thing.)
Since then,
I've been watching her.
(Throughout)
(the design process,)
(Su Man Lin was often distracted.)
(I knew something wasn't right with her.)
Your phone is ringing.
I'm going to the restroom.
(I never thought)
(she would steal our design.)
Sorry, Sister Man Lin.
Sorry.
Ever since I joined the company,
she has really helped me a lot.
She led me
in some of the projects.
She would teach me
if I didn't understand anything.
I couldn't fathom
the reason she did all this.
I find it hard to believe.
I feel the same.
Su Man Lin has worked in the company for years.
I didn't want her
to leave with a bad reputation.
All right.
Let's not talk about that.
You should think about
where you want to go
if I give you a few days off.
You're giving me a few days off?
Of course.
Anywhere?
Whatever you say.
I'll have to make a plan then.
Come here.
Come on.
That's my plan.
Hello, what's up?
Hold on!
Something urgent came up!
I'll call you back.
Thank you for the design.
Don't say that.
The client loves your plan.
-You did a good job.
-Yan Yan!
Thank you.
You're here.
You're early today.
Not at all.
This is Zhou Xiang.
He's my new colleague.
Hi, I'm Zhou Xiang.
Xu Cheng Ran.
Yan Yan's husband.
Don't listen to him.
Well, future husband.
How about this, Yan Yan?
I'll make you some soup tomorrow.
Don't order delivery food anymore.
No need.
Just leave the tough job
to her future husband.
Next time.
What are you looking at?
Get in the car.
What are you doing?
Does his cooking taste better?
Are you jealous?
Me? Jealous? You've got to be kidding me.
Why would I be jealous?
You're not confident.
He's quite good-looking.
But so am I.
He's just slightly younger.
What's the big deal?
I was once young too.
You're so childish.
Haven't you heard?
Love makes people childish.
Missy.
Aren't you into
a childish pretty boy?
Don't call me that. It's so gross.
Can you
not eat the food others make?
Missy.
All right.
Mister.
What are we having?
Missy.
Let's have
some savory hot pot.
Sure, Missy.
Say that again!
I was wrong.
Safety first.
-Sit tight.
-Shut up.
Okay.
Here I come!
Didn't I ask you to wait at home?
Why did you come here?
I just wanted to see you sooner.
I'll drive.
How can I let you drive?
I'll be driving today.
Just sit and enjoy
sitting on the passenger side.
Okay?
Here.
Fasten the seat belt.
Here we are!
Home sweet home.
Let's go inside.
Watch your step.
The ground. Look.
There's a step here.
Here.
Look.
Xiao Mai.
Where is this place?
Xiao Mai, look.
This is our house.
Look.
This was Guang Da's room.
When he was a kid,
he would do his homework
by this window.
That's right.
My brother's grades
were good back then.
If he was
still alive,
our lives
wouldn't be this tough.
Aunty.
We're back here
to cheer Grandma up.
Don't talk about the sad things.
You're right.
My bad.
Why did I bring that up, right?
Grandma.
The condition of your house
will not remain like this.
Xiao Ning has told me.
She will personally design
and renovate this place
and let you move back in here.
Who's that?
Mom, don't you recognize him?
This is Xiao Ning's boss.
Hi, Boss.
Grandma.
Don't worry.
Xiao Ning
will be a great designer
in the future.
Not only
she'll fix this place,
she'll also
give you a better life.
That's great.
That's awesome, Boss.
You have to help her.
Don't worry, Grandma.
I'll surely help her.
Xiao Ning.
Your boss said he was going to help you.
Grandma, say no more.
If you keep talking,
we're going to start to think
that you only pretended to be a dotard.
How could you say that?
I'm not a dotard.
Not at all.
When being back here, she's sober-minded now.
Right? Let's go.
Let's go over there
and check out my room.
All you think about is Guang Da.
Why don't you remember my room?
This is...
This is the scene
that I keep imagining.
My aunt holding my grandma
and taking a walk in the yard.
There are all kinds
of flowers and plants in the yard.
What's wrong?
Thinking about the days to come
warms my heart.
♪The summer in July♪
Grandma.
Do you remember taking us here
when we were kids?
We even went into the water to catch fish.
Xiao Ning.
Just like a boy,
you were swimming right here.
Really?
That's right.
I was so worried
and told you to stop.
While I wasn't looking,
you went back there to swim again.
I'm good at swimming.
I heard from Xiao Ning
that you brought her here before.
Yes, we came here before.
Do you really like Xiao Ning?
Yes.
This girl
is very simple.
And she's a little silly.
But she has a good heart.
Although
she has done many part-time jobs,
she doesn't have much social experience.
If she
does anything the wrong way,
please bear with her.
Aunty.
I think Xiao Ning
is a very sensible
and hard-working person.
I don't have to bear with her.
She's the one who's been forgiving to others,
me included.
All right.
I'll get some water for my mom.
♪You smile and say hello♪
♪My love is long gone♪
♪Where have you been♪
♪Is it the rain, mist, or the tears♪
♪I want to run away from this summer day♪
♪Where have you been?♪
What's up?
Did my aunty bag you out again?
No.
She was just telling me
that if I were to give you a hard time,
she would throw me into the river
and feed the fish.
I'll turn into a mermaid
to save you then.
♪Goodbye forever♪
Can you do it?
Let me do it if you can't.
I know how to do it.
Be careful.
Hello?
No loan, no investment, no house.
Thank you.
What happened?
I got electrocuted.
Bear with it.
Does it hurt so much?
Not at all.
I'm a tough guy.
I'm just worried about the floor.
You should just worry about yourself.
Why are you
so concerned about me suddenly?
Yan Yan.
Look at the candles.
Don't you think it's romantic?
Don't you think, at times like this,
we should...
At times like this, you're still thinking
about all this nonsense.
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
Scared?
Of what?
I'm scared
that you live a life of luxury
and got used to living a good life.
You're now with me
just for the sake of fun.
After some time,
you'll want to return
to the fancy lifestyle.
You get emotional all of a sudden.
I'm not quite used to it.
Come on.
Give your king a massage.
Here?
Further down.
It hurts!
That's what you get for talking drivel.
Well, I'll talk about the serious stuff then.
I went abroad with my mom
since I was a kid.
I've never lived
a life of luxury
or lived a good life.
I've always looked out for myself.
After I graduated from college,
you know the story
about my relationship with my dad.
I don't use his money.
I made it to where I am today
all on my own.
Well, I depended on Gu Chuan and myself.
In short,
to me,
being with you is the most blessed thing
no matter what kind of life it is.
I'll prove my love to you
with my action.
Go easy.
I need to rest for a week.
Go down further.
Feeling better?
Are you sure you don't want to go to the hospital?
No.
Director Xu, you were asking for me?
It's about the bidding meeting.
It's been making the rounds on the Internet
by the media.
I want to talk to you about it.
Sure.
I learned some news
through a friend of mine
and would like to verify it with you.
We asked the expert
to check on Chuan Design Studio's initial design
and indeed, it was similar to Zhi Mu's.
That's between
those design companies.
It's hard to tell
who was plagiarizing.
Zhi Mu Group
is a new design company.
You and the guy named Zheng
are the investors.
Director Xu would like you
to clarify this.
Director Xu.
I just think that
the company has too many projects recently.
We need a design company
and I see no reason
for project bidding.
That's why I set up this company
with my friend.
I hope you won't mind.
I really didn't know
that the design could be changed.
Director Xu.
That's enough.
I get it now.
To put it bluntly,
you're still wet behind the ears.
That's why you lost big time to Gu Chuan.
Business is a battlefield.
Is it wrong to cook up a scheme?
Not at all.
But that was a humiliating defeat.
You're right.
I was wrong, Director Xu.
Leave.
Give me another chance,
would you?
I won't make mistakes again.
I...
Have a good rest then.
I'm sorry, Director Xu.
Assistant Liu.
Anything?
The board of directors
didn't pass your resolution for
the CEO appointment.
Director Xu arranged for you
to be a department manager in the
Administration Department.
(Notice of Job Transfer)
This is an internal transfer order.
Please sign it.
(Gu Chuan)
Hello?
It's me, Gu Chuan.
Come to the studio.
Okay.
(Chuan Design Studio)
You're here.
Take a seat.
Why did you ask me to come here all of a sudden?
Actually, in the past few days,
I've been waiting for you.
Waiting for me?
Waiting for you to come clean with me.
Come clean about what?
I've always trusted you.
Your ability.
Your character.
I've always told myself
that you
are my most trusted friend and work partner.
But I now realized
that I don't know you at all.
I...
I didn't follow you.
Jiang Xiao Ning has never done harm to you.
Why did you treat her that way?
I didn't.
What happened to her
on the rooftop that night
will be trauma to her for a really long time.
And now,
you gave my design
to Tang Xu.
If I hadn't made preparation in advance,
you would have ruined me
and everyone
in Chuan Design Studio.
What was your reason?
In the past few days,
I have been thinking of giving you another chance.
As long as you come to me,
I'll forgive you.
But right now...
Sorry.
I'm just not resigned.
I've worked with you for six years.
Why couldn't I win your heart?
But everything
came so easy
to Jiang Xiao Ning.
Why?
I'm not obligated to answer these questions.
Su Man Lin.
Pack your things.
Let's not see each other again.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪