Her recovery is slow.
I can't say for sure
how long she'll hold out.
Hee Tae, you'll be a great doctor.
I only accepted you as my son...
because I believed
you would prove useful.
Hee Tae!
Please save Seok Chul! Please!
Oh, you're up.
You should have some hangover soup.
Yes.
Where's Myeong Hee?
Myeong Hee.
I'm ready to be hurt.
Do you want to go out with me
just until the end of May?
Let's talk later.
I'll give you my answer...
when you're sober.
Ms. Kim.
The manager said you can stop by
before lunch for the meeting.
Okay, I will.
By the way, do you have a fever?
Your face looks a bit flushed.
Maybe it's my spring tan.
(Episode 4, Crossing the Line)
My goodness.
Okay. So everyone is available
next week, right?
You made such a big fuss
first thing in the morning,
so I thought
it was about something important.
It is important.
Everyone in Seoul wants
Gwangju's confirmation...
and vice versa.
You're all just putting it off.
Anyway, I'll give this date
to those in Seoul.
What is your relationship
with Jang Seok Chul, by the way?
She's neither your family
nor your spouse.
Why are you putting so much time,
money, and effort into this?
I have to say, I'm really curious.
I'd say, we're offender and victim.
Let's leave it at that.
1, 2, 1, 2. Halt!
1, 2!
What are you doing?
I told you not to make it so obvious
that you're a leftist nerd.
Private Kim Kyung Soo!
I wasn't studying.
Hand it over.
About, face!
You dimwit.
Must you always be one step behind?
You drive me crazy.
Here it is, sir.
My gosh. A letter?
Are you planning
a secret rendezvous...
with your comrades outside?
Even going forward,
you're not allowed...
to send letters
or make any phone calls.
- Answer me!
- Yes, sir!
Yes, we'd like to transfer
patient Jang Seok Chul.
Right, we made the decision
with the risks in mind.
The hospital in Gwangju can do it
next week.
Two weeks?
Can we expedite it a little?
As you know,
the patient's current condition...
Aren't you going to have lunch?
- You go ahead.
- Okay.
Yes, I'm aware.
Right, so...
That's why...
(Pay Phone)
Yes. Please kindly look into it,
Professor.
Myeong Hee.
What brings you to the hospital?
Oh, I have a bad hangover.
I was hoping to get
some IV fluids in the ER.
It doesn't look like
that's why you're here.
What is it? Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
I have to say, you're so mean.
Why didn't you wake me up
when you were heading out?
I can't believe
you just left me there.
You were sound asleep.
If it's something to do
with the hospital, I could...
You didn't wake me up
because I was sound asleep?
Does it mean you peeked at me
when I was sleeping?
What are you talking about?
Anyone could see
that you were fast asleep.
Sure, all right.
I have a tutoring session later.
I'll see you at home.
Gosh, that makes it sound like
we live together, doesn't it?
Nonsense.
Get going already.
See you later.
(Letter of Resignation)
Oh, dear.
You always talked about going abroad
since you were a newbie.
Are you finally going?
Even if you submit
this resignation letter,
you know you have to work
for another month, right?
I'll work extra hard until I leave,
so don't you worry.
Hello?
Hey, Myeong Hee.
Today? Sure, I have time.
Why?
Did Hwang Hee Tae bother you again?
I'm glad to hear that.
Do you want to come over after work?
Soo Chan, aren't you going to work?
Auntie is coming over today.
Oh, right.
I guess I'll have to meet
Myeong Hee somewhere else.
No need for that.
We have plenty of food at home.
Just tell her to come over.
Gosh, I don't want to hear
Auntie's nagging.
She'll start nagging me now...
since you'll be
getting married soon.
Who says I'm getting married?
Aren't you about to?
I'm sure I'm not.
Why? Did you two fight again?
I told you
that you have the wrong number.
How many times is this already?
Ma'am, who was that?
The thing is,
someone keeps calling
since this morning...
asking if this is
some kind of publishing company.
Wait, I received that call too.
Wasn't it Jihye Publishing?
Oh, you're right.
Oh, that...
- Oh, gosh.
- My goodness, Soo Ryeon.
Soo Chan, I have to go somewhere.
What? I thought Myeong Hee
was coming over.
Oh. If she comes,
tell her to wait in my room.
Wait a minute...
Hey, Soo Ryeon!
Sir, I'm from Jihye Publishing.
Hey.
No one is coming after you,
so you can eat slowly.
Take off your shoes too.
Gosh, I'm so sorry.
I couldn't call anyone,
not even my house.
Has anything been decided in Seoul?
They've decided to hold
a full protest,
and the leaders will get together...
on the ninth at Korea University
to set up a specific plan.
How are things at the university?
Pretty much the same.
We'll shift the focus from
government-funded professors...
to demanding
the withdrawal of martial law.
We're still working closely
with Chosun University...
and trying our best
to fill your shoes,
so don't worry.
Won Seok, are you in there?
You have a call.
He says his name is Sang Min.
Sang Min?
Wait.
I never told her my name.
Won Seok,
don't make this worse than it is.
What are you doing? Get out of here!
Why isn't she coming?
(Lee Ji Eun, 22,
Ewha Womans University)
This young lady is
the youngest daughter...
of Baekwoon Textile.
She may be young,
but I hear she's an elegant lady.
- Auntie.
- What?
I'm really not interested
in blind dates.
Why you little...
You'll turn 30 soon!
If you keep living
as a lonely old bachelor,
you'll humiliate our family.
You should tie the knot
before Soo Ryeon...
so people don't talk
behind our backs.
Goodness, this is driving me crazy.
Hey, Myeong Hee.
Are you leaving already?
Yes.
- I'd better get going.
- Hey.
Did you say
you're Soo Ryeon's friend?
Can you come over
and look at this with me?
Look at what?
Women are a better judge of women,
I tell you.
Why don't you come and have a seat?
Come on.
(Choi Eun Ji, 26,
Lee Ji Eun, 22)
Who do you think is
the best candidate?
Number 1 is 26 years old.
She's the eldest daughter
of a judge.
Number two is...
22 years old. The youngest daughter
of Baekwoon Textile.
- Number 3 is 24...
- Auntie!
Who do you think you're yelling at?
Why don't you choose someone
yourself then?
Naive guys like you always let
cunning girls coax you...
and end up bringing home
the worst girls.
Auntie, you'd better go now.
Are you kicking me out right now?
I'll take care of myself,
so please mind your own business.
What? Hey, Soo Chan,
how can you say that to me?
- Please just go.
- What are you doing?
Let go of me. I said, let go!
Am I a stranger to you?
I'm your aunt!
Please! Go!
I'm sorry.
She's a very feisty woman.
She's just doing that
to find you a perfect match.
They all seemed like
great candidates...
I bet your aunt is going through
so much trouble for you...
since you're so picky.
What? I'm not picky.
I just don't like blind dates.
It's not like someone can meet
their other half...
based on
some silly matchmaking cards.
I'll look around too.
There are plenty of girls around me.
What's your ideal type?
Someone who's like a wildflower,
I guess?
Someone who never gives up
on her dream...
no matter how hard it is...
and never complains...
about having to devote herself
to her family.
A strong person that says no
to a sheltered life.
That's you.
Aren't I right?
Your ideal type is
a female version of yourself.
Gosh, it'll be very hard to find
someone like that.
("It's Been a Long Time,"
Love and Peace)
Then who is
Myeong Hee's favorite singer?
I'm not sure.
Bae In Sook?
Bae In Sook.
Then what is
Myeong Hee's favorite snack?
Sweet red bean jelly
and butter bread?
But what does this have to do
with math?
It's a necessary step
to figure out your study pattern.
Your previous tutor
used to be Myeong Hee, right?
If you don't review your past,
you will never move forward.
Jin A?
I have a new dream.
If I win an award
at the University Song Festival,
I want you to play my song
on the radio show...
that you produce in the future.
And the DJ will say,
"This is the musician..."
"that our producer discovered
before anyone else in the world."
- Hee Tae.
- What do you think?
Will you help me achieve my dream?
Then will you help me
achieve my dream?
Can you show me around Seoul
this summer break?
Show me TBC's broadcasting station
and your university too!
If you promise you'll do
all the homework I give you.
- I promise.
- Okay.
From here...
to here.
You want me to solve
all these questions?
Yes. If you start now,
you'll probably be done
in about two days.
You can do it!
- I can do it!
- Jin A can do it!
Repeat it three times!
- I can do it!
[Kocowa Ver] KBS E07 'Youth of May'
"Waiting for Myeong Hee's Answer"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
(1 p.m., Visit Sarang Orphanage)
It's tomorrow.
They might be fake coughs,
but you sound like...
you're coughing up a lung.
Gosh...
Do you want to go have
some butter bread at the bakery?
Or do you want to listen to
Bae In Sook at the coffee shop?
We could also go to the bookstore
and read some poetry.
Who tutored who now?
So aren't you going to tell me...
why you came
to the hospital earlier?
Goodness. I said it's nothing.
You're being awfully suspicious.
You don't strike me
as the secretive type.
So I wonder just what it is
you're keeping from me.
Give me an answer first,
and I'll tell you.
- An answer?
- Yes, an answer.
I've sobered up completely.
I'll give you my answer
when you're sober.
- Gosh.
- You should leave now.
Why? Are you still not ready
to give me an answer?
I have to study later,
and I'm pretty beat
after my long shift.
Anyway, get going now.
All right.
Do you have time tomorrow then?
- I don't.
- You're lying!
It's true.
I have somewhere to be.
I'll come with you.
You don't even know where.
What? Is it somewhere I can't go?
Suit yourself then.
Really? Are you sure?
Meet me at the bus stop at 11 a.m.
You volunteered to go.
Sure.
So I guess we meet again.
I never imagined
I'd see you here though.
Eat first.
You'll need the energy for later.
I don't know anything.
If you're talking about
the wanted man that you were with,
he got caught.
I guess you're very trusted
by your gang.
He didn't doubt you
even for a second.
Have you been spying on me?
Let's just say I'm interested
in my future daughter-in-law.
Who says I'm going to be
your daughter-in-law?
Do you remember the company,
Bongdeok Brewery?
About ten years ago,
they were number one
in the entire Honam region.
In an effort to expand
throughout the country,
the chairman even made his daughter
marry a man in the KCIA,
but something went wrong.
Then, the company...
went out of business
after a series of tax audits.
The son-in-law was demoted
to South Jeolla Province.
That's how things are in this field.
They never force you...
into the direction
they want you to go.
They just slowly
bleed those around you dry...
until you go in the right direction.
But human nature is a funny thing.
As you remain quiet,
you feel like you're a worse person
than the one bleeding everyone dry.
So...
keep your mouth shut...
as long as you want.
Right now,
your father must be busy
with the new factory.
So an engagement ceremony will do.
Also,
this is my limit.
Make sure
you don't cross the line again.
Get some sleep...
or meditate if you like.
Hee Tae. Please save Seok Chul.
Hee Tae! Please save her.
Hee Tae!
Please save her.
I must be getting weak.
I'm even hearing things now.
Jung Tae.
Jung Tae, open the door.
I'm joining the camp.
Later. Later, okay?
Father is on edge lately.
Later when?
I bet you'll make me quit track
next year.
Stop acting like a little child.
Do you really want me to look
like a complete fool?
Why? You don't have to.
This is why people call you
a mistress behind your back.
What?
Well...
I'm going to the bathroom.
Where's Jung Tae?
Is he still in bed?
He's at school. He left early today.
This early?
He's still in grade school.
He said he had to leave early
and do some homework.
Homework?
I saw him leave.
He doesn't have homework.
I just recommended
a few books to him...
that he should read
before middle school.
You recommended books to him?
It wasn't a friendly recommendation.
I told him all the sports
could make him stupid,
and he rushed
to the library right away.
He's still a little kid after all.
At home, maybe.
At his age,
I was already earning my rent.
Hae Ryung, you shouldn't be
so protective of him.
(City bus)
Myeong Hee!
Well, first off, some boiled eggs.
And some soda
for when we get thirsty.
Last but not least,
your favorite, butter bread.
You don't even know
where we're going.
Do you think this is a picnic?
It's a picnic whenever I'm with you.
Wait. What did you bring? Show me.
I didn't bring anything special.
Come on.
I see you packed a bunch of stuff.
- Show me.
- No.
No, because you hate me?
- Come on. Hand it over.
- I just...
- Let me see.
Look at this. It's so heavy.
Sweet red bean jelly.
Candy? My gosh.
What's this?
Herbal breath refresher?
Are you trying to quit smoking?
No, that's for...
Just in case I get car sick.
Oh, boy.
The more I get to know you,
the more I think
that you're like an old man.
Goodness. Give it back!
It's not like
you're all that sophisticated.
Grandpa Myeong Hee.
I shall peel an egg
for Grandpa Myeong Hee.
What? "Grandpa Myeong Hee?"
I have to say,
you're always so chipper, Hee Tae.
That sounded a little sarcastic.
No, it was a compliment.
Do I sound sarcastic when I talk?
No.
Here.
Where are we going anyway?
Tell me.
Come on, tell me!
Jae Young!
Oh, the witch is here!
Did they just call you a witch?
I gave them vaccination shots
last time I saw them.
Reverend Mother!
Myeong Hee!
(Sarang Orphanage)
My gosh.
I thought you wouldn't be able
to come.
Aren't you really busy
at the moment?
No.
- How have you been?
- I've been well.
By the way, who is this young man?
Oh, this is...
- I'm Myeong Hee's...
- He's a doctor.
What?
My gosh, you're a doctor?
That's great.
We have a few kids
who need to see a doctor.
No, I'm not yet...
He just got his medical license.
He's a rookie doctor.
- Let's go inside.
- Okay.
Myeong Hee, I can't treat patients.
I told you already,
I haven't even graduated...
You passed
the medical licensing exam.
You only deferred your graduation
for the University Song Festival.
No. I really can't do this.
I'll do something else.
I can clean, carry heavy things...
Oh, I'm good with kids too.
You don't have to treat them.
Just examine them.
I'm not asking you to do surgery
or anything.
Just examine the kids
to make sure they're all well.
You've done that much in school,
haven't you?
Well, I have a lot to do.
I trust you'll do a good job.
Gosh.
Let me listen to your tummy
for a second.
You're all good.
Say "ah." Open wide.
There you go. Look up. Good.
Stick it out even further.
This might sting a little.
- He'll get better soon.
- Thank you, doctor.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Kids take twice as much energy
as grown-ups, right?
What...
Well...
Why are you more tired than me
when I did all the hard work?
Are you okay?
It looked like
you were sweating a lot.
Well, that's because...
my blood sugar level dropped.
This is great.
I was debating...
whether I should stuff myself
with the grass or the soil.
It's like we communicate
through telepathy.
My energy level is shooting back up!
Just don't become a pediatrician
in the future.
I'll go and finish up some work.
- Stay here and rest up.
- I can help you.
Forget it. It's only some paperwork.
Enjoy the bread.
But...
Oh, dear.
Hi there.
We haven't met.
Do you want some?
Here you go.
Slow down.
By the way,
about that good-looking doctor...
How do you know each other?
This is the first time
you've brought someone along...
apart from Hye Gun and Sun Min.
For a nun,
you sure are interested...
in relationships
between men and women.
I knew it.
So is it that kind of relationship?
That's not what I mean.
What I mean is,
we're a man and a woman,
biologically speaking.
That's all.
Myeong Hee.
Something's wrong with the kid.
Young Mi.
Open your eyes. Young Mi.
Did you perhaps give her
something to eat?
I gave her some bread.
The bread you gave me.
She has gastroenteritis
and is not allowed to eat.
It's okay. Goodness.
It's okay.
Keep going, Young Mi. Don't worry.
Hee Tae, it's okay.
Hee Tae.
Hee Tae!
Yes.
It's okay.
It's nothing serious.
She's okay now.
I'll go get some water.
No, I'll go.
Sit down and get some rest.
I'll be right back.
Hey, wait!
Hey, can you please not do this
during exam season?
Just take him to the hospital.
You know I brought him here
because I can't do that.
Please be gentle.
You won't find a surgeon...
who'd be gentler than this
even at a university hospital.
That's true.
He's the top student
at our med school.
- We call him Hua Tuo.
- Hua Tuo, my foot.
I'll stitch your lips together.
Hua Tuo?
Is my specialty treating fugitives?
What if I get caught doing this
and get expelled from school?
Will you take responsibility
for my future?
Yes, I should.
I'll write lyrics
while you compose songs.
We'll win the grand prize
at the University Song Festival.
You troublemaker.
At this rate,
we'll be dragged to Namsan first.
Seriously!
Stay still
while I'm stitching the wound.
- Careful. Watch your step.
- Thanks.
Hee Tae,
you'll be a great doctor.
Go write some lyrics
for the song festival.
Don't use the night school
as an excuse to date.
Hey, what are you talking about?
You know what I'm talking about.
I can tell from the lyrics
you've been writing!
Hey.
Don't bring anyone else, please.
Thanks.
- Get going.
- Bye.
Bye.
Hey, do you realize what time it is?
Hee Tae.
Please save Seok Chul.
Her pulse is weak,
and she's lost a lot of blood.
You should take her to the hospital.
No, not the hospital.
I know you brought her to me
because you can't take her there.
Darn it.
You know the small clinic
down the street?
Knock on the door,
and someone will come out.
Tell them I sent you.
It's my friend's clinic.
Okay.
Hee Tae.
Save her.
You must save her, no matter what.
Okay. You need to hurry.
Darn it.
Gosh, this is crazy.
Stop!
- Let go! Let go of me!
- Stay still!
- Let go of me.
- Hey!
Cuff this punk.
Please...
Can someone please come
and help me? Anyone?
Hee Tae.
I'm not qualified to be a doctor.
I chose this path
because I wanted to treat the ill,
but everything I touch...
just breaks.
Maybe your heart is the one
that is broken.
You know,
we don't decide who lives or dies.
That decision is up to the Almighty.
All we can do is do our best
within the lines...
drawn by the Almighty.
And...
if I may share my opinion
as someone...
who's working in the same field,
I know for a fact...
that you'll be a great doctor.
You're beating yourself up
like this...
because you're
a very responsible person.
And people like that
are hard to come by.
I'm not being sarcastic.
There.
I can't believe you did this again
knowing what's going on.
Aren't you ashamed
to face your family?
I've never done anything
to be ashamed of.
How could you say that...
after humiliating me in front of
your future father-in-law?
Father.
I won't get married.
What? What are you talking about?
I just...
couldn't muster up the courage
to say this to you.
I have no interest
in getting married...
and getting involved
with that kind of family...
That family will help us
with the business.
What?
The company is about to go bust,
so I couldn't turn down their offer.
All my enemies want my business
to go bust.
And my daughter jumps into flames...
with gunpowder in her hand
any chance she gets.
So what choice do I have?
Father!
It's already decided.
Earlier today,
your brother met the investor
they put us in touch with.
Technical partnerships...
are already very common
in other countries.
The construction for the factory
is expected to be completed soon.
So I'm certain...
we can start selling the products
by the end of this year.
(Lee Soo Chan,
Changhwa Pharmaceuticals)
This isn't some kids' game.
We can't just back out...
because we've now changed our minds.
With just one word,
he can make companies go bankrupt...
and make people disappear.
You, of all people,
must know
what Mr. Hwang is capable of.
Just get married.
I don't care if people criticize me
for selling off my daughter.
Our family...
is already on the back of the tiger.
If we fall off,
we'll get eaten alive.
[Kocowa Ver] KBS E08 'Youth of May'
"Hee Tae's Trauma"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
- What...
- I can go on my own from here.
Why? Let me go with you.
We're almost there anyway.
That's why I can go alone.
Jin A might cause a fuss
if she sees us.
Come on, she's probably busy
doing her homework right now.
I can go alone.
Okay then.
I enjoyed today's picnic,
Myeong Hee.
Handshake?
Me too.
Thank you for everything today.
Look back.
Look back. Look back...
Look back!
Hey! Gosh.
I was wishing you'd look back.
Did you hear it?
I'll give you my answer...
tomorrow.
Can't you answer me today?
There's something
I need to sort out.
I'll tell you tomorrow afternoon
after my shift.
Here.
Yes!
(Head of Anti-communist
Investigation, Hwang Ki Nam)
(Kim Myeong Hee)
(Father, Kim Hyun Chul)
(Kim Hyun Chul, Choi Soon Nyu,
Kim Myeong Soo)
- Hello?
- Hey, Soo Ryeon.
What happened the other day?
I couldn't reach you.
Myeong Hee.
Something suddenly came up.
What? Is it something serious?
No. It's not serious at all.
So, what's up?
Can I see you
before I go to work later?
The thing is...
I have something to tell you.
Sorry, I don't have time today.
I have plans.
(Watch repair)
Can I get my watch repaired now?
You'll have to wait
about 15 minutes.
Can't you look at mine first?
I just need a new battery.
Let me see it.
(The Blue House)
Oh, look who it is.
Aren't you Hyun Chul?
How have you been?
Is your mother still alive?
Just tell me what you want.
There's no need to be so edgy.
I just came to get a new battery
and see you as well.
We're old neighborhood friends
after all.
I see your daughter is having
a lot of fun lately.
Keep a good eye on your daughter.
She's not a kid anymore.
I won't go easy either.
You don't have to pay me.
I'll see you later.
Let me say it again.
The most important thing
in track and field is the line.
Especially when you run,
if you cross into
another runner's track,
you may get disqualified
for deviating from your own track.
Hence, do not trespass
into another runner's zone,
and always stay within your line...
and run as fast as you can.
That's my main point.
- Can I help you?
- Oh, yes.
Is there a boy named
Myeong Soo here?
That's me.
Father.
Be careful, you might fall down.
Why are you here?
I thought you were coming tomorrow.
No reason.
I missed my little bear,
so I came early.
How is Myeong Hee doing?
She's doing fine.
Father, I shortened my record
by two seconds.
My coach told me...
that I can run
with the middle schooler next time.
Is that so?
Gosh, that's amazing, son.
Are you getting along well
with the other kids?
Well, almost all of them,
except for one guy.
Hey. Are you Myeong Soo's friend?
Speak of the devil.
Man, that annoying jerk.
Don't say that to a friend.
Here.
I bought plenty,
so share it with the others.
Wait, isn't this pulbbang?
Gosh, you didn't have to.
My goodness.
Where did you learn to say that?
You don't have to say that to me.
Me too?
It's good.
Hey, let's go this way.
I told you!
I told you it's this way.
Come on, let's go.
- Hurry up, it's this way.
- Okay.
I'd better get going now.
Already?
You should come meet my coach...
and the place I'm staying at.
It's okay, there's no need.
Your mom sent
some clothes and underwear.
You should go now. Go on.
Go on.
Go on now.
Hey, isn't that pulbbang?
Let's go inside and eat it
before the others see us.
Shall I call Jung Tae over?
Let's just keep it a secret.
Do it again! That's so funny.
I don't have time
for bickering today.
Get straight to the point.
I met your father yesterday
at the Defense Security Command.
He tried to threaten me...
into getting engaged to you.
That's my father's specialty.
So?
Your family is getting involved
in my father's business.
Did you know that?
How would I have known?
Like I said,
we won't be able to back out
once things get more serious.
So what's your plan?
My father's factory...
will be finished in a month.
Let's keep this up until then.
After that, I'll do as you say.
Once the factory is finished,
should we get engaged to make sure
the factory runs smoothly...
and even get married...
until the business takes off?
I don't need your sarcasm.
This is driving me crazy as it is.
Fine. I'll be straightforward then.
I don't want to.
- You don't want to?
- No.
Then what about
my father's business?
What about my family?
Look, don't put all the blame on me.
You started all this.
Hwang Hee Tae.
Let's tell the truth...
and take responsibility equally.
We shouldn't cross the line
just to save ourselves for now.
If you need someone
to beg for forgiveness with you,
call me.
Why did you do that?
I mean earlier.
Why did you punch him?
Just because. I couldn't stand him.
You're impossible.
Didn't you hear
what the coach said earlier?
"Don't cross the line."
Why cross the line
and get yourself into a mess?
You must've missed
some of the stuff the coach said.
What?
In long-distance running,
it's okay to cross the line.
You need to know
just when to cross the line.
That's what makes a good runner.
And we run 1,000m.
Eat them
before you brush your teeth.
(Cashier)
So Ms. Jang will be transferred
in a private ambulance...
that you hired in Seoul?
Yes.
I already paid for it.
Then please make sure
she is transferred here on time.
(Receipt)
Is everything all set?
Yes, you're good to go.
(Receipt)
Hey, grunt.
It's me again, Hee Tae.
Your dear Seok Chul
will be transferred to Gwangju soon.
So visit her in Gwangju
if you miss her.
You see,
if only you knew
how much trouble I went to,
you'd write me back immediately.
Her transfer won't get you out
of the military...
or help her recover,
but I hope it'll help us all...
finally take a step forward
from that day.
(From Hwang Hee Tae,
To Kim Kyung Soo)
I'm finally ready
to slowly walk forward...
from the line I drew that day.
(Samyang Flower Shop)
PS,
you once told me...
that I wrote bad lyrics
because I didn't know love.
But I think I'm ready now.
There's someone who can help me.
Myeong Hee.
Hee Tae.
Yes?
Can you...
get engaged to Soo Ryeon?
(Youth of May)
To settle the situation,
I thought I should tell you
as soon as possible.
Hwang Hee Tae.
- Aren't we even saying hi now?
- I didn't have time to.
You can continue to see other women
even after you get married.
Like how you dated my mother?
Hwang Ki Nam, the Head of
Anti-communist Investigation, right?
She was picking out a ring,
looking all happy.
I was going to return your favor.
You're supposed to buy a new outfit
when your sibling gets engaged.
- Soo Chan, you're here.
- My future brother-in-law.
My goodness,
you look like a movie star.
Myeong Hee, what are you doing here?