♫  Nowhere to escape  ♫
♫  No one to rely on  ♫
♫  Withdrawing smiles  ♫
♫  Never give in  ♫
♫  Forget about one's youth  ♫
♫  I've never been afraid of loneliness when
embarking on this journey  ♫
♫  Tears and regrets go hand in hand  ♫
♫  But my heart is still fiery-hot  ♫
♫ To the distance ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken ♫
♫ I will keep flying ♫
♫ Following the direction of the light ♫
♫ I'll forget you ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness ♫
[The Long Ballad]
[Episode 21]
I don't like war,
but I don't fear it.
Hundreds of thousands of soldiers gather on Weishui River shore.
I don't want the blood of soldiers to flow into the river.
I'm much less willing to see the warriors from grassland die here.
We're the warriors from grassland.
We fight for faith and are not afraid of death.
If you insist to fight, along the Weishui River
we won't withdraw from the battle tonight.
If you'd like a backup plan, the noon of tomorrow,
I'll give you a second chance at this bridge,
so that you may make up with Tang.
Go.
Li Changge.
Why are you wearing a Tang costume?
Where did you go?
What are you doing?
Come with me.
You may leave.
Your Majesty, good night.
Your Majesty.
Where's Changge?
Please forgive me.
I'm so useless
that I lost the princess.
Where did she go?
To the north bank.
As long as she's alive, it is great.
If she wants to leave,
nobody can stop her.
You may leave.
Yes, your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Your Majesty, please don't do it again.
Your Majesty, it's a pity that you didn't see
how agitated Minister Du was.
He was either looking around outside the tent,
or walking in circles inside the tent nonstop.
Like a loach trapped in a pot.
Got me so dizzy.
Xuancheng, say something.
Congratulations, your Majesty.
Your wish finally comes true.
But we won't know it for sure until tomorrow.
Go and have a rest, all of you.
I'll rest for a while, too.
We're counting on tomorrow.
Good night, your Majesty.
Do you know were it not for me, you would be dead now.
Take a hide here.
Be good and stay within the campsite.
Without my order, you may go nowhere.
You...
I'm the boss here.
You're trying to force me again.
Yes, so what?
I didn't plan to ruin my Eagle Division here.
No one wants a battle.
You mean it?
Believe it or not.
Is Ashile Sun here?
Yes.
Father.
Li Shimin wants to ally with me.
And makes a peace treaty,
which I've agreed to.
Tomorrow on the make-shift bridge,
I'll sign the treaty with him, face to face.
Like I'll really ally with him.
Listen up, both of you.
When I'm signing the treaty tomorrow,
dispatch the best archers of your divisions.
Bring bows and arrows, and lurk at the north bank.
After I drink the wine,
shoot Li Shimin on the spot.
They want to shoot Li Shimin on the spot.
To defeat the Tang army on the battleground this time
is rather unlikely.
I have no choice but to murder Li Shimin.
To win or to lose depends on tomorrow.
Yes, uncle.
Sun, any problem?
No, sir.
The alliance is tomorrow.
And you're breaking the treaty.
How do you win others' trust with such caprice?
Even if you kill Li Shimin, with the numerous armed Tang soldiers,
you really think you can take charge of the Tang State?
Say something.
I have to do it.
Ashile Sun, you said you wouldn't ruin the Eagle Division here.
Then what is this?
I can't disobey the order of the Great Khan.
Even if I don't do it, Sher will go.
If Sher doesn't do it, Tu Kashe and Qibi Duo will go.
We have numerous archers,
this assassination is going to happen.
Such being the case, we shall part ways here.
Where are you going?
Take note.
You're not going anywhere from now.
Guards.
Tegin.
Take her away and lock her in a camp.
Don't let her out of it.
Ashile Sun, you have no right to do this to me.
I'll say this again.
You owe your life to me.
Take her away.
You didn't change at all.
Still so arrogant just like before.
Changge, I'm not being arrogant.
It's you who are too stubborn.
You don't understand me at all.
But that's okay.
The alliance will be after dawn.
No one knows what will happen.
So it's good that you've gone.
As for Leyan, if I'm lucky enough to get through tomorrow,
I will find her.
You're so noisy.
Get out of my way.
It's a wide road.
I'm not in your way.
What are you looking at?
It takes me a lot of efforts to get these.
I won't share with you.
Wait.
You coughed.
Are you having a cold?
No, I'm not.
Stop cursing me.
What are you doing?
Making fire with trunk.
You don't know it?
How do you even make it to today?
So many mushrooms.
Can you eat them all?
I'll wrap up the rest if I can't.
Save them for tomorrow.
How about I buy some from you?
Or I can trade some with my cakes.
No.
That's fine.
They don't look good anyway.
What a nasty brat!
I've changed my mind.
Come and eat with me.
Thank you.
My name is Li Leyan, and you?
I don't have a name.
Just call me Mr. Wu.
Why would somebody be nameless?
There are many people who don't have a name.
It's not uncommon.
I grew up with no parents.
Nobody has ever named me.
You're so young.
Nobody is taking care of you?
I've been living here for as long as I can remember.
Growing up alone.
Hanging out with a bunch of guys who beg and steal.
As long as they get some food, I won't starve.
Don't look so sad.
We are very happy together every single day.
I used to rank the fifth.
I had several little brothers.
Thanks.
So where are your friends?
They are... dead.
Because of the war?
No.
We are beggars.
They died of hunger, coldness, illness
or being caught and beaten to death while stealing.
It's quite common.
You are so nagging.
Are you going to eat it?
Stealing is not decent,
but those thieves should be beaten to death.
What are you crying for?
I'm not bullying you.
I'm not crying.
I just feel...
I just feel there's nothing I can do to help.
Here.
I finally found you.
Dared to trick me?
Run!
Hurry.
You little brat!
Don't you run away from me!
Brat!
Xiao Wu.
Save yourself.
Stop!
You ate a lot just now.
Now don't waste it.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive us.
I shouldn't have messed with you.
My sister and I are both sorry.
Please forgive us.
Little brat.
Don't expect me to buy it.
Didn't you throw a stone at me?
Xiao Wu.
Threw stones at me?
Please forgive us.
We're so sorry.
We've learned our lesson.
Okay.
I'll let you go today.
Do keep in mind.
Stay away from me as far as possible.
Should I ever see you again, I'll kill you two.
Brat.
Don't let me see you ever again.
Xiao Wu, are you all right?
Let me have a look.
I'm fine.
I've been beaten up more than you could imagine.
You...
Are you really okay?
You're spitting blood.
I'm good.
That was like a massage to me.
Don't make a fuss.
I just bit my tongue by accident.
Let's go back.
The fire is about to go out.
Xiao Wu.
Wake up.
They've already left.
We need to hurry.
Come on.
I wanna sleep... Xiao Wu, wake up.
Xiao Wu...
You have a fever.
Your Majesty, I've asked Wei Shuyu to get the guards ready.
General Yuchi will be there, too.
But the Ashile Tribe is known for sudden caprices,
taking such a risk by yourself, what if...
So you know it's an "if".
Don't meet trouble halfway.
Your Majesty... Your Majesty, it's time for the alliance.
We may go.
Should anything happens to me,
please assist the crown prince to govern.
Yes, your Majesty.
I've dispatched the best archers of the Wolf Division.
The honor of killing Li Shimin is mine.
Don't you bother to try.
It's too soon to say it.
We shall see.
Go.
Go!
Time is running out.
It is not a military fortress that I'm guarding,
but the welfare of the people.
Their safety and happiness are really important.
Since you're looking forward to peace,
and have agreed to retreat today.
The Tang State will let the past rest.
Now we'll give your man back.
Khan.
Tegin.
It can wait.
But... the military counselor is gone.
What?
I found it just now.
I've searched the campsite.
She's not there.
There's no sign of a fighting in the tent.
But I found a small opening.
I think the counselor has run away.
Li Changge.
Keep an eye on it.
Yes, sir.
The emperor of the Tang State is truly generous and tolerant.
Protect his Majesty.
Protect his Majesty!
Hold on!
How dare you try to assassinate his Majesty?
It's a misunderstanding.
What was that?
It was him.
He fired the arrow in advance, and missed.
Take him away.
In a quiet manner.
Yes, sir.
Considering the alliance with the Ashile Tribe before,
we've met you halfway again and again.
We did it for our people, as well as for your warriors.
But it seems you don't want to take the opportunity.
Your Majesty, it must be a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding?
How do you explain this arrow?
We have treated the Ashile Tribe with sincerity,
yet you did this to us.
Instead of being grateful,
you tried to assassinate his Majesty in our territory.
Even death cannot atone for your guilt.
If I really intended to assassinate you,
I wouldn't have waited until now.
Yesterday at the Wei River, I could have fought to death against you.
We need to investigate this accident.
It's likely that someone wanted to set me up
and take advantage of our rivalry.
Your Majesty is valorous and wise.
But I'm no fool, either.
In my tribe, there are tens of thousands of excellent archers.
It's unlikely that we couldn't find even one crack shot,
and got me in this situation.
If it's really the case,
then I don't deserve being king of the prairie.
As for this accident,
please trust and understand me.
The minute I find out about the truth,
I'll give you a satisfactory explanation.
It sounds beautiful.
But you break your words again and again.
It's hard for us to believe you again.
If you really mean it, tell your men to retreat 90 miles.
Then we will let you go.
Otherwise...
General Yuchi.
Tell them.
Move the campsite north and retreat 90 miles.
Yes, sir.
Didn't you hear the Great Khan's order?
Retreat!
Now!
I said now!
Retreat.
Hurry.
Let's go.
Stop.
Nobody move.
Stop right here.
We haven't gone that far, which doesn't meet their requirement.
Qibi Duo, what are you doing?
Keep going.
What do you know?
Now is a perfect time for a surprise attack.
They think we're retreating.
So if we turn back now, we can destroy them.
Surprise attack?
Don't you forget the Great Khan is in their hand?
Do you want to commit treason?
My Qibi Tribe has trekked this far with no reward.
We deserve more than this.
If the surprise attack works, we will not only get properties,
but also the whole central plain.
True.
He's right.
Who dares?
What's Qibi Duo doing?
Warriors, let's return to the Wei River.
Get the Great Khan out.
It's a perfect opportunity.
Hold on.
Stop!
You're going to get the Great Khan killed.
Nobody move!
Somebody take him down.
Yes, sir.
Don't you touch me.
Anyone who tries to stop me shall be punished with him.
But the Great Khan...
Even if the Great Khan dies, so what?
Then things will...
His life is not your responsibility.
See, Ashile Sun didn't say anything, either.
Ashile Sun, what are you thinking?
Warriors, follow me back to the Wei River.
Get the Great Khan out.
Go!
Eagle Division!
Yes, sir.
The Great Khan has ordered us to retreat.
Anyone who disobeys shall be killed on the spot.
Yes, sir!
Tegin Sun.
Shixin Sili.
Yes, sir.
Keep retreating, make a campsite 90 miles away,
and wait for Khan's return.
Wait for Khan's return!
Thanks to Heaven's blessing, Your Majesty didn't get hurt.
I really broke out in a cold sweat.
Heaven's blessing?
Your Majesty.
Hitting the glass in my hand from ten feet away.
If Heaven is not behind this,
it must be somebody with excellent skills.
Send the scout to the Ashile Tribe to look into this.
Find out who fired this arrow.
Your Majesty, you mean...
If it's someone whose loyalty belongs to us, do get him out.
Yes, sir.
Please prove me wrong.
Bring the guy who fired the arrow and missed.
Ask Sun and Sher to come here.
I want to see which division this idiot comes from.
Yes, sir.
Idiot, even if you're cut into pieces,
it won't atone for the trouble you caused today.
- Father.
- Uncle.
Sher, so this is what you've trained?
I'm sorry, Great Khan.
I was so eager to earn honor for the Wolf Division and you
that I missed the target.
Bullshit!
Why are you dressed like this?
I've never seen you.
There are so many warriors in the Wolf Division.
It's natural that you don't know me.
I made a mistake for being impatient.
But I'm a hundred percent loyal to you.
Great Khan, I swear to Sirius,
my whole family was killed by Li Shimin.
If he hadn't raised the glass so suddenly,
I would have already avenged their death.
Great Khan, please give me a second chance.
Not killing Li Shimin will make me turn in the grave.
I don't care about your history with Li Shimin.
Now tell.
Why are you wearing this outfit?
I'll kill you if you don't tell the truth.
If I had succeeded in killing Li Shimin,
would you still doubt I'm one of the Wolf Division?
So this is one of the best warriors of your division?
Uncle, he... he's trying to fool us.
One outfit of my division.
It's easy to get if someone intends to set me up.
Why are you looking at me?
Well?
You think I set you up?
It's not unlikely.
Great Khan, it's Shixin Sili.
Come in.
Great Khan.
What is it?
Qi...
Don't waste time.
Qibi Duo really did this?
That was too easy for him to die like that.
It was.
Were it not for Tegin Sun, things would have got very terrible.
Sher, answer me.
What were you doing when Qibi Duo betrayed me?
If Sun hadn't shot him,
would you have turned on me?
No, I would never.
Uncle, please allow me to explain.
I've never meant to hurt you.
Ever.
I... I was just in shock then.
Please believe me, uncle.
Idiot.
You've trained an idiot.
You're an idiot, too!
Sun, you did a good job.
No matter what, I'd never let you in danger.
Son, you've saved my life.
A son doesn't have to beat about the bush with his father.
Now tell me what you want.
Father, please don't kill him.
Why?
No particular reason.
It's just that he said
to kill Li Shimin and earn you honor was his lifelong dream.
If everyone is like him,
it won't be long before we defeat the Tang army.
He only missed the target because of bad luck.
Death is too harsh a penalty.
Besides, this long trek has produced no fruit.
The morale is low.
Soldiers are on edge.
If we kill a loyal warrior,
I'm afraid it'll chill their hearts.
Why not spare him as he's loyal?
The soldiers will not forget it.
In the future,
they will fight for us with more determination.
Did you hear it?
You always see the big picture, and always think long-term.
Okay, I'll allow it.
You useless idiot.
Take your guy away.
Do not let me see him again.
It's best that you stay out of my sight for a while.
Yes, sir.
Take him away.
♫ Crossing the river to pick hibiscus,
♫ the brilliant orchid and many fragrant herbs.
♫ I pick it and desire to give it to someone.
So cold... is it snowing?
Xiao Wu, are you feeling better?
You were singing?
It was beautiful.
I know you suck at many things.
Didn't know you're good at singing.
When you get better,
I'll sing to you everyday.
Where are the others?
Why are we here alone?
The others... they've left.
But that's all right.
When you get better, we can catch up with them.
I thought you were just a little silly, but you're actually an idiot.
You think we're in the city?
You have nothing with you.
How do you have the nerve to be left alone?
Let alone reaching Luoyang, you'll get eaten by the wolves soon.
Xiao Wu...
Why are you still sitting here?
Go catch up with them.
I'm not going anywhere.
You've already called me your sister.
No sister will leave her little brother alone.
So you got yourself a little brother.
Took advantage of me.
Xiao Wu, let's make the best of our lives.
So girlish.
Careful.
I'm young and strong.
It will take more than a fever to kill me.
Let's hit the road.
Come on, or we'll never catch up with them.
Come on.
Careful.
Slowly.
Here he comes.
Tegin.
Where's the counselor?
She claimed to be from the Wolf Division.
Sher took her.
She's sacrificing herself for us Eagle Division.
No, I'll go to save her.
You can't go.
You going there now won't save the counselor.
It will only prove she's connected to us Eagle Division.
Then her effort will go to waste.
That's right.
We can't do anything now.
But the troops are going to leave,
and we need to return to our domain.
Then the counselor will be at the capital all alone.
We need to do something.
Young Khan won't spare her.
I will save her.
There's no way I'll stand by and watch her die.
Save?
Who are you going to save?
The guy who couldn't even hit his target?
He claimed to be one of my men.
Why do you care so much?
I wasn't sure if he is one of your men back there.
Now watching you like this,
I am sure of it.
It's fine that you don't admit it.
There are plenty of ways to get him talk.
Sher.
Don't you dare.
Let's see.
I took a nap.
And dreamed about this arrow.
But I just couldn't see who fired it.
I was wondering whether he did it to save me
or it was just a failed assassination.
Your Majesty, you've narrowly escaped death.
You're thinking too much.
Please take care of your health.
I'd like to hear what you really think about this.
Your Majesty, I never believe in coincidence
when it comes to life or death.
I believe coincidences are careful plannings.
Whether the man who fired this arrow is loyal to us,
there's one thing that's for sure.
He definitely disapproves Yanli Khan's act of aggression.
Your Majesty, I heard it from my son.
The night before the negotiation,
Princess Yongning went to the Ashile Tribe.
So you think it was Changge?
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter ♫
♫ As your silhouette weaves ♫
♫ and locks in my nostalgic dream ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the yearning flowing through thoughts ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ where the wilderness burns in my heart ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into an eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ where the wilderness burns in my heart ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into an eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
♫ It is sleepless ♫
[The Long Ballad]