♫  Nowhere to escape  ♫
♫  No one to rely on  ♫
♫  Withdrawing smiles  ♫
♫  Never give in  ♫
♫  Forget about one's youth  ♫
♫  I've never been afraid of loneliness when
embarking on this journey  ♫
♫  Tears and regrets go hand in hand  ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot ♫
♫ To the distance ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken ♫
♫ I will keep flying ♫
♫ Following the direction of the light ♫
♫ I'll forget you ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness ♫
[The Long Ballad]
[Episode 22]
My son told me that Princess Yongning
went to Ashile Tribe before the negotiation.
So you think it's Changge?
I have no idea about it.
But I believe if she knows the assassination,
she'll try her best to save you.
If she really did so,
I will be sorrier to her.
Hurry.
Halt.
Have you ever seen the lady?
No...
We've never seen her.
No.
Sir.
We haven't seen her.
Only your team sets off from Yunzhou.
How can you haven't seen her?
Sir, please listen to me.
See, how far have we walked?
Some of us refused to walk halfway.
Some chose to join another team.
And some...
We don't know where they have gone.
- He's right.
- So...
how can we know where she is?
Am I right?
Do you agree?
We haven't seen her.
He's right...
- I don't know her.
- I haven't seen her.
So do I.
Enough. It's getting dark.
Let's go on our way.
Let's go.
Princess, where are you?
Your Majesty.
Scouts have found out the source of the arrow.
Who's its owner?
An elite from Young Khan's Wolf Division of Ashile Tribe.
Yan Li has reprimanded him.
And now they've gone back to grasslands.
Mr. Wei.
What do you think of the news?
Don't be nervous.
It's a chat.
Your Majesty, to tell the truth,
my first thought is
fortunately not Changge.
Please forgive me.
That's also what I think.
Khatun, Great Khan is back.
Alir.
Let's go to welcome him.
Khatun.
I heard that they returned with nothing.
Please be cautious.
I see...
Let's go.
Welcome back, Khan.
Please have a cup of wine first.
Hundreds of thousands of troops brought nothing back.
Is it a pleasure?
Your dejected expression...
makes me feel unlucky!
Don't show up in front of me again!
Yes.
Khan.
Young Khan comes to greet you.
Greet me?
I think he wishes me to die!
Ask him back to reflect!
I don't want to see him!
Yes.
Why are you still freezing here? Get out!
Sun, you're back! Are you okay?
What's going on?
Have you seen the counsellor?
Sheer captured her and brought her back.
What happened to Changge?
Prepare some gifts. I'm to see Khan.
You're just back without a rest.
And what's your reason to see Khan?
- Report on military affairs.
- What are they?
I'll write at once.
I'll go with you! I want to see...
Mimi, please!
It's no use of you to go with him.
Haven't you heard that Changge is arrested?
Should I wait here and do nothing?
Shouldn't you prepare gifts to see Khan?
Why are you scouring your sword here?
Kurultai will be held in three days.
I'll request to fight a duel with Sheer.
I want to win her back.
Sun, are you mad?
He's stuck for how to kill you fair and upright.
How can you provide him a chance?
You'll show mercy but he won't.
I won't either.
Mimi wants to follow you to the capital.
Don't bring her there.
It's too dangerous.
I'm worried about you.
So I can't let Changge stay there for long.
Tegin, let me go with you.
Why?
Changge must be cold and hungry now.
Maybe she's injured.
So I bring her some food, drinks and medicines.
Give it to me.
No.
I must see her with my own eyes.
Tegin, please bring me there!
I'll be useful!
Young Khan.
We've just met the slave whom you brought back.
Do you dislike him either?
No.
We've seen him before.
When?
When we're in Youzhou.
And also he helped Ashile Sun.
He's the friend of the scamp...
Khan, would you please
keep him alive?
I will save him.
I won't stand by and watch her die.
As expected, their relationship is unusual.
Tuluk.
Go to bring him here.
Yes.
Tegin.
Have you seen a new slave with a nevus under his eye?
Yes, I have.
Where's he?
Young Khan's soldiers brought him to the archery field.
Wait for me here.
No woman can enter the archery field so don't bring me more trouble.
Once again.
What did that scamp ask you to do in Wolf Division?
To frame up my troop?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Do you think I won't kill a slave?
I'll count to three.
You still have time to regret.
Let's go to see Great Khan
and confess that you're a member of Eagle Division.
I am not.
Fine.
It seems you know no fear of death.
Sheer, are you crazy?
It seems he's special to you.
You can start to fight against me for him.
Let a man be your target?
Don't you fear to be damned by the god?
Ashile Sun.
Sober up.
Here's the capital, not your place.
And he's not your man.
He's my slave.
How can't I shoot him?
You've come just in time.
We haven't had a competition for long, right?
I don't think we should have one.
Don't try to refuse me so easily.
As you mind him a lot, then he'll be the award.
What do you mean?
Do you remember that
we always scrambled for small rewards by battles of archery?
No.
Never mind. I still remember it clearly.
Our first competition was for such a tiny Ping Po.
Sheer.
Release him. Let's have the competition.
How can I release the award?
It's a ready-made target.
It's right for us to test our archery.
You...
Choose the winner within three rounds.
If you win, I'll allow him to go with you with no other words.
Deal?
Deal.
Again!
You lost that game.
It's the past.
It won't be the same now.
You not only lost the game
but also cheated.
Father.
Sheer.
Is it enough?
I've told you to compete in three rounds so none can be omitted.
Let's change into a smaller target this round.
You...
What's wrong? Hate to see?
Or do you think I shouldn't do so?
It's too small.
You can't hit the target as it's windy.
Ashile Sun.
You're really arrogant.
You can hit it. Of course, I can!
Sheer!
You've suffered a lot.
Why are you here?
I...
I come to report to Great Khan.
Tegin Sun!
Great Khan summoned you to report! Hurry up!
Ashile Sun.
Nobody hit the target in the last round so we drew.
And you can't take him away.
Leave now.
I'll be fine.
Sun.
Wait for a few days.
I will bring you back.
Boring.
Tuluk, bring him back.
Yes.
Get in!
Changge!
Mimi...
Changge.
Why are you here?
You're injured...
Any wounds on your body?
Li Changge!
Tegin Sun told me that you would care for yourself!
Then why did you get hurt?
Why are you laughing?
I'm fine.
Or you can touch it.
I refuse.
Sit here.
Come on.
Does it hurt?
If you can't take good care of yourself, I'll...
You can break my head, okay?
How can you make fun of it?
Don't worry. I'm okay.
I will return to Eagle Division
and eat the boiled mutton legs you made.
Eagle Division is brave and skillful indeed, with strict disciplines.
During the battles in Weishui, your casualties are the least.
Thanks to Father.
As you've made a great contribution, I'll grant you a large reward.
Thanks, Father.
Comparing with the reward, I hope that Father could grant my request.
Go ahead.
Kurultai will be held in three days.
I want to duel and win the award of Sirius.
I hope to gain Father's permission.
It's a snack.
I agree.
You're really my son.
I'm waiting for your victory in three days.
By the way.
I know what you want but I still need to remind you of one thing.
You can fight for the victory
but don't act precipitately and unfriendly.
I see.
Father, please be at ease.
I won't embarrass you.
That's fine, good boy.
Kurultai is coming soon so don't leave in a hurry.
Stay here for a few more days.
Let's live together, chat all night and improve our skills.
Okay.
Report to Great Khan.
Luo Yi has been captured.
He'll be taken to Khan's Tent soon.
Okay, leave.
Yes.
Sirius!
I know you won't treat me badly all the way!
It's all your will!
Father. Was he General of Tang, Luo Yi?
Yes.
It's him.
He's commanded Tianjie Army to guard Jingzhou for years.
We fought many times
and I seldom won.
His good luck has simply run out this time.
I heard that Luo Yi was close to Li Jiancheng.
Therefore he hates Li Shimin very much.
That's why he led the Tianjie Army to rebel,
making Tang lose the north defense line.
While he escaped and hid after the defeat, how did we capture him?
After Li Shimin defeated him,
only a few trusted followers survived and protected him.
In desperation, he fled toward the grasslands.
As I got the news, I dispatched troops to find him along the border.
To my surprise, we found and captured him.
With Kurultai coming soon, Sirius really gives me a lavish gift.
Congratulations, Father!
How do you want to deal with him?
He knows the posts and the march deployments well.
If he can surrender to us, we could be more powerful
and it'll be easy for us to succeed.
What if he refuses?
If so,
I'll keep on torturing him.
My resentment won't be eliminated only until his spirit is destroyed.
Once a day. Don't forget.
And here's the food.
Hide it.
Don't be snatched by others.
You've stayed for a long time, so you'd better return now.
You shouldn't stay long here.
It'll be terrible to be found by Sheer's men.
Don't drive me away.
I don't know when we can meet again.
Maybe...
I'll be back to Eagle Division without finishing using them.
Time to leave.
I refuse.
Mimi.
You go first, Mimi.
Take care of yourself.
Greet to Young Khan.
Where were you these years?
No matter where I am, I've been a slave in the grasslands all the way.
Not so bad...
I thought you're...
Where do you live now?
I...
What are you going to do?
She's now a member of Eagle Division.
You're now in Eagle Division?
You're his slave?
Mimi.
Go back.
Yes.
Please forgive my leaving, Young Khan.
I have to leave now.
Mimi.
Do you want to say something to me?
Li Changge is my friend.
I hope you do not kill him.
Could you?
Fine. I promise.
I promise her that I won't kill you.
Well, don't want to live in comfort.
I'll bring you a hard time!
Have you seen Great Khan?
Did he embarrass you?
No.
Just a chat.
You've been arrested so why are you worrying about me?
You're right...
It'll be a long period for me to stay in Khan's Tent.
I'm afraid I can't come to accompany you.
Don't worry about me.
Mimi left something to me.
Three days.
Hanging on for three days, I'll come to take you back
as soon as Kurultai is over.
Young Khan, why do you call me in a hurry?
Do you still remember Mimi Guli?
Yes.
A slave from Mobei.
Why do you suddenly mention her?
Tell me... where she went.
Why did she suddenly disappear without telling me?
Great Khan worried you would lose your ambition for her
so he expelled her to some other place.
But why is she now with Ashile Sun?
She's now his slave!
The slave was handpicked by Great Khan.
Damn it!
So I'm the only fool...
Please give it to me.
Okay.
Just put it here.
Why are you in a daze? You want to die?
Young Khan asked me to keep my eyes on you.
Don't try to loaf! Get to work!
I was wondering who would rush to see me.
Well... It's you.
Long time no see.
Luo Yi.
I scarcely recognize you!
Are you still the brave and skillful man in my memory?
Ashile Chuobi.
I heard that you went out to battle yourself with nothing back.
You're now really good-for-nothing!
As you're captured by me, you're still reluctant to admit your defeat!
As long as you can kneel to surrender to Ashile Tribe
and fight for us, I'll now provide you a feast and a higher rank.
Ashile Chuobi.
Don't lose in your daydream.
How can I associate with a rubbish like you?
Want to kill me? Just come on!
Incorrigible.
You want the hard way?
It must be a tiring journey for him
so give him a "nice massage"!
Yes.
Young Khan, what are you looking at?
Mimi Guli called him Changge.
Effeminate!
No machismo.
I really don't know why she's close to him.
Just a liking between young people.
Why do you worry about the two slaves?
She's my slave.
Why does she love him?
That's past history now.
Just a female slave.
You can have as many as you want.
If you need, I'll find one for you.
I didn't mean that.
Uncle Lei.
Instruct them to assign him more jobs. Don't let him relax.
Yes.
Who's coming?
I'm ordered to clean the cell, General.
Shiba, hold on!
He called me General.
Bandits of Ashile won't call me General.
You have the sleeping-draught!
You made the guards faint.
You want to rescue General Luo?
Who are you?
Ten years ago,
you sent me a horn bow and praised me as brave as my father
in the garden of Eastern Palace
Princess Yongning.
Shiba, release her! Don't be rude!
But why are you here?
It's a long story.
Let me get you out first.
No need.
Even though you open the lock,
my legs will prevent me from escaping.
How dare he hurt you so badly!
We fought against them continuously all the way.
Then I was careless and hurt my right leg.
It's good to know that you're alive.
It's still hopeful.
It seems I can reconsider his suggestion.
Yongning, listen to me.
I know the position of Tang Army well.
As long as I agree to cooperate with Ashile,
we can use their forces to storm Changan.
We can appeal his Majesty's former subordinates in your name
and then kill the traitor, Li Shimin!
We can't!
Why?
Don't you want to avenge?
I see...
That's it... You've been close to your uncle from childhood.
I didn't mean that.
Since then,
he is not my second uncle anymore.
He's only my enemy.
I've suffered day by day
to find a chance to revenge.
But...
if we help Ashile Army to storm, we cannot repent anymore!
Uniting with another party to attack is a common occurrence.
We cannot find another good chance again!
General.
As a superb military commander,
how can't you know it's hard to return the military forces?
As I just ran away from Changan,
I thought there's nothing more to lose.
Nothing could hold me back.
I thought to borrow troops from Youzhou and Shuozhou to attack
but I knew I was wrong after a series of difficulties.
Bodies are piling up at battles
and how innocent are they?
If we help Ashile Army to attack,
how can the people of Tang yield without resistance?
At that time, corpses and blood will be all over the land.
Soldiers will die for their nation.
I hope you could think carefully!
Why do you laugh?
I was to sound out your intention.
Princess of Tang. His Majesty's daughter.
It's suspicious for you to be in the capital of Ashile Tribe.
It seems what you've done is better than mine.
As your father was my friend,
I just wanted to speak out against injustice.
I thought to force Li Shimin to abdicate
while I've never thought to be defeated.
An overwhelming defeat.
Ashile attacked Weishui for it lacked troops.
I brought the people a disaster. I should be reviled.
There's no need to blame yourself up for this.
Though Ashile Tribe attacked Weishui,
they soon retreated because of the trap.
You've been to Weishui.
Is that the reason why you're arrested?
Brave girl.
You're really as courageous as your father!
I'm...
very grateful to you
for maintaining my integrity!
Don't worry.
Though I've been trying to rebel against Li Shimin,
I've never forgotten I'm a member of Tang.
I won't surrender no matter what!
The most critical thing for you is to take good care of yourself.
I will come to save you.
By the way, Shiba should leave here as soon as possible.
I'll contact you to fetch him when I rescue him. Is that okay?
Shiba, listen to her!
Leave here now!
You!
Stubborn as a mule!
You dare to violate my words now?
You're the last one of 18 Cavalrymen of Yanyun.
I've already ordered you to escape long ago.
But you violated my order and came here secretly.
Do you want to drive me crazy?
Rules of 18 Cavalrymen of Yanyun are strict and can't be violated.
Don't you remember?
Leave now!
Go back, Yongning.
Be careful in the enemy camp.
General Luo, here's the medicine.
It'll be useful.
Take good care of yourself and wait for my help.
Thank you.
Don't move!
Who are you?
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter ♫
♫ As your silhouette weaves ♫
♫ and locks in my nostalgic dream ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the yearning flowing through thoughts ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ where the wilderness burns in my heart ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into an eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ where the wilderness burns in my heart ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into an eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
♫ It is sleepless ♫
[The Long Ballad]