♪ Ask the sword and knife,
and do away with resentment ♪
♪ I fear that new and old grudges
will add to my troubles ♪
♪ Ask each tactic and move
to see who is more skilled ♪
♪ Fate changes and cannot be predicted  ♪
♪ Ask the road and journey ahead ♪
♪ Where is my soul mate? ♪
♪ Ask the rain and clear skies
about the troubles on my mind ♪
♪ Face the moon every day and night ♪
♪ Ask the flowers and leaves,
their colors are perfect ♪
♪ Happiness and pain are both short,
how many springs are left? ♪
♪ Ask autumn and winter,
the snowstorm continues ♪
♪ The rainbow scatters easily
but the days are hard to endure ♪
♪ No one knows why
the flowers blossomed early ♪
♪ Heaven doesn’t mock us,
you’ve also grown old ♪
♪ The pugilist world is small,
but the rest of the world is vast ♪
♪ I’ve forgotten those who are gone ♪
♪ No one knows why
the flowers withered early ♪
♪ Heaven feels no sorrow,
you’ve also grown old ♪
♪ The heroes have died
and little time is left  ♪
♪ I’ve forgotten those who are gone ♪
[Word of Honor]
[Episode 31]
King.
The two ghosts have waited
for a long time outside.
Should I bring them in?
Scorpion King.
How many casualties are there?
We lost 47 people this time.
There were 3...
Enough!
Though we got nothing from this trip,
we contributed a lot to it.
Qian Qiao.
Grant them the antidotes of this month.
Yes.
Thank you for your kindness, King.
Thank you, King.
Master.
Hurry up!
Scorpion King, look who I’ve brought you.
Antidote.
Where’s my antidote?
Ah Xiang!
Xiang’er!
Scorpion King.
Xiang’er is just a tiny servant in in the Ghost Valley.
Why are you doing this?
Scorpion King.
This girl is the only person
whom the Lunatic Wen trusts.
We can definitely find out
the Lunatic Wen’s whereabouts from here.
Why the rush?
- Qian Qiao.
- Yes.
Hurry and untie Miss Amethyst Fiend.
I want to have a good talk with her personally.
Leader.
Do you still remember the motto of
our ancestor of the Gentle Wind Sect?
“A man lives when his sword is intact.
A man dies when his sword breaks.
Be righteous
and demolish demons.”
You still remember.
Then do you remember
that one of the rules of our sect?
“A disciple of the Gentle Wind Sect
will not associate with the demons.”
Today, you will explain yourself in front of
the portrait of our master.
Why did you do that today?
I associate with the Chief of
the Five Lakes Alliance.
He is not a demon.
He choose to ask a tiger for its skin*,
(*Ask a man to act against his interest)
bribe Scorpion and
tame the evil ghosts of the Ghost Valley.
I can’t control what they do.
Leader.
Do you want me to explain
to our disciples with these excuses?
Chief Gao’s death was a mystery.
It’s very suspicious.
It must be Zhao Jing!
Chief Gao handed you the Glazed Armor,
which he cherished
more than his life.
But you...
Firstly...
I didn’t hand the Glazed Armor to anyone.
Secondly...
in such a dangerous situation today,
could you resolve it
without my association with Zhao Jing?
As the Leader,
mt priority is to
maintain the legacy of our Gentle Wind Sect.
I’m not guilty of anything.
But if one day,
we are forced to a corner
and that’s the way to rescue the whole sect,
I don’t mind
losing my reputation.
I would rather die
than act against the principles.
Back then,
everyone accused Chief Gao of associating
with the Ghost Valley
and killing his brothers.
Looking at it now,
Zhao Jing is the one who’s working
with the Ghost Valley!
Enough!
Do you think I’m too stupid or too cruel?
I’m acting along with Zhao Jing.
I have my own plans.
Senior Brother, what are you planning to do?
Only if I become the supreme leader
of the martial arts world
in the upcoming Heroes Conference
and lead all heroes
to exterminate the Ghost Valley,
I will then have the rights to take control.
Brother Gao died tragically.
I must carry his burden.
But what can these stones do?
You must trust me.
Follow my lead.
I trust you, Senior Brother.
I know you didn’t do it.
I misunderstood you.
Open the door.
I’m sorry.
Leader, we are late.
Xing Ming?
Be careful! Protect our Leader!
You were the leader of
the Window of Heaven.
You were once powerful
and ruled over people’s lives.
But in the end, you’re saved
by your juniors
and are fleeing for life.
Without the Prince’s favor,
who do you think you are?
You!
What’s your name again?
You’re a disciple of Old Bi, right?
I’m Bi Xing Ming.
Old Bi is stupid enough.
I didn’t expect that his disciple
would be more foolish.
Do you think you can snatch
a culprit out of prison
just by your coordination
with your people outside?
Absolutely idiotic!
You’re the disciples of the old subordinates of
the Window of Heaven.
A few spies are keeping an eye
on each of you.
I found out since the moment
you planned to break into the jail to rescue him.
But you sensed nothing.
Did your dead masters
know how stupid you are?
But, thanks to you
for bringing out Leader Zhou.
Anything could happen in combat.
When I was chasing after the fugitive,
I killed Leader Zhou by accident.
I’m not violating the Prince’s order, right?
I am not stupid!
Leader, I, the disciple of Cheng Xiu,
Cheng Zi Chen
am willing to sacrifice myself
today to protect you!
I will make your wish come true then.
♪ The world is torn apart ♪
♪ The river water has dried up ♪
♪ If I don’t return ♪
♪ Let the resentment disperse like clouds ♪
♪ As times passes by ♪
♪ Even a broken soul would know its death ♪
♪ The waves will return ♪
♪ As if it’s immortal ♪
♪ Unstoppable fate ♪
♪ Stole the sun and the moon
in my eyes ♪
♪ Let’s pursue what’s righteous ♪
♪ Despite all the ups and downs
between heaven and earth ♪
What are you waiting for?
Leave with them.
Retreat with the brothers first.
Yes.
Brothers, let’s go!
Who are you?
Wen.
Wen Ke Xing.
The Chief of the Ghost Valley?
This was supposed to be a secret.
You’re putting me in an awkward situation
when you say it out loud.
Chief Wen, you’re here at the right time.
Even if you’re not here,
I will visit the Ghost Valley
to ask you for a thing.
Did I mishear you?
I didn’t kill you
yet you’re asking me something from me?
Chief Wen, stop pretending to be a god.
You’ve been too self-centered for too long,
not knowing any better about this world.
How dare you snatch this criminal
from Jin all by yourself!
You’ve underestimated the Window of Heaven!
You’ve revealed yourself.
The army will be here in no time.
Even if you’re excellent at martial arts,
you’re all alone.
Who said that he’s alone?
Where’s Cheng Ling?
I’ve escorted him to a safe place, rest assured.
In this case,
us brothers can give it a go.
Wen Ke Xing, what are you trying to do?
You’ve called me Chief of the Ghost Valley.
As the Chief of 3,000 ghosts,
would I come alone to
save him?
- Retreat!
- Hurry up!
Retreat!
Valley Chief!
Greetings, Leader. I’m Bi Xing Ming!
Greetings, Leader. I’m Cheng Zi Chen!
Greetings, Leader!
Senior Brother.
Before Brother Han died,
he handed me these children.
I decided by myself and accepted them.
It was Brother Han’s wish
to include them into
the Four Seasons Manor.
It’s my wish too.
I’m the unworthy Second Disciple of
the Four Seasons Manor, Wen Ke Xing.
Greetings, Leader.
Ah Xiang, they are back!
Master!
We are here.
Sick Dude! This is great!
Master, are you injured?
Who can hurt me?
Why are you here?
It’s a long story. I’ll tell you later.
Sick Dude.
How did the dog prince hurt you like this?
Master and I will
take revenge for you later!
Just with your martial arts?
Bei Yuan?
Zi Shu.
It’s been many years.
How have you been?
Master Wen, don’t be restless.
Though the Nails of Seven Torments are
hard to deal with,
it’s not hopeless.
Zi Shu has overcome many difficulties.
He will overcome this one too.
Lord Seven, as long as you can heal
Ah Xu’s injury,
I will...
I will try my best to repay you.
You don’t have to say this.
Zi Shu and I have known each other since young.
It’s just that he became colder as he grew up.
He never asks for help even if he needs it.
He never treats me as his friend.
Lord Seven, you knew Ah Xu?
Yes.
Looking at it now,
it’s been a long time ago,
as if it was something from my past life.
Master Wen.
The brothers are all here.
Lord Seven.
These children
are the disciples of our
Four Seasons Manor.
Before the Manor is rebuilt,
I might need to keep them at your place.
Master Wen.
Wu Xi and I are who we are today
thanks to Zi Shu.
I’ll be offended
if you keep being so polite.
Bi Xing Ming greets Lord Seven.
What’s your relationship with Bi Chang Feng?
He’s my master.
I was fortunate to inherit
my master’s surname.
Very good.
Oh, right.
Talking about this.
I received a piece of news
from my warrior, Qin Lai.
He has escorted Cheng Ling
to Leader Shen Shen
of the Mount Dagu Sect safely.
Since Zi Shu is rescued,
should we bring him back?
Grand Wizard, how was it?
Can you save him?
Please allow me.
I’m used to serving my master.
It’s fine. I’ll do it.
Let me do it instead.
Well, why does he do as you say?
By the way, Leader.
I forgot to inform you.
It was all thanks to Master Wen.
He contacted me with a mark left
by Brother Han.
He made a good plan and led us.
What did you call me?
You should call us Master and Martial Uncle.
Greetings...
No rush.
You can acknowledge us formally
along with your senior brother.
Lao Wen.
I have 19 young men in my sect now.
Aren’t you gonna share some of my burdens?
No problem, Leader Zhou.
You may leave first.
Yes.
Let’s go.
Ah Xu.
Why weren’t you shocked
when you saw me out of the jail?
I was looking forward to your expression.
What’s so surprising?
I didn’t know when and how you would come.
But I did know
you would definitely come.
No wonder.
So you wanted to run away with your lover?
Yes.
Little girl.
Why aren’t you feeling shameful
but proud?
Of course.
If Brother Cao is willing to come along with me,
it means that I’m more important to Brother Cao
compared to all the stupid rules
in the martial arts world.
Of course I am happy!
You’re right!
Miss Ah Xiang, you dare to love and hate.
You are the girls in South Xinjiang.
Yes, she’s like the people from South Xinjiang,
who’s good at taking away
children from decent families.
By the way, Little Ah Xiang.
Tell me how you two ran away.
It’s a wonderful story.
Ah Xiang! Ah Xiang!
Ah Xiang.
Why aren’t you lighting up your room?
I forgot.
How was it? What’s happening?
I still don’t get it now.
I feel like I’ve had a nightmare.
Master has formed an alliance
with the Five Lakes Alliance.
No.
Then what’s with the Drug Men?
If they were allies,
why did the Drug Men surround Mount Qingfeng?
Did you see the man in the black robe?
He’s the Black Grim Reaper.
Why was the subordinate of
the Ghost Valley there?
Chief Zhao has convinced the seven sects.
They will hold the Heroes Conference again.
Those evil ghosts
have already surrendered to Chief Zhao.
Impossible.
It’s not strange that the Black Grim Reaper
would turn his back.
Bu Sister Qian Qiao would never betray Master.
You don’t know.
Sister Qian Qiao is the Beauty Ghost.
Don’t listen to Zhao Jing’s nonsense.
He is not a decent man.
Ah Xiang.
Martial Uncle told me these.
I can only listen to him.
Ah Xiang, I don’t understand.
I don’t want to look into it either.
Martial Uncle said that Master
was planning to pursue more.
He asked me not to look into it.
But...
But I understand even if I don’t ask.
This is not right.
Not right.
Brother Cao, what’s wrong?
I’m just...
Ah Xiang.
We promised each other.
If Master and Martial Uncle don’t agree to our marriage,
we will run away.
Are you being serious?
Let’s run away.
I don’t care about being a righteous man.
You’re not evil.
We should leave.
I don’t understand.
And I don’t want to.
We should leave this martial arts world.
We can open a dessert shop
or a cosmetic shop.
We can raise cows and farm.
We can do anything.
What do you say?
Yes.
Just like that we ran away.
Isn’t it great?
That is quite wonderful.
Brother Cao can distinguish right from wrong.
He’s a real man.
You’ve married the right man.
Wait a minute.
I still don’t understand.
Zhao Jing allied with Mo Huai Yang
from the Gentle Wind Sect
since the beginning?
Yes, but he hid it.
He didn’t tell his son, Scorpion King.
Scorpion King fought for nothing.
He’s extremely angry.
This is not right, Ah Xiang.
Since you’ve decided to run away,
how did you meet the people
from the Ghost Valley?
How did you find us?
What’s wrong?
I’m sorry, Lord Seven.
Master Wen doesn’t allow Ah Xiang to say this.
He will cut her tongue off
if she does.
Alright, then.
It’s fine, you don’t have to.
Luckily, you found Master Wen in time.
Otherwise, we had to
throw our lives in.
But Ah Xiang.
Does Brother Wen have to return
to the Ghost Valley?
He finally reunited with Brother Zhou.
He will come back after stepping down
from the chief position
and help Aunt Luo
and her subordinates settle down.
But the Exorcism Assembly is starting soon.
All the heroes will go to Mount Qingya.
They can do whatever they want.
I only care about my sisters
from the Department of the Unfaithful.
I don’t miss anyone there in the Ghost Valley.
Who cares if they’re dying?
Okay, I hope everything goes well.
How does this silly girl
fold the clothes normally?
You’re here in time.
What’s wrong?
Why do you look so gloomy?
Master, I’m still a little uneasy.
Can you not return to the Ghost Valley?
We just have to take care of the girls
of the Department of the Unfaithful.
Let the other ghosts find their own homes.
They are all betrayers anyway.
Who cares if they are dying?
You sound like a kid.
Don’t worry.
I’ll come back right away.
You just have to take care of Ah Xu for me.
Master, you can’t hide from me.
I’m not stupid.
I brought Scorpion King to you
because I thought you could
make him surrender.
But if you get hurt from this,
I...
I will never forgive myself
for the rest of my life.
And I saw it with my own eyes.
Those silly ghosts were controlled by
Scorpion King’s secret medicine.
They listened to him like pugs.
Why do they come back and serve you
after your secret talk with Scorpion King?
Although Scorpion King hates Zhao Jing,
that’s not a reason for him to help his enemy.
You even know that he’s helping his enemy.
Seems like you’ve gotten smarter
after being with Little Cao.
Master, don’t you change the topic!
Brother Cao has said
you’re asking a tiger...
Asking a tiger for what?
Asking a tiger for its skin!*
(*Asking a man to act against his interest)
I know
you can do anything
to save Zhou Xu.
But Master,
you should tell me
what you have promised him.
I’ve told you previously.
Never mention my plot
with Scorpion King to anyone else,
especially Ah Xu.
I didn’t.
I just think that I should know
what’s happening too.
Master, I’m really worried about you.
Silly girl.
Scorpion King acts along with me
because it benefits him too.
I’ll explain this to you sometime.
The priority now
is for Ah Xu to heal as soon as possible.
Don’t worry.
Grand Wizard said
once Ah Xu’s condition improves to his best,
we need another master to be here
to remove the nails.
I’ll come back before then.
Now that you say this,
you should go then.
Right, you have left me behind a hundred times,
but not even once when it comes to that Sick Dude.
You’re jealous of a man?
No.
Why are you jealous because of me?
Why aren’t you jealous because of
your Brother Cao?
He won’t make me jealous.
Master, you must come back safely.
Have a little confidence in me, okay?
Even if I’m asking a tiger for its skin,
can’t I defeat Scorpion King?
Who’s the tiger? Who’s the hunter?
We still don’t know yet.
Valley Chief is back.
All evils retreat!
All ghosts return!
Welcome back, Valley Chief.
My apologies.
But there’s only one chair
in your hall.
If you like it,
I can let you be the Chief of the Ghost Valley.
How about that?
No, thanks.
I don’t think
I can handle a critical situation.
You should keep
the position instead, Chief Wen.
Brother Cheng Ling, enough.
Stop practicing!
Brother Cheng Ling!
You can’t learn martial arts overnight.
I know you’re annoyed at yourself.
But you can’t push yourself too hard.
Training days and nights
might not benefit you.
Cheng Ling.
Uncle Shen.
Can you talk some sense into Cheng Ling?
[To the Leader of Mount Dagu Sect, Shen Shen]
[Dear Chevalier Shen of Mount Dagu Sect]
[Demolish the ghosts and cleanse the world]
[It’s held on the 15th this month at White Deer Town]
The Exorcism Assembly is confirmed?
We finally have the chance to carry out
what Big Brother couldn’t.
White Deer Town?
The name sounds familiar.
White Deer Town is right outside Mount Qingya.
The first chief of the Ghost Valley,
Rong Chang Qing,
is buried in White Deer Town.
We chose that place
so that we can exterminate the Ghost Valley
at once with this opportunity.
Uncle Shen, are you going to the assembly too?
I want to ask you about it.
If I was the only one here,
I wouldn’t bother to be there.
I just want to fulfill the wishes of
Big Brother and Fourth Brother.
Watching you grow up into adults
and form your own families.
But Cheng Ling.
Although I don’t know
what kind of man is Zhou Zi Shu,
Wen Ke Xing would definitely return
to the Ghost Valley.
What do you think?
Valley Chief, I deserve to die.
Who did you offend?
Why are you here to serve me
as the scapegoat?
Yes... Serving...
Being able to serve Valley Chief...
is... is my honor. Is...
Enough, get out.
Yes.
What are you afraid of?
No matter how fierce a ghost is,
as long as it  finds the path to man’s world,
it will choose to become human again.
♪ The more I expected
the more unpredictable it was ♪
♪ Twined by the carnal thoughts ♪
♪ The rain washed my love and hatred ♪
♪ It bloomed and swayed ♪
♪ I suffered alone and acted calmly ♪
♪ Times passed ♪
Aunt Luo.
What?
Shouldn’t you be serving your new master?
♪ I couldn’t hold onto it,
I couldn’t escape ♪
Ah Xing.
♪ I wanted it but I let it pass ♪
Why are you back again?
Why don’t you leave?
♪ Who smiled ♪
Aunt Luo.
♪ Who was blinded ♪
It’s been eight years
since you last called me this.
♪ Who was blinded ♪
♪ It’s cruel but it’s beautiful ♪
I’m sorry, Valley Chief.
It was a slip of the tongue.
♪ It’s cruel but it’s beautiful ♪
I know I don’t deserve to call you like this.
Scorpion King used Drunk-Like-A-Dream
to neutralize the effect of the Water of Lethe.
♪ Who missed it ♪
Now,
I remember everything.
♪ Dreams are vague ♪
Back then, in the Healer Valley,
your parents were the one
who took care of me
and consoled me.
They not only cured me
but also offered me help
when I needed it.
But I...
I hate myself for failing to
save them.
Luckily...
Luckily, I saved you.
But I didn’t take good care of you.
Aunt Luo.
I always remember your kindness.
I really don’t understand.
Why are you going back to this place of misery?
Aunt Luo, I’ve remembered everything.
I thought I succeeded in resisting
the effect of the Water of Lethe
and remembered
all the murderers who killed my parents.
These years,
you watched me killed them one by one.
You must know it clearly.
But I was wrong.
The moment I drank the Water of Lethe,
my obsession was
that I led an evil person into my family.
I killed my parents indirectly.
Everything might end differently.
But it’s a different story now.
I’ve been the Chief of the Ghost Valley
for eight years.
I’m alert in case anyone wants to kill me.
I have to come up with plans
to kill others too.
Even after killing all the murderers,
I didn’t feel happy
because I’ve finally taken my revenge,
but anxious and tortured.
I thought that was hatred too
because I didn’t take revenge on all the people
who pushed my parents down the cliff.
So I put all my effort to set up a trap.
An interlocking murder game.
Aunt Luo.
Do you know my initial plan?
Hanged Ghost didn’t steal my Glazed Armor.
I don’t have the Glazed Armor either.
I’ve killed him secretly long ago.
That was just an excuse.
Valley Chief!
My plan was to re-enact
the Battle of Mount Qingya.
No.
I wanted to light a bigger fire
to burn up all the filthiness in this world!
Those so-called righteous sects
in the martial arts world
are just greedy ghosts
covered with human skin!
They should die together
with the demons and monsters
of Mount Qingya!
I let you out to the martial arts world
and released the news of the Glazed Armor
all for this plan.
Once you enter the Ghost Valley,
you’re isolated from the man’s world.
Whoever comes to Mount Qingya
for their desire of the Glazed Armor
will die here!
Ah Xing, what do you mean?
Are you...
Are you planning to die with them?
Since I set up such an evil trap,
I didn’t worry about too many things.
I didn’t consider
the number of innocent people
who would die from this.
Because at that time, I thought
the world had turned its back on me,
so I wouldn’t mind killing everyone in the world.
Until later,
a man taught me something.
Hatred is the same as greed.
They are caging ourselves.
My parents
and even you, Aunt Luo.
You tried so hard to save me,
not to bury yourself in the past.
Aunt Luo.
I’ve made a deal with Scorpion King.
We’ll get what we need.
Tomorrow onward,
I’ll ask him to
remove the poison in you and Qian Qiao.
Bring the girls from the Department of
the Unfaithful out of this valley.
As long as we let go of our hatred,
we are in the human’s world.
Why should we cage ourselves up?
Since you’ve decided to let go,
I’ll bless you.
You have your own decision.
I’ve made mine as well.
I’m willing to
suffer in this Ghost Valley forever.
♪ The sky was gray
as I crossed the cold river ♪
♪ The moon in my cup at night
reflects the sadness in my smile ♪
♪ Who allowed me to roam
around the world on horseback? ♪
♪ Who is drunk in their dreams
but can’t find home when they wake?
♪ The cold rain kisses my windows ♪
♪ I don’t mind hate and slander,
but my melancholy persists ♪
♪ The spring breeze
brings greenery along the river ♪
♪ But can’t warm my cold heart ♪
♪ Is that our light out of nowhere? ♪
♪ I regret not meeting you earlier,
but we’ve finally met now ♪
♪ Don’t let the seasons pass in vain ♪
♪ Give up the adventures on horseback
for a peaceful quiet life ♪
♪ The lights of ten thousand families
light up the world ♪
♪ The past disappears like smoke
in a sandstorm ♪
♪ I will spend the rest of my days
enjoying my life with you ♪
♪ I will be with you forever ♪