Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath ♫
♫ brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 7]
Thanks.
Brother?
Given his way of avoiding a problem by walking away from it, if I were her, I would find a new lover too.
With which eye did you see that he was good-looking?
He's very radiant. Girls like his type.
Your mother is always wishing to the moon and the stars for you to return.
But the first thing you do upon returning wasn't to see her. Do you think I don't know?
Anxin doesn't count as an outsider.
Look at her shameful behavior.
She is made of the same mold as her mother.
Whatever bad thing she does, I wouldn't be surprised.
That's enough, stop fighting. Our son just came back.
However you look at it, Anxin is a child of our Gu family.
You also promised Sister Jin Guan that you would take good care of her.
This child was indeed too headstrong in the past.
But I trust that she now knows she was wrong.
Oh right, Yuanchao. It's your birthday in a few days.
How about we welcome her over to get together?
You can organize it.
Leave it to me.
Son,
eat more.
[Aunt Hong]
Hello, Aunt Hong.
Anxin, have you eaten?
Yes.
So, tomorrow is your dad's birthday.
We're celebrating at the Howard Johnson hotel.
Look, you are after all a child of the Gu family.
It's not right for you to stay adrift for so long.
How about you take this opportunity to come back?
Aunt Hong.
Ever since he drove me out of the country,
I stopped being a part of the Gu family.
Are you blaming me for not taking good care of you?
No. Aunt Hong, you've been very good to me.
- It's just...
- Anxin, your mom was my good friend.
I am partly responsible for your current state.
It's normal for you to blame me.
It's just... your dad's health isn't as good as before.
He wishes for you to come see him more often.
What's more, Ansheng has come back too.
You two have such a good relationship. You must want to see each other.
Then it's settled.
I'll have Ansheng come pick you up tomorrow. Sleep early tonight.
You sleep early too.
Brother!
Isn't there still a lot of time until the banquet? How come you're here to pick me up so early?
I'll take you to buy some clothes first.
Buy clothes?
Isn't what I'm wearing fine?
It's fine, but it can be better.
Let's go.
[Happy birthday]
Xin'er, let me introduce you. This is Uncle Jiang.
- Hi Uncle Jiang.
- Xin'er?
I haven't seen you in so long. You've grown up to be so beautiful.
Whose eye fell into this?
Am I right, you little brat?
Stop staring.
That's the eldest son of the Gu family, right? Who's that girl by his side?
I don't know. She's quite pretty, isn't she?
Do you feel like this girl
and Chairman Gu's predecessor, Mrs. Jin,
look somewhat similar?
They are really quite similar!
Could she be the daughter Mrs. Jin
had with someone out of wedlock?
What "someone"? Isn't it the chairman of Ling Group?
That news has gotten around.
Elder Brother.
Are those people gossiping about us and the Gu family?
What else?
With how loud they're talking, I bet they're afraid others will hear them.
Lao Gu,
is this Ansheng's girlfriend?
She's so pretty.
Alright then, you should talk as a family. I'll go find Lao Qin.
You go ahead.
Dad, happy birthday.
This is the gift Anxin chose specially for you.
Happy birthday.
It's good that you've come. No need to make yourself ill at ease.
That's right, Anxin. We're all family. No need to be so formal.
So that person is the five percent?
If only Dad were here.
Why would he come here?
Come to someone else's territory to recognize his daughter? That's crazy.
I've looked for her for so long. In the end, finding her didn't take any work at all.
As it happens, Second Brother's troublemaker isn't here today.
[Gu Ansheng's resume]
[Gu Ansheng's awards in school]
Is this Gu Ansheng a stamp collecting machine? What does he need so many awards for?
His gaze is gentle and soft, and his eyes are resolute.
There aren't many who are good-looking, approachable, and a top student.
Girls all like this kind of man.
When did you learn to judge people by their faces?
This is called having a sharp eye for people. If you don't believe me, ask Ai Li.
As a woman, does she like your
icy face, or this kind of
radiant man.
President Ling is of course the most perfect.
You are her boss. Of course she doesn't dare say the truth.
Say what you believe. I won't blame you.
President Ling, there is something more important than this.
The Gu banquet today invited Miss Anxin.
Gu Ansheng went with Miss Anxin.
This Gu Ansheng is...
Mrs. Gu's son with her previous husband?
He doesn't have any blood relation with Anxin.
Do you feel a little threatened?
Why are you still here?
Do you want to live in my house?
That's not such a bad idea. Your bed is big and wide.
President Ling, the most recent news is that Director Ling Fang is also going.
- Make preparations.
- You want...
To the Gu banquet.
May I be so bold to ask if you like magic?
You are...
What's interesting about magic is that it's full of secrets.
But once the veil is lifted,
it may leave people disappointed.
Are you prepared
to meet the beautiful secrets of a new world?
Why does his manner of speech give me the impression of multi-level marketing? Is he a swindler?
All of a sudden, I don't want to know.
The thoughts of women are indeed hard to discern.
Especially beautiful women.
Your attempts to cheat me of my money won't work.
You think I'm here to cheat you of money?
Isn't that the President of New Way?
- He stole a lot of business from Gu Group. How come he's here?
- You're right.
Xiao Ba...
It's been a while.
Let me introduce myself. Ling Yue.
-Ling Yue...
-Second Brother, you're quick.
Tell me, what's better, Doctor Xiao's medical skills
or your acting skills?
Can I ask for a dance, Miss Anxing?
I don't think I have the right to dance with you.
Then may I have the honor?
It's been a while.
Let's have a dance together. Let's go.
Let's dance.
Let's go.
Let's go too.
Now you see that I wasn't cheating you, right?
How long have you known my younger brother?
We just met by chance.
Then I must warn you.
My younger brother is not a good person.
Most importantly, he doesn't do anything that has no value for him.
What does that mean?
I know you have a lot of doubts. I will explain everything to you.
But right now, can you stay away from my older brother?
I understand. You want me to stay away from your Ling family.
That's not true, Anxin. That's not what I mean.
Jerk.
Brother Yue, how do you know my sister?
It's a long story.
If my younger brother purposely tries to get close to you, then you better watch out.
After all, you have five percent of our Ling family stock.
What five percent?
Aren't you curious about the world behind the secrets? Once you meet my dad, you'll understand.
Your dad?
The President of Ling Group, Ling Tian.
He's also an old friend of your mom, Jin Wan.
Your dad doesn't have the slightest relationship with my mom.
As for this five percent of stock, I don't know anything.
Don't make irresponsible remarks.
I'm sorry.
Gu Anxin, do you still remember me?
- Anxin!
- Anxin, are you okay?
- Anxin.
- Are you okay?
- Hurry and call the police!
- Don't call the police.
- This is my friend.
- Who is your friend?
I must have gotten eight generations of bad luck to have met you.
If it weren't for you, I wouldn't have fallen into such a state.
What are you doing?
Anxin, how much of a mess do you want to make?
Dad!
Chairman Gu, shouldn't you be protecting your daughter at a time like this?
Ling Yue, this is my family matter.
I hope you can stay out of my business.
But I can't stay out of things concerning Anxin.
Chairman, we've disturbed everyone's banquet.
We'll leave right now.
Yu Guo,
I looked for you for so long and never found you.
Let's find a quiet place, and I'll explain everything to you, okay?
Let her go.
- Anxin.
- I'll go with you.
This is my private matter. You don't need to follow.
If you keep following me, I won't speak to you again.
Alright, everyone can stop looking. It's a small incident.
Confiscate all the cameras. Delete all the pictures.
Yu Guo, I'm sorry.
I never thought our first encounter would be like this.
I didn't only lose my hands. I lost my whole life.
Can your one word of "sorry" fix things?
Yu Guo,
I know there's nothing I can do to make things up to you.
But I will do everything I can to make things up...
That's right. You're now a rich girl at the top of society.
What can't you do? What can't you make up?
Stop!
Zoom in.
After that, they disappeared.
- I'll do anything you ask of me.
- Alright.
Right now I want your hand. You can use this hand to make things up to me.
What part of the hotel doesn't have monitoring?
The locker rooms and bathrooms don't have any.
Let's hurry and search them one-by-one.
Anxin. Anxin.
Gu Anxin.
Move aside.
Anxin. Anxin!
Send her to the hospital.
When did he become so cunning?
Anxin.
Thank you, President Ling. You can hand my sister back to me.
No need.
What did you say?
Even if your Anxin's friend,
to brazenly take my sister from my Gu family banquet
is not very appropriate.
She is mine.
What nonsense are you saying?
I said, she's mine.
Both of you, take it easy.
Mr. Gu, President Ling and Anxin's relationship
is closer than you think.
What can one picture prove?
Look at the mess you've made.
Let them leave.
And you.
For this trivial matter, you've left all those guests
to the side.
- Dad, how can this be a trivial matter?
- Anxin is already—
- Ansheng!
Come back with me.
Xin'er, goodbye.
Elder Brother, why are you holding your stomach?
It's nothing. I ate something bad.
Where is Second Brother?
Second Brother already left.
Let's go home.
Are you okay?
- Is your stomach okay?
- I'm fine.
[Go back to the countryside for a while now.]
[I will come find you.]
Gu Anxin, we will meet again.
Didn't you say she's fine?
- Why hasn't she woken yet?
- She hasn't woken up yet
not just because of her physical health.
But its because she has too much responsibility to handle at once
I don't have to say who this was caused by right?
Here
Are you uncomfortable anywhere?
It's none of your business.
Where is Yu guo ?
Don't worry, I won't let her get away with it.
If you dare do anything to her I won't let you get away with it.
You're too kind. He's already caused you to be like this and you're still protecting him.
Yes, I'm too kind.
If I hadn't been this kind when I first met you
I wouldn't have been lied to.
- It's my fault.
- It doesn't matter.
Let go.
You should go out first.
Me?
Close the door on your way out
Let's talk.
Talk about what?
Talk about how much the hospital fees are?
- That's not what I mean.
- Then there's nothing to talk about.
Let go.
If-if I let go and you leave, then what happens?
I won't leave, let me go.
Then we've agreed, you won't leave.
Agreed, I won't leave.
No, you must be lying.
If you don't let go of me, I'll bite off my tongue and commit suicide now
I'm going to bite
Don't be rash.
What century is this even ...
Can you give me one minute of your time
Go ahead.
I'm sorry. I've come back too late.
Since you left you don't have to come back.
I only left
because something urgent happened at home. I had to go back.
Do you have to go to the hotel for urgent matters?
Hotel?
- How did you —
- How did I know?
I already don't know too many things.
Amnesia?
Also lying about the leg injury?
No, you've been lying since the start.
Just for the 5% of stocks.
President Ling, you've worked hard at acting.
Ai le is just my assistant
It's my fault for not telling you somethings right away.
Though my leg healed and I didn't tell you, that was my fault.
But my feelings for you have been true all along.
[time's up]
- Dad.
- I don't care where you are right now,
you come back right away!
Anxin, wait for me for a moment.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Keep your word
Stamp this
Childish.
This is what you taught me
Why are you taking my shoes?
I'm keeping it, in case you leave.
Ling Yue, do you know a girl named Gu Anxin?
Yes.
- She's the one that I like.
- Someone you like?
So you're saying you knew all along where she was
but you hid it from me?
Is this for the 5% of stocks she has?
Brother, now that's wrong of you
How can you cheat Gu Anxin's feelings just for the 5%?
Also, what if
Anxin is really dad's daughter
then you made a huge mistake!
I truly like Anxin.
Also, she's not dad's daughter.
This is Anxin's DNA report.
It says she's not your daughter.
If Anxin isn't our family
then why did dad give her stocks?
You're right.
Anxin isn't my daughter.
Since everyone is gathered here today
I'll just tell everyone at once
I'll tell you everything.
The reason I gave her the stocks
is because of her mother, Jinwan.
To me, Ling Tian, Jinwan is
someone I am grateful to for the rest of my life.
I remember when I first started and failed
if it weren't for Jinwan's help
there's no way we could have today's Ling Group.
That's why, to me Jinwan
is my friend and also my savior.
The 5% of stocks
was my promise to give to Jinwan.
Even though she's not here anymore, my words
will not be taken back.
Although Anxin doesn't have blood-relations with me,
Jinwan's daughter is my daughter.
So you all remember this, do not
do anything towards Anxin.
Brother, didn't your leg just recover ?
Be careful when you walk
You don't have to worry about it, Big brother.
Have a safe trip.
Big brother, why are your words so harsh?
How was that harsh?
Big brother, didn't dad just say
we can't bother Anxin.
Are you thinking of doing something else ?
That is what is said
But is the daughter and daughter in law
But I still feel like, you are still not on par with Ling Yue
Wait, what did you say ?
My sister is in this ward room right?
No...ahh.
Don't make things difficult for me.
Anxin.
Anxin, you big brother is here to pick you up.
Anxin?
Anxin!
- Big brother!
- Come up, quickly.
- Why are you here?
- Come back up quickly!
I can't get up.
- Can I go down instead, it's not that high up.
- Wait for me. I'm coming right away!
Hold on to the rope
You almost scared me to death, when did you recover
You go tell Ling Yue
Medical fees and anything I owe him I will return to him.
Big brother, let's go.
Let's go.
How about I give the medical fees?
Can you not leave?
Ling Yue will get mad at me
Your call cannot be connected.
President Ling.
President Ling, you should knock.
Where is Anxin? Where did you hide her?
Isn't hiding people, your specialty?
Mr. Gu, we are looking for Miss Anxin to talk about something.
Then wait here a second, I will get her to come out.
What are you doing?
Guys can't just go into a girl's room.
I am Gu Anxin's brother, who are you?
I am her soulmate. I slept here several times.
Watch what you are saying.
You are both guys, so it's not convenient. Let's wait for Miss Anxin.
The greatest son of Ling Group
lying like this in other's house, is it appropriate?
This sofa belongs to me.
That cup is mine.
What a coincidence!
That cup is Anxin's.
Brother-
This President Ling said he wanted to see you.
I already said what I had to say.
I don't have anything else I want to say.
I just wanted to come see you.
Since you already saw me, you can leave.
Let's go.
I am also hungry, so let's go together.
We are heading a small and dirty restaurant, you sure you are coming together?
-Fly?
-That's right.
It's those restaurants with a lot of germs, dust, and flies that fly around.
Maybe when you are eating, there may be something that drops into your food.
Do you still want to go?
I... like flys.
We don't.
I think you are like a fly right now, buzzing around me all day.
You can go eat, I don't want to eat.
I'm not going, please don't starve yourself.
Miss Anxin, President Ling is trying to be nice.
Let's go.
I'd not see you out.
If you don't want to go out, then let's not go out. I'll make something at home.
What do you want to eat?
Brother...
Why aren't you asking me?
Ask you what?
About everything that happened recently,
About what my relationship with Ling Yue is,
About why I am treating him like that?
If you don't want to talk about it, I don't want to force you.
No matter what happens between you two,
it's all his fault. Right?
Brother.
Did he bully you? If he did, tell me.
I will go teach him a lesson.
You have always favored me so unconditionally since childhood
I remember when we were younger,
I fought with my classmates
and even though I was the one who hit him,
you just had to rush to his house and drag him out, making him apologize to me.
Aunt Hong punished you to keep writing self-criticism for a whole week for this thing
You are the one to talk- who was the one, at that time,
told me to just photocopy my self-criticisms instead of writing?
Then, who told you to be so bad at lying?
Become terrified every time you get caught
Right. Who could ever be smarter than you?
I'll go cook for you.
No need!
You probably put a lot of good food in my fridge?
You should go home early, it's his birthday.
Why can't Dad see your good?
Once I left the house, I used my own hands to keep myself alive. I am very happy.
Okay! As long as you are happy.
If you are tired, come and find me. I will always be here.
Okay. Then I'm leaving.
[Curricula Vitae of Yu Guo]
Curricula Vitae of Yu Guo
We are still finding her.
Let's go.
I'm sorry everyone, because of my own personal reasons
I will stop the updating of
I will be looking forward to seeing you all again.
[Weibo account page]
Xiao Wang, why are you here?
Anxin, it's really you? This is your delivery.
Mine?
Yes it's even an emergency order. And it's still hot. Eat it as early.
Thank you.
If you have nothing else, then I'm leaving.
-Be safe.
-Okay.
Mine?
Then I will make food for you every day.
Gu Anxin, you need to be stronger.
How can you be so easily bought?
Oh yeah, I still have instant noodles.
Brother, why can't you let me enjoy junk food.
What smells so good?
Wow!
Weren't you thinking about it yourself? How come you come back this fast?
It's enough as long as I keep it in my heart, right?
Did you make it? Your cooking skills are pretty good, can you make me some?
I didn't make it.
You didn't do it? Then who did?
You made it for Anxin?
We have known each other for so long and you haven't made me a meal yet.
Just because you knew her for a few months-
You are paying too much more attention to women than to your friends!
President Ling, since Miss Anxin is still mad at you, will she eat what you made?
She is still mad at you?
No matter how made she is, she won't be upset at the food.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫