(THUDDING)
(SONAR PINGING)
(PINGING CONTINUES)
(GATES RUMBLING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(PINGING CONTINUES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Relax.
Anything in here
would be dead by now.
There she is,
the Indominus Rex.
(WHIRRING)
(BEEPING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
SUB PILOT: (ON RADIO) Specimen collected.
Sent to the surface.
Roger that.
Air One, clear for takeoff.
Begin tracking.
- HELICOPTER PILOT: Copy that.
- Go, go!
Tracking on.
(WIND HOWLING)
(RUSTLING)
(GASPS)
HELICOPTER PILOT: Land One, the asset is secure.
We got what we came for.
We're coming back for you.
Close the doors.
Marine One, I gotta close
the gates. Get out of there.
Understood.
We're heading out.
(RAPID BEEPING)
JACK: Marine One, I need to close the gates.
Confirm position.
Can you hear me?
Are you out?
Marine One?
- Guys?
- What is that?
(BRANCHES SNAPPING)
JACK: Marine One,
I'm closing the gates.
(ALARM BLARING)
Seriously, guys,
I'm kind of exposed out here.
Marine One-
Confirm you're out, Marine One.
Confirm position.
Can you hear me, Marine One, where are you?
(MEN SHOUTING)
Come on!
I can't reach them!
- MAN 1: Come on!
- What?
- (THUNDER CRASHES)
- (GROWLING)
MAN 1: Behind you!
What is going on?
I can't hear you!
(SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
JACK: No, no! Wait!
Don't go! No!
(BEEPS)
Throw him the ladder.
JACK: Come on!
Bring it down!
Slow down! No, no, no!
Don't go!
(WHIMPERING)
Oh, God!
(SCREAMING)
No, wait! No, no! No!
(ROARS)
(WHIMPERING)
(YELLS)
Oh, God, no!
God, no!
- (ALARM BLARING)
- We're gonna stall!
Cut it now!
- MAN 1: Give him a chance!
- HELICOPTER PILOT: We're gonna die here!
Come on! Come on!
No, no, no!
Oh, God!
I said cut it!
Don't do it! It's horrible!
I don't wanna die!
- Yeah! (LAUGHING)
- (ROARING)
(LAUGHING)
- Yeah!
- Come on!
(ROARING)
(ALL PANTING)
(BEEPS)
MAN 2: DNA sample secured.
Tell the boss we're coming back home.
(ROARING)
(RUMBLING)
NEWS ANCHOR: Three years after
the fall of Jurassic World,
the debate
over Isla Nublar rages on.
The island's long-dormant
volcano, reclassified as active,
has shown considerable unrest
in recent months.
Geologists now predict
an extinction-level event
will kill off the last
living dinosaurs on the planet.
Since the disaster
that shocked the world in 2015,
the Masrani Corporation has paid out
more than 800 million in damages
to settle class-action lawsuits
brought by survivors.
Activist groups have mobilized
around the globe
in what has become
the flashpoint animal rights issue of our time.
With an eruption expected
at any moment,
the US Senate has convened
a special committee
to answer a grave,
moral question.
Do dinosaurs deserve
the same protections given to other endangered species
or should they be left to die?
MALCOLM: I think
that we should allow
our magnificent
and glorious dinosaurs
to be taken out by the volcano.
(ALL MURMURING)
MAN: Murderer.
SHERWOOD: Silence, please.
As deeply sad as that would be,
we altered the course
of natural history.
This is a correction.
Are you suggesting the Almighty is taking
matters in his own hands?
Senator, with all due respect,
God's not part of the equation, no.
What I mean is that,
in the last century,
we amassed landmark
technological power
and we've consistently proven ourselves
incapable of handling that power.
Eighty years ago, who could've
predicted nuclear proliferation?
But then there it was.
And now we've got genetic power,
so how long is it gonna take for
that to spread around the globe
and what's gonna be
done with it?
It ain't gonna stop with the
de-extinction of the dinosaurs.
I'm not sure I know
what you're talking about.
(SIGHS) I'm talking
about man-made,
cataclysmic change.
What kind of change?
Change is like death.
You don't know what it looks like
until you're standing at the gates.
(ELEVATOR CLANGING)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
WOMAN: Yes, absolutely!
MAN: We would love to have a
photo op with the senator.
As a matter of fact, I do have the
dinosaurs' best interests in mind.
I'm a paleo-veterinarian.
DELGADO: (ON PHONE)
Is that a real thing?
That's a real thing.
No, I haven't seen one
with my own eyes.
You know, not everyone can afford
to spend their life savings...
(WHISPERS) Claire!
Oh, uh...
Hello. Hello, um...
(WHISPERS)
Congresswoman Delgado.
I'm Claire. I'm the lead
organizer here.
Of course, but if I could just
get a moment of your time?
Great. Thank you. Um...
So, our mission here at the
Dinosaur Protection Group
is to secure federal funding
for a safe, natural...
That was, like, 40 seconds.
You're getting better.
You gotta stop letting
your mom shop for you.
You don't need to insult me every
time someone pisses you off.
Dude, I'm a doctor,
not a telemarketer.
What is your job again?
You plug in cords, right?
It's actually more important
than it sounds.
- Can I ask you a question?
- DELGADO: Go on.
- Do you have kids?
- girls.
Okay. So, your kids,
an entire generation,
has grown up in a world
where dinosaurs
are living and breathing.
But soon, they're gonna have
to watch them go extinct.
Or not.
If people like you
make a difference.
Set up a meeting with my
office after the hearing.
(SIGHS) Great.
ZIA: Yes!
NEWS ANCHOR: We now go live
to the Capitol...
- Claire, it's on.
- MAN: Turn it up.
NEWS ANCHOR: ...the US government
will take preventative action
to protect the dinosaurs
on Isla Nublar.
After thorough deliberations,
the committee has resolved not to
recommend any legislative action
regarding the de-extinct
creatures on Isla Nublar.
This is an act of God.
And while, of course, we feel
great sympathy for these animals,
we cannot condone
government involvement
on what amounts to
a privately-owned venture.
(TV TURNS OFF)
They're all gonna die
and no one cares.
FRANKLIN: We do.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(SIGHS)
Give me one second.
Let's get back to work.
Okay, everyone, come on.
Hello? (SIGHS)
WOMAN: (ON PHONE)
May I speak with Ms. Dearing?
Yes, this is Claire Dearing.
Good morning, I'm calling from Mr.
Benjamin Lockwood's estate.
Would you mind holding
for a second?
Yes, of course I'll hold.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Ms. Dearing, you're early.
Would you like to step in?
Thank you.
I will inform Mr. Mills
that you've arrived.
MILLS: John Alfred Hammond,
the father of Jurassic Park.
But of course you knew that.
Hello, Claire. I'm Eli Mills.
I work for Ben Lockwood.
We actually met once,
seven, eight years ago,
- and you don't remember.
- Of course I remember.
- Haven't you run his foundation since...
- Since college, yeah.
- You remember?
- Yes.
- Wow. Cool.
- (CHUCKLES)
He wanted someone young and
idealistic to spend his fortune
and I used to be both.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Follow me.
Let me give you
a bit of history.
This is where it all began.
Before the island,
Sorna, Jurassic Park, all of it.
Hammond and Lockwood built a
custom lab in the sub-basement,
extracted the first DNA from
amber right beneath our feet.
Oh, my goodness.
What they did here
was a miracle.
I still believe that.
So do I, Claire.
So do I.
And I still believe it matters
what happens to those animals.
There is something Mr. Lockwood would
very much like you to do, Claire.
You can call it a favor
for an old friend.
We have a piece of land.
A sanctuary protected
by natural barriers,
fully self-sustaining.
A new home where the dinosaurs
will be secure and free.
CLAIRE: You're gonna
get them out?
You're gonna save them?
BENJAMIN: No, Ms. Dearing.
I'm going to save us.
We could both use a touch
of redemption, couldn't we?
Lovely to see you again.
And you, Mr. Lockwood.
BENJAMIN: This was all
John Hammond's dream.
To let these creatures
live in peace.
So, we have created sanctuary.
No fences. No cages.
No tourists.
Just as Mother Nature intended.
John said it best.
"These creatures
don't need our protection.
"They need our absence."
When we were young,
we both shared this passion,
John and I.
What fools we were,
trying to run before
we'd learned to walk.
As all young men do, I suppose.
But we learned.
Unfortunately, in the end,
it drove us apart.
Life teaches us
some very hard lessons,
doesn't it, Claire?
Yes.
- Hmm?
- Sir Benjamin.
Ah.
My bloody medicines.
Will you excuse me, Claire?
Of course.
BENJAMIN: Eli here will
help you with the details.
We will save them.
What a gift
for our children.
Thank you.
Iris?
(COUGHING)
Does he have children? I thought I saw...
Was there a little girl?
He has a grandchild.
His daughter died
in a car accident.
That's awful.
Yeah, I know, but they're very close.
Really close.
So, what do you need from me?
MILLS: There was a tracking
system in place at your park.
Radio-frequency ID chips
in each dinosaur.
- I remember.
- Right.
MILLS: So, if we could
access that system,
our ability to locate and
capture those animals safely
would increase tenfold.
We need your handprint
to access the system,
but what I really need, Claire,
is you.
Moving endangered species
isn't exactly legal,
but it's the right thing to do.
No one knows this park
as well as you do
and we need that expertise.
- How many can you save?
- Eleven species. For sure.
I mean, more if we can,
but time is against us.
I'm afraid there is
one animal in particular
that poses a real challenge
for us.
- Blue.
- I didn't know she had a name,
but Blue is potentially
the second-most intelligent
piece of life on this planet
and she's the last of her kind.
She must be preserved.
She can pick up your scent a mile off.
You'll never capture her.
Well, we thought you might
know someone who could help.
Maybe you could convince him.
(EXHALES)
(HAMMERING)
OWEN: (SINGING) Oh, Time, she is
a freight train chugging
Oh, stalling Time is, too
When the light
at the end of the tunnel
Is growing small behind you
Hey, Owen.
I still love you in the morning
Owen!
Oh, boy.
Hi.
Back for more, huh?
Can I buy you a beer?
Did you bring them, or do we
gotta, like, go somewhere?
- (MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
- (CLAIRE LAUGHING)
I'm sorry.
Seriously?
I can't believe you think
that you left me!
Replay the conversation
in your head, all right?
You said, "You wanna go live
in your van, like a bum?
"Go ahead, Owen."
And I said, "Okay."
So, how is that you leaving me?
Because I left. I left you.
You left because I told you to.
And then, I left.
Because you didn't wanna live in
a van on the side of the road.
- No. No, no, no.
- Remember?
Because you wouldn't let me drive
the damn van for five minutes.
I'm chivalrous.
What can I do?
You are so stubborn.
Well, look at you now.
You're saving the world.
I'm trying, at least.
You can't just run away
from everything, Owen.
So, you're what...
Dating an accountant now?
An insurance actuary?
Your skin looks nice.
Dermatologist?
Owen...
- Does he check you for moles?
- Stop.
A ventriloquist?
This is not
why we're here, okay?
Yeah, I know why we're here.
Lockwood's little
flunky called me.
Rescue op.
Save the dinosaurs from an
island that's about to explode.
- What could go wrong?
- I'm going.
- Don't.
- I don't have a choice.
What? Of course
you have a choice.
So, what, I should just
build my own cabin,
play pool, and drink beer
all day
while these dinosaurs
go extinct?
Yeah. I like pool.
Blue is alive.
Jesus, Claire!
You raised her, Owen.
You spent years of your life
working with her.
You're just gonna let her die?
Well, yeah.
Come on, you're a better man
than you think you are.
You should write
fortune cookies.
Forget it...
There's a charter flight
leaving tomorrow morning.
You're on the manifest.
I just wanted to let you know.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DINOSAURS SCREECHING)
OWEN: (ON VIDEO) All right,
chow time, chow time.
Whoa, whoa.
Back up. Back off.
Hey, hey, hey. Jeez.
Take it easy. Echo.
Jeez, there's plenty of food.
God, you guys been
eating sugar or something?
You're hyper today.
Okay, okay. Back up.
Thank you, Blue.
(SCREECHING)
Whoa, whoa.
(CHITTERING)
Did you get that?
Relax. You're more likely to die
riding on a horse than in a plane.
No, I'm not, because
I won't get on a horse.
My chances are zero.
ZIA: Planes are
the safest way to travel.
FRANKLIN: You call this a plane? My
cousin has a drone bigger than this.
(FRANKLIN AND ZIA
ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- Owen!
ZIA: Franklin, you wiener,
get on the plane.
Didn't think you were
gonna ever show up.
Oh, um...
This is Zia Rodriguez.
Zia.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Yeah, real good. How are you?
Good.
Franklin Webb.
Systems analyst.
Nervous flyer?
Would you ride a thousand-pound horse
that's been abused all its life?
I rode my motorcycle through the
jungle with a pack of raptors.
We're not compatible.
(WHIRRING)
IRIS: Maisie?
You're always hiding from me.
This is not my job, looking for you.
Maisie!
(SIGHS)
Come out!
(RUSTLING)
Boo!
- You silly sausage.
- (LAUGHING)
You'll be the death of me.
You know, one day,
my heart might really stop.
Then what would you do?
Go and live in the forest
with the lions?
There are no lions
in the forest.
Your grandfather's
been asking for you.
- Really?
- Mmm.
So, you go see your grandfather, and
then you go straight to your bath.
- I don't want a bath.
- What?
Queen's English, girl.
- (IN BRITISH ACCENT) Bath.
- Bath.
Bath, not "bath,"
you're not a wild animal.
- (ROARS)
- (YELPS) Stop.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hi, Grandpa.
Ah, there you are.
Come over and sit by me.
I've missed you.
I was on safari
all the way through the Cretaceous
to the Jurassic in one day.
Oh, my. What'd you see?
Mostly herbivores.
There was one T. Rex, though.
Casualties, of course.
Iris included.
She jumped out of her skin.
(CHUCKLING)
You have your mother's wicked sense of humor.
Do I look like her?
Oh, yes.
You could be her mirror image.
Did my mother
ever visit the park?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Once, a long time ago.
She would've saved them,
too, you know.
She would have saved them all.
(ANIMALS CALLING)
MAN: That's two klicks
past the LZ.
WHEATLEY: Claire.
Ken Wheatley. Welcome back.
Quite an operation
you've got going on here.
Mr. Lockwood takes his humanitarian
efforts very seriously.
Where's the, uh,
raptor wrangler?
Animal behaviorist.
- Owen Grady.
- Hey, Owen. Ken Wheatley.
And you are
the Great White Hunter?
(LAUGHING)
I guess. I'm the
expedition facilitator.
Oh, God! It's hot.
It's about to get
a whole lot hotter.
Keep it moving!
You're all clear!
Go! Go! You've got
the green light!
This way!
Let's go! Let's go! Keep it moving!
Hold it! Hold up!
(ALARM BLARING)
Need some bug spray?
Bug spray?
The T. Rex would be dead
by now, right?
ZIA: No, it's impossible to know
the max lifespan of a clone
in a completely different
environment.
Take a caveman that
would've lived 20 years.
Feed him prime meals,
give him health care,
he's gonna live
five times as long.
So, she'd be dead by now? Right?
(ALARM BLARING)
WHEATLEY: Bad memories?
Some were good.
(CHITTERS)
What was that?
(DISTANT RUMBLING)
Is it the T. Rex?
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
I have to see this.
Hey! Miss? Miss!
This area is not secured.
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(DINOSAUR BELLOWING)
(BELLOWING)
ZIA: Look at that.
Never thought
I'd see one in real life.
She's beautiful.
(BELLOWING)
Can we...
Okay, let's go.
(GRUNTS)
FRANKLIN: Okay. Okay.
- Okay, main system...
- (COMPUTER BEEPING)
And turn on the controls.
(RUMBLING)
It should be working.
- WHEATLEY: Come on, tiger. Do you know what you're doing?
- (BEEPING)
After you, tiger.
ZIA: Are we sure these biometric
chips are still transmitting?
Battery would be dead by now.
CLAIRE: The dinosaur
is the battery.
They're powered by
body heat and movement.
(SNAPS FINGERS) Hand.
How much longer until...
(SYSTEMS POWERING UP)
FRANKLIN; I'm in.
There's a large concentration
on the east dock.
That's our boat.
We've already captured a bunch of them.
Without the tracking system?
The big herbivores
are easy to find.
Can you isolate that raptor?
- I need a species code.
- D-9.
There she is.
I'm gonna need
to borrow your truck.
I'm coming with you.
We don't know what kind of
condition she might be in.
Miss, things could get
hairy out there.
These are powerful sedatives.
One too many,
and she could have respiratory failure.
Also, I'm not as soft and witless
as your comment implies.
Let's go, beefcake.
Oh, Owen?
Be careful, okay?
If I don't make it back,
remember, you're the one
who made me come.
I'll be all right.
- (VEHICLES APPROACHING)
- (CHITTERING)
(BEEPING)
OWEN: We're not going to get any
closer to her in this thing.
- We should stop here.
- Hold up.
Load out, look alive,
stay alive.
- We got your back, brother.
- Yeah.
OWEN: (ON RADIO) Claire, I'm going to
have to track her alone.
I'll need you to be my eyes
if she runs. Copy?
Copy that.
(BEEPING)
(DISTANT RUMBLING)
(DISTANT SCREECHING)
(RUMBLING CONTINUES)
(SCREECHING)
Wheatley, I'm on fresh sign.
Wait for my signal.
(RUMBLING CONTINUES)
(RUSTLING)
There you are.
(SCREECHING)
(ROARING)
Hey, girl, you miss me?
Easy. Hey!
- (HISSING)
- Hey.
I brought you something.
(GROWLING)
Here you go.
That's right.
(GROWLING)
Okay.
- Hey!
- (DEVICE CLICKING)
(ROARING)
You know me.
- (CLICKER CLICKING)
- Eyes on me.
Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah.
You know me.
That's right.
Hold your... (GRUNTS)
(SCREECHING)
I told you to wait
for my signal.
(GUNS COCKING)
(SCREECHING)
Back your men up
right now. (PANTING)
- (ROARS)
- (GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
No, wait! No, no!
No, don't shoot her!
(SCREAMING)
(SCREECHING)
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
Wheatley, you son of a bitch!
(BLOWS AIR)
Owen!
What are you doing?
(PANTING)
You shoot me
and that animal dies.
I think we have
the drop on you, sweetheart.
She's losing blood.
And if I don't treat her,
she'll never make it
back to camp.
(EXHALES)
How about this?
That animal dies, I shoot you.
You're gonna take care of her.
Let's move out!
(RUMBLING)
(RUMBLING CONTINUES)
(BOTH SCREAM)
MAN: Cut the cord and let's go!
Let's get out of here!
(DOOR BEEPING)
No, no, no! Wait!
Wait, are they protecting us?
What's going on?
(BEEPING)
I don't think so.
- (DISTANT EXPLOSION)
- (FRANKLIN YELLS)
Why am I here?
WHEATLEY: Hey, Mills, we got her done.
Mission accomplished.
(LAUGHING)
Just in the nick of time.
Wheatley, what the hell
is going on there?
We're a day
behind schedule already.
WHEATLEY: I want that money
in the bank by the time I get back, all right?
Okay, good. Listen to me.
No more delays, okay?
- If we don't get those animals...
- Mr. Mills?
Not now, Maisie.
Thank you. If we don't get
- those animals...
- Mr. Mills, are the dinosaurs safe?
I said not now!
WHEATLEY: Mills? Mills?
I'm sorry, honey.
This is an important call.
If you go up to the library, I'll
meet you up there in a few minutes.
- Okay.
I'll tell you all about it,
I promise.
- Okay.
Wheatley, you get
those animals here now!
I want that bonus.
We got the blue one.
MILLS: Bring her to me first!
WHEATLEY: All right.
(RUMBLING)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(INSECTS BUZZING)
(GROWLING)
(OWEN GROANING)
(STRAINING)
(ROARING)
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
(STRAINING)
(GRUNTS)
No! (GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
Hello, can anyone hear me?
Hello?
Hello, is anybody there?
- Can anybody copy?
- (BEEPING)
I'm... I'm trying everything.
It's jammed.
"Just take the job, son,
build your people skills."
Yeah, thanks, Dad.
(BEEPING)
- That's it.
- (DOOR OPENS)
(ALARM BLARING)
Proximity alert.
Something's coming.
Where does that tunnel lead?
Well, it connects
to the rest of the...
(DISTANT GROWLING)
Park.
FRANKLIN: It's the T. Rex,
it's the T. Rex! Claire, it's the T. Rex.
It's the T. Rex,
it's the T. Rex.
Will you stop?
It's not the T. Rex!
(SIGHS) Probably.
"Probably"?
(GASPS)
Lava! Lava! Lava! Lava!
Deep breaths, Franklin.
- (GROWLING)
- (GASPS)
(ROARING)
(WHIMPERING)
(HIGH-PITCHED SCREAMING)
See? Not a T. Rex!
How is this better?
(ROARING)
Claire, what do we do?
What do we do?
It's stuck!
Chair!
(GRUNTING)
CLAIRE: Come on! Let's go!
Come on, Franklin!
We made it! Yeah!
- (ROARS)
- (SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
- FRANKLIN: Come on, come on, come on!
- (ROARING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Yes, yes, go, go!
Go, go!
(BOTH PANTING)
Claire!
Holy...
(EXPLOSIONS)
OWEN: Run!
Run!
(DINOSAURS SCREECHING)
(BOTH GASP)
Run!
(SCREECHING)
Oh, my God!
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(BOTH SCREAM)
OWEN: Go! Go!
- Okay.
- We're okay.
- Buckle up.
- It's okay.
Get in!
(ROARING)
(GROWLING)
(GASPING)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
Owen!
(PANTING)
- (ROARS)
- (GRUNTS)
(SCREECHING)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(DINOSAURS ROARING)
CLAIRE: We gotta get out.
FRANKLIN: We just fell
from the cliff. We're alive.
We're alive!
Franklin, move!
No, no, no!
No. Claire, we're gonna sink!
Water's leaking!
CLAIRE: (GASPS) Oh, God.
We need to get out!
Franklin, watch out!
(SCREAMS)
I wanna go home!
Owen. Owen!
FRANKLIN: Owen?
CLAIRE: Owen. Okay.
Move! Move!
No! No, no, no!
Push!
(GRUNTING)
Owen! No.
FRANKLIN: Where's he going?
CLAIRE: Okay,
don't panic. Don't panic.
FRANKLIN: We're running out of air.
We're not gonna make it.
We are. We are.
Take a deep breath.
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING)
(RUMBLING)
(COUGHING)
(ALL GASPING)
Where is Zia?
OWEN: It was a double-cross.
They took her, she must be with Blue.
Hey! Can you still track them?
Not anymore.
It was a lie.
It was a lie. Bastards!
It was all a lie!
(AIRPLANE PASSING OVERHEAD)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
(ROARING)
Not all of it.
(SHIP HORN BLARING)
WHEATLEY: Let's move it!
Move! Move!
Anything of value,
I want on that boat!
- How you doing?
- MAN: The bolt won't give!
Just button it up,
and we'll tow it on! Let's go!
- (ROARING)
- MAN 1: Lock it up! Move it out!
- MAN 2: Come on, now.
- (ROARING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(DINOSAURS SCREECHING)
Hey! Hey, hey, hey!
Hang on! Wait up!
Stop that truck! Stop it!
Hey, sweetheart.
Hello, hello.
- (GRUNTS)
- (ROARING)
Beautiful.
You're gonna feel that
when you wake up.
ZIA: Hey, put your weapon down!
You got the barrel pointed
right at her head!
OWEN: They have Zia.
They're loading out.
If they already had the dinosaurs,
why did they need us?
They needed the tracking
system to capture Blue.
OWEN: There she is.
She don't look good.
(RUMBLING)
We need to get on that boat.
The rock's good.
We're safe on the rock.
It's the boat
or the lava, Franklin.
All right, boat's good.
I'm all about the boat.
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
Go, go, get on the boat!
Get on the boat, now! Go, go!
- MAN 1: Move it, move it!
- MAN 2: Go, go, go!
OWEN: Get that truck!
(SHIP HORN BLARING)
(ALL SCREAM)
(GRUNTING)
- Franklin!
- Hey, get that truck going!
Okay.
- You okay?
- Am I dead?
Not yet, kid.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Come on!
Come on. Give me
your hand! Reach!
Come on, reach!
(GASPS)
Hold on!
(ENGINE REVS)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(YELLING)
(PANTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(BELL RINGING)
(CHATTER CONTINUES)
(DINOSAURS BELLOWING)
(GASPING)
(BELLOWING)
(CONTINUES BELLOWING)
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(DOORS CLOSING)
(BEEPING)
(INTERCOM BEEPS)
IRIS: Mr. Mills?
Your visitor's waiting.
(SIGHS)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
MILLS: Mr. Eversoll.
It's a pleasure to meet you in person after all this time.
How are you?
- Excuse me.
- Yeah?
Where are the dinosaurs?
The dinosaurs are, uh, are en route.
Oh, so, am I supposed
to sell these ones?
You don't need to worry, okay?
They will be here soon.
I don't really work
with amateurs,
so I'm gonna contact my buyers
and call this off.
They will be here tomorrow,
and your buyers won't be disappointed.
- (CELL PHONE DIALING)
- Trust me, whatever their interest,
agricultural, industrial,
sport hunting,
we will have something
to suit them.
Eleven species,
each with unique
biopharmaceutical properties.
I estimate four million
per species.
Four million is a slow
Tuesday where I'm from.
You're wasting my time.
You ever made 100 million
on a Tuesday?
- (LAUGHING)
- Huh?
All this is in the past.
I wanna talk to you
about the future.
I'll give you 10 minutes.
The whole point of selling
the Isla Nublar dinosaurs
is to finance our future
operations here.
It's, uh, seed money.
Call it an overture
to something much more ambitious.
EVERSOLL: Yeah, and more
lucrative, I guess.
MILLS: Right, we've reactivated
the old facilities,
updated the technology,
and imported the best geneticists
from around the world.
This operation has been
many years in the planning.
Genetic power is
an uncharted frontier.
The potential for growth
is more than you can fathom.
This way, please.
If the entire run
of our sorry history
has taught us
one irrevocable lesson,
it's that man is inevitably
drawn to war
and is willing to use any
means necessary to win it.
You're gonna weaponize them?
We've been using animals
in combat for centuries.
Horses, elephants.
The Soviets used
disease-bearing rats
against the Germans
at Stalingrad.
Yes, yes.
Our geneticists have created
a direct descendant
of Henry Wu's masterpiece,
the animal that took down
Jurassic World.
Indominus Rex.
Her DNA, retrieved from the island
way before its destruction,
forms the architecture
of a completely new creature.
Every bone and muscle designed
for hunting and killing.
And thanks
to Owen Grady's research,
it follows human command.
We call it the lndoraptor.
(DOOR CREAKING)
MAISIE: (WHISPERS) Grandpa?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Grandpa?
(VENTILATOR HISSING)
- (GRUNTS SOFTLY)
- (GASPS) Grandpa.
Maisie, what are you doing up?
There was a man here
today with Mr. Mills.
It was probably just some business
about the sanctuary. That's all.
I heard them talking.
They're going to sell
the dinosaurs.
- They're bringing them here.
- Oh. Huh.
I'm sure you misunderstood.
I know what I heard, Grandpa.
Maisie, it's way past
your bedtime.
Let's talk about this
in the morning.
- But...
- Maisie,
I'll find out tomorrow.
Go to bed.
Good night.
Good night, my heart.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(DINOSAURS BELLOWING)
- (DINOSAUR ROARS)
- (GASPS) Jesus.
(GROANING)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
- (RUMBLING)
- (SCREECHING)
It's okay, Blue,
just a little longer.
Oh, my God!
You guys are alive!
OWEN: Oh, look what
they've done to her.
Who are these assholes?
Animal traffickers.
Look how they're treating them.
They're not gonna take them to a sanctuary,
they're gonna sell them.
Not Blue, they need her
for something else.
Like what?
I don't know, but she's...
She's hemorrhaging,
and I don't have instruments
and they want to keep her alive.
Hey.
(SHUSHING)
- You're all right, you're all right.
- ZIA: Claire, come here.
Come on.
Put your hand here.
Steady pressure.
- (SCREECHES)
- Hey, hey, hey.
Watch out.
I can't take the bullet out without
a transfusion from another animal.
Which one of you knows
how to find a vein?
Oh! I did a blood drive
for the Red Cross.
Great. Okay.
Franklin, take over for Claire.
No, no, no.
Franklin, now!
- Steady pressure.
- (BLUE GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Is it in my mouth?
- Did it get in my mouth?
- Mmm-mmm.
- You sure?
- You're good.
FRANKLIN: I can feel it
on my face.
All of the animals
should be sedated.
Look for any kind of Tetanuran,
their blood type
should be close enough.
Look for carnivores with two or three fingers.
No more than three.
I think there's one on board.
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(INSECTS BUZZING)
You gotta be kidding me.
(BREATHING LOUDLY)
(GASPS)
She's tranqued.
Okay, okay. Okay,
I got it. Come on.
Okay. (EXHALES)
(GASPS)
Oh, no. Are you okay?
(STRAINED)
I'm okay.
Come on.
- You're gonna have to do it.
- I can't.
The skin is too thick.
I have to use both my hands
to put pressure on the vein.
You gotta do it.
I... I can't...
I can't reach.
You're gonna have to
climb up there.
Oh, I'm not... (SCOFFS)
No, no. I'm not gonna
climb up there.
You'll be okay.
It's like riding a bull.
"Riding a bull"?
I didn't grow up at a rodeo
- or wherever you came from.
- She's asleep now.
I can't say that she's gonna
be asleep a minute from now, so get up.
Okay, fine.
Oh, my God, she stinks.
- (GRUNTS)
- Gently. Gently.
No, no, no.
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(CHUCKLING)
Good job.
You're making this
look totally normal.
(CHUCKLES)
You're gonna have to jam it in there,
it's really thick skin.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay. One, two...
- One, two...
- Stab!
- (SNARLS)
Owen!
(GROANS)
It's working.
(MEN LAUGHING)
MAN 1: The pee is silent.
MAN 2: That door is open.
MAN 3: I got it.
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(ROARING)
CLAIRE: The bars!
The bars, Owen.
Owen, I can get
through there. Come on.
(ROARING)
(GRUNTS)
Jump, Owen!
(ROARING)
(METAL SCRAPING)
CLAIRE: Owen, jump. Now!
(PANTING)
- (ROARING CONTINUES)
- (BOTH PANTING)
Did you see that?
Uh-huh.
Please tell me
you got the blood.
(DOOR OPENS)
(BEEPING)
(WHIRRING)
(HEART BEATING)
(MACHINES BEEPING)
(CHITTERING)
OWEN: This is Delta.
She's one of the hold over theropods,
one of the survivors
from the second group.
Now, watch this.
I show any sign of weakness
whatsoever...
(WHIMPERING)
- (SCREECHING)
- (GASPS)
See that?
Day 176. Blue is showing
unprecedented levels of compliance.
Here I am with Blue.
She's a theropod
from the new group.
I show signs of weakness...
(WHIMPERING)
(PURRING)
Hey.
I'm okay.
(CHUCKLES)
She's pretty extraordinary.
(BLUE BREATHING RAPIDLY)
(MACHINES BEEPING)
OWEN: Blue, displaying levels
of interest, concern,
hyper-intelligence,
cognitive bonding.
See that?
She's tilting her head,
she's craning forward.
Increased eye movement.
She's curious.
She's showing empathy.
ZIA: Okay, I'm gonna make an incision
in her leg to remove the bullet.
(SCREECHING)
It's a lot of muscle tissue.
(BLUE GROANING)
(SHUSHING)
- (CHITTERING)
- (LAUGHING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
She's gonna be okay.
(SOBBING)
(CHUCKLING)
OWEN: Blue is the key.
(CHITTERING)
That's it. You have Blue,
- you get these raptors to do anything.
- (DOOR OPENS)
DR. WU: You're sure she'll live?
If it dies, we have
blood samples.
DR. WU: No, no, no.
That's not good enough.
The raptor is a behavioral specimen.
We need her in good health.
I didn't shoot the damn thing.
What do you want me to do, huh?
You don't have the faintest
comprehension of what I'm doing here.
Do you understand the complexity of
creating an entirely new life form?
No, but I understand the
complexity of paying for it, okay?
All your money will have been wasted if
I don't get Blue here in good health.
To get the next iteration
under control,
it needs to form a familial bond
with a closely related genetic link.
- English, Henry.
- It needs a mother!
Blue's DNA will be part of the
next lndoraptor's makeup.
So, it will be genetically coded
to recognize her authority
and assume her traits.
Empathy. Obedience.
Everything the prototype
you have now is missing.
- Okay, so how long is this gonna take?
- (SCOFFS)
It's not a sprint, Mr. Mills.
It's a marathon.
A marathon sounds expensive.
Besides, time is running out,
and so is my patience, Henry.
DR. WU: You have to understand,
this is all uncharted territory.
A wolf, genetically,
is barely distinguishable
from a bulldog,
but within that gray area
is art.
MILLS: (GROANS)
Spare me the poetry, Henry.
Can you do it? Can you do it?
DR. WU: Yes, I can do it.
MILLS; Well, then do it.
DR. WU: Thank you.
MILLS: God,
you're a pain in the ass.
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
Hey. Hey! Maisie!
(GROWLING)
What is that? What is it?
(GRUNTS)
Keep her in there
and keep the door locked.
You want to keep her locked in?
That's exactly what I want.
Sir Benjamin needs
to see you now.
I believe it's important.
(SHIP HORN BLARING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT OVER PA)
(INHALES)
MAN: (ON PA) All crew, prepare for docking.
All crew, prepare for docking.
MAN 1: Let's move it, boys.
WHEATLEY: Jeez! Will somebody shut that thing up?
It sounds like my ex-wife.
We're here.
Where?
- (DOOR OPENS)
- WHEATLEY: Just get in your truck and let's go.
- OWEN: Move. Move!
- Move, move, move!
You got a heartbeat?
Yeah. Do you?
I need blood samples.
I'm not here to help you
reset the food chain,
so take your own damn samples.
(EXHALES)
What a nasty woman.
Go, go, now, now. Go.
MAN: (ON PA) Attention, all crew.
Attention, all crew.
Drivers, get to your vehicles.
Hey!
- What the hell is going on?
- I was...
I needed an extra pair
of hands. He volunteered.
- Are you deck crew?
- Aye, aye.
We're loading out.
Follow me.
Uh, does that mean we're
leaving the ship right now?
That is what “loading out" means.
Now get moving. Come on, follow me.
- Come on, kid. There's lots to do.
- Shit!
- CLAIRE: Oh, no. He's not gonna make it.
- Get a move on. Come on.
- Move it! Come on. Move!
- CLAIRE: We have to help him.
Stay here, I'll get him.
(TRUCK ENGINE STARTS)
There's no time.
Let's go.
MAN 1: I got five. I'm on it.
MAN 2: Why is this truck
still here?
MAN 3: Good to go!
MAN 4: Roll out!
Where are they taking them?
- We're about to find out.
- MAN 5: Let's go!
Ready to roll!
MAN 6: Keep it coming!
MAN 7: Move it out!
Keep it rolling!
WHEATLEY: Good to go!
ZIA: Come on, girl.
- (SNARLING)
- (GASPS)
Yes!
This is Lockwood's estate.
He must have one big-ass garage.
(RADIO BEEPS)
MAN 1: Let's go! We want
this offloaded in 10 mikes!
MAN 2: Big door's open.
(ROARING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(BLEATING)
BENJAMIN: Did you really think
you could get away with it?
In my own house.
You entrusted me
to guide your fortune
into the future.
- I have done that.
- Damn you!
Pick up that phone.
I want you to call the police.
It'll be easier
if the story comes from you.
As you say, sir.
You know, I've been thinking,
John Hammond was right.
(BEEPS)
It was an unholy thing
that you did.
I'm not the only guilty one
here, am I, sir?
Hey.
We hit that town, we call the
cavalry, shut this down.
Whoo. Hello.
You should have stayed
on the island.
Better odds.
- (GUNS COCKING)
- (GASPS)
MILLS: Hi, Claire.
I just wanted to come
and apologize.
I didn't wanna bring you
into any of this,
but it was the only way
that we could get the raptor.
We needed it.
Come on.
(CLAIRE EXHALES HEAVILY)
So, what? This is it?
I mean, you're a smart guy,
you could have
started a foundation,
cured cancer,
but instead you,
what?
Sell endangered species?
I saved these animals.
You betrayed a dying man
for money.
Claire, I admire your idealism,
but we both exploited
these animals.
At least I have the integrity
to admit it.
I never, ever did anything
remotely illegal.
You authorized the creation
of the lndominus Rex.
You exploited a living
thing in a cage for money.
How is that different? Huh?
And you, the man who proved
raptors can follow orders.
You never thought about the
applications of your research, Owen?
How many millions a trained
predator might be worth?
You two,
you're the parents
of the new world.
- (GROANS)
- Hey! Let him go.
- Owen.
- I think I'll break it.
Let him go.
(GROANING)
Claire, I just want...
(GROANS)
(CHUCKLING)
Say, how we gonna end this?
Well, as far as everybody else is
concerned, they burned up on the island.
MAN 1: (ON RADIO) Buyers on approach.
Looks like a full house.
MAN 2: Roger that.
- EVERSOLL: Good evening.
- MILLS: Good evening.
- Welcome, gentlemen.
- EVERSOLL: Good evening.
MILLS: Welcome.
And these guys are development
rep for Aldaris Pharmaceuticals.
Great.
The guy in the beard is a
proxy for Gregor Adlrich,
a Slovenian arms dealer.
Equine buyers.
Rand Magnus, an oil magnate
from Houston.
MILLS: What's their interest?
EVERSOLL: Strictly personal.
His kid wants
a baby Triceratops.
Glenn, how's Janet?
GLENN: She's doing fine, thanks.
EVERSOLL: (CHUCKLES)
Straight ahead, Glenn.
(CONVERSING IN RUSSIAN)
(IN ENGLISH) Well, he only wants
carnivores. Two of them.
Looks like Lookwood's gonna
have a very good night.
Will he be joining us?
MILLS: Um...
That's very unlikely.
(WHISPERS) Grandpa?
Grandpa?
Grandpa, wake up.
Grandpa!
(SOBBING)
Grandpa, wake up. Wake up.
- (MONITOR FLATLINING)
- MILLS: Iris!
Iris!
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
It's over.
What a tragedy.
I suppose now he's gone,
you'll be looking
for another situation.
No.
Maisie needs me.
MILLS: I'm her guardian now.
What she needs
is no longer your concern.
IRIS: You don't understand her
the way I do.
MILLS: I understand her value.
But I raised her.
I raised both of them.
- Please, Mr. Mills.
- MILLS: Goodbye, Iris.
(CREAKING)
(DINOSAUR ROARING IN DISTANCE)
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
Do you remember the first time
you saw a dinosaur?
First time you see them,
it's like
a miracle.
You read about them in books,
you see the bones in museums,
but you don't really believe it.
They're like myths.
And then you see
that first one alive.
This is not your fault.
But it is.
No.
This one's on me.
I showed them the way.
Listen.
You and I are gonna have plenty
of time to talk about this later.
If there is a later.
Yes, there is.
I got a cabin to finish.
(THUD)
(DINOSAUR GRUNTING)
CLAIRE: What is that?
Well, look who just woke up.
(WHISTLES) Go.
(ROARING)
(THUD)
We're getting out of here.
Welcome, ladies, gentlemen,
to this extraordinary evening.
Let's dive right in
with lot number one,
the Ankylosaurus.
- (ALL GASP)
- (GROWLS)
She's a herbivorous quadruped,
late Cretaceous.
This is one of the largest
armored dinosaurs,
known by paleontologists
as a living tank.
(ROARING)
- (WHISTLES)
- (DINOSAUR GROWLS)
- (GASPS)
- (THUD)
What are you doing?
Escaping.
You sure about this?
Nope.
- (WHISTLES)
- (THUD)
I have $4 million, anyone five?
- BUYER 1: Five.
- $5 million.
$5 million. Do I hear six?
- BUYER 2: $6 million.
- EVERSOLL: $6 million, thank you.
Any increase on six?
Seven. $7 million.
$8 million.
Nine million on the phones.
Do I hear 10 million?
- 10 million? 10 million.
- 10.
$10 million! Once, twice...
Sold!
To the gentleman from Indonesia.
Congratulations, sir.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
- (WHISTLES)
- (THUD)
Lot number two,
ladies and gentlemen.
A juvenile Allosaurus.
(ROARING)
(CHUCKLES) A fierce
and an aggressive predator.
(ROARS)
- (WHISTLES)
- (GROWLS)
Sold!
(OWEN WHISTLES)
Sold.
Wonderful.
- Wonderful bidding.
- (ROARS)
(BELLOWING)
MAN 1: Come on. You're good.
Let's go.
- MAN 2: Move it out.
- MAN 3: Here we go.
MAN 4: Bring it on back. Let's go.
(WHISTLES)
CLAIRE: Okay.
Hey! Hey, you.
Look at me! Look at me!
Hey!
Come with me.
Come with me!
Okay, there you go.
(WHISTLES)
- (CLANGS)
- (GROANING)
You're welcome.
(CLATTERING)
(MAISIE WHIMPERING)
CLAIRE: Hey, wait!
Please, please wait.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(WHISPERING)
That's Lockwood's granddaughter.
Hey. Hey, kid. You wanna
come down out of there?
- Uh...
Do you remember me?
Yeah?
My name is Claire.
What's yours?
Maisie.
Maisie Lockwood.
This is my friend, Owen.
I saw you
with the Velociraptors.
Blue.
Oh. Oh, yeah?
Uh...
You like dinosaurs?
So do I.
Tell you what,
you come on down from there,
I'll tell you everything
you need to know about Blue.
That sound all right?
All right, yeah.
Come on down.
CLAIRE: Sweetie,
we need some help
finding your grandfather.
Can you take us to him?
(SNIFFLES) No.
You made it down here
all by yourself, huh?
Brave kid.
Looks like you could
use a friend.
He's gone.
Listen, I'll tell you what,
we were just about to go
and find our friends
and then get
the heck out of here.
You wanna come with us?
CLAIRE: We could use
a friend, too.
- BUYER: (IN DISTANCE) 19.5!
- EVERSOLL: (IN DISTANCE) 19.5.
Do I hear 20?
Do I hear 20? 20? Thank you.
Thank you.
20. Do I hear...
$21 million!
21 million...
- (GAVEL BANGS)
- Sold!
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
that we are halfway through
the evening...
(GROWLING)
...we 'd like to offer
a special treat to our
discriminating buyers.
This evening we will preview
a new asset that
we've been developing.
A creature of the future
made from pieces of the past.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please be warned,
this is the perfect blend of the
two most dangerous creatures
that have ever walked the earth.
We call it the lndoraptor.
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
- (ALL GASPING)
The perfect weapon for the modern age.
Built for combat.
With tactical responses more
acute than any human soldier.
What is that thing?
- (ROARING)
- (ALL EXCLAIMING)
MAISIE: They made it.
Mr. Mills and the other man.
What man?
MAISIE: Him.
EVERSOLL: Designed
by Mr. Henry Wu
with an intelligence quotient
comparable to the Velociraptor.
Biospecs include
a heightened sense of smell
and trained to respond to a
pulse-coded laser targeting system,
enabling it to isolate
and track prey
in complex environments.
Voilà.
Now, first, the laser
sets the target.
- (GROWLS)
- (ALL GASP)
EVERSOLL: Once locked on,
the acoustic signal
triggers the attack.
- (HIGH-PITCHED TRILLING)
- (ROARING)
(ALL GASP)
(CHUCKLES)
This animal is relentless.
Now, modifications
are still being made...
20 million!
EVERSOLL: No,
this is a prototype.
Uh, not for sale.
21!
- It is still a prototype, but...
- BUYER 1: 22!
BUYER 2: 23!
BUYER 3: 24!
$24 million.
25 million!
Do I hear 26?
OWEN: That thing
can't leave this building.
BUYER 4: 26!
- Any advance on 26?
- 27!
$27 million from the back.
What are you doing?
This animal is not for sale.
If you wanna create an addict,
you have to give them a taste.
He's a prototype.
This prototype is worth
$28 million right now.
Relax, we'll make some more.
So will they.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(GROWLING)
(CLATTERING)
Hey, buddy.
You thinking what I'm thinking?
EVERSOLL: Once. Twice.
- Sold to the Russian friend.
- (ALL APPLAUDING)
Well done, sir.
And congratulations...
- (ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
- ...for this magnificent animal.
(GRUNTING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
MAN: Oh, God!
(GRUNTS)
Get this thing out of here!
MAN: Hey, you! Turn it out!
(ROARS)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
(GASPING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(TRUCK HORN BLARING)
WHEATLEY: Mills!
Mills, where are you?
I want my bonus!
(GROWLING)
Holy cow!
What are you?
I didn't see you on the island.
(GROWLING)
(ROARS)
(ROARING)
Oh, you're a tough guy.
Look at you.
You're some kind of hot rod
with really pretty teeth.
This'll make a perfect
centerpiece for my necklace.
(GRUNTING)
Open wide.
- (ROARS)
- (SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
(WHIMPERING)
No. No.
Please. (SOBBING)
- (ROARING)
- (SCREAMING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
Shh!
Move! Move!
Out of the way!
(SCREAMING)
(ROARS)
(BEEPING)
(SNARLING)
(SIGHS, CHUCKLES)
(ROARING)
(EVERSOLL SCREAMING)
- MILLS: Don't!
- (GUNS COCKING)
You two, you deserve each other.
Maisie, come with me.
You got your money,
now walk away.
Oh, what are you gonna do, huh?
We're gonna stop this.
All of it.
How?
What, are you gonna go back in time
before Hammond decided to play God?
You can't put it back
in the box!
- We have to try.
- It's too late.
Maisie, come.
Oh! So, you're gonna
take care of her now?
Huh?
You have no idea what she is.
What do you think drove Hammond
and Lockwood apart, huh?
Lockwood never had a grandchild.
He just wanted
his daughter back.
And he had the technology.
He created another.
He made her again.
- (MEN GROAN)
- (ROARS)
- (MAISIE SCREAMS)
- (MEN SCREAMING)
Go.
- (ROARING)
- (MEN CONTINUE SCREAMING)
- Come on!
- (BREATHING SHAKILY)
Come on.
MAN: Eggs need to go
in a sterile environment.
Where are those genome kits?
Get this to Mills.
Be very careful, it's extremely valuable.
You, I need blood samples
from the raptor.
Don't just stand there
like an idiot!
Get me 50 ccs carfentanil
and a phlebotomy kit!
It's right there! Now!
Come on. Come on.
I need this raptor's blood.
- (ROARS)
- (YELPS)
Sure, go ahead.
Where is that kit?
Okay, now listen to me.
It is better for you
to cooperate.
I'm gonna get this blood
with or without your help.
This blood's contaminated.
I designed this animal myself.
It's pure.
Every cell of her body was created
in the most controlled environment
under the most demanding
of conditions.
Yeah, but I did an intravenous
blood transfusion with a T. Rex,
so, it's a sock drawer in there.
You what?
- (GRUNTS)
- ZIA: Franklin! What are you doing?
Saving your life!
Yes!
MAN: Stop!
- Don't move.
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(GROWLING)
Now step away
from that cage. Now.
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
- (ROARS)
- Easy now.
(SCREAMING)
(PANTING)
(GAS HISSING)
(SCREAMING)
Run. Run!
(SNIFFS)
(POWERING DOWN)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(GROWLING)
(SNIFFING)
(SNARLS)
(CREAKING)
(STATIC ON RADIO)
MAN: (ON RADIO) Dave, do you copy?
Dave, you there?
Run!
(ROARING)
(SCREAMS)
(SNARLING)
(SNIFFING)
(TAPPING)
(TAPPING CONTINUES)
- (GROWLING)
- (CLATTERING)
(GRUNTING)
(ALARM BLARING)
You see that?
ZIA: That's hydrogen cyanide.
If it reaches the containment
level, it'll kill them all.
The ventilation system is down.
Can you bring it back up?
(SOFT GROWLING)
(CLAWS TAPPING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
(ROARING)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
FRANKLIN: (SIGHS)
The server's unresponsive.
I have to reboot
the whole system.
- So, reboot it.
- I'm trying.
What?
(BEEPING)
Franklin, we don't have time.
I know, I know, I know.
Okay.
(BEEPING)
(SYSTEMS POWERING UP)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (SCREAMING)
- (ROARING)
(SCREAMS)
Go. Go.
Run, run. (SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS)
(MAISIE SCREAMING)
(SNARLS)
(PANTING)
(SCREAMS)
- (ROARING)
- (SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS)
(PANTING)
(SNARLING)
(ROARING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (CLAIRE BREATHING HEAVILY)
- Hey. Here. You're okay.
Put pressure on it.
Don't look at it.
Look at me.
You have to go find her.
I can't leave you here.
Go. Go, I'll be fine.
Run!
(SNIFFING)
(ROARING)
(WHIMPERING)
- (FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
- (ROOF CREAKING)
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(TILES CLATTERING)
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(SOFT GROWLING)
(GROWLING)
- (WHIMPERING)
- (DOOR CREAKING)
(TAPPING)
(GROWLING)
(MAISIE GASPING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Maisie, stay down!
(SNARLING)
(GROWLING)
(GUN CLICKS)
(SNARLS)
(ROARING)
(MAISIE SCREAMING)
Shh!
(SNARLS)
MAISIE: Follow me.
I know a way on the other side.
Come on.
Come on!
(MAISIE SCREAMS)
This way!
(SNARLS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GROWLS)
(GLASS CRACKING)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMS)
I got you.
(STRAINING)
(METAL CLANGING)
Hey!
(SNARLS)
(GRUNTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(GROWLING)
Come on.
- (HIGH-PITCHED TRILLING)
- (ROARS)
(GROANS)
(SNARLING)
(GROWLING)
(ROARING)
(ROARS)
(SCREECHES)
(ROARING)
ZIA: What the hell?
OWEN: Hey!
FRANKLIN: Hey!
You good?
Yeah. You?
Nope.
Hey, we got a problem
downstairs.
I need you to come see this.
(GAS HISSING)
(ALARM BLARING)
(CLANGING)
(GRUNTS)
(ROARING)
(DINOSAURS ROARING)
(CLANGING CONTINUES)
They're all dying.
The blast damaged
the ventilation system.
We did everything we could.
I can open the gates from here.
Claire, be careful.
We're not on an island anymore.
- (ROARING)
- (CLANGING)
(BEEPING)
(GASPS)
(DINOSAURS ROARING)
(BELLOWING)
OWEN: Claire.
You press that button,
there is no going back.
We can't let them die.
(SHUDDERING)
(SOBBING)
(DINOSAURS ROARING)
(DOOR OPENING)
I had to.
They're alive,
like me.
(DISTANT RUMBLING)
(RUMBLING CONTINUES)
(SCREECHING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
Don't! Don't!
- (CHITTERING)
- (GASPS)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(WHIMPERING)
(AIR HISSING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(SCREAMING)
(DISTANT ROARING)
(PANTING)
(CHITTERING)
(ROARS)
(MILLS SCREAMING)
(BOTH ROAR)
(ROARING)
(GROWLING)
Hey, girl.
CLAIRE: Owen.
Shh!
It's okay, she won't hurt us.
(BLUE BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GROWLS)
Hey.
Blue, come with me.
(PURRING)
We'll take you
to a safe place, okay?
(CHITTERING)
(SCREECHES)
(CHITTERS)
(DISTANT ROARING)
MALCOLM: How many times do you
have to see the evidence?
How many times
must the point be made?
We're causing
our own extinction.
Too many red lines
have been crossed.
And our home has, in fundamental
ways, been polluted
by avarice
and political megalomania.
Genetic power has
now been unleashed
and of course,
that's gonna be catastrophic.
This change was inevitable
from the moment we brought the first
dinosaur back from extinction.
(ROARS)
We convince ourselves
that sudden change
is something that happens outside
the normal order of things,
like a car crash,
or that it's beyond our
control, like a fatal illness.
We don't conceive of sudden,
radical, irrational change
as woven into
the very fabric of existence.
Yet, I can assure you,
it most assuredly is.
And it's happening now.
Humans and dinosaurs are now
gonna be forced to coexist-
(GROWLING)
These creatures
were here before us.
And if we're not careful,
they're gonna be here after.
(ROARING)
We're gonna have to adjust to new
threats that we can't imagine.
(SCREECHING)
We've entered a new era.
Welcome to Jurassic World.
(GRUNTING)
(SCREECHING)
(HORNS BLARING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(SCREECHING)