[whistles loudly]
[boards creaking]
[man yells] Malenchenko!
[man yells] Hey, I need help here.
[man 2] This area smells like shit.
[sighs]
The dead number at least 47.
Hard to get a firm count with
the state of some of the bodies.
Survivors?
- [man] The horses are here.
- Well, Okhchen?
A small group.
Attacked last night.
Then headed back the way they came.
[man] Headed back for their barrow?
I believe so, sir.
Have the men prepare to move out.
Signal the other teams we've made contact.
We will track and destroy these monsters.
Permission to speak freely,
Comrade Lieutenant?
Of course, Sergei Pavlovich.
I fear the teams are too far apart.
We cannot support each other
if we encounter too many of them.
[Lieutenant] I raised that concern also.
But the major thinks we can
cover more area this way.
He's confident each team
can handle itself.
[Sergei] And the planes we requested?
[Lieutenant] The Air Force is busy with
the Germans besieging Stalingrad.
There's darkness
in every direction these days, comrade.
We'll have to find our own way through it.
There are places like this
scattered throughout the deep forest.
Old places.
My people believe they are cursed.
[Lieutenant] I can feel it.
The air feels...
heavy.
They are close now. They know we're here.
- [beastly roar]
- [man yelling]
[men yelling]
[man] Go!
[man] Cover me!
[man 2] Reloading!
[Lieutenant] In the trees!
Behind us!
[gun clicks]
[man yells] Move out!
[chains clink]
[men cough and groan]
[man whimpers and groans]
[Okhchen] Comrade Lieutenant!
- [Lieutenant] What is it?
- A body, one of ours.
Whatever happened to him,
it was some time ago.
Cheka.
Secret police.
[chuckles]
This place was bad luck for him too.
Yes.
And the sooner we're gone, the better.
[coughs]
[distant flare fires]
Hey.
Can you play?
Yes, I can, but I should not.
Play for Maxim.
- [gunfire]
- [men screaming] [balalaika playing]
[men hum]
It was my fault, sir.
[Lieutenant sighs]
[Sergei] Who was he?
A Major.
Boris Grishin.
He was assigned to Operation Hades.
Does that mean anything to you?
I've heard rumors of it.
An operation focused on
exploring arcane peasant myths.
[Lieutenant] In November 1919, after
the White Army was forced to retreat,
Grishin was dispatched
on a secret mission.
He was an occultist.
His assignment was to perform
a certain black magic ritual,
whispered about among the Koryaks.
It was meant to summon unholy creatures
who could fight beside the Red Army.
The operation doesn't seem to
have worked out very well for him.
[ground rumbles]
[beast growls]
[beast roars]
[Sergei] We must take this information
to our superiors.
They could end this plague.
[Lieutenant] They would more likely end us
for revealing their past mistakes.
No, we have our mission, comrade.
Nothing more.
Nothing less.
Have you ever seen
a ghoul barrow that big, Lieutenant?
Never.
- [Lieutenant] Pogodin!
- [Pogodin] Sir.
[Lieutenant] Time to earn your pay.
Of course, comrade.
[Okhchen] I've never seen so many tunnels.
I don't like it down here.
[Pogodin] Stop your whining.
[growling and hissing]
[Okhchen] I can hear them coming.
- Pogodin.
- I'm working on it.
[rapid gun fire]
One more wire.
Pogodin!
Almost.
- They're closing in!
- [ghouls howl and chitter]
[Okhchen]There's too many of them.
What's the hold up?
[distant rapid gunfire]
You are getting older... and slower.
[laughs]
Next time, you do it!
[rumbling]
Is it sealed?
Are we done?
No.
Sir, shall we prepare to fall back?
The horses cannot outrun that horde.
The creatures will catch us in the trees
and tear us apart.
We must make our stand here.
Sergei, bring me the fastest horse!
Kaminsky, unload all
the ammunition and explosives.
Maxim, Oleg!
Take those charges
and set them at the base of the cliff.
Double time!
Set up the machine gun positions
on our flanks.
How can I help, sir?
Hold the reins tight. She is fierce.
One of us can make it through
if we slow them down.
No. Please, sir. No!
[ghouls howl]
I'd rather die with you.
- I beg you, let me stay.
- Give the Major our coordinates.
Tell him to bomb this place
into scorched rubble.
- Father, please.
- That...
is an order.
Ride like hell and don't look back!
Comrades, we stand here.
We die here!
- It has been an honor!
- [men yell]
[yells]
[intense orchestral music plays]
[inaudible]
[ghouls growl]