[woman in Irish accent]
Jockey Mother, this is Anthem.
I'm on station at satellite LV426.
[man] Copy, Anthem. We got you monitored.
Appreciate the company, Bill.
These solo jobs tweak my nerves.
[Bill] God damn company penny pinchers,
am I right?
Why pay two when one'll do?
Prepping EVA.
[Bill] Now, you be careful out there,
Alex.
[electronic beeping and whirring]
Locate panel, sync and navigate.
[sighs]
[yells]
[rapid beeping]
No! God damn it!
Damn it!
Come on.
No...
No!
[panicked breathing]
Come on! Fuck!
Fuck.
[shouts] Fuck!
[Bill] Anthem. This is Jockey Mother.
Alex, what the hell's going on out there?
I'm fucked. Impact on my mobility unit.
It went non-functional
and the backup's damaged as well.
[rapid beeping]
Oh, for fuck's sake.
[Bill] Alex, rescue team are on their way.
The boys will be with you in 58 minutes.
Jesus.
[rapid beeping]
Listen, Bill.
That impact...
Well, it looks like it damaged
my oxygen tanks too.
The rescue team's
not gonna make it in time.
- [Bill] Now, just hold on a second...
- No.
Math's come in. I'm done.
Just do me a favor, okay?
Next time the suits come calling, would
you kick them in the bollocks for me?
[Bill] Now, Alex, just wait...
[radio clicks off]
[hissing]
[screams]
[silence]
- [hissing]
- [beeping]
Alex, you idiot.
Of course!
[grunts]
[heavy breathing]
Here we go.
[yelps in pain]
[gasps]
[controlled breathing]
Okay.
Wait.
[grunts]
- No! God damn it!
- [rapid beeping]
[cries]
Shit!
[groans]
Come on...
[groans in pain]
[bones crunching]
[screams]
- [yells]
- [bones snapping]
[screams]
C'mon, you fuck!
[panting]
[coughing]
[Alex] Anthem to Jockey Mother.
You read?
[Bill] Jesus, Alex. Thank God.
We thought you were dead.
What happened?
I had to make a wee sacrifice
to the great nothing.
But I'm still breathing.
[Bill] Well, thank the fucking Lord.
So, you still need a hand?
[laughs]
Funny you should ask...
but I got things under control.
Just get a few beers chillin', Bill.