♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 33=
The longer you delay,
the slimmer chance you get
to win Ye Zhi Qiu.
More importantly,
you have to use Martial Soul Shield beforehand.
Or else you can't cleanse the effect
once you get attacked.
His Martial Soul is very unique
but once you know what it is,
you still stand a chance.
Master, you're very knowledgeable.
You managed to decipher his Martial Soul.
By the way,
before fighting against Cang Hui School,
you still have one more match.
Do you know who your opponent is?
Chi Huo School.
This school...
Why? Is it special?
There are all sorts of Soul Master schools.
The most extreme one
is the one that only focuses
on one type of Martial Soul.
I don't get it.
To put it simply,
Chi Huo School
only recruits Flame Branch Soul Masters.
Other Soul Masters won't be considered.
Do you mean that
all the students are of the Flame Branch?
Then they are easy to constrain, aren't they?
Your Blue Silver Plant
is weak
when facing Flame Branch Martial Soul.
So now,
you have to improve its fire resistance.
How?
Ma Hong Jun!
All the schools that took part
already showed up.
I made a list of those that are
noteworthy
and proposed some countermeasures.
Especially Shi Lan Ke School.
Tang San's Blue Silver Plant.
Figure out
how to deal with it.
Noted.
Any news from Du Gu Bo?
He agreed to do our bidding.
He is waiting for us
to give him more details.
Good.
You performed well today.
You assaulted me.
Dismiss your Soul Skill.
You've recovered your memory.
Spirit control won't work forever.
Someone with a strong will
can wake up sooner or later.
That's why you assaulted me.
Do you think you can win?
Kill me then.
Do you think I don't dare to?
The contest has already begun.
The name list of the contest cannot be modified.
If I die,
how can Cang Hui School
still join the contest?
So you think
you can threaten me with that?
Can Hui toiled so hard
to get into the final.
I can always spend a tiny bit
more effort to control you again.
I know how Mind Branch Martial Soul works.
Once the spirit control fails,
if you try it again straight away,
your target will
most probably go insane.
A puppet is not bad, either.
If I lose my mind,
how am I supposed to fight in the arena?
If the Grand Soul Land Masters
from Martial Soul Hall
see something's wrong with me,
what do you think will happen?
What do you want?
I want to live.
I've never planned to kill you.
I don't know what your plan is,
but judging from how you handled us,
you weren't planning to let us stay alive.
All right, you have my words.
Once we succeed in getting into the final,
I'll set you free.
I want to see the Hao Tian Soul Master.
Why?
I only believe in
a Grand Soul Land Master's words.
He's not in Tian Dou City.
Where is he?
Once you get into the final,
you'll find him
in Martial Soul City.
I've satisfied your request.
Dismiss your Martial Soul.
I want to see the others on the team.
Ye Zhi Qiu,
don't get too greedy.
Someone has to take care
of their current condition.
Fair enough.
You can take care of their nourishment
but don't ever think about rescuing them.
Your friends are not like you.
Without me,
they will never recover.
I know.
Once your plan succeeds,
set them free too.
Can do.
What exactly is your plan?
After we get into the final,
what are we supposed to do?
The questions you have now.
Save them for
Hao Tian Soul Master.
Your Martial Soul
is quite good for ambushing.
I look forward to seeing you enter the final.
It's indeed not afraid of fire?
Such high fire resistance.
Seems like Brother Dai and I
don't have to fight next round.
Both of you
are our trump cards against Cang Hui School.
We can't show our hands that early.
Then,
should I
ask Teacher Er Long
to come here to test it out?
Her flame is stronger.
But she has Seven Soul Rings, Master.
Let's try it.
Today is the day of the contest.
Aren't you going to spectate, Your Highness?
I dislike Shi Lan Ke School,
but I must admit that they are strong.
It's quite obvious who'll win
the contest today.
Your Highness,
I didn't expect that you
would visit Qibao Amber Clan.
There's a female student in Shi Lan Ke
whose Martial Soul is Qibao Amber Pagoda.
I assume she is your disciple.
Jumping into conclusion
with just one Martial Soul.
A bit premature, I'd say.
If she wasn't your disciple,
then Chief Ning wouldn't have bought
Tang San's herbs in the auction.
Your Highness,
are you here to question me?
I did my research.
That female student
is called Ning Rong Rong.
When
she just joined Shi Lan Ke School,
she was just a Soul Master
with Double Soul Rings.
I didn't expect her
to become a Soul Sect with Quadruple Soul Rings
within such a short time.
A Soul Sect at this age.
How many Soul Sects does the Ning Tribe have?
Just her alone.
So she's a genius.
A genius like her
should be taken back to her clan
for intensive training.
Are you trying to tell me
how to do my job, Your Highness?
Allowing your student to study
in another school
is never something good.
If you need my help,
feel free to turn to me, Chief Ning.
Why did he come here
to tell you that?
He just wants me to summon Rong Rong
back to our clan.
What can he gain from this?
He wants to dismantle Shi Lan Ke's team.
Why is a prince
targeting a normal school?
I think it's weird too.
Prince Xue Xing,
came to me
for one school.
I feel that
he overreacted.
So
even Teacher Er Long
can't burn your Blue Silver Plant.
This must have something to do
with the fact that I took Octo Dark Frost
and absorbed Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
Now my Blue Silver Plant
is immune to
both water and fire.
That's amazing.
How shall we fight this round?
Depends on the rules.
The third round of Soul Master School Contest.
The participants
are Shi Lan Ke School and Chi Huo School.
Captains, please come up to the arena
and draw for the rules.
I'll go now.
Sure.
I'm not worried about the rules.
We won against
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad.
These pyromaniacs are nothing.
Right?
Exactly.
Win this round as soon as possible.
We should get ready
for the match against Cang Hui School.
Didn't Master decipher
Ye Zhi Qiu's Martial Soul?
Cang Hui School is just a piece of cake.
And also,
we have taken some premium herbs.
It could be a landslide victory
and we'll possibly take the first place.
Yes!
Do not underestimate our foes.
Do your best in every contest.
Why are you so quiet, Master?
Master,
how do you think
we should fight Cang Hui School next round?
Patient.
We'll discuss this
after we're done with this round.
They are drawing for the rules.
Okay.
Five versus five.
Both teams pick five members
and fight until
the enemy team can't fight anymore.
Come.
What?
You'll fight next round.
I want to wish you all the best.
Childish.
Break a leg.
Wait for the good news.
Childish.
Break a leg.
Come on.
This can withstand the flame attack.
We've been surrounded.
Blue Silver Cage.
Why are you guys so split up?
Aren't you afraid that we can always pick you off
one by one?
Should we attack them, Tang San?
Wait.
Let the flame through.
When they notice that
Blue Silver Plant cannot be burnt,
they must be shocked.
And when they are
thinking of countermeasures,
we'll fight back.
That's right! Give them a good scare!
The fire is spreading quite slowly.
Stacking Martial Soul.
It's taller.
The colour has changed.
So what?
It spreads so slowly.
Even now we're still safe.
It's still changing.
Is it hot in here?
Are you feeling hot, Rong Rong?
A bit.
It's so hot.
Are they trying to wither us down like this?
Let them be.
They spend more energy than us.
Tang San.
I can teleport
and ambush one of them.
Wait.
Let's wait a bit before attacking.
Is Prince Xue Xing absent today?
Look!
We keep winning,
so he must have gotten so pissed
that he refused to spectate.
Are they crazy?
Why are they maintaining the flame wall
instead of attacking?
Are we not attacking?
Get ready
to get through the flame wall
and pick them off one by one.
I'm seeing stars...
How about you?
Tang San, your Blue Silver Plant.
Are you okay, Tang San?
I'm a bit out of breath.
I think I might faint soon.
What's happening?
It must be a mind attack.
Impossible.
They are all Flame Branch Soul Masters.
I'm actually quite surprised.
You guys stayed inside
so obediently.
Everything should end now.
What's happening?
Get ready to bring them back.
We've lost.
Impossible.
Brother San's Blue Silver Plant
is immune to fire.
He has lost consciousness.
How can he use his Martial Soul?
But the fire didn't reach them.
What Soul Skill is this?
This is not a Soul Skill.
It's just fire burning.
The only special thing is
all five of us
can increase the flame power further.
No Soul Skill is involved.
The power of the flame
is not just for burning.
Shi Lan Ke's team fainted.
Chi Huo School won this round.
I think one of the five Soul Masters
is a Mind Branch Soul Master.
Or else it wouldn't have turned out this way.
There's no Mind Branch Soul Master.
Master.
Come here.
What?
Why did the fire die out?
Because the air that surrounds you
is essential to combustion.
So,
when you put on the lid,
there was not enough air, and the fire died out.
It's one of the two reasons why
Chi Huo School won.
You guys were standing
in the middle of the arena.
It's as if you guys were stuck
in a cup made of flame.
As the flame burned, the air slowly depleted.
You guys couldn't breathe
and ended up fainting.
Fire.
Fire depletes the air.
And the second reason?
Over-confidence.
Stand up, Tang San.
You're the tactician.
When the opponents were making a flame wall,
why didn't you counter-attack?
Tang San wanted to use Blue Silver Plant
to block their attack,
and we were supposed to fight back
when they were caught by surprise.
You wanted to undermine their confidence
because you thought they'd never
get through your Blue Silver Plant?
Before the battle,
I heard what you all said.
I'm not worried about the rules.
We won against
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad.
These pyromaniacs are nothing.
Right?
Exactly.
Win this round as soon as possible.
We should get ready
for the match against Cang Hui School.
Didn't Master decipher
Ye Zhi Qiu's Martial Soul?
Cang Hui School is just a piece of cake.
Also,
we took some premium herbs.
It could be
a landslide victory
and we'll possibly take the first place.
You just won two rounds and
you've already started to be a snob.
You think you're unrivaled.
Tang San never said that.
He didn't say that
but he was so confident about his own strategy
that he never took the opponents seriously.
And now, they didn't even have to
use their Soul Skill
to defeat you all.
I made a mistake, Master.
Everyone is at fault here.
Can any of you here say that
you didn't get too snobbish?
You looked down on Flame Branch Soul Masters.
Tang San,
your Blue Silver Plant
had always been the laughing stock.
Have you ever felt inferior?
What did you say to yourself?
There's never a useless Martial Soul,
only a useless Soul Master.
Louder!
There's never a useless Martial Soul,
only a useless Soul Master.
What constitutes a useless Soul Master?
Arrogance. Ignorance.
Lack of observation.
Lack of respect.
During this battle today,
you guys were all useless Soul Masters.
We're not useless,
we were just a bit
careless today.
If it was a live-or-die contest,
you all would've been long gone.
What's the point of your excuse?
Each one of you is a Soul Sect
with Quadruple Soul Rings.
Each one of you took premium herbs.
That's why you thought you were
the genius of all geniuses.
And now, the opponents didn't even
have to use Soul Skill
to defeat you guys.
Aren't you ashamed?
Those who didn't fight.
Reflect upon your own mentality
and see if you were like them.
Don't cry, Rong Rong.
Chief Ning.
You gave a good lecture.
Rong Rong didn't know you came.
Don't tell her.
Teenagers are hot-blooded.
They get excited easily.
But if they encounter an obstacle,
they get discouraged easily too.
After you scold them,
you let them reflect upon themselves.
As such,
will someone
give up completely then?
I have faith in them.
It's not like we've never suffered a loss before.
When we were in Soul Arena
of Suo Tuo City,
we all lost, didn't we?
But the opponents back then
were stronger than us.
But some students
from Chi Huo School
are just Soul Honours with Triple Soul Rings.
I like to fight
but I can't win every fight, either.
If I lose this time, I can always try again.
Wu is right.
It's not like we'll lose
for the rest of our life.
Recently,
we've become over-confident
and arrogant.
What Master said is totally true.
But ask yourself,
are you willing to accept this loss?
They didn't even use Soul Skill
before we fainted.
Are you willing to admit defeat?
Chi Huo School is strong
and they know how to use
Flame Branch Martial Soul
to its fullest.
But no, I will not admit defeat.
Me, neither.
I respect them,
but I want to fight them again.
Yes.
I want to use everything
and fight them again.
And what if we lose again?
Then we'll train harder.
Didn't you say that
we won't lose forever?
Next round, we'll face
Cang Hui School.
They are stronger and more dangerous
than Chi Huo School.
Defeat them then.
Yes.
Get stronger and defeat them.
We'll get stronger.
Stronger!
Stronger.
Definitely stronger.
Yes.
Stronger!
Yes, definitely stronger.
Very excited, I see.
Dad.
Did you say you were defeated once?
Chief Ning,
we can work together actually.
Was Grandpa Sword not with you?
He was there.
He was defeated by a direct attack?
No, it was an ambush.
It was a cloud of flickering black smoke.
Black smoke, are you sure?
Perhaps it was green?
I can't be mistaken. It's black smoke.
The smoke of Venom Soul Master is green.
It's not him then.
The foe could turn invisible.
Grandpa Sword was injured
and then was defeated before fainting.
But even if he was ambushed,
Grandpa Sword is a Grand Soul Land Master.
Yes,
a Grand Soul Land Master can only be defeated
by another Grand Soul Land Master.
He's an indiscreet
Grand Soul Land Master who ambushed others.
What did he want from the clan?
I want to help you guys.
I want to help you to restore
the power of Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
How...did you come to know this?
If we work together,
I'll provide enough resources
to prepare a solid foundation
for the mutation of Qibao Amber Pagoda.
The Martial Soul in your family
will return to its peak form.
Isn't this
what you've dedicated your life to, Chief Ning?
Are two more layers
that important?
Jiubao Amber Pagoda
is a miracle created by the first chief
of Qibao Amber Clan.
It represents the hope of our clan's revival.
Wait,
so you agreed to work with him?
I have no other choice.
But he ambushed you two!
The revival of our clan's Martial Soul
is the most important.
When did this happen?
You must have wondered
why I sent you
to Shi Lan Ke School out of a sudden.
So is this why
I was sent here?
Yes,
I asked you to leave the clan immediately
after I agreed to work with him.
If something bad happened to us,
you'd be safer outside.
Uncle Ning, I have one question.
What did he ask you to do exactly?
Soon,
Martial Soul Hall will hold
Douluo Soul Master School Tournament.
The final will take place
in Martial Soul City.
You want my clan to take part in it?
This is not important.
My request is simple.
During the final,
the Grand Sword Master and you
should appear in Martial Soul City
as spectators.
And then?
I want you to kill someone for me.
Who?
I'll tell you on the day of the final.
My instinct told me that
something huge would happen
in the tournament.
That's
another reason why I sent you to
Shi Lan Ke School.
Shi Lan Ke School
couldn't join the tournament.
Now you can imagine
how worried I were when I found out
that you were in Tian Dou City
and Shi Lan Ke School
was joining the tournament.
So is that why you asked Grandpa Sword
to send me away?
I wanted him to hide you somewhere
but
a fool took you away.
Fool?
Who?
Wasn't I the one who took you away?
Idiot.
Another Grand Soul Land Master
who uses poisons
was asked to go to Martial Soul City too.
Dad,
will you go then?
Yes.
But now I have
mutated into Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
The sudden changes of Douluo Continent
will be in Martial Soul City.
As a Soul Master,
there's no way I'd miss it.
I want to witness
what exactly will happen.
But
what if you bump into
the Grand Soul Land Master
who threatened you?
Grandpa Sword said that
after the first encounter,
he already had an idea.
That guy won't be able to ambush us
the second time.
Please be cautious, you two.
You guys are the ones who should be cautious.
The final in Martial Soul City
will definitely usher in new changes.
Do you guys still want to join the final?
I have to, for personal reasons.
Everyone is free to quit, however.
No need to take a risk with me.
My brother is waiting for me in the final
so I also have to go to Martial Soul City.
Wherever Tang San is,
I'll be there.
You helped me previously, Brother San.
I'll help you to get into the final.
I won't quit.
Me, either.
Think carefully, Rong Rong.
Don't be reckless.
Dad.
You should know that
the premium herbs from Brother San
helped my Martial Soul
to mutate into Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
So,
if I quit now,
won't I bring shame to the Ning family?
You're right.
The Nings
will not run away.
Me, either.
Ou Si Ke.
You don't have to join.
Me?
Your dream is to make art.
You don't have to join us.
But I...
I'm of the Support Branch.
I'm useful during battles.
I can support them.
Just pursue your dream.
But...
But as for Headmaster, I...
We'll deal with Headmaster.
You've walked with us
long enough,
it's time
for us to support
your dream together.
Exactly.
No...
I...
I have to buy something.
You can tell me if there's anything
when I come back.
All right.
It seems like
only one person quit.
Rong Rong,
we respect your decision.
If you guys can enter the final,
Grandpa Sword and I
will be waiting for you in Martial Soul City.
Don't worry, Uncle Ning.
The Grand Soul Land Master
who uses poisons
will be at Martial Soul City to protect us.
Rong Rong is in good hands.
Good.
Here, Rong Rong.
That idiot's dream
is to not be a Soul Master, is it?
His biggest dream
is to establish a theatrical club,
write his own play and perform.
In that case,
is he a good actor?
Then,
when he was risking his life
to save you last time,
was he acting?
No way, dad.
Actually,
he can't act at all.
Really? That's great.
Rong Rong,
are you in love with that fool?
Dad!
What do you fancy?
How much is the Flint Powder?
Its price depends
on its flammability.
It mainly depends
on what you want it for.
It's for my cane.
Cane?
Yes.
It will burn if I can produce heat.
In the arena,
it can be used as a gadget.
Arena?
Did you join Soul Master School Contest?
I did,
but I guess
I probably don't have to fight anymore.
Why?
Because being a Soul Master
is not my dream.
So this is useless for me.
What are you guys doing?
I'm just looking around here.
Get out!
You...
Why are you keeping me here?
Are you Ou Si Ke?
Don't worry.
If I want to kill you,
I won't show myself.
Your Highness, are you telling me that
it's a pure coincidence that we met today?
Of course not.
I'm waiting for you.
Relax.
Among the three theatrical clubs
of Tian Dou City,
which one do you like?
What?
Don't you know them?
Of course I do!
The best actors, the best scripts.
Those three theatrical clubs
are the treasures of arts.
They are sacred beings in every
performer's heart.
Of course I know them.
I'm glad you like it.
This...
For me?
What do you mean?
The last row is empty.
Write your name down
and the Starry Theatrical Club
will be yours.
I...
-You heard it right.
-Mine?
This is the ownership transfer letter.
As one of the three theatrical clubs,
the Starry Theatrical Club needs a new president.
Martial Soul Shield
cannot last long.
So we have to defeat
Ye Zhi Qiu
quickly
to avoid being affected by his Soul Skill.
We also have to consider
the other four students from Cang Hui School.
So we need to defeat Ye Zhi Qiu
even faster.
All right. We'll throw everything at him.
I will think about other strategies
to deal with various situations.
We'll practice together soon.
Okay.
Young Master.
We're friends, not master and servant.
But my grandpa
asked me to address you so.
You can call me Tang San in private.
I can't.
If my grandpa hears it,
he will punish me.
It's okay. I'll explain to him.
All right.
Come, come in.
Okay.
Prince Xue Xing asked my grandpa
to buy Starry.
Starry?
A school?
A theatrical club.
One of the three theatrical clubs
in Tian Dou City.
Haven't you heard of it?
It's fine.
Just know that it's famous.
But why did the prince buy a theatrical club?
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪