♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 32=
Did you take part in the siege?
Of course not!
If I did,
then I'm no different
than a dirty swine!
Then why did you apologize?
Master Tang, you asked for me?
I need a favour from you.
You saved the whole Tai family once,
even my life belongs to you, Master Tang.
I'll do anything.
Have you heard of the Island of the God of Sea?
What is that?
It's a myth in the clouds.
They said
the Island of the God of Sea lies within the ocean
away from Duoluo Continent.
I spent some time
to reach Duoluo Continent's border.
When I was looking for a boat,
I heard
that Martial Soul Hall
was going after Master Tang.
Only then did I realize
that Master Tang
didn't want me to
look for the Island of the God of Sea.
He already knew that
Martial Soul Hall was
going against him,
so he asked you to leave
and stay away from that?
When I finally got it,
I immediately rushed back
to Martial Soul City.
I just hoped that
I could help Master Tang.
But you were too late.
When I arrived,
the battle has ended.
I heard that the Lady was killed,
Master Tang was severely injured and missing.
I've asked everyone I know
for their whereabouts.
They all lead to nowhere in the end.
And then?
Then,
I decided to
charge into Martial Soul Hall!
I know it's suicidal.
But
they've done that to Master Tang,
how could I not
take revenge on that?
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
Since you had the intention,
I should thank you.
That year Chief Qian Xun Ji
was severely hurt by Master Tang.
After that,
he sent some Grand Soul Land Masters
to kill Master Tang in Douluo Continent.
That's how I survived.
But I've also annoyed Martial Soul Hall.
With no other option,
I ran away with the whole tribe.
When we finally reached Tian Dou City,
it was Prince Xue Xing
who accommodated us.
Of course,
he also knew about
the power of our tribe
and thus tried to rope us in.
We owe him that anyway.
So,
I decided to do anything for him once.
I didn't expect
I would almost hurt you, Young Master.
Oh.
All these years,
Master Tang was working as a blacksmith?
He has seen better days.
Why did he have to do that?
Where's Master Tang now?
I should seek his punishment myself.
I'm still looking for him too.
Grandpa Titan,
have you heard of Cang Hui School?
Yes.
It's not one of the first-class schools
in Tian Dou City.
There's something mysterious
behind Cang Hui School.
I heard from someone
that it's the Hao Tian Soul Master.
Do you mean
Master Tang is expanding his power
in Cang Hui School?
I'm not sure yet.
They said if we can enter the final,
then we'll be able to see him.
So, you took part in the contest
in order to find Master Tang?
But
I also hope that
he's not behind all of this.
Why?
In order to fight Martial Soul Hall,
Cang Hui School has hurt
many Soul Masters
with dirty tricks.
Hurting Soul Masters?
Not only them,
but also many citizens.
Then I don't think it's him.
Why?
Master Tang has been a righteous man,
even if he's taking revenge,
he won't hurt the innocents.
Young Master,
anyone who wishes to hurt Master Tang and you,
no matter who he is,
must be over my dead body first.
Grandpa Titan,
please don't tell the others
about our relationship yet.
You're all here?
The tea is good.
Well,
someone from Cang Hui School came.
Was it Shi Nian?
It was a student, Ye Zhi Qiu.
What did he say?
He gave me this.
What is that?
Antidote,
but only for one person.
It's to cure Yan Yan's poison.
They said they had shown
their sincerity.
What did they ask for in return?
During the finals,
they want Yan Yan and me
to go to Martial Soul City.
They
need my help at that time.
When it's all done,
they'll cure my poison.
Who are you going to fight against?
No idea.
Did you say anything about
that your poison has been cured?
Of course not.
Like I promised you,
I pretended to be angry.
And then?
I agreed.
Cang Hui School
is inviting a Grand Soul Land Master
to fight in Martial Soul City.
This might turn into big chaos.
But
this Ye Zhi Qiu,
he's having a little problem.
What is it?
It seems he's being controlled
by spirit power.
It must be Shi Nian.
Why did he even control Ye Zhi Qiu?
I was curious
and used
the power of Grand Soul Land Master
to suppress the spirit control.
That's a loophole.
If Du Gu Yan and you aren't cured,
you surely won't do that.
After suppressing his spirit control,
Ye Zhi Qiu was acting strange.
Strange?
He wanted to see you.
Me?
No point to talk further,
just follow me
and you'll know.
Venom Soul Master is there with you,
it'll be fine.
Isn't Du Gu Yan here?
She's in the battle training.
And I don't want her to know much
about all these troubles.
What is wrong with him?
I'm not from the Mind Branch,
I can only use the power of Nine Soul Rings
to forcefully suppress his spirit control.
It was his full cooperation
that keeps him sober.
Tang San.
You looked for me?
Shi Nian has some regard for you,
he wants to use Shi Lan Ke as his pawn.
What is his motive?
I'm not sure.
I only know that Cang Hui School
has to enter the final.
Why did you tell me this
all of a sudden?
I always thought
that I was Mr. Shi Nian's most favorable student,
and that I should fight for Cang Hui School.
Isn't that so?
After unlocking spirit control,
many of my memories came back to my mind.
Only then did I realize
I was being controlled by Shi Nian all this while.
Not only you,
I'm also
a pawn that is abandoned after used.
So, what do you want me to do?
Nothing.
I'll fight Shi Nian by myself.
If I fail,
I'll seek your help.
I'm here to send a reminder to you.
But we don't know each other well.
I've been in Cang Hui School for years,
yet I haven't known a lot of people
or found anyone I can trust.
And you trust me?
In Xi Si City,
I saw you
fighting against Fiend Battle Team.
Under that situation,
you didn't kill them.
You're someone with principles.
Among those whom I know,
you're unlike the others.
Surely I'm not the only one.
You're the only one
who will trade with me.
Trade?
Do you know what I want?
You wish to see
the Hao Tian Soul Master
behind Cang Hui School.
Do you know where he is?
I don't.
But if we team up,
I'll help you to track him down.
May I suggest
that you just kill him?
When you reach Cang Hui School,
just say that I killed him out of rage.
Since Cang Hui School
needs me for a favour,
they won't care about
a Quadruple Soul Rings Soul Sect.
He isn't lying.
My instinct tells me that
he wants to rebel towards Shi Nian.
How can we believe
a little girl's instinct?
I...
All right, I'm in.
We can now discuss
ways to help you.
No.
You don't have to do anything.
I'll handle Shi Nian
alone.
Can I go now?
Are you serious?
I trust Wu.
I cast off my power,
and now his spirit control is resumed.
I've broken the barrier
and I'm keeping myself sober with willpower.
I have to go back now,
or else Shi Nian will start to suspect.
I'll tell Shi Nian
that Du Gu Bo
is willing to come to Martial Soul City.
Whatever happens today
won't be known by anyone else.
What are you planning to do?
I'll think about it
after tomorrow's contest.
If I fail,
I'll look for you again.
If you fail,
I'm afraid you'll lose your life.
After the contest tomorrow,
my life
will be safe temporarily.
What does that mean?
Once the contest starts,
the participating school list
can't be changed anymore.
Are you the only one
representing Cang Hui School?
Come and watch tomorrow.
He's determined.
He's keeping himself sober
all by his willpower.
Normal people can't do that.
What has Shi Nian done to him?
Excuse me.
Luckily, the food is safe.
Wu, didn't you go to buy drinks?
But these look delicious.
Try it.
All right then.
Look at Cang Hui School.
There's only one student.
The man standing there is Shi Nian.
Actually,
we can be friends.
Yes, we're friends.
Let's eat together.
Later on,
do it your own way.
Ye Zhi Qiu is acting normal.
This young man seems to have
something in mind.
Is it delicious?
Yes.
It's good to be young.
Master, do you want some?
I'm good.
The second round of
Soul Master School Contest.
We have
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad
versus Cang Hui School.
Captains, please get ready on stage.
Here are the contest rules.
Starting second round,
the contest will be conducted
according to the chosen rules.
Both captains, please show your hands.
What a coincidence.
Tag match of one versus one,
just the same as the first round.
Captains, please step down
and get ready for your sequence.
I'm the only one from Cang Hui School.
May I stay?
Yes.
Where are your team members?
Do you plan to fight all of us alone?
You'd better hurry up
and arrange your sequence.
It's fine. I'm the first one.
He's really alone
in Cang Hui Battle Team?
That's one versus six.
Have you seen him fight?
What is his Martial Soul?
He crashed my Blue Silver Plant back then,
but I didn't see
his Martial Soul clearly.
Contest begins!
Where's your Martial Soul?
It has shown up.
Are you planning to dodge till the end?
It's almost time.
You lost.
Tai Long's power and speed
is dropping drastically.
This feels as though
he has fallen sick.
We still haven't seen
Ye Zhi Qiu's Martial Soul.
What is going on?
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad
lost this round.
Is that airwave his Martial Soul?
No.
That's the power of
an explosion of Soul Ring.
Every Soul Master can do that.
Then how did Tai Long lose?
Master, what are you looking for?
Actually, I have no idea
what I'm searching for.
But I know
that every Soul Skill used
will leave some traces.
Traces?
Ye Zhi Qiu's Martial Soul
isn't invisible.
I can do it myself.
Patients should sit still.
It's all right,
I'm almost recovered.
Sit back.
Open your mouth.
I can...
Are you still thirsty?
You don't have to take care of me.
You're injured.
Let the others help me then.
There's no one else.
Ma Hong Jun is taking care of
Ou Si Ke.
Teacher Liu is taking care of
Ning Rong Rong.
I'll take care of you.
You...
What about Tang San and Wu?
Master brought them
to watch Cang Hui's contest.
Thanks.
Here.
What are you doing?
I'm helping you with the medicine.
I can do it myself.
You can't even see the wound.
Let's wait for Wu to come back.
What for?
It's improper for a man to touch a lady.
Well,
Tang San once applied medicine
for Wu too.
She didn't say anything.
That's a different situation.
Why are you so talkative?
You!
Don't move.
My sister said...
My sister once said,
you were going to die soon.
This should be related to your brother.
Then will you give up
participating in this contest?
What would you do?
Of course I'll fight till the end.
But
it's the life-and-death battle
between you brothers.
We both have Quadruple Soul Rings.
It's early to tell
who will have the last laugh.
Are you worrying about me?
Dai Mu Bai.
Coming.
You owe me an answer.
Don't move around.
Tang San, Wu and I just came back
from the contest.
Who won?
Cang Hui School.
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad
lost again?
They were all beaten by Ye Zhi Qiu alone.
Tag match?
He beat all six from Tian Dou?
Till the end,
no one has seen
his Martial Soul at all.
Is he that strong?
It's Mutant Soul.
As long as we know
his Martial Soul nature,
our winning chance will be higher.
But
none of you saw it, wasn't it?
I probably have a guess now,
but I'm not too sure.
I'll have to observe a little longer.
What is it?
I'll tell you when it's confirmed.
I don't want to mislead you.
So, why are you looking for me?
Our next opponent
is the Elephant Armoured School.
It's one of the Seven Clans.
In the next round,
I hope that you and Ma Hong Jun sit back.
Why?
Master said,
after two more rounds,
we're going to fight Cang Hui School.
Judging from the current situation,
Cang Hui School
is our greatest enemy now.
So, you and Brother Dai
will be our secret weapons.
Ma Hong Jun has become
our secret weapon now!
You've grown up now! That's great!
Don't look down on him.
It was an extra bonus
that we got premium herbs
to level up our Martial Souls.
No one would believe that
we have all advanced
to Quadruple Soul Rings now.
Yes.
Not me.
I only have Triple Soul Rings.
Wu is an exception.
Even though I only have Triple Soul Rings,
but when it comes to fighting,
I'll never lose.
You're great.
Awesome.
So, you and Brother Dai
should hide until
our battle with Cang Hui School.
Then only we give them a big surprise.
But there are two more rounds.
The three of them are wounded now.
I've fully recovered.
I'm totally fine now.
Touch it.
Me, Ou Si Ke,
Wu, Rong Rong and Zhu Zhu Qing,
the five of us will survive
these two rounds.
It should be just fine.
I'll listen to you.
But
Sister Qing's injury is quite severe.
It's enough. Don't worry.
At the worst, four of us will do.
That's right. Don't worry.
Of course I can make it.
I'll recover very soon.
Why are you looking at me this way?
Does it still hurt?
No.
Lie down and sleep.
It's daytime now.
You're injured,
you should rest.
Then what about you?
I'll be here.
But
you can go back and rest as well.
Don't teach me
how to take care of a patient.
Close your eyes.
Close.
Give me your hand.
Hurry up.
Why is your heart beating so fast?
Are you feeling unwell?
That's how my heart beats
when I sleep.
What a strange symptom.
So, all these parts
are used to make armours.
It feels cool.
It doesn't affect our actions at all.
Brother, you're really skillful.
They will surely like it.
I've also experimented on it.
This Armour can resist certain damage.
A normal Martial Soul
can't break it at all.
That's great!
Our clothing will get protected,
and it's convenient when we move.
Brother, are you tired?
Drink some water.
All right.
Here.
Be careful.
Captain of Shi Lan Ke,
come up and draw your rules.
Let's start.
Five-versus-five team battle.
Each team shall send five members.
You have only one chance!
All the best!
Of course.
Let's go.
You must win.
Full Recovery Big Sausage!
Jiubao Boosts!
First, Strength! Second, Speed!
Here!
Hurry up and eat it if you're feeling weak.
Elephant Armoured Clan is famous
for this team battle.
Ou Si Ke, I need a kiwi.
Rocketing Kiwi!
Remember, it's only for 15 minutes!
Got it.
Let's get rid of this
Control Branch Soul Master together.
Zhu Zhu Qing!
Wu! Zhu Zhu Qing!
Hang on!
Are you treating your teammates
as puppets?
I'm just serving as their eyes.
It's bad. That's explosive!
Tang San is the main role in Shi Lan Ke.
His Blue Silver Plant
controls the situation.
There are still two more persons.
They won't appear anymore. Let's go.
The battle hasn't ended.
There's no need to watch anymore.
Elephant Armoured Clan will lose.
This team from Shi Lan Ke
is way much stronger than I expected.
Don't panic.
Just the three of us would be enough.
I lost!
Shi Lan Ke School wins!
Master, we won!
We were in good shape
during the five-versus-five
team battle today.
It was a big triumph!
We also listened to you,
Brother Dai and Ma Hong Jun
didn't go on stage.
Not bad. Keep it up.
Here, sit.
Regarding Ye Zhi Qiu's Martial Soul,
I think I've figured it out.
Here, have a look.
What is covered in it?
Those bread and fruits days ago.
I've put them inside this basin.
Master, these are all mildewed.
Hang on.
Come.
Look.
What is this?
After the battle
where Ye Zhi Qiu defeated
six people from
Tian Dou Imperial School's Second Squad,
what did we find?
But the colour isn't the same.
At least the nature is the same.
What exactly is this?
Do you know
there are microorganisms
that we can't see with naked eyes?
Can't see with our eyes?
The activities of these microorganisms
cause decay and decomposition.
They are everywhere around us.
Some are harmless,
some can cause illnesses,
or even death.
Then why won't we decay
when we're alive?
Inside our body,
there are also microorganisms
that are resisting them.
The resistance won't stop until we die.
That's when the human body
starts to decay,
and everything goes back to the earth.
Do you mean that
Ye Zhi Qiu's Martial Soul
is controlling
and creating these microorganisms?
Ye Zhi Qiu's Martial Soul
can not only control microorganisms,
but also inhibit
the resistance mechanism in the body,
cause the decay to happen sooner
and end the opponent's life.
But Master,
when Tai Long was defeated,
his life wasn't endangered.
That was because Tai Long
kept using his Martial Soul.
I suppose
if we can cast out
our Soul Power beforehand,
maybe we can resist
the attack of microorganisms.
So, when you fight with Ye Zhi Qiu,
you have to cast out
all your Soul Power.
Master,
that will consume a large amount of Soul Power.
That's why you have to
finish it quickly.
The longer you delay,
the slimmer chance you get
to win Ye Zhi Qiu.
What is more important is
that you have to use
Martial Soul Shield beforehand.
Or else you can't cleanse the effect
once you get attacked.
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪