ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Is this the wrong way?
That hurt…
I came the right way.
This is so exhausting.
I'm hungry…
Achasan…
ACHASAN ECOLOGICAL PARK
Which way is it?
Found it!
It's too far to take a detour.
Seo-hae!
Mom?
Gang Seo-hae!
-Seo-hae!
-Mom?
Seo-hae!
Gang Seo-hae!
Hold my hand!
It's okay now.
It's okay.
-Dad…
-It's all right.
It's okay now.
You're safe.
It's all right.
You should steer clear of sand.
Always follow the paths. I told you that.
Right.
And I told you to rest
if you're exhausted,
to make sure you can see ahead,
and to take the safe route
even if it takes longer.
-Right.
-But you didn't do as I told you.
You can't get to the uploader by yourself.
Seo-hae.
I want you to have a comfortable life.
Let's smuggle ourselves
out of the country.
No.
I made a promise to your mother. Please.
You brat…
Take this.
If you want to get to the uploader,
you'll have to shoot me first.
Dad!
-What?
-This isn't like you.
What are you so scared of?
I'm scared
that you might suffer, get hurt,
and die.
I'm not scared.
I'm only scared of giving up
before trying anything.
I can do it. I'm going to do it.
It's something only I can do.
I can't get to the uploader by myself.
I need your help, Dad.
Please.
I want to go to the past.
I MISS YOU, MOM
GOODBYE, MY FRIEND
SLEEP WELL, MY DAUGHTER
GOODBYE, BROTHER
Seo-hae, promise me
that you'll take care of yourself first
over there.
Dad.
And come find me
if something happens, okay?
Okay.
You'll need a lot of valuables
to get on the uploader.
And you have to pay the brokers.
They say people sell them for money
to settle down in the past.
Things like weapons or medicine
that doesn't exist in the past.
Dad, that's…
This will be enough for one person.
What about you?
How long have they been following us?
For two days.
State your names.
Your names!
Seo-hae. Gang Seo-hae.
Why do you want to take the uploader?
Answer me!
To stop the war.
How?
I just need to save one person.
Who?
Han Tae-sul.
Han Tae-sul?
-Tae-san.
-Han Tae-sul!
Han Tae-sul! Get down!
I said, get down!
So it was you.
Dad.
This.
I got this scar when I fell from a bike.
When I was eight.
It's not that I doubt you.
I'm sorry. I'm just a bit confused.
You look the same as you did
when you were a kid.
You look like your mother.
You always said that.
And you're quite tall.
Your mother used to give you
herbal medicine to make you grow taller.
She'd be so happy to see you.
Here. This is how to get to the bunker.
I don't know who made it and why,
but a war breaks out on October 31.
So you and I lived there for 15 years.
BUNKER UNDER THE BRIDGE
What about your mother?
She…
If we knew about the war,
why didn't we leave the country
beforehand?
We can't.
People don't know it yet,
but the airports don't let us leave.
If the Control Bureau puts you
on the watch list, you can't leave.
You kept the promise you made to Mom.
You promised to keep me safe.
I did get injured here and there,
but it's only because
I kept going to dangerous places.
But I survived and grew up healthy.
I know what you're going to say.
You want to ask me
why I came to the past, right?
Because you wouldn't have let me go.
You're right.
But you did.
Thank you.
I tried fruit as you told me to.
Real fruit, not canned ones.
I even went to an amusement park,
and I met Mom.
And I met so many good people.
They don't try to steal what I have.
They get upset when I get hurt,
and risk their lives to save me.
I can do well on my own now.
And I'm not alone anymore.
I'll make sure
those people don't get hurt.
I'll make sure they can complain
about everyday life
without knowing anything about a war.
I'll change everything.
I can do it.
So when you're lonely,
stressed, or exhausted,
just look around you, and I'll be there.
I love you.
Hey! Mr. Han!
How does it feel to come back to life?
It feels great.
My entire life flashed before my eyes.
I felt that I should live kindly.
You should try it
when you have the chance.
No, thanks. I've committed too many sins.
My brother…
What have you done to him?
You promised to tell me. Come on.
All right.
Your brother Tae-san
was caught and tortured by Sigma.
Sigma took his key
and found out where his safe was.
And Agnes,
who worked for the Control Bureau,
took the opportunity to smuggle
your brother out,
along with the key.
So you're saying you were
all in on it together?
Sigma, Seo-jin, and the Control Bureau?
Don't say it like that.
We just have a complex…
Well, I guess I could say
it's a business relationship.
Anyway, after that,
I stole your brother from Agnes.
Then I offered him a deal.
I promised him that I'd protect you,
Han Tae-sul,
if he got me that key.
So you told him to come back
through the uploader once he got the key?
That's right.
Oh, don't you remember
our first phone call?
In Gimpo.
Mr. Han Tae-san.
Did you bring the key?
Yes, I have the key.
Are your limbs all there?
-What?
-Are your limbs all intact?
-Yes.
-Good. Your health is most important.
All right. Let's meet. Bring the key.
Where should I go?
We'll come pick you up.
Where are you now?
I'm at an acquaintance's house.
An acquaintance?
You said your limbs are all intact, right?
Yes.
But let me ask you something.
What's the number written
on your right arm?
Hey.
You're not Han Tae-san, are you?
Hey. Go get him.
Hurry up.
But Han Tae-san got caught by Sigma again.
Then Agnes was afraid that
Sigma might get his hands on
the uploader blueprint Tae-san had.
So she ended up injecting your brother
with the drug.
-Why didn't you tell me?
-I was told not to.
Anyway, the deal was that
Han Tae-san would get me the key,
and in return,
I'd provide
support and protection for you.
That's it.
Hey, you're here.
But did your father leave?
Her father seemed to have quite a temper,
didn't he?
I guess personalities are hereditary.
Let's go. I feel nervous staying here.
But I still have something left
to do here.
What are you two whispering about?
I helped save your girlfriend,
so you fix this now.
Hey. Do you have a flash drive?
A flash drive…
-A USB flash drive.
-Right. Yes, I do.
What's he telling you to fix?
I broke his downloader.
But you know,
I can't really trust you.
How can I trust you to let us go
in one piece after I give you this?
All right. Then I'll just kill you all
and take it.
Bingbing! Come over here.
Sis! Are you all right?
What about you?
I'm not all right.
Stand up straight.
Stop hitting me, will you?
Be quiet, you jerks.
Come on.
I locked it with a passcode.
You're trying to play tricks, are you?
Is that so? Shoot his hand.
-Just give it to him.
-What?
Just give it to him. It's okay.
Well, I'm not okay with it.
I'll take care of this.
Come on. Give it to me.
Right. The passcode.
-One.
-And?
Eight, one, eight.
Wow. What a simple passcode.
Bingbing!
Put this in and fix it.
Is it working or not?
I'm working on it!
I just rebooted the system.
I didn't even put it in yet.
Hurry up.
It's working.
Then can we go home now?
It was nice meeting you.
Darn it! I knew you'd do this.
What are you doing?
You owe me a debt.
I was taken to the Control Bureau.
That kid was shot,
and he got crippled for life.
Whose fault do you think that is?
Why are you blaming me?
You're in charge of your own life.
Stop this.
You said it's all predestined.
Getting taken to the Control Bureau
and not seeing your family
must be your destiny.
So why are you taking it out on me?
Taking it out on you? That's cute.
Right.
I'm angry
because I can't do anything about it.
I'm furious because it's all fixed!
Do you feel better if you say that?
Do you say that it's impossible to
change things in case you fail to do it?
You're just making an excuse.
But too bad. Let me tell you something.
Some things have already changed.
Seon-jae!
I was supposed to get shot.
It was written in my diary
that I'd be crippled after getting shot.
Give this to your brother.
-They're stem cells.
-What's that?
They can fix his legs.
They're not fully developed yet now.
You might be too cowardly to do it,
but I can change the future.
And it's already changing.
So shoot me if you want to.
Let's go.
I'm furious because I can't change things
that are predestined!
Seo-hae! You were so cool!
-But how are you feeling? Are you okay?
-Yes. I'm fine.
Gang Seo-hae.
What you said back there, is it true?
Was that bullet meant for you?
-Yes.
-Why didn't you tell me?
Then you knew about
getting taken to the Control Bureau?
What else have you been hiding from me?
I don't know everything.
-What do you know then?
-Why are you so upset?
What's with you all of a sudden?
You're hurting me.
Seon-jae.
Are you feeling okay?
I sometimes have a certain dream.
I saw a grave.
It was my grave.
That's where I found my diary.
Then I touched something.
I've been having that dream since then.
What dream is it?
It's about what's going to happen.
Yes.
On the last day,
I was in some kind of a church.
We were wearing wedding outfits,
and I got shot.
Sigma told you to choose.
-Mr. Han Tae-sul?
-Are you Sigma?
Is it the girl or the world? Pick one.
Choosing between you and
the world.
How did you know?
I met Sigma
while you were asleep.
What did he say?
He told me to make the uploader.
That's why I told you not to find Sigma.
You have to choose between the two.
-And last time…
-I made the uploader, right?
If you face that situation again,
don't make the uploader.
Even if you do,
I'll die anyway.
No.
I have another chance now.
We'll just all die again.
What happens to you
if I don't make the uploader?
Without the uploader,
nobody would be able
to come from the future.
-Then you--
-Promise me
you won't make it.
See all this money?
I ordered water.
If it arrives, put it in the basement.
I wrote down a list.
Medicine and guns.
Just buy all the guns you find.
Gas masks, hazmat suits, salt, sugar,
canned food, and chocolate. Got that?
What about ramyeon?
No, the smell is too strong.
It'll attract everyone.
Oh, and get lots of jerky.
-We already have enough.
-We do?
Anyway, we can't leave
for several months this time.
So buy everything you can.
And if there's any money left,
bring it back.
-Where are you going?
-Somewhere.
-Where?
-Somewhere!
Don't forget anything.
Hey. I heard Mr. Park survived
because he was in jail.
I heard it myself yesterday.
-I already knew that.
-Me too.
I know you didn't know.
I did.
-Why was he in jail, then?
-He killed someone.
Really? He's a total scumbag then.
You didn't know that?
-Who did he kill?
-I don't know.
Darn it.
He's pretty secretive
about his personal life.
Goodness.
Nothing has changed.
I'm going to jump!
Have you lost your mind?
Who's the jerk that sends you
three million won every month?
I told you, I don't know!
Are you having an affair with him?
What?
-Are you crazy?
-Am I crazy?
You total scumbag.
You should be working hard instead of
beating up your wife like a loser.
You need to learn a lesson.
I'll teach you a lesson, you jerk.
What crazy asshole threw a rock at me?
If I catch you, you're dead!
Darn it. This is all your fault!
What are you doing?
Just getting some fresh air.
I heard you did a good job
at the Control Bureau. Thanks.
No, it's nothing. I didn't do much.
I just ran around
and stayed there as a hostage.
But I was really scared
that you wouldn't come back.
About that last day, is it true?
Did you eavesdrop?
No, I just overheard from the other room.
Honestly, I don't get anything
about the uploader, downloader, or war.
What if you leave the country with me?
Then nothing will happen to you, right?
I told you. I can't leave.
Why? Because of Han Tae-sul?
Did something happen between you two?
Darn it. I knew it.
Jae-sun.
Over there.
What? The Hangang Bridge?
My house was there. A bunker below it.
So you had a river view.
The river was all dried up.
No way.
Everything you see over there
is going to burn and crumble down.
I'm not staying because of someone.
I'm staying because I want to.
Then let me ask you something.
Why does the war break out?
Sigma explodes a nuclear bomb.
But he came here through the uploader.
-Right.
-Then get rid of the uploader.
-If you get rid of the person who made--
-Hey.
You're not acting like yourself.
You never hesitate to do things.
Sis.
You like Han Tae-sul, right?
-Why?
-I feel uncomfortable.
You can't do this so suddenly.
Oh, I only brought two cups.
Do you want one?
What's with him?
There's something I didn't tell you.
I told you I met Sigma, right?
And it felt like he knew me.
-What do you mean?
-He asked me
if I remembered him.
So I tried to recall him,
but I can't remember him at all.
He could have just been bluffing.
I'm not sure.
What's "bluffing"?
Hey.
Bluffing is like acting tough.
Pretending to have something
when you don't have anything.
That's what you always do.
You pretend to know everything.
Hey, that's different.
I really do know everything.
You're so ridiculous.
Do I really…
have to choose between you and the world?
I hate stuff like that.
I hate making choices. I always order
everything on the menu at a restaurant.
Stop joking around.
Fine.
It's just that
I don't exactly know how I feel.
I know that I should kill Sigma
and stop the war,
but you'll disappear if I do.
I'd hate that.
What could it be?
Did he know that we were going
to go to that house?
Did he
leave us this drawing on purpose?
But the drawing's a bit strange.
Strange? How?
This part.
The buildings don't exist in the future.
What's this?
Sorry?
This.
Hang on. I've seen this before.
I didn't know
why Tae-san was carrying these around.
I saw the drawing when I was little,
and Sigma seemed to know me.
So he and I must have met before.
WOOHYUNG ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
So he's in one of those?
Yes.
We'll have to check all the photos, then.
-But are you okay with this?
-What do you mean?
You may want to hide your ugly past.
Hey, you even know
how to make jokes like that?
Who taught you?
I guess it was Jae-sun.
-Shut up.
-I don't have an ugly past.
I was born perfect.
All right. Fine.
WOOHYUNG ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
LET'S BE POLITE
What?
What is it? Did you find him?
No…
This girl. She used to have a crush on me.
I remember her. Song Ji-hye.
She made me 100 origami frogs, you know.
She's pretty. I guess you can ask her
to protect you now.
Come on, don't say stuff like that.
What?
That's enough, Seo-hae.
Wait a second.
You know, I've been thinking
scientifically.
I've been thinking scientifically
about that day.
The things that happened
while we were wandering
through time and space
weren't fixed events.
But I concluded that it was real.
What do you mean?
What we did at the beach…
We…
Hey. We only did that
because we thought it was the end.
What?
We were just saying goodbye.
Hang on.
Is that how you say goodbye in the future?
Are you all that passionate?
Do you have a different culture?
Or are you treating me like this
because I'm someone from the past?
-You said you're a misogamist.
-What does that have to do with this?
Do you even know what "misogamist" means?
Hey.
TAE-SUL FIXING A FALLING PLANE
I found it.
It's this, right?
TAE-SUL FIXING A FALLING PLANE
INVENTING A TIME MACHINE
TAE-SUL FOUNDING
THE BEST COMPANY IN KOREA
Who drew these?
There's no name.
-Don't you have another one?
-Who'd keep two of these stuff?
Right.
CLASS MAGAZINE
NANJEONG ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
-Is this the place?
-Yes.
Everything started here.
INTRODUCING MYSELF
DREAM JOB: A WRITER
FAVORITE COLOR: PURPLE
You like pink, don't you?
-Why do you ask?
-I mean…
Your diary was pink, your gun was pink,
and all the little accessories were pink.
There are only about 72 hours left
until the war breaks out.
But that's all I know
about you.
I've wasted my whole life
on useless things.
What have I done so far?
There's no time left.
My favorite food is bulgogi.
I already noticed that at the sauna.
And yours is tonkatsu.
What else? You should tell me about three.
Bananas, and…
Tteokbokki. My mom used to make it for me.
I see.
And your favorite song?
"Spring Day" by BTS.
-Who do you respect the most?
-My parents.
Who's your favorite person?
Cut it out. Why do you keep
asking such questions?
So I won't forget.
How may I help you?
Checking your old student record?
Please write your name
and year of graduation here.
Well, I didn't graduate here.
Then write the year you entered.
HAN TAE-SUL
-"Han Tae-sul"?
-Yes.
The Han Tae-sul?
Oh, my goodness! I'm such a big fan!
You look much more handsome in person.
-Thank you.
-I'm…
I mean,
the students in my class are huge fans.
At our science drawing contest,
everyone drew you fixing the plane.
Their dream jobs are all scientists now.
Is that so?
I thought only your brain was sexy,
but so is your mind and body as well.
Wow, that's a unique expression.
My goodness.
Hey, we don't have time.
-One of the students from 1991…
-Are you his girlfriend?
-No.
-Yes.
Could I take a photo with you?
-Of course.
-Thank you.
-Please don't upload it online, though.
-Oh, right.
I won't.
I can't believe this.
All right. One, two, three.
My goodness. Thank you so much.
I'll go find it right away.
No, it's fine.
Can I just go find it myself?
-Why…
-Well,
I'm not so confident about my old photos.
All right. Feel free to do so.
Thank you. Where's the archive room?
The end of the hallway
on the second floor.
All right.
Thank you.
Be quiet.
If you do that one more time, you're dead.
We found the suspect.
We got the location of Han Tae-sul.
-What about the girl?
-She's with him.
It's 20 minutes away.
Is it here?
Yes.
STUDENT RECORDS
YEARS 1990 - 1995
-Which class were you in?
-Class Four.
Do it gently, will you?
Just hurry up and find it.
What's with you?
"I thought only your brain was sexy,
but so is your mind and body as well."
-Is that what this is about?
-You were totally enjoying it.
Hey, I had to win her favor
to get in here.
STUDENT RECORD
HAN TAE-SUL
Han Tae-sul.
"He has good grades
but isn't focused in class.
He's selfish and lacks consideration
for his classmates."
-Is that really written there?
-You're still the same.
"Very bright yet lacks social abilities.
Needs more guidance
in participating in group activities."
Hang on.
STUDENT RECORD
SEO WON-JU
Tae-sul!
Han Tae-sul! It's me, Seo Won-ju!
Hey! Han Tae-sul!
Yes.
It's him.
You dung fly!
-You disgusting dung fly!
-You dung fly!
You dung fly.
I told you to stay away from me.
Gross!
Are you borrowing books from the library
to spread your germs?
Lord of the Flies?
You always read books like this.
That's so disgusting.
He got his spit all over that.
My mom told me that he spreads rabies.
Your dad sells dog meat, right?
-Gross!
-You dung fly!
Rabies can't be spread between people.
And Lord of the Flies isn't about insects.
It's on our recommended book list.
Haven't you read it?
Who's this jerk?
It was Han something.
-Han Tae-sul.
-You knew how to talk?
You were staring at the sky all the time,
so I thought you couldn't speak.
We'll let you go since you have
good grades. So get lost.
I can't do that.
I'm in charge of the library books
this week.
I have to get borrowed books back.
You stupid orphan.
Do you have a death wish?
What's this?
Sodium and water. Try mixing them.
Mix them.
Get lost
before I explode something bigger.
He really mixed it
just because I told him to?
We just learned that in science class.
We were told to be careful
since it could explode.
Thanks.
For what? I was just reviewing
what we learned today.
Return it by tomorrow.
Don't forget.
Your dad's here!
-You brat!
-He's sleeping.
Aren't you greeting your dad,
you little jerk?
-Hey! Come out here! You brat.
-What's with you?
-Jeez.
-Stop drinking, will you?
-Hey!
-Stop it!
Did you lock the door? Open up!
Can't you hear me? Open up, you brat!
You little brat!
-Don't do this.
-You useless jerk. Get up!
-You little… Come over here!
-Stop it!
You're dead!
What's that?
I bet you're going to become
someone great when you grow up.
How would you know that?
I can see the future.
The things I draw
always happen in real life.
You're going to save the world.
I saw it.
-What is it?
-You don't have to know.
You're always drawing pictures.
-It's not a drawing.
-Then what is it?
-It's a blueprint.
-A blueprint for what?
Oh, for traveling in time?
Yes. I can't do it now,
but when I grow up,
I'm going to make one for real.
Cool. Then can you go to the future, too?
No. Only to the past.
Why? Isn't it boring to go to the past?
You already know what happened.
I'm going to go to the past.
Tae-sul.
If you really succeed
in making a time machine,
can I ride it first?
-Jeez!
-Darn it!
-If I see you again, you're dead.
-That jerk.
-He's so annoying!
-Darn it!
-Hey, let's go.
-Does anyone still bully you?
-No.
-That's nice.
-Yes.
By the way, where did you get that bruise?
What?
Hey…
Can you teach me that thing
from last time? The explosion.
-Why?
-What?
Well…
I just want to review what we learned.
It was water and…
Sodium.
But where can I buy stuff like that?
Is it expensive?
I'm not sure. But there's a lot
stored in the science room.
Open the door. Open up, you jerk!
Hey, open this before I break it.
Open the door!
You brat. I won't let it slide
if you keep ignoring me like this.
Open up! Open the door!
Open the door, you brat.
Hey! You're dead!
Seo Won-ju.
Is Seo Won-ju absent?
-Han Tae-sul.
-Yes?
-You and Won-ju are close, right?
-No.
You always went home together.
He was just following me.
Mr. Yoon!
Study quietly in your seats.
Guys, gather round.
Did you hear?
My mom said Rabies' house was on fire.
Didn't you hear
some kind of explosion yesterday?
-Really?
-Yes!
His grandma and dad died.
All the dogs burned to death.
-Really?
-Yes.
I can see the future.
The things I draw
always happen in real life.
Boom!
It's quiet now.
I'm so happy that it's quiet.
What have you done?
You taught me.
I did the same thing you did.
Go away. Stay away from me.
Turn yourself in to the police.
Why?
I did the same thing you did.
How come you can do it and I can't?
You told me to do it!
When did I do that, you lunatic? Get lost!
What did you say?
Stay away from me. Get lost!
Those eyes…
You're no different from the other kids.
I'm going to kill everyone.
He said he'd be the first to ride it.
Ride what?
The uploader.
It was a trap.
Tae-sul! Come play with me!
Han Tae-sul!
That crazy jerk.
Come play with me!
Han Tae-sul!
Tae-sul! Come play with me!
Seo-hae.
I always wanted to do this
at a moment like this.
They're making a fuss about us!
Tae-sul did this all by himself.
Don't fight. You can't beat Sigma.
It's a gathering of people
who have control over Korea.
They're all from the future.
The advance team.
-Seo-hae, no.
-You're all playing into Sigma's hands.
Let's just go. There's another chance.
There isn't another chance.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park