ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Mom?
Dad.
Mom.
You shouldn't have come here today.
Why?
It's not my fault.
What do you mean?
He's here
right now.
Who?
Who's here?
Look who's here.
Finally we meet, Mr. Han Tae-sul.
What's going on here?
This? Ask this old lady here.
Hey, easy!
Hey, come on. Easy. Goodness.
Okay, all right. Jeez!
Let me take these off at least.
So it was you.
Long time no see.
Why did you bring him here?
Mr. Han here kept pestering me
for the cure like crazy.
I had no choice.
You ruined everything, you bastard.
Gosh. Sister Agnes.
We both did some bad stuff.
It's not like you can undo them
by praying.
Enough.
Let him out.
Enough, okay?
Come on! Don't do this to me.
We're like partners.
You, 101.
I told you I can't stand people
who don't keep their word.
You're the one who didn't keep
your promise, bastard.
Why didn't you send my wife and kid?
I kept my promise.
I found your wife and daughter
and took them to the uploader myself.
It was their choice whether to get on it.
Maybe
she doesn't want to see her daddy.
I swear,
I will kill you with my own hands.
Some people can't handle it
when they're treated with respect.
Sit down.
All right, thanks.
Oh, boy.
Sorry it got a little tense there
when we just met.
Han Tae-sul, it's very nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Why did you leave like that last time?
I was disappointed.
That wasn't the day for us to meet.
Then what about today?
You arranged this meeting?
Were you finally ready to meet me?
I came here to see Agnes.
I did think you might come here,
but you actually did.
Had I known,
I would have put on nicer clothes.
Why are you here?
To get the cure.
Oh, no.
I guess that girl got the injection.
You probably know this already,
but Agnes made that drug
to torture people from the future.
You see, she despises illegal entrants.
So why should we give you the cure?
Agnes, I guess he thought
we'd just hand it over.
On a side note,
I really don't understand
why one would make poison
and also create an antidote to it.
You shouldn't do something you'd regret
in the first place.
Why go to such lengths to undo it?
Right? Don't you agree?
In my opinion, people are fickle-minded
because they aren't honest
with themselves.
What do you think?
What? Why are you scoffing?
Then I suppose
you're very honest with yourself.
I know what kind of a person I am.
And I know exactly what I want.
So I don't change my mind easily,
and I never lie.
You can believe every word I say.
You start a war, but you don't lie?
That's right.
Is that so?
Then, what do you want from me?
Your uploader.
Can you finish coding the program?
Then I'll save the girl.
No, I won't.
Why not?
-Did you ask why?
-Yes, isn't it an enticing offer?
Because the world will fall to pieces
because of the uploader.
Wait.
To be precise, it's just the Korean
peninsula, not the entire world.
By the way, the world can't fall
to pieces? Why not?
Gosh, that crazy bastard.
People always swear
when they have nothing to say.
Hey, I'm not crazy.
Answer my question.
Why shouldn't the world end?
Well…
Where do I begin?
First off, normal people
wouldn't want the world to end.
You're wrong.
Go ask anyone you see on the streets.
"In front of you, there's a nuke button
to end the world. Will you press it?"
I bet so many people will say yes.
Look on the Internet.
You see countless people
who want the world to end.
And some people say this.
"There are too many people on this planet.
We must wipe out
75 percent of the world population."
Han Tae-sul.
I bet you're no different.
Why don't we do a little experiment?
Take it.
You know how to shoot a gun, right?
Just pull the trigger.
Shoot me.
If you kill me now,
you can save the world.
Shoot me.
Come on.
Do it.
Shoot me.
You just
pressed the nuclear button.
I bet this was your train of thought.
If you kill me,
my buddies here will kill you.
They'll also kill Agnes and 101.
You won't be able to get the cure.
So that girl will die too.
You made a choice that will end the world
just because of a girl.
But don't beat yourself up too much.
That's just how people are.
Even if everyone were to die,
they'd still put themselves,
their families, and money first.
Agnes is no exception.
She can't shoot me because
I'm taking good care of her mother.
Neither can 101
since he wants something from me.
I gave everyone a chance,
but not a single person chose
to save the world.
I'll be honest with you.
I really don't care about the future.
I mean, why would I…
You folks call me despicable.
But you're the despicable ones.
You're putting all the blame on me.
Then,
why did you kill Kim Dong-hyeon?
Tell me. You said you never lie.
-Kim Dong-hyeon was--
-What about my brother?
Why? What did he do wrong?
You said other people are putting
all the blame on you.
-As for your brother--
-You're the one
who's blaming others for what you did
with your sophistry.
Don't cut me off.
I didn't do anything to your brother.
I did yell at him to scare him a little,
but 101 and Agnes are the ones
who put him through hell.
They deceived him and used him.
I guess you haven't told him yet.
We're just business partners.
I'll fill you in on the details later.
You see, Kim Dong-hyeon betrayed me.
I turned a brokerage clerk into a magnate.
But then he tried to kill me.
I just took back what I had given him.
But come to think of it,
Agnes and 101 aren't the ones
who tortured your brother the most.
It's you, Han Tae-sul.
Okay, back to where we started.
Let me ask you again.
I was going to get the blueprint
from your brother.
But he got away, thanks to someone.
Can you make it again?
Get lost.
That's your answer?
You said you came here for the cure.
Take it.
It must be injected in a specific way.
If you're not sure, take Agnes too.
What are you up to?
I just like you.
My, I wasn't ready for that.
I mean it. I really like you.
You're so precious to me.
You're the last piece of the puzzle
for my plan.
That's why I invested in your research.
If it weren't for me, you'd still be stuck
in that shipping container,
running your physics engine by yourself.
Right?
Everything you've achieved so far…
You owe it all to me.
You should feel grateful once in a while.
Hey, 101.
What should I do with you?
I'm the one who dug you up,
so I can simply bury you back in.
I think you could still be useful,
so I'll spare you for now.
But if you betray me one more time,
I'll send your wife and daughter to you,
dead.
Got anything to say? Or any questions?
You sneaked into my place
and wrote "Don't look for your brother."
How did you do that?
IF YOU DO, YOU'LL DIE
I used spray paint.
I mean, how did you get in?
Oh.
You see,
I can get in anywhere.
That's it?
All right, then.
I'll see you again.
Oh, right. I didn't ask you this
because I wasn't sure.
Han Tae-sul.
Don't you remember me?
I guess you don't.
Sorry about that.
But aren't you guys going to flee?
There will be a war. If you stay here…
-It's all blocked anyway.
-What do you mean?
Illegal entrants get caught
if they go near the airport.
The Control Bureau, you know?
I sure know about them.
Damn it!
Doesn't that thing download people
from the future?
Why? Is it broken?
That scum Han Tae-sul
backed up the server.
Isn't that a good thing?
There will be no war. Am I wrong?
I guess I'm wrong.
Oh, because you have to shut down
your business?
That's none of your business.
I'm waiting for one more person.
Who?
Shut it, will you?
You're really getting on my nerves.
You need a license to own a firearm,
and minors can't possess guns.
Is that so? I didn't know.
-Hey.
-What?
Did Sigma or whatever his name is
also cross over through this thing?
-Yes.
-And he starts a war?
-That's right.
-Is Tae-sul that much of a genius?
Only he can fix this thing?
Yes, because he invented it.
He invented
both the uploader and the downloader.
So without him, there will be no Sigma.
Because the uploader
hasn't been invented yet. Right?
And there will be no war.
Well, I guess so.
By the way, why didn't you leave?
That visa was very expensive.
-I know I should.
-You'd better hurry.
Leave when flights can still take off.
I know.
But do people in the future
not use honorifics?
We do. Why do you ask?
Never mind. I was just curious.
Did you get the cure?
She seems to be asleep, but she's
in a state of temporal displacement.
She'll help us.
The receiver.
Get started right away.
Those of you who don't have
any business here, leave the room.
Get out, all of you.
Did you not hear me?
Get out, except for Tae-sul.
-Me too?
-Then do you want to do this?
I'll get out, then.
All right. Get it done quickly.
No funny business.
Guys, let's go.
Let's begin.
She's lost and wandering aimlessly.
She seems to be asleep right now,
but she's actually wandering around
different timelines.
I heard that. So what do we do?
We can't wake her up
by giving her the injection here.
Someone has to go to where she is
and administer the injection.
But it's too dangerous.
It will take a toll on you.
Wait, Tae-sul.
If you fail, you can't come back.
First, let's find out what's going on.
When we know more…
FOS decomposition. This is it, right?
Why are you doing all this?
I told you.
I don't want to lose her.
Inject 10ml, and the FOS proteins
will start breaking down.
Then you'll be transported.
To which point in time?
Sometime in her past.
Go there and find her.
Then what?
There's one shot for each of you.
There's no more, so you must pick
the right time to administer it.
Do it when you're as close
to the present time as you can be.
Okay?
If you lose this or make a mistake,
you won't be able to return.
You'll wander through
the space-time forever.
What? Like a wandering ghost?
What?
Where's number one?
That one failed.
My gosh.
What a relief.
Make a fist.
You know, right?
This is exactly what Sigma wants.
I deceived you my whole life.
I made you look like a lunatic
and put you in danger.
This morning, I even locked you up.
Will you still get this shot?
I have no other choice.
Even if you do this,
the future won't change, Tae-sul.
It's not about saving that girl.
Don't you get it?
For you, it's the future.
But for me, it's the past.
No matter how hard we try,
we can't change our past.
We can't undo our mistakes
or the things that we regret.
The future won't change, either.
Because your future is
a mirror image of your past.
It's your reflection in the mirror.
Even if you can't stand
what you see in the mirror,
and feel ashamed of it,
you can't change it.
Because that's who you are.
Tae-sul.
You can't beat the mirror
no matter how fast you are.
Seo-jin, I don't think I agree with you.
The mirror can't be faster than us.
Good luck.
Thanks.
Gang Seo-hae!
HONG U-HYEONG, KIM HYE-JIN
MY HAPPY FAMILY
GANG SEO-HAE
Hey, kids. Wait, just a second.
Strangers aren't allowed to come in.
Right, sorry. But I'm looking for someone.
A girl.
Her hair comes down to here.
She's quite tall.
And she's pretty. Have you seen her?
-No.
-No, we haven't.
Mister, are you not feeling well?
I'm fine.
You don't look well.
You should see a doctor.
What was that?
Seo-hae.
Seo-hae!
Seo-hae…
Seo-hae. Gang Seo-hae!
Oh, my.
-Look here! Look at me.
-Let's go to Mommy.
-Make a V!
-Let's go!
Make a V.
-Keep pedaling.
-Make a V!
Nice. Turn around.
Seo-hae…
Seo-hae.
Gang Seo-hae.
Get off of me.
Seo-hae…
What's wrong?
Gosh, I have a splitting headache.
Seo-hae, are you all right?
What are you doing here?
I came to save you.
This is…
It's very complicated.
But to put it simply, I risked my life
and traveled back in time to save you.
I'm so cool, right?
Thanks.
So what do we do now?
I'll take you home.
Your parents are waiting.
I'll take you to the present
and give you an antidote.
Just a second.
Hey, are you all right?
Are you okay?
MARRIED COUPLE IN THEIR 30S KILLED
WHILE HELPING TRAFFIC ACCIDENT VICTIMS
Where are we?
This is my childhood.
Something is wrong.
REST IN PEACE, FATHER AND MOTHER
From now on, I'll be your mom and dad.
I'll pack your lunch for school
every morning.
With your favorites.
Ham and anchovies.
I can make all those things.
Nothing's changed.
My gosh.
This must be so hard for you.
You must stay strong
for your little brother
so your late father can rest in peace.
Hey, Tae-san.
The thing is…
I feel horrible bringing this up
on a day like this.
-Gosh, how do I begin…
-You can tell me.
Before your dad passed away,
he borrowed some money from me.
That's a lie.
He's lying to take
the insurance money from us.
Tae-san, don't listen to that jerk.
He's trying to dupe you.
Get yourself together. They can't see us.
PROMISSORY
BORROWER: HAN DONG-MIN
5 MILLION WON
Let's get out of here.
Yes, teacher.
I'll go to a vocational high school.
I won't go to college.
I'm sorry.
Going well?
I'll tell him when he comes back.
Come on.
Mr. Han Tae-sul will never see you again
if he finds out what you did
to Han Tae-san.
It's all your fault.
You promised that we'd go to Tae-sul
together if I got Tae-san out.
But what did you do?
You stole the safe and everything else.
I nearly died because of you.
It's not like I did well because of you.
You let Han Tae-san slip away.
So Sigma got all angry,
and I almost died because of it.
I'd say we're even.
We all did some bad things.
You stuck-up, don't talk like
you've never dirtied your hands.
Just wrap that up well,
and don't look at me like that.
You disobeyed orders, committed theft,
conducted unauthorized interrogation,
lost a suspect, used your gun,
and left the office without permission.
Impressive.
Got anything to say?
-Am I one of the people who came back?
-What?
That's what 811 told me.
That I took the uploader from the future…
Hyeon-gi, I told you.
We don't believe what
illegal entrants say. She lied to you.
Is 811
really Lieutenant Gang's daughter?
She is. That we've verified.
Looks like 811 already met
Lieutenant Gang and his wife.
The day we captured the girl,
Lieutenant Gang's wife was there.
And we have security footage
that shows Han Tae-sul
visiting his home a few days ago.
I sent a few agents over,
but they lost him after a fight.
We're trying to track down
the entire family.
Based on what we've got so far,
it doesn't seem like 811 ended up
at your place by coincidence.
There's a chance that
Lieutenant Gang gave her your address
before she got on the uploader
in the future.
It must've been the perfect place for her
to get a gun and a car
upon her arrival in the present.
Did you always keep a gun at home?
Yes.
This is why you have to be careful
of those who know you well.
The higher-ups are fuming mad
that you let a suspect get away.
A letter of apology won't be enough.
Stay home until I call you.
Sir.
You can return to work
when things die down.
-Return your gun and radio.
-Sir!
Now.
Go get some rest.
CONTROL BUREAU TEAM 7 CHIEF
Hey.
It's been a while, sir.
Why didn't you give me a heads-up?
I was just stopping by. How did it go?
I took care of it
as per your instructions.
Good.
Will that be sufficient though?
Of course.
CHO CHAN-HYEOK
EXPATRIATE LIST
GANG SEO-HAE
DETAILS
1ST HALF OF 2011
Was his name Jung Hyeon-gi?
You see, people just believe
what they want to believe.
Rather than admitting that his mother died
while he was neglecting her out of anger…
Seeking revenge is easier
than living with guilt.
I'm sure he wants to blame
someone else, you know?
You're truly impressive.
Oh, come on.
So Han Tae-sul is taken care of.
We've dealt with Jung Hyeon-gi as well.
Then do we just wait now?
We just need to build the uploader now.
Tell everyone I want to say goodbye
in person before I leave.
Yes, sir.
Tae-sul, Mom and Dad are in heaven now.
They passed away after saving many lives,
so I'm sure they're in heaven now.
If we do good deeds and never hurt others,
we'll meet them again.
No.
What?
Tae-san, time is irreversible.
The second law of thermodynamics.
In a thermally isolated system,
the entropy can never decrease.
So natural processes
and the past-future asymmetry…
Anyway, we can't see Mom and Dad again.
We'll never see them again.
You said we must return to 2020.
Why are we lost in your past?
I have no idea what's going on either.
There must've been a mix-up.
We just keep moving forward
in time, right?
Don't let it get to you.
You've already been through this once,
so just let it go.
Okay.
Lie on my lap.
Let's sleep here tonight.
This is still a house, you know.
Looks like this used to be
someone's bedroom.
See? There's wallpaper on the wall.
-What about the blue part?
-That's easy.
If you draw these lines,
it's like subtracting the square
from the circle.
How?
First, draw this. Then like this.
So what's the answer?
If we say the radius is 10cm,
it should be 228cm².
You're the smartest person I know.
-Are you cold?
-Yes.
I've never seen him cry before.
He never cried in front of me.
Tae-sul, we can't stay here.
I know that door scares you.
We don't know what we'll encounter next.
I saw my past too.
My mom, dad, and the war.
Be prepared.
That's all you can do.
CONGRATULATIONS
QUANTUM & TIME LISTED ON NASDAQ
What happened on this day?
This is the day my brother died.
My gosh.
Let's become rich, Tae-sul.
I provided this guy with room and board
all through college.
Turns out, it wasn't all for nothing.
What? You guys lived together?
I even used to hand-wash
this jerk's underwear.
In that shipping container
with no heating.
I did that in the middle of winter
and ended up with hand eczema.
Just so Tae-sul could focus
on his research
without having to worry about anything.
Hey, you prick.
You'd better be good to me.
He's about to cry.
I'm serious.
-Where are you going?
-A lady over there
keeps staring at me, and I'm curious.
I should go talk to her.
So just enjoy your dinner, you two.
Hey, Seung-bok! Eddy Kim.
What was that about?
10 MISSED CALLS
TAE-SAN
Jeez…
Wasn't that your brother earlier?
Yes.
Looks like he got worse
than before he was hospitalized.
Yes, I wonder if it's the alcohol.
He's usually okay
but acts strange when he drinks.
He goes on about the future,
how our phones are tapped, and so on.
He's still like that?
Many people suffer from
stress-induced delusional disorder.
He should get therapy again.
Gosh, I'm so annoyed.
But it's still nice to have a brother.
I was always so bored
since I'm an only child.
There's nothing nice about it.
It's worse than not having one
since we're so different.
Lately, I'd rather talk to a stranger.
Tae-san thinks that
he practically raised me.
Of course,
I'm grateful for everything he did for me.
But he goes on about what he did for me
and says that I owe it all to him.
That annoys me.
Now that his brother is successful,
I guess he feels
it's unfair that he made
all those sacrifices for me.
That's just your past. It's not you.
Crazy jerk.
-I said, it's not you.
-It is me.
-That prick is me.
-How was I earlier?
I hated him from the beginning.
He's mean and he thinks
he's the most pitiful person in the world.
He thinks he's better than everyone else.
-Stop.
-It's not Sigma's fault.
Because of that jerk,
the nuke went off and killed everyone.
-That is not true.
-I am that jerk!
Tae-sul.
Tae-sul!
Han Tae-sul!
What is this?
Tae-sul, wake up.
Wake up!
Get up. Hey, get up.
Get up already!
Let's go. Come on.
I don't want to see it anymore.
Do you know what we'll see
once we walk through that door?
My brother's funeral.
And me turning into a rich bastard
who hurts everyone around him.
I've never been happy in my life.
Not even a single day.
You can go alone.
How can you not have happy memories?
I lived on rotten canned foods
in a bunker after the war,
but I have happy memories.
After the war,
my dad took me to school every March.
The school was in ruins, but I packed
lunch and my backpack to go there.
It was the one day
I could put my worries to rest
and just play with my dad
in the empty classroom.
And I had so much fun.
Right. Once, I went to the stadium
where BTS had their last concert.
There was a huge banner.
My dad and I struggled
to carry it back to our bunker.
It was too big,
so we had to hang it outside.
In the future, the sky is very clear.
There are no lights,
so you can see all the stars at night.
Have you ever seen the Leonids?
Once, I read in a book that
a comet passes through
the constellation Leo every 32 years.
Whenever that happens,
you see a prolific meteor shower.
There was one in 1998, so no one
yet saw the meteor shower in 2030.
Except for me.
I saw it all night, on top of the bunker.
It was so beautiful.
We all have trivial but happy memories.
That's what keeps us going.
I'm sure you have some too.
So try to recall them.
Tae-sul.
Tae-sul!
The sea?
It's the West Sea.
But what point in time?
Over there.
That's my company's training center.
I told them to build it here
because I love this area.
It was scheduled to go up by this year,
and it's all done.
This is the present. We're almost there.
-So what do we do now?
-We'll get the antidote and go back.
Seo-hae, when we go back,
you'll see your dad there.
Really? My dad is there?
How did you bring him over?
Did he believe you? What about Mom?
Yes, he believed everything I told him.
And your mother is waiting for you
at your place.
You look just like your mother.
And you obviously got
your personality from your dad.
Thanks for coming to get me.
You should go back first
since you came in here first.
-What about you?
-I'll get the shot after you.
What?
Nothing.
I'll begin now.
I feel dizzy.
You should get one too.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, Seo-hae.
For what?
Hey.
I guess it broke along the way.
Listen, Seo-hae.
When you return, you'll wake up
at Asia Mart. You know my place.
You know how to get there, right?
You can stay there.
If you're not sure about anything,
Sun will help you.
-And your parents are there too.
-How could you…
There will be a stranger as well.
That's Kim Seo-jin.
She came from the future
through the uploader, just like you.
She must know some things about Sigma.
Seo-hae.
You have to catch Sigma.
You can do it.
I've been racking my smart brain,
and you should be the one who goes back.
They need you more than me
to save the world.
No one's waiting
for me to come back anyway.
You know that everyone hates me.
Seo-hae.
Stop being so serious all the time.
Laugh and smile more often.
What about Tae-sul?
What happened?
We only had one vial.
You jerk.
Can you hear me?
You can hear my voice, right?
Wake up.
Wake up at once.
I will kill you. Wake up!
How could you say
no one's waiting for you?
I'm waiting for you.
Wake up.
I said, wake up!
You fool, wake up.
You're not going to die today.
You woke up.
Tae-san?
I told you
that we'd meet again.
Tae-sul, over here!
Pass me the ball. Over here!
What happened?
We share the same past
because we're brothers.
I told you I'd be hiding in a place
where no one could find.
So you were here all this time?
Tae-sul.
Tae-san.
I'm sorry. It was all my fault.
I'm sorry for everything.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I said it's okay.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry…
Hey, why are you sorry?
I should be the one saying sorry.
I should've been a better brother to you.
I'm really sorry.
I'm so proud of you
for everything you've accomplished.
Thank you.
Tae-san…
Oh, right.
I brought this with me
in case I'd need it.
I guess now's the time.
Tae-san.
Hold on.
Tae-sul, listen carefully.
You shouldn't be here.
Well, I think this will be the last time
we see each other.
We won't cross paths like this again.
Tae-sul, you have to remember this.
Even when you couldn't see me,
I was always right by your side.
And that won't change.
So when you're lonely, stressed,
or exhausted,
just look around you, and I'll be there.
Now, get going.
I love you.
I've come a long way to meet you.
It was such a difficult
and terrifying journey.
Please wake up.
You're smart.
You can do anything, so please…
Figure out a way to come back.
I miss you.
Tae-sul.
Did you just say
you miss me?
Have you lost your mind? Got a death wish?
No, I don't want to die. Sorry.
I thought you were dead!
You owe me a debt.
I can change the future.
And it's already changing.
Then get rid of the uploader.
-If you get rid of the person who made--
-Hey.
You total scumbag.
Did he leave us this drawing on purpose?
But the drawing's a bit strange.
Everything started here.
We found the suspect.
We got the location of Han Tae-sul.
-Who drew these?
-There's no name.
Han Tae-sul!
It's him.
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi