♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 24=
What’s wrong with her?
She’s injured.
How?
Qingqing.
Hand off.
It’s time to give her medicine.
Leave it to the General.
Listen to Long Yan.
Then take good care of her.
Don’t need your advice.
Don’t try to take advantage of her.
What did you say?
I said,
do not try to take advantage of her.
General, I’ll see this gentleman out.
Qingqing.
What’s wrong with your forehead?
It’s fine.
Didn’t you hear what she said?
I took advantage of Qingqing.
When did she have the right
to judge me and my Qingqing?
Your Qingqing?
Did she accept you?
She didn’t turn me down.
So maybe
she did.
You think so?
How long haven’t you met?
We...
You’re busy.
She’s idle but she never went to you.
I’m not optimistic about it.
I don’t believe what you said.
Besides,
you said I’m a traveling physician.
Should I say you’re the lord
of Luofeng Pavilion?
Still hurts?
You did come as soon as
the meteor mark disappeared.
Tell me who hurt you.
No one.
I will find him
and make sure he learns
the consequence of hurting my staff.
Actually,
it’s me.
You?
Why did you do that?
Because the mark was ugly.
It scared people off.
And spells couldn’t hide it.
It really bothered me when I saw it.
So I decided to cut it off.
You fool.
Forehead is where the third eye is
for our kind.
The meteor mark is a defect
of your beauty.
But what you did
will only weaken your power.
That is so reckless.
I don’t care about the power,
or intend to become an immortal.
All I know is
that beauty is significant.
I don’t want anybody to dislike me.
Are you an idiot or what?
Who would dislike you for that?
Yes.
I’m an idiot and fool.
I’m stupid.
So beauty is the last thing I got.
Without that,
what do I have?
If...
If you don’t like it,
leave me alone.
Go.
Always like that. Disappear in a puff.
Goodbye.
A bird’s brain is small.
I didn’t think much.
Were it not for you,
would I even do that?
Didn’t you leave?
I went to tell Bingxing
to stop looking for the attacker
and get this for you by the way.
You’re no longer angry with me?
What’s the point of being angry?
Now focus on how to prevent the scar.
(Dongluo Hall)
Your Highness,
the Seven-Gem Cutlass has...
It has been found by them.
Get up.
Are you done?
Yes.
A man who can’t even hide something
doesn’t deserve a life.
Calm down, Your Highness.
How?
If Feng Chenyue is chopped into pieces.
Can you do it?
Feng Chenyue and her Sergeant At Arms
are tough.
We should form a long-term plan.
Get up and turn around.
Yes.
I don’t want to do this.
You promised you’d never question me,
remember?
When I told you to kill someone,
you never dissented.
Forgive me for my incompetence.
Rui said Feng Chenyue and you
were childhood friends.
Is it true?
Yes.
Why didn’t you tell me?
Feng Chenyue and I
are no longer friends, but foes.
So, I didn’t report it to Your Highness.
I think you want reconciliation.
Is your heart soft?
Of course not.
Come here.
Come.
You remember who your foe
and your savior are, right?
I’ll always be in your debt.
Your Highness is my savior.
Look.
How bright the moon is tonight.
I’m a just man.
The punishment is this.
It’s full moon tonight.
So for the Life-saving Pill,
come and get it tomorrow.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Well,
what’s that physician’s name?
Which physician?
The one who took advantage of Qingqing.
He is Xue Qianxun,
a good man.
Sounds like
a traveling physician’s name.
How is he to Qingqing?
Trust me, General Feng.
His love to Qingqing is real.
If he ever mistreats Qingqing,
I’ll chop his arms off.
Jin.
Jin, what’s wrong with you?
I don’t need your concern.
What happened?
You’re wounded.
Leave me alone.
I’m just a maid.
Thank you for your concern.
Jin.
Leave me alone.
(General’s Mansion)
This lady’s pulse is messy.
Forgive me for my incompetence.
I can’t tell what disease this is.
Is there a way
to relieve her pain?
Then I’ll make some
Pain Numbing Soup for her
to kill the pain.
Thank you, Physician Lin.
I’m afraid she’s not ill,
but poisoned.
Poisoned?
The symptoms on her body
match my father’s description.
It’s a poison from Dongluo.
Mandrake.
Right.
Once poisoned,
you have to take in more
to relieve the pain.
Yes.
It’s a rare poison.
How were you poisoned?
General, it’s time for dinner.
You must stay strong.
Jin.
You’re awake.
You haven’t recovered yet.
None of your business.
Jin, you’re not ill.
You’re poisoned by Mandrake.
I don’t understand what you’re saying.
Stay here. I’ll find the cure.
I’m from Dongluo.
You should stay away from me.
You gave me this.
(Feng)
I’ve been keeping the commanding badge
in it.
(Jin)
Over the last years,
I’ve been carrying it with me
wherever I go.
When he took us there,
we found nothing but this.
(Feng)
The Fengs’ commanding badge.
Was it a fake?
Answer me. Do you know
that seven years ago,
my father was killed by your army
at Tiger’s Howl Valley?
Seven years ago?
We were not in war.
But my father’s death is a fact.
My wound is fully healed.
Thank you for your treatment.
I must go.
Jin.
Don’t take Mandrake again.
It stops the pain temporarily,
but will worsen it.
(Dongluo Hall)
You must hate me so much.
I dare not.
I just hope you learn
the lesson.
I deserve the punishment.
You can only get the Life-saving Pills
from me.
Remember?
I will not forget.
Thank you, Your Highness.
I’ll leave you.
(Dongluo Hall)
Your Highness.
Mr. Guo,
when can I see
Feng Chenyue’s head off her body?
My patience is running out.
If we kill a general in the capital,
His Majesty will be alerted.
By then,
it’ll lead to us
and cause trouble.
Since she’s a general,
it is her fate
to die on the battlefield.
Don’t you agree?
Nanzhao State is attacking.
I’m thinking the South Army
isn’t as solid as the Feng Army.
You’re not ill.
You’re poisoned by Mandrake.
Mandrake?
(Feng)
I’ve been keeping the commanding badge
in it.
(Jin)
I’ve been carrying it over the years
wherever I go.
Was the badge
really the Fengs’ commanding badge?
This is the eldest prince.
When he took us there,
we found nothing but this.
(Feng)
The Fengs’ commanding badge.
Father,
were you really killed by the Fengs?
Don’t take Mandrake again.
It stops the pain temporarily,
but will worsen it.
Why does the pill have to go down
with liquor, instead of water?
What if it’s put in water?
Smells good.
Why?
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, Nanzhao State attacks.
I just learned from the emergency report
that General Lin was killed in action.
Please assign
another commanding general.
Who do you think we should assign?
I volunteer to go to the south now.
(General’s Mansion)
Lu Zheng.
I’ll go with you.
I’m granted the position
as the Military Supervisor of the south.
And His Majesty permitted Deputy Zhao
to lead reinforcements to the south.
Uncle Zhao is also going?
Fantastic.
He’ll give a pair of wings to our army.
You just came back
for a few peaceful days.
Why would you go back to battlefield?
I’ll go
wherever you go.
We’ll be together forever.
Good.
We will win the war.
I’ll meet with someone.
Be careful.
Don’t worry.
(Jin)
Jin.
Stop.
It’s really you.
You look much better.
Take care
in Nanzhao.
Alright.
I’m not worried about you.
It’s a warning.
What do you mean?
That’s all I can tell you.
Good luck to you.
Dangers are lurking in Nanzhao.
I want you to peel your eyes.
Yes.
We just arrived.
It’s not wise to attack
with the situation unclear.
In wars, speed is the key.
If we attack now,
I’m sure we’ll catch them by surprise.
Uncle Zhao, what’s your opinion?
I came all the way from the north
not to sit on the bench.
I surely want to stretch my limbs,
so go!
Alright.
But take it easy.
If we burn their provisions
and provender,
their men and horses will starve
and in the end withdraw.
We adopted the tactic on Dongluo Army.
But the south is ample with
wild fruits and grass, I’m afraid...
Don’t worry. I’ll poison the woods.
The plants will wither in three days
and become inedible.
Good idea. Move out.
Let’s go.
Keep firing.
Fire! The provisions are on fire!
Put it out! Hurry!
Hurry. Hurry.
General, the provisions are burnt.
We can withdraw now.
General.
Fall back!
Charge!
Split up in two.
Come this way.
Yes. Go!
Get them!
-Come on!
-Don’t let her run away.
-Go!
-Faster!
Long Yan,
lead the men to fight a way out!
Gao Yang!
General, go!
Chenyue!
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
Is it you,
Dragon King?
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪