♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 23=
(Puer tea)
Just now,
you dodged it fast.
So I said your skills
aren’t sharp enough.
After all these years,
your aim is still so bad.
Seems that
you’re not doing so well
in the underworld.
My aim is bad?
You might be the only person
who dares to say that
in the four nations.
Really?
When we first met,
I learnt how good you were.
Have you forgotten?
You came to Wind City from Dongluo
all by yourself.
You look so thin.
And you?
What brings you here?
And you know the Crown Prince.
It seems you’re
much smarter than before.
Do you mean I was foolish?
Who was it that couldn’t unlock
the labyrinth casket
and asked for my help?
It’s getting late.
Have dinner with me.
No, thanks.
I have business to attend to today.
-Tomorrow...
See you tomorrow.
At noon
and here.
Prime Minister.
Prince Yun, His Majesty is delighted
that you come
to his birthday celebration
and orders me to welcome you.
When His Majesty sees my gift
on the banquet,
he’ll be exhilarated.
For this precious gift,
I ordered my guards
to watch it around the clock,
in case anyone steals it.
Prince Yun, you’re in Wind City now.
Please wait for His Majesty’s
birthday banquet.
Sure.
Please.
Your Majesty,
Dongluo Crown Prince has
a priceless gift
for your birthday.
It’s a cutlass decorated with gems.
It’s said to be the treasure of
the previous dynasty.
The treasure of the previous dynasty?
So seven years ago,
the winner of the treasure hunt
at Tiger’s Howl Valley
was Dongluo State.
Your Majesty, is it
the Seven-Gem Cutlass that marks
the sovereignty over the world?
Well it seems
Dongluo State has come with sincerity.
They’re our guests.
As the super power of the world,
we must make them feel at home.
Throw a grand welcoming banquet.
All high-rank officials must attend.
Your Majesty,
I’m afraid
I’d better not attend the banquet.
General Feng,
are your defying His Majesty’s order?
General Feng wounded
the Crown Prince’s eye.
He’ll be irritated
to see General Feng.
Your Majesty are so wise.
(Yue)
Your Grace,
General Feng seeks your audience.
Invite her in.
She can come without report next time.
Yes.
Your Grace.
I kept my promise to visit you.
It’s nice of you to keep your promise.
Take a seat.
(Yue)
Labyrinth casket?
Yes, you know it?
Your Grace,
how did you get it?
My maid Jin made it.
Jin?
Your Grace, where is she?
Can I see her?
Jin...
She went to Xingyuan Pastry
to buy bean paste cakes.
Look, she’s back.
General Feng, you know my maid?
General Feng?
You...
You’re General Feng
who defeated Dongluo?
Jin,
you came to Wind City from Dongluo
with Consort Rui?
Aren’t you a wanderer?
That is my dream.
You can be a general.
So can I be a maid.
That’s the difference between
reality and dream.
Jin, you know General Feng?
I’m Jin. Pleasure, General Feng.
I didn’t know you’re the lady general.
If I offended you, please forgive me.
Jin,
we’re friends. No need to apologize.
I’m sorry I had to lie to you.
But it was my father’s order.
Jin,
no matter what,
our friendship is not changed.
You’ve not changed, General Feng.
But I have.
I’ll leave you to it.
You...
You two...
Your Grace,
she’s my childhood friend.
(Yue)
Your Highness.
It’s not full moon now.
The agony strikes early this time.
Is anything bothering you?
I feel guilty about not being able
to blind Feng Chenyue’s eyes.
It’s not like you.
There are things you cannot complete?
I...
I didn’t do my best.
I don’t know why.
But from your looks, I can feel
you’re hiding something from me.
I’m sorry, Your Highness.
Please punish me.
It’s not a big deal.
Who killed your father?
The Fengs.
Who wounded my eye?
Also the Fengs.
Take it.
Thank you, Your Highness.
You’re welcome.
I’ll stay more days
for the birthday banquet.
In the meantime,
I need your cooperation
to get the Fengs’ commanding badge.
You know how.
Your Highness and Feng Chenyue
don’t see eye to eye.
Everybody in Wind City knows it.
To frame her with her badge
doesn’t seem a good idea.
If I’m right,
this is the first time you
question me.
Forgive me, Your Highness.
I’ll spare you this time.
But never...
Never...
Never do it again, alright?
Yes.
All I need is for Feng Chenyue
to be investigated.
I have hands in the Ministry of Justice.
Do you think she can get out?
No, I don’t think so.
What do you think?
I’ll do as told, Your Highness.
Tell Rui to invite Feng Chenyue over.
Yes.
Let them talk.
(Yue)
Why did they kill my father?
(Feng)
Remember the hatred.
(Yue)
(General’s Mansion)
That’s it.
Ice-cold face, no expression.
My suitor? It’s a lie.
The saying is right.
I’d rather believe there are ghosts
than words coming out of a man’s mouth.
Fortunately, I didn’t take it seriously.
Or, my pure feelings
would be hurt again.
I’ll make you sorry.
Don’t dodge.
Face it.
Stay put.
I’m sure the stone can hit you.
Also missed.
Even the stone stands in my way.
Hey, what are you looking at?
I didn’t ask you to look at my meteor mark.
Your Grace, it’s dark.
I should leave.
Are you leaving so soon?
Have another cup of tea.
No thanks. I’ll come on another day.
Alright.
General Feng, it’s unintentional.
General Feng, are you burnt?
Summon a physician.
I’m fine. There’s no need.
Don’t call the physician.
The tea is boiling hot.
Maybe you’re burnt.
Please undress and check it.
Right. Right.
Jin, go with her.
Yes.
I’m fine, really.
Just go with her.
General, this way.
(General’s Mansion)
(Feng)
General Feng,
let me apply the balm for you.
I can do it.
You’re a general. I’m a maid.
Please let me do my job.
Jin,
can you stop acting like a stranger?
I’m from Dongluo.
You should keep safe distance from me.
The war is over.
You and I are friends for years.
It doesn’t matter.
You’re a general.
I’m a maid.
The rank keeps us apart.
But your father
was also a general in Dongluo.
Jin,
why did you leave your home
to be a maid here?
My father died in the war.
I’m homeless now.
I’m sorry.
General, your clothes are dry.
Let me help you dress up.
There, General.
(Feng)
Take the badge.
You can come to
my mansion to visit at anytime
with this.
(Feng)
I’m just a maid too humble
to step in the General’s Mansion.
Please take it back, General.
I’ll leave you.
Qingqing,
look what I have for you.
Bean paste cakes, osmanthus cakes
and pumpkin cakes,
all your favorites.
What’s up?
Nothing.
Nothing?
You didn’t ever look at
your favorite cakes.
Tell me. What’s wrong?
Let me ask you.
If you detest something
that you can’t get rid of,
what will you do?
Something you detest
but can’t get rid of.
What is it?
It’s...
Anyway, if you’re stuck with it
and can’t get rid of it,
what will you do?
This is
a difficult question.
Let me see.
I’ll put it in this way.
If you have tails in combat,
and the battle is terribly fierce,
the best way out
is to blow the enemies
with thunder cannon.
But the thunder cannon
will cause casualties on your side too.
If you were commanding,
would you use it?
For victory, I’d have to.
Right.
On the battlefield,
victory is the only goal.
Better a little loss than a long fight.
So cut the losses.
Your Highness.
(Dongluo Hall)
We got it.
Great.
Any casualties?
Your Majesty,
Dongluo Crown Prince
was slightly wounded
but many of his guards were killed.
And,
the Seven-Gem Cutlass to Your Majesty
is stolen.
Dongluo Crown Prince is attacked
in the capital.
Send as many men as needed
and find out the truth.
Yes.
Mr. Guo of Justice
is investigating in Dongluo Hall.
I’ll supervise it personally.
Your Majesty.
Any leads?
Your Majesty, look.
Your Majesty,
these men
were the Crown Prince’s personal guards.
He must have grabbed
the badge on the assassin
before being killed.
(Feng)
This is...
The Fengs’ commanding badge?
Your Majesty.
It’s...
Impossible.
General Feng,
take a look.
Feng Chenyue, look closer.
Is this your commanding badge?
In fact the jade badge...
What else can you say, General Feng?
The evidence is solid.
Your Majesty,
are you going to protect her?
General Feng,
is this your commanding badge?
Your Majesty,
it does belong to my family.
Feng Chenyue,
now that you admit it’s your badge,
why did you steal the Seven-Gem Cutlass?
Do you want to be
the ruler of the world?
Watch your tongue, Mr. Guo.
I said the badge belongs to my family.
But I never said it’s
the commanding badge.
Feng Chenyue,
I can’t believe you’re still
trying to justify yourself.
First,
it’s not the commanding badge.
Second,
someone must have stolen it
and framed me for it.
How innocent you are.
What is it if it’s not
your commanding badge?
You don’t believe her blatant lies,
do you, Your Majesty?
General Feng,
do you have proof?
Please come to my mansion,
and you’ll see the proof.
(General’s Mansion)
Your Majesty, just a moment.
(Feng)
Please take a look, Your Majesty.
So many identical jade badges.
Your Majesty,
since there are so many,
it can’t be the Fengs’ commanding badge.
Your Majesty,
when my father was alive,
each time we returned from the border,
there were men
trying to steal the badge.
So I ordered
these fakes to be made for the thieves.
They’ll stop when they get it.
These jade badges
are made specially
for the thieves with sinister motives.
Beyond the fine jade they’re made of,
the badges are worthless,
not to mention the commanding badge.
Prince Yun,
these can perfectly
prove General Feng’s innocence.
I agree that someone framed her.
Prince Yun,
do you agree?
Framed soon after returning,
it seems you have many foes.
When was I ever
afraid of foes?
One
at a time,
I’ll finish them off.
Really?
General Feng, I swear
I’ll find the truth
and the man who is so bold
to frame you.
Yes.
And the cutlass, find it.
Your Majesty,
I’ve searched Dongluo Hall.
Though the thieves’ footsteps are messy,
I can tell them apart.
But what’s odd is
there are no footsteps leaving
across the wall,
which means
the thieves didn’t escape
with the cutlass.
So you mean...
The cutlass is still in the hall.
Find it.
Take men to find it.
Yes, Your Majesty.
(General’s Mansion)
It’s your fault. It’s your fault.
Better a little loss than a long fight.
So cut the losses.
Yeah.
Better a little loss than a long fight.
Today,
I have to remove you.
My Lord, are you alright?
Qingqing is in danger.
Qingqing, Qingqing.
Qingqing.
Who hurt you?
It’s you.
You won’t
be scared off by it again.
Who is it?
My Lord,
I’ve searched miles around here.
No signs of demons,
immortals or beasts.
Keep searching.
Anyone who came left a trace.
I will find the attacker.
Yes.
Qingqing.
Let her go.
General.
This gentleman and Qingqing
love each other.
When did it happen?
How come you know and I don’t?
You were busy with work lately, so...
So this makes sense?
He’s a traveling physician
and is curing Qingqing.
What’s wrong with her?
She’s injured.
How?
Qingqing.
Hand off.
It’s time to give her medicine.
Leave it to the General.
Listen to Long Yan.
Then take good care of her.
Don’t need your advice.
Don’t try to take advantage of her.
What did you say?
I said,
do not try to take advantage of her.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪