Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 11
Let's analyze the identity
of this monster first.
Is it a Soul Master or a Soul Beast?
I fought with it yesterday,
and I'm sure
that it was a human form.
So we can rule out
the possibility of its being a Soul Beast.
Then his identity should be
a Soul Master.
A Soul Master who is
against Ma Hong Jun's family.
Why does he remain in the Nightfire Village?
Not only prolonging his stay
in the Nightfire Village,
but he also kept trying to approach Ma Hong Jun.
The village head said that the fire
had burnt Ma Hong Jun's father to death.
They buried him.
Yesterday,
when I went to the cemetery,
there wasn't any new grave.
There was no sign of the surrounding
being dug up.
It means the village head lied to us.
I can't help but think of a possibility.
What's that?
This fire
was just an accident.
But it happened to be discovered
by an outsider
and reported to our school.
The village head doesn't want
more attention on this incident.
Because there's no monster
in the first place.
He's not a monster!
He is my father.
What?
How can a human become a monster?
I'm Tang San.
He's Dai Mu Bai.
Ou Si Ke.
And she's Zhu Zhu Qing.
We are from Shi Lan Ke School,
and we are here to help you.
If you agree,
we can even help your dad.
Can you save him?
We will do our best.
But you must tell us the truth.
I was asleep
that night.
When I was startled,
my dad had turned into that.
He couldn't even recognize me.
Then, the village head rushed over
and saved me out of the fire.
I cried out for my dad.
But he didn't seem to get it.
Instead, he escaped.
Your dad was a Soul Master?
I don't know.
But how did he turn out like that?
I really don't know.
So why were you hiding here?
The village head allowed me
to take shelter here.
He said...
He couldn't let you know the truth.
Otherwise...
You will kill my dad.
The village head knows
where your dad is hiding?
He doesn't know.
He is searching for my dad too.
We already know
where your dad is hiding.
We'll go there immediately
and find out how we can help him.
Don't worry.
I promise
we will never hurt him.
I'm going with you.
Bring Ma Hong Jun along.
That might lure his father out.
Won't it be dangerous?
I'm not afraid.
Maybe he is about to regain consciousness.
Maybe
he will be fine when I wake him up.
Let's bring him with us.
I'm quick on my feet.
If there's any threat,
I'll bring him with me.
Let's go.
The chicken droppings, Tang San.
Chicken droppings.
It's more suspicious
to appear now.
Let's go.
It's nothing. I'll get going.
Be careful.
Where's Wu?
She hasn't been around since morning.
She went with Hu Lie Na
to lead the village head away.
We should be enough.
If the opponent is too strong,
you are responsible for bringing
Ma Hong Jun away.
Then ask Headmaster to come over.
Sure.
I thought
you wouldn't agree
with Brother Dai's arrangement.
I only hate him.
It doesn't mean I don't know
what's important.
Village Head.
Only you here?
The two female students
who were with you
came this morning
and wanted to show me
the monster that burnt the hut.
But halfway down the road,
they both disappeared.
Where do you think
they went?
And the rest?
They...
They said they found
some leads on the fire incident.
They even found
a particularly strange entrance.
So...
They found out the truth?
Yes.
Village Head.
About saving Ma Hong Jun's dad,
stop trying to hide it from us.
You've got to trust Shi Lan Ke School.
We're very strong, you know?
I know, I know.
We could definitely solve your problems.
You've got to trust us.
Yes, yes.
Here, have some water.
In that case,
the strange-looking entrance,
where could it be?
The entrance...
I think...
There's an empty hut
in the middle of the village.
So there's the entrance.
I didn't expect
he would place the entrance there.
You, you...
You have always known that?
I... This...
I'll attack in the front later.
You'll approach from the sides.
You've already lost once.
Now there are three of us.
It's different from the last time.
We still have to understand
each of our Martial Soul,
and come up with a tactic.
I'll attack him up front while you guys
keep him in check.
This is our tactic.
Tang San, what do you think?
Just do as Brother Dai said.
What if we lose again?
Haven't I told you?
If we can't defeat him,
you go to bring Headmaster over.
Why don't we ask for his help
in the first place?
This is our test.
Stop trying to rely on others.
We have to try with our strength first.
I keep seeing these specks.
There should be a source.
That's the source.
Dad.
Dad!
Dad, do you recognize me?
White Tiger Intense Light Wave!
Nether Claws!
You promised not to harm him.
Don't worry.
There's a chance.
Nether Spikes!
White Tiger Vajra Transformation!
Tang San, what are you doing?
Let's get some rest here.
What happened to him?
You can't trust these Soul Masters.
But...
They promised to help us.
They were lying to you.
Let me tell you.
Their real intention
is to capture your father!
When they capture your father,
they will study the cause of his mutation.
And...
And you will
never see your father again.
Are you sure?
Yes.
But they...
Hong Jun, do you trust me?
Then, follow me.
Let's go.
Follow me.
Go and help Tang San out.
I'll follow them.
This... This is my home.
Hasn't it burnt down?
Where is this place?
Why do we capture him?
These Soul Masters would do anything.
We take one of them hostage
to protect us.
Are you misunderstanding something?
Stand still.
The fire is protecting this house.
Hong Jun,
go forward.
This fire won't harm you.
Hong Jun,
trust me.
I won't lie to you.
If you go through the flame barrier,
you'll be able to help your father.
Is that so?
Yes.
Ma Hong Jun.
Ma Hong Jun, don't go.
It'll burn you to death, Ma Hong Jun.
Don't go. Come back.
Don't go.
Please don't go, Ma Hong Jun.
Trust me, you can't go.
Come back.
I went through it.
The fire didn't burn me.
It's finally done.
Move.
I'm not going.
-Go!
-No, I'm not going.
I...
Go...
It's you?
Why didn't you go and help Tang San?
He doesn't need my help.
Keep an eye on them.
I'm going in to take a look.
What are you doing?
You want to go in, don't you?
As long as we don't attack first,
he won't harm us.
He even knocked me out yesterday.
But why didn't he take your life?
After dragging you here,
did he attack you first?
We took a move first.
How did you know?
When we heard the fighting,
I rushed over here with Wu.
He was the first one we met.
Then where did he bring you?
Outside the village, Ma Hong Jun's house.
Why did you
keep this information from us?
I couldn't talk about it in the village.
Because we were being watched.
Who?
Those chickens.
How come there are plenty of chickens,
but no chicken droppings?
It means that they are not real chickens,
but Martial Soul.
What?
Our teacher has mentioned
that the Martial Soul takes its animal form
by combining a Tool Soul
with a Beast Soul
into a Mutant Soul.
Combining a Tool Soul with a Beast Soul?
Didn't you see the chicken droppings?
That's because
I told you about my concern.
Do you still remember?
This village has chickens everywhere.
But there are
no chicken droppings on the ground.
You mean...
You said that in front of the chickens
on purpose?
Yes.
This loophole happened
to be fixed in the end.
The chicken droppings that we saw today
prove that these chickens
are there to spy on us.
If what you said is right,
it means there are many Martial Souls around.
How many Soul Masters will be needed
to control them all?
Unless
everyone in this village
is a Soul Master.
You lied to us first.
How did you get here?
Did you fight with the monster?
I just lured the monster away.
You're injured?
Yes.
There were flames on the monster.
You said you had lured the monster away.
But you weren't there
when we saw him.
What's more,
Brother Dai fought with him once.
But he didn't mention anything
about the flame.
Therefore,
your wound
was not caused by the monster.
But by this flame barrier.
You want to enter this house.
So, can I enter now?
No way.
You're not fighting me?
I'm only interested
in the Martial Soul in the house.
There's no need to fight you.
So there's a Martial Soul in the house?
I'll just have a look.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Let me see it.
I promise I won't do anything.
Only a glimpse.
That chicken is a Martial Soul?
A Martial Soul
that can control flames at will.
There are only a few of them.
Judging by its appearance,
there is only one possibility.
It's a turkey!
It's a phoenix.
Phoenix Soul?
That's very rare.
But...
Why would it say here?
The flame barrier doesn't harm him.
It's because that's his Martial Soul.
His Martial Soul?
But the villagers have mentioned
that there's no Soul Master
in the Nightfire Village.
Besides, why is his Martial Soul
locked in this house?
I don't know.
They are here!
Village Head.
Come, Ou Si Ke.
Come and give me a hand.
Quick.
Where's Ma Hong Jun?
He's still there?
Yes.
In the house, there is...
How do I describe it?
It's like a...
It looks like a chicken.
Yes, that's great.
It's a success, it's a success!
Village Head.
The chicken in the house
is Ma Hong Jun's Martial Soul?
Yes.
"Dark fire was born from the void."
It's the phoenix in the legend!
It's the Evil Phoenix.
I know!
Three hundred years ago,
heroes arose.
The Soul Masters battled it out
in Doulo Continent.
That stunning battle.
Don't you guys watch comedies?
One of them is the Evil Phoenix.
And it's the villain.
It's super evil
and powerful.
He's right.
The Soul Master with the Evil Phoenix
participated in the battle.
He was actually our ancestor.
After our ancestor passed away,
his blood has been passed down to us.
So all the villagers are Soul Masters.
Their Martial Souls are those chickens.
You have keen eyes.
Village Head,
this is not what you told us previously.
The villagers don't even admit
they are Soul Masters.
They were not lying to you.
Even though we have Martial Souls,
we can't be real Soul Masters.
Why do you say so?
We can't advance without the Soul Ring.
Do you think we deserve
to be called Soul Masters?
But there's always an exception,
am I right?
That's true.
We're fortunate that our blood
finally stands a chance
for a possible mutation.
Ma Hong Jun's Evil Phoenix
is the result of a mutation of Martial Soul.
That's true.
After years of trials,
our Evil Phoenix
has finally appeared again!
Trials...
Ma Hong Jun's mutation of Martial Soul
is not natural?
I used a special medicine
to prompt a possible mutation.
But that's not right.
So what actually happened
to Ma Hong Jun's father?
My medicine
has taken effect on him!
Did he agree to that?
Of course.
This is for the rise of our tribe.
How can he not agree?
However,
by chance,
I was surprised to find
his son, Ma Hong Jun,
has better talent.
His Martial Soul
could be perfectly mutated.
Therefore,
Ma Hong Jun became
your experimental object.
This infuriated his father.
He burnt his own house?
He was short-sighted!
He should understand
that his son is the hope of our tribe!
How did he turn out like that?
That night,
I was about
to take Ma Hong Jun away
while he was asleep.
But this man wanted to fight back.
But he couldn't overcome the effect
of the medicine.
When I was about to leave the house,
the Martial Soul in his body
started to burn.
Eventually,
the flame turned him
into this monster now.
Remember!
Your son
is the hope of our tribe!
I won't let my son suffer
the same pain that I went through.
Hong Jun!
Village Head!
Come here.
Come here quickly.
Village Head.
Dad!
Dad...
Something went wrong with your father.
He has now turned into a monster.
Don't approach him.
But why didn't he kill you?
Even though his Martial Soul was burning,
he couldn't resist the effect
of the medicine.
So he couldn't hurt me.
I never thought
that when his Martial Soul was burning,
he gained the power of the space element.
He opened up a space like this.
Everyone.
Thank you
for bringing me here.
I will double your reward.
This has nothing to do with money.
I want to help him.
What's wrong?
This is weird.
Why I don't see them in the village?
Are they in their room?
They can't stay in the room forever.
It has been a while.
Something's wrong.
Wait here.
I'll go in and have a look.
Who do you want to help?
Him.
I want to tell Ma Hong Jun the truth.
The truth?
All the things we did
are for the reappearance of the Evil Phoenix!
With this power,
the Ma tribe will be able to rise again!
The process may be cruel.
But it's worth it.
It's not up to you
whether it's worth it or not.
So, do you think you can decide?
No one can decide it!
But this has gone too far!
I can't stand it!
Brother Dai!
I agree.
Let's put an end to it quickly.
Put an end to it quickly?
A bunch of arrogant brats.
Fine.
All of you will die here.
You think you can defeat us?
The early phase of
a Mutant Soul
will affect the person's mind.
In a while, he can only obey
orders from a familiar voice.
Along with my medicine...
Do you think
Hong Jun will listen to you?
Hong Jun, listen to me.
Reach out your hand.
Try to touch it.
Brother Dai.
He wants to control your son!
He is basically a corpse.
You think he can understand your words?
Consider yourself lucky.
To be able to witness
the legendary Martial Soul,
Evil Phoenix!
Why does he have
two Soul Rings around him?
You won't know
about the power of the Evil Phoenix.
Hong Jun, listen to me.
They want to harm us and the village.
They want to harm your father.
But they promised to help me.
That's a lie.
They are all lying to you.
They are all liars!
Ma Hong Jun.
The village head wants to hurt you and
your father.
Don't ever trust him.
Hong Jun, did you hear that?
They even threaten to harm me.
Liars.
Liars!
Watch out!
Stay out of it.
Let go of your hand.
For Ma Hong Jun,
the village head is the one
he trusts most.
If you hurt him,
it'll only infuriate Ma Hong Jun more.
That's right.
Let go of your hand!
Did you see that?
This is the Evil Phoenix!
The top Martial Soul!
There's a big gap
between talented and ordinary Soul Masters!
A Double Soul Rings.
He even wants to kill us.
What happened?
Your opponent is me.
So this is the Evil Phoenix?
What a disappointment.
What happened?
Let me tell you.
There's a big gap
between talented and ordinary Soul Masters.
All of us
are the best of the best!
Nonsense!
It's impossible
for a poor school
to have such students.
What is he trying to do?
He...
He wants to help him.
He wants to control his son's body.
He wants to control
the Evil Phoenix's power.
Look!
This space won't last any longer.
Are you all right?
I'm all right.
We... We came back.
Hong Jun!
Dad.
You're back.
Our house isn't burnt.
Everything was just a dream.
That's great.
Dad,
what happened to your face?
My child,
I burnt my Martial Soul and life
to create that deep space.
It's only in that space
that I can give you all I have.
It's only when you possess
my Martial Soul and power
that you can break through all chains
and create your own future.
I...
I don't understand.
I have to go now.
Dad, where are you going?
I'm glad
to see you one last time.
Dad...
I will give you all my memories.
Wake up
when you have found out the truth.
No, no.
No!
He's still alive.
You... You're awake.
I can feel my dad's agony.
Are you still Ma Hong Jun?
He suffered all his life because of you.
His heart was full of holes.
Why?
Why did you do that to him?
I... It's for...
It's to awaken the Evil Phoenix.
It's for the rise of our tribe!
Evil Phoenix...
Just because of that,
you killed my father,
and ruined my home.
Hong Jun...
Listen to me.
Since you want
the Evil Phoenix's power so much...
I'll let you have it.
I know you're in pain.
But you have to calm down!
Ma Hong Jun!
It's over...
He has completely lost control.
When the Evil Phoenix loses control,
he will...
He will become a madman
that burns everything to a crisp!
Kill him, kill him.
Otherwise, we will all be dead!
Blue Silver Plant is powerless
against flames.
Let me do it.
White Tiger Intense Light Wave!
Nether Spikes can't reach him.
This power far exceeds
the maximal power of two Soul Rings.
How did it turn out like this?
It's over...
Everything is done for.
If this continues,
this village will be burnt to ashes!
That's right. I have a solution!
I have a solution!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪