Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 13
What about him?
It's impossible that he's stronger than me!
You're strong.
I'm not stronger than you.
Your Martial Soul...
must be the Qibao Amber Pagoda.
If he is a Soul Master
in the Support Branch like me,
I don't think
there's a Support Branch Martial Soul
that can be stronger than the Qibao Amber Pagoda!
Indeed.
The Qibao Amber Pagoda
is one of the strongest Martial Souls
in the Support Branch.
However, the Soul Master's strength
takes precedence
over the Martial Soul's quality.
Other than Tang San,
Ou Si Ke is the most gifted here.
His talent alone ranks above Dai Mu Bai.
What makes you so sure?
When your Martial Soul awakened,
how strong was your Soul Power?
Level Nine.
Have you heard of
people born with full Soul Power?
The Support Branch...
has never seen...
anyone born with full Soul Power.
The person right in front of you is one.
He is the first one
in the Support Branch's history!
Every student here
is brighter than you.
How can you be proud?
If you can't accept it,
it's alright.
Since you are neither gifted
nor perseverant,
just pack up and leave.
Go back to your Qibao Amber Clan.
Go to your father and complain about it.
You...
I won't give up!
Rong Rong!
You have all witnessed
what happened with Ning Rong Rong.
If you want to continue your training,
you must follow the school's rules.
Your lessons
will be extremely tough and painful.
If you don't think you can take it,
you can drop out now.
Alright, dismiss.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Headmaster!
Brother Dai.
Where are you going?
Suo Tuo City.
You're going to the city now?
Keep it down!
Don't let Headmaster hear it.
What are you doing there?
The Soul Arena Competition.
You've joined the competition?
How can I become stronger
if I don't challenge myself?
Can I go?
You go?
Why would you go?
The village head mentioned
that Bu Le might be there.
Didn't Headmaster say
that it was dangerous,
and we shouldn't get involved?
Had it not been for Bu Le,
my dad wouldn't have died.
Alright, alright.
Hurry.
Don't let Headmaster see us.
Master.
Headmaster.
Master,
what are you reading?
"The Principles of Soul Burst"?
This book has become popular recently.
I heard that the author
even won a prize.
But in my opinion,
your theories and research
are profounder than this book.
Why don't you write a book too, Master?
Stop disturbing him, Ou Si Ke.
I'm not disturbing him.
Give me!
I'm here to help.
You're helping me?
Why does it seem
that you are asking me for help instead?
Headmaster, you're wise.
You can see through everything.
What do you want?
Well...
Can Rong Rong stay?
You're pleading for Ning Rong Rong?
Yes.
She's just young and rash,
and maybe a little bad-tempered.
Won't you just forgive her, please?
Please?
That little girl...
If she hadn't stood up for you earlier
when I was punishing you,
then I would definitely have given up on her.
It may seem
that she's rather arrogant,
but she's not a bad person.
You mean
that she can stay?
That's up to her.
Aren't you going to comfort her now?
Alright!
Also...
Forget about the 20 laps.
Thank you, Headmaster!
Oh yeah.
There's one more thing.
Ma Hong Jun...
When he goes berserk,
his crimson flames
is very powerful.
Its heat is really intense,
and it's adhesive,
making it really hard to extinguish.
What's more,
his flames
won't burn
his clothes or hair.
Everything apart from him
will be burned to ashes.
His Martial Soul is a Mutant Soul,
the Evil Phoenix.
Normally,
when a Martial Soul mutates,
there are only two circumstances.
One, it will grow weaker,
and the Soul Master
will have to suffer the consequences.
Two, it will become stronger.
Even though Ma Hong Jun's mutation
is positive,
the strengthened Soul Power
brought about by the mutation
affects his body.
That is why he cannot
control the evil flames well.
I didn't witness
his mutation process,
but according to what Boss Lan said,
the reason why the flames
don't burn Ma Hong Jun
is due to his father.
His dad?
His dad didn't leave him anything.
Everything he has
was given by my dad.
It's not a matter of substance.
It's love.
His father should also know
the Evil Phoenix's weakness after mutation.
That's why he chose to sacrifice himself,
burning his own power.
His love turned into a protective umbrella.
Even though
Ma Hong Jun is unable
to control the Phoenix Soul,
he is safe from harm.
A father's love is great.
Amazing theory, Gang.
Amazing?
A pay raise?
What?
Why don't you give me some paternal love?
What about a better supper tonight?
You're getting bolder, you little brat?
Do you want to run those 20 laps?
No, no!
Bye, Dad!
Bye, Master!
Rong Rong.
Headmaster was a little harsh,
but don't keep it in mind.
Why won't you say something?
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Don't be rash.
Why don't you open the door?
Rong Rong!
If you don't open the door,
I'm going to barge in!
Rong Rong!
I'm totally fine.
It doesn't hurt at all.
Why do you come to see me?
I've spoken with Headmaster.
You can stay.
You can continue your studies here.
Who says I'm leaving?
That's great!
As long as I'm here,
everything will be alright.
I'll take care of you.
Boastful.
Were you really born with full Soul Power?
But that thing about being the first in history...
I'm not that good.
You're a Support Branch Soul Master?
Kind of.
Oh yeah.
I still haven't seen your Martial Soul.
I...
There's nothing special about mine.
This is my Martial Soul.
Qibao Amber Pagoda.
There are seven levels, one for each Soul Ring.
I only have two Soul Rings now.
So I can only use the power of the first two levels.
Qibao Boosts.
First, Strength.
I'm feeling stronger all over my body.
It's so much lighter.
The table didn't get lighter.
You got stronger.
Really?
And there's the Second Soul Skill.
Second, Speed.
I'm not feeling anything.
Try running.
This speed is really high.
I'm feeling a little...
a little dizzy.
It's your turn.
Me?
Show me your Martial Soul.
My Martial Soul?
It's really nothing.
Are you looking down on me?
Of course not!
Then show me!
Let's not do it. It's awkward.
Are you saying I'm not good enough to see it?
No.
I...
If you don't show me your Martial Soul,
get out!
No...
Alright, alright.
I'll show you.
I'll show you, alright?
But first things first,
don't laugh at me.
Sure.
I'm telling you, you can't laugh.
Why are you such a nag?
I already promised you.
This is your Martial Soul?
Enough.
Get some rest.
If you get exhausted tonight
and can't finish
the lessons tomorrow,
I won't give you a refund.
I don't want money.
I want to win.
Since you've paid double tuition,
I'll give you some advice for free.
Sometimes,
victory may not be a good thing.
Perhaps this is not what you want to hear.
But who do you really want to defeat?
Your opponent?
In my opinion,
the greatest opponent
one has to face in life is one's self.
It's the enemy.
How do you define an enemy?
How do you determine whether
a person is an enemy or a friend?
A person who did something wrong
may not be a bad person for life.
But...
Enough.
I've given you enough advice.
Think it through.
Determine what you really want.
I need to go back and think about
whom I should bet on
in the Soul Arena Competition.
After all, there's only one chance.
We can't change the outcome.
So I really need to be serious
and think it through before I place my bets.
Right?
Rest early.
Thank you.
The Soul Arena Badge
shows that you're a competitor.
Do I need this to enter the arena?
Then...
Brother Dai, do you come here often
to battle against others?
Of course.
Then I want to sign up too!
Calm down, Wu.
Remember
for what reason
we came here.
Support Ma Hong Jun in the competition
and see if we can find Bu Le.
Exactly.
Alright, I'll listen to you.
Thank you, everyone.
Don't thank me.
I'm not getting involved in your matters.
I'm going in.
What about me?
Just do what you did at the Nightfire Village.
Release your Martial Soul once you're up there.
But... I'm afraid I won't be able to control it.
It's alright.
Being uncontrollable
is the trait of a Mutant Soul.
If Bu Le is around,
he will definitely see you.
Both of us
stay here to keep watch.
We'll see if anyone
is paying attention to Ma Hong Jun.
Then we'll capture him!
No.
We can't make our move here.
Our mission is
to find our target and follow him.
Then we'll capture him!
Yes, you got it this time.
Then we'll come back to join the competition.
I've already thought of our alias.
We're the San Woo.
How is it? Sounds great, right?
Alright, you should go.
Competitors in this round,
please go to Arena Eight immediately.
It's there.
Wu, over there.
Competitors,
please go to Arena Eight immediately.
Coming, coming!
Excuse me, excuse me.
Thank you.
Here.
This way.
Are you taking part?
No, not me.
Him.
I...
Badge.
Get ready to enter the arena.
Do your best, Hong Jun.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Battle, start!
Release my Martial Soul.
I give in!
I surrender! I surrender.
I need to pay?
You destroyed our facilities,
and also hurt the judge.
Even the judge got burnt by me?
But... I don't have money.
Can we use his prize money
to pay?
A single match's prize money is not enough.
This guy again? He's too strong.
Don't get too close.
He'd even attack the audience.
Be careful.
We have to watch out.
Careful.
Move!
Watch where you're going!
Boss Bu Le.
A Mutant Soul has appeared at the Soul Arena.
What Martial Soul?
Body covered in flames.
Sometimes, a shadow would appear behind him.
Like a bird.
Evil Phoenix?
The Nightfire Village...
really had a Mutant Soul?
He's still there.
Do you want to take a look?
Tian Ya.
Don't be rash.
He just came out.
Be patient.
Let's see what he can do.
We must confirm that he is strong enough
before we inform the higher-ups.
Borrow money?
We have to pay
for the ruined stage and medical costs.
Didn't he win a few matches?
He should have money.
Someone got hurt in every match.
His prize money isn't enough to cover the losses.
We've already used up all our money.
Don't worry, Brother Dai.
We'll definitely pay you back soon.
How do you plan to do it?
With the little money you earn
at the ironsmith shop?
I'm not doing it for you.
If you go out and work,
nobody will take care of this kid.
You can pay me back when you've found Bu Le.
Thank you.
Thank you, Brother Dai.
Are you going to continue battling tonight?
It's getting late.
And Bu Le didn't appear.
We should go back to school.
All of you must keep it a secret.
We must not let Headmaster find this out.
Don't worry! We won't say anything.
Let's go.
Okay!
You're getting bolder!
Going to the Soul Arena
in the middle of the night to fight!
I didn't.
Look at this!
He's quite tough.
He's got exposed and he's still so calm!
Wait, who told you
that we had gone to the Soul Arena?
It's already printed on the local Soul Master tab.
Read it yourself!
"Last night a fiery devil appeared
in the Soul Arena,
fighting and burning things.
The stage was in a mess."
"Flame Soul
that almost never appeared
suddenly appeared last night."
Ma Hong Jun!
Are you saying it wasn't you?
It was me.
What is this?
I went there by myself.
It has nothing to do with them.
Nothing to do with them?
Me.
I went with Hong Jun.
I know nothing,
Nothing?
If you know nothing,
why would I ask you to come?
Without you,
how would they even find their way
to the Soul Arena?
Do you really think I'm not aware that you've been
going to the Soul Arena secretly?
Since you know about it,
I admit.
Haven't I told all of you
that this is a complicated matter,
and you must not get involved?
Headmaster.
I'm willing to drop out of school.
Are you going to throw a tantrum?
No.
Looking for Bu Le is my own business.
I can't implicate the others.
If I drop out of school,
no matter what trouble I get into,
everyone here will be fine.
Thank you for taking care of me, Headmaster.
Please don't blame Brother San and the others
for the mistakes I've made.
What is it? Being the hero?
No, Headmaster.
I just don't want to cause any more trouble
to the people around me.
Headmaster.
I'll take my leave now.
What about the tuition you owe me?
We had a deal.
You'll pay me back with the money
you earn after you graduate.
If you leave now,
what about my money?
No way.
You cannot leave.
Also, from now on,
nobody is allowed to go to the Soul Arena.
Real battles are the best training
a Soul Master can have.
Calm down.
In my opinion,
you can continue to battle in the Soul Arena.
But there's a condition.
If Bu Le comes to Ma Hong Jun again,
you must inform us.
The school will be responsible
for everything that happens next.
Is that alright?
Okay!
Ma Hong Jun.
How do you feel
after the matches last night?
I'm still unable to control my own Martial Soul.
That's why we have to train you.
You need to figure out
how to control your Martial Soul.
Dai Mu Bai, help him with the training.
Why me?
You brought them to the Soul Arena.
This is a little punishment.
Besides, you're the team's captain.
Who else could it be?
Slowly.
Increase your strength
while keeping yourself at peace.
Release it when you've found the balance.
Conscious?
Yes.
Again.
That's the consequence
if you can't control it.
Hong Jun.
Are you alright?
Again!
Gang.
Are you really allowing them
to continue battling?
It's right to gain more experience
with real fights.
Also, they can meet
different types of Soul Masters
in the Soul Arena.
It'll be helpful.
Seems like you're letting them learn on their own.
Didn't you know from the start
that Dai Mu Bai had been battling?
Why haven't you stopped him?
I'm just giving him
a chance to train.
I heard that there's betting
for every match in the Soul Arena.
Really?
Isn't this a betting ticket?
You even bet on Dai Mu Bai.
Dai Mu Bai is very strong.
I just place a bet sometimes
to help with the school fees.
Don't tell anyone.
You're a teacher!
We'll resume tomorrow.
Brother Dai.
Thank you for training Hong Jun seriously.
Don't thank me.
I'm just following
Headmaster's orders.
Moreover,
it's not an option.
This guy will borrow money from me
each time he burns someone.
If he doesn't control it,
I'm going to be broke.
I did it.
I'm conscious.
I've succeeded!
Get up, Hong Jun.
You were
in a conscious state of mind
when you controlled the flames.
You've improved, Hong Jun.
Again!
I still can't do it.
Close your eyes.
Imagine that there's a scale within you.
Mental strength on one side,
Martial Soul on the other.
Use your mind to balance them.
Don't try too hard.
You have to relax to find your balance.
I've succeeded.
Now try using a Soul Skill.
Continue.
Make sure he remembers his condition.
Are you alright?
Why are you hitting him again?
What's that?
The lunch is ready.
We made porridge.
Hurry and eat it
before it gets cold.
Where are you going?
This is for Rong Rong.
What happened to her legs?
Can't she get it herself?
It's alright.
This is no big deal.
Have fun. I'm off.
Continue.
Wait.
What is it now?
It's not good without pickles.
Continue training, continue.
Bye!
Let's wait for a bit.
Sister Qing, let's eat together.
Yeah, that's right.
Let's eat together.
I can
go to the canteen myself.
Here you go.
If you're unhappy with it,
you don't have to bring me food next time.
I'm not.
I'm doing this willingly.
You're my junior.
This...
This is what I should do.
What happened outside?
Why is it so noisy?
Outside?
Brother Dai is training Ma Hong Jun.
He's helping him to control his Martial Soul.
He got splashed with water, and got beaten up.
That poor thing.
Ma Hong Jun?
Yeah.
That... Mutant Soul,
the Evil Phoenix?
I want to have a look.
Rong Rong.
I can maintain it.
Can't you feel any pain?
You've already tried so many times.
Do you really think you can control it?
None of your business.
I'm telling the truth.
Certain things
can't be achieved by just being persistent.
Obviously, his Martial Soul is flawed.
What are you doing?
I know I might not get anything out of this.
But if I don't even try,
there's really no hope at all.
You want to become a Soul Master?
I don't think I can become a Soul Master.
But at least,
I need to control my Martial Soul.
But you're hurt.
I'm fine.
I can still go on.
We're busy.
Please leave.
Let's continue.
You didn't even eat it.
I'll heat it up for you.
Who made you angry?
Rong Rong.
Why are you angry?
Who is it?
What are you doing?
I...
I'm training my stealth skills.
Did you see everything?
Clearly.
Everything I said
was for Ma Hong Jun's own good.
He wants to control his Martial Soul.
Is that really an easy feat?
Look at how arrogant that Dai Mu Bai was.
He just lost his temper at me
without even understanding my intentions.
He's so annoying!
Do you speak like this at home?
Yes!
Do you have any friends?
What do you mean?
If you speak to everyone
with such an arrogant tone,
who would accept you?
I'm not.
This is Shi Lan Ke School.
Not Qibao Amber Clan.
You're not a princess here.
We're all from the same school.
You should learn
to communicate with others.
Sister Qing.
You said
that you had been
practicing your stealth skills?
That's why I saw it clearly.
Then were you concerned about Ma Hong Jun,
or, in fact,
you were concerned about Dai Mu Bai?
I have nothing to do with him.
Sister Qing.
Shouldn't you also learn
to communicate with others?
Drink it.
I didn't go berserk.
I controlled it.
I didn't go berserk! I did it!
Not bad.
He didn't go berserk at all this time.
As long as I don't fully release
my power, I can control it.
Then it's not full control.
Continue tomorrow.
Hong Jun.
Hasn't Bu Le appeared?
Not yet.
He should have appeared.
Hong Jun already fought so many times.
The Mutant Soul is already very famous.
Perhaps his opponents weren't strong enough?
Ma Hong Jun.
Choose your opponent tomorrow.
Choose who?
Me.
He's controlling it well.
Come on!
His Second Soul Skill is Flame Boost.
Blue Silver Plant can be used in this way?
Just to avoid the impact.
If it's a direct blow,
it may not be enough.
Hong Jun!
Awesome! Cool!
Dai Mu Bai, I want to challenge you!
Great! Awesome!
Bring that little girl to the tavern.
Little girl?
Not Ma Hong Jun?
He comes here every day.
If that little girl leaves,
she will be gone.
I understand.
Don't worry.
No problem.
Let's say,
after I register,
I'll challenge Brother Dai tomorrow.
Good?
Can't you do the same at school?
It's different.
It feels better
to fight at the Soul Arena.
Then you should
ask Brother Dai first.
He has to accept your challenge first.
Alright.
Little girl, come with us.
Did you get the wrong person?
You can go.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪