Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 12
I got an idea!
Headmaster!
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
It's not his power.
His father passed it to him,
but he failed to control it.
That's why he became so strong.
The fire will keep burning
until the whole village
is turned into ashes.
Headmaster, can you put off the fire?
We have two choices,
wake Ma Hong Jun up,
or kill him.
It seems
it's harder to wake him up now.
If he doesn't wake up,
what could be the worst consequence?
He'll be dead too,
just like his father,
burning up his Martial Soul
and his life.
There will be nothing we can do.
You can stop him.
I can defeat him
and suppress him,
but I can't put off the fire.
Unless he's wakened.
Yes.
Tang San.
The flame of Evil Phoenix
will devour everything.
You can't hold on for long
with your current Soul Power.
Are you out of your mind?
He'll burn you to death!
Headmaster.
Respect others' decisions.
He's getting his rebirth.
Ma Hong Jun, wake up!
Ma Hong Jun, keep your Martial Soul,
or else you'll destroy
the whole village!
I don't care!
They killed my father!
They have lives too,
you can't decide their fate.
Furthermore,
if it continues,
you'll end up getting burnt too.
Listen to me, Ma Hong Jun.
Your father chose to burn himself
in order to pass you his Martial Soul,
not to destroy
his hope on you.
You must live well
with the power he gave you.
Embrace your potential
to create your own world!
You can't
and shouldn't give up!
Do you get it?
Listen to me, Ma Hong Jun.
You still have our back,
we can be brothers.
Headmaster and teachers
can be your fathers!
All right?
Hong Jun!
Keep your Martial Soul!
It's been put off!
The fire is been put off!
Hand over your special medicines.
Calm down!
Did you try to drug me just now?
How about you try mine now?
Don't!
I'll get it.
Don't kill me.
Hurry up.
That's all I have.
Where did you get this?
I prescribed it.
What are the ingredients?
How did you prescribe it?
Actually, someone gave it to me.
Who has eaten it?
Everyone in the village.
After they've eaten it,
they became weaker
and more obedient.
Who gave it to you?
A guy named Bu Le.
Where's he?
I have no idea!
I'm telling the truth!
He came to me
and gave me the medicine.
How did he know
you're experimenting for
Mutant Soul?
He said
he has already investigated
most descendants of Old Soul Masters.
He gave this medicine
not only to our villagers,
but also people in other areas.
He said he's helping
those fallen Soul Masters to revival.
This is the posture.
Revival!
The guy named Bu Le
just gave the medicine to you
and didn't ask for anything
in return?
That's right!
He said,
if any Soul Master
has successfully mutated,
they can go to
the Suo Tuo Soul Arena.
Does that mean
we can find him at Soul Arena?
Not really.
He said,
let the Mutant Soul Masters
take part in battles.
If they're strong enough,
he'll come and look for us again.
I'll let you handle this.
Wait.
Mutant Soul
has always been a tough issue
to handle for Martial Soul Hall.
Since your medicine is so precious,
why don't you sell it to me?
Just name your price.
What're you going to do with it?
I'll send it for research
in Martial Soul Hall.
Let's see if we can disseminate it.
Haven't you seen
what it has caused
to Ma Hong Jun's father?
This medicine is definitely evil.
That's why the research has to continue.
Declining bloodline
in Nightfire Village
happens at many places too
in Douluo Continent.
Maybe this medicine can really
allow them to rise again.
No way.
The Martial Soul Hall can offer
a price that you can never imagine.
I don't want any of that.
What do you want?
Power, status,
or enrolment in Martial Soul Hall?
What do you want?
I want nothing.
If it was not because of it,
my father wouldn't die.
Any price
won't bring back my father anymore.
I could feel my father's pain.
I believe
he wouldn't want more people
to feel what he did.
That's what I thought.
What's your plan afterwards?
I'm going to Suo Tuo City.
You're going to look for Bu Le?
I haven't made up my mind yet.
It's on our route,
why don't you follow us?
How dare you ask me this?
That's right.
Master!
You're back?
Master,
your Martial Soul theory
has been overturned.
By who?
Him.
What about me?
Didn't you say Soul Ring
can only be evolved by
hunting down Soul Beasts?
That's right.
Just now
while we were in inner space,
Ma Jun Hong already has
Double Soul Rings
when his Martial Soul is awakened.
There's only one possibility.
He was born with Double Soul Rings.
But once he has gotten his power,
it mutated.
Right.
I was born with Double Soul Rings.
Before this, it was Plymouth Rock,
now it's Phoenix.
I rather have my father here
than any mutations.
What your father has done
is to make sure you can live well.
Tang San,
you did great this time.
I didn't do anything,
If it wasn't you,
I might not be able to wake up at all.
Headmaster.
Ma Hong Jun has nowhere to go,
can he stay here?
Would you like to be Soul Master too?
Can I?
Mutant Soul itself
is a strong starting point.
Just pay your fees.
Fees?
Fees for Shi Lan Ke School.
Fifty Gold Soul Coins.
I don't have so much money.
You do have some
living expenses, right?
My house is burnt,
I'm now
penniless.
Why do I always meet unlucky people?
It's okay. Just follow us.
Hong Jun.
Well,
after you graduate
and have the capability,
are you willing to help the school?
Yes.
Enough, father.
All right.
Let's go back to the school then.
Ou Si Ke,
clean it up.
Make sure it's clean.
Let's go, back to the school.
Why me...
Let's go.
Here, Hong Jun.
Hong Jun,
this is the male dorm.
This is my bed,
Brother Dai's,
and Tang San's.
You can choose one from the rest.
Close the window before you leave.
It's all dusty.
There's a well at the door.
But if you wash it now,
it won't be dry by night.
Why is our school
in the village?
The rent here is cheap!
If we help out their farm works,
we can even get discounts!
So, the school
isn't that rich after all?
That I must disagree.
You're being too polite.
We're utterly poor!
I heard there are allowances
for Soul Masters.
There are three ways
for a Soul Master to get his allowance.
Offer your service to the Empire,
join the Seven Tribes
or seek refuge in Martial Soul Hall.
The same goes with the school,
we have to depend on this wealthy power
in order to get financial support.
You'll know after looking at our school,
we don't stand with any side.
Not belonging under any power,
that's the real freedom.
Only by breaking restraints
can students learn
to choose their own paths while growing.
What he said has some points.
Indeed,
but we can't even afford
to eat meat now.
Brother San!
Wu, Headmaster.
Wu, you brought so much stuff!
Here, give it to me.
Ma Hong Jun.
Which bed are you sleeping at?
That one.
All these are for you.
For me?
Not for you, but borrowing them to you.
You have to pay after you earn money.
Little Freak,
since you've joined Shi Lan Ke,
just treat here as your home.
We're all your family members.
This is Dai Mu Bai,
he's your boss.
You all are elder than him,
guide him more.
-All right.
-I'm good at this.
I'll protect you from now on.
Good kid.
Tang San and Wu,
come with me.
Master and I have something to tell you.
Just the both of us?
All right.
Hurry and come.
Let's go.
We'll make a move first.
Where's the well?
Well?
You're washing his bedsheet
just to thank him for saving you?
I saved you too at that time.
I was the one who put off the fire!
Have you forgotten?
Let me remind you then.
Look, at that time,
Tang San and you were in the fire.
I took such a big barrel of water
and walked so far,
then...
I don't get it.
The fire is off.
And then?
And then I saved you.
Don't you think you should thank me too?
Right?
Thank you.
You're being too polite,
we all are a family.
Come here,
boy.
Wash my bedsheet too.
Why must he help you?
Everyone has been helping
during this mission,
even our observer, Hu Lie Na
provided us information.
Except you.
Not only you were first captivated,
others even have to save you.
I...
I helped
splashing water!
Everyone saw that.
The Evil Fire is
Ma Hong Jun's Martial Soul.
Do you think your water can put it off?
Either you're being silly after years
becoming Soul Master,
or it's because you've been writing
too many opera lines.
From your professional perspective,
even if you're making stories,
you have to consider it rationality.
I have
records here!
They are all being recorded here!
Look.
I wrote how did I question
that village head
and draw something out of him.
It's impossible that
I make up these dialogues, right?
Look at it!
You shouldn't neglect my contribution
just because I'm a writer.
All right,
just live in your own world.
What do you mean?
Where's he?
He has already left.
Hurry and take a look at him.
Me?
Hurry up.
Stop being so mean to me next time.
Headmaster
has informed the City Main Office
about the Nightfire Village incident.
If the officers are investigating it,
then both of you
shouldn't bother anymore.
Also,
take good care of Ma Hong Jun.
Don't let him do anything impulsive.
Got it.
Oh, right.
You should always keep a distance
from Hu Lie Na,
after all she's from
the Martial Soul Hall.
Xiao Gang, I've already told you.
She came here for Dai Mu Bai.
What's the use of reminding him?
Oh, right.
There's another frosty lady.
I can't believe she's...
What did you say, Wu?
Her name is Zhu Zhu Qing.
I still think
Hu Lie Na's motive isn't that simple.
She must be hiding something from us.
Enough.
Both of you go back first.
We'll make a move first then, teacher.
I wanted to say
Sister Qing is Brother Dai's fiancee.
I know.
But that's others' secret,
let's not mind it.
You scared me.
Come here.
Put them down.
Come.
What is it?
Are you interested in acting?
Acting?
Right.
I feel that your life experience
is extremely dramatic.
I'll write the lines
and you act.
When you set yourself on fire,
I'm sure the audience
will like it very much!
On fire?
That's right.
You have to learn to release
and keep your Martial Soul
at your wish.
This isn't even close to perfect.
You should train more
so as to practice with me.
Did you get it?
At that time, you'll get
half of the profits.
The school is too poor now.
We should think of
a way for us to survive.
All right.
Oh, Brother Ou.
What's your Martial Soul?
My Martial Soul...
is just that.
Well...
There's not much use for
Support Branch Martial Soul.
It's absolutely useless.
Who said so?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Don't you know that
the Qibao Amber Clan,
one of the top three tribes
of the Seven tribes
belongs to the Support Branch?
I'm talking to you.
I'm talking to you!
Your voice is so nice.
Is this Shi Lan Ke School?
Do you know where is the headmaster?
I'll lead the way.
This is heavy.
I'll do it if you can't take it.
I can.
Hello.
Why isn't he responding?
Is he crazy?
Luckily I didn't ask him
to wash my bedsheet.
I have nothing to do with this.
He set himself on fire.
I have to take the box.
No, I should look for someone.
I'll look for someone.
Ma Hong Jun.
Such a young Soul Honour?
What Martial Soul is this?
Fire Flamingo?
Burning Sparrow?
It doesn't look like a Phoenix.
Don't.
I'm sorry.
What happened to him?
Why was he out of control suddenly?
I have no idea too.
A girl who was looking for Headmaster
greeted him,
look what happened to him.
It should be
the defect from the mutation
of Martial Soul.
He was just temporarily out of control.
Will this happen again in the future?
It might.
It's all right.
He'll recover once his power is used up.
Take good care of him.
Okay.
This kid.
That means he's a time bomb.
So we'll have to be prepared
to fight him when the time comes?
I...
Not bad.
We can train our resilience.
Re...
Brother, I'm of the Support Branch.
What should I do then?
You can practice to restrain
from the flame.
How do I...
What Brother Dai meant was,
you'll get used to be burnt.
Please remind me
not to spend time alone with him.
Where are you going?
I'll check out that lady.
She must be frightened now.
I'll leave first.
Is the school inside the jungle?
This is the school.
This is the school?
Where's the gate?
The walls?
The dorms?
Where's the stadium?
None.
You don't have any of those?
If there's no dorm,
then where the students stay?
Look.
That's the boys' dorm,
and there's the girls'.
Just two wooden houses?
Is it sufficient?
How many students are there?
How many?
Let me count.
Six!
Just six students in a school?
Little girl!
I heard that you're looking for me.
You're the headmaster?
Yes.
You're the Soul Saint
with Seven Soul Rings?
Who told you so?
What's your name?
Lander.
That's right.
This is the letter from my father.
You're Ning Feng Zhi's daughter?
Do you know him?
Do you know the Seven Clans?
Of course I do.
It's formed by
the seven most powerful clans.
Even the Martial Soul Hall
and the Empire
dare not provoke them.
Among the Seven tribes,
the top three are called three elders,
the Qibao Amber Clan is one of them.
And for this term,
the head of the Qibao Amber Clan
is Ning Feng Zhi.
Does that mean
you're the princess of
the Qibao Amber Clan?
Did your father ask you to
join the Shi Lan Ke School?
I've even brought my luggage.
This year's enrolment has ended.
Come again next year.
Are you going to reject
such a pretty lady?
I didn't expect Headmaster
to hold still on his principles.
My father also said,
as long as I'm in,
your debt to the Qibao Amber Clan
will be canceled out.
Wu,
hurry and bring our new girl
to the dorm
and familiarise her
with the environment.
Let me do it.
Hello, Junior.
I'm Ou Si Ke,
your senior.
Just let me know if you need any help.
I'm Ning Rong Rong.
Rong Rong.
What a cute name.
Rong Rong!
What are you looking at?
We owed them a huge amount.
The school isn't doing well recently.
Come back and gather here
in half an hour.
Be careful. Careful.
Are we in a rush of training?
I haven't finished cleaning up my room.
Since your father is being sincere,
I must put more effort
into teaching you too.
Both of you are
Support Branch Soul Masters,
so you can practice together.
What's your Martial Soul?
Ou Si Ke.
Let me ask you.
What's the important role
of a Support Branch Soul Master
during a battle?
Protect ourselves.
That's right.
Most Support Branch Soul Masters
aren't skillful in fighting,
so their first job
is to avoid danger.
A Support Branch Soul Master who
doesn't know how to escape
is considered a bad Soul Master.
Let me ask you, Ou Si Ke.
What's most important in escaping?
Long legs.
It's stamina!
Correct!
It's stamina.
Stamina.
An extra step in the crucial moment
will save you from being killed.
So, you must first complete
the stamina training.
From now on,
run 20 rounds around the village.
Finish up before the sky goes dark.
You can use your Martial Soul.
Should we start running now?
From where do we start?
Ou Si Ke knows that.
Right.
Just follow me.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Let me ask you,
how far is one round?
Let me be frank,
it's considered lucky
if we can finish up before dinner.
What?
Do we have to keep running until dinner?
That's right.
Don't stop. Hurry up and run.
Or else we'll really miss the dinner.
Tell me honestly,
is that one man picking up bones on me?
Why did he punish me with this?
No,
this is how we train normally.
Why training stamina?
Because
as a Support Branch Soul Master,
you'll have to know how to run.
Why run?
If there's really a battle,
the Combat Branch Soul Masters
should fully protect us
from the Support Branch.
But during a battle,
you should learn how to
protect yourself.
Where's Suo Tuo City?
The city is that way.
Where are you going?
Shopping.
We haven't even
finished running one round here.
No one is checking on us,
who would know?
You...
How's that?
Are you following me?
I...
Hey.
Hong Jun.
What are you doing?
I...
I'll just lock myself up.
So, next time when I'm out of control,
I won't hurt you all anymore.
This is not necessary.
Brother San,
do you think my Martial Soul
can be controllable?
Surely it can.
If I fail to control my Martial Soul,
then my father died for nothing.
It'd be good if
my Martial Soul wasn't mutated.
Let bygone be bygone.
You have to learn to accept it.
At least you have the power now
and hope to be stronger.
But is this what he wants?
Whatever he wants,
he'll have it after becoming stronger.
You mean,
he can have everything when he's strong?
That's how the world runs.
What can you do about it?
What are you trying to do?
When I was in despair,
Brother San was the one
who lent me a hand.
So, is all his words right?
Will you fight
whoever quarrels with him?
Not all arguments
have to be solved by fists.
Then what?
By your mouth?
If we only value a person through
their strength and not the truth,
then the world will be terrible.
That's the reality.
What can you do about it?
If it's really like this,
then I'll change it.
I really would like to see
whether you change the world,
or the world changes you.
My Martial Soul is a Ghost Cat.
Speed means everything.
That's why I need a pair
of comfortable shoes.
Later on,
I'll polish the sole.
In this way,
I can walk without any noises.
You're considerate about it.
In order to give full play
of Martial Soul,
we should consider every aspect.
It takes time to become stronger.
Are you doing that
to defeat Brother Dai?
Not so much as defeating Dai Mu Bai,
but challenging my own fate.
I don't wish to live
a well-planned life,
I need to set myself free.
So, I must be stronger.
Defeating Dai Mu Bai,
is just my first target.
I want to be stronger too,
I want to free myself too.
What's your target then?
I'm going to win Headmaster.
Why?
Defeating him
means I can change
the school rules.
Then I can enter the boys' dorm!
Wu, you're still young.
Don't get cheated.
By who?
My sister told me,
girls have to learn to be independent
and live for ourselves.
Men are unreliable.
But I feel
Tang San is a reliable man.
Even though Ou Si Ke isn't that good,
but Brother Dai isn't that bad too.
What's so good about him?
Every day he's flirting
with that Hu Lie Na.
Hu Lie Na?
Oh, right.
Headmaster told us just now
that Hu Lie Na came to Shi Lan Ke
for Brother Dai.
Really?
What happened?
No idea.
Headmaster told us to come.
I almost died running.
Oh, right.
Where's the new girl?
New girl?
She...
There she is.
You both finished running so soon?
I...
That's right. We finished.
But you don't look tired at all.
I have good stamina.
I didn't get to
introduce myself properly
this afternoon.
Hello, I'm Ning Rong Rong.
I'm Wu.
Zhu Zhu Qing.
Why did you come to Shi Lan Ke School?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Yes.
My father gave me a letter
to ask me to come to Shi Lan Ke.
Here I come.
How about you all?
I came here with Tang San.
Ou Si Ke.
All of you, come over here.
Headmaster.
Ou Si Ke.
I told you both to run 20 rounds,
have you finished it?
I've finished it.
I said you both,
not only you.
We finished also.
Great.
You now know teamwork now too.
Run another 20 rounds.
Why?
Because
he lied.
You didn't finish the 20 rounds.
Who said so?
How did you know?
I also know that
you went to Suo Tuo City,
shopped at three jewelry shops,
eaten dessert in the city west,
and watched the street circus.
Did you follow me?
No.
I'm Headmaster,
I'm responsible towards
every student here.
I called you all here
to make sure you all remember,
no matter how tough the course is,
never run away from it.
Don't even lie to me.
Why are you still standing there?
You don't need to run.
He lied in order to help me.
He didn't do anything wrong.
This isn't his fault.
If lying can be forgiven,
then what about you?
Leaving the school without permission,
ignoring the teacher's order,
you even asked your friend
to lie for you.
If this was a battle,
Ou Si Ke might die because of you.
Actually, it isn't her fault too.
This isn't a battleground,
it's just a school.
But this is my school.
I give you two choices.
Leave the school
and return to the Qibao Amber Clan.
Your performance
proves that you don't deserve
to be a member of us.
Another option,
prove to me that you are fit to stay.
This is too much!
Lander,
you're just a little Soul Saint.
Do you know
how many Soul Saints are there
in the Qibao Amber Clan?
They don't even worth
to be my teacher!
You're right.
I'm just a little Soul Saint.
And you,
if I'm not mistaken,
you're just a
Soul Master with Double Soul Rings.
I'm the greatest talent
among my generation
in the Qibao Amber Clan.
Talent?
Then I must say
this generation of the Qibao Amber Clan
is really disappointing.
How dare you humiliate our Ning family?
You said you're the greatest,
that's why I'm telling the truth.
Let me tell you,
every student here
is stronger than you.
Impossible.
Dai Mu Bai,
his Martial Soul is White Tiger.
He's the youngest Soul Honour
in the history of Shi Lan Ke.
He's quite strong,
but that's only one of them.
Tang San.
Not even a year after
his Martial Soul is awakened,
he's already the same as you,
a Soul Master with Double Soul Rings.
His Soul Power is so pure and condensed,
almost reaching
the level of a Soul Honour.
Soul Master with a year of experience?
That's impossible.
Show her.
Your Martial Soul is awakened
for only a year?
Less than that.
Zhu Zhu Qing.
A soul Master with
Double Soul Rings like you.
But I'm not as talented as them,
I'm still working my way up.
Her Soul Power is alike with yours,
but she has
the most determined heart
among all of you.
Let me ask you,
what's your purpose in the school?
To become stronger.
What would you do
for all the arrangements by the school?
As long as I can become stronger,
I'll carry it out with
no hesitation.
What if it'll burn your face
or get your hands chopped off?
If that's necessary,
I'll accept it.
What about him?
Ma Hong Jun?
You should have seen
when he's out of control.
Flame Soul.
That's right.
His Martial Soul
is the Evil Phoenix,
found once in a blue moon.
Liar!
Ma Hong Jun, show your Martial Soul!
Calm down!
All of us can prove that.
Once his Martial Soul forms,
his body will be on fire
and you'll see the Phoenix tail.
That's the Evil Phoenix.
Also,
didn't you already
witness that this afternoon?
If what they said is true,
then many clans
should be looking up for you.
I feel good being here.
I only have one Soul Ring.
Besides Wu,
everyone else here is stronger than you.
What about him?
He can't be stronger than me!
Of course.
I'm no match to you.
I suppose your Martial Soul is
Qibao Amber Pagoda.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪