Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 10
Still, I would like to try.
I'll accompany you.
You two,
go quickly.
Nobody is here.
What is it?
The village head just said
Ma Hong Jun's father
had been burned to death too.
Yes.
But there is
no new grave here.
He wasn't buried here?
Let's look again back in the village.
Sir,
do you know where's Ma Hong Jun?
Thank you.
Search on your own.
Don't disturb me.
You...
The villager doesn't seem to know much.
It seems like
you've been staring at those chickens.
Since we entered the village,
we've seen many chickens along the way,
but there are no droppings at all
on the ground.
Could it be
that the villagers care about hygiene,
so they've swept the floor?
No way.
I grew up in a village too.
I know if you have chickens,
there's no way
to keep the ground clean of droppings.
Besides,
would you clean the droppings
and leave the rubbish behind?
Chicken droppings. Chicken?
It's very weird.
Let's have a look at other places.
There's no one here.
Hu Lie Na.
Let's take a look.
Hu Lie Na, what are you doing?
I just found something
in this house,
but it disappeared instantly.
What did you find?
I don't know.
The walls and the floor
are fine,
and there shouldn't be any place to hide.
Then, did you see Ma Hong Jun?
I did.
He was in this house just now,
but he ran away when he saw me.
Why didn't you stop him?
I'm just sitting in on the class.
What happened in this village
is a test for you,
not for me.
Which way did he go then?
I don't know.
Wait.
What?
Why do you have to fight against me?
You
really don't remember who I am?
You mean we've met before?
Spit it out.
Ma Hong Jun?
Why are you running?
What are you doing?
Had it not been for you,
I would have caught him!
I've told you that I'm in charge.
I didn't agree with it.
Isn't that the village head's house?
Where's that child?
Village Head.
You're back.
Did you see Ma Hong Jun?
Didn't you go and look for him?
We saw him,
but he ran away as soon as we spoke.
We went after him to this area,
and he was gone.
That boy grew up here.
If he hides,
it won't be easy to find him.
No.
But why did he run?
Maybe he's timid.
What happened?
Ou Si Ke.
Did anyone go in just now?
No. It's just me.
Don't stand in my way next time.
Why? Want to fight again?
You're no match for me.
You guys are really fighting?
Let's go back to the village head's house.
All right.
You're not coming with us?
I won't join you two.
I'm very interested
in what I've just found.
Be careful.
That might be
the monster who started the fire.
If I see it,
I'll let you know.
Do you hear any sounds?
It sounds like a fight.
Come on.
Still want to fight?
I admit
I'm no match for you now.
But someday,
I'll defeat you.
Let them in.
It's fine.
I can take care of it on my own.
Village Head,
we're so close to finding
Ma Hong Jun in the afternoon.
But he ran away when he saw us.
Why is he hiding from us?
Perhaps it's because
what had happened in his house
terrified him.
I've asked the villagers,
but no one knows
where he has been.
No one has given him any food these days, either.
Is that so?
It's my bad for not noticing it.
How about this?
Let me see
if I can find a villager's house
for him to stay.
He's so pitiful.
Right.
That's what I have been saying.
Actually,
this is also the main reason
that I wanted you to leave.
He was traumatized by the sudden event.
He is also
afraid of strangers.
Actually, it's very normal
that he doesn't want
to meet with people.
After you leave,
maybe he'll come out.
Village Head,
are you blaming us now?
I think that's how we should be.
What's the most important thing?
It must be kindness,
isn't it?
Yes.
Kindness is the most important.
I'm not blaming you.
But we searched
for a whole afternoon,
and there was no monster to be seen.
What does this mean?
This means that there's no monster.
And the black object,
it could be that I misled you
because of my poor eyesight.
All right then.
If we can't get anything
out of tomorrow's investigation,
we'll leave.
Children,
it's better
to put more effort into your training.
You don't have
to waste your time
with these trivial matters
in the village.
I feel bad
for taking up your time.
Let's do this.
Tonight,
please spend the night at my place.
Village Head,
is there any Soul Master
in this village?
No.
Understand.
Village Head, you should rest early too.
Sure.
It's very late now. Can you see clearly?
Did you forget
that my Martial Soul is Four-eyed Eagle Owl?
My eyesight becomes better at night.
Come and rest for a while.
You've stood there for a day.
You seem to care a lot for them.
They are my students.
Then why don't you follow them in?
Let me tell you.
There's something weird
in this village.
It's a Soul Master or Soul Beast?
It's hard to tell.
Even you have no idea?
The troublesome part is
the black monster
is very sensitive about
the capability of Soul Masters.
It hid away as I approached
the village.
So you let the children enter the village
because they're weaker
and have a higher chance
of getting near the monster?
It'd be best
to let them lure the monster out
and then I'll rush in
to finish it at once.
Did the monster set the fire?
I don't know.
At first, I thought it was
a normal fire
so I came earlier to investigate.
Then I found out
that there's a monster
hiding in the village.
You have seven Soul Rings already,
but you can't find it
when it hides?
That's the weird part.
After it disappears,
you won't find any traces of it.
I only have two Soul Rings,
I should go and see.
You don't have to.
I've thought it over.
I wanted to give the children on this team
a chance to face
and solve a problem independently,
so as to train them.
You've started to train a team so soon?
It depends on their fate.
Besides,
those children,
each has one's own personality.
It's not easy
to make a team of them.
Brother Dai,
I'd like to tell you something.
Where did you go today?
Did you find out anything?
I was in the village,
and I didn't find out anything.
But there's something
that bothers me.
There are many chickens in this village
but there are no chicken droppings
on the ground.
What does this have to do with chickens?
It's not reasonable.
What chicken droppings?
What matters now is to find Ma Hong Jun,
and find out what's the monster
behind the fire.
Nothing else matters.
I think
someone is taking care of Ma Hong Jun.
Search from house to house tomorrow.
Brother Dai, listen to me.
I met Hu Lie Na in the afternoon.
She said she saw something weird.
What was that?
She said she didn't see it clearly.
I'm thinking
that if the monster
did set the fire,
why does it still stay in the village?
Why did it come?
About something so important,
you only tell me now?
I...
Just this much medicine left.
The effect can only last for one night.
Never mind.
I'll use everything that's left.
Didn't we agree
that you'd stay indoors for two days?
Why didn't you listen to me?
I just wanted to have a look back home.
Don't go out during these two days.
You can come out
after they leave.
I still want to see my dad.
Here.
Drink it while it's hot.
It'll warm you up.
Your dad.
Your dad is not a human anymore.
Not a human.
Hong Jun,
listen.
Don't go out.
I'll figure it out
after the Soul Masters leave.
There is a question that I couldn't understand.
Why don't you leave even when the house
has burnt down?
It's because you still have something to do.
Run?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
What is it?
Not feeling good?
I just feel
that the more people we've met,
the more rules there are.
Of course.
If everyone
could do as they please,
the world would be in a mess.
Isn't it good to do whatever we want?
I think
not all rules
are bad actually.
For example?
For example, I wanted to be a Soul Master
and I enrolled in the school.
And then,
I met you.
If so,
going to school will be the best rule.
That's right.
Then I want to keep going to school.
Keep going to school.
In that case,
I can always be with Brother San.
What you said
is right.
Did you hear any sounds?
Let's have a look.
Come.
What do you want from me?
Why?
The fight in the afternoon
was not enough?
It's them again.
Want to try again?
You asked me in the afternoon
why I must fight with you.
You want to tell me now?
Give me some time
to challenge you again.
If I fail again,
I'll accept my fate.
What good is it if you defeat me?
My name is Zhu Zhu Qing.
You really forgot
the name of your fiancée.
Fiancée.
Why should I marry a man
who I've only met once?
Why no one asked me
if I was willing to get married?
Why can't I
have the right to choose my fate?
I came to break off the engagement.
Break off?
Okay.
You can tell me directly.
Why must you challenge me?
Because you said
you'd only
change your mind if I defeat you.
Fine!
I'll become strong
and let you lose completely.
So, I'll have the right
to make you give up this marriage!
Didn't my family tell you?
Tell me what?
One of the reasons why I left the tribe
is that I refuse a political marriage.
I agree to call off the engagement.
We're on the same page in this matter.
This is very ridiculous.
Growing up, we only met once.
How could it
turn into a marriage?
It's all because of you!
Me?
This was decided by the tribe.
What does it have to do with me?
If you hadn't insisted on kissing me
at that time,
why would they have...
I kissed you?
I don't remember it at all.
You're abandoning me!
No, this is not the right word.
Anyway, you're a jerk!
Did I kiss her?
On the surface, you can't tell
that Brother Dai is this kind of person.
No wonder she has been picking on Brother Dai.
What's wrong with Dai Mu Bai?
You scared me!
We just found out
that the amazing sister's name
is Zhu Zhu Qing.
She is Brother Dai's fiancée.
She came to Shi Lan Ke
to break off the engagement.
Where is he now?
Over there.
I didn't know that her curiosity
is stronger than mine.
Zhu Zhu Qing is your fiancée?
What does that have to do with you?
I can help you catch the monster
who set the fire.
In exchange,
you have to tell me the matter
between you and her.
Okay?
Why?
Curiosity.
It's late now.
If there's nothing else,
I want to rest now.
Sorry.
I was impatient.
I just wanted to know you better.
We're just from the same school.
You don't have to know me better.
You know where the monster is?
I know.
Bring me there.
You're not bringing the others?
I alone suffice.
Let's follow them.
If Brother Dai is in danger,
we can help him.
He always picks on you,
you still want to help him?
It's just a misunderstanding.
We can't let him risk his life, can we?
Let's go.
Okay.
Wu,
later when you go in,
try not to make any noise.
What are you looking for?
There's no chicken?
Of course, the chickens are sleeping.
It's fine. Let's go.
You said you followed the monster here?
Look, this house is abnormal.
I chased after the monster and got here.
It escaped from this door.
It escaped from this door?
Then why did you bring me in?
Because this door
can only be opened from inside.
My goodness. What is going on?
It seems like...
the chicken is monitoring us.
Something is weird.
Wait for me here.
How did you find this place?
I was looking for the monster,
and I found
it had been watching the village head's house.
I want to talk to it,
but it ran away.
Then I chased after it to this place.
This is probably caused
by Space Branch Martial Soul.
You're saying
this is an independent space
built by a Martial Soul?
That's right.
But this kind of independent space
won't be too big.
At most, it'll be the size of
the Nightfire Village.
So,
the monster is a Space Branch Soul Beast?
It's hard to determine now.
But why does it want to set the space
in the Nightfire Village?
Now we have to find it
to know the answer.
Last time,
I lost it here.
So, I'm not sure
where it is now.
Let's search again.
We'll get the answer for sure.
Don't have to search anymore.
It appeared of its own accord.
It's so weird here.
It looks exactly like
the Nightfire Village.
But there are no villagers.
That's not my point.
What is it?
This place is giving off
a very sad vibe.
Sad?
What is it?
Brother Dai.
What happened?
How did you come here?
You fought with the monster?
I just lured the monster away.
You're injured.
Yes.
There were flames on the monster.
What's going on here?
Among the Space Branch Soul Masters
or Soul Beasts,
there are a few exceptions
that can create an independent space.
It is a Soul Master or a Soul Beast?
I don't know.
All I know is
it is very strong.
Dai Mu Bai was hit by it in the front.
Let's help Brother Dai
to get back first.
Brother Dai.
Here.
Why am I here?
Do you remember
what happened last night?
Last night.
Last night I got through the door
with Hu Lie Na.
And then...
The monster came out...
And I passed out.
How strong was that monster?
It can't be compared to Headmaster.
Did it have flames on its body?
Flame?
No.
How did I come back?
Tang San carried you.
Then I put you on the bed
and covered you up with the blanket,
Brother Dai.
Where are Hu Lie Na and Wu?
They went to inform the village head
that the monster had been found,
and managed to trick
the village head out.
Why did they have to trick him?
Hu Lie Na said the monster
had been roaming around
the village head's house.
You're saying that the monster
wanted to harm the village head?
Yesterday we found Ma Hong Jun
hiding
in that burnt house,
and the monster
showed up nearby.
This monster keeps lurking
in the Nightfire Village?
It must think that the fire last time
didn't kill Ma Hong Jun,
so it's waiting for another chance.
It's possible.
How is the village head
connected to it?
I also thought about it yesterday.
That house has burnt down for many days.
There should be someone
taking care of Ma Hong Jun.
So I went
to the village head's kitchen
early in the morning,
and I found yesterday's dirty dishes.
In terms of the quantity,
there's an extra set.
This means
Ma Hong Jun has been staying
in the village head's house.
You tricked him out on purpose?
Tang San,
with so many suspicious points,
you should have told us earlier.
This village is too weird.
I dared not say it.
Can you two
not argue at this time?
Hurry and find it.
Brother Dai, your wounds.
Ou Si Ke,
your Martial Soul.
Martial Soul?
I...
I'll pour you some water, Brother Dai.
Hurry up.
Here.
Here you go, Brother Dai.
Here, here, here.
Your Martial Soul can heal wounds.
Brother Dai,
you promised not to tell.
But I have to capture
the monster quickly.
If not, Ma Hong Jun and the village head
will be in danger.
Tang San,
go out for a while.
You can't peek.
I'm not peeking.
That...
You go and stand in the middle
of the courtyard.
Fine, fine, fine.
What are you all doing?
Brother Dai is injured.
Ou Si Ke is using his Martial Soul
to heal his wounds.
Dai Mu Bai is injured?
Recover fully!
He said what fully?
I heard it wrong.
Didn't you say he was injured?
You're done?
What is your Martial Soul?
It's so amazing.
I won't tell.
You can't tell either.
Let's find Ma Hong Jun first.
Are you Ma Hong Jun?
We're the Soul Masters
from Shi Lan Ke School.
Don't worry.
We've found
the black monster.
His mental condition
is different from what I saw yesterday.
He's more distrait today.
Brother,
if you don't sleep for a night,
you would be like this too.
This child is so pitiful.
He lives in such a shabby shack
with the wind blowing everywhere.
He must not have a good sleep
last night.
Look at his dark circles.
I'll bring him some water
for him to wash his face.
It should be able to wake him up.
Brother Dai,
last night Hu Lie Na said
the monster could have killed you,
but it didn't.
Right.
Why didn't it kill me?
I get it now.
I'm such a genius.
Tang San said before
that there were no chicken droppings
in this village.
Now this monster doesn't kill anyone.
Why?
This means that the monster
lives by eating chicken droppings!
I'm so smart!
It used to be a scary monster,
but you just made it disgusting.
Isn't this right?
Stop, stop, stop.
Let's analyse the identity
of this monster first.
Is it a Soul Master or a Soul Beast?
I fought with it yesterday,
and I'm sure
that it was a human form.
So we can rule out
the possibility of its being a Soul Beast.
Then his identity should be
a Soul Master.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪