ALL PLACES, CHARACTERS, FIRMS AND EVENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS SHOW ARE FICTITIOUS.
This is unbelievable.
Hey!
Seriously!
Your head! Hey!
EPISODE 6
Drink it.
Don't forget this!
SEVEN HOURS AGO
Geez, why are you so heavy?
My password is my birthday.
I know. You said that a hundred times.
Is it this one?
I can hear my house crumbling down.
No.
Mind the steps!
Slow down.
Good. Slow down.
You're as big as a bear.
Hyun-seung, let me take your bag off.
-My bag...
-Sit up.
-I don't have my bag.
Head.
Ow, you pulled out my hair.
Why are you laughing?
Hyun-seung, you know
this is your house, right?
I'm going home now. Bye.
No.
Why can't I go?
Let go!
-Let go!
-No, never.
Stop! You're being bad!
You're the worst.
I'll leave now.
What do you want me to do?
Let's go.
Huh?
-Let's go!
-Where?
Sit here, please.
Sit down, please. Okay, thank you.
Okay.
Wait a second.
What are you going to do?
Here.
These are all yours.
-Huh?
-Eat it all.
Oh! Okay.
It's 100% juice...
Drink it.
I can leave after I finish this, is it?
Finish it. It's good for your health.
Seriously.
Open your mouth.
You better remember this tomorrow.
Don't forget this!
You eat well.
You're pretty.
Pretty.
What?
What are you going to do now?
I'll get even with you tomorrow.
Starting from tomorrow,
we don't know each other.
Don't ever talk to me.
Do you remember what happened yesterday?
Yes, bit by bit...
Why did you drink so much?
You're not even a newbie.
It could've been hard to decline
since it was your first time.
Did they force you to drink?
No, it wasn't like that.
Why did you get drunk then?
That's not like you.
Well...
I wanted to do well.
Do well?
I wanted to fit in and adapt well,
so that you wouldn't worry.
Though I made you worry in the end.
I taught you wrong.
It's good to fit in,
but you must know how much you can handle.
Also, I never worry about you.
You're already doing well.
Why would I worry about
someone who's doing well?
In fact, you did too well yesterday.
Anyway, don't let this happen again.
Alright.
This is for you.
How do you feel?
I'm fine.
Why were you there last night though?
I was passing by.
The place?
Yes.
Let's go, we have to work.
Passing by?
Yes!
Come quickly!
Okay.
The reason I asked for the two of you
is because the chairman
demanded something.
Do you have data comparing between
the color cosmetics
of global brands and that of our brand?
Something about managing products or SKU?
We do, but it still has some rough edges.
SKU (STOCK KEEPING UNIT):
NUMBER OF PRODUCTS BEING MANAGED
How long will it take
if you two work on it together?
I can't be sure.
It's impossible to finish it by today.
Send it to me as soon as possible then.
After we presented the Europe Project,
he's gotten very interested
in color cosmetics.
You may leave now.
Sir, there's something I need to tell you.
What is it?
In this project, I...
I'll tell him.
I'll tell him about that.
What is it about?
ABM Yoon's mother lives alone.
So?
So it's hard for her to leave for
Europe for several years.
She's the only child.
So she's decided not to go?
Yes.
That can't be helped. What else can we do?
Find an alternative quickly.
Okay.
To meet your deadline,
it'll be really hard
to start from the design.
However, we can modify
what you're wearing...
I'll just go with this one.
Really?
But you have to meet the deadline
no matter what it takes.
-I'll leave now.
-Good job today.
What time is it?
-Good work. Bye.
-See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
I sent the report form already.
Fill in and send it back to me.
Yes, sir.
If you're feeling uncomfortable,
you don't have to do it here.
It's okay, sir.
Do as you wish.
I'm stepping outside for a bit.
Do you have a lot of work to do?
Do you need help?
No, it's okay. Go home.
Hey, Chae Hyun-seung!
Can't you show up in a normal way?
No. This is my charm.
Are you off work? Want to grab dinner?
Dinner?
Up for it?
Is that a yes?
What the...
I just don't feel like eating alone today.
This is the sandwich you like.
This is the strawberry milk you like.
This is mine.
What? Do you need something else?
Did I not bring wet wipes?
I'm okay.
It's just work.
Man.
You know what I'm thinking
even before I tell you.
It's so rewarding, being your boyfriend.
Just eat already.
Okay.
Seems like you need to write
a lot of reports these days.
Apparently, the company
is preparing a huge project.
So the chairman asked for
a bunch of information.
Oh, even the chairman?
Yes.
Are you on the fast track to success now?
Become an assistant manager
at a young age, and all the way to BM?
Why? Do you want me to guide you?
I'll be so grateful if you do.
I'll trust you and follow you.
I can never beat you.
Thanks for the food.
Enjoy your meal.
How may I help you?
Huh? Son!
Lee Se-dong's son, Mr. Lee Jae-shin?
Yes.
I told you my son works in a huge company.
How could you not believe me?
My son graduated from
the best university in Korea!
What's going on?
Mr. Lee Se-dong is
the victim of an assault.
The assailant is the man next to him.
-Ouch!
-Sheesh.
He can agree to a settlement...
I'll never agree to a settlement!
Then what?
You want to put him in jail?
You committed attempted fraud against him,
don't you know that?
I was wronged!
He was looking for a way
to earn some money,
so I recommended him
an investment scheme.
But I didn't know it was a fraud.
I was conned too!
And what's with your attitude?
I'm the sole victim here! Huh?
You swindler!
Seriously.
Sit down!
We'll find out the truth
after investigating his case.
We called you because he said
you can be his guarantor.
Can you do it?
We shouldn't have settled like that.
Why did you agree
to take that little money?
Didn't you go to a top university?
I got hit for nothing.
Hey, let's go somewhere for a bite.
I was in there for hours. I'm so hungry.
Hey! Where are you going?
Give me some money before you go.
I need money.
If I got a better settlement,
that would've solved my problem.
But I didn't because of you,
so you have to give me money.
So? Can you give it to me now?
Or
should I pay you a visit to your office?
You still work
at that shiny building, right?
Text me your account number.
I'll treat you to
something good next time.
If you insist.
Take care.
You, too.
Bye.
Jae-woon's sister took some pills
because of me.
After that, Jae-woon asked me
to marry his sister.
It was actually an order.
I had no option to refuse the order.
I had no choice but to marry her.
I can't get out
unless they let me go.
I just have to live like this.
So don't let me ruin
your opportunity to go to Europe.
I won't either.
I'm just an unpleasant eyesore
to you now, right?
Sooner or later, you won't even
care about me anymore.
Don't miss this golden chance
simply because of me.
Just focus on what's good for you.
You've always wanted a chance like this.
So pretty!
You're so pretty, Ha-eun!
It's so pretty.
Do you like it too, Ha-eun?
Your dresses are the prettiest
in the world.
You're even prettier.
Happy birthday, Ha-eun.
Thanks.
Go get changed so that
you can wear it on your birthday.
No, I want to wear this home.
It'll get wrinkled.
You can iron it for me.
Geez.
Can't you make dresses, Mom?
Why? Do you want me to make one for you?
Aunt Ji-seung makes dresses
while Uncle Hyun-seung makes cosmetics.
But you stay at home all the time.
What do you mean?
I'm busy raising you to be a pretty girl.
Do you want me to work?
Like Aunt Ji-seung?
No, you should do whatever you want.
Your favorite thing is raising me.
Of course.
So there's nothing wrong
with the mascara container?
Nothing changed?
The post-process and the thickness
are the same as before.
Shall I make the container thicker?
What about the cost variance then?
There's not much difference.
Then ask the manufacturer to...
Huh?
See you downstairs!
Oh, yes.
Here.
Thanks.
I should be buying.
No, it's okay.
When did you get back to Korea?
It's not the time for you
to return to the office yet.
I still have a few months left.
I dropped in because
I had something to report.
How have you been?
I hear your work is excellent, as always.
I'm just doing my best.
Don't work too much though.
So that you can work hard when I return.
The BM position in your team
might become vacant.
I have my eye on it.
Oh...
Wait, you know about that?
Are you involved in the Europe Project?
No. They did make an offer,
but I'm not sure.
Why?
It's such a good opportunity.
You have to take it.
Something is keeping you here?
Family? Boyfriend?
No.
I'm just wondering
if I'm qualified enough to go.
Oh? It's BM Choi. When did she come back?
Who is she?
She's at the European branch office.
She's a real hotshot.
Hello.
-I'm the one who contacted you.
-Nice to meet you.
Come this way, please.
Hyun-seung.
Yes, ma'am.
Go inside and get more freebies.
Please open them too.
We should organize it
in order to avoid confusion later.
Okay.
Sir!
We couldn't reach the model.
So the male model couldn't come?
They said he left,
but we couldn't get a hold of him.
There's no substitute, is it?
What did the agency say?
All the A-list models are booked.
Those who are available
aren't suitable for cosmetics.
What should we do?
We can't do this without a male model.
It's the main part.
I know.
Should I get prepared then?
Don't I look dandy today?
Just say something if I'm not.
It's awkward if you
don't say anything.
Did you invite male beauty influencers?
Yes, there're a few of them.
Should I ask them?
Let's call them first.
Where's the list?
Hyun-seung has it.
Hyun-seung!
Yes?
You have the list, right?
Huh?
Wait!
Wait for a second...
Me?
Hyun-seung, turn around.
Look, he's perfect.
There's no need to find someone else.
He has great complexion and build.
He's practically a model.
Isn't that right, sir?
Is it okay?
We're not forcing you,
so don't feel pressured.
Do whatever you like.
He seems to feel uncomfortable.
Find someone from our clients.
I'll do it.
I'll do it. I'll try it out.
That's a great decision. We're safe now.
Thanks, Hyun-seung.
Let's get you changed.
Help him with it, Song-ah.
Okay. Let's go, Hyun-seung.
Okay.
I'll go inside and get ready.
We should do a final check.
I'll make preparations.
Do the clothes fit well?
Yes, they do.
Give that to me.
We don't have much time.
Come here quickly.
Okay.
Wow, you have a great complexion.
It's better than
the beauty product models.
I'm flattered.
I'll style your hair first.
Okay.
All done.
Thank you.
Hello, everyone.
First of all, I'd like to thank
all the VIP clients
who took time out of their busy schedule
to come to the KLAR event.
This event is a beauty class
for our VIP clients.
It will be led by the makeup artist,
Jeon Hyun-hong.
Before we start, let's watch
a short video from KLAR.
WELCOME TO KLAR'S VIP BEAUTY CLASS!
Get the artist and
female model ready first.
Already?
Hyun-seung has only
gotten his hair styled.
Song-ah, help him with the skincare then.
You can do it, right?
Yes, I can...
Okay, I'll do it.
Great. Please follow me.
Thank you for doing it.
Ignore my clumsiness, okay?
You'll do fine. Don't worry.
Senior Yoon.
Huh?
Can I ask you something?
What?
Are you going to Europe?
How did you know about that?
No matter what your decision is,
I'll support you.
I really wanted to say that.
They ask for the male model now.
Okay!
Okay.
Hurry up.
KLAR'S VIP BEAUTY CLASS INVITATION
Let's jump into the next stage
of KLAR's makeup world.
The model is very handsome, isn't he?
Yes!
Please give him a round of applause
so he'll do well today.
Thank you.
You should brighten up three spots
with the foundation.
First,
the forehead.
Then, the ridge of the nose.
Lastly, the triangle zone.
Keep the amount to a bare minimum.
The shade should be one level
brighter than the skin.
How many levels? Yes, one level.
Go along the texture of the skin.
Do it gently.
Will you face the audience?
Thank goodness, he's doing well.
I can do well too.
Never.
You can just say no. Why say never?
It often looks awkward
because of the color difference.
Brighten the front part of the neck
with the same shade
to give it a three-dimensional effect.
No matter what your decision is,
I'll support you.
If you apply it vertically
and horizontally,
it will fix better on the skin.
Now, I'll show you
how to apply lip products.
Hello.
You can give it to me.
Here.
Please follow me. This way.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me!
We met before, haven't we?
We met at the store the other time.
Don't you remember?
Hello.
I thought you were a store employee.
Turns out you're from HQ.
KLAR Team.
Yoon Song-ah.
I have to go now.
Okay, bye.
Are you going inside?
No, I'm done.
Wow, this is great. How much is it?
3,000 won?
It's cheap and good.
Hi, I'm here.
Welcome.
Bracken and bellflower roots.
Okay.
It's for my husband's memorial service,
so give me the best ones.
Okay, you're so fussy.
What about your daughter?
She's on her way.
By the way, shouldn't she get married now?
My nephew works in Seoul too.
Should I set them up?
She's only 28 years old.
She's too young to get married.
Stop talking nonsense
and give me my stuff.
Alright.
Why is everyone interested
in her marriage?
She's my daughter.
Wait a minute, is this girl coming or not?
Sheesh.
Yes.
Have you reached?
Don't get into a fight with her.
I know, don't worry.
WE'RE CLOSED FOR TODAY.
Spend the night there.
Okay, I'll call you.
Okay.
MY LOVELY DEAR.
Hey, you're home?
Sweetie! Where are you?
Huh?
Sweetie!
When did you get here?
Throw these away.
And Dad's photos too.
Why sleep in the living room
when you have your own room?
You just came home
and you're nagging me already.
Also,
they represent your father.
Why would I throw them away?
They're precious.
All done.
Really?
Let's see.
Great, it's sturdy and good.
The task is done.
Why order self-assembly furniture
when you can't do it?
Why do you think I did?
Because it's cheap.
Didn't you do well
in the finance business?
Where did all that money go?
Where do you think it went?
I bought you meals and drinks
when you were in school.
I don't recall you buying me anything.
I did. Think hard.
Okay, I'll think about it on my way home.
Bye.
What?
What are all those?
How can I do that all by myself?
I called someone to help you out.
Who?
Why would you call me
on a weekend?
I hope your dad enjoys the food.
He loved my radish sprouts.
So, how are you doing?
If you hung up like that,
you should've called back.
Don't you wonder
if your mother is dead or alive?
Did something happen last time?
It sounded like you were crying.
Let's hold Dad's memorial
at a temple or somewhere else.
What are you talking about?
It's been 13 years since he left.
You're still young.
You should make a fresh start.
Are you telling me to
abandon your father and get married?
Abandon who?
He died a long time ago.
You're one heartless girl.
Your father means so much to me.
How could you tell me to abandon him
and go find another man?
What kind of daughter are you?
Are you, by any chance,
trying to get rid of me
because of your boyfriend?
What kind of person was he?
What?
Was Dad such a great person
for you to be devoted like this?
What are you talking about?
Of course, your dad was a good person.
He behaved socially even without laws.
He loved me so much.
He was good to you too.
I can't believe how ungrateful you are!
Huh? Where are you going?
You haven't finished eating.
I finished it.
Seriously, that girl.
Every time...
Thanks for working so hard!
It was worth raising you,
my precious juniors!
So that's why you bought us meals
when we were in school.
It was all for today.
Right? I bought you a lot of meals, right?
But why don't you remember?
You bought meals mainly for girls.
I acknowledge that.
But among the guys,
I treated you the best.
By the way, about the money I spent on
buying you drinks...
You can pay me back
by hanging out with me until I die.
That's too harsh.
I didn't even drink that much.
I'll just pay you back in cash.
Keep it.
Anyway,
accidental death can't be helped.
I'll deal with dying of hunger.
You two are responsible
to prevent me from dying alone.
Including me?
It'll bore me if I see
the same person all the time.
You're being picky
under such circumstances?
I'm good at scheming.
You're almost like a loan shark.
Man.
This won't do.
Huh?
I should find a woman for him.
There must be an angel out there
who will take him in.
You don't have any preferences, do you?
Nope. None.
Okay.
That's wise.
Got anyone?
I'm in the lobby.
Okay, I'll wait. Take your time.
Did you, by any chance, come to see me?
I guess not.
What brings you here?
If it's okay for you,
would you like to have lunch with me?
It's lunchtime.
Sir, you're on your way
to a lunch meeting.
I can cancel it.
It was planned a month ago, so you can't.
I can make the impossible possible.
Yes, I'm quite competent.
I made plans already.
Oh, I guess not today then.
But we'll see each other soon.
You'll soon be able to buy
the lipstick you were looking for.
When you get the word,
you can come anytime you want.
I'll doll up and wait for you.
Ji-seung!
Hey!
What brings you here?
The pop-up store project.
I've decided to do it.
You did?
You're on a roll!
But I don't know
if I made the right decision.
I don't know if I can
handle a bigger business.
You'll do great. I guarantee it.
You've gotten thin.
Something happened?
Me?
I'm fine.
For real. Nothing happened.
Do you want me to set you up
on blind dates?
It's better for you to go.
How's it going with the blind date
Yeon-seung mentioned before?
I don't know.
By the way...
What?
Is it easy to reproduce
a discontinued makeup product?
For example, lipstick.
Of course not.
We have to revive a dead product line.
The process is complicated,
and it doesn't always succeed.
It's harder than increasing
the production volume.
Why do you ask?
Huh?
No reason. Have your lunch.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Manager Yoo.
She went to the training team.
ABM Yoon, come with me to the store.
It's urgent, so get ready immediately.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting, sir.
Hello, sir.
Are you an employee?
Yes, I'm ABM Yoon Song-ah from KLAR.
I thought you'd be curious
about the products.
She knows everything
about color cosmetics.
Is that so? Nice to meet you.
This snack tastes better
when I eat it like this.
You already ate a lot at lunch.
The cafeteria lunch wasn't enough for me.
Manager Ahn? Hey!
What's on your mind?
Why is BM Lee taking Song-ah everywhere?
Is there something going on?
Senior Yoon left with BM Lee?
Yes.
They hurriedly went to the store.
It's not good to be
called to urgent matters.
Still,
there must be something going on.
You must be really exhausted
with all the wild thoughts.
You make me more exhausted.
Yes, hello?
This is Chae Hyun-seung from KLAR.
I'm Chief Kim.
Oh, yes. Hello.
Hi, is ABM Yoon Song-ah not in?
She's on outside duty right now.
You can talk to me.
What?
We took special care
in displaying the products.
As you can see,
the eyeliners are over here.
The front part here is the skincare line.
The lipsticks I told you about
are our main items,
so we placed it close to the entrance.
Would you like to see it?
Darn it!
I saw you take it.
You saw it wrong.
Go check on them.
Show me what's in your pocket.
Why should I?
If you keep this up, I'll call the police.
Call then!
What's going on?
This girl stole a product,
but she insists she didn't.
I didn't steal it!
Let me see what's in your pocket then.
Why should I show it to you?
You should prove me wrong.
Are you sure she stole it?
Yes, she definitely stole it.
There are surveillance cameras, right?
Yes.
But it's a blind spot,
so it might not be on the camera.
I should call the police.
Just send them away.
This isn't important right now.
Just send them away?
What's the problem?
What's going on?
This student stole a product, sir.
I told you I didn't!
You're confident
you didn't steal it, right?
Right! I didn't steal!
How many times do I have to say it?
You tell me.
She said she didn't steal it!
Not that. Tell me what you know.
She didn't steal.
Is that so?
You're at the age
where you want these things.
Fill a basket with all kinds of products.
Yes, sir.
I want to make a deal with you.
If you tell the truth,
I'll give you everything in that basket.
You'll really give me all of it?
Hey!
Of course.
Fill another basket.
Yes, sir.
Well...
Darn it! Seriously! Here!
I was just going to test it.
Let her go.
I can take these, right?
You said I can take them
if I tell the truth.
What have you done?
You got this back because of me.
Did you say your friend stole it?
You lost your chance while hesitating
for your shallow friendship.
If you ask for something
when you did nothing,
you become a thief too.
Don't you agree?
What a jerk!
Young ones and old ones alike...
They say they're friends and all,
but when there's profit involved,
they stab you in the back.
That's why you shouldn't
let strangers in your house.
Things that need to
stay outside must stay outside.
Let's go.
So the package was misprinted
for the re-produced lipstick?
Yes, the previous one
was for limited edition,
so Senior Yoon sent them a new one.
But they printed the previous one.
I'm sorry, I must've been out of my mind.
The event will take place
two days later, isn't it?
Director Lee is paying
extra attention to it.
Can we ship it tomorrow
if we print a new one now?
They said it's possible
tomorrow afternoon.
It can't be shipped tomorrow then.
Well,
let's report to BM Lee first.
Oh, stickers!
That's what Senior Yoon did
when they misprinted the leaflet.
Can't we do that this time?
I don't see why not.
We can take care of
the urgent ones that way.
You can make stickers quickly, right?
Yes, I'll tell them to make it quickly.
Attaching them is the problem.
Will the factory do it?
It's hard to get part-timers
on short notice,
and I can't go either.
I'll go then.
We need to send the stickers anyway.
Is that okay, Manager Kang?
Go if you want to suffer.
Why would you say that?
Proceed with the stickers first.
-Yes, ma'am.
-I'll ask the factory to get part-timers.
Let's see if you'll
need to go, Hyun-seung.
I'll report to BM Lee.
Okay.
Go on ahead.
Why would you put up with that?
You said they wouldn't let you go.
Then why are you being treated that way?
What's wrong with it?
In return, I can live like
a decent human being elsewhere.
I have to pay back my debt.
I think you've paid back plenty
for what you've been doing.
If that's not it...
Do you want to
keep your position that much?
Yes.
If I put up with being humiliated
by a few people,
no one will think I'm that criminal's son.
Is it because of your father...
I'm going to persevere.
No matter what.
That's why I need you.
You haven't changed a bit after two years.
You still live like the teenager
who had nothing.
I taped cushions on the stools
for your comfort.
Thank you.
I tried to get more part-timers,
but only the two of them are available.
And they only work until nine o'clock.
-Nine o'clock?
-Yes.
Thank you for doing this.
Sure.
The stickers?
Here, they are here.
Okay. Good luck.
Thanks.
Goodbye.
Bye.
Wow, when will you finish all of that?
Seems like you need to
pull an all-nighter.
-Goodbye!
-Bye.
Okay, then. Let's begin.
-Okay.
I'm already sick of this.
When will we finish everything?
You'll buy us coffee, right?
Coffee? Oh, okay.
Oh, I made a mistake.
Luckily the stools are cushy.
Right.
So Hyun-seung is at the factory now?
Yes.
They hired part-timers,
but there are not enough people.
So we sent him.
He stepped up for his ex-trainer's job.
You raised him well.
I should've raised my trainee well too.
Right, Manager Ahn?
Major fail.
Oh, no. I don't know what to say.
We have to go now.
Oh, I'm sorry. Feel free to leave.
But will you be able to do this all alone?
Even if you're up all night,
I don't think you'll finish.
I can do it. I'll have to try.
He's so optimistic.
Take it easy.
-Okay.
-Let's go.
Get home safely.
You're so handsome.
I feel bad.
I can do this!
Senior Yoon.
Are you still attaching stickers?
Yes.
How many do you have left?
Well...
I'm almost done.
I'll finish in an hour or two.
That's good.
I heard the stickers were your idea.
Good work.
It's all thanks to you.
Since I have to do well
without you after this.
Huh?
Without me?
Yes. Without you.
But I'm staying though.
What?
I'm not going.
I'm not going to Europe.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Really?
You can do that?
Why can't I do that?
Hello?
Oh, uh...
I'm sorry. Please wait.
I'll call you back in a second.
What?
Yes!
Calm down.
Calm down, Chae Hyun-seung.
I said calm down.
Thank you!
Yes, the water in Europe tastes bad.
She's not going!
Black hair.
Her height is...
European song.
What the...
What in the world!
Senior Yoon?
You dance really well.
What is this?
You said you'll finish in an hour or two.
Where should I start?
One glass, please.
Okay.
You haven't changed a bit
after two years.
You still live like the teenager...
You scumbag!
Who had nothing.
Son!
What do I have then?
Senior Yoon.
Huh?
Can I ask why you decided
not to go to Europe?
Because it's not what I want to do.
I like what I'm doing now.
Also,
Korean food suits my taste better.
SHE WOULD NEVER KNOW
That's our BM Lee, right?
-I think so.
-He's the only BM who is still unmarried.
I'm getting married.
Congratulations!
Are you okay?
What do you like about me?
Because I'm very ambitious.
Let's go. I'll maintain the distance
if that's what you wish.
-Stop laughing.
-Just like now.