(Doom at Your Service)
(All characters, locations, organizations, religions,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
The deity is on my side.
Choose. Will you die here and now?
Or will you take my hand?
And the answer is...
Me.
Don't let go.
Don't let go unless you want to die right now.
(Episode 2)
How is this possible?
All we did was go back in time.
- It's nothing that grand. - Not that.
Your...
How do I put it?
I'm searching for a term that won't sound rude.
- My identity? - Yes.
Are you suspicious or curious?
Neither. I'm simply being rational.
But you saw earlier.
You experienced it first hand. Accept it.
That's easier said than done.
- You're alive right now. - So?
It was Switzerland and then Italy outside your door.
So?
In your dream, on the subway, and at work.
Don't you remember?
I do remember. But it makes no sense.
I feel like I've gone insane.
Okay. Watch.
What?
- Oh my gosh. - Did the lights go out?
What's wrong with this?
What about this?
That's odd. What's going on?
A timely coincidence?
- What's going on? - My phone turned off.
- Why did it suddenly turn off? - It won't work.
Did the battery die?
A timely coincidence?
I see.
Are you an electric type?
- Look. - What's that in the sky?
Are they comets?
My gosh.
Comets out of the blue?
Okay. I get it, so stop.
Why? I didn't do that.
I'm an electric type.
I said to stop it.
Stop it.
What's going on?
The power's back.
I'm not very nice.
My phone turned back on too.
That's with whom you entered into a contract.
Remember that I'm evil.
I need to stop fooling around, and go.
- All of a sudden? - Something annoying happened.
Consider that a show to commemorate our contract.
I hope you enjoy yourself.
You didn't want to hold it before. Now, you don't want to let go?
You said not to let go.
- What's this? - My promise.
I said I'd make sure you don't feel pain.
Don't relax too much.
You have to recharge it once a day before midnight.
Recharge it? How?
- By holding my hand. - What? Why?
In case you run away.
And think of a wish, Tak Dong Kyung.
Hey. How do you know my name?
Hey!
Excuse me.
Yes?
Do you remember the crosswalk earlier?
- You don't remember? - No, I don't.
I guess it really didn't happen.
You're such high maintenance.
I'll kill you in due time.
I said not to park your car in my spot,
but you keep trying.
Doom is my domain.
Do something.
I keep hearing the voices.
I can't sleep. It's driving me crazy.
- Die. - You piece of trash.
- Stop. - Coward.
- Die. - He deserves to die.
Die, you murderer.
- Coward. - Die.
He should be ripped apart!
- Die! - Die.
How does it feel?
I deal with it every day.
Please kill me! I'm begging you!
Three of the people you stabbed died.
Two of them are still in a coma.
But you're alive and well. You should thank me.
That wasn't my plan.
It wasn't.
Life doesn't go as planned.
I'll stop here for today.
I got a good contract today, so I'm feeling chipper.
Who are you?
Have you ever heard this phrase?
"I am the first and the last, the beginning and the end."
I'm that. The last. The end.
Hey!
Why are you doing this to me? What do you want?
Doom.
(Jo Scum)
Why is he calling me?
Hey. I know you won't believe what I'm about to tell you,
but hear me out without giving me lip...
Hello?
Ji Na!
What's wrong?
What is it? What's wrong?
I'm going to die.
- What? - I'm going to die!
Why?
Wait. Don't tell me...
I lost it all.
It's divine will.
My writing was garbage, so the powers at be deleted it.
They should've done it before I finished it.
What was with those comets?
What was with the power outage?
What else?
It's a sign that I should die.
Take care. Goodbye.
Why should you die?
This is all that jerk's fault.
That jerk?
Who? Bill Gates?
Just someone. Anyway.
Ji Na.
Sit down for now. Okay?
Stop acting like an amateur.
You know better than anyone what you must do in this situation.
No, I don't. Should I die?
There is only one solution, Ms. Na.
What?
Write it all again within an hour.
What? My suicide note?
The chapter.
The chapter?
I'm going to the roof.
Finish your chapter first.
What's the point though?
No one likes it.
They don't like it much at the company either, right?
What did they say? Be honest.
It's boring.
I don't think romance is her forte.
The male protagonist is too bland.
The number of reads keeps dropping.
But once readers have to pay to read a story,
the number drops to half on average...
Jung Min, would you go out with that male protagonist?
- Excuse me? - Not me.
I'll ask her to reduce the number of chapters...
and to end it sooner.
Sure. Let's end this one.
Let's see how she does on her next story.
They said it's worth waiting and seeing.
Don't lie to me! The number of reads dropped to half.
Half the readers stop reading...
once they have to pay for the chapters.
That's true.
So let's just write, okay?
If you miss the upload time,
you'll lose the remaining half too.
Here.
Did you eat?
That's not real food.
This is filling.
I have no time to write, let alone cook.
This is much better than anything I cook...
in both taste and nutrition.
Ji Na...
Where do I even start?
What? Did you say something?
I'm going to run to the convenience store.
Okay.
Hello.
(Mr. Jung Dang Myun)
Hello, Mr. Jung. May I help you with something?
You're the one who needs help, Ms. Tak Dong Kyung.
Why are you full-naming me?
Was there an error with the upload?
Are you even scared?
I'm calling as a doctor, not a writer.
I'm calling to threaten you.
I see. That.
You may feel fine now,
but it'll become so painful that you'll want to die.
This isn't a threat, it's a fact.
Will it keep getting worse?
Are you kidding me?
In other words, do I want to die after suffering tremendous pain...
or after suffering slightly milder than tremendous pain.
I have to choose one or the other, right?
I don't want either.
Don't think of doing anything rash.
Don't do that.
I already did something rash.
I don't regret it.
Doom is knocking at the door.
Repent and be saved.
(The world is coming to an end.)
- It is? - Yes.
The countless evil deeds that we've committed...
angered the Almighty.
For example,
the comets today were proof that the end is near.
Doom is coming. It's knocking at our door.
(The world is coming to an end.)
You're right.
The Almighty is angry. Doom is drawing near.
Are you angry?
I'm feeling fine today.
Maybe you will be angry soon.
You said to become a human's wish.
But that human's wish happens to be doom.
- That's amusing. - Isn't it?
Until now, humans only wished to win the lottery,
for their health or happiness, and things like that.
Do you know? If the garden is gone...
The gardener and the butterfly won't be needed anymore.
At least respond.
Do what you want. I plan to do what I want too.
Tell me this one thing.
Why me?
Who knows?
Fate?
That's cruel.
Fate is cruel to everyone.
You'll be punished if you do something bad.
I'm already being punished.
(Jo Scum)
You're screening my calls?
You'll regret it.
(You're screening my calls? You'll regret it.)
I said you'd regret it.
Ji Na, I need to rush back into the office.
Sorry. I'll buy dinner tomorrow.
What?
Tak Dong Kyung must repent!
Tak Dong Kyung, who works here,
is a homewrecker.
She seduced me, a well-behaved, happily married man!
Seduced?
That doesn't belong in the same sentence as "Do Kyung".
The naive man that I am, I fell for it.
Naive?
And I ended up losing my precious wife!
How could this happen?
Tak Dong Kyung must repent!
Excuse me. You can't do this in our office.
- Get out. - I'm angry, that's why.
Get out.
Tak Dong Kyung must repent!
Let's talk outside.
You are just incredible.
How can you eat after ruining my life?
I said let's talk outside.
Forget it.
What did you say to my wife?
What did you say that she wants a divorce?
"I didn't know he was married."
"I was deceived."
"I did nothing wrong."
"He's the one who was wrong."
That's what I said. So?
I am dumbfounded.
Hey. It wasn't love for me.
How do I put it?
It just happened.
Even if we end it, we should have manners!
Manners?
You're talking about manners?
That's right! Manners! M-A-N-E-R!
M-A-N-N-E-R.
To be honest, what do you have to offer?
You don't have anything everyone else has.
You have no parents or money. What do you have?
And think of a wish, Tak Dong Kyung.
Should I make that wish right now?
What?
Forget it.
It'll be too much of a waste to use it on the likes of you.
Is this the time?
Is this the time for what?
Doom.
What are you babbling about?
I'm saying I want to kill you.
You can tell when someone grew up with no parents...
in these situations.
This is why...
I won't let my child grow up without a dad!
Excuse me!
Excuse me. From what I can see,
you're the highest up here.
It's extremely bad for the company image...
to have an employee like her.
So... Wait. Hold on.
Darn it.
Don't let outsiders in so easily.
Is everyone okay?
I think the lunch gave me indigestion.
Fire the homewrecker...
Tak Dong Kyung! Fire her!
- I'm this nitwit's wife. - What...
- Everything he says is a lie. - Honey.
- Sorry for the trouble. - Wait.
I was about to leave. You have the wrong idea.
- Hey. - Let's go.
Honey, the baby. Be careful of the baby.
Hey, you, Dong Kyung!
Hold on. Honey!
I'll kill you!
- Darn it. - Shut it!
Wow. Gosh.
("Life" group chat)
(I'm staring at the clock. I'm getting coffee.)
Big news. You'll never guess what happened in our office.
If I hear anyone typing, I will kill you.
Hey!
It wasn't me.
(Resignation)
I'll resign.
I don't have the authority.
Mr. Park isn't in right now.
Please submit it for me.
I can't be bothered.
And it isn't business hours yet.
- When will Mr. Park be back? - I don't know.
Excuse me?
He went to Bali with his girlfriend to celebrate making up.
Bali to make it up to my queen.
A man in charge of a company.
However, for tonight, a man who exists for one woman.
Looking good, sir.
Enjoy your vacation.
Enjoy a long vacation, sir.
(Like)
Recharge.
Why couldn't you cross the street?
- I was too scared. - Then you should've called me.
- How? - However.
You sound like you're on my side.
That's all in your head.
How was your day?
Why are you asking that?
Who knows?
You may want to bring doom today.
That will make things easier.
I have a question.
What happens if I break this contract?
If you break it?
What if I don't feel pain until I die and get my wish,
but I die without asking you to end this world?
Will you do that?
Then someone else will die instead of you.
The person you love the most at that moment.
What? What do you...
I'll remove the doom from here to there.
It's simple.
That's not what you promised.
I made no promise.
All contracts have penalties for breaches.
I don't know. Regardless, you've entered into a contract.
It's a done deal.
You fraud.
Would it have been different if you had known?
I doubt that.
Okay. I'll be fair.
I'll give you another chance to choose.
What will you do now?
Choose quickly. You'll die at that rate.
Hey.
When you gain something, you must lose something.
Think hard.
Everything you've gained in life were thanks to things you lost.
Why?
Why me?
Why? Why must it be me?
Fate.
That's cruel.
Fate is cruel to everyone.
Stop! Stop it!
See?
Scumbag.
I've heard that so much.
Is it fun toying with me?
Like I said, I'm not on your side.
It was your choice.
And naturally, I will always respect your decision.
Will you keep standing here?
Fine, suit yourself. I'm going to cross.
It's getting boring.
Why?
Why me?
Why? Why must it be me?
Fate?
That's cruel.
Dong Kyung!
I got your favourite rice cake.
Look. I bought a lot.
Then someone else will die instead of you.
The person you love the most at that moment.
What's wrong?
I took care of the insurance matter.
It turned out...
the owner of the rental car company was my classmate's brother's...
distant aunt's fourth cousin...
Anyway, it was someone I knew so I got it resolved.
It's true!
What's wrong?
Were you drinking?
Did you come up with a new way to kill me?
Dong Kyung.
Excuse me. One roll of gimbap please.
Okay.
That's a dollar. Thank you.
I'm so angry.
The most important thing is to keep them wanting more.
You have to play hard to get.
That way, the readers will wonder what happens to the characters...
and will drool and follow us.
Know what I mean?
It should be like a skirt that you can almost look up.
A shirt?
Does the author Lee Hyun not go to the office much?
Pardon?
I hear she's really pretty.
I hear you two are close.
Let me meet her.
Who knows?
Writers get each other.
If we hit it off,
we may...
You know.
People need to know their place.
What?
Him.
This wrinkly old man...
doesn't know his place and does what he does.
Did you do that on purpose?
Does he die later on?
That has nothing to do with social perspective.
It's a set-up to accentuate a truly pure, innocent love.
That's the kind of jerk...
that lies about his marital status to lure an ordinary single woman.
What?
Why does social perspective have nothing to do with love?
Love that goes beyond social perspective is a crime.
Is he a criminal?
Ms. Tak. How can you say that?
What's wrong?
I'm in awe because your writing is so realistic.
You weren't like this.
People who suddenly change die soon.
Is this because I asked about Lee Hyun?
No. It's because my time's almost up.
I'm already wondering if it's today or tomorrow.
What? Where are you going when we're still talking?
I'm off to see the pretty Lee Hyun.
- It's because of a man. - A man?
What man? I don't even know a male insect.
Think carefully.
He's very close to water.
Water?
He's standing right in your way.
You're being dragged down by a ghost that drowned!
You can't change your pen name now.
The fortune-teller told me to get rid of everything about him.
- Thanks. I'll enjoy the food. - Sure.
Why did I take his name as my pen name?
And why did he have to swim?
It's really chilling.
How did she know about water?
Ji Na, who is this fortune-teller?
Why? Is something not working out?
Work's a problem.
Will you change jobs?
Do it. If you don't like it, jump ship.
There are many other publishers.
I don't exactly want to jump ship.
- Tak. - What?
Should I...
quit writing?
Ji Na!
I'll cook the rice for you.
You can eat once the cheese melts.
Ji Na.
What do you want to do if you die in 100 days?
Why? Am I dying?
I'm just curious.
First, I want to buy a five-tier cake and eat it whole.
- What else? - I guess I'd go travelling.
What else?
I don't know. I never thought about it.
I thought about it just now, while our rice was being cooked.
I want to die after making you a success.
That's why I'll say this.
It'll be shocking, but don't be too shocked.
Quit publishing serially.
Not right away but within the month.
Consider it wrapping up your story short.
It's all his fault.
Lee Hyun Kyu, the darn water ghost.
Also, this isn't that big of a deal,
but it turned out that my boyfriend...
was a married man.
What?
He's insane!
You saw it for yourselves,
and you have brains to think with.
What do you think, Mr. Cha?
I have no thoughts.
Okay. Go on having no thoughts.
Jung Min?
Whatever the situation may be,
it's a fact it was an affair.
Would she do that?
You can never truly know someone.
The guy looked pretty loaded.
Would you like anyone with money?
Why don't you seduce our CEO, then?
What does that mean?
You seemed to envy her for dating a rich guy.
You're gutsy for saying that to his face.
I suddenly feel sick.
I think we reached an agreement. Let's go.
We can't leave work on time, so let's try to do less overtime.
- I'm not yet... - You haven't agreed?
I have.
Guess what?
The café owner's dad owns this building.
- No way. - No way.
Welcome. Just a moment.
- He must live in the penthouse. - Come by again.
I heard the landlord's son stays here to maintain the building.
Then the yellow sports car in the basement parking...
must be his as well.
I heard it belongs to the landlord's son.
(Lee Hyun Kyu)
- Bye. - Take care.
Welcome back.
- I thought you quit. - You said no.
Why won't you go home, then?
I have some editing to do.
Why work hard if you're going to quit?
Will you do this for me, then?
Work hard.
What did Ms. Lee Hyun say?
She said yes.
She knows better than anyone her work isn't that popular.
What did you and Jijo talk about?
It's Jijo King, not just Jijo.
I can't bear saying his full name.
I criticized him a bit.
What's the occasion? You never criticize anyone.
Good for you.
He wants a different editor. Someone pretty.
Does he think we edit with our looks? That's just stupid.
Pretty Jung Min can handle him.
- Am I pretty? - Yuck.
Sorry. I have a weak stomach.
I said I'd edit his work. I'm the prettiest here.
Why did you date someone like that?
I was working at a café...
and someone passing by almost spilled coffee on my laptop.
I'd almost finished editing about 80 episodes worth of a novel.
He suddenly showed up and shielded me with his body.
- He scored. - He scored.
He scored.
I said I'd pay for the dry-cleaning and he asked me out for coffee.
And you saw the rest.
I did. It must've been tough.
I can only fill this many pages.
In movies or dramas,
people who are about to die...
leave everything behind just fine.
And think of a wish,
Tak Dong Kyung.
I have no money to spend, dreams to achieve,
or love to work on.
If I had 10 years to live, I'd want money, dreams,
or even love,
but I only have 100 days left.
Then someone else will die instead of you.
The person you love the most at that moment.
The life I'll live after that...
is nothing short of doom.
You wanted this world to end.
I'm exhausted.
Does everyone live like this?
Being harassed by both...
life and death?
As if they're neither alive nor dead?
(5th Ward)
- Ms. Kim, the defibrillator. - Okay.
Are you all right?
I don't think I'll see my 20th birthday in this lifetime.
What kind of deity is always sick to death or dead sad?
Someone has to pay the price for this world to exist.
Is the price tag this time a heart disease?
I think it's because people here call for the deity the most.
True. They called you to be born.
I opened my eyes the moment a lot of people called out for me.
So I will willingly pay the price.
That is the job of a deity the people called upon and...
your job as the creation of a deity.
You already know that...
you cannot avoid your fate.
She will not give up on the world.
Not like you did.
I will make her give up on it.
Will you?
Even if you do, will it be possible?
Humans created the deity. Of course they can bring doom to this world.
You and I both are humans' will.
Then I must do whatever it takes.
Because that's not all the humans want.
You should go before midnight.
The deity is never ignorant.
We just pretend to be.
Are you ready?
One, two.
I'll take one more.
No. Smile brightly.
Do you have a death wish?
- Pardon? - Why are you here?
Do you want another slap?
Is that how you usually apologize?
I don't feel sorry.
You can fight after I take your photo.
Smile.
Smile. He wants you to.
Can you shave a little more off my chin?
Then it won't be your face.
- Does that matter? - It does.
ID photos are used to identify you.
This isn't for an ID.
Print it out in that size.
And frame it too.
It's usually black, right?
Shall I make your eyes bigger too?
- Yes. - Then...
Do you have to do this? A car would be more comfortable.
I won't ride your car.
Who knows what'll happen?
Then take a bus.
Don't talk to me. I feel like walking in silence.
You waste your time.
Shouldn't you be trying to spend every second well?
You only look at me when I pick a fight.
Humans are really weird.
Why make things like that?
You never get to see them yourself.
It's for others, not me.
I'm like that sometimes.
Then you decided to die.
Do things like you only care about yourselves?
You have no idea how much I put others first.
Look at me now.
You slapped me, but I'm here to save you.
Time's ticking.
Get used to it, if you want to walk with me.
Did you do that?
I didn't do it,
but it is because of me.
(911 Ambulance)
Was that you too?
Sometimes.
(18 traffic accidents yesterday in Seoul, 2 dead, 8 injured)
Yes.
How do you live like that?
I don't live. I just exist.
I'm just a button of doom.
Every step I take, every move my hand makes,
every breath I take.
Everything about me leads to doom.
I exist for that.
And if you don't do anything?
What if you don't do anything?
All hell breaks out on earth.
Unusual temperatures persist and the cause is yet unknown.
It's October, and all over the country,
heat waves and drought...
This year's harvest is a disaster.
- There's no point. - I hate the world.
- It's crazy. - It's insane.
- How can he kill his kid? - Why won't Mom just die?
- You darn scumbag. - Why won't a deity kill him first?
"If you gain something, you lose something."
"Everything you've gained in life were thanks to things you lost."
I get what that means now.
You need winter to have spring,
and darkness to have light.
Death must exist for life. It's like that, isn't it?
So you are winter, darkness,
and death.
Yes.
Like you said, you really do care for nothing but others.
You just had to come to me when you cared only about yourself.
How long must we hold hands for?
I thought you held on because you liked it.
Why follow me all the way here? It's too much pressure.
But thanks anyway.
You can go now. I won't run away again.
Shall we meet again tomorrow?
- What? - Shall I come for you?
It's up to you.
Why are you like this so suddenly?
Why do I care whether you crawl in pain or not?
Do you have a mood disorder or something?
Why do you suddenly change tune?
Hey, things were nice between us just now.
We were beginning to understand and figure out each other.
I'm saying you should be more clingy.
To you?
To your fate that came to you.
Hey, Tak Dong Kyung.
Tak Dong Kyung.
What do you want?
I don't see straight right now.
I was out of my mind, Dong Kyung.
I didn't mean what I said.
It shouldn't be past tense. You still are out of your mind.
You have completely lost it!
We loved each other. We were in love!
What I said at your work wasn't true. That was nonsense.
This is how I truly feel. I'm drunk but honest.
Yes, "Drunk Honesty".
I sang that song for you many times.
Don't you remember?
Let go of me. I said let go!
If you're drunk, go home! Why did you come here?
Yes, I might be drunk
This might be a mistake
Every morning
Now I will confess
I loved you from the start
Let go of me.
Let go of me already.
Get out of my life!
My awkward ramblings
Darn you.
- I may be crude - Let go!
- I may not sound trustworthy - Oh, gosh. Let go!
Who are you?
Let go. Let go of me!
Was that a wish?
- What? - "Get out of my life."
Are you crazy? Why would I waste my wish on him?
Will you let go of me?
Then shall I get rid of him like this?
Honey.
"Honey"?
Your husband.
"Honey"? Tak Dong Kyung, who is this jerk?
This must be the sicko you were talking about.
Leave him to me. Go inside and have dinner.
I made cold cucumber soup, your favourite, sweetie.
"Sweetie"?
Cold cucumber soup?
Tak Dong Kyung.
Were you seeing someone? Were you living with someone?
This actually works much better.
I lied about being married and you that you live with a guy.
That makes us even. We can start over, can't we?
What are you lot doing?
What's going on?
Hey.
It's not what you think. Don't.
Who is married and who's she living with?
I'll whack the married one first.
- No, wait, why... - Hey.
- Hey. - What are you doing?
- Come here! - Darn it.
Shoot.
It's hilarious.
Just dumbfounding.
Leave it. I'll clean it up.
Thanks for help...
I said I'd make it so you don't hurt.
I see why you thought of me.
I wondered what kind of person would make that wish at that time.
I wasn't thinking of you.
I am doom myself.
You were the only person who had the same thought at the same time.
I'm grateful.
In many ways.
Hey.
This won't do.
Let's live together.
You and me.
(Doom at Your Service)
Why did I ask him to live with me?
Embarrassment lasts but just a second.
- Hi, brother-in-law. - Hey.
What are all these bottles? And this sofa?
Where do I sleep?
Was that him?
The one you love the most.
Can't you change his fate?
Give me your hand.
I'm not human.
I feel no pity or love.
I don't have that kind of feeling.
I do, because I'm human.
So become the first human to love me.