LAW SCHOOL
ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS, CASES
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIOUS
-Damn you…
-Hey, you!
Assemblyman Ko Hyeong-su.
You can't do this to me!
Let go…
That's not enough to kill him.
Damn it.
Choke him harder!
COURT
DEFENSE COUNSEL, ACCUSED
Is the defense counsel not here yet?
ACCUSED
PROFESSOR YANG JONG-HOON
Don't come closer.
Kill him!
Get that out of my face.
I said, get it out of my face!
Come on!
Finish him up and rot in jail
until you die…
as a murderer.
Get lost!
Professor Yang.
-Damn it!
-Hey.
What? Hey!
Had he actually killed me,
you would've been charged
for incitement to murder as well.
Incitement to murder?
I showed you that
he has no intention of killing you.
Would he kill someone
wearing a GPS ankle bracelet?
He wouldn't.
He does not want to go back to jail.
Delete that.
About the medical certificate.
The one that says there's a slim chance
your son's right arm and leg will recover.
What about it?
You and the hospital president are close.
Did you ask him to write it like that
to screw my client over?
Although he can recover
with physical rehabilitation.
That's right.
That's who you're dealing with here.
So cut the self-defense crap.
If that stupid girl says
she will gladly accept her punishment,
I'll, at least, spare her
from a harsh sentence.
Shit.
Width, 13cm. Length, 30cm.
They're for a shoe size of 275mm.
Size 275mm.
Hey.
Why would you catch me?
Because I want to ask you something.
I've been meaning to visit you.
This.
It's my uncle's.
But someone did this.
My daughter did as her mom said.
What about it?
What you want to ask is "How."
Isn't that what you want to know?
How this ended up in my hands.
Prof. Yang gave it to me.
He said it was my uncle's.
Catch you later.
They're tracking you anyway.
See you at the police station.
Witness.
COURT
You went to the hospital
upon receiving the defendant's call.
Yes, the emergency room.
Who was with the defendant at the time?
Han Joon-hwi was with her.
JUROR
Just Han Joon-hwi and no one else?
Correct.
Did they seem pretty close?
I thought they were dating.
He was very protective of her.
No further questions.
COURT
JUROR
Counsel, you may cross-examine
the witness.
No questions, Your Honor.
JUROR
-No questions?
-Correct.
PROSECUTION
How come he's not asking anything?
NOVEMBER 9, 2020
PERSONAL INFORMATION
NOVEMBER 9, 2020, 20:15
MESSAGE FROM MY HUBBY
I'll go testify.
JUROR
I won't show the photos on the screen
because they'll remind the defendant
of the painful memories.
EVIDENCE FOR ASSAULT
Witness, you're the doctor
who issued her this medical certificate.
Correct.
Were these bruises caused by being beaten?
Yes, that is correct.
How badly was she beaten?
Worse than this?
Yes.
PROSECUTION
JUROR
Someone kicked me,
and it was very painful.
I can't imagine how painful
that must've been.
LEFT SHOULDER, LEFT EYE, LEFT WRIST
-Objection.
-Can you imagine the pain?
Do you have evidence to prove
that Mr. Ko hit her?
Do you have evidence to refute it?
Up until the medical certificate
was issued, she was always with him.
The text messages and the photos here
prove that.
But none of them states or shows
that he physically assaulted her.
We can't assume he assaulted her
just based on the fact
that she was with him
before seeing the doctor.
What if she saw no one else
before going to the doctor's?
JUROR
Did she have company the first time
she visited your clinic?
Yes, she did.
Who was it?
From what I recall, it was her boyfriend.
"Boyfriend"? Are you referring
to Mr. Ko Yeong-chang, the victim?
I actually checked before coming here.
The name on the credit card
was Ko Yeong-chang.
I see.
What did Mr. Ko say to you that day?
He was very angry.
JUROR
He said his girlfriend was assaulted
by her stalker.
He asked for a medical certificate
proving bodily harm.
Knowing the assaulter could be prosecuted
even if the victim agreed to a settlement?
Yes.
How did the defendant react to that?
She didn't really say anything,
so I issued a certificate
proving bodily harm.
Did you, by any chance,
suspect that he might be the person
who assaulted her?
No, I never thought that.
Did you hear that?
Mr. Ko wasn't the assaulter
who caused her to go to the hospital.
In fact, he took her there
as her guardian.
MARCH 26, 2020
Get out.
A FEW MONTHS
BEFORE THE KO YEONG-CHANG INCIDENT
Ye-seul.
Let's get you treated
and get a medical certificate.
I'm a complete asshole if I do this again.
If this happens again,
use the medical certificate
and file charges against me.
Okay?
Let's go.
EVIDENCE FOR ASSAULT
Nonsense.
He took her there after hitting her.
Juror no. 4, please be quiet.
The jurors are not permitted to speak
during the trial.
If you have a question or anything to say,
please write it down and submit it.
JUROR INFORMATION: AN SUK-JA
HAS TWIN DAUGHTERS, KANG SOL AND KANG DAN
Looks like Juror no. 4
is on Ye-seul's side.
Weren't you aware that
the content of your post was defamatory?
I had no other option.
Had they paid child support
as they promised--
So you deliberately humiliated them
to force them into giving the money?
Is that it?
I want to ask them
why they're refusing to pay child support
for their own child.
-What brings you here?
-The kids did nothing wrong.
Our Legal Clinic is helping the defendant.
I see.
What about your son's trial?
I get that they hate me,
but why take it out on the kids?
Nonsense.
He took her there after hitting her.
I feel bad that Mom has to see this.
-No! Stay away from me!
-Open the door!
I said, open the door!
-Stop.
-Let go.
-Don't touch me.
-I'll kill him.
I told you to stop!
MENU
Why are you out here?
What?
You don't want to watch the trial?
I should watch it.
Because of Juror no. 4?
I thought she looked familiar.
I never forget a face.
Your Honor.
This witness examination will be focused
on how Mr. Ko sexually assaulted Ms. Jeon.
It will bring back the painful memories,
so please allow Ms. Jeon
to leave the courtroom for a moment.
This is an aggravated assault trial,
not sexual assault.
Which wouldn't have taken place
had it not been for
the sexual assault and the video.
COURT
Ms. Jeon should be protected
as a sexual assault victim.
This claim cannot be sustained.
We do not agree that the defendant
should be seen as a victim.
COURT
ACCUSED
Witness.
You performed a rape kit
on Ms. Jeon, correct?
Yes.
Ms. Jeon.
If you're uncomfortable,
you may step out for a moment.
WITNESS
JUROR
I'll just stay, Your Honor.
JUROR 2
Joon-hwi said Juror no. 2
will be a wild card.
But aren't you getting a bad feeling?
You've examined
a number of rape victims, right?
Yes, I'm usually the one
who handles it at our hospital.
The day Mr. Ko was injured,
the defendant was also brought
to the hospital and was examined by you.
Yes.
As an experienced medical professional,
do you believe that
she was raped by Mr. Ko?
JUROR NO. 2
First and foremost, Ms. Jeon
seemed very nervous
when I first examined her.
In the examination, I noticed a few things
that would not have occurred
had she willfully engaged
in consensual sex.
Such as defensive injuries that occurred
while struggling?
The question is leading.
What are these "few things"
you're referring to?
There were abrasions and bruises
on her arms and legs.
Mr. Ko's skin cells were found
under her fingernails,
and there were signs of genital
and vaginal trauma. Based on such--
Can't they happen
during a couple's sexual activities
that are sadistic or rough?
But normally--
Yes or no?
Yes.
Everyone has a different palate,
and the same goes for sexual taste.
That is true.
That's right.
They mutually decided to record themselves
on video while having sex.
So why claim that he raped her
and recorded the video secretly…
Oh, sorry.
Your bullshit made me choke.
COURT
Now, let's talk about whether or not
the video was secretly recorded.
In other countries,
failure to pay child support
could be considered child abuse
and may lead to criminal penalties.
It is a crime that threatens
the child's right to life.
Failure to pay child support
infringes on the child's right to life.
Therefore, it is different
from other financial obligations.
Their personal information was published,
but since they are threatening
their children's right to life,
they brought it upon themselves.
They should have the decency
to pay child support if they can afford
a lawsuit like this.
They're not deliberately withholding
payment. They don't have the money--
The website was created because
of bad parents who can pay it but don't.
PYO YEONG-IN
RESOLVED
Do you know who was here?
Why do you ask?
What?
RESOLVED
Even a lawyer at a big law firm
that everyone knows
refused to pay child support
for his two daughters
until the media got wind of the story
and sent 100 million won a few days ago.
If you don't believe me, you can go
to the other courtroom
where a jury trial is being held.
He is there now,
as the plaintiff's attorney.
Assemblyman Ko Hyeong-su
supports Bad FaMa.
But he hired Song,
the child support-evading lawyer
whose information was posted on Bad FaMa,
to represent his son.
HAEWON DAILY, REPORTER CHOI JUNG-HYEOK
I am covering this, but…
OBC REPORTER KIM HYEON-JAE
Hey, Kim.
I should've done an exclusive story
on this.
Where are you? Hurry.
What? You don't care?
COURTROOM 418
MY HUBBY
The prosecutor insists
it was recorded with consent,
so we'll call it "the video."
JUROR
The defendant received the video
from Mr. Ko
at 20:15 on November 9th.
November 9th, 20:15.
This is when she received it.
CAM01
MY HUBBY, 1 VIDEO
She was so shocked
that she fainted right away.
Did you know then that
it was a secretly recorded sex video?
I could only guess.
Ye-seul was panicking,
so I couldn't ask her.
WITNESS
If it was recorded with her consent
like the prosecutor is insisting,
would she have reacted that way
upon receiving it?
JUROR
-Because it was secretly recorded--
-We can't conclude that the reaction
was caused by the video
based on this footage alone.
Witness, you ran to the hospital
with Ms. Jeon on your back
when the ambulance could've taken her.
Yes.
And you were with her the whole time
she was at the hospital.
Yes.
I also heard you asked a friend
to check on the defendant's room
after the incident.
PROSECUTION
Yes.
That was to ensure they wouldn't think
that she might flee
or try to destroy evidence.
You were afraid she'd be detained
or arrested without a warrant.
That's why you went all out
to protect her.
Then based on that, wouldn't anyone assume
that they're very close?
I wanted to protect her from abuse.
If you think I went "all out"…
Sure, I did it to protect her.
I stopped Assemblyman Ko when he tried
to slap her in the face at the hospital.
But even if it was another friend,
I'd never let something like that happen.
JUROR
I'd never let a friend suffer injustice.
Here, what were you and Ms. Jeon
talking about?
Must I tell you everything?
Let me rephrase that
if you're uncomfortable answering it.
At the time, did you know
that she was planning to testify
in Mr. Yang's trial?
I was guessing she might.
So you didn't know for sure.
Earlier, you said you had guessed
it might be a secretly recorded video.
That means you didn't know for sure.
I guess not.
COURT
As a law student,
shouldn't you have refrained
from testifying if it was something
you weren't sure about?
It could incite the jurors
to jump to conclusions.
You're right.
If I taught criminal law
at Hankuk University,
I'd teach such basics first.
He didn't teach you this?
The way the two of you
exchanged glances just now
makes me think that you two
must be very close.
I'd like you all to remember this.
JUROR
There, what did you give her?
A pledge.
Mr. Ko signed a pledge that he'd never
sneak into her room again.
Why is it that you got it from Mr. Ko?
You said you and Ms. Jeon
are just friends.
-That's--
-What did you say when you handed it over?
"You should listen to Prof. Yang,
not Yeong-chang.
You must listen to your professor
to survive law school."
If Ms. Jeon, who was taken aback
by that remark…
CAN WE MEET NOW?
…happened to see this text message
from Mr. Yang, her professor,
she must've been terrified, right?
That is why she dropped her phone
and panicked.
JUROR
-Objection, Your Honor--
-Really?
I thought you'd say "No objection"
or "No questions" again.
Why did you ask her to meet up
at that late hour?
Why did he want to see his student
who was going to testify against him?
After this, Ms. Jeon changed her mind.
So to thank her,
you volunteered to represent her.
Isn't that why you're here?
JUROR
Excuse me.
JUROR 4
The restroom…
We were all totally focused.
Must you interrupt the flow like this?
We don't have time.
Can't we just continue?
Could you wait?
No…
COURT
We'll take a 30-minute recess.
WITNESS, JUROR
JUROR
I had a bad hunch when I heard her name,
Bae Sim-won.
She'll be a hard one to beat.
The jurors seem persuaded.
Don't we need a forensic investigation
to prove what Ye-seul saw
in the lobby was indeed the spy cam video?
Hey, you. Why are you here?
What? Why?
Come with me.
Come on. Quick.
Come here. Listen.
Go to Mirinae Middle School.
Pick up this kid
and take him to his academy.
What?
Go. He's a school violence assailant.
I must get him.
Shouldn't the police catch him?
We don't need to "catch" him.
I just want the case.
I can charge a lot
for school violence cases.
Oh, I see.
His mother said she'll hire us
if we help her with this.
Hey, get going.
Now? Ye-seul's trial isn't over yet.
Hey, this is part of your internship.
Hurry.
-But…
-Hurry, go!
Drive safely, okay?
But…
KO HYEONG-SU SUPPORTS BAD FAMA
So many people have read this
and commented on it.
Thanks to you, Choi scored big.
All the other reporters wasted their time.
He acted as though he wouldn't cover it.
I told you he would, 100 percent.
We have the recording,
so he can no longer use Prosecutor Jin.
Thank God the police think
he should be indicted.
I told you that they would.
They had to, because of the recording.
Prosecutors are the problem.
They'll defend their colleague.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
At the moment, you're one of us.
You're interning under my supervision.
I take my ramyeon very seriously.
You can drink the broth.
KO HYEONG-SU SUPPORTS BAD FAMA
Kiddos, stop trying to mess with me.
They say,
"Once a family, always a family."
So I'll let him off this once.
But you will be hurt.
If you keep messing with me,
you'll regret it big time.
It was 275.
Not 270.
The shoe size of the real culprit.
Since you're my supervisor now,
let's catch the killer together.
It'd be embarrassing for the prosecution
to bark up the wrong tree.
Have some rice with the broth
that I left for you.
Shouldn't you be suspicious of it by now?
The needle mark on his stomach
that wasn't from an insulin injection.
Being stabbed
with this needle right here
would puncture the stomach, right?
Yes, it would.
I'm under a lot of stress
because of my trial.
Please don't visit me again.
Did you see a puncture wound
in his stomach?
No, not during my examination.
It was already quite damaged
from the first autopsy.
What exactly do you mean?
Because of you, I was nearly convicted
of murdering my own uncle.
Please tell me the truth.
I think I heard someone talking about
a puncture wound in the stomach
when I went in there briefly
during the first autopsy.
That is not true. He just gave you
the answer that you wanted.
And to get that answer,
-you said you'd file a petition for him.
-A petition?
If the victim files a petition
requesting leniency for him,
he may be let off with a fine
instead of probation.
To a mere civil servant
at the National Forensic Service,
that is a matter of livelihood.
To keep his job, he had no choice,
but to give you the answer you wanted.
Why not lash out at me if he's that angry?
Why did he have to treat me
as if I was invisible?
The thought of becoming a prosecutor
is scaring me
for the first time in my life.
PROFESSOR YANG JONG-HOON
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
Have you eaten…
Did he just flat out ignore you?
He wants nothing to do with you.
It's not like we wanted that conversation
to be recorded.
What's with that scoop?
You didn't even tell me.
What?
WORLD WITHOUT CORRUPTION
How can this be part of the internship?
I get that school violence cases
pay a lot, but I'm not his driver.
Lawyers bust their butt to get clients.
This is hands-on experience.
-I have to go.
-Hey, Bok-gi.
At least, Mr. Park gives you stuff to do.
Prosecutor Jin would only talk
to Joon-hwi.
To him, I'm practically invisible.
Want to be Mr. Park's driver then?
Why did I want to become a lawyer?
I'm fundamentally regretting my decision.
AT LEFT TURN SIGNAL
AT PEDESTRIAN CROSSING
I mean, Ye-seul' trial is taking place
right now.
I should be there.
I'll try to keep you in the loop.
Everything was going great
until the press conference, but…
NICE JOB, HAEWON DAILY
People were so supportive,
but they've suddenly gone cold.
Why did you have to ruin everything
for me?
What were you thinking
when you hired a jerk who refused
to pay child support?
Oh, don't get me wrong.
I only found out today
that he's representing your son.
Here are some precedents
that could be helpful for Ye-seul.
This one's very recent.
She said to the police
she didn't report it
because she feared retaliation,
but she told the prosecutor
that love was the reason.
Such inconsistency could put her
at a disadvantage.
You found a case where the court
ruled in favor of a rape victim
despite inconsistency.
This will be very useful.
Hello.
Going down.
CONSTITUTIONAL LAW CONTEST
I heard you didn't get
the court internship.
Right.
Do you think it was because
of the plagiarism scandal?
About that…
I told Prof. Kim
that your conviction is dangerous.
You only see what you want to see.
That's not a fair statement
as I have a smoking gun.
Go public with it.
CONSTITUTIONAL LAW CONTEST
That person doesn't want to,
so you can get another chance.
Attorney Song, this crazy idiot.
I can't believe
you withheld child support of all things.
Oh, that was…
I got it all resolved recently.
You're off the case as of this moment.
Sir.
I attended the Bad FaMa trial
to divert media attention,
but the reporters ended up flocking
to my son's trial because of you!
My apologies, sir.
Get lost.
Don't even loiter around the courtroom
for my son's trial.
There's an issue with the jurors.
The jurors?
Are you all right?
SOL
MOM
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
Why isn't she replying?
It's not like I can go talk to her.
This is frustrating.
Hey.
About last time…
Now, I know why you want to be
a prosecutor.
Your penetrating question got me
and my conscience.
Tell Prof. Yang I found out
what time Ye-seul first saw the video.
-My gosh.
-Hello.
Hello.
The trial seems to be going well,
thanks to Prof. Kim's testimony.
Even if I don't get acquitted, I want
to thank you from the bottom of my heart.
You helped me the most.
I didn't even do much.
If you are found guilty,
you can file an appeal.
But the prosecutor can do the same
even if I am found not guilty,
so I really hope they pass the bill.
The one Assemblyman Ko proposed today
for abolishing the current defamation law
for publicly alleging facts.
That bill is…
I promise you that I will fight with you
until the end.
-We got this.
Right, it'd be nice
if they passed that bill.
No.
But I refuse to support Ko Hyeong-su.
What?
I'm also against punishing those
who tell the truth
and think the defamation law
should be abolished.
But I'm really against Ko Hyeong-su
getting credit for it.
I can't let that happen.
So what's your point?
My point?
So I'm going to…
Why isn't she texting me back?
JUROR
LEFT EYE, LEFT THIGH, INNER AND OUTER
LEFT SHOULDER, LEFT WRIST
ACCUSED
JUROR
COURT
ACCUSED
JUROR
COURT
There she is.
Where's Prof. Yang?
-I thought you guys were with him.
-No.
Maybe he's pulling his hair out somewhere
because Prosecutor Bae got him good.
Based on the evidence so far,
it'll be difficult for Ye-seul
to prove that she was trying to stop him
from disseminating…
What?
COURT
We know when she first watched the video.
Are you going to have Seung-jae
testify for her?
I don't want to be on the witness stand.
DIGITAL FORENSICS REPORT
MESSAGE, INCOMING
DON'T FORGET THIS LONG NIGHT WE HAD
MY HUBBY
Are you saying you just helped Ms. Jeon
with her studies because you two
were in the same study group?
You're just friends and nothing more?
Correct.
In the group, there is someone
who I really want to look out for,
but it's not Ye-seul.
JUROR
It's someone in the study group?
Then the person must be here.
Everyone in the group is here
to help Ms. Jeon.
-Yes.
-Who is it?
Tell us who it is.
You can tell us unless this is a trick
to hide your relationship with Ms. Jeon.
Where is it?
How dare you touch my stuff?
I have no power, you see.
All I did was carry out the orders.
-Hey.
-Get lost!
Damn it!
Shit.
JIN HYEONG-U
YANG JONG-HOON
Damn.
If your Bad FaMa client
is found not guilty,
you'll have me to thank for.
So I have to say I was pretty upset
when you brought up Attorney Song.
But I hope…
you're not going to break your promise
just because of that.
The promise you made
upon receiving the Lee Man-ho bill.
Of course, I won't.
I even got choked by him
while provoking him
with the recording that you had sent.
You must keep the promise
even if someone threatens you
with a knife.
Yes, of course.
As long as
Yang Jong-hoon isn't the one
holding the knife.
Don't drag me into his problem.
I have to go watch your son's trial.
Well, then.
-Shall we head out together?
-Go ahead.
Hey.
What?
JAMES
Hi! How's it going?
I'm doing great. How are you?
-I'm fine.
-Are you busy right now?
Ms. Jeon, you're studying law
to become a law professional.
Right?
WITNESS
Yes.
Then I'm sure
you were fully aware that filming someone
without their consent,
especially during sex,
is considered a serious criminal offense.
Yes.
If Mr. Ko physically abused you
and also filmed you
without your consent,
why didn't you report it to the police?
As someone who is studying to work in law,
why didn't she report such a crime?
Especially when she has a history
of filing a police report
against a college friend
who stalked her
before she started law school.
JUROR
What's going on?
-Who's that?
-Ko Yeong-chang!
-What?
-Mr. Ko.
-Ko Yeong-chang, right?
-Mr. Ko!
-Mr. Ko.
-Why is he here?
-Is it really him?
Mr. Ko, how are you feeling?
-Mr. Ko!
-Please step back.
Just a comment!
Please step back.
-What's going on?
-My apologies.
The victim wanted to be here,
so I brought him.
Prosecutor, please continue.
WITNESS
You can have some water before you answer.
According to your statement,
you didn't report him to the police
because you loved him.
Was that the reason?
You put up with the sexual assault
because you loved him?
That doesn't make much sense.
But if this statement is true,
you loved him enough to put up with it.
Then it's understandable
that you totally lost it and attacked him
the moment you heard him say
he wanted to end things.
-That is total baloney.
Hoping he'd let you go unpunished
for the injuries you had inflicted
upon him,
are you now saying you were raped
though you actually had sex with him?
Her claim that she kept quiet out of love
is not true.
She had no reason to report him
in the first place
because Mr. Ko never assaulted her
in any way.
Defendant.
Calm down and return to your seat.
COURT
If you leave the courtroom now,
it may be used against you.
Please make that jerk leave the courtroom!
Juror no. 4, if you speak
without permission one more time,
-you'll be asked to leave.
-Tell her to leave now.
I request we take a recess.
Let's just continue.
JUROR
Your Honor.
COURT
I'd like to give Ye-seul what she wants.
Mr. Ko, I will give you a chance
to speak--
It's okay.
I have nothing to say.
Ye-seul and I were going to get married.
But just because she cheated on me
with a smarter guy at the law school
and let her professor threaten her
and toy with her,
I wanted to end things.
So it is my own fault.
I understand why she got so angry
and lashed out at me.
Your Honor.
Please just give her what she wants.
If she can be happy,
I'll gladly
be called a rapist.
Jeez, that douchebag is really something.
JUROR
Half of my body is paralyzed now anyway,
so I don't care if people call me
a shameless criminal.
I just feel horrible, thinking about
what my father might have to go through
because of his stupid son
who was crazy about his girlfriend…
Hurry. Take him back to the hospital.
-What?
-Wait, hold on!
-Mr. Ko!
-Out of the way, please.
-Hurry.
-Just a comment, please!
-Mr. Ko!
-Just a comment!
-Wait!
-All right.
-Tell us about your condition!
Order.
-Wait!
-Mr. Ko!
-Just a comment, please!
-Wait, Mr. Ko!
-One moment!
-Mr. Ko, are you okay?
HOW DID THE REPORTER FIND OUT ABOUT THIS?
NICE JOB, HAEWON DAILY
-Wait!
-Just a moment!
-One moment!
-Are you okay?
Tell us about your condition.
-Wait! Stop!
-Who's that?
Ko Hyeong-su's son.
-Ko Hyeong-su?
-How are you feeling?
-What?
-How do you feel?
-Just a comment, please!
-Are you okay?
-Wait!
-Mr. Ko!
WITNESS
Prof. Kim.
I don't want to do this anymore.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
I have to say, provoking Assemblyman Ko
helped me score big.
If you want something bigger…
What's this?
Give a statement to the prosecutor.
Now?
-If you hand over that photo.
-After you give
-your statement.
-Hey.
He's pissed you're scoring all the scoops.
Where are you going?
All scoops are exclusive.
So first, let's--
Then Reporter Kim can score them all.
Mr. Kim.
It's nothing. Hey, let's talk.
JUROR
Counsel, you may continue
to examine the defendant.
I am afraid
I can no longer represent Ms. Jeon.
DEFENSE COUNSEL
I am afraid
I can no longer represent Ms. Jeon.
JUROR
What's going on?
I beg your pardon?
PROSECUTION
I resign.
Counsel.
What is this about?
Is this some kind of joke?
You requested to be Ms. Jeon's
special defense counsel.
I apologize, Your Honor.
I wish to stop defending her
so that she can exercise
her right to defend herself.
Prof. Yang.
COURT
Am I your teacher?
What are you doing?
We'll begin.
Case number 2020-GH311.
Ms. Jeon and Mr. Ko
were in a relationship.
Jeon was indicted for inflicting
serious injuries on Ko
during their heated argument
about a video of their sex.
However, Jeon insists that
she acted in self-defense
while trying to stop Ko
from disseminating the video.
What is the main issue here?
PROSECUTION
What is the main issue?
COURT
Depending on the results of our trials,
this could be our last class.
So I expect your full participation.
WITNESS
The main issue…
JUROR
It's whether or not the video
was recorded secretly.
-That's it?
-Pardon me?
Is that enough for her to claim
she acted in self-defense?
Also whether he tried
to disseminate the video…
Why do the prosecutors disagree?
PROSECUTION
-After watching the video, I--
-Ms. Jeon.
She didn't get angry at him…
She neither got angry at Ko
nor told him to delete the video.
JUROR
When he texted her and asked
if she had watched it,
she wrote back "yeah" instead of "yes".
-Did you watch it?
-Yeah.
What's wrong with writing "yeah"
instead of "yes"?
That's…
"Yeah" connotes closeness.
It's not a reaction expected from someone
who's shocked after watching such a video.
TEXT CONVERSATION
At the Training Institute,
one of my peers asked me out.
I rejected her,
but she acted as if
we were even closer than before.
I was quite puzzled by her reaction.
I flat out rejected her,
so she must've been shocked.
Why didn't she get angry--
Not everyone gets angry when they're
shocked or when their pride is hurt.
Unless she was going to cut ties with him,
getting angry at him--
I see.
PROSECUTION
Another reason they think the video
wasn't recorded secretly?
I…
Because Jeon's statements
weren't consistent.
They weren't consistent?
WITNESS
Initially, she said it was because
she feared retaliation.
But then, she said it was because
she loved Ko.
The lack of consistency means
she wasn't raped and knew about the video?
I see.
Do you agree?
Did you not do your assignment again?
I told you to read up on the precedents.
ONE HOUR AGO
SEXUAL ASSAULT CASES
The Supreme Court
recently quashed the acquittal
of a sexual assault assailant,
granted due to the victim's
inconsistent statements.
Why was it quashed?
Because a little bit of inconsistency
does not mean
her arguments and their credibility
can be nullified.
And the victim's extraordinary
circumstances weren't considered--
Then what are Jeon's extraordinary
circumstances in this case?
-What are her extraordinary circumstances?
-The fact that…
she was raped by the man
she was engaged to and loved.
So intimate partner rape is different
from other types of sexual assault.
How's it different?
Open your eyes!
Tell me how it's different.
If it was a complete stranger,
I'd think of it as a terrible nightmare
and shake it off.
But it was my boyfriend, who was part
of the rosy future I had dreamed of.
JUROR
IT WASN'T YOUR FAULT
After watching the video,
Jeon was shocked and started to panic.
But she felt that she had to text him
"yeah" as usual,
because had she not replied,
he would've called her hundreds of times.
And he would've…
JUROR
…come to her school had she not picked up.
TEXT CONVERSATION
She was confused whether it was love,
or he was just abusing her.
JUROR
So she probably didn't even know
how to react to it.
Ye-seul, how dare you?
You've become awfully arrogant
since getting into Hankuk Law.
Let go. Don't do this.
How did you get this?
This angle is way better than
that of Ko Yeong-chang's dashcam.
He can't refute this.
He wanted to disseminate it,
not delete it.
How long have you had this?
Don't ask me
why I didn't share this sooner.
9:20 P.M., DECEMBER 5, 2020,
THE DAY OF THE KO YEONG-CHANG INCIDENT
Professor, you were wrong.
I wanted to kill him.
When I found out about the video
and was threatened
that he'd disseminate it…
I wanted to hit that jerk with this
and pummel him to death.
JUROR
I was wrong indeed.
I didn't report it to the police because…
I couldn't even bear the thought
of telling someone about it.
I was
raped by the man I loved.
But you forced yourself to tell others.
TEXT CONVERSATION
Victims of intimate partner violence
rarely file police reports.
TEXT CONVERSATION
You know why that is?
PROSECUTION
Because they'll be asked these questions.
"You'll file charges
against your boyfriend?
Are you sure you were sexually assaulted?"
-Objection--
-That is not allowed in my class.
COURT
Now, if you were the judge…
If I were the judge…
COURT
What would you do if you were me?
I pondered this question over and over.
"What did I do wrong
that I'm being tried in court?"
PROSECUTION
While trying to protect herself
from the horrendous situation
of the sex video
being widely disseminated,
she unintentionally caused injury to Ko
by pushing him.
Based on the Criminal Code Article 21,
this was an act performed
to prevent unjust infringement.
ARTICLE 21 OF THE CRIMINAL CODE
- SELF-DEFENSE
So I'd conclude she acted in self-defense.
COURT
IN SESSION
Mr. Kang.
Prof. Yang said he has a smoking gun
of some sort.
Is it you?
Dad, is it you?
Then who…
IN SESSION
TODAY'S COURT SCHEDULE
It's me.
Your dissertation.
COURTROOM 418
I helped my uncle
when he was working on it.
It can only be ruled self-defense
if it was an act
performed in order to prevent impending
and unjust infringement.
COURT
JUROR
If he punches me
after getting kicked in the shin,
it's considered mutual combat
and won't be ruled self-defense.
If he tries to defend himself
as I'm attacking him like this,
it'll be ruled self-defense.
Let's look at the screen.
Here. The phone fell on the ground.
Ye-seul kicked him after that,
wearing her high heels.
Oh, you're right.
Ko dropped his phone, which means,
he couldn't disseminate it at the time,
so she should've stopped attacking him.
No.
She was panicking.
What if she didn't see him drop his phone?
-I mean, it was dark.
-Did you know he dropped his phone?
We'll consider
all extenuating circumstances.
You knew about his phone,
but kicked him wearing the heels
because you were so angry, right?
You kicked him knowing that his phone
had fallen on the ground, didn't you?
You said this earlier.
"I wanted to hit that jerk with this
and pummel him to death."
She should say no even if she knew.
That's what I'd do.
Ko is the bad guy here.
I'd save myself.
You kicked him even though you knew
that his phone had fallen
on the ground, right?
Yes.
For this to be ruled self-defense,
the defendant should've stopped
attacking him
the moment Mr. Ko's phone
slipped out of his hand.
But as she admitted just now--
Are you blind?
Look at that.
She did it because she was afraid
that jerk would pick up his phone.
COURT
Juror no. 4.
JUROR 4
WITNESS
I don't think I can say no
if I knew about it.
But I probably would've done
exactly what Ye-seul did.
Out of fear that he'd pick up his phone.
I think that's what happened.
In other words,
the unjust infringement continued.
He didn't actually pick it up.
If he tried to pick it up, we cannot say
the unjust infringement continued.
Say that again.
They proved his attempt to disseminate it.
Depending on whether or not
it's ruled self-defense--
Damn, that idiot Jin Hyeong-u!
What has he been doing?
-I even went there and put on a show--
-Shut up!
-Tell Prosecutor Jin
-Yes, sir.
to do whatever it takes
to get Juror no. 4 kicked out
before the jurors' discussion begins.
Thankfully, Juror no. 4
is an alternate juror.
I see.
I'll take a quick shower
and return before the discussion is over.
Okay.
I sent the photo to Choi after confirming
that he gave his statement.
He wrote an article right away.
Okay.
KO HYEONG-SU ATTACKED
ATTACKED BY LEE MAN-HO
Assemblyman Ko wants to get Lee Man-ho
locked up for attempted murder.
I'd appreciate that.
So I won't have to check this.
Give it to my roomie
you want to look out for.
What? Are you disappointed
that it's not you?
Well, that makes me want
to look out for you, too.
Byeol is home alone.
Right, alternate jurors also have to stay
until the end.
MILL
Hold on.
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT COURT
You somehow managed to win
Reporter Choi over.
You think you can use this
to bring me to trial?
You will be indicted.
You want to clear your father's name
by making me a defendant?
I told you to stop messing with me.
You just can't take hints.
Why do you think I sat in on this trial?
What you see isn't everything.
But then again, how would you know
the substantial truth
that even your father didn't know
until he died?
You need to learn about it
if you want to work in law.
Am I wrong?
This is Yang Jong-hoon.
Did you read the article about Lee Man-ho?
Where is he now?
He hasn't stepped out of his house
since the article came out.
EUNPYEONG-GU
LEE MAN-HO
Please call me
if you notice anything unusual.
KO HYEONG-SU ATTACKED
I gave you my blood to save your life.
You can't do this to me.
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi
The real culprit is caught.
As if it was not enough to dig up
Ko's back. You didn't bribe them, did you?
It won't be acknowledged as self-defense.
It means Lee Man-ho is the real culprit.
Tell that jerk Choi
to walk back his remarks
and make it
look like you caught the culprit.
I don't think I can work for you anymore.
Did you really kill Seo Byung-ju?
But Lee Man-ho…
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs