Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
I'm still half asleep.
It's 8 degrees hotter than it was at this time yesterday.
Due to the abnormally high temperatures, we anticipate a very hot day.
The cause of the abnormally high temperatures
is my burning love for you.
I need to sleep. This is all because I'm tired.
What's all the fuss, so early in the morning? Did you have a dream?
What the hell are you doing in my room?
Stop touching my things!
Goodness. You lent my clothes to someone else, and now what? Nice double standard there!
Your pimples have sprouted in such nice locations!
Love Revolution Episode 3: Dreams vs Reality
#pimples #this_is_a_Dream
princess_0 @prince_rim: Cute >u<
- Have you decided what to wear for the retreat?
- Retreat?
- Don't we all just wear our gym uniforms?
- No, I mean on the way there.
Also, even with our gym uniforms, we have to make it seem like we effortlessly look good.
Is it possible to do that with our school's gym uniforms?
I am capable of accomplishing that very difficult task.
Ja Rim!
- Hello! Hi!
- Hi.
- I dreamt of you yesterday.
- I didn't ask.
Should I tell you what kind of dream it was? Aren't you super curious?
I really don't care at all.
Really? Then I'll just cherish it all by myself.
Anyway, it made me so happy. Thanks for coming out in my dream.
- Then give me my appearance fee.
- An appearance fee?
Okay, I have an appearance fee for you. Appearance fee...
Tada! This is a very precious thing
that my mother prepared especially for me. It'll probably be good for acne, too.
I happened to have something like this on a day your acne was acting up.
As expected, we are meant to b...
Hey!
Ah Ram likes it. Bring some again next time, too.
I brought that for you.
Wang Ja, something happened on the day it rained, huh?
What the hell are you saying?
I'm just saying because you and Gong Joo Yong seem to be a little different these days.
I think you're kind to him.
Are you sure we were walking together? When was I nice to him?
Even just a few days ago, you ignored him. But now you respond to everything he says.
I'm not responding to it, but retorting.
Good. On a scale of 0, no interest, to 10, would date, where are you?
- Zero.
- Awesome!
What the hell? I said zero.
I mean, you always start at -10, so 0 is quite far.
If it continues like this, you'll be dating in no time.
Stop talking about Gong Joo Young. Why do you keep trying to pair us together?
It's just because it's good to see you get along with him.
There's no reason not to get along with him, since he's not a bad kid.
Then there is at least a small chance you could end up dating him.
Be quiet. A rat is listening.
Hey, Lee Kyeong Woo. You're awake, aren't you?
♫ Careless, careless, shoot anonymous, anonymous  ♫
♫ heartless, mindless, no one who cares about me ♫
♫ I've lost it ♫
What the hell is going on here?
These punks are going to participate in the retreat talent show.
You slaves for attention.
Isn't that a given? It's a chance for me to appeal to Ja Rim.
You doing a courtship dance? Plus, the stage will look hella empty if it's just the two of you dancing.
Hella lame, too.
We have three people though.
One, two, three!
Are you crazy? Why would I participate in your class's talent show?
The kids in my class would curse me.
Nah, if you're the Kyeong Woo I know, you'll definitely help me.
We're real friends, aren't we?
You only ask for loyalty when it's in your favor.
Here. This is loyalty.
Holy...
I really didn't want to dance, but...
Anything for a friend.
Jesus, he's a slave to capitalism.
I can't just give this to you. I'm going to take video proof.
Vow to participate in the retreat talent show.
Hey, do we have to do this? Between us?
I, Lee Kyeong Woo, vow to participate in the retreat talent show with Gong Joo Young.
Happy?
Hmm... Don't you have more?
- I guess I'll just use these.
- Okay, okay!
I'll raise you to diamond level.
Are you crazy? How could he become diamond?
It's already unbelievable that you're platinum.
Okay! Here.
You're a real friend, knowing when to spend.
We're going to practice at my house later, so swing by, okay?
Why would you practice at home? Let's just practice right here, you jerk.
Yang Min: How is this?
It's a bit agressive.
Ah Rong: What about this instead?
LOL. You're crazy.
Is this a competition to see how aggressive we can look?
Wang Ja, what are you gonna wear?
I dunno. I'll just decide whatever when the day comes.
Whatever what? We can't match.
Hurry up and give a pic.
I almost forgot about this.
No way. Are you giving this to me?
It was originally yours, you know.
I'm so touched. I understand your feelings.
Then, I have something to give you as well.
Please marry me.
Why do you overreact every time I'm just a little bit nice to you?
Hey, Wang Byeol Rim.
What?
What is it?
Hey, what are you doing? We need to practice.
Ten-minute break.
We've been on a break after practicing for 10 lousy minutes.
I'm in a feeble state right now.
A trusted friend stabbed me in the back.
Stop and help me out. This is really important to me.
I'm going to sing a confession song after I dance too.
Are you out of your mind?
If you do that now, it'll have the opposite effect. Events like that only work when the time is ripe, you moron.
I also think that's a bit ... rushed.
Exactly. But this punk has messed up his timing from the beginning anyway.
Goodness, hey!
You don't even know what happened between me and Ja Rim on that rainy day.
Ja Rim's heart has already moved towards me. Then I have to go meet her on the other end.
Hey, Wang Ja Rim says she has zero feelings for you.
Emotional Quotient: 0
- What do you mean?
- I wasn't going to tell you, thinking you'd be disappointed,
but I heard the girls talking about it in the classroom earlier. On a scale of 0-10 of her feelings for you,
she says she's at zero.
Emotional Quotient: 0
Hey, th-that's just her hiding her feelings in front of her friends!
Idiot...
Wang Ja Rim: Come out.
Hey, Ja Rim texted me to come out.
She says to come out. Is this a zero? Is it?
I'm off, ya losers.
Oppa, are you Gong Joo Yeong?
Huh? Yes, but who...
I'm Wang Ja Rim's—
I'm Unni Ja Rim's younger sister. She says to give this to you.
This...
Don't you have something to give me?
Hey, what did she say? Did she ask you out?
You met Wang Ja Rim, so why the long face?
That's an expression you would make when you expected to see Wang Ja Rim,
but saw her younger sister instead. That kind of vibe.
I saw it with my mind's eye.
You guys really... Let's maintain some privacy.
Tell your sister thanks, I used it well.
These are my clothes, though.
I'm back!
Money.
But is he really your friend? Be honest.
What the hell do you mean?
You even let a guy borrow some clothes. So out of character!
It's not like that.
At the very least, he definitely likes you.
- Is that what he said?
- Nope!
Look at this! I mean, why did he package borrowed clothes that he's returning?
That's hella funny!
Wow... He even sprayed perfume. This isn't any ordinary devotion.
Even my heart is all fluttery!
Then you can date him.
Poor him. Why did he have to like Wang Ja Rim?
- This one?
- Please load it up for me.
I'll put it in for you.
Ja Rim!
Peanuts
Eat some in the bus when you get bored. Nuts are good for acne.
Wow, how thoughtful.
It's for Ja Rim.
Rude. Let's go, Min Ji.
Pooling Sweat Together Makes Us One
Yisam Information High School Student Retreat
Everyone put your hands above your heads!
Close your eyes!
I ask all students hiding forbidden objects to reveal them now, voluntarily.
If you hand them over now you won't be liable.
However, if they are found after investigating your belongings, there will, of course, be penalty points
but also an excruciating physical training.
Alright. At ease!
Teaching assistants, guide them.
Class 3. Open your bags and wait.
- They're snacks.
- Of course, they're snacks. Anybody could see that.
Close your eyes.
Pringle Potato Chips
It's smoke snacks?
Why are there so many? Are you operating a business?
Do you think it's the first or second time I'm dealing with guys like you?
I know all of your methods, so just take them out in advance.
I didn't bring it.
- What?
- Cleansing foam.
Can't you just use mine?  I use hypo-allergenic too.
My skin is sensitive when I have pimples, so I can only use my products.
- I'm totally screwed.
- Hey, let's go.
Why are you guys coming only now?
What's with our homeroom teacher all of a sudden? Everyone else is resting but we're the last ones out!
Hong Jin Hui (17/High School student)
The one with long arms and legs
It'll already be dinner time in a little bit.
All students are to stand out in the hallways against the walls. We will take attendance.
Take attendance again? They did it already.
Hey, apparently someone disappeared.
I think it's Gong Joo Yeong.
Lee Kyeong Woo was asking where he was.
Why? Do you know him?
It is getting late, so we will proceed to dinner.
We will move according to classes.
Left, face!
Forward march!
Yes, sir!
Kim Baeng. Did he not say anything to you? You're in the same class.
I'm not sure. He was there when we were emptying our bags, but all of a sudden he was nowhere to be seen.
What is he? He normally doesn't do this.
- Surely he didn't go to buy alcohol—
- Come on!
So you ordered him to... and then you're pretending not to know...
- Hey, Wang Ja. Did he not say anything to you?
- He didn't.
I don't know about you guys but Gong Joo Yeong really didn't seem like that type of kid.
What do you mean, "I don't know about you guys"? I live a very proper life, you know?
- A properly smooth-talking life, you mean?
- I don't smoke!
Good for you. Why'd it come out of your bag, then?
I only brought that to sell it.
- Why isn't he answering his phone?
- Maybe there's no signal?
We're in the mountain in the middle of nowhere, he could have no phone signal.
Hey, there.
Wow, that bastard really...
Where did you go, princess? ( T/N "Gong Joo" is a homonym for "princess.")
He's Cinderella, Cinderella.
Why doesn't he come back as the clock strikes midnight, while he's at it?
- Where did you go?
- I ...
- I went to buy something I had forgotten to bring.
- What is it?
There are no stores nearby here, exactly how far did you go?
To the city. I didn't know it would be that far. I thought I could come right back.
Whether you go far or near, unauthorised outings are prohibited!
This will go on your record, you know?!
I'm sorry.
Since we're not at school right now,
let's follow the rules of this retreat center.
Instructor, I'll leave him to you.
Oh, right.
Do 50 squat jumps first.
- STAT!
- Yes.
Hey, hey.
Bonajour Milk Cleanser
Where did you get this? Is it yours?
No, somebody said to give this to you and then left.
Hey, that bowl cut dude...
He's Gong Joo Yeong, isn't he?
Hey.
You went out unauthorized to buy this, didn't you?
Yeah.
Who told you to break the rules over something like this?
I know. I wasn't thinking of doing that either...
but it seemed like you needed it.
Don't do anything like this again, it doesn't make me happy at all.
Okay.
Hey, Gong Joo Yeong.
Drink it.
Thank you.
- What about food?
- Food?
Ah, food. I couldn't eat...
The penalty exercise was so extreme I felt nauseous.
Did this get stuck on its own, then?
Anyway, thanks.
♫ Even if I keep telling myself it’s not real ♫
♫ Every morning when I wake up, I can only think of you ♫
♫ I used to sing only sad songs ♫
♫  But now there’s something I realized ♫
Love Revolution
- Ten!
- Aw...
It's not me! We're all being deceived!
- What's he going on about?
- He's gone crazy.
You should go now.
Is this a melodrama or a thriller?
- Do you like me?
- What the hell?
Hey, your boyfriend must be planning something!
You're not going to take pics of your boyfriend?
He's not!
- What's going on?
- What's happening?