This idiot screamed even when there wasn't anything. I couldn't watch the movie properly because of him.
No, but I was scared because of the sound!
If we talk about that, he's even more of a chicken. He was wearing his headphones and playing games.
I don't like fantasy. Why do you watch stuff about ghosts that don't even exist?
How would you know they don't?
That's right. There are pictures of spirits and even real stories.
If there really were, it would be all over the news. Do you believe those?
They do exist. Actually, my mom said I would see a ghost today.
What does your mother do?
She's a psychic.
No wonder, I was feeling sweaty today.
You're always sweaty. This is all psychological stuff—
What's happening? A blackout?
What the hell is happening?
Gosh.
Lee Kaeng, what are you doing?
Mandu, mandu, mandu, mandu, five!
(T/N: game of guessing the number of fingers open.)
Gosh, look at him flipping out.
Dammit, won't you get up?
- Did you guys hear?
- Hear what?
All first-years are having after-class study today.
What? Why all of a sudden?
Someone cheated on the math performance test and Dokgo Moon threw a fit.
So all first years are getting a re-test.
- The heck.
- Whoa, he's gone nuts.
- Why are we also retaking it?
- In case there's someone else who cheated. I'm so mad.
He said he'll supervise each test, so every class will take it one after the other.
- Will our class take it first, then?
- They said they're starting with the top floor.
Then we're the last... What are we going to do until then, seriously?
Love Revolution: Boo! A ghost in school!
Episode 27. #Where'sTheGhost #What'sTrueStory #BattleOfFear
bang_H @princess_0: I just love scary stuff!
What was that?
Quiet, quiet! You're all grown-up. Why are you making a fuss over this?
- Hey.
- What?
- Did your mom really say you would see a ghost for real today?
- Yeah. She said to be careful because I was going to see one.
Big boys like you still believe in ghosts?
In movies, those people are the first ones to die.
How long do I have to fool around with these punks?
He just had to hold a retake test.
Dokgo Moon. He really lives up to his name.
He is so dogged, really.
Why do I also have to work overtime—
People usually turn around in these situations. But I won't.
- What's that!
- What is it?!
Gosh. What are you doing?
That's what I want to ask.
Why are you here?
Well, I just... I came because it's class 3's turn to take the test.
- Right, go ahead.
- Right.
All the questions are different from the other class's tests.
So what you were told by the kids who took it first is no use.
So?
I flunked. I didn't even try the last one.
- I didn't even have the courage to do it.
- I flunked too.
- You scared me!
- Ja Dim, Ja Dim! Did you do well?
It's super dangerous outside. Let's go now. Dangerous, dangerous.
We've never been in school this late before. I somehow feel like doing a courage test.
- Want to do one?
- You're in? I'm in.
- How do you do it?
- Like they do on TV—having to bring back a hidden object.
What do you get from doing that?
What about we all bet one thousand won (≈ $1) and one person gets it all?
- It's freaking not worth it.
- Why? Are you scared? If you aren't, it's easy money.
- What a chicken.
- Okay, let's do it.
What do we have to get back, and from where?
Let's do the music room. That room is the scariest for me, because of the piano ghost's story.
Why the heck are you mentioning a piano ghost? You have a death wish?
Good idea. Then we'll decide on the order by rock paper scissors.
Let's go by teams of two.
Teams of two?
Ja Rim won't expect me to protect her anyway.
Ja Rim, I'm so scared!
In that case, this is a golden chance to say I'm too scared and cling onto Ja Rim.
Okay. This is one team.
Nonsense. Let's play the hand-flipping game, to be fair.
We're obviously one team since we're a couple.
- Palm up, palm down!
- Up!
- Down.
Palm up, palm down.
First Team
Second Team
Third Team
Fourth Team
Does this make any sense? Exchange with Ja Rim, please.
Let's go like this. Min Ji also has a boyfriend, if you look at things that way.
That's right. This is the most peaceful way. I'll go first and hide it.
You will just have to bring this back. Okay?
Hey. Come.
Wait, wait for me!
Hurry up and come.
Hey. I thought you had made up your mind?
I left the pencil case, so next team, go!
Since it turned out like this, let's empty their wallets.
What a joke. Just don't faint like last time.
Hey, you better protect Ja Rim well, Lee Kyeong Guard!
Hey, wait, wait!
Can you get off me a bit?
Well, uhm, your boyfriend told me to protect you.
Don't people usually protect from the front? I've never seen anyone do it from behind.
Well, you're seeing it now. Me protecting from behind.
Gosh, seriously.
Hey, wait! Wait for me!
Darn, it's super dark in here. Can you see anything?
- I found Jin Hui's pencil case.
- Okay, let's hurry up and leave.
Sorry.
Hey. Want to hide and scare the others?
What? You like this stuff?
- I just thought of something super funny.
- What?
The piano ghost Kim Byeong Hoon told us about...
- They should be back by now.
- Don't you think something happened to them?
What's this? A blackout?
Gosh, the lights don't even work. They must be scared and looking for me—
I don't know about Lee Kyeong Woo, but there's no way Ja Rim would.
This won't do. I'm too worried. I'm going first!
Min Ji, go with him!
Dammit. Gong Joo Yeong, we should go together!
Next team is starting!
Want to go together?
Gosh, that startled me. What's wrong?
Why is it so dark?
The music room. It was in the music room, right?
When will we arrive at the music room?
Should I have gone home instead? It's much darker than I thought.
The music room...
Be quiet! Your voice is even scarier!
- What's that?
- Dammit!
- There was a piano sound!
What sound? I didn't hear anything!
Am I the only one who heard it? Gosh. Wait a minute.
The music room is the scariest for me.
- Don't tell me...
- Because of the piano ghost's story.
What? Are you scared?
No, I'm not. Stay away—
Wait, why are you pushing me?
Ja Rim? I'm here.
You're the one who played the piano, right?
I don't think they're here.
I told you!
That was damn funny.
My legs are falling asleep. Let's go.
- Thank you.
- Ah, sure.
Are you okay?
Just hold onto me.
I'm fine. It's not like I got hurt.
What are you doing there?
I went to the music room, you see? There was no one, for sure!
But the piano went "ding"—
Ja Rim! What's wrong? Are you hurt? Did you get attacked by a ghost?
I saw a ghost. I really—
Hey! My legs just went numb.
Why did they go numb?
What?
But what about Min Ji?
What the heck, Gong Joo Yeong?
I ran away on my own, so I don't know.
You darned chicken! It's dangerous to leave her alone!
Ah Ram, let's look together!
Where were you two? You were outside, I'm sure.
We should have bet ten thousand won (≈ $10). Those punks—
I mean, those guys. They don't get into it because it's just for one thousand won.
Just hold onto me.
Am I really nothing to him?
♫ It is difficult for me ♫
It's annoying. What's so great about him?
♫ Everything  ♫
♫ feels unfamiliar ♫
♫ But nevertheless ♫
Drink some.
♫ When I think of you, there is only one answer ♫
If you act cute when singing, you're dead.
And it totally makes me cringe when you lower your voice when you sing.
♫ I guess I love you ♫
What was that? When did you become so close?
What's it to you?
Do you like him?
But what were you going to ask earlier?
Whether you gave your number to Sang Hoon or not.
Then I'm letting Sang Hoon have my lunch coupon.
Sang Hoon. You can get treated to lunch by Yang Min Ji.
So annoying.
What's even more annoying
is that I still wished
you were the one to come find me.
I'm annoyed at myself the most.
You're quite amazing for holding a retake exam on such a day, of all days.
As a teacher, I have to teach the students what responsibilities they bear when they do wrong.
Yes, you are impressive. Thanks to you, I am lucky enough to admire the night scenery.
What? Which kid hasn't left yet?
What will you do if it's a school staff member?
Just until inside the room, please. It's too dark!
Just go in.
What a coward.
I'm serious! I heard the piano even though there was no one. Why doesn't anyone believe me?
I believe you since I'm the one who played it.
What?
But...
For real? But why tell me now?
I kept talking about it since earlier, so why...
- Sorry about earlier.
- What?
I bought it for you some time ago. I didn't know I would give it to you while apologizing.
It's just that I thought you might have used up the one I gave you before.
Ja Dim... I'm so touched.
They say there's always light at the end of the tunnel. That was true.
Thanks to you, I've completely recovered.
Again, you're exaggerating.
My lovely Ja Rim, would you like to shoot the kisses?
Shoot what, you idiot. Want to die?
Okay.
Hi everyone. The product I am presenting to you today
is Real Barrier Extreme.
It's great for— Why did you turn off the light?!
Come on!
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
princess_0: My Ja Rim's surprise gift ♥︎
I'm not even done with the one you gave me before because I was using it so sparingly. Love you ♥︎
#LoverBoy #JaDimJaDim #KyeongMin #AndHisDirtySkin #AndNoGirlfriend #CouldNever
#LoverBoy #JaDimJaDim #KyeongMin #AndHisDirtySkin #AndNoGirlfriend #CouldNever #RealBarrier
princess_0: My Ja Rim's surprise gift ♥︎...
an.king_min @princess_0: Should I kill you?
bogyeong232 liked your picture
From Bo Gyeong: Joo Yeong, it's been a while haha. How are you doing? ^^
What's your number?
All my contacts disappeared TT
Why is she suddenly...
Something scarier than the piano ghost was coming toward me.
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
Love Revolution
What? Kwak Bo Gyeong?
She hasn't contacted me all this time. What's going on?
Bo Gyeong was really pretty.
- I know.
- Gong Joo Yeong! We agreed to talk today.
No but why here, now?
Sorry. I didn't see your girlfriend was next to you.
Isn't she crazy? Why come see him when she knows he has a girlfriend?
So that means you contacted her without telling me a word of it.
Hey, stick to the facts.
I really feel like crap, but I don't why.
Jealousy? Gosh, stop your bullsh*t.
This is a historical day.
♫ I can do all this and more ♫
♫ After breaking up with me ♫