The cakes here are delicious!
- What's that?
- It's nice, but don't eat it.
- Don't eat.
- Let me take this call.
What is it?
Are you still at the cafe? Should I come over?
Why? I thought you said you're going to the internet cafe with your friends.
I already went. We played a few games but I missed you.
The game I want to play the most is a dating simulation game with Ja Rim.
Do you want this game to get a "bad ending"?
We said we would meet our own friends today.
You can keep having fun. I just came because I missed you.
How impressive. You guys have been dating for a few months now, and your heart still hasn't changed since the start.
No, it has.
I like her even more than before!
Like this...
A sweet cake and...
Cake...
- Our sweet relationship!
- Ja Rim is making a sour face, though.
Just go. I can't hang out with couples. I don't want to see them at all.
There's another couple here too.
Yes, but at least she's not like someone, who comes saying "I miss you" and tags along.
Aren't you going to meet Jeong Sang Hoon?
Yeah, have you guys even met after you started dating? I never saw that.
We both had exams. We should meet soon.
Oh, right. Why do I feel like I didn't have exams? Did I want to deny it that badly?
- Why? Did you flunk?
- I don't know. I didn't even bother looking at my average.
Our Ja Rim's grades improved a lot.
- It seems like you guys studied quite a bit together.
- His grades got worse than before.
I studied with Ja Rim, but why did my grades go down?
It's exactly because you two studied together. Would you even look at your books with her around?
- Bingo.
- You're saying that so shamelessly.
Mom
Mom.
Love Revolution. Room-away Party
Episode 26: #RoomTakenAway #Party #TruthGame
bang_H @princess_0: The lie detector is the truth
What's with your expression? Is something wrong?
Sweetie, we might not be able to meet like this anymore.
If we don't meet like this, then are we going to meet like that?
That's not it.
I...
have to move out of my place.
What?
Cham, cham, cham!
What are you doing after school today? Do you want to meet if you're free?
Exams are over now, so I guess we should meet, right?
We are dating, after all.
Yes, I think I did well. Should we meet this weekend?
Sorry,  I already made plans this weekend.
Oh, I see. With your friends?
Yes. We made plans to hang out after our exams.
Oh, then what about tonight? Do you want to eat together before I go to tutoring school?
Sorry. I said I'd eat with my friends after studying.
Sang Hoon, if I screw up on my exams this time, I'll get scolded. Can I contact you after the exams?
I see. Sure. Good luck on your exams! If you're feeling down, message me anytime.
Did you do well on your exams? I heard the guys say their exams are over. I found out late.
Just so-so.
- What? Really?
- Yeah.
Mom told me she's taking my studio away because my grades dropped.
She said it looks like I've only been playing after she let me live alone.
Your mom is also someone who really does what she says.
Exactly like my Ms. Shin (his mom).
This is heartbreaking.
If Gong Joo Yeong moves out, then where will we hang out now?
Hey, just tell her you'll leave, but don't stop renting the flat.
Don't tell me you'll have to transfer schools too?
Over my dead body! Don't worry, no matter what, I'll take care of that.
It takes one hour by bus from my parent's home.
If I want to go to school with Ja Rim, then I'll have to wake up a little earlier.
Forget about that. What's so important about going to school together? It sounds tiring  just hearing it.
It's not tiring at all! I'm going to do it because I want to.
Just sleep a bit more and come straight to school.
I'm really okay with it!
It's because I'm not comfortable with it. That's why I told you to study!
- And you said you had to improve your grades.
- Sorry.
Wow, is she even monitoring her boyfriend's grades now?
How hilarious. So, she'll only date people who are smart?
She's already being picky with people's education? Honestly, I don't even think she's that pretty.
She just looks hella rude.
Why? I like her, she's pretty. I like that kind of face.
It's because of girls like you that she thinks she's all that.
That's true. What did her boyfriend do wrong? Even I feel sorry for him just watching him.
- Oh, that guy who confessed at the school retreat? Was his name Gong Joo Yeong?
- That's right.
- She heard us.
- Let's go.
Who cares? Let her hear us.
What are you doing after school today? If you're free, want to meet?
Sure. What time do you finish?
- Hey, do you guys want to come today too?
- To what?
- Gong Joo Yeong's room-away party today.
- What's that?
We're holding a party before Gong Joo Yeong gets his place taken away.
His mom told him to move out and go back home.
Oh my gosh. Then does that make Gong Joo Yeong and Ja Rim star-crossed lovers now? (Folktale: The Cowherd and the Weaver Girl—forbidden lovers who could only meet once a year.)
We'll still see each other at school all the time.
If it's a party, we're eating good food, right?
- I'll come then.
- Me too. It's my first time going to a guy's house.
You?
I'm... meeting Sang Hoon.
You're finally meeting?
Is that so? Then enjoy your date.
No, but we're just going to eat, so...
Forget it. Don't come. I don't want Sang Hoon cursing at me.
Those who are coming, remember to bring money for the food.
Gong Joo Yeong, when you move, you must have to throw out a lot of things, right?
Yeah, I looked through my stuff and there are a few things indeed.
Hey, why don't you throw this out to me? It seems heavy.
Are you nuts? Why would I give you my computer?
What about this?
Boys, you know I'm just leaving this neighborhood, not this world, right?
No. I'm just worried that if you take your PlayStation with you, your mom will scold you.
Leave these behind too. You won't have time to play when you go back home anyway.
That's enough. We're here for a farewell party, not to steal stuff.
Exactly. Hurry up and eat.
She's already eating.
I said I'm taking a photo!
- Hey!
- Stop her!
Should I have told him to meet up tomorrow instead?
Forget it, he'll know I was with the others anyway.
Min Ji.
Oh, hi.
Long time no see. It's nice to see you.
I know. Sorry. I had a lot of things to do all this time.
No, it's fine! I'm just saying I'm glad to see you after so long.
Ah...
- Should we go have lunch?
- Sure.
Is it right to do this?
If you are playing with him, put an end to this soon.
Why did we even gather then? Is there nothing we can play all together?
Ah right! I was forgetting that I brought something for us to play.
Ta-da! What might this be?
It's a lie detector! This'll be so much fun. Come on, guys!
Why did he bring that stuff?
After I saw it on TV, I wanted to try this first thing once I came here.
So as soon as I moved here, I bought it at Artbox.
Gosh. I guess they don't sell this in those backwoods of Gwanggok-ri you lived in.
Okay, tonight is the night of truth. We'll go clockwise.
I'll be the first batter and test the machine.
"Kim Byeong Hoon is the most handsome of everyone here." Yes.
Oh, it's accurate then! I'll join.
"On Monday last week,
I stole Oh Ah Ram's dried squid."
No. I don't know about this.
The test is done. Who wants to ask the next question? Should I?
What do you want to ask that's making you so excited?
"I currently have someone I like."
You call that a question? There's no one.
What? You're already over Bang Ye Seul?
Let's check it out.
What the? There is someone, then!
This punk, he was pretending to be over her.
That's not true! There's really no one! The machine must be broken.
- What was the question?
- What?
Prince, your turn.
Don't you dare ask something weird.
"Honestly, I know that my food tastes awfully bad."
- Come on!
- Whoa!
You're going hard.
Honestly, I think it's edible.
For real?
It's even more shocking that it's the truth. How can the truth lack conscience so much?
- She's my friend, but I'm still astonished.
- Stop teasing me.
No, Ja Rim. I think the food you make is the tastiest in the world.
Okay, then here comes the lie reader.
- Hey, wait.
- Honestly, Wang Ja Rim's food tastes bad.
I don't know about others, but it tastes delicious to me. Really.
I think this punk is holding it in.
Look at his eyes trembling.
No! This was fabricated! It's a trap! Kim Byeong Hoon, was it you?
- Why are you like this to me?
- You're the one who brought it over!
It's not true, Ja Rim. The lie detector is lying. I swear.
Yeah, I can't make myself like him, so it's probably better to stop it here, right?
He has probably felt it all this time as well.
What's wrong? Do you not like it?
No, it's delicious here.
Really? I searched online and this was the top result.
I'm really fine. If you don't like it, should we go somewhere else?
- No, that's not it...
- Then...
I have something to say...
This was prepared by this man. Enjoy your time here.
We hadn't seen each other in a while,
and you worked hard during the exams, so I was wondering what I could do for you.
It's too sudden, right? Is it bad?
You don't have to take it if you feel burdened.
No, I'm not. Thank you so much.
I like the flowers.
I'm glad.
May you always be happy.
We have a lot of memories in this room.
Gong Joo Yeong. Do you remember when you stood stark naked in front of Wang Ja Rim?
- Right over there.
- What? Really?
Shut up! We had barely forgotten about it, dammit.
Why forget it? Why forget that pee-pee— I mean, that precious memory?
Hey.
Honestly, this place is the one I'm most attached to after my house.
I feel my body odor permeating from every corner.
Sh*t, you farted again? Goddammit!
No wonder, I was thinking it was weird since earlier.
What the heck are you doing in front of Ja Rim?
Smell it to your heart's content. You won't be able to in the future.
You also fart at school, darn it!
What are you saying?
That's you. Stop putting the blame on me.
What?
- Come here.
- Dammit.
What time is it?
I'm going to tutor you according to your level. Should we start with multiplication? Three times six is?
Ta-da. Enjoy!
It does feel sad.
Wow. I can't believe Wang Ja Rim said that.
That's how bad I feel, Joo Yeong. Do you get it?
What was that? It's not like you.
I feel like this happened because of me.
I wonder if I prevented you from studying properly.
No, it's not your fault. Don't say that.
Gosh, how do I say it?
Your turn, go on.
[Ten minutes before]
Ten Minutes Before
Next one!
From Father: Joo Yeong, good news! You don't have to move out of your studio.
I persuaded your mom.
I trust you to study hard from next time on!
Hang in there, my son!
Fighting!
Yes, let's tell them right now.
What's this?
We all pitched in to prepare this. Ja Rim suggested it.
Ja Rim...
I just felt like I should do at least this much.
Thank you.
I'm also getting sad now.
You've never been here before, so how come?
Hey, I also made good memories just now! Come on, let me be included.
What's so sad about this, making me tear up?
How can I say it in this atmosphere?
They gathered their money to throw me a party and get me a cake.
And even Ja Rim is doing this.
What are you doing? Hurry and blow out the candle.
- Prince's arm is going to fall off.
- What? Ah yes.
What's with your face?
Why do you look like you've just learned you can keep your studio, after acting all miserable all this time?
- That's true.
- What?
- Really?
- What? Yeah.
That's how it turned out.
Dad sent me a text saying he persuaded my mom.
Sorry. It turned into a party for nothing.
♫ I wonder about every single thing about you  ♫
Well, then... Today was the farewell party. Let's have a "cancel the farewell" party tomorrow!
Okay!
What "okay"? Is this your house?
You'll be staying here, then?
Yes. Sorry for making you worry over nothing.
It's okay. It's a relief you don't have to go through that trouble.
Of course! Now nothing will pull us away from each other.
We'll only be getting closer.
If we get married, we'll be living in the same house. How many kids should—
You need to learn when is the appropriate moment to stop.
♫ About you ♫
♫ Pit a pat ♫
So delicious.
I couldn't say it, in the end.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
From Jini: I've arrived home. It was fun, guys!
♫ The day you left goes by ♫
♫ And so does the next day ♫
♫ Like that, the painful season passes ♫
If I had been a bit more honest back then, maybe things wouldn't have ended up like this.
♫ All the autumn leaves fall  ♫
♫ And everything blooms anew  ♫
♫ So why is my season the only one that stays still?  ♫
What should I do now?
♫ I'm still the same
What am I expecting? ♫
♫ Am I still waiting, holding onto the lingering hope that you’ll come back? ♫
♫ The only things that are still the same ♫
♫ Is this street we walked on together, hands in hands ♫
♫ And me, wandering everywhere looking for you, crying ♫
Love Revolution
My mom said I'd be seeing a ghost today.
- What does your mom do?
- She's a psychic.
I want to go on a courage test.
- What kind?
- Having to bring back a hidden object.
I'm most scared of the music room because of the story about the piano ghost.
- Hey, hey!
- Stay away a bit.
Your boyfriend told me to guard you.
- What's that?
- Gosh!
Ja Rim, what's wrong? Did you get attacked by a ghost?
What's this? Who hasn't left yet?
What is it?
But what about Min Ji?
You chicken! How could you leave her alone!
♫ And me, wandering everywhere looking for you ♫