Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Damn, I thought you were Pig Oh, but you're actually Abs Oh.
- What are you saying?
- An athlete should look like that.
We're not here to play. Let's start by warming up.
Pass it, pass it! Throw!
Nice!
Go down. Okay.
If you can't, put your feet together.
Now...
One, two, three, four...
Is this the best you can do?
Don't make me talk.
Breathe, breathe out. One, two...
Stop, stop, stop!
Just a little more, just a little bit. Go down.
- Hello.
- Good to see you again, Namgoong.
My name is Namgoong Ji Soo, not Namgoong. Ji Soo. Anyway, did you come for boxing lessons?
We decided to try it out for a day, but I think we can stop now.
Why? You should try it to learn it. It's the best kind of exercise.
You'll lose one kilogram a week, guaranteed.
- Is it obvious we came to lose weight?
- We get a lot of people during breaks.
Hey Ji Soo, if you're done with your practice, can you go through circuits with them in my stead?
- I'm going to run a lap.
- Yep!
And you must pick the easiest routine.
Yes, ma'am! Noonims, this way.
(T/N: Noonim is used by a male toward older females)
- Oh!
- Are you okay?
Yeah.
Love Revolution: Humidity level 99%
Episode 13. #Summer #IsTheWorst #YouToo #YoureTheWorst
princess_0 @prince_rim: Ja Rim, you aren't talking about me, are you? ㅠㅠ
I think I figured out your skill level. This is so boring, it's killing me.
I'm going. For a fake.
Idiot. How is it a fake if you say it out loud?
Sorry, sorry! Hey, Lee Kaeng!
Hey, pass!
- Yeah!
- Darn it.
Sorry about that earlier.
I told you to pass.
How would you have gone through when the center was right in front of you? Stop ignoring your position.
I've got the feeling you must be a spy for the other team.
Halftime over. Let's take a ten-minute break.
Okay.
- Did you see me playing?
- Yeah, you were cool.
- But when can we leave?
- In a bit, I'm almost done.
- Why are you mad again?
- I don't know, it's hot.
What am I doing here by myself?
What did you promise to do while we were together?
Sorry.
When my lips are bored...
What was that?
I'm bored.
- There are people watching.
- Who?
- Rest here for a bit.
- Yeah.
Do any of you guys have girlfriends you can call? My Jeong Ah seems bored.
Jeong Ah? You said your girlfriend's name was Joo Hui—
Won't you shut your trap?
So, nobody has a girl to call over? My Joo—
Jeong Ah is bored.
Gong Joo Yeong, you said you have a pretty girlfriend. Call her.
I don't think I can call her right now.
He's trying to get close to his girlfriend right now.
What? Even though you've been dating for months?
- How far have you two gone?
- What? For what?
Physical contact, you fool.
See? He can barely hold her hand.
At this level, you're not frustrating, you're hella pitiful.
Hey, should I give you some tips on how to make progress?
- There's nothing I have to learn from you.
- Wow, you're making me upset.
Then what about you, Kyeong Woo? You have a lot of girls. Call one.
- Forget it. I don't have a lot of girls. Do you think I'm like you?
- You little punk.
What about you, Jeong Sang Hoon? You don't have one to call over?
What's with him?
Who's left?
There isn't a single one of you who can call a girlfriend.
Hyung, don't look down on us.
Shouldn't you at least ask us?
Do you two have girlfriends to call over?
- No.
- Jab. One, two. Jab.
- One, two. One, two, one.
One, two, three, weaving. One, two, one, two. End with an uppercut.
Did you see that? Now you'll follow along.
One, two. One, two, one. One, two, three, four. One, two, weave. One, two, one, two. End with an uppercut.
Good. Very good. Let's try one more time.
One, two. One, two, one. One, two, three. One, two, one, two. Weave. One, two —
Hey! Why the hell are you teaching combinations to first-timers?
Stop acting cocky.
Yes, ma'am.
Ten-minute break.
Follow me.
Ja Rim, I have a favor to ask.
- Sweetie!
- No.
- What? But I haven't even told you yet.
- What is it?
We're playing basketball. Can you come cheer—
I reject.
We're at Ah Ram's gym to learn boxing. That's why I can't go.
- Two.
Go away!
Ta-da! Us playing basketball.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's fine.
Your screen cracked. I'm really sorry. What should I do?
No, only the screen protector cracked.
Thank goodness.
Hey, your girlfriend isn't coming?
Looks like you're the only one who thinks you're dating.
That's not true.
Woman
Gong Joo Yeong: Let me know when you guys are done exercising.
Let's go eat. Let's go fill our stomaches.
- Me too.
- You, leave.
I taught them so diligently.  Is that all you can say?
What are you whining about? Are you a kid?
He whines less than Gong Joo Yeong.
I don't know how he knows we're done, but he's whining I should come to cheer for him.
Noona, that's very important for guys.
Yeah.  Go over and save Joo Yeong's face.
How is this that important?
- Were you waiting?
- Yeah.
Oppa, I'm going. See you after my part-time work!
See you later.
Your girlfriend didn't come after all.
She didn't come because she had an important appointment today.
What the!
Umm. Is Gong Joo Yeong here?
He went to the washroom to wash up.
Wang Ja Rim?
Hey, Wang Ja Rim!
Did Ja Rim come?
Is the girl you are dating
Wang Ja Rim?
Hyung, do you know Ja Rim?
Do I just know her?  I used to date her.
What are you saying?  She said she never had a boyfriend.
She said that?
Well ... I remember going out with her. Maybe not?
Anyway, now I understand how you never had physical contact with her. She's got a huge iron wall up.
So I told you you should learn from me.
Hyung.
Where did Ja Rim go?
That way.
Ja Rim, what happened?  Are you hurt?
Ja Rim, what's the matter?
Sorry.  I'm going.
Wait a minute.  I want to ask you something.
- Later.
- Talk to me now.
- Let go.
- Just a moment, Ja Rim.
Do you know Choi Jeong Woo?
- I don't want to talk about it.
- What does that mean? Are you saying you know him?
Don't annoy me and let me go.
Did you date hyung Jeong Woo?
Ja Rim, please talk to me.
I'm not close to him, he's just someone I know.
His relationships with girls are messy and the rumors also aren't nice about him.
But if you don't tell me anything, like this,
I can only imagine the worst.
Let's talk later.
Did Wang Ja Rim go? She looked better with long hair.
That's too bad.
Gong Joo Yeong:  Sweetie, come after your work-out. I miss you.
I bragged so much about you to the others.
- Please come.
- Ja Rim:  Give me the address.
-Joo Yeong: Whoa. Just come to Leesam basketball court!! Thank you, Ja Rim. I love you
I'm sorry I left suddenly. But ...
Two years ago
- I'm first.
- I entered first.
What are you gonna do? I'm going to take a dump.   You can stay if you want to smell it.
Hi, Ja Rim.
Can you give me your phone number?
Good bye.
Wait, Ja Rim.
- You dropped this.
- Sorry?
Your beauty.
It's not mine. Please leave.
Ja Rim.
A present for you. I'll leave now.
I'm okay
When he said he dated you
It's just that you met him for a bit but you didn't actually date, right?
Please read my texts.
Say something.
I want to believe you.
Please...
Reply to me please.
♫ The painful season passes ♫
♫ All the autumn leaves fall  ♫
♫ And everything blooms anew  ♫
♫ So why is my season the only one that stays still?  ♫
♫ I'm still the same ♫
♫ What am I expecting?  ♫
♫ Am I still waiting, holding onto the lingering hope  ♫
♫ that you will come back?
The only things that are still the same ♫
♫ Is this street we walked on together, hand in hand ♫
(T/N: the messages show as unread)
♫ And me alone, wandering everywhere  ♫
♫  looking for you, crying ♫
7 unread messages from Gong Joo Yeong
The next day, 1:02 pm
- Who is it?
- A damn handsome dude.
- Get lost, Kim Byeong Hoon.
- We brought chicken, though?
You could have just put in the code and come in.
You might have been watching porn. We've got great manners, don't we?
Do you think I'm like you?
Eat your chicken and leave.
So did you break up with Wang Ja Rim?
Hey. You shouldn't ask so bluntly.
Why? Does the outcome change if I ask cautiously?
- They didn't break up.
- Why are you the one answering?
I don't know much about dating, but who doesn't have a past? You also had a girlfriend before Wang Ja Rim.
And even if that guy's fishy, what does it matter if they dated? It's all in the past.
This punk is totally right. Isn't the present what's important? You like Wang Ja Rim, don't you?
But she doesn't like me.
You haven't gotten any more texts from Gong Joo Yeong?
Gosh, does this make sense? Who knew you'd meet Choi Jeong Woo again?
Hey. Why aren't you saying anything to Gong Joo Yeong? It's not like you even dated that guy.
That jerk was toying with you from the start. How's that dating? Tell Gong Joo Yeong things as they are.
That's right. You should tell him what happened to prevent a misunderstanding.
I'd have to tell him every single detail just to explain that we didn't date.
It's a bit difficult and exhausting, to be honest.
What? If it were me, I'd find it harder to bear if he misunderstands things.
You've done nothing wrong in regards to what happened with that jerk.
Plus you said they know each other. What if he says weird stuff to Gong Joo Yeong?
Gosh, what's all this? You guys were doing fine.
I do like Ja Rim. But she doesn't tell me anything,
so I keep on thinking the worst.
Hey. You say you like her, but is that all you can think of?
If Ja Rim would only tell me that it's not true, I'd believe her.
But why isn't she saying anything?
Because I'm nothing to her. She probably thinks there's no need to tell me anything.
Gosh, I don't give a f***. You end it or you keep dating, it's your problem!
Should I? Should I just break up?
Yeah!  Huh? What?
We're off now. Go back in.
- Bye.
- See you.
Wang Ja Rim.
It's been a while. Why did you just leave last time?
I'm your ex-boyfriend, you shouldn't ignore me like this. Let's have a chat.
I'm actually glad to see you. Aren't you?
Who's my ex-boyfriend? I don't know what you're thinking, acting like you know me.
Wow, aren't you speaking too rudely? You're even dropping formalities now.
You used to say you wanted me to.
Was your personality always like this?
You're the one who was rude first. It was right here.
You don't even remember, do you?
♫ I like you ♫
♫ I'm being sincere ♫
♫ I don’t want to stay as a friend to you anymore  ♫
I remember everything about how much of a piece of trash you are.
Whoa, my Ja Rim—
- I heard you guys broke up?
- You want to break up?
Sometimes he acts like that guy, so it makes me anxious.
I'm telling you not to stay quiet thinking, "It's not me, so I don't care."
- This jerk.
- Hey hey!
You nuts? What the hell are you doing?
- What's with them?
- Let go!
- Is it because of Wang Ja Rim again?
- Then you, what do you want to do?
Do you not care if things end this way?
I don't think I'll stay put if you keep on picking on Gong Joo Yeong.
♫ I do feel a bit worried ♫