If you act cute again while singing, you're dead.
It also makes me cringe when you force your voice to be lower when singing, you know.
Dammit.
- What is that? Isn't that Lee Kyeong Woo?
- Huh?
♪ Stars flood the sky ♪
♪ So what you think about that? That, baby what do you think? ♪
♪ So what you think about that? I'm so curious about you ♪
♪ So I can feel your love, So I can smile ear to ear ♪
♪ Only think about me. Oh baby would you only look at me? ♪
Ugh, I'm so tired.
Who was it?
It was yours? Sorry.
Do you want to have this then?
It's empty!
I can just buy you something right? Is anything fine?
Anything? Let's go together.
One popsicle for me while you're at it!
Shut up.
But Joo Yeong wants a popsicle...
- Hey.
- Yeah?
Shut up.
- I think I should change my name to "shut up" from today.
- Yeah, suits you well.
Shut up.
One minute. It's my mom.
Yeah, I am at the karaoke with my friends.
Yeah, I'll be back before 9:00 pm. Hmmm.
Hey!
- Hi.
- Yes?
Aren't you Lee Kaeng's girlfriend?
I saw you guys together earlier. What is our Lee Kyeong Woo's new girlfriend's name?
Hey. What does that matter? Let's just go.
- Who are you?
- Me? Oh, I'm Kyeong Woo's friend.
Tell him you saw Jo Seung Min. He'll know.
Ah, why does his girlfriend not know anything? F*ck.
She's not my girlfriend.
- This one is my girlfriend, you idiots.
- Do you want to get hit? Why am I your girlfriend, you crazy fool?
No, it's just that she was with you earlier.
Wow! You have a lot of girls.
Is it dating if we are together? Are you a kid, you fool?
Hey, but your girlfriend looks like she does some sports.
Look at that hunk.
Crazy bastard.
How did you know? She does some sports.
Who is he?
You don't need to know. Hey, go inside with her.
- Ah, this f*cking girl.
- Hey hey hey! I was kidding. She's not my girlfriend.
Ah but... Why the f*ck do you act like you know me?
This punk! Meeting again after so long and you're being rude.
Ah, this is a shameless punk.
Ah, I saw Gong Joo Yeong too earlier. Shall I go greet him?
- Mind your business and go your way.
- Yeah. Let's just go.
The room they all went in earlier, was it there?
I told you to go, goddammit.
Go.
I just wanted to say hi. What's with the serious face?
Are we that close that you'd say hi?
Wow! Your bangs grew a lot.
What?
I heard your eye being like this isn't from getting beaten up by the guys.
I heard it was your dad who hit you.
I didn't even know that and felt sorry for nothing.
You should have told me.
If I'd known it, I would have understood.
- How did you know?
- Is that important?
- F*ck.
- What? You're going to hit me?
Hit me, hit me, you fool.
Hey what's with you?
Step out, you son of a b*tch.
I should go if he asks me to. Things haven't been that fun in a long while.
Love Revolution: Unprecedented case of Kyeong Woo's absence.
Episode 17. #LeeKyeongWoo MIA #Misunderstanding #Fight
bang_H @kyungwoo: Are you eating properly? ㅠㅠ
Kyeong Woo's absent today again.
He's not opening any of my texts, either.
Why is he suddenly out for two days in a row? This has never happened before.
This won't do. Let's find Kyeong Woo. We'll go to his house first.
Detective Ahn, get ready. We're going on a stakeout.
Gosh, there he goes again with another concept.
Hey, forget it. I'll just go and see.
You said he didn't open the door when you went yesterday.
Let's go together. We are in the same neighborhood anyway.
I'm going to the gym today. Ask him what the big deal is for me.
What's the point in walking around in a big group like this?
Should we choose some places where he might go and search there?
Fine. Then, Detective Gong and Detective Wang go to the internet cafe,
Detective Yang and I will check out the billiards place.
The suspect is very dangerous, so make sure to be careful —
Can you chill with your unfunny concepts already?
Joo Yeong!
Oh, hello ma'am. She is Kyeong Woo's mother.
Hello ma'am.
You guys are Kyeong Woo's friends? Did Kyeong Woo not finish at the same time as you?
- Uh that is, Kyeong Woo... went to study.
- He went to the internet cafe.
Ah, he just left before us because he had some other plans.
Is that so? Goodness, where is he roaming around?!
Ma'am. Actually, Lee Kyeong Woo didn't come to school for the last two days.
Huh?
This is not stuff to hide. These things should be told.
He didn't come to school? He surely wore his uniform when he left this morning.
Then where did he go?
Oh my, did he go cause trouble somewhere?
Oh, don't worry ma'am. Kyeong Woo doesn't get into trouble.
He is very diligent at school. I know it very well.
Is that so? Anyway thanks for telling me.
I've been working late the past few days so I couldn't take care of Kyeong Woo properly.
I think I should talk to him.
Yeah, Mom.
Rice, rice, rice.
(T/N: playing a game called "Barley-Rice")
Two plus... minus...
Hey what happened to you?
Hey, aren't you too much? You're ignoring my texts, calls, now even my words.
Don't you have anything to tell me?
I am talking to you now. Ah. Did you eat anything?
- Uh?
- Are you like this because you don't know?
What are you saying? Did your mom scold you a lot yesterday? Is it because of that?
That was you too?
I was the one who told your mother.
F*ck, leave it. What can I talk with you about?
It's fine as long as I disappear.
Why was Lee Kyeong Woo like that earlier? Do you guys know?
We are also frustrated because we don't know.
It's strange. It's damn strange.
Lee Kaeng isn't someone who gets angry for no reason. What could it be?
Happy now? F*ck, you really can't take a hint.
Lee Kyeong Woo seemed to be sensitive about his bangs.
Yeah, that's right. He's hella sensitive about his bangs because of the scar on his forehead.
So we're finally putting together the unsolvable puzzle.
Lee Kyeong Woo's bangs were actually like a bomb that could go off at any time.
You better cut this unsightly hair immediately.
Shoot, I guess this is how I get caught in the end.
Gong Joo Yeong, where are you? Save me!
You came for me, my friend!
Teacher! I have the hair clippers here!
This could happen. One hundred percent possible.
I'm 100% sure it's bullshit, idiots.
No, I'm sure it's not the bangs. In my opinion,
sseeing that Lee Kyeong Woo hurt his hand, he surely fought someone.
During the party, at the karaoke. That hell of a mean-looking jerk. Remember?
- Jo Seung Min?
- How do you guys know Jo Seung Min?
He was trying to start a fight with Lee Kyeong Woo.
He said he was Jo Seung Min, his middle school classmate.
You guys know him? You guys were also friends during middle school.
I don't really know him, because I transferred to that school only in the second year.
Jo Seung Min was trying to start a fight with me too, saying I seemed close to Lee Kyeong Woo.
Something like that might happen again.
Fill me in. I need to know so I can be prepared.
Did something happen between him and Lee Kyeong Woo?
Gosh. We also don't know everything.
In middle school, Lee Kyeong Woo
went around with Jo Seung Min's crew and didn't have much to do with us.
2 years ago, Ilsam Middle School
Gong Joo Yeong followed Lee Kyeong Woo around on his own and worried a lot about him.
Because actually, Jo Seung Min kind of—
So he liked Lee Kyeong Woo.
What bullshit is that?
What nonsense are you saying, seriously?
With my deep experience in investigation, I can sense something.
Shall we start from the time we met Jo Seung Min at the karaoke?
- She's not my girlfriend.
-  At that moment,
- This one is my girlfriend, you idiots.
-  I got a hunch as soon as I saw the look on that guy's face.
Anyone could see what it was:
"This person is your girlfriend?"
Jealousy, of course.
In that case...
Jo Seung Min liked Lee Kyeong Woo,
and Lee Kyeong Woo liked Gong Joo Yeong,
but Gong Joo Yeong liked Jo Seung Min.
But Lee Kyeong Woo liked Gong Joo Yeong and Gong Joo Yeong liked Jo Seung Min,
but Lee Kyeong Woo liked Gong Joo Yeong.
And thus Lee Kyeong Woo, after learning all about this tragic tortuous love, grabbed Gong Joo Yeong by his collar today.
You guys should stop playing detective.
Why? It's possible. What do you think about my deduction, Gong Joo Yeong?
It's nothing like that.
Still, you guessed that Lee Kyeong Woo had a girl that he liked, I'll give you that.
Someone that he liked? Who?
I'm not sure. Lee Kyeong Woo didn't really tell us.
Gong Joo Yeong, you must have heard something, right?
Her name was...
Nam Yu Ri
♫ The only place where I could rest ♫
♫ You alone are enough for me ♫
Hey give me your phone number.
What will I get if I give it to you?
You'll make a nice friend, that's all.
I have a hell of a lot of friends. Buzz off.
Ah you will play hard to get? I will just ask Hyeong Bae then.
♫ Every day, every moment ♫
♫ Let's be together ♫
- That was crazy!
- You're already so handsome!
Really! Why do you also sing well?!
My heart skipped a beat. I'm fainting.
I have to go now.
You are going already? Shall I walk you home?
Do you think I can't find my home?
Hey Lee Kyeong Woo! You walk me home.
Hey Nam Yu Ri! You said you don't need anyone to walk you home.
I know my address well, but I want Lee Kyeong Woo to know it as well.
Sure.
Your father isn't coming home tonight. You will come home, right?
Waaaa! Gosh!
What the heck, Lee Kyeong Woo? You're a total scaredy-cat!
Dammit. No, I'm not. Tie your hair, will you?
Ohhh you aren't? Then will you watch a horror film with me next time?
Why would I go watch a movie with you?
Why not? Do you have a girlfriend, by any chance?
- What if I don't?
- I should seduce you.
- If I do?
- I should steal you from her.
Wow, you're spunky.
And you? Will you come to me if I seduce you?
I am not sure. I may or may not come. Depends on what you do.
Hey!
Hey hey hey hey hey, this is minus100 points. Hey, ah, don't do this.
Hey Lee Kaeng. We are going to the gaming cafe, come with us.
I have plans.
Nam Yu Ri?
Look at him smiling. This punk is dating!
Hey, how long has it been? How long?
Hey! Let's leave him and play just the three of us.
Hey! If I am born again
then I want to be born as Lee Kyeong Woo. The girls like only him.
Right. I am darned envious of you.
Hey can't you share your face?
Shut up.
Lee Kyeong Woo was probably the happiest at that time. He really liked Nam Yu Ri.
Then why did they break up?
That is... because of Jo Seung Min.
So it is a tragic love story. I was right, see?
Well, to some extent. Actually, I think Jo Seung Min liked Nam Yu Ri.
So he told weird stuff to other girls and made them spread rumors on purpose.
It's obvious what kind of rumors they were.
Kyeong Woo did you hear the rumor?
- What rumor?
- Nam Yu Ri is already married.
- Her second marriage too.
But her ex-husband came back alive.
Hey!
What the hell is wrong with you? Did you eat something weird?
But if it was the reason for their breakup, then it must not have been a good rumor.
Yes, that is... It was saying Nam Yu Ri's relationships with guys were a bit problematic.
What a very pathetic rumor.
So? Lee Kyeong Woo believed that?
Back then we were young, so...
The rumor was one thing, but Jo Seung Min was the main factor, driving a wedge between them.
Hey! Did you hear the rumor? Nam Yu Ri and Hyeong Seung Jin—
Don't butt in. It is none of your business.
I was in contact with Nam Yu Ri, but it felt uncomfortable.
What are you saying?
Well, it is a bit awkward to say it myself,
but on the day we first met the girls from Baekchil Middle School, she contacted me first.
At first I thought she was interested in me
but after a few days, she started dating you. Honestly, I was baffled.
But now I am just interacting with her as a friend.
Ah f*ck. Friend? Interacting?
Hey. Whether you like her or not, she is dating me so shouldn't you have stopped contacting her?
I didn't contact her first. Today also she contacted me first.
Then you just don't have to reply.
Hey, you're making me upset. I am telling you because I'm worried, as your friend.
Nam Yu Ri is known to lie to get whatever she wants. I also almost fell for it a few times.
Hey Jo Seung Min, what are you trying to do since earlier?
Hey I am telling you because I am worried about you.
F*ck.
Wow, she's freaking pretty.
The advent of the crazy witch Nam Yu Ri.
Crazy bitch LMAO
Why is it so hard to see you these days?
Noona, read my message.
Darling! Did you wait long?
- Don't you have anything to tell me?
- What?
About what?
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
Love Revolution
Then it was revealed that all the bad rumors at school about Nam Yu Ri were that jerk's doing.
On top of that, he also made bad rumors about Lee Kyeong Woo.
After that, Kyeong Woo suddenly got hospitalized.
Then how did he get hurt?
You grew a lot, Joo Yeong.
You're just Lee Kyeong Woo's lackey, you moron.
Come out. Gong Joo Yeong got hit because of you.
- Get up. Hey!
- Dammit! What are you doing?
Do you see me as a guy who would spread false rumors behind your back?
Do something about your bangs. Doesn't it feel suffocating?
♫ I do the homework I had put off and meet with my friends ♫
♫ My friendships strengthen and I have some free time ♫