Let's go to the  snack shop. I'll treat you today.
Would you hold still?
Hurry up and let’s go before break time ends.
You must be hungry.
What would you like? Our Ja Rim's
- favorite bread is cheese bread.
- She's quite impressive.
It’s not easy to sponge off someone that much.
I feel sorry for him every time I see them.
Hey, I need to go to the bathroom. Go ahead.
Yeah! All right. I'll meet you at the snack store.
Excuse me. What was that just now?
- About what?
- What did you just say?
You said something about Gong Joo Yeong.
I feel sorry for Gong Joo Yeong.
What?
You're pretending you don't know. You're playing with Gong Joo Yeong.
The rumors have spread in our school.
You should make it less obvious. Every time I see him, he’s always looking out for you.
Exactly! Let's go.
Let's go.
He and Bo Gyeong made such an adorable couple.
Exactly.
Bo Gyeong? Who is that?
Love Revolution: The sudden appearance of the ex-girlfriend
Episode 28. #Boyfriend'sPast #ItBothersMe #DefinitelyNotJealousy
kyungwoo @prince_rim: Everyone has a past
That's a pasta restaurant, but the tiramisu they sell for dessert is totally awesome.
That's nice. Are you going home right after we eat that?
No. I’ll get tickets for a movie too.
Joo Yeong, I'm Bo Gyeong.
You didn't reply to my DM.
Why? Is there anything to see?
Nope!
What is this? How did she know my number?
- What? Kwak Bo Gyeong?
- Yeah!
Suddenly! She hasn't contacted me once all this time.
What's going on? What is this?
Just ignore her. You have a girlfriend now.
Of course I'll do that. I don’t have any lingering feelings for her.
I blocked her on Instagram, but she kept...
But...
No. I'll put an end to this by myself.
Don't say anything to Ja Rim.
Why do you have a passbook?
Oh! Did you see it?
- You took it out—
- Ta-da!
This is a couple's bankbook! Let's save 1,000 won here every day
so when we go on a date or on a trip, we could use it.
What do you think? What do you think?
Bothersome.
You just need to give me 500 won every day, and  I'll put it in.
Do what you want.
That crazy witch was on the verge of cursing at us too.
I was so scared.
He has really bad luck.
If he had kept on dating Bo Gyeong, he would never have played around with that wench.
You're right.
They had a pretty relationship.
Like an artist
I'm here. Did you wait long?
Bo Gyeong, big news. Gong Joo Yeong seems to really let others leech off him.
Today also he was like, "Do you want me to buy you something?"
Really? So the rumors were true.
Bo Gyeong, you should go after him. Surely,  Gong Joo  Yeong will be waiting for your call.
Still, he has a girlfriend. That would be going too far.
This is frustrating. You're too kind.
Hey! Everyone at school knows she’s just messing with him.
What movie do you want to watch?
Ka-talk (message)
Ka-talk
Joo Yeong, where are you?
I'm in the city center.
What's with her again?
- Come on, take a look.
- Huh?
- What?
- The movie.
There are 3 at 7 o'clock, let's watch one of these.
Ka-talk
Yeah, sure.
- What are you doing? Look at your texts. Who is it?
- What? Ah.
Well, just... a friend.
You nutcase. What did you just say?
But I can’t tell her it's my ex-girlfriend.
What's the matter?
Oh nothing.
I'm sorry.
But I have a girlfriend right now.
It’s uncomfortable for me that you’re contacting me.
I've thought a lot about you.
Can't I just contact you as a friend?
Sorry.i>
If this continues,
I'll have no choice but to block you.
I'm only asking you to be my friend.
Why are you being like this?
Why do you think I'm doing this when I know you have a girlfriend?
I really gathered up my courage because I'm going through a hard time.
Sorry.
I don't want you to contact me.
I even had a hard time forgetting you.
Truthfully, it was because of Song Ye Jin
that I broke up with you unwillingly.
What did Gong Joo Yeong say?
I guess his girlfriend is scolding him.
- Crazy!
- What?
I just can't believe it. What about the things she does?
Did you ask him out? You only asked him to stay in contact.
She just can't watch her boyfriend doing that when he's together with her.
She's afraid she'll lose him.
But she has nothing to say even if he's taken by someone else.
It'd be a different story if she was good to him.
Don't say that.
Did you poop? Why are you coming out so late?
No, no! I just had to wash my hands also.
Wait, Ja Rim.
Did you book the movie tickets?
No. We still didn't select the movie yet.
I'm really sorry, but shall we just go home early today?
Okay. You don't seem okay today.
My stomach feels bad today.
Gong Joo Yeong, you are the worst guy!
Ja Rim, I'm sorry. I asked you out first and then...
Instead, let's watch a movie tomorrow without fail.
Pharmacy
Open your mouth.
Drink it.
Your stomach hurts, your face is yellow, and you're burping.
Do you have indigestion?
Ja Rim...
- Or is there something on your mind?
- What?
- No.
- Let's take a taxi today.
I'll pay.
It's true.
I had no choice but to break up with you.
Why?
What forced you to do that?
It's already late for today.
Let's talk again tomorrow.
What if Ja Rim finds out I'm chatting with her like this?
I really don't feel anything for her.
She'll misunderstand.
Okay. I'll just listen to the reason she broke up with me and completely end things there. Right.
Things will surely end tomorrow.
Gong Joo Yeong!
Will that thing be my life?
Joo Yeong.
Why are you here?
We said we would talk today.
No, but why here?
Sorry. I didn't see your girlfriend was here.
You guys go.
Hey, what are you doing? Dammit, let go!
I told you to keep a low profile.
You're surprisingly tight-lipped. Gong Joo Yeong still doesn't know.
Exactly. Have some sense and don't pretend you're close with Gong Joo Yeong.
But even if Gong Joo Yeong is dating, why did he choose that kind of girl?
I heard Wang Ja Rim dated a big shot before.
Are you talking about Choi Jeong Woo? Know your facts before you blabber about it. They didn't date.
Is that so? But she already has a bad reputation in your school.
Hey.
You're the one who spread those sh*tty rumors about Wang Ja Rim at our school, right?
What?
I never did anything like that.
Those rumors suddenly came about, and you suddenly contact Gong Joo Yeong.
If it wasn't you, who else could it be?
It's a coincidence.
Those rumors only exist because she acts that way.
Because you're so f**king much better.
What about me? I'm so good at maintaining my social relationships.
Keep living like that then. Trouble will come for you one day.
Yes, I will live like that.
Who was that?
Who could it be that you agreed to talk with her and Lee Kyeong Woo ended up dragging her away?
- About that...
- It's his ex-girlfriend.
- She's even his first lov—
- You're dead you bastard.
Ex-girlfriend?
No. She suddenly came herself.
I really don't have any feelings for her.
She... she kept saying she's having a hard time.
You guys talked on KakaoTalk?
I'll show you. This. We didn't say much.
If you look at it... And I even already blocked her.
I rejected her firmly too, but she kept...
She's not listening.
The point is you contacted her without telling me. You ass, when did this start?
That cow and you, are you two insane? Why are you guys talking?
I feel like the odd man out.
I really don't have any feelings for her anymore!
Trust me, Ja Rim.
He and Bo Gyeong made such an adorable couple.
Exactly.
I'm leaving.
Ja Rim!
You nutcase, you were in contact with her?
This is a problem.
You seriously...
I thought you said you would end things. Why were you talking to her secretly?
No, I told her I would block her,
but she kept saying she was having a hard time.
She said she was forced to break up with me because of Seong Ye Jin.
What? She said that?
But it is true that she suddenly stopped hanging out with Seong Ye Jin and her friends.
Damn it. So what? So what if it's true? Are you going to date her again or something?
No! What nonsense are you saying?
It's just... I didn't know why we broke up.
I just wanted to know the reason.
You could reject her ten thousand times and it wouldn't be enough.  Everything she says is bullshit, so just ignore it.
Hey, Lee Kaeng. Were you the one who got dumped by Kwak Bo Gyeong? Why do you hate her so much?
Hey, but wasn't Wang Ja Rim a bit strange just now?
- What?
- She didn't even get mad.
Usually, if an ex comes and hooks arms with your partner, wouldn't you get mad?
You're right.
Is she nuts?
When she knows he has a girlfriend, why would she seek him out?
I'm speechless. She linked arms with him even though you were right there. Is she crazy?
Didn't she do that for you to see?
Exactly.  She's outright crafty as a fox.  What's her name? Kwak Bo Gyeong?
I heard she goes to Poongil High School. Show me. I couldn't see her face earlier.
bogyeong232
- What is this?  What happened to her face?
- Let me see.
Crazy.  She looks like one hell of a foxy witch.
Hey, stick to the facts.
You should have just grabbed her hair.
Honestly, I'm very angry.
But these days there's a rumor that I'm playing with Gong Joo Yeong, so I couldn't let my anger out.
- Why?  I thought rumors don't bother you.
- That's right.
Usually, wouldn't you say "get back together with your ex if you want"?
Hey, she likes Gong Joo Yeong.  She's worried that Gong Joo Yeong is being treated as a pushover.
Never mind. That Kim Bo Gyeong? Don't pay any attention. She's not someone who will shake Gong Joo Yeong.
- Kwak Bo Gyeong.
- Yeah, her.
But the thing is, she looks kind of cute.
Since they say that she and Gong Joo Yeong made a nice couple, it feels a bit ...
They look damn great together.
Damn. I really feel like crap, but I don't know why I feel so crappy.
Isn't that just jealousy?
Why is Ja Rim not getting angry? She didn't even ask me more questions.
- Did you finish your homework?
- Huh?
You also have English homework today, no? Some text analysis?
Yes, but I haven't yet—
Copy that. Or you'll lose points.
- Thank—
- Do you want to eat this?
- Ja Rim. Why all of a sudden—
- Aren't you taking it?
What the? I dropped ranks to Gold four. I'm doomed.
Gosh.
Hey. Ja Rim is strange.
She isn't angry and she's taking care of me.
Even weirder, she gave me candy.
What's going on? Why  is she being so nice to me?
- Must be a farewell present.
- Don't say something like that.
Right.  I didn't see Ja Rim swear at you.
Is it because she saw your ex-girlfriend yesterday? No way, don't tell me...
- Jealousy?
- Don't say such bullshit.
I don't want to see him breathe in all these false hopes.
A lot already entered the lungs.
Wow.  So that was it.
I really don't want to see this.
Hey.  Wang Ja Rim?  That doesn't make any damn sense.
Why? It's exactly like that. Seeing how she's treating him well after seeing his ex yesterday.
This is a historic day.
Hey, Kwak Bo Gyeong has gotten prettier.
What are you saying?
She is cute. She acts cute a lot, too.
When I think about it, she's the exact opposite of Prince.
Hey, Joo Yeong.  You liked her a lot.
- What are you talking about?
- I guess she was your first kiss.
As for the kiss, it was a deep kiss.
Are you guys insane?
DANGER
It must have been nice.
- Ja Rim, this is a misunder—
- If you follow me, I'll rip your head off.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
The Big Picture of the Singles
You guys have a death wish?
You asked us to do it.  We did it for you.
Did I ask you to do it in this way?
- Don't mess—
- Does it bug you that much?
Yes, it does.  I am very bothered.
How could I not be.  I heard he had such a good relationship with her.
Even if Gong Joo Yeong doesn't say anything,
he'll definitely compare us.
Hey.
Follow me.  I have something to tell you.
♫ I like you  ♫
♫ I'm being sincere ♫
Love Revolution
- Kwak Bo Gyeong is waiting for me again.
- I have to talk to you.
- What the hell?!
- Wang Ja Rim went to meet Kwak Bo Gyeong.
- What?!
- Don't come looking for Gong Joo Yeong.
I am only contacting him as a friend.
Friend, my foot.
The idiot who is contacting me when he has a girlfriend, or you who is dating that idiot
Idiots are meeting each other well.
You want me to stay put when Ja Rim is hearing such words?
- Why are you crying?
- You aren't fine, right?
I am perfectly fine.
You are hugging me now like this.
♫ I wish you would let me carry some of that burden  ♫