Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Guys.  No end-of-day homeroom today. You can go.
- Really?
- Yay.
Five, four, three, two, one. Enter!
- Darling, let's go home.
Jeez.
Next one, enter on three.  Three, two, one Daeng!
Kyeong Woo.
Kyeong Woo, it's over.
Are you two some kind of puppies?
It seems they remain in a "stay" until their masters are finished.
Do you attend school to date? You should be studying.
You don't study either. Please date at least.
I don't hear.  I don't hear anything.
F/W SPECIAL PRICES
5% discount
- Damn, we lost.
-  Lee Kyeong Woo, what are you doing?
How long are you going to do that?  I'm a bit bored.
Oh. just a little longer.
- Another round.  Go Go.
- Are you going to play more?
Just one round.  Only one.
We're good right now.
Kyeong Woo, I don't have anything to do.  Is it okay if I leave now?
- Are you going?
- Why? Why? We're only just now getting fired up!
Sorry.  Never mind about me and have fun.
Ye S—
Ye Seul.
Ability is decided by
one's own effort.
Wow Daebak!  I won!
What?
I entered every time I went to see a movie with Ja Rim, and now I got a Lotte World free pass.
F*#%.  For how many?
- Two right?
- Wait a sec.
Wow, daebak.  I can bring three with me?
Four passes? It's just perfect for the four of us to go. Shall we go this weekend?
What are you talking about? Why would I go with you guys? I'm going with Ja Rim.
"I'm going with Ja Rim."  Then you shouldn't have told us at all, you disloyal bastard.
Kaeng?  What about you?  Would you like to double date with Ye Seul?
- I'll ask her.
- Wow.
Even Lee Kyeong Woo is dumping us because he has a girlfriend.
- Come to think of it, how many days has it been?
- Ja Rim and I—
Not you, I don't want to know.
Around twenty days?
How far have you progressed?
Right. We can't not talk about this.
- Has this dude already—?
- You nutcase.
Hey!  Don't say that in my house. Ja Rim comes to hang out here and that's dirty.
We did kiss.
- When?
- Where?
- Damn. Why do you need to know?
- Please tell.
Dude.  Did you make the first move?
She did it first. In front of her house.
What? F-First?
I freaking envy you.  When will I get a girlfriend?
- First of all, you won't ever.
-  Yeah, that's you.
- No.
- Yeah, no.
- You won't either.
- You, you. You're also forever single.
- You won't. I'm reflecting it back to you.
- Yeah you won't. That's right.
- You also won't ever have one.
- No you won't.
princess_0
Love Revolution
Temperature Gap
Episode 23
#Doubledate #LotteWorld #Kiss
kyungwoo @princess_0: I don't want to go on double dates anymore.
When I think about it, I've been dating Ja Rim for half a year but I only held her hand.
No.  For me I just want Ja Rim to be there for me.
But for Kyeong Woo it hasn't even been a month,
and they already kissed...  Is something wrong with us?
I don't think I can fall asleep.
Darliiiiiiiiiiiiing.
What's the matter with you now? At school.
How can you say that to your boyfriend?
Don't do this at school. Seriously.
Do you want to hold this?
Darling, the whole school knows we are dating, so why can't I hold your hand?
I can't tell you who, but there are kids these days who recently started dating
and they're already kissing.
This punk.
So, what? You want to squeeze our mouths against each other's?
Yes, no, nope.
We can just squeeze hands affectionately.
Oh. seriously. If you don't want your wrist cut off, don't ever touch me at school.
Yes.
Never mind.  That's not the point.
Prince.  He wants to go to Lotte World this weekend.
Yeah.  I won four tickets and we decided to go on a double date with that couple.
Why the four of you? Wouldn't you normally want to hang out just you two?
Yeah.  But when I learned I won, he was with me.
I couldn't act like he wasn't there. I'd look like a cheapskate.
- So Darling, do you want to go?
- Well...
- Okay.
- Super!
Okay. I'll ask too.
This Saturday?  Great!
That's good.
Is it too spicy?
I can bear it.  It's okay.
Really.  You can't even eat spicy food.
No, no.  It's tasty.
You play games so often.
Well, sometimes.
Even when you are with me, you keep doing it.  Yesterday, too.
No, look.  I'm not doing it now.
You really like games. You'll stop playing so often, right?
Okay.
Saturday.
A date with Ja Rim at Lotte World.
I'll hold Ja Rim's hand as much as I want, link arms with her,
and in front of the merry-go-round,  I will  ki - i - ss ...
Okay.  It's been almost half a year since we started dating.
Today is indeed the day.
All the popular rides have a half-hour wait so should we ride the merry-go-round first?
- I'd like that.
- Hey, why would we come all way here and ride that?
Just ride it.  I don't want to start with waiting.
Right? I knew that so I found the ride with the least waiting. I did well, right?
Good job. Ye Seul, what do you think?
I like it too.  Let's take pictures.
Okay. Then it's okay for everybody except Kyeong Woo? Let's go to the merry-go-round.
Does it only matter if you guys want it?
Let's go, darling.
Aren't you coming?
I am.  I was turning on the app.
I'll help you up.
Put on the safety belt too.
Thanks.
Thanks. Sweetie, I'll take a photo of you.
One, two, three.
So pretty. Can you smile a bit this time? One, two, three.
Okay! Now let's take a pic together.
It's dangerous. I'll go to you.
It's more dangerous for you!
I'm okay. One, two, three.
We will make a short announcement for our passengers on the merry-go-round.
We should also take some pics.
Cute. Look here, I'll take some.
Why would you? I'm fine. Take your picture.
Ah, click one pic for me. I'll keep it as my wallpaper.
We will be departing now. Enjoy your ride!
Hey, let's take a pic here.
Did you come to take pictures? You keep on asking to take pictures everywhere we go.
The only thing that remains from such outings are pictures, you brat.
Hurry up and stand there.
Shall we?
No, If you don't want to—
No no, let's go.
♫ I know very well it won't ring ♫
♫ But tonight, for no reason,  ♫
♫ I find myself waiting ♫
♫ Honestly, how should I put it?  ♫
Im taking it. One, two, three!
♫ I secretly hoped we'd run into each other again ♫
One, two, three.
♫ Maybe that’s what I was hoping for tonight ♫
Wow!
♫ Walking on this street ♫
Did it come out well? Let me see.
♫ Why is the jet-black city so beautiful? ♫
♫ I am thankful you came to me when I was done ♫
Why am I the only one smiling? You should've smiled. You look handsome, even if you smile.
I'm feeling awkward today.
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
I'll take a pic for you guys also.
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
♫ Whenever I felt sad sending you back home ♫
Darling, shall we also take a pic while kissing?
Sure, if you want that pic to be the one at your funeral.
♫ Why do I ?  ♫
Give me the phone.
♫ remember this now? ♫
I'm taking the pic.
♫ Midnight Midnight ♫
One, two... three!
♫ Midnight. Why do I remember only now?  ♫
- It's done.
- Tactless fellow. You should've taken a few more pics.
♫ Midnight, midnight ♫
What is this?! If you were going to do this, why say you'd take it?
You were better looking with only half of you showing. It's better than your actual appearance.
Let's go if we're done with the pics.
Ja Rim, let's go together.
Shall we go?
Zombie Experience
It looks fun.
This kind of thing really doesn't scare me at all.
Can you guys go, just the two of you? Kyeong Woo doesn't like things like that.
Ah! He's more of a coward than I thought.
Hey! It's o-only that I d-don't like it. Yeah.
Le- let- let's go.
You saw him stammer, right? He gets scared easily.
- Let's leave quickly.
- I'm scared!
- What, why?
- There's a person!
Isn't something going to jump out at us?
Hey, where are you going?!
princess_0: Lotte World with Ja Rim♥︎ Double date with KaengSeul.
Annoying.
How did things end up this way?
Yang Min Ji idiot, seriously.
New message from Sang Hoon
You seem to like good restaurants.
Yeah. But I'm going to go on a diet now.
Are you okay? He's still out of it.
I won't go ever again. You might as well ask me to ride the gyro drop a hundred times.
Ja Rim, do you want to do that?
Okay! Let's go to the arcade.
Hey! Hey! What's so urgent?
- When shall we go home?
- I don't mind as long as I'm with you.
Okay then.
- In for a bet? The losers buy food next time we hang out.
- Deal.
Ja Rim and Bang Ye Seul go first.
Ye Seul, do you know how to play this?
No, I haven't played this. Not once.
Ye Seul doesn't know. Give her a handicap.
Oh really? Then let's not count five of Ja Rim's bullets.
What if I'm bad at it?
It's okay, I'll cover for you.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Ye Seul is good at this. She'll be fine even without the handicap—
When you played with me last time, you won so easily.
Hey. So you suggested a bet knowing Wang Ja Rim is good. You're a thug.
I can just buy food for everyone then. Retract that pout.
It's fine. Let's say this was a practice game. Ye Seul is good at it, too, anyway.
This is fun.
This time we're starting at the same time.
Milky white Wang Ja Rim, milky—
Stop it! Are you trying to prevent me from playing or what?
My sweetie is doing well! My Ja Rim is a tough one!
- Tough Ja Rim! Tough Ja Rim!
- You have a death wish?
Hey, Prince, go easy. You're damn fierce.
- Ye Seul, what are you doing?
- What?
My sweetie won!
You got them all? You're crazy.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Hey, stop that and reload it.
My darling, you did so well.
Stop it.
We could have gone with them. Their homes are in the same direction as ours.
No but... They would also
want to spend time alone together too, I think.
It's so pretty.
What is it? What's wrong?
- What do you mean?
- Do you have something to say?
- Do you need to poo?
- No, that's not it.
Then what is it?
You won't get mad, right?
I won't.
You won't curse at me, right? You won't hit me?
I'm on the verge of cursing right now. Hurry up and talk. Three, two—
No, th-that's not it.
We...
d-don't really show any p-physical affection.
But other kids,
they would k-kiss within three days of d-dating and all.
You were saying that last time too.
- So you want to do that too?
- Yes. Ah, n-no!
It's not that I wouldn't like to. It's not that I just want to or anything...
I do want to, but...
What the hell are you saying?
- Hey. I'm giving you three seconds. Three,
- What?
- two, one.
I gave you a chance. If you bring this up again next time, you're dead—
I never told you to do it on my lips.
- And you went over the time!
- What?
You want to die?
It's a pity we lost the game. We'll have to buy them a meal next time.
It's okay, I'll buy.
Why would you? Don't.
It's fine. Ah.
- You're playing a game again?
- Just for a sec.
- You know—
- No it's fine, I'll buy.
When should we hang out with them again?
We're almost at my place. I'll go now.
- What's wrong?
- Forget it, you can go home.
You couldn't play your game all day today.
- Are you like this because of that?
- It's not because of that.
Hey, there's vomit!
- You're too much. You were really mean.
- What?
You're not even curious about how I feel, are you?
- What are you saying? That's not true.
- You don't seem to be curious at all
about how I feel or what I want to do.
Why do I feel this lonely even when I'm with you?
When we're together, you just look at your phone.
I always feel like I'm being a hindrance when you'd rather hang out with your friends.
- That's not it.
- It was the same today.
Looking at you after seeing how Gong Joo Yeong treats Ja Rim, I wonder if we're really dating.
- He's just like that.
- I know he's like that. But I'm telling you I feel too lonely.
It's not like I was bad at that game because I wanted to, but you openly showed your disappointment.
I don't feel good, but you keep playing your game.
♫ And everything blooms anew  ♫
You weren't even listening to me.
♫ So why is my season the only one that stays still?  ♫
Why are you crying? I'm telling you that's not true.
♫ I'm still the same ♫
Your girlfriend stepped in vomit but you just laughed.
♫ What am I expecting? ♫
Sorry.
♫ Am I still waiting, holding onto the lingering hope that you’ll come back? ♫
You...
♫ The only thing that's still the same ♫
Do you actually like me?
♫ Is this street we walked on together, hands in hands ♫
- I do like you.
- Then why don't you pay attention to how I feel?
I'm always trying to read your mood.
♫ And me, wandering everywhere looking for you ♫
I'm lonely because I feel like you don't like me back. Aren't you dating me because you like me as well?
♫ Crying and crying again ♫
♫ You are still the same  ♫
♫ Still in my heart, same as ever ♫
I got it. I'm leaving.
♫ Can I go on holding onto the lingering hope that you will come back again? ♫
♫ The only things that are still the same ♫
♫ Is this street we walked on together, hands in hands ♫
I guess you really don't like me, seeing that you're not holding onto me.
♫ And me, wandering everywhere looking for you, crying ♫
I don't think I can be good to you.
I was giving it my best. But I didn't know you had that on your mind.
I'm sorry.
princess_0: First Lotte World with my Ja Rim
#LoveStagram #World'sPrettiest #BestPic #MerryGoRoundPic #AhnKyeongMin #CouldNever
New message from Lee Kaeng
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
Love Revolution
There was an accident in the canteen and they're doing emergency repair work.
They told us not to order food in, so what do we do?
I'll make your lunch together with mine.
- Looks delicious!
- I think it's gone bad.
- Is that Lee Kyeong Woo?
- Let's just keep going our way.
Does the food I make taste bad?
How can you say it's garbage?
For cooking, do it like you do math. Think of it as a formula and stick to the quantities.
Hey, want to eat this?
Did you make it for me?
Have you stopped liking me?
Since the moment I first saw you, I really liked you.
I'm a bad guy.
Then should we...
What's this? Wh-Why does it taste good?
♫ But you suddenly come back to me tonight  ♫