Guys, give some ideas for the class meeting. No one?
Come on, participate a bit. I'm tired.
Class meeting: Festival preparations
Each class gets a 200,000 won support fund, right?
Then what about choosing a representative for each class and holding a combat competition? Awesome.
Amazing, right? I, we've got the victory unconditionally secured, I tell you.
We take an admission fee and make people bet too.
Hey, if we give food to her as her fighting fee, then it'll be cheap for us!
I don't need fighting fee to make you guys shut up.
Hey, this might be fun. We will get reported for school violence also. Don't joke around.
Let's do nail art. There are many people in our class that go to beauty academy.
Ah I like the idea. Let's do nail art.
Nail art? It does sound good, but everyone in the class should have a role.
Let's keep that on the side for now and think of what to do as the main activity.
Let's just do a cafe just like other classes. Hey Lee Kyeong Woo you have worked part-time in a cafe, right?
"Customer what would you like to order?"
Your fake capitalistic smile was quite something.
Right, he's good at it. You can just teach the others.
Shut your trap.
Many classes are already doing a cafe so it would be nice if we had a concept...
Something enough to attract people, isn't there anything like that?
For a cafe, we need a hot guy and hot girl part-timers.
Where would we have such hot girl and guy in our class?
Ah yeah! Those two over there.
You both can do the advertising.
On a closer look, don't they look good together?
- Crazy.
- What the hell are you saying to a girl with a boyfriend.
Just that both of them are the prettiest and most handsome ones, right?
What is so handsome about Lee Kyeong Woo? Such a snotty teenager.
I think it will be better to do a cafe with a pretty photo zone where we take photos for the customer.
Hm, nice idea. You are clicking pics with them, right?
- Uh?
- You said uh, that was a yes.
This doesn't sound bad. Then whoever the customer requests has to take a picture with them.
Okay good.
Okay. Then.
Wang Ja Rim and Lee Kyeong Woo will both advertise and take pics with the customers.
Hey hey hey hey hey! This is total slave treatment.
It's okay. Fighting.
- Fighting!
- Yaaay!!
Let's choose something from the ideas Teach Dokgo suggested. A reading game classroom,
a math quiz classroom, or a smoking prevention activity.
- Gosh, that went to far.
- I really hate it.
What about an atomic and chemical attack experience game? I have enough gas ready.
- Gosh, stop that.
- Someone stop him.
Then a massage parlor? The Thai way.
Sawasdee khap, khop khun khap.
(T/N: "Hello" and "Thank you" in Thai.)
Hey stop him right there.
Ah, let him be. Listening to him, it's better than the ones recommended.
- Is there anything fun?
- Hey Gong Joo Yeong. Don't you have any ideas?
Right! What happened to you?
Ja Rim isn't even here.
You guys do it yourself.
Then we should just do what Dok Teach tells us to do.
There's the smoking prevention awareness I mentioned,  the scientific experiments,
- and the business management board game...
- Gosh, that's no fun.
Damn.  Why am I not in the same class as Ja Rim?
Oh? Then your class is also doing a cafe?
Nope. At first, it was supposed to be a cafe but it changed to a no-alcohol cocktail bar.
Your class is doing a cafe?
The homeroom teacher barely gave us permission. You should come by!
I think I'll be busy serving for our class.
Then I'll come over.
As you wish. I am going to sleep now.
Okay. Sleep well and let's meet in our dreams.
Do dreams go according to your wish? Just sleep.
Dream of Ja Rim. Ja Rim should appear in my dreams.
Love Revolution: Festival
Episode 16. #TheStar #OfTheFestival #IsMe #It'sMe
princess_0 @bang_H: Yup today's wallflower is you
The day of the festival.
The 8th Yisam Art Festival
Yisam Information High
DIY Perfume
Come to the corridor of class 7
- Don't eat it!
- I didn't eat any!
- Oh, 5,000 won (≈ $4).
- No, it's 10,000 for you (≈$9).
"You just have to do it." "Patience is bitter but its fruits are sweet."
Gosh, your classroom is quite a sight to see.
What the hell is your class's concept that you look like this?
Headband— Ugh.
It's a cocktail bar where we take pictures.
I have to take pics like this with the customers.
One minute. Everyone in your class is like this?
- Yeah.
- Every single one?
Yeah.
What the hell. Where is Ja Rim?
Inside.
Where is Ja Rim?
There.
Heart attack.
Hey, what made you collapse?
Ja Rim, you are so pretty. Let's not take this off forever.
Are you out of your mind? I am being forced to do this.
Ja Rim Ja Rim. Pic pic pic.
- Look here.
- Don't do this!
- There. One, two, three.
- If you give 500 won,
we take professional quality pictures for you in the photo zone over there.
Okay.
Hey here's  ₩5000. Take 10 pics of us for me.
Customer, let me escort you this way.
Ja Rim, I paid for it so take pics with me.
Really!
Just click some, he even paid money. Don't think that it's Gong Joo Young.
With this amount, he's a big investor for us.
Think of it as "for our class." There!
A bit affectionately.
Smile a bit. Yeah yeah yeah, you look really sh*tt—
No no no, you look very good. I'll take it now. One, two, three.
Okay. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
- It's coming out well right?
- Yeah it's coming out very well.
- Hey should we also go and ask to click pics?
- Please click some pics for us also.
Okay. Give me your phone, your phone.
Hey, actually,
I'll take ten more pics after these ten. Take mine first!
Ah, wait a bit. I'm sorry but wait a few more minutes.
- I'll take some more. One, two, three.
- Then it's me first.
Nice nice nice.
Ah, she's freaking pretty.
Is she human?
It's running smoothly.
It's running very smoothly, without their homeroom teacher even having to lift a finger.
Then I guess you have lifted all ten fingers, Teacher Dok. Which results in this.
But why are you laughing?
My students show unity, it's quite nice to see.
You must be happy they are so calm and quiet.
- Let me go, let me go!
- Stop it, come on.
Obstruction of business? What the hell are you talking about?
You've got over 10,000 won with just what I spent in your class. Don't talk nonsense— Oh!
Good morning.
Sure.
Your class is increasing our classroom's performance. I'm so thankful.
Okay, done.
Have a cocktail before you leave. The people who had nail art have a 10% discount.
- Hello.
- We got a discount coupon.
Ah, yes thank you. Please go that way and wait for a bit.
- You have to pay in advance.
- Here are your drinks.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you for coming. Welcome.
It looks so good!
Please take a good picture.
Hyung Byeong Hoon!
Oh Namgoong. Did you come to have fun?
Yeah, Noona Ah Ram told me about this. But, where is Noona's class?
I know, I know. Sit here for now.
- Sit down. Remove your shoes.
- Why? What are you doing?
When you do sports, meditation is a must.
Follow my lead. I'll teach you how to breathe with your brain.
Ah Hyung, I am fine. I'll just go to Noona's class.
You do sports! So you have to clear your mind.
Get in position. Breathe in.
Breathe out while rotating your head.
Breathe in.
Breathe out rotating your head to the right side.
Breathe out and rotate to the left again.
I thought I was going to die. It's some brain respiration but you have to rotate your head so much.
Why didn't you just die? What are you going to drink?
Don't you have Hawaiian punch?
If you don't want to get hit by a Korean punch then choose from the menu.
I don't know anyway. Just give me anything.
- Here you go.
- And by the way,
can you take a pic with me?
Aigoo, come this way. One pic is  ₩500.
- Take one with me too.
- I'll take it now.
- One, two, three.
Damn.  How many does she have to click?
Will you really take pics with us if we come?
- Yeah yeah.
- Really?
- Ah but it's expensive!
What's wrong with him?
I'll take it. One, two, three.
- Should we do one more each?
- Should we?
Not even an ant is coming to our class.
Did you see Dokgo Moon's face earlier? He looked so sour.
Hey, hey. Shouldn't we do something?
I don't care.
Oh hey, by the way, lend me some money.
I have to click pics with Ja Rim, but I already ran out of money.
Do you think you can use money to handle the problem until the end of the festival?
It'd be easier to stop the guys from going there.
If we steal some male customers from class 3,
then there will be fewer guys sucking up to Ja Rim.
Anything we can use here?
Hey hey hey. I got a pretty nice idea. Come here.
Hey! There's a super fun event in class 2 right now, come quickly.
- Ah come quickly!
- What is it?
- Come and see.
- Let's go see!
What is it?
- Where are you going?
- To the restroom.
I have a stomachache.
'Human sandbag'
We take your hits. 500 won for 1 minute.
A boyfriend who cheated
Ah, wait a second, wait.
Hey. We change places every 30 minutes. No running away.
I got it. How many times will you tell us?
But isn't this idea too old-fashioned?
Look. I think all of class 3's customers are here now.
Don't you know "oldies but goodies"?
But why am I "a boyfriend who cheated"?
There is nothing better than this to attract a woman's fist.
Hey! I can get hit by a man too. Are you looking down on me?
Then do you want to change with me?
Ah you scared me. What is this? Take it away.
I will let you hit me.
Take this, take it!
- A bit more.
- You've gone over one minute!
- Okay, get this!
I will let you hit me
Human sandbag
Wow! Gosh.
Hey. Doesn't it hurt?
Hey. It actually doesn't hurt a bit, but I have to act like it hurts so that customers come.
He says so. I think you can hit him as much as you want.
Hey, if you bring in a real fighter...
then what do I do?
Yes yes yes. One minute is over.
Okay, next customer.
Ja Rim this is only a concept. It's not true.
Boyfriend who cheated
What are you doing? You don't have anything better to do than to get hit for money?
Ay customer, if you're going to hit him then you must pay first.
- Why are you asking for money?
- We should collect what has to be collected.
Hey, I am reserving him for 20 minutes.
Y-You aren't hitting me?
No way. Is it because you don't like to see me getting hit?
Think as you wish.
- Thank you.
- Don't.
The others are all here.
Then let's go somewhere else. Let's go see what the other classrooms are doing.
- Hey, where are you going?
- Hey, Ja Rim gave  ₩10,000.
Awesome.
I have been reserved for 20 minutes. Help me get this off.
Hey! Next person.
- Ah quickly.
- You do it quickly.
Min ji.
Oh hi. Did you come to hang out?
Yes, because we have some time and I heard that your cocktails are tasty.
Ah, you just have to order here and get it from Ah Ram.
Hey, where is the handsome guy from your class? Was his name Lee Kyeong Woo?
- Come on.
- Why?
Why him?
- Ah to click a pic with him?
- No it's fine if he's not there.
- Ah Ram. An apple mojito for me.
- Okay.
Hey. I think it is him. What are you going to do?
Stop it. Wait.
- Hey.
- Yeah?
She wants to click a pic with you.
- It's mandatory to buy a drink.
- Here.
Oh Ye Seul is here. Hi!
Ja Rim hi.
What? You guys know each other?
We went to the same middle school.
- I'll clean this up for you.
- Hey, aren't you leaving now?
What? I feel like not even five minutes have passed.
I already ordered a drink. Take a boyfriend-like picture, please.
Okay.
Enjoy!
One, two, three.
Your cocktails are really tasty.
Ah Ram makes them well.
Min Ji, are you close with Lee Kyeong Woo?
- Just a bit I guess.
- He doesn't have a girlfriend, right?
Can you introduce me to him?
- Him?
- Yeah. By any chance does he have a girlfriend?
He probably doesn't. But he's not that good.
Why? He seemed a good guy.
Right, he hangs out with Gong Joo Yeong so he won't be a bully.
I'm not sure, I don't really know.
For now, just ask him. I'll go now.
Okay.
- Don't set them up.
- Huh?
- Lee Kyeong Woo, don't set him up.
- Why?
You like Lee Kyeong Woo, right?
What? What the hell are you saying? Why would I? You crazy?
Really? If not, then fine.
No! What is there to like about that snotty teen idiot?
The girl who likes him is the weird one.
Hey, if it's not so, it's not so.
Overreacting much?
- What is it?
- You
want to go on a blind date?
- Suddenly?
- I don't.
- Hear the whole thing before you answer.
It's the girl from before, the one who took a pic with you.
Were there 1 or 2 people that took pics with me? I don't want to.
Just take a look at her before saying this.
It's her.
Ye Seul
Ah her?
Not interested. Work hard.
Hey, this is considered pretty!
Forget it, tell her I have a girlfriend. I'm off.
He doesn't even have a girlfriend, so why?
Hey, I couldn't try it. Can I try now for ₩500?
No way! After Oh Ah Ram hit me I got PTSD.
(Post Traumatic Stress Disorder)
Hey Wang Ja, what was that earlier? Paying ₩10,000 and taking Gong Joo away?
Don't tell me you didn't want your boyfriend getting hit?
Yeah, that's right. It was to save me.
She is my prince. My prince, when will you go on a date with your princess?
Do you want to get hit now for the ₩10,000 that I paid?
If you act cute again while singing, you're dead.
It also makes me cringe when you force your voice to be lower when singing, you know.
- Gosh, seriously.
- Dammit.
What is that?
- Isn't that Lee Kyeong Woo?
- What?
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
♫ Whenever I felt sad sending you back home ♫
Love Revolution.
- He didn't come today either.
- Ah this bastard, suddenly skipping for two days.
Seeing that Lee Kyeong Woo's hand is hurt, he surely fought someone.
- Cho Seung Min?
- Hi. You're Lee Kaeng's girlfriend right?
- She's not my girlfriend.
- Your eye.
- You said that you didn't get hit by those hyungs.
- F*ck.
I think he is a bit sensitive about his bangs.
It's like trying to solve a difficult puzzle.
Lee Kyeong Woo was probably the happiest at that time. He really liked Nam Yu Ri.
Will you come to me if I seduce you?
I am not sure. Seeing what you do.
Then why did they breakup?
Are you asking because you don't know?
♫  After breaking up with me ♫