I'm going to take it now!
Is your foot okay?
Didn't you see me dancing yesterday?
That's why I'm asking if it got worse.
You worry over nothing.
Hey, let me see.
- It's her.
- Why? Who is she?
- The ascetic hug yesterday, remember? So cringey.
- Seriously Cringe!
You know, that boy who sang.
He's been constantly hitting on her since the beginning of school.
Really?
But they're still not dating?
Look at these ascetics! Crazy.
Ja Rim!
Ja Rim! What's wrong?
I'm just tired.
Hey! Yang Min Ji! Picture!
Ja Rim, drink this on your way back.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Love Revolution Episode 5: Don't pity me.
#Dark past #In My Heart #Storage
glasses @princess_0: Get up, soldier.
You know, Ja Rim has been really cold to me since the talent show.
Hi, Ja Rim.
Hi!
Do you think I made a mistake at the retreat?
I don't think she's changed that much. She's always been cold.
- I think she changed about 360 degrees.
- Right?
That means that she's the exact same, dummy.
Her temperature is different. It's gone down by at least two degrees.
Then isn't it pretty much the same?
Two degrees means ice cold.
Right now, I feel like I'm standing on thin ice.
No, I doubt it.
I watched Wang Ja Rim when you were singing.
I could just feel it right then and there, that it's over.
I thought that you guys would definitely date if you would just confess.
But I can't really trust you, considering that you've been single your entire life.
Hey, before I'm a single man, I'm a person.
I have the basic ability to read the room.
Your song wasn't bad.
It seemed okay.
So when are you guys going to date?
What do you mean date?
With the whole singing thing, the kids in the other classes think that you guys are already dating.
If you're being honest with yourself, you liked his song, right?
That's bullsh*t.
No, it showed all over your face.
Do you want me to play the piano with your face?
- The atmosphere was pretty good if I'm being honest.
- Didn't that recreation teacher ruin everything?
I know, right?  If it just weren't for the recreation teacher.
That guy overreacted and so Ja Rim felt super uncomfortable.
You played a part in it too.
What is that? Idiot.
That was just because I thought I needed to do something to not let her down.
I thought it was alright. They were manner hands.
Wouldn't it only be considered manners to not raise your arm in the first place?
Hey, hey! Girls love this sort of detail.
Look.
Where are you going?
Are you crazy?
What do you think you're doing?
Did she dislike it that much?
No, no, no. That's just because it's Kim Byeong Hoon.
Stop pretending like you don't like him. You say that, but you're really nice to him.
I saw it all.
- What did you see?
- You took off a grain of rice that was on him.
- What?
- Woah.
Then you totally gave him a sign.
No, it's not. I just took it off because it was messy.
- Hey. You could've told him to take it off himself.
- Yeah.
Anyway, you don't know what Yang Ja Rim really thinks, so stop it now.
Just wait and keep your eyes open.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
My hand moved by itself because that rice grain was bothering me.
It's Ja Rim's voice.
At that rate, you would date because you feel frustrated.
Hey, technically speaking, you never cut him off totally and said you disliked him.
Oh, that's right.
Why did you do that? Why can't you cut Gong Joo Yeong out?
I mean...
It's just because I pity him.
Hey, what are you doing, Gong Joo Yeong?
Oh, wow. You're r-really good at playing the piano.
On this graph, the way you can tell the distance between these x-values is...
Yeah, everything finally makes sense now.
When we first met
and when it rained.
When she took the rice off my face, it was all my misunderstanding.
- ... Joo Yeong.
To Ja Rim, I'm just a pitiful guy.
- Gong Joo Yeong!
- Yes.
What? Yes?
I called your name three times. Pay attention, will you?
Go stand outside.
You feel pity for me too, right?
You could've told me to go down on a plank and raise one leg,
but you've only told me to go stand outside.
With the quadratic function and quadratic equation,
you can find the parabola of the water flow springing out of the fountain...
Won't you make a proper parabola with your leg?
I'm so hungry.
Are you down to have tteokbokki on our way back?
Don't you want to wear short clothes during the summer?
I don't even have money.
You can eat with the money not spent on clothes.
You're a genius.
Gong Joo Yeong!
Hi.
What's wrong with him? Something's off.
He's never the type to do that. Normally he comes running like, "Ja Rim, Ja Rim," like a puppy.
It's nice that he's not bothering me.
That means he heard.
- What?
- When she said she felt bad for him.
Oh, that's right. Yep, that's it.
Are you just going to leave him like that? I think he's upset.
Welcome.
Gong Joo Yeong.
Hey. Stop there.
What now?
Did you hear what I said in the music room?
I don't know what you're talking about.
So you heard.
Yes, yes I did! I'm sorry! This pitiful bastard even eavesdropped on you.
No. I'm not blaming you—
Stop! Stop pitying me.
What's so funny!
You're a celebrity.
Are you guys practicing asceticism?
Yang Min: Yeah, I also just saw it.
It must have been someone from our school who uploaded it.
Vegeta: Oh my god, without even asking?
Monk Hye Min: Are they crazy?
How could they do that without permission from the people involved?
Ah Ram: Are you just going to let it go?
Immediately tomorrow: go go...
Nuna! There's a guy here.
(T/N: Nuna is used by a male toward an older female)
What does it matter? You also take your shirt off when you're hot.
If you'll keep this up, want me to call you hyeong?
(T/N: Hyeong is used by a male toward an older male)
Instead of wasting time talking nonsense, you'd better hit the sandbag one more time.
The competition is next week.
A regional competition is a piece of cake.  I'm damn strong.
Buzz off while I'm saying it nicely. Clear off.
Ah Ram: We have to find who it is and ask them to take it down.
I'll try to find out from the students in other classes.
Yang Min: I'll also ask Jin Hui and Hye Eun.
Thanks.
Gong Joo Yeong, right?
Yes... Who are you?
You're a good singer. I saw it on YouTube.
- Sorry?
- Lend me your cell phone.
Why?
I lost mine, so I want to call me. Lend it to me for a minute.
Pick up the phone when you get a call.
Nuna Jang Hae Ri.
Good morning!
You say hello because I look pitiful, right?
What are you talking about?
Forget it.
Madam, do you give me a lot of food because I look pitiful?
Here. Thanks, I used it well.
Are you giving me your notes out of pity?
What are you spouting? I'm giving them to you because they're yours.
Then why are you looking at me pitifully?
Stop it! You're going to become neurotic!
Gong Joo Yeong, You need to see this.
Are you guys practicing asceticism?
Heol.
What's this?  Is he making money from filming others?
Apparently, it's some jerk from class 6.
Wang Ja Rim just went to argue with him but aren't you going?
It's also your business.
What's the use of someone pitiful like me going?
This guy has lost all his flavor. Are you really the same guy who went AWOL for Wang Ja Rim?
No matter what I do, I'm just a pitiful guy to her.
- I'm pitiful—
- Ah you darned pain!
Why are you spouting all this self-pitying crap since before?
I know! Yeah!
He's completely crazy.
You guys think I'm pitiful, so that's why you guys are leaving without me, right?
What the f*ck do you mean, delete it?
It's up to me because I filmed it.
The one on the video said she doesn't like it.  Don't you know she has portrait rights?
You're nuts. Do you think you're a celebrity or something?
Everyone has portrait rights.
If you don't delete it, I'll have no choice but to report it to Google, so they do it.
I uploaded it on YouTube. Why would you report it to Google?
YouTube is a part of Google, idiot.
Hey.
What? What are you going to do?
Hey, talk to me.
If you don't take it down, we can even ask for your account to be deleted after we report it.
We can stop you from doing YouTube.
F*ck! Then report it!
It's not even a big deal, and you're making one hell of a fuss!
Don't be so ridiculous after you did that to get attention!
Hey, you ba—
Let's just go.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
What's with you?
- Are you that ascetic hug?
- Yes.
You uploaded the video, didn't you? Hurry and take it down.
How dare you make money off of other people's concerns?
Hey. Calm down. All right! I got it!
Are you agreeing because you pity me too?
What are you talking about?
This is so good!
Time to Get That Super Tasty Kimbap
Don't be so ridiculous after you did that to get attention!
Try it. Come on, try it!
- It's delicious though.
- Oh?
What's this? The video got taken down.
Really?
I guess he got scared.
Look. It has been taken down.
My school's attention seekers who transformed the retreat into an entertainment show. ROFL.
It's gone.
Saturday - 1:02 p.m.
Lee Kaeng
Ahn Saeng Gyeong Min 2 Missed Calls/ Kim Baeng  6 Missed calls/ Lee Kaeng 12 missed calls
What's up?
- Are you at home right now?
- Yeah, why?
Then, perhaps, could you go to Gong Joo Yeong's place and check if he's okay?
Why should I?
You live closest to him. He hasn't been picking up his phone since this morning.
He's been acting a bit strange these days.
He's probably doing fine.
All you have to do is go and ring the doorbell.
I don't want to. It's even more weird if I go.
So heartless. All right.
Hey, Gong Joo Yeong!
Pitiful.
I ended up showing my most pitiful side.
I don't want to receive any more pity.
Why the hell are you running away?
Why? Why did you follow me? You should just leave the pitiful one alone.
You should just let a guy like me live a quiet life.
Shut up! You're not pitiful. You're pissing me off, so stop crying!
I said you're not pitiful at all!
I'm not buying it for you because I'm pitying you.
It's in return for getting me the cleansing foam when we went on the retreat.
Seriously. I'm not pitying you, so eat!
Listen to me while you eat.
Listen to me while you eat, I said.
What was it...
When I said I pity you, I didn't mean it like that.
If my words offended you,
I'm so...
Never mind. I didn't say it with that intention, so just forget it.
I didn't sing the song to make you uncomfortable either.
I know.
You were good, actually.
Really? What is it, what am I good at?
I don't know. You're so dirty.
I'm your pitiful puppy. Woof! Woof!
Cut the crap and just eat.
Okay.
What should we do now?
We have to report it.
Do we call? Or do we send it in by email?
But do we have to report it in English?
- I can't say.
-  Well, I'll go settle the matter.
Never mind. I don't want to make a big thing of it.
And as an athlete, you shouldn't be fighting.
♫ On this night when the darkness thickens ♫
Love Revoluion - Preview
♫ I look at my phone sleeping quietly ♫
Ja Rim is a tsundere, cold on the outside but sweet inside. The truth is that I'm actually on her mind.
What is that nonsense?
Joo Yeong! Who is that girl?
What business is ...
Even if it's not our business, it's Ja Rim's.
No. I don't really care.
- Ja Rim?
- What is it you wanted to say?
Look at her. She's so disrespectful.
It's Rose Day this Saturday. There's no way Gong Joo Yeong is going to let it pass by...
Accept this. Let's date.
I'll tell you by text.