Jumping jacks, ten times!
Do not count the last number out loud. Start!
One.
Two.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
- What the...?
- Aren't you going to focus?
Twenty jumps this time. Same thing, do not say the last number out loud!
Start!
One.
Two.
Eighteen.
Nineteen.
-  Twenty!
- Gosh! Who is it?!
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Hey, Kim Byeong Hoon, it's you isn't it? You jerk!
No, it's not me! Everyone is being tricked!
Let's go for lunch, come on. Stop it, guys.
Who is making noise? Do you still have strength left?
This time, it's a hundred jumps!
- How many?
- Hundred.
One-hundred jumping jacks. Start!
One.
Two.
Three. Four.
What's Gong Joo, that jerk, doing?
Six.
My brain is secreting to much endorphin.
Love Revolution Episode 4: Go Back Retreat
#For_me_too # Soon #Lovestagram
bang_H @princess_0: Aren't you going to practice?
You idiot, you can't even do that?
- It really wasn't me!
- You were the furthest one in the back! Who else would it be?
I'm telling you it was your homeroom teacher!
It sounded just like your voice.
Hey, you guys have known me for three years and you don't even recognize my voice?
Of course I do! Your voice sounds super old. Like a grandpa.
That's because my voice broke early with puberty.
Hey, Gong Joo.
There is a grain of cooked rice.
Who do you think you are to get rid of my grain of cooked rice?
What's this, why the sudden lurch?
What's the matter?
- What the heck is he doing?
- He's lost his marbles, that's all.
Ready?
- Ah Rong, new attempt!
- Ooh, will she really make it?
Oh Ah Ram! Oh Ah Ram!
Ja Rim!
- What is it?
- Ja Rim.
Go while I'm talking nicely.
Master, what might this be?
That grain of rice on his cheeks, the desperate look,
and Ja Rim's disgusted expression. If we put all that together...
- I think he's asking her to take off that rice for him.
- No, no.
It's degeneration due to lack of affection. Friends, prepare for suction.
Ja Rim, just this once please.
Take care of it.
Wow, that's level up!
- It would have been better if Ja Rim did it.
- If I did, I probably would've kicked your face.
It's fine. Since if I get kicked by you, it's a physical exchange of affection.
If getting kicked is physical affection, then boxing matches must be blind dates?
- Then UFC must be s—
- Socks, like these ones.
- You crazy girls!
- Let's stop here.
- Anyway, he's nothing ordinary.
- I also want a guy to obsess over me.
- I hate this. Come here.
Hey, you should go now. Free time is almost over.
Yang Min Ji, good luck!
Here I go.
Hey! Don't do that.
Is that a melodrama, or thriller?
It's definitely not a melodrama.
Hey.
It's not as feasible as I thought. I'm actually the only one who didn't fall in the water.
Gosh. Anyway, just don't clown around and get hurt for nothing. Okay?
If you guys get hurt, my confession is doomed. Got it?
- Hey.
- Hey, hey.
- Are you okay?
- Hey, hey!
Hey! It really hurts. It really hurts.
- I'm not the one who did this.
- Hey, that was totally attempted murder there.
What the heck.
Oh? What's wrong with him?
What is this? Lee Kaeng, did you get hurt?
- He was messing with Ah Ram and she retaliated.
- Thanks to her, I'm off the boot camp training so it's nice.
I asked you not to get hurt!
Thank you for your warm-hearted words of worry, you jerk. Dammit.
Doest it hurt a lot?
♫  Careless careless. Shoot anonymous anonymous ♫
♫  Heartless mindless. No one who care about me.  ♫
♫ In a state of loss  ♫
How is it? Don't you think I would look like the visual of the group if I danced with this?
So much bluffing. It's fine, forget it. I'm fine, so don't push yourself.
For the dance... we'll do what we can.
- How?
- We should do it just the two of us, I guess.
But Kyeong Woo's part will be empty. And there are movements we put together for three.
We don't have choice then. I'll have to take action.
- If Gong Joo takes my part—
- No, he can't.
He has the part just before, the moves will clash.
Don't ignore me! I watched you practice all the time.
I even completely memorized all the moves.
The longer you think about it, the more I get hurt.
- Let's try to do it for now.
- Great.
Hurry up. You in the center, you on the right.
I didn't even stick it in yet.
- You're boring a hole in my scalp!
- Bear it, bear it. Done.
One more.
Hey Ja Rim, your cleanser is nice. It's light like a lotion and has a nice scent.
It's nice, right? I want to change to that one too.
Done! All done, Ah Rong.
(T/N: Ah Rong is Ah Ram's nickname)
- Give me that.
- What is it?
- Hey, this side is a bit higher.
N-No! Look. Like this.
No! Hey, look at this objectively. How is it?
- It's cute. It suits you well.
- You're really good at tying hair into buns.
- Okay, out now, Ah Rong.
- Okay.
Okay, next! Ja Rim. You need to look good in front of your boyfriend.
Are you nuts? Who's whose boyfriend? I'm fine, so do it for Jin Hui.
Okay, come here.
- What do you want?
- Buns too.
The talent show will start soon. All students are to go to the assembly hall.
Hey. Hey, are you a motorcycle?
Let go! Do you want to get hit by a motorcycle? I should just stab you with this.
- Hey, you almost got stabbed for real.
- Wow, I almost died.
By the way, Gong Joo Yong prepared something, right? I caught a glimpse of him earlier, and he was all dressed up.
Hey. You absolutely can't tell Wang Ja, okay?
Gong Joo worked super hard to surprise her.
Of course, I won't! But Gong Joo Yeong is really unlucky.
Class 4 is before them, but there's one guy in that class who used to be an idol trainee.
Even if they do quite well, they'll get crushed.
- Hey, hey, help me.
- Don't wanna.
Pooling Sweat Together Makes Us One
Yisam Information High School Student Retreat
♫ So down ♫
♫ I see you, I try to approach but stop in my tracks at another sun  ♫
♫ The glow of the sunset spreads  ♫
♫ And covers my heart, babe ♫
♫ I'm down, I'm down for your love ♫
♫ I pray one day I'll show myself in front of you, show ya ♫
♫  I envy the one who owns your smile ♫
♫ Now that I see you happy it's already game's over lady ♫
♫ I'm down, I'm down for your love ♫
Why are they so good? Making me nervous.
Hey, Ahn Gaeng. Don't be nervous. You're stressing me even more.
I never realized I have stage fright.
People need to go through various experiences.
- I don't think I can do this.
- You scared me. What's going on with you?
Drink this and relax.
You drink it, Gong Joo.
Why am I trembling like this?
Don't be nervous. I'll do it.
What about your foot?
- It'll be fine for two minutes.
- Are you really okay?
Worry about yourself. Since you decided to do it, push through to the end.
I won't make you say it was ruined because of a mistake.
Then... I'll leave it to you.
Wow, it's crazy! The crowd is on fire!
It was amazing. Come on, give a big round of applause for class 4.
It's really amazing. What's this? I thought you were Yisam Information High School.
But you're actually Yisam Arts High School!
Okay, very good. I'm really looking forward to the next contestants. The next contestant is...
Class 2! Come up the stage!
Hey, your boyfriend must be performing something!
Aren't you going to film your boyfriend? Should I do it for you?
I'm telling you he's not!
- Hey, Lee Kyeong Woo! Isn't that Lee Kyeong Woo?
- He's there, over there.
- Hey!
- Lee Kyeong Woo!
Is his foot alright?
Class 2! Class 2! Class2!
♫ Careless careless Shoot anonymous anonymous ♫
♫ Heartless mindless No one who care about me ♫
♫ In a state of loss, it's like I am looking away ♫
♫ I can only hold it in ♫
♫ Though I shut my eyes ♫
♫  Your Highness, answer me now  ♫
♫ Tell me why people have changed  ♫
♫ Tell me if there really ever existed a time that was beautiful  ♫
♫ Now they even forgot how to love  ♫
♫ And lost their thoughtfulness as well  ♫
♫ Too busy living with their backs turned to each other  ♫
♫ The mask of anonymity hides a jealousy filled with murderous intent  ♫
♫ Even with the end in sight, they seem hungry ♫
♫ We are satisfied now ♫
♫ Will we never face each other again?  ♫
♫ Will we never communicate?  ♫
♫ Won't we love? ♫
♫ The painful reality ♫
♫ Makes me shed tears once more ♫
♫ We are able to change it, we can just change it.   ♫
♫ Say so, Your Highness. Your Highness.  ♫
What's happening?
What's going on? Darn it.
Let's just go.
Gong Joo what are you doing? Let's go down.
What the hell is happening?
They must be planning something.
♫ I want to get that star and place it in your two hands as a gift. ♫
♫ I want to gather everything I have and give it to you ♫
♫ Sometimes I cry, afraid I'll lose you ♫
♫ Sometimes I feel you sleeping in my arms ♫
♫  I promise you on the day of the first snow ♫
♫ I promise with you.  Together with you ♫
♫ as we stroll through the day hand in hand  I will shout ♫
♫ "I love you." I hope those two hands holding each other ♫
♫ won't ever know of the passing of time. ♫
What the? He was hella nervous, but he's good.
♫ I want to keep all your warmth in there ♫
♫ That's how I feel, for a long time ♫
♫ Sometimes I cry, afraid you will forget me ♫
♫ Sometimes I feel you gently closing your eyes. ♫
♫  I promise you  on the day of the first snow♫
♫  I promise you.  Together with you♫
♫ as we stroll through the day hand in hand  I will shout ♫
♫  "I love you." I hope those two hands holding each other won't ever know of the passing of time. ♫
I'll give five hundred points to the one who gives the loudest applause!
Class two! Class two!
Okay, class one. I'll remember you.
Wow really, isn't this school's level far too high?
- He did really well, didn't he?
- Yes!
Okay, great. You've done well. You can step off the stage now.
That's what you thought I'd say, right?
If I just let him go down, I can just quit my job as the recreation instructor, no?
Yes!
Okay, then. The student who thinks they are the one
he sang this song for, please hurry up to the stage.
Go up! Go up!
No matter what, I think it was for me!
I knew he would get hit, I knew it.
Okay, the girl from class three who wears red!
If you come up to the stage now, I'll give you a thousand points.
If you don't come, you'll get minus thousand points!
- Hey Wang Ja Rim, go up. Go.
- Hurry up and go.
- Hey, go up.
- Hurry.
The points are meaningless anyway.
Come on, go up.
Hey, go up.
Here. Go.
- Good!
- Go, go!
- Okay, stand on this side.
- You look good together!
Can you each tell me your names?
I'm Gong Joo Yeong.
Gong Joo Yeong. You have a pretty name.
And you, what's your name?
She's Wang Ja Rim.
You're Wang Ja and Gong Joo?
(T/N: homonyms for "prince" and "princess")
Wait, I got goosebumps right now. You didn't set this up, did you?
No!
So they're a match made in heaven!
Alright, then. How long have you been together with your boyfriend?
He's not my boyfriend.
He's not your boyfriend? What's this, what's your relationship?
Give me the mic, and do this.
Okay, today is their first day of dating!
Alright then, as a celebration of you becoming a couple,
should we have a duet?
Can't you stop?
Kiss!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
No, no! They can't kiss! Their homeroom teacher is here at the back.
He's staring directly at them, they can't kiss.
What? I got it. Okay then, since it's their first day of dating,
they can hug. If you hug each other, you can get off the stage.
Hug! Hug! Hug! Hug!
Let's not drag this out! It's boring!
Hey, shut up.
- But they're no fun.
- Won't you shut the hell up?
Shut it!
Yisam Information High School Student Retreat
Hey, don't do it.
Hey.
- What's that?
- Is that a hug?
- What are they doing?
- No fun.
Are you guys practicing asceticism?
Now that I'm in here,
I feel like I'm being protected.
His arms really give a sense of security.
Okay, give him another round of applause!
Alright, next contestant is class five! Class five, come up the stage!
♫ Everyone looks happy  ♫
♫  and everyone is busy with their lives  ♫
♫ So why did time stop only for me?  ♫
Love Revolution
It's her, the ascetic hug. Hella cringe-worthy.
Cringe!
Have you gone nuts?
Ja Rim is really cold to me since the talent show.
So when are you two going to date?
Stop the nonsense, what date?
- You're Gong Joo Yeong, aren't you?
- Who...?
- That means it was uploaded by someone from our school.
- Unbelievable. Are they nuts?
- Are we going to stay put? Let's go tomorrow right away.
- Fuck it, delete what?!
- Do you think you're some bloody celebrity?
- Hey.
Wang Ja Rim did just go to argue about it, but it's also your business you know. Aren't you going?
What do you want?
♫ I’m still the same. What am I expecting? ♫