Okay, okay!
Okay! Okay!
I got it, I got it!
What? What?
- Oh, sh*t.
- Give it back.
Here, here! Give it to me.
Wait, wait!
Ja Rim... We'll reveal it in two week—
What the? She said, "Let's date."
Let's date then.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Your house isn't on fire.
What's on fire... is my heart!
Go away!
Why?
Ja Rim, thank you so much.
I'm sleeping.
Okay, I promise I'll do well!
Good night.
Wang Ja-nim  ("Respected prince")
Wang Darling.
(T/N: Play on words with the name "Wang Ja Rim".  Ja Gi = Darling)
Wang Darling
I'm dating now.
Really? First of all, congratulations!
Don't congratulate me.
Who knows when we'll break up.
Gee, why are you thinking like that?
Don't tell me you're dating him because you felt forced?
I don't know.
Things have blown up.
Why? Gong Joo Yeong is a pretty nice guy.
Other than the fact that he overreacts.
We'll see.
Anyway, since you've decided to date, try to get along well.
I'm not sure.
My heart is fluttering, I can't sleep!
Love Revolution:   Apparently, your grades drop if you date
Episode 7 #Dream #Come_True #☆
glasses @princess_0: Then I'd be the top student.
Darling...
Don't call me like that.
Can... I hold your hand?
You may not.
Then...
I'll put my arm around your shoulder.
Hey.
I'll go to school by myself starting tomorrow.
We have exams next week. Are you getting along with your studies?
I want to get along with them, but my studies hate me.
Hey, should I teach you?
You always got hit because of your report cards in middle school. Where is that confidence coming from?
I was still building up my energy back then!
Don't you know what a ki blast is?
I'll show you how I crush the whole school in one blow.
What ki blast takes a year to build up?
But where is that punk, Gong Joo Yeong?
Where else could he be?
Is this an exhibition or something? He keeps coming to admire her at every break time.
I think we can even start accepting admission fees.
I knew this would happen.
You guys look good together!
Hey. Stop staring at me.
The more I look at you, the more I want to keep looking.
Can I hold your hand?
No.
We're dating, but I can't even hold your hand?
Is there a rule that you have to hold hands when you're dating?
That's true. Then, should we hold hands when we go on a date?
Ta-da!
This is our dating schedule.
For now, let's have six dates a week. Four hours on weekdays and eight hours on weekends.
In total—
Are you crazy? Who goes on dates every day?
Don't you know we have exams next week?
Right.
Then, we'll go on dates after the exams.
We'll see.
I thought things would be different now that we're dating.
From the look of things, it's more like you got scammed rather than you're dating.
Don't make jokes. I'm being serious.
But to put it bluntly, it was hilarious. Wang Ja Rim is pretty impressive.
She's consistent.
If that's how it's going to be, why did she say yes?
No, it's just because it's still a bit awkward.
If we spend a little more time together...
Anything, then?
Ja Rim!
We're going to the library to study.
What? Us?
Yeah. We said so earlier.
Studying happens at the library, of course.
Don't just play around there.
Then, if I get an average over 60 this time, we get to hold hands, okay?
Why are you setting the conditions yourself? Plus, what's so impressive about 60?
How bad are your grades exactly?
That's why I'm going to the library!
If I go to the library, I'll be able to concentrate,
and there are a lot of books there.
Ja Rim, let's go study at the library too.
Why? I thought we're going to your house to study.
If we go to my house, we might just end up watching TV.
Right?
Yeah. Let's go to the library.
♫ Friend, what are you doing? I’m curious. What do you like? I’m curious  ♫
♫ I wonder about every single thing about you ♫
♫ May I ask? May I approach you? ♫
♫ I keep on getting excited ♫
♫ All day long, seeing you and your smile puts me on a roller coaster ♫
♫ My mood goes up then down, on a roller-coaster ♫
Hey, aren't you going to study?
Stop staring me and look at your textbook.
I am studying.
Studying you.
The Law of Ja Rim.
Don't go too far.
Hey, where did all the other kids go?
♫ As you wish, as you wish, la ♫
Do we have to go this far for them?
I thought you were pushing them together too?
If they decided to date, it's done. What more is there to do?
They need to share the same feelings for it to be done.
Wang Ja doesn't even like him. Why did she agree to date him?
Rather than saying she doesn't like him, it's just complicated.
Does Wang Ja Rim even want a boyfriend?
She seems completely indifferent to dating.
That's not true. She wasn't always like that.
She wanted a boyfriend, too.
Wang Ja wanted a boyfriend?
What? Then why is she acting like this now?
I don't know.
- Ja Rim, Ja Rim, look at this.
- Damn it.
What about it?
I feel like you're even colder to me after we began dating.
I was always like this.
So, you don't like it?
No. I'm going to turn you into a total cutie monster.
That's never going to happen.
Just wait. I'm going to be super good to you.
I'll just make you melt softly.
Do you like me that much?
Yeah. Extremely.
How long do you think that'll last?
Forever.
Don't say that so easily. People change.
Then you can change, too. Into a cutie monster.
I'm an exception.
Then I won't change, either.
I'm not saying this carelessly. I'm going to like you forever.
You laughed. Thanks.
I was scoffing.
That's still laughter.
Can you laugh one more time?
Stop following me. I'm going to go to the bathroom too.
I want to buy a drink, too.
Here. Drink this, and good luck!
I'm already hungry from dancing.
Where were you two?
You said you wanted to study.
We're going to start now.
How was your library date?
Stop it, already. Why are you two like that, too?
I'll deal with him on my own.
Here, drink.
No.
Oh my goodness, Oh Piggy turned down food?
Gong Joo Yeong gave it to you.
If you don't like him, it's not too late to break up with him now.
What are you doing when you agreed to date him?
Hey, Ah Rong.
I don't dislike Gong Joo Yeong.
Then?
Hey, that trash is different from Gong Joo Yeong.
I don't know.
Exam Day
Could I get another answer sheet?
Ja Rim  00:12:55,490
You have ten minutes left.
♪ Ding, dong, daeng, dong ♪
♪ Arrow head ♪
(T/N: Korean "eeny, meeny, miny, moe...")
Ja Rim, let's go on a date since exams are over.
- I already made plans.
- What?
What plans?
We're going to karaoke together.
That sounds fun. I can just go with you guys then!
Why? Someone who doesn't know you is coming too.
Even more reason I should come. You can introduce your boyfriend.
Right?
R-Right.
♪ Even if you wash your eyes and look everywhere ♪
♪ Cool, cool, cool ♪
- Hong! Jin! Hui!
♪ There won't be a girl as cool as me ♪
- Hey.
- Hi.
Come over here.
- Let me see that.
- Here you go.
This is my treat.
Hey, Joo Yeong is a really great guy. You two get married.
Shut up.
This is my friend from middle school, Bae Ji Yeon.
Hi. I go to Yeokdong High School.
- Hi.
I'm Gong Joo Yeong, Ja Rim's boyfriend.
I know. Hey, he's much cuter in person!
- Another one.
- I don't know that one.
- This one then.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♪ My light steps fly up, following the wind ♪
♪ I will gaze at you only Oh ♪
♪ You're the light of my life, you're the one in my life ♪
♪ Even if I lose everything ♪
♪ I won't regret it, for you only ♪
♪ Through my unwavering love ♪
Hey. Hey, hey.
His name is Kyeong Woo, right? How come he's so handsome?
What? You like that type of guy?
He does look good.
But those bangs of his are a bit...
- I know, right?
- Hey.
Should we move it out of the way?
- I'm so curious.
- Let's do it.
You do it.
- Me?
- You do it.
You go and just, like that, casually.
You push back his bangs completely.
♪ Your love ♪
Here.
Ja Rim, I'll choose the next song okay?
'We Fell In Love' - Ga In & Jo Kwon
Ta-da!
What's this? I don't want to.
Why? Let's sing it together.
I told you no.
You still have a lot of time left in this room.
- Where were you?
- In room 7.
- With the guys from class 2.
- Hey!
You can do it, go.
- Don't you have a mic for me?
- Nope.
- Why?
- I don't want to listen to your voice.
Ugh, your breath smells.
So close!
He's like an insurmountable fortress.
I'll go to the bathroom. Think of some ideas.
Okay.
- Hey.
- What?
You don't know I'm being patient with you all this time, do you?
Happy now? F***, you really can't take a hint.
That was so funny!
Something's wrong. Should be a hundred points.
Come here.
- You're embarrassed, aren't you?
- Min Ji!
Seriously.
- Again, again. I'll do another one.
- Hey.
It's weird, the machine is strange.
Hey. I have a super awesome idea to do it in one strike.
Let's stop, it's no fun.
Why?
Just. Let's stop.
If we go down—
Shut up. Shut up!
Hey, let's go to an internet cafe.
- And Joo Yeong?
- Let's go.
Let's just go. Hurry up.
- Hey, let's go to Olive Young. (T/N: Cosmetics chain)
- All of a sudden?
Wait, what about me?
What should we do?
What do you think? I'm going home.
♫ Even if I keep telling myself it’s not real ♫
♫ Every morning when I wake up, I can only think of you ♫
Aren't you going home?
♫ I used to sing sad songs only ♫
Then can we go together?
Don't hold my hand. Walk a bit far from me.
♫ But now there’s something I realized ♫
Okay.
♫ I like your smiling face the most ♫
I told you to walk further from me.
♫ But the picture you posted today, where was it taken? ♫
♫ Why does it make me so anxious when you are somewhere I’m not? ♫
♫ I like you  ♫
♫ I’m being sincere ♫
Love Revolution
Preview
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing? Are you nuts?
I'm still not sure we're actually dating.
Then let's stop.
What a fuss.
It took me so much effort to start dating.
You should make up now. He was wrong.
You weren't waiting for that, were you?
From the start, she dated you in order to dump you.
What do you see in this cow?
You're damn pathetic.
This crazy moron.
Ah, f***.
♫ I’m being sincere ♫