We've got exams next week, so in preparation for that... we should go to the internet cafe, right?
Hey. what about Gong Joo?
I don't know. You guys go, I have to study.
Shit. You don't have money? Let yourself be treated!
By Kyeong Woo.
Crazy fool.
No, I really have to study.
If I don't raise my grades this term, my mom said she will throw away my computer at home.
Idiot, do you believe that?
My mom always says that but she never does it because it would be wasteful.
You don't know my mom.
When my father was crazy into fishing, she said she would throw it  away if he ever went again.
The fishing gear?
She threw Dad in the ocean.
bang_H
Love Revolution
Studying will change your future spouse.
Episode 25
#Byeong Hoon #Ideal Type #Escape From #being Forever Single
glasses @bang_H: You can escape being forever single over my dead body!
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
I'm a Teen, My Hair Has Started to Grow!
Essential Sex Knowledge for Teens
Because This Is my First Time With Sex
Yes.  Are there any books as helpful to life as these ones?
All of this is going to be of crucial help—
I'm sor—
Oh, are you okay?
May I help you?
-  I guess you like this sort of thing.
- What?
Just like this, if I impute the wrong to her,
she will say it's not hers and will run away leaving the books behind.
Now, take off and leave the books behind.
- Yes. I do like them.
- What?
Thank you.
My Hair Has Started to Grow!
I'm doomed. Does she really intend to read them?
Then I can't have them. If I can't have them...
then I'll have to study!
I ...
- I guess you like them?
- What?
Yes.  I do.
One, two.
Go.
One. Two.
One. Two.  Hey, aren't you paying attention?
Go empty your heard.  One hundred burpees.
Yes.
What is it? Did you get scolded?
You're going to the National Sports Festival. How can you compete with such a poor performance?
What's wrong with it?  No matter what, I'm better than you.
That's bragging. We're in different weight classes, so you are naturally stronger.
Even if I were in your weight class, I would be stronger.
Noona. Would you like to see who finishes doing 100 burpees first?
What are we betting?  I won't do it unless there's a bet.
- Buying a meal.
- Deal.
Then we'll have to eat together, you know?
Of course. You have to eat with the one paying.
Okay, start.
One.
You seem to be a high school student. How old are you?
I'm threshold.
You're sure you're not bold?
Then are you: behold! A ray of sunshine?
I'm ask-me-anything-but-my-age old.
The flow of this conversation has gone up threefold.
You're so adorable.
Do you come here often?
Yeah. Nearly every day? I like doing my homework here.
So you're a college student.
I'm in the exam period too, so I think I'll be coming often.
Really? Oh yeah, I just made an eating buddy.
Not just eating buddies.  Let's be Boo-Bud. Book cafe buddies.
Wow, kids these days make shorter versions for anything.
- Shor-ver!
- Shor-ver.
Come on!
Ninety-nine.
- Ninety-nine.
- One hundred.
One hundred. Urgh, I’m so tired.
I lost.
I'll treat you. Let's go.
What? Right now?
It's time to eat.
- But I came dressed like this today.
- Does that matter?
Can we eat tomorrow instead of today? Tomorrow is Saturday.
I have other plans today, actually.
Really?  I'll see you tomorrow then. Decide on the time and text me.
Yes.
I'm so freaking hungry.
Dummy! Why insist on tomorrow? Why must it be on a golden Saturday?
Today would have been fine! What's special about eating with that Noona?
Why did I suddenly tell a lie?
What am I doing now? Let's behave the same as usual.
You called me to study with you, but you're sleeping?
Still,  a finger flick was too mean.
It's to wake you up.
Waking me up with a kiss would wake me up more.
A punch would probably wake you up perfectly.
Even so, I did do a little studying.
If you were to smack me with your lips, I would be blessed by inestimable grace.
What? Why is it so silent?
Why did you come?
Oh! Did I interrupt you? Shall I come again later?
- It's not like—
- It's not like that. Get lost.
I should change my password. So why did you come?
To borrow some clothes.
It's exam time but you're going out?
To study.
Why dress up if you're going to study? Did you get a girl?
That expression is a blatant "yes."
Really? You? You sure it's not your imagination?
No, we aren't dating. I just like her.
So you want to look good in front of her?
I know that feeling very well.
So you came to me because I am a senior in dating?
- Brat.
- Senior?
It's different from kids dating. The girl is an adult.
So you, elder, want to borrow clothes from this kid?
But, do Gong Ju Yeong's clothes even fit you? The height...
Is not important, of course.
- Wang Ja Rim also treats you like a kid.
- That's not true!
Don't worry about pants, just lend me a top. You have some big ones you bought for when you'd grow taller—
Go. Get lost. Get lost! Get lost with all your strength!
Thanks!
That's 100% going to end as an unrequited love.
Why would an adult date him? He is also a kid.
Don't mind that. Let's study.
Darling, shall we also go out to study?
When is she coming?
Hey, kiddo!
- Noona, did you just wake up?
- No. Do I have sleep in my eyes?
No, I mean, why did you come in such comfy clothes?
I'll be going to the gym right after lunch anyway. You won't?
No, I'll go too. I usually wear this style.
What are you saying?! So, what are we going to eat?
- What you want to eat.
- Really? Gosh.
This is the weather for gukbap (rice soup). Let's eat gukbap.
Pizza! Let's eat pizza.
Pizza?
- Hi.
- Oh. You're already here.
- You want to sit here?
- Yes.
You're studying the human body today too?
It is your book. If you keep doing this, it'll be awkward.
What are you saying?
Wow! It is real. I can't believe Kim Byeong Hoon is being this friendly with a girl.
- You really have to live long to see sich a sight.
- Is this why you wanted to come out?
What? Well, I'm also going to study.
But still, I'm curious.
- I'm going somewhere else.
- No, Ja Rim!
Eh? Why are they here?
These idiots!
Noona, I'll go to the restroom.
Okay.
What are you guys doing here?
That's what we want to ask you. Instead of studying like you're supposed to, you dare to hit on a girl!
We came to study. Don't make such a fuss.
But she was really pretty. Who is she?
Isn't she a social worker?
Look at her spending time with him. It is filling up her volunteer hours.
Dammit, that's not true! You told them, didn't you?
No? I really came here to study. It somehow turned out this way.
Friends. This is really important to me. I don't want to miss out on this.
Will such a thing ever happen to me again?
- That's why we came to help you.
- Buzz off.
Anyway, you guys just try and stop me. I'll hate you forever.
It took you long. Was it number two?
It's because I'm so healthy. Strong bowels make a strong country.
You really say just anything. You should fill it up now that it's empty. Let's go eat, my treat.
You don't have to...
You're already standing up, though.
What was that? Let's go.
What's so funny about what this buffoon says?
She's full of laughter. Honestly, am I not a better smooth-talker than him?
Do you think girls like funny guys? They find guys funny when they like them.
When you look at it, he's all right. He's tall, and his personality is the best of all of you.
Him? He always farts, burps,
and says nonsense. But such a guy can get a girlfriend?
Garlic, garlic.
It's nice to see you eat.
What's with this nausea-inducing sentence?
What? No, just... I think you'd be really popular if you filmed yourself eating.
I hear that often.
- Aren't you eating?
- Just eat a lot, Noona.
What? You're already full? Don't bet meals from now on. You can't even get your money's worth.
You've got such a weird personality.
Come to think of it, you aren't asking me to introduce you to a girl these days. You used to ask all the time.
- Well...
- Did you find someone?
- Well, I guess.
- I see.
- Noona.
- Yes?
Should I order one more garlic sauce?
Gosh, Ji Soo, why didn't you do that earlier?
Let's go now. There's nothing more to see.
Should we? They seemed to get along well. I hope it works out for them.
Oppa, you really came. I thought you were just saying that.
- It's on my way home, after all. You were still studying?
- Yes.
- Where are you sitting?
- Over there.
Really? What do we do? If the three meet, I think Byeong Hoon will be super shocked.
I know. Shouldn't we tell him in advance?
Right, I knew it. Finally, the world is going as normal. This is how it's supposed to be.
Don't you feel bad for your friend?
- Let's talk!
- What the? You guys still haven't left? I'm busy.
- Hey! Why did you only get one for her? Buy us some too!
- What are you doing?
Let's go to the karaoke! Should we call the others?
Forget it! You guys are trying to stop me, aren't you?
Why are you trying to ruin my life? Do you hate it that much, seeing your friend doing well?
Just let him go. He wants to ruin his own life, let him be.
I'm off.
Thanks for the food! Even though I'm the one buying.
- Thank you for the food.
- Let's go now.
- You're going to the gym, right?
- Nope. Jin Hui called me, so I'm going to see her.
- Hey...
- Yeah?
- I mean, aren't you having any dessert?
So disappointing! I thought you'd bet for ice cream at least.
You're right. Now that you said it, I'm craving some.
Forget about betting. I'll buy some for you since you treated me.
Gosh, then I'm grateful. Let's go.
- Noona.
- Yeah?
- Introduce me to a girl.
Like usual. Let's act as usual.
Out of the blue? But you said you found someone.
Yes. That girl is you.
Like I've always acted.
Do you want to be introduced to me?
This is my way.
No.
- You're not even thinking it over?
- No.
Cancel. Pretend you didn't hear anything.
Idiot.
I'll pay with this.
Thank you.
- Aren't you coming?
- What? You turned me down.
That's one thing, but you said you'd buy ice cream.
Then, can we keep being the same as before?
Does getting turned down allow you to break promises? Hurry and get up. One, two, three, come out.
- You're back?
- Yes.
- This person is...
- He's a senior at my school.
And this is Byeong Hoon. I met him here, and he's a really funny boy.
Hi. Are your final SAT revisions going well?
Come on, he's a first-year in high school. He's far from his SATs.
- Maybe it's because he's so tall?
- Maybe.
Hello, I'm the funny boy.
You two must be dating, you look really good together.
It feels like two people who were meant to meet. Just like Rain and Kim Tae Hee.
Whatever-Spouting Feast
What are you saying? No, we're not.
Hearing you talk, you're indeed a high school first year. I get why you find him funny.
It's because I'm the funny boy.
These are gifts for you two.
What's this? Thank you.
- I have to go, actually.
- What? Already?
- There's a drama I'm watching these days.
- Oh, there's something on air these days? What is it?
It's called "The delusion of the funny boy."
- There's such a drama?
- Yes, it's a new series.
It's very... sad.
Then, I'll take my leave.
Noona... she must like that guy, right?
That's right, even her gaze was different.
I'm just a funny boy.
I'm nothing more than funny. If you're funny, just go be a comic. Why try to date?
What is it? Did you follow me to make fun of me?
You're really...
It's okay. You're alright, you're okay.
Half of the world's population is women. It's all right.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
♫ Whenever I felt sad sending you back home  ♫
Love Revolution
My mom is taking away my room because my grades went down.
Say you'll go, but leave the place as is.
- We're having a room-away party at Gong Joo's.
- What's a room-away party?
- Why did we gather if this is how it's going to be?
- Ta-da!
Does she even take care of her boyfriend's grades?
- What did her boyfriend do wrong?
- Was his name Gong Joo Yeong?
- Long time no see. It's nice to see you.
- Right.
I have someone who I like.
I do think it's a pity.
Uh? What?
We all pitched in to prepare this.
Ja Rim suggested it.
Ja Rim!
♫ Your name I used to call so often ♫