You're not going to eat?
Snacking is a big no-no. I'll just eat a salad for dinner, too.
How can you live like that? Just eat. You are already thin.
Hearing that from skinny people doesn't comfort me one bit.
You've never had flab. You wouldn't know what it's like.
Still, didn't you lose some weight?
About, well, 1.5 kilograms?
Hey, don't you lose that much after you take a dump?
Good for you if your poop is big.
Just eat and exercise. Don't make the girls feel uncomfortable for eating.
Exercise...
Hey, there was an accident in the canteen so they're making emergency repairs.
Then what do we eat today?
We have to buy something at the snack store. Oh yeah!
What "Oh yeah," you bonehead? The entire school will be going to the snack bar.
The place will burst.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
So stingy, did you have to clear out the store?
Hey, what's this?
We were going to tell you to order in, but you guys ran out before. We don't have time to queue at the snack bar.
Dammit, I ran for nothing.
Ja Rim! The pizza and pasta are here!
Put it there!
Thank you, how did you know I wanted pizza?
Let go, it's for Ja Rim!
So it's fine if your friend starves to death?
What an exaggeration. Just eat a little.
I'll take this one.
Nope, it's mine.
Go eat with your girlfriend! Why come here and be annoying?
That's true. I haven't seen her today.
What, did you guys fight?
What the? Looks like you guys really did fight!
Ja Rim. I thought Joo Yeong was going a bit overboard at first, but is he normally this caring?
I think it is how he is. But it's true he goes overboard.
Really? Must be nice.
Kyeong Woo is a bit inattentive, even though I do like that too.
Ja Rim! Eat up.
Ta-da.
Gosh. Why did you have to fight now of all times? Adding another mouth to feed.
It was already unbelievable that he was even dating.
You really won't eat? You can have just a little. Just eat.
Leave her be. That makes one less person to feed. You're trying to lose some of that chub?
What? Do you have a death wish? What's wrong with me?
I don't think you'll look any better even if you lose any weight.
You're so annoying.
What? It was a joke.
Why is she so serious all of a sudden?
Why did you bother her? She's already sensitive because of her diet.
- Ja Rim, open up.
- Gosh.
I have hands, you know.
Gosh, seriously.
Quickly eat up before the others finish everything.
I think if I keep looking at them while eating, the pizza will come back out through my mouth as a stir-fried pancake.
Honey, you used to do that just for me. You've changed.
- Feed me too, me too!
- I will. I will feed you.
Sorry.
They told us not to order food in anymore. What do we do? Should we buy something beforehand?
No, I'm going to prepare a lunchbox.
But you're Snorlax, you love sleeping.
I can just make it tonight.
Wait, this might be an opportunity for me to show my worth as a family man.
She'll want to marry me.
Do you want me to prepare your lunchbox too? You love the food I make.
It's fine. I'll make yours too.
You've cooked a lot for me. I feel bad.
Wh-What?
Why? Are you afraid it'll taste bad again?
No, that's not it. It's because I'm scared it'll be tiring for you.
It's fine. Making something for two people is quick.
Really? I'm sure it'll taste great.
Love Revolution: The lunchbox from hell.
Episode 24. #CookingChallenge #HomemadeLunchbox #What'sOneTablespoon?
Arong_fighter @prince_rim: Just buy it...
Looks delicious.
This is stir-fried sausages, d-dried laver,
and even kimchi stew! Wow!
It's not. This is stir-fried fish cakes, to which I added sausages because you like them.
Stir-fried sausages - Wrong
And this isn't kimchi stew, it's stir-fried kimchi.
Kimchi stew - Wrong
Ah, really?
It looks delicious. Thanks for the food.
Okay. There's no way kimchi can taste bad, honestly.
Let's start with this.
How... the kimchi is bland. Did she add water?
It's so good.
Did you... add water maybe?
Yes. I was scared it would be too salty.
It's driving me crazy. She's so simple.
So cute.
Then I think it would be tasty if you added some onions too.
If it doesn't taste good, don't eat it.
No! It's delicious. Give it to me.
A lunch made by Wang Ja Rim?
Hey, just let me have one bite.
No!
No. I can't let Ja Rim get hurt.
Ja Rim went through the trouble of making these for me. Why would I give it to you guys?
- Leave.
- Come on.
That makes me want to take it even more.
Oh yeah.
- Ah sorry.
- I think this has gone bad.
What?
What the hell are you saying? It's delicious!
Did love blind your tongue, too?
From Sang Hoon: Many people do home workouts these days.
It could be difficult to go out to exercise, so I thought it would be all right with things you can do at home.
This workout is the most popular among the easy ones.
I already said it last time, but I'd like it if you didn't push yourself too much.
You're already more than pretty enough.
That makes one less person to feed. You're trying to lose some of that chub?
I don't think you'll look any better even if you lose any weight.
- It's really Devoted Hoon.
- You scared me.
(T/N: pun on Jeong Sang Hoon: jeongseong means devotion)
- Have you made your decision?
- About what?
If you aren't playing with him, put an end to this soon.
What are you saying? I'm not playing with him.
But he likes you. You don't, so why are you exchanging texts with him? He's going to misunderstand.
I don't know...
I have something to ask you guys. Please answer honestly.
- What?
- What is it?
Does the food I make taste bad?
Ah, your food...
I don't know. I haven't eaten it lately so I can't tell.
Why? Did Gong Joo Yeong say it tastes bad?
He says it's fine, but the others couldn't eat any.
They must have suffered a lot.
Then it must still taste like garbage.
How can you say it's garbage?
It's not that bad. It's just... a creative taste?
Be careful when adding seasoning. Don't put sugar without thinking to sweeten it. I'm sure you add water if you feel it's too salty, no?
But they say estimating the amounts by following your instinct is the best.
No, that can never work with you. People who are good at it do that, but you aren't.
That's true.
Can you maybe help me? With the lunchbox?
Okay. I'll come to your house later when I'm done.
Don't think too much about what the guys said earlier.
They lied because they're jealous of our relationship.
I think what you made is a hundred, a thousand times tastier than the food my mom and dad make.
Mom, Dad, I'm sorry.
I'll prepare our lunchbox for tomorrow. What do you want?
Should I make the stir-fried spicy pork you liked last time? Or mushroom marinated beef?
Just make what you want. Everything you make is tasty, anyway.
Really? Everything I made for you suited your taste?
Then you'd be really glad if we get married later, won't you?
You're going overboard again.
Why? I'll make you delicious food every day.
I'm back.
Hey, why are you putting that on? The hell...
You keep on wanting my clothes, you.
What's wrong? Let's share a bit.
You're so darn cheap.
Gosh. Ja Rim gave this to me as a gift!
I was being careful not to use too much.
Such a fuss.
Real belch extra? Real burp?
Real Barrier Extreme
Why did you take that out?
"Strengthens the skin barrier and moisturizes."
Isn't this something girls use?
Guys use it too. You should buy some and use it, too.
If you don't want to be "no girlfriend Kyeong Min" all your life.
Cook like you do math. Think of it as a formula and follow the quantities.
The next most important things are timing and controlling the flame.
Math is my worst subject, though.
So that's why you're this bad at cooking. It's alright. Here.
Start by cracking the egg and putting it in.
Here.
Hey, stop!
Look. There's a shell in it.
Really?
You see how there was a shell inside?
Your hit was too light so it didn't break cleanly and a shell fell in. Got it?
Try with a bit more force. Go on.
Okay.
You don't know how to settle for the middle.
Look, kimchi is already seasoned, so you don't really need to season it more.
But when you want to stir-fry it, you can add some sugar to make it a bit sweeter. It tastes nice.
Give me the sugar.
Wow. This will definitely taste good.
Gosh, it's salty.
Dammit, this is salt!
Really? Sorry. It looks too much the same.
If you want to cook food, either write the name or make some mark on this.
Is it fine?
Does this look fine to you?
I think you should just become a regular at a side-dish shop around here.
That's the only solution.
Hey. Want to eat this?
You made this  for me?
For real?
Did you really make this, Nuna?
Why, does it taste bad?
I-It's good. Wow, so tasty.
Actually, my friend made this but it felt like a waste to throw it away.
I knew it. There's no way a gourmet like you could have made this.
Ew. I thought it was a hit-or-miss lunchbox or something.
But she made that with me while I taught her.
No wonder. Just like for a hit-or-miss, there are tasty things and the others must be your friend's.
Hurry up and eat.
Eat up.
If we go there, you can eat too.
No, it's fine! You should eat what you want to.
How can I do that? You won't be able to eat.
I found a tasty salad restaurant so it's all right.
Isn't that Lee Kyeong Woo?
Should we go say hi?
It's fine, let's just go on our way.
Sure.
So annoying. Why am I the only one bothered by him?
He's nothing special.
Let's just go eat something tasty! I don't want to diet.
- Is that all right?
- Yeah.
You said I'm fine as I am. I don't think I need to go through the trouble.
Yeah.
The way you are now... you're pretty.
♫ Like that, so much time passes ♫
Let's go.
♫ Everyone looks happy ♫
Let's... continue to date.
I don't want to break up with you.
I think I was having too many expectations and burdened you. I'm sorry for whining.
♫ The day you left goes by ♫
I won't expect anything from you.
♫ And so does the next day ♫
Sorry.
I've been feeling sorry ever since hearing what you said that day.
Dating you with my current feelings...
♫ All the autumn leaves fall ♫
would feel wrong toward you.
♫ And everything blooms anew ♫
What's wrong with
♫ So why is my season the only one   ♫
your current feelings?
♫ that stays still? ♫
You don't like me anymore?
Even if we keep dating,
I think I'll only be feeling sorry to you, rather than feeling love for you.
♫ Am I still waiting, holding onto the lingering hope  ♫
I'm a bad jerk.
♫ that you’ll come back? ♫
You bad jerk.
♫ The only thing that’s still the same ♫
*sshole.
♫ Is this street we walked on together,  ♫
I'm sorry. Really.
♫ hand in hand ♫
♫ And me, wandering everywhere  ♫
♫ looking for you, crying  ♫
I'm so happy.
I should have given up earlier. I held back for nothing.
Did I look like a pig just now?
No! It's nice to see you eating well.
Do you really think I'm alright the way I am now?
Yes.
Why do you like me?
I... From the first time we met, I really liked you.
You're bright, you smile a lot...
And even now, I still really like you.
Then should we... date?
The lunchbox of love for Ja Rim!
Enjoy!
Thanks.
Sweetie. What's this?
Don't tell me, a lunchbox of love for me?
That's not it, so don't overreact—
Of course, I should overreact! You made it for me not only once, but twice!
You want me to die from being touched?
Quiet down before I just kill you.
Thanks for the food.
Ja Rim. It tastes good!
What's up? Why, how come it tastes good?
How come?
Well, as long as it's good, it's fine.
♫ What do you like? I’m curious ♫
♫ I wonder about every single thing about you ♫
♫ May I ask? May I approach you? ♫
♫ I keep on getting excited ♫
Do you think this tastes good? Are you wearing a thimble on your tongue or what?
♫ My mood goes up then down, on a roller-coaster ♫
♫ I can never know how you are feeling ♫
This is a bit... salty but putting me in a bad mood.
Byeol Rim, Byeol Rim, come here.
No, no way, I'm not eating it.
- Just once.
- No!
Are you trying to torture my tongue on purpose or what?
I'll just make it for you.
♫ Pit a pat ♫
At this rate, I'll be the one going crazy.
Ja Rim, it's really delicious. Make it  again next time.
I'll try.
- You're so bad at it.
- I couldn't do it.
It's not bad, right?
Hey, the lunchbox Ja Rim prepared for me today was totally tasty.
Friend. How long have we been doing business together? How dare you try to trick us?
It's true!
Just try and say that Ja Rim can't cook, you'll die.
- Right, Yang Min Ji.
- Yeah?
I heard you're dating Sang Hoon?
Yeah, that's true.
What the? One couple disappears and another one is born?
Is it the law of conservation of couples or what?
One disappeared?
This fool broke up with Bang Ye Seul.
But I was sure they were on a date that day.
Really? I'm only finding out now.
Why?
You don't need to know. It's my fault anyway.
No doubt, that's for sure.
Forget about me. These two are dating.
Sang Hoon is a really good guy so do well.
Okay.
♫ Everything feels unfamiliar ♫
♫ But nevertheless  ♫
Ye Seul - profile message: "Phew..."
♫ When I think of you, there is only one answer ♫
They really broke up.
♫ I guess I love you. I've been waiting ♫
♫ I wished for this very moment ♫
Love Revolution
We're going to study, why did you dress up? Did you get a girlfriend?
- His face says he does.
- You?!
- You must like it.
- I do.
You're really cute.
Nuna, do you want to see who can do hundred burpees the fastest?
- Betting a meal.
- Deal.
She's so pretty! Who is she?
Isn't she a social worker?
Do you want to be introduced to someone?
What's with this sentence? Making me want to puke.
- Let's have a talk.
- What the? You guys still haven't left?
This is a super important matter to me. I don't want to let this go.
Will such a thing ever happen again in my life?
Just you try to stop me. I'll hate you forever.
♫ I felt it from the beginning ♫