Is it going well with Bang Ye Seul?
More smoothly than for you.
Look.
Seems pretty nice.
Wait.
What is the difference? Why does this side look better?
Are you asking because you really don't know?
Oh, that's it. The guy is taller, so it looks better.
Could that really be the reason?
Wait.
Did you grow taller?
Did I? I'm not sure.
It seems like you grew 1cm more since we entered high school.
What's the big deal with height? They say our height varies by one to two centimeters between the evening and the morning.
What? Not a big deal? Jeez, you are already tall.
Hey, even 1cm is precious to me.
Try harder. At this rate, won't Wang Ja Rim grow taller than you?
Hey! Don't say stuff like that!
Sorry, did you wait long?
No, it's okay.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
- What are you looking at?
- Huh? Ah...
- Nothing. Just...
- What is it?
Ja Rim, have you perhaps...
Wang Ja, have you grown taller?
I've grown around 1.5cm since I started school here.
What? Really?
Ja Rim, so you're still growing?
It seems so. Let's hurry and go.
Love Revolution: How tall are you?
Episode 21. #ShortGuy #Complex #HowToGetTaller
bang_H @princess_0: Want to exchange my height for your face?
Ja Rim, should we go to the snack store?
Oh, what? You already went. But why did you buy so much?
- I've been craving food these days.
- She's eating as much as I am these days.
Oddly enough, she doesn't gain any weight. Has it all gone to her height?
You guys are so lucky. I'm envious you can eat without worry.
Hey, eat and exercise afterward. Why stupidly starve yourself?
- Do you want a bite?
- No. I'm not made for exercising.
- Give it to me.
- No!
- What the? Why?
- Are you scared she'll grow taller or what?
That's not it! I just wanted to suggest going to buy something tastier.
Something tastier? What is it?
Let's go.
Hey. What's with you?
Ja Rim.
Why don't you gain weight instead?
What the heck? Didn't you say we're going to buy some delicious food? Where are you going?
So, how tall is Wang Ja Rim?
- 163cm.
- What about you?
-  173cm.
- That's the average height then.
Is it okay to be average? If it were grades I would be in the 5th tier.
If you say it like that, I can see what you mean.
But there's still a 10cm difference between you and Wang Ja Rim. That's good enough.
That's the case now, but if she keeps growing taller, at this rate,
Ja Rim will be taller than me by third year.
Do you think Ja Rim is a giant or something?  Why would she keep growing?
Who knows what will happen?
Once we're all grown up and graduate, Ja Rim will be an adult and start wearing high heels.
She'll be the same height as me then.
You really think you'll be dating until then?
- We're going to get married!
- Gosh.
Oh my god.
Ja Rim can't be taller than me at our wedding!
- So embarrassing!
- Wedding my foot!
Did she say she'll marry you? Why in the world are you worrying about stupid stuff like that?
Anyway, my current height won't do.
No matter how much you grow, it's no use when you're Gong Joo Yeong.
Look at this turd. He's tall, but because he's Kim Byeong Hoon, he doesn't have a girlfriend.
What about you? You're short and you don't have a girlfriend. You should at least have the height.
What's wrong with my height? What?
I'm just the right height! I'm taller than Gong Joo Yeong! Jeez!
185cm
176cm
181cm
Why am I the only one not growing?
Wang Ja didn't even say anything about you being short. Why are you uselessly worrying?
- Still...
- Hey.
The teacher has sent me for an errand. Can you help me?
I have to get something from the science lab.
Okay! I'll help you!
But...it's somewhere up high.
Kim Byeong Hoon, can you help me?
Okay.
So, I can't help because I'm short?
Sh*t!
How to grow taller.
Stimulate your growth plates with regular exercise.
To exercise in a restricted space, "sergeant jumps" are the best.
Light jumping exercises are the best kind for stimulating the growth plates.
- Who is this?
- I live in the house below.
Why is it so noisy in the middle of the night? I thought some construction work was happening.
Sorry.
Sweetie, if you're tired, sleep for a bit.
I'll sleep for a bit.
Ja Rim, did you just grow taller?
They say you grow taller while you're sleeping.
No. Wake up!
You can't sleep! Hurry and wake up!
Stop sleeping, Ja Rim!
I need to become tall.
If that was how you could get taller, the entire nation would be 180 cm tall.
Then you? How did you become so tall?
I ate well and pooped well.
So you're saying your genes did all the work.
You've been blessed with it, how can you understand how I feel?
What's this now? Treating your athlete's foot?
Ah, it's an acupuncture point for growth. I have to press on it.
You're really doing all sorts of things.
If you're going to say such stuff then get lost.
Or help me. Massage my back.
- Where do I have to press?
- Press along my spine.
Ah, that's good.
You are doing well. Ah.
Gong Joo Yeong!
You look busy.
Oh, Ja Rim! This is only a massage.
- Where shall we go after class?
- I'm not sure.
- Internet cafe?
I don't know how to play any games.
- What about Kart?
- Ah right, I can play that one.
Okay. Then let's play that.
See you later.
Min Ji, I looked into it thinking that it might be of some help,
and rather than suddenly changing your diet,
changing your food little by little while maintaining a regular diet is better.
They say that way you can keep doing it consistently, and that if you starve yourself, you'll definitely get the yo-yo effect.
There won't be a problem as long as you eat according to your basal metabolism.
I don't know your specific requirements, but they say the average basal metabolism for women is 2000 calories.
and that it's good to intake all the essential nutrients within those 2000 calories.
That will be more helpful for your diet.
Truthfully, for me you look good as you are now.
I hope you won't push yourself too much. You even like spicy foods.
I'm worried now that you can't eat them during your diet.
Wow. It's amazing!
Thank you, Sang Hoon.
What is it?
Teacher, I have such huge worries that I can't sleep well.
- How can I become taller—
- What, you punk?
Sorry?
Gosh...
Hey! You want to die?
You're blessed to be over 170 cm. Are you making fun of me?!
N-No. Sorry.
Teach, they say doing sergeant jumps help in getting taller.
My growth plates closed, you brat!
What a weirdo!
Have you seen any movies recently?
The one released this time seemed fun.
No, I haven't watched anything recently.
Then this weekend,
Do you want to go see a movie?
Weekend Morning
Growth gymnastics for the evening: the plow pose
This helps to grow?
- Who is it?
- It's me Jeong Sang.
0323 star.
What's up?
- See if my clothes are fine.
- Why?
What's this suddenly?
Hey! What the hell?!
Wow, did you go through a hand-me-down clothes box?
- It's new.
- It's new?
Did you take a time machine and go to the past for shopping?
- Is it that bad?
- Yeah!
It's crazy bad.
But why do you suddenly want me to check your clothes?
Are you going to meet a girl?
- Yeah.
- Eh? Really?
Who?
Min Ji.
Ah right! Oooh! Wait up.
- You guys finally going on a date?
- Yeah.
Then I should put in some effort for you.
Monk Hyemin: Min Ji, are you downtown?
Yeah. To meet Sang Hoon
Vegeta: So you're meeting him in the end.
Monk Hyemin: Ah, that prim guy?
Ah right! F*ck!
Vegeta: LOL, hella funny.
What will you do if he wears what he wore last time?
Ah his clothes. I didn't think of it.
Please just wear something simple.
I'd rather you wear a tracksuit, even.
Min Ji.
Hi.
Oh! Hi.
- Are you hungry?
- Do you want to eat?
Shall we go eat?
You came? The food is almost ready.
We could just eat outside. It's bothersome.
No, not at all. It's because I want to cook for you from time to time.
The food is almost ready, so just wait a little.
- I'll use your laptop a bit.
- What? Okay.
I guess you must have hidden your porn well, then.
No, I don't watch that stuff.
Acupuncture point for growth / Food for growth / Do girls dislike short guys
Height difference with girlfriend / How to grow taller / Exercise for growth
Ja Rim, so you're still growing?
Ja Rim. Why don't you gain weight instead?
Gong Joo Yeong!
♫  What do you like? I’m curious ♫
♫ I wonder about every single thing about you ♫
What's this? Cute.
Huh? What did you say?
Nothing, nothing at all.
♫ May I approach you? ♫
♫ I keep on getting excited ♫
Ta-da.
♫ All day long, seeing you and your smile puts me on a roller  ♫
♫ My mood goes up then down, on a roller-coaster ♫
Okay, let's eat now.
Why is yours like this?
I'm craving these sorts of things these days.
Ah...
♫ I can’t slow down ♫
Is that so?
Enjoy!
♫ I'm curious ♫
♫ About you ♫
♫ Pit a pat ♫
Food for growth
♫ I'm curious ♫
- I want some too.
- No, you can't!
If you grow taller—
Ah... Uhm.
♫ Pit at pat ♫
I'll eat this.
The rabokki is tasty.
(T/N: rabokki = ramyeon with spicy rice cakes)
♫ And it will be a cold day in hell ♫
♫ Before I let you back ♫
You're going to pay? Let's pay together.
I want to treat you here.
It's the first time we're having a meal together, and I thought I'd feel better if I'm the one paying.
I'm buying to make myself feel good.
Really? Thanks for the meal.
♫ I'm holding on ♫
Isn't he quite alright?
♫ And letting ♫
[Bobired]
What's this? Are you finally dating?
Really? He's your boyfriend, Min Ji?
No, it's not like that.
Yeah, we just agreed to see a movie together.
So it's a date. Wow, Jeong Sang!
Hey, do well. He's Jeong Seong Hoon, overflowing with devotion, after all.
Your name is really Jeong Seong Hoon?
(T/N: jeongseong means devotion)
No, it's Sang Hoon...
You do well yourself. Hurry and go on your way.
Right, let's not disturb them and go.
- Have fun.
- We're off.
Min Ji.
Yeah?
Should we go?
Yeah.
I must be crazy.
Hey, I heard Min Ji went on a date with Jeong Sang Hoon?
It looks like she wants to make it work, after all.
I thought she wasn't interested.
Let's go to the snack bar.
I don't really like tall guys.
What are you saying out of the blue?
Isn't just over 170 cm a nice height?
When did you get here?
Ja Rim!
What? What is it?
I'm going to the snack bar.
She must have eaten something funny.
♫ Even if I keep telling myself it’s not real ♫
♫ Every morning when I wake up, I can only think of you ♫
Are you not doing sergeant jumps today?
No thank you.
What the...? You said you wanted to grow taller. You gave up?
Ja Rim says she doesn't like tall guys. She says she likes guys just my height.
As long as I look good to Ja Rim, I'm fine.
♫ I like your smiling face the most ♫
What the hell is that height of yours?
♫ But the picture you posted today, where was it taken? ♫
♫ Why does it make me so anxious  ♫
♫ when you are somewhere I’m not? ♫
Belated surge of cringe
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♫ I'm being sincere ♫
♫ I don’t want to stay as a friend to you anymore ♫
Love Revolution
- What's that?
- A game of flipping chicken coupons over.
Get ready for battle!
Look at how he talks. He's a complete addict.
This is also all for your sake.
How do you do it?
She's One Bang Man.
Two hundred coupons?
Twenty chickens, Gosh.
Where's Lee Kyeong Woo?
Gong Joo Yeong doesn't play anymore. He's different from you.
As expected, the rumors about you being One Bang Man weren't lies.
I used my brain, of course. You can't play games if you're ignorant.
- Is something wrong?
- I'm chewing on the bitter taste of defeat.
Hey Lee Kyeong Woo, let's do a revenge match.
Deal.
♫ I wish you would let me carry some of that burden  ♫