The weather is wonderful.  The sky too is pretty.
But these days, no matter how beautiful things are, they're just so-so to me.
Is it because my standard for beauty has gotten too high?
If you compare anything to my Ja Rim, it is insignifi—
Shut your trap!
Did it get broken? Why do the words in your head keep leaking out?
So cringe-y.
But I keep thinking of you.
I have to at least do this to empty my head.
Ja Rim, when do you think of me?
When I get a text from you.
- Then I should text you once a minute.
- Yeah. You'll get blocked.
Actually, I too think of you just once a day.
From the time I wake up until I fall asleep, exactly once.
Sorry.  I'll stop.
It was far from a done deal, but somehow they're still dating.
But it's more like having a pet than a dating relationship.
At least when you have a pet, you nurture it. This is just a master-servant relationship.
Do you think this snack will really be able to enter your mouth?
Let me go, let me go. Hurry and let me go.
Ah, ah, you're too much.
Are you crazy, seriously!
If you have something to say, say it.
- Are you busy this weekend?
- Yeah. I am. I have to go clothes shopping.
There, it's done.  Thanks.
You can go now.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Gong Joo Yeong. Have you still not managed to take Ja Rim on a date?
-  Yeah.  Because Ja Rim seems to not want to. What if we break up again because I keep pushing?
Gosh, I do feel bad for you, but you two are really something in your own separate ways.
Totally frustrating.
Hey! Extra! Extra!
Look at this.
Ilsam-dong cafe with a nice ambiance.  A place where handsome guys work
Shall we go together this weekend?
Not fond of that idea.
- Oh why? I need you to bring Ja Rim.
- What? You want me to help again?
Please. When you date I will support you totally.
- What's up?
- What?
Oh? About what?
I'm asking what are you doing?
You want to surprise Kyeong Woo?
Okay.  I get it.  Over.
I mean, you guys can just tell me you're throwing me a birthday party. Why make up an excuse?
Surprise party
kyungwoo
Love Revolution: Surprise Party
Episode 9 #Today'sWork # Strange #Customers #NoThanks
Min_jji @Kyungwoo: Please call the boss.
- I'm here.
- What?  You're early.
- I had some free time. I'll change.
- Okay.
Hey, you need to wear a bowtie.
If I button up the shirt tightly, my neck will bruise. The customers wouldn't like to see that.
Jeez.
- There's a call from room 2 so go there first.
- Yes.
Is there anything I can...
- Hey!
- Hi!
- What's with you, guys?  How did you know I work here?
- Look at you.
We are guests.  Why aren't you speaking politely?
I think we should call the boss.
Boss!
Is that a birthday punch?
I heard the concept here was handsome guys,
but there's no handsome guy and the service is so poor.
Aren't you going to order? If you're going to fool around, please beat it, dear customers.
We'll order, though.
I will get rosé pasta.
Please use hand-made noodles and keep them separate from the sauce.  I like to dip.
For the cream in cream pasta, is it whipping cream?
Yes.
You are cruel. Please give me cream that's already dead.
For me, give me water as clear as Italy's Lake Como in which you put ice colder than an Icelandic glacier,
into a minimalist cup of Swedish sensitivity.
I want to admire the dew that forms like jewels on the smooth surface of the cup.
-  Iced water?
- Yes.
These punks. So you're throwing me a surprise party?
Okay, okay.   I'll play along with you for now.
Do you bring the Hawaiian pizza directly from Hawaii?
You can leave for Hawaii, then.
(T/N: famous line from the 2001 movie "Friend")
Boss, could you make some seafood-ri zotto for me?
It's seafood risotto.
Yes. With a lot of zotto, please.
Guests. Could you just order what's written in the menu?
We'll let you know once we've decided. Just go for now.
How boring.
Why do you want to have fun at someone's workplace? Is this what you called me for?
No, well, we thought it would be fun.
Then you guys should play. I'm leaving first.  I was going shopping for clothes anyway.
Okay.  Leave Super Serious out.
Hey! Don't speak carelessly about my girlfriend.
- All right. I'll sit next to Min Ji then.
- Bye.
Yeah.  You guys are going to buy me a cake.
I'll wait for you.
Are they all acting gods?
Ja Rim, wait for me.
What are you coming along for?  I'm more comfortable shopping alone.
I'll just be with you. I won't bother you and be like the invisible man.
If you need, I can carry your stuff.
Okay, follow me.
You would come even if I told you not to, anyway.
How do you know me so well? Are you thinking about me?
It's room 2.
What?
Some water please.
Some tissue please.
What is it?
The air conditioner is too cold. Please hug me.
Warmly.
Order everything at once, dammit.
The joke is going a bit far.
Kyeong Woo.
- Please tell your friends to stop playing around with the bell.
- Yes.
And there are other customers around, so speak politely to them.
Why did you call for me again, dear customers?
I pressed the bell by mistake. Sorry!
Too funny!
- How was it?
- You did well.
Excuse me.
Yes. Do you need anything?
Your phone number, please.
- Mine?
- Yes.
Don't tell me they really forgot my birthday?
Do people like this kind of stuff?
This is filled with eternal love for you, my dear. Love you.
Of course, I love it!
Guys! Thank you so much.
I really thought you guys forgot about my birthday.
Of course not! That's impossible! We're so close!
How can we forget your birthday?
Did you prepare this?
Of course. We're all gathered here for Byeong Hoon, right?
Right. That's right.
But, did you prepare this yourself?
Well, I just brought it in.
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday! Congrats!
Ja Rim. I think this will look good on you.
I said I'll choose myself.
Ja Rim. One is for me, right?
No. Both of them are mine.
I'll buy these, please.
No. I'll pay...
By chance, did you get those on purpose?
You're so mean.
Do you want to hang out with me that much?
Of course. Hanging out with you is my life-long dream.
Okay then. What do you want to do?
Happy birthday to you!
Happy birthday to our dear Byeong Hoon!
- And the candles?
- Don't we have candles?
- No candles?
No candles?
If there's none, let's just eat it.
- Let's eat!
- Looks so tasty!
Take this one at least.
- Are you Gong Joo Yeong?
- What the?
You're Wang Ja Rim, Wang Ja Rim.
Let's eat, let's eat!
Hey, these strawberries are super sweet. Eat some, hurry up.
- A valley?
- Yes.
Last year, us guys went to Byeong Hoon's grandpa's house.
He told us to come this year as well. He said the more friends we bring, the better.
- Forget it. I'm not going.
- Come on.
If you don't, you'll regret it so much. The water there is so clear and refreshing.
Plus, you don't have to pay anything, and they even prepare food for us.
Also, you can see that there are plenty of stars in the night sky.
You can also see the Milky Way there.
You like dogs, right? There is even a really cute dog there.
What do you think?
I'll think about it.
Okay! Then, you're going.
I told you I'd think about it. Just decide where do you want to go now.
I've already decided where I want to go with you.
Don't hold my hand.
Why are you calling for me again?
Kyeong Woo. Come here and eat some cake.
Hey.
By any chance, this cake is...
Yes. Thank you.
You worked hard to secretly prepare for my birthday.
You crazy morons! Why would you eat it?
You didn't prepare this for my birthday party? I just brought it in, that's all.
Didn't you prepare it yourself?
It was left here by a customer for a surprise event.
What are we going to do now?
Right. Then that means no one knew about my birthday in the end.
But still, you had a birthday party.
I'm sorry about that, but what are you going to do about this?
What do you think? It's not going to fix itself while we whine about it.
What time is the event?
There is less than an hour left.
We have to keep these on?
Yes. The concept of the room you chose is where you have to escape while being handcuffed together.
- Hey. You chose this place on purpose, right?
- What?
No. I didn't know it was like this either.
But still... It seems fun, right?
Can't we just do it without handcuffs?
Ja Rim, let's give it a try.
It's not even holding hands anyway. Can't we just do it?
Okay.
- ka-talk
- The guys tell me to come back.
- I also got a message.
They say it's super urgent, and to bring you back no matter what.
But, this is our date.
Hey...
What happened?
Can't you see? It's a complete mess.
We looked through a few places...
But there was only this left.
It's too different.
- What should we do?
- Lee Kaeng.
- Maybe it'll be okay if you use your capitalist smile a bit.
- Dammit.
Can you joke in this situation?
There isn't even much time left.
- Kyeong Woo. There are various types of whipping cream in the kitchen, right?
- Yes.
Okay.
Then, for the roses... Byeong Hoon and Kyeong Min, you guys are experts at rose paper folding now, right?
- Well, I could do it with my eyes closed now.
- Yeah...
Okay. Then, who is good at handwriting?
- Kyeong Woo, strawberry powder please.
- Okay.
Min Ji, ice.
Yes, Sir.
- I'll be back.
- Okay.
Ja Rim, the strawberries please.
- Here.
- Thanks.
It looks pretty similar.
Wow.
Dear...
What do you think of this big bro's skills?
Not bad.
When you come in,
please play a moist— no I mean, a sweet love song.
And please say "The eternal love you have ordered is here,"
Can't believe there are other people besides Gong Joo Yeong who do this kind of stuff.
Who on earth is he?
Here is the eternal...
♫ Cause you are my girl  ♫
♫ You are the one that I envisioned in my dream ♫
(T/N: popular sitcom "High Kick Through the Roof" OST)
♫ And when you're around, I can't express— ♫
The eternal love you have ordered...
is here.
Yes.
This is filled with eternal love for you, my dear. Love you.
So, you working part-time
to help out in the cafe is really commendable.
Yes. Thank you.
About what you saw today... Forget it all.
I also... want to forget about it.
Right. Okay.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
It's coming, it's coming.
♪ Real, real, real, real, it's real. It's totally real. ♪
♪ The real thing appeared now ♪
♪ I'll love you with all my might ♪
Mister, one more hour for this room, please!
From what I saw earlier, you're good with your hands.
I always have been, that's true.
I probably take after my father. He's a chef.
Oh, really? Are you good at cooking too?
Yeah. Look forward to your birthday. I'll make you something so good you'll cry.
You can have great expectations. Okay?
Not okay. If you do that, you're dead.
Then, go in safely.
No. I'll walk you all the way home.
Forget it. It's right in front anyway. Just go in.
Since it's right in front of us, I'll walk you there.
- You're really being stubborn.
- Come on.
I would have already brought you home by the time you say this.
Do whatever you want.
♫ I like you ♫
♫ I’m being sincere ♫
♫ I don’t want to stay as a friend to you anymore ♫
Love Revolution
Couple outfits!
It's such a coincidence! Right?
Who are you?
Hi.
- I'm here.
- Byeong Hoon!
My cute puppy!
What do you think about getting married to Byeong Hoon?
Put on some ointment.
Hey, did you call us here to work?
Anyone have water?
Out of the way.
What's wrong with you?
Hey, Wang Ja Rim. Don't live like that.
Hey, where is this punk?
Joo Yeong!  Joo Yeong!
What are you doing?
♫ But you're the only one for me ♫