Darling, did you wait a lot?
- Don't you have something to tell me?
- Huh? About what?
Did Hyung Seung Jin go to your house yesterday?
Yeah. He came over. What about that?
"What about that?" You let any guy in your house?
Why do you say it like that?
It wasn't me alone in the house. My younger brother was also there.
It wasn't for a moment. I heard you let him sleep over.
What? I never let him sleep over.
He came over only for a moment!
The others were right.
What is right? What did they say?
Leave it. I was the fool for thinking you would apologize.
Apology? Why should I apologize?
What did I do wrong?
You can't trust me?
He really came over for just a moment!
Then what about Jo Seung Min?
What? Why are you bringing Jo Seung Min up now?
I heard you contact Jo Seung Min. Why would you contact my friend?
What's with you? Is this as far as your affection goes?
Whomever I am with, whomever I contact, whatever the  others say,
if you like me you should believe me.
- Give me your phone.
- Why my phone?
Give it to me. If there's nothing with them, you can just show it to me, right?
I don't want to. Why do you want to see someone else's phone?
- Give it to me.
- I don't want to.
I said give it to me!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Is that important?
Leave it. I'm going.
Love Revolution: Kyeong Woo's story
#Middle schooler Kyeong Woo #Story #Guy's friendship
Min_jji @kyungwoo: Don't act like the hero of a tragic love story
I know the story that comes after that.
It was revealed that jerk Jo Seung Min was the one that spread all the false rumors about Nam Yu Ri.
On top of that, he spread weird rumors about Lee Kyeong Woo.
I think it said that Nam Yu Ri had a hard time because Kyeong Woo was very rash and violent.
Eventually, it spread everywhere and even reached Kyeong Woo's ears.
Did Lee Kyeong Woo come to school? I heard he hit Nam Yu Ri.
How could he do that, with that face of his?
I am getting goosebumps.
That guy always had a bad temper.
Hey, I was with him for a while so I know. I knew that he would do that someday.
You guys have it hard because you made a bad friend.
Hey! Don't be with him from now on. Why would you be with a guy like him?
Lee Kyeong Woo is a thug and his girlfriend is trash, they suit each other.
- So true.
- Hey Jo Seung Min! What is this f*cking nonsense?
Why are you spreading false rumors here and there?
What do you mean by false rumors? It is true that you fought with Nam Yu Ri and said mean stuff.
I was just pitying Nam Yu Ri.
No matter what, you shouldn't hit a girl.
When did I hit Nam Yu Ri?
I saw it.
Crazy!
Hey, hey, Kyeong Woo, what's wrong with you? You want to hit me too?
-  F*ck! Let go!
- I can't let go!
You might get expelled if you continue this. Don't do this.
Why are you taking his side when you know nothing, you fool?
Why would I take that fool's side?
I am taking your side. I am doing this for you.
Buffoon! He can't even hit me.
Hey Gong Joo Yeong! Thanks a freaking ton.
Hey, hey, you don't have to look at me like that.
I will give you some advice. Don't hang out with that jerk too much.
He thinks so, so highly of himself that he will steal
everything that you like.
After all this, Kyeong Woo suddenly got hospitalized.
Why? Did he get ill from anger?
No, you dumbo.
He was hurt somehow. Did they say he fell?
Ah, I heard it, but I can't remember. What was it?
Nam Yu Ri's ex-husband! They had a fight.
Oh Ah Ram, stop with your over-the-top melodrama now.
Oh right! I heard he got hurt while fighting with Nam Yu Ri.
Does that even make sense? What's this nonsense, out of the blue?
What do you mean by nonsense? A woman's fury has always been scarier.
Hey, even if they fought, would she unleash such fury that he would get hospitalized?
There are many cases of crimes of passion like that!
It was not Nam Yu Ri.
Then why did Lee Kyeong Woo get hurt?
Gong Joo Yeong, you know right?
Actually...
It was because of me.
You're here?
- Are you okay?
- Well.
What are you doing? Sit.
It was revealed that all the false rumors about you had been spread by that jerk Jo Seung Min.
It seemed it was revealed because Nam Yu Ri used all her personal connections.
And Jo Seung Min, that b*stard, was embarrassed—
Hey! I know it all.
Even that that jerk Jo Seung Min transferred schools because he was embarrassed?
Yeah. I told him everything.
Hey, but why did you get hurt? Did someone hit you?
Hey, by any chance, did Nam Yu Ri hit you?
According to the rumors, you and Nam Yu Ri had a fight.
Stop with the nonsense and go refill the water. Go.
Seeing that he's changing the topic, I am right. He got hit by Nam Yu Ri.
Hey. For real, how did you get hurt? Did something happen?
Ah he fell down the stairs.
Why? How?
I pushed him by mistake.
Ay, this fool. Are you crazy? Pushing a person down the stairs.
You should have been careful!
What? He got hurt because of you, Gong Joo Yeong?
I thought there would be something dynamic. Boring.
I'll say.
The bell is going to ring.
Let's just get up now.
Yeah, let's go.
If it isn't Gong Joo Yeong!
Hey, I came to see Kyeong Woo but I even get to meet you. So glad to see you.
Are you still being a good lackey as usual?
I don't have anything to say to you. Just go.
What a man. Is it because there is a girl here?
Is she your girlfriend? She's freaking hot. Why is someone like her dating you?
I said just go.
What?
You grew a lot, Joo Yeong.
Hey hey, don't overdo it, let's go.
Ah right. You must know because he is your best friend.
About Lee Kaeng's forehead injury. I heard it was from getting hit by his father.
It is not that. I pushed him down the stairs by mistake.
What are you saying? Some say he was beaten up by the guys, and you say it was the stairs?
He said he saw it! Saw that buffoon getting hit by his father with a soju bottle.
Why say that, dude?
Why would you hide it?
I told you that's not it. I said it was me.
Hey! What are you doing now?
You're just Lee Kyong Woo's lackey, dammit.
F*cking girl.
F*ck.
F*ck. What are you again?
A police car was coming earlier. What happened?
- Seung Min, let's leave.
- F**k, let go.
Don't make things blow up!
F*cking b*stards, really!
Gong Joo Yeong, are you alright?
I am fine. What about you, Ja Rim?
I am fine.
Is it okay even if you don't go to the doctor?
Yeah. It's okay.
Is what Jo Seung Min said earlier true?
That...
No. Jo Seung Min lied about everything.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You swear to me?
- No.
- So it was true
what Jo Seung Min said.
It's just that Kyeong Woo is a complicated friend.
I understand. I won't ask any more.
For now, get a good rest.
Come out.
Gong Joo Yeong got hit because of you.
Long time no see.
What are you doing?
It isn't even that bad. I heard that was because of your father.
Gong Joo Yeong even told you? Gosh, he never freaking changes.
You said you've been friends with Gong Joo Yeong for ten years. Then you should know what kind of guy he is.
Or are you pretending not to know?
I didn't hear it from Gong Joo Yeong.
Jo Seung Min said it when he came to pick a fight with Gong Joo Yeong.
Gong Joo Yeong wouldn't tell me no matter how much I asked.
He didn't even tell me, so do you think he told Jo Seung Min?
Hey! You really don't have to cover your scar.
Forget it. Do something to your bangs.
Don't you feel suffocated?
I'll go get some water.
Bulletproof Yu Ri
Are you alright?
Hmmm.
I want to go see you at the hospital.
Can I come tomorrow?
Are you still mad?
No.
Then?
Let's stop contacting each other.
Why? I cut ties with all my male friends and—
Is it because false rumors about you are going around in my school?
- I took care of all—
- Yu Ri, it's just...
I'm going through so much at the moment, to the point I can't see you.
I am sorry.
When did you wake up?
Are you feeling alright?
I contacted the teacher.
He said not to worry about school for the time being, because he'll register you as you being sick.
Right, your mother is also here.
She must be talking with the police now.
You don't want to talk, huh?
I saw you're better, so I'll get going now.
Don't go.
Huh?
Hey, is it very painful?
Rate your pain from 1-10. Is it around 5?
Isn't it uncomfortable when you have to wash yourself?
It is a hassle, so just don't wash up till you take the bandages off.
Are you practicing silent meditation right now?
Or did you also get aphasia when you got hurt?
Why did you ask me to stay if you're going to be like this?
Right. I am also regretting it.
Kyeong Min and Sang Hoon are coming tomorrow, so don't ruin the mood then.
Joo Yeong, you're doing so much.
Coming here every day. Thanks.
I have to talk to Kyeong Woo for a moment.
Yes, please talk.
Why is it so difficult to see my handsome son's face?
I am sorry.
From now on, let's both
live our lives looking at each other.
What are you saying?
I have decided to divorce your dad.
You don't have to worry about me anymore.
Hey transfer student! That is Lee Kyeong Woo's seat.
The owner of this seat is Lee Kyeong Woo?
The teacher told me to sit here because he is hospitalized.
The owner of that seat has been discharged.
- Yo, you came?
- Finally, you're back.
- Are you all right?
- Kyeong Woo, hi!
It's my seat, move.
It seems the teacher didn't know you were coming. He told him to sit here and that they will give him a desk tomorrow.
Thanks for the kind explanation.
You heard, right?
Move over, you fool.
Then where are you telling me to sit?
Is that my business?
What are you doing?
I am sitting because it is my seat. Is there any problem?
Crazy psycho idiot. Are you a nutcase?
Want some?
Okay.
Wow, Lee Kyeong Woo is completely unable to touch him. He's a formidable opponent.
Hey, let's become friends with him to keep Lee Kyeong Woo in check.
On whose watch will we become his friend? I don't want to.
- You want to eat this?
- Okay.
Good benefits.
Get up.
I said get up.
Can't you just leave when I'm pretending to sleep?
- Hey.
- Darn it.
What are you doing?
You also hit me, then. Hit me, you buffoon!
- Hit me!
- Dammit.
Dammit, seriously!
Sorry.
Do you see me as a guy who would spread false rumors behind your back? You're so important to me.
I am sorry.
I am also sorry.
Anyhow, I am sorrier.
No, I am sorry.
I said I am sorry.
- I am one time sorrier than you.
- And I am double sorry.
I've been sorry since elementary school because I think this is all because of me.
Then I am sorry for saying that you pooped your pants when we were in elementary school.
- Crazy fool. I said I didn't.
- Forget it.
Just, whatever it was... I am sorrier.
No, never mind.
Then we don't have anything to feel sorry toward each other about,
because we apologized for everything.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
♫ Whenever I felt sad sending you back home ♫
Love Revolution
Should we wait upstairs?
How can I face Ja Rim now?
- Hey Lee Kyeong Woo!
- You cut your hair.
Is that chicken that tasty?
His taste is so—
That Bang... Whats-her-name. Give me her number.
Lee Kyeong Woo asked you for a meal?
- You also come along.
- Why would I come along?
What on earth are you doing in this sacred school?
Teacher! How many details will you give us?
In order to avoid unwanted pregnancy...
It is not a thing to be embarrassed about.
♫ After breaking up with me ♫