Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Gong Joo Yeong used to go to tutoring school diligently, but who knows what garbage that b*tch told him.
He stopped going to tutoring school one day. His grades weren't bad before.
He even sold his favorite shoes to buy stuff for her. Sh*t.
Is that called dating? He was more like her underling.
But that idiot still thinks she dated him because she liked him.
But she knows he's soft-hearted, so she probably contacted him to take advantage of him again.
I'm sure about that.
You said she didn't date him because she liked him?
Their group of girls were fighting or something,
and one of them spilled the beans to me. From the beginning... Damn it.
She was trying to get introduced to some other dummy at first.
It didn't work, so that's why she went to Gong Joo Yeong.
What are you saying? She went after Gong Joo Yeong because she couldn't get another guy?
How are they related?
I have to protect that dummy's identity too.
[That other XX]
I'm speechless. I know he looks naive, but still...
I did find it strange when Gong Joo Yeong started
going around borrowing money.
Are you mad?
That b*tch.
Sweetie, are you mad?
You don't believe what the guys said just now, do you?
They're all lies! Seriously, nothing happened between us.
Are you mad?
How can I not be mad?
Should I tell Gong Joo Yeong?
Then those rumors about you will stop too. That b*tch will be screwed over too.
What is this? Why is she like that?
Does she believe them?
I know it's not true.
- What?
- Stop letting me have my way all the time.
And no need to be so cautious around me.
I'm dating you because I like you too.
Ja Rim.
Love Revolution: Vying for the princess
Episode 29.
#ExVSCurrentGF #HairSwappingProcess #LongKeptSecretsDon'tLast
glasses @princess_0: I'm hella envious
- Hey, let's go.
- Yeah.
Bo Gyeong: Joo Yeong, I'm in front of your school.
Let's talk today for sure.
- Kwak Bo Gyeong said she's waiting for me again.
- Gosh.
What do I do? Should I just meet her and make things clear to her?
Forget it. Just go. I'll tell her to scram.
Apparently, Kwak Bo Gyeong came to our school again.
Leave through the back door with Gong Joo Yeong.
Tell Joo Yeong I left with the girls already.
- What? Why?
- I have something to say to her.
Hey, I know how you feel, but she won't get it. You'll just be getting into this mess for nothing.
Even so,
I can't just leave this mess be.
Should I tell Gong Joo Yeong?
Then those rumors about you will stop too. That b*tch will be screwed over too.
Don't tell him.
- Why not?
- He'll know she never liked him.
He'll be really hurt.
What about the rumors about you?
Never mind about that. It's better than him finding out about this.
You absolutely must not tell him. I'll handle it.
It looks like when she slightly disliked someone, she would spread gossip like hell.
But what, events?
Gong Joo Yeong didn't know any of that. She ordered him around.
Let's talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
But I do.
Hey! What the hell?
Quick, come.
- Why?
- Wang Ja Rim went to see Kwak Bo Gyeong.
What?
Why did you drag me all the way here?
What is it? Scared that there will be bad rumors about you again?
How do you know that there are sh*tty rumors about me in our school?
It's like you spread the rumors.
What about you, nothing you feel guilty about?
Did you hear something from Lee Kyeong Woo?
Since you know, don't come looking for Gong Joo Yeong. Don't even contact him.
Why should I stop? I'm just contacting him as a friend.
Friend? What b*llshit.
Do you not have a conscience? It seems you're trying to take advantage of him again because he's nice.
He's not someone you can exploit however you want.
You're so funny. Seeing how Gong Joo Yeong behaves, I think you aren't any easier than me.
Did I extort money from him or something?
He opened his wallet on his own because he liked me.
But seeing him spend his money on another girl, it felt like such a pity.
When it's thanks to me that he gets called a romantic boyfriend.
I didn’t want my efforts to be in vain so I contacted him.
And he replied to me.
He still likes me, you stupid wench.
The idiot who's keeping in contact with me while he has a girlfriend, and the idiot that you are for dating that idiot...
You idiots sure have such a nice relationship.
Wait, no. You're also playing Gong Joo Yeong, so you're not an idiot.
You're a b*tch like I am.
Except I'm not a sl*t.
I heard you dated Oppa Choi Jeong Woo.
You did everything with that man-whore, and now you're playing with Gong Joo Yeong.
Is your life comfortable? I'm quite something, but you're also impressive.
Don't do it.
Let go. Ja Rim has to hear such words, but you're telling me to just do nothing?
Wang Ja Rim was the one who said she wanted to meet her first.
She must have her own plan. Just step back for now.
Yeah. There are nasty rumors about me. But that's probably because I'm pretty.
But you’re not pretty,
so I’m not surprised there were no rumors about how you played with Joo Yeong.
It's you guys who made sure of that. Do you think I don’t know you stay quiet because you don’t want that pushover to get hurt?
It's clear, seeing how you haven't told him yet. What? Do you want me to tell him?
No, you don’t need to do that.
- Because I have recorded everything.
- Crazy witch.
It's a lie. Looks like you are actually scared of being found out?
- Ja Rim, are you okay?
- Joo Yeong, did you see that?
- She was telling me not to see you—
- Yes, I saw. All of it.
Still, it's a relief you didn't actually like me. Don’t contact me again.
- Bo Gyeong, are you okay?
-  Wang Ja Rim, are you crazy?
- I'm okay.
- You crazy bitch.
So it's not only your boyfriend you treat like crap, you're a real thug.
Who do you think you are to beat her? Should I report you for school violence?
Your friend hit her first. She’s a total psycho. We heard everything.
What the hell? We saw Wang Ja Rim hit her first.
Don't cover up that kind of thing.
You're defending her even when you saw who hit whom.
As Gong Joo Yeon's friends, you also only care about looks, right?
I usually don’t care about looks. But thanks to you, I plan on doing that as of today.
Appearance and personality are proportionate to each other.
What about you? The ugly ones like you always butt in to look cool.
I know. Look at him wearing brand-name shoes to try to impress.
And who's that dumb-looking beanpole next to him? Are they playing a couple of fools?
I hear this all the time, so it has no effect on me now. And what you just said also includes you two.
You are a... Jeez...
Forget it. It’s not worth fighting with them.
You used "forget it" and also "worth." You've got nothing else to say now, have you?
Jeez, you crazy fool.
Just take her and leave now. It's true she was the first to hit the other.
Then what did we see? We saw Wang Ja Rim was the one who hit her first.
My hands are trembling. She told me she didn’t want me near her boyfriend.
Did I extort money from him or something? He opened his wallet on his own because he liked me.
But seeing him spend his money for another girl, it felt like such a pity.
When it's thanks to me that he gets called a romantic boyfriend.
As soon as I told her I had recorded everything, she hit me.
You told me it was a lie, you crazy punk!
- Wang Ja Rim, well done.
- PotG, right? (PotG: a game-changing action)
- Yep.
Do you hear that? Girls, why don't you say anything?
The atmosphere has suddenly turned cold, right?
Kwak Bo Gyeong, I never want to see you again.
Girls, that was—
Bo Gyeong, I'm sorry.
But we'll get going first.
What's that? It really was Kwak Bo Gyeong's voice, right?
Seriously, this gave me goosebumps. She's a psycho.
A real psychopath. I got the chills.
- Let's go.
- Jeez.
Wang Ja Rim, are you crazy?
- You crazy bitch.
- So it's not only your boyfriend you treat like crap, you're a real thug.
Who do you think you are to beat her? Should I report you for school violence?
Still, it's a relief you didn't actually like me.
They probably won't do that anymore, I guess.
Thank goodness the misunderstandings have been cleared.
Are you okay now?
And you. Are you okay?
Me? Why do you ask?
Uh...
- The thing about her not liking you.
- What?
- What does that matter? It's actually a good thing.
To me, you’re the only one!
It would be extremely complicated if someone else liked me.
And...
I’m sorry I played the recording in front of the guys.
What are you sorry for? You did a good job. That made me feel relieved.
Don't apologize. I should be the one apologizing.
I didn’t know she was like that, and I made you suffer for nothing.
I'll make your favorite cream pasta today! I'll put a lot of shrimp in it
Let's go.
What's wrong with you? This makes me embarrassed.
Ja Rim?
Don't move!
♫ Are you all right?  ♫
I don’t want to.
♫ How are we? ♫
♫ I know this above anything else:  ♫
♫ I love you ♫
Why are you crying?
You aren't okay.
I'm totally fine.
I don't care at all what she used to think of me...
because you're hugging me like this right now.
♫ If you would only stay by my side ♫
♫ Then it will always be paradise, my dear ♫
♫ Let's be together now. ♫
I love you, Ja Rim.
- I think now I know what it really means—
- I know.
to like someone.
No, no. You should say "Me too"! Let's do it again.
I love you!
Do you have shrimp at home? Or Should we buy them?
Come on! Don’t change the topic.
How much are shrimp these days?
I don't know!
Me too.
Eh?
Do you know where to buy shrimp for cheap?
I don't know. What was that? You just replied "Me too", right?
Did it sound like I was answering you?
I don't know.
Me too.
Come on!
Let's stop by the grocery store. I'll buy the shrimp.
Okay.
You thought I'd just let it go, right?
I told you not to tell him but you made him hear everything directly.
But in the end it all worked out.
Are you feeling better now?
You should have thrown one more punch at her.
Because I didn’t want to get my hands dirty.
Eat it. It's your reward.
Ja Rim.
Hurry, let's go to the snack store before the bell rings.
Okay.
Ja Rim?
What? Did Prince just take his hand first?
And at school?
What's wrong with her?
I'm suddenly confused. Is this a dream?
Hey, let's check if it's a dream or not.
Why do you have to check through me?
What's going on? Did something happen?
You're right. What's wrong with our puritan Miss Wang?
Hey, be quiet you guys! Ja Rim is going to bleed from her ears.
Hey, you be quiet!
Okay!
Ghana Mild Chocolate
♫ I'm still the same ♫
♫ What am I expecting? ♫
♫ Am I still waiting, holding onto the lingering hope that you will cone back? ♫
♫ The only things that are still the same  ♫
Love Revolution
I bet no one knows what day it is tomorrow.
It's a special anniversary day created by me just for us.
I'm already screwed from the beginning.
Did you only have eyes for him since back then?
It would have been better if I had liked him from that day.
- This place is very famous but does not take reservations.
- But it's closed.
Geez! What the hell are we doing?
It’s time. H-hour.
Reply, you crazy punks!
Sorry, Darling
All the plans went wrong and today is ruined.
What do you mean ruined? This is just the beginning.
Close your eyes.
♫ The only things that are still the same ♫