Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
- Hey, let's go to the snack bar.
- You already have lots of snacks.
We need to stock up to last until the afternoon.
Are you a squirrel getting ready for winter? Oh, wait, and Ja Rim?
What about Ja Rim?
You already know that I like you,
but I haven't been able to tell you the important part.
Without realizing I might have been afraid to say it.
But, I think I can tell you clearly today.
Do you want to go out with me?
I've been waiting for you to say that.
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't get too immersed in practice. The mood got weird.
Hey. Why are you practicing that, you idiot?
If she likes you, it will work out even if you're not smooth. She doesn't like you, that's why it's not working.
I'm sure she likes me.
After yesterday's meeting, I could see what kind of girl Ja Rim is.
She looks cold on the outside but she is sweet inside, a tsundere.
The fact is the more she seems not to like me, the more she actually cares for me.
What the hell are you on about?
It's true! Yesterday while  she treated me to a meal, she said I was like a puppy.
Aren't puppies adorable? She was looking at me as adorable.
Don't you mean you are like a dog?
Don't tell me.  Didn't  you misunderstood son of a bitch as puppy?
Correct  Answer.
- Damn.
But if Gong Joo Yeong confesses, it's likely to work.   It also made my heart pound.
Why are you getting excited?
Then you two can just date, F***.  You'll make a totally crazy couple.
What a joke.
Noona Jang Hae Ri
(T/N: Noona is used by males for close older females)
Joo Yeong! Why don't you pick up?
Let's go to the snack bar. I'll buy you something.
I'm okay.
I am not okay. Let's go!
- Who is she?
- What's going on? That punk and a girl.
It seems obvious that she's trying to hit on Gong Joo, right?
I can't believe such a delinquent is flirting with a naive boy like Gong Joo Yeong.
She should flirt with me instead!
Love Revolution
Analog Confession
Episode 6
#Again #Once More Again #Confession
kyungwoo @princess_0: Gross.
This Saturday is Rose Day,
(T/N: May 14th,
a day couples exchange roses.)
and there is no way a boy like Gong Joo would just let it pass. I look forward to it, Ja Rim.
Don't look forward to anything. I want to spend at least this one weekend calmly.
With his personality, he is probably preparing a surprise.
- Calmly.
- Are you talking about Gong Joo Yeong?
Actually, He asked me when Ja Rim and I were going to hang out on Saturday.
Don't you think he will be waiting until Ja Rim goes out on Saturday?
- That's why I'm planning on staying home.
- Really?
How disappointing. You should accept it sometimes when he does something for you.
Let us experience it vicariously through you.
If he confesses, maybe you should try dating him for a while.
Am I supposed to date anyone just to please you guys?
Are you going?
- Like it?
- Give me some too.
Give me some too! Give me!
Oh? It's Gong Joo Yeong.
Who is that girl, the one stuck to Gong Joo Yeong?
She must like him.
She is a second-year at our school.
Ja Rim!
Are you going somewhere? I see you're on the way from the snack bar.
If you'd told me, I would have bought it for you.
- Hi!
It looks tasty. Let's go.
- Ah Rong, let's go.
- Yeah.
Okay, tell me.  Who is she?
I have so many women that I don't know who you are talking about.
Did I ask about your relationships with girls?
I'm talking about the girl who was stuck to Gong Joo Yeong before.
Oh, Jang Hae Ri.  She's a second-year at our school.
What's her connection to Gong Joo Yeong?
She has been acting close for several days but I have no idea.
Do I look like a dried squid vending stall?  Don't touch it. I'll rip your hands off.
But does Gong Joo Yeong just allow that?
If it's nothing bad, should he tell her to piss off?
Even so, while he likes Ja Rim, isn't getting involved with another girl a little ...?
Hey. She's coming on to him as she pleases. What do you want him to do?
And what business is it of yours whether Gong Joo Yeong does it or not?
Even if it isn't ours, it is Ja Rim's.
Hey Wang Ja. do you care? You're not even dating.
No, I don't really care.
See. Don't do this to me.  Go complain to Gong Joo Yeong.
But again, does he have any reason to stop someone who likes him?
She says she doesn't care.
You're put in front of a case and have to decide
wether it's an opportunity or a crisis...
Noona Jang Hae Ri: Joo Yeong, want to meet at recess?
Fourth: Crisis management. There's a danger...
Why aren't you replying?
Power-off
Ja Rim, what are you doing on Saturday?
I'm staying home. What's it to you?
No ... because I'm free too, so I thought we could hang out together you and—
I'm busy.
You just said you're staying home.
I'm busy at home
Noona Jang Hae Ri
This noona, really ...
It must be that unni from before?
Did you see her? Ja Rim.
Just in case you might misunderstand, I don't have any relationship with her.
Is that so?
Ja Rim.  You really don't have a misunderstanding, do you?
That's not it. I'm just busy on Saturday.
I'm free on Saturday.
As for me, I am busy.
What are you busy with?
That is ...
You seem like you need to talk.  I'll leave.
No, no. I have nothing to say to her. Wait for me.
What are you doing? The bell rang, go to your classroom.
Ja Rim, do you really have no time on Saturday?
- I think I might.
- Really?
- But you don't have time.
- Huh?  M-Me? Why?
- You're meeting her.
- Why would I?
I have nothing to do with her. Truly.
Don't follow me around for nothing and date someone who likes you.
Then, you should also date someone who likes you.
Me! Hmm?
Hey. The bell rang. We have math.
I don't want to.   I'm not going until you reply to me.
Ja Rim?
Can we talk?
It's okay.  Go on ahead.
Aren't you eating?
You're freaking pretty.
Are you glaring at me like so I acknowledge that?
What do you want to say?
Before that, I need to deal with your eyes.
Can you soften your stare?  I just admitted you were freaking pretty, no?
Just say what you need to say.
Look at her. She's freaking rude.
Is that why you're rudely toying with Gong Joo Yeong?
I don't think I ever did that.
Well, I'm a pro at toying with boys, so I know it when I see it
But you're a bit different, actually.
What should I say? You're one hell of a cow.
Oh my.  Did that offend you? It's too vulgar, isn't it?
Sorry.
So can you please make your position clear so we don't have to see each other too often?
How?
What is she saying? Are you asking because it's difficult or because you don't know?
I'm telling you to reject Gong Joo Yeong in a clear and definite way.
I clearly and definitely reject you.
I reject your rejection. Ja Rim, let me like you.
I really have no realationship with her.
Incoming call: Gong Joo Yeong.
Bye.
Hey, you won't date him anyway. Will you?
That little, seriously. Toying with him until the end.
You don't want to have Gong Joo Yeong but it's a waste to let someone else have him.
F***.  Why am I getting all steamed up instead of her?
I don't know much about this, but are you sure this is how you confess? Is this really the trend nowadays?
This is the least I should do! Ja Rim keeps getting the wrong idea because of Jang Hae Ri or whatever
so I have to make myself clear so there aren't any more misunderstandings.
By the way, why is it 99 flowers? Shouldn't we fold 100?
Kyeong Min told me something, that's why.
You fool, there's a reason for everything. Read a book!
Yeah, read a book.
If you date according to a book, aren't you 100% screwed?
I think going with 100 flowers would be better.
Really?
This is making me think seriously.
Lee Kaeng, what do you think?
Hey, Lee Kaeng! What do you think?
About what?
Weren't you paying attention? What's better, 99 flowers or 100?
It won't matter. I told you at school.
How you confess doesn't matter if she doesn't reciprocate your feelings.
That's why I'm checking her feelings through this confession.
Come on, which one is better?
You really don't plan on dating another girl?
Absolutely not. Isn't that a given? Who else would I date besides Ja Rim?
Jang Hae Ri?
Definitely not her. She's not my type, whether or not Ja Rim is involved.
She stinks of cigarette smoke and keeps linking arms with me.
She's kind of scary and all.
But, you're speaking as if you expect me to get rejected.
It's not like that.
But if Wang Ja has no intention of going out with you,
what are you going to do?
I don't know. I'm not going to think about that right now.
I just want to show Ja Rim my true feelings.
Finally!
I think I can go on a TV show as a master of paper rose folding.
Hey, did you actually contact her?
I bet she'll come out easily.
She will.
It's so good!
What happened? I thought you weren't leaving your house?
I thought about it, and I wondered why I had to be stuck at home because of Gong Joo Yeong.
Yeah, it's not like he's a terrorist.
But did nothing happen when you came out? Gong Joo Yeong wasn't there?
Nope, nothing happened.
Does he plan on doing something when you go back home, then?
He's not the type to sit still on Rose Day.
Ja Rim! Your apartment is on fire! There are firetrucks and everything!
- Hey!
- What is it?
Hey, Gong Joo Yeong, are you serious?
Yeah, I am. I saw smoke coming from your apartment and I came over.
Looks like things have calmed down now, but shouldn't you still stop by?
- Okay.
- Mister!
- Hello, ma'am.
Did something happen here?
One pot burned,
but the firefighters came over and there was such a big fuss.
- I had such a hard time.
- Gosh, I thought it was something serious.
- You can go up.
- Okay, keep up the good work!
Goodbye!
- Kids, you don't plan on using fire, right?
- No, Sir.
- Be careful with fire!
- Okay. Thank you!
Hey, wasn't the fire part too extreme?
No, it's a relief that there wasn't really one. And fire trucks really did come.
You're a lucky guy.
Wang Byeol Rim, there was a fire at our building. Come home right away.
Wow! I see. Anyway I'm sorry, but I'm watching a music show
so I don't have time to watch the fire.
I'm not kidding!
Whoa. Really? What about Mom and Dad?
- They're not picking up, either of them.
- Okay, I'll go right away.
Where's the fire?
Ja Rim.
Your house isn't on fire. What's on fire...
is my heart.
What did he just say?
Is it fun to lie?
The fire trucks really did come.
It wasn't a big deal, though.
Today's Rose Day. Please accept this. It's a hundred roses.
Huh? There's a flower missing. Where is it? It was the prettiest one, too.
I hope you don't plan on saying that Wang Ja Rim is the last rose!
- Hey, stop it.
- Why not?
The last flower...
is me!
- Hey, let's go out.
- What?
- Really?
- I'm just kidding.
How do you feel when you're the one being tricked? Don't pull something like this again.
Ja Rim, what do you mean I was kidding? My confession isn't a joke.
Let's go out. I'll try really hard.
Are you guys making a drama or something?
Is the title "Playing With Fire"?
(T/N: also a metaphor for having an affair)
- Let go.
- No, give me an answer.
I'll give you an answer. I'll text you.
Can't you just tell me now?
In my current mood, dating you is the last thing I want to do.
I'm sorry, ma'am. Please take your time.
Take this one at least.
It's pretty.
It's pretty entertaining.
Yeah, this drama is fun.
Hey, so is Wang Ja Rim
really going to text him an answer later?
- For now, let's go to Joo Yeong's house and see the outcome.
- Sure.
Hey, let us know how it went when you get the answer.
Okay.
Hey, are you going out with your phone?
Yeah, punk. It's only been a few minutes since we got home and you're so jumpy. I'm getting more anxious than you!
Then go home. Why are you guys still here?
How can we miss out on this fun spectacle?
Hey, hey, since we're bored, let's make a bet. I bet 100 won that Gong Joo Yeong is rejected.
Hey, hey, hey. Why are you gambling on a matter of life and death?
What do you mean, life and death? You're so overdramatic.
Give me ramen!
You want ramen?
Hey, you want ramen? Ramen? You want to eat ramen?
You want ramen? It sounds good, right?
Should I make you some ramen? Do you guys want, too?
Who was it?
- Not me.
- Me neither.
It's not me.
So freaking frustrating. Are you dismantling a bomb?
I'll check for you.
Hey! Hey, come on! What did she say?
What?
Hey.
Don't be too shocked.
- Why?
- Wang Ja... said...
To be revealed next week!
Hey, you SOB!
- How dare you pull such an old trick!
- Why would you bring up a joke from January 8, 2014? (T/N: The webtoon episode that this scene is from was released on this date.)
You crazy jerk!
♫ Even if I keep telling myself it’s not real ♫
What the?
Ja Rim, thank you so much. I'll be really good.
I'm so excited, I can't sleep!
- Hey, get your arm off.
- You two look good together!
How's your studying going for the test next week?
- Aren't you going to study?
- I am studying.
Studying you. The rule of Ja Rim.
Happy now? F****, you're freaking clueless.
If you don't like him, break up with him already. What are you doing right now, when you told him yes to dating?
- I don't dislike Gong Joo Yeong.
- Then what?
♫ I like your smiling face the most ♫