Ja Rim, it's really a misunderstanding. That noona isn't my girlfriend.
I heard it all.
You said you dated me because you pitied me.
I was just flustered. I didn't mean it.
I really like you.
I was going to end things with that noona while I was seeing you, but...
- I felt bad.
- Sorry, I don't want to see you anymore.
Ja Rim, you like me too, don't you?
I'll end things and only see you.
Sorry.
Ja Rim, did you not like me?
Were you just acting all along?
I came to you first instead of going to that Noona.
- What more—
- Stop it.
Hey, do you think you can do this to me?
Let go!
I can't believe this. Sh*t.
I wanted to date you for a bit because you're pretty.
Are pretty girls all like this?
You go around flirting to your heart's content, but if I try to hold your hand
then you get frightened.
And you act damn coy.
Do you actually think I dated you because I like  you?
F*cking delusional.
Fine. I must've been a fool for dating you.
What a f***ing load of bad luck.
Even if you may have forgotten everything,
I remember how much of an asshole you were.
How scary.
Our Ja Rim...
You've gotten so much cooler.
Are you really the girl who got all shy when we kissed?
- Who kissed...
- Hey.
Your boyfriend is here.
See you again.
I heard you guys broke up.
Love Revolution: Ruminating. Episode 14. #MissingMyGirlfriend #ButCan'tSayIt #It'sMe #I'mGongGilDong
glasses @princess_0: More like you're talking Gil Shit.
Can you wait for me a bit? Just now...
Cany (sent)
- Crap.
Deleted Message
What? It looks like you'll break up? What does that mean?
- It's exactly as I said.
- Did he ask to break up?
He didn't say that, but...
If that's not it, then why are you saying that? Do you want to break up?
I don't know.
But when I see Gong Joo Yeong, he does things that are similar to that jerk, so I feel uneasy sometimes.
I think I've said this several times already,
but don't put Gong Joo Yeong and Choi Joong Ang on the same level.
How unfair would it be to Gong Joo Yeong?
Who's Choi Joong Ang? It's Choi Jeong Woo. Why do you keep getting the name wrong?
I've never even seen the guy anyway. Choi Joong Ang or Choi Ji Ral. Close enough.
(T/N:  Joong Ang means "center" and Ji Ral has the meaning of "insane.")
Anyway, Ah Ram is right. Gong Joo Yeong and that oppa are different. Why do you want to break up?
But it seems like Gong Joo Yeong will ask to break up now.
What? Is that even possible?
It is.
Then, what do you want to do?  You don't care if you end it like that?
Don't tell yourself "It's not me, so it doesn't matter"
and stay quiet again.
You have to talk for him to know. How can he, if you don't say anything? Is he going to read your mind?
Yeah. Please communicate. So frustrating.
Whatever. I'm done here.
- I'm so frustrated, now I'm starving. Let's go and eat.
- How are you starving from being frustrated?
- Are you not hungry?
- No.
- You are?
- Yeah.
Hey, your bracelet is so cool.
I've had it since middle school. Why are you saying that now?
Hey. Did Buddha tell you to play pool like this?
He said to love your neighbor!
You nutcase. I'm not wearing it for Buddhism.
And isn't loving your neighbor something taught in church?
Buddha probably said something similar too.
But freaking seriously, if you take five points in a row when you're on 120,
then even Buddha would get angry.
If you're going to be like this, then make it 150.
I'm just lucky today. I usually can't play 150.
If you're going to play, hurry up.
Three, two one...
You do it.
That's a real bouquet. Who's next?
Is it Gong Joo Yeong? That's like a freebie right there.
You couldn't even hit that? That's ridiculous.
He's no fun to compete with. Are you rich?
Well, it is good for me though.
I told you I didn't want to play, but you guys dragged me here.
If we hadn't, you'd be shut in somewhere weeping.
At these times estrogen should actively be used.
It's astrenaline you idiot.
It's adrenaline.
You always tell me to stay put.
Ah, right! Are you coming for basketball tomorrow? I heard that hyung will also come.
Hey, don't talk nonsense. Of course, he shouldn't go. Shall we all just not go?
Do you want to get cursed out by those hyungs?
What if they can't play because we're not there?
You guys should go.  You don't have to do this just because of me.
Really!
Its okay.
Yang Min Ji
Hello?
Gong Joo Yeong?
Did you come to play basketball? What's with these clothes?
Are you really going to play?
Then take off your top at least.
- Hello?
- Ja Rim still didn't contact you?
Oh, yeah. Not yet.
You said you know Oppa Choi Jeong Woo, right?
A little bit.
This is something I am telling you so that you don't misunderstand.
They didn't actually date each other.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
Hey Gong Joo Yeong, foul!
Sorry.
It's fine.
- This bastard, really!
- Hey hey hey!
Hey hey hey, don't don't don't.
Leave me.
Have you gone crazy? What are you going nuts for? F*ck you are doing this because of your girlfriend, right?
Did I do something to her?
Ah just because I dated her before, you are flipping out, right?
You're goddam overreacting just because I talked to her, you damn f**ker.
- Hey hey are you crazy? What happened to you?
-Leave me
Sorry! Sorry!
Hyeong, the heat must have got to him.
Look at him, the kind of clothes he's wearing!
He forgot his outfit at home, and his common sense together with it!
You also know that he usually isn't like this right?
- He was playing so passionately that he took himself for Dennis Rodman and—
- Darn it.
Crazy bastard. Don't you see how much you messed up the mood?
Also, no matter how much you hate that hyung, how can you do that in front of the other hyungs?
You aren't going to play with these hyungs anymore?
No, I won't.
This moron came today only to piss off that hyung.
Is this because of Wang Ja Rim? What on earth did  that hyung do?
You always talk loads, but at times like this, you don't say a word.
Anyway, thanks for stopping me.
If not for you guys I would've been smashed by that hyung.
So you do know.
That's a given. You frail little punk.
If he's frail, then what are you?
What about me? What?!
Why suddenly talk about me?
I am going. Sorry for today.
He is not taking responsibility for this mood.
I'll put in good words to those hyungs.
They're close to my brother after all.
Gong Joo Yeong
Sent a picture
Gong Joo Yeong: New message
Gong Joo Yeong: ^^
I'm in front of your house. If you don't come out quickly I'm kissing this.
Ah, you scared me! Where are you going suddenly?
Did I just see Magic Girl Transformation or what?
Who is it? Why so urgent?
A friend.
You mean, a friend who's a boy?
I missed you.
- Good job today Hyung.
- Good play.
Hyung.
Are you okay?
Nah, it's nothing.
Whatever the reason is, I apologize for the commotion today.
Sorry.
Shouldn't Gong Joo Yeong be the one apologizing?
Yeah, he should be.
But there probably won't be a reason for him to see you again.
As long as you yourself don't go and find him.
Do I look  like I would do that?
Wouldn't it be good to end it here, with each of you getting a few punches?
It's only an emotional fight anyway.
If you keep picking fights with Gong Joo Yeong, I don't think I'll stay put either.
He's my friend after all.
- Bastard, is this an apology or a threat?
- Come on.
I am just saying it's like that.
You don't need to worry over nothing. I don't want to have anything to do with Wang Ja Rim either.
Do you know that me quitting school was because of her?
I don't really want to know.
Goodbye then.
You came out dressed so prettily.
I just roughly put something on and came out in a hurry.
So you're this pretty even if you just roughly dress up.
Were you not mad at me?
I did get mad and even worried a lot.
I was so frustrated I thought I was going to go crazy.
Why did you just leave like that? Why didn't you tell me anything?
I had a lot of things to ask you if we could meet like this.
But now that we've met,
the only thing that comes out is that I miss you.
♫ It is difficult for me ♫
♫ Everything feels unfamiliar ♫
I missed you. I really like you a lot.
♫ But nevertheless ♫
Why exactly do you like me?
♫ When I think of you ♫
I like you because you're you.
Even though I talked harshly to you?
Yes.
Even if I purposely gave you a hard time?
Yes. I like everything about you.
♫ I have been waiting ♫
♫ I wished for this very moment ♫
Did you catch a cold?
Dammit. I have a runny nose.
♫ Then it will always be paradise  ♫
Are you crying?
I just yawned!
♫ You can just trust in me ♫
♫ Are you all right?  ♫
I'm sorry.
♫ How are we?  ♫
For what?
For everything.
It's okay. From now on, let's not say sorry anymore.
Let's not do anything to feel sorry for.
Got it?
♫ I will be able to say it now ♫
♫ If you would only stay by my side ♫
Do you want me to tell you?
What?
♫ Then it will always be paradise ♫
♫ My dear ♫
♫ Now let's ♫
First of all, I never dated Choi Jeong Woo.
♫ be together ♫
- I know.
- How?
I can find out about everything.
They never dated. They definitely didn't.
Anyhow, Choi Jeong Woo was a jerk.
Are you listening?
But does Ja Rim know that you're telling me this?
No, but you guys need to clear things.
Then, I'll pretend I never heard anything.
Why? You're misunderstanding things right now.
I never misunderstood Ja Rim.
Thanks for your concern.
Did you tell anyone else?
No. You're the first I told of course.
Don't tell anyone else then.
All right.
Ja Rim: I met with Gong Joo Yeong.
Those two will probably work things out themselves.
Sorry for thinking you two were the same.
It's because you guys acted similarly. The way you talk and act
was too similar to what that jerk did.
So it's true that I dated you with a breakup in mind.
I also thought this incident would be the reason for that breakup.
I didn't want to bring up something I had already forgotten.
I also didn't want you to know...
Hey, are you listening?
I'm not saying any more.
I'm listening.
To sum things up, I'm your first boyfriend then, right?
That's quite a severe way of summarizing things, but that's true.
Honestly, it doesn't really matter.
In terms of how much I like you, I don't lose to anyone.
What? Usually, this is the time when you'd swear at me saying I'm too corny.
- Seriously...
- Oh?
- You smiled!
- I didn't.
I just sighed.
- Oh, Ja Rim, you know what?
- I don't know.
- It's our 100th day anniversary today.
- You even counted?
Of course. I have something to give you.
Ta-da!
This is yours.
And this is mine.
Ta-da!
I don't have anything for you.
I haven't even given you a birthday gift yet.
What? Are you asking me to give it back?
No. I'm asking you to hold my hand. For the whole day.
Why did you just leave that day?
When Choi Jeong Woo came to find me.
That time... Honestly, I was really happy to see you,
but I thought I had to ignore you, considering the situation.
When would I have another chance to do that?
I was having a really hard time trying to hold back my smile.
You really do all sorts of things.
Are you hungry? Let's eat.
All right.
But where did the button on your shirt go?
That? A bad guy stole it. Help me sew a new one on, sweetie.
Laundromats are good at sewing those on. Let's go.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
What are you thinking?
I was thinking about where the laundromat is.
I don't think so. It seems like you were thinking about me.
Right? Right?
What are you saying? You're right in front of me. Why would I be thinking about you?
♫ I'm being sincere ♫
♫ I don’t want to stay as a friend to you anymore ♫
Love Revolution
Hi, birds! Hi to you too, sweetie!
We decided to go on a date this weekend right? Let's just watch a movie.
I'll book the tickets.
What the heck? Did I get hacked?
Just lend me 40,000 won, respected elder brothers!
Yeah, I'm poor as a beggar too.
What's wrong with him these days? He looks like he's been starving for a few days.
Hey, I also like LoL you know!
Then I'll call you this weekend.
Hey, hey! Are you good at LoL?
Ten thousand won per ten minutes.
Stop wallowing in self-pity and just sell a few things on second-hand sites.
- You can just let Yang Min Ji buy you food.
- What?
The hell. It'd be cheaper to go all the way to Italy to eat.
Ah shut up. I've only been receiving things from you all this time.
Thank you Ja Rim.
♫ But you’re the only one for me ♫