Hey, look at this.
Wow, you're good! How come?
Hi.
- You came?
- You cut your bangs?
See, it looks much better.
I know, right. Honestly, you looked like a snotty teen.
Gong Joo Yeong didn't come out yet?
- Not yet.
- Why are you here?
To give his game console back. I can't give it to him at school, right?
- But why isn't he coming?
- Sorry. Something urgent popped up so I've got to go.
Huh? What's that urgent thing?
Awkward
Shall we go wait upstairs? Since I need to return the console anyway.
Shall we?
What the? Where is he?
Ahn Kaeng, you're here? What time is it now?
I'm going first.
Yeah, go.
Hey!
- Don't do it!
Love Revolution: Shy Boy
#not an exhibitionist #sex education time #misunderstanding
prince_rim @princess_0: I'm buying eyes that didn't see that.
- Crazy punk!
Hey Lee Kyeong Woo!
You came early.
- You cut your hair?
- Why? Did your heart skip a beat?
Eh? It was better when your face was half-covered.
You should have covered the other eye and made it balanced.
Your bangs are worse. Grow them quickly and hide your faces.
Seriously.
- Is it strange?
- No, its pretty.
I'm going crazy. Did she see? She wouldn't have seen, right?
I'm not sure. It was brief, but enough time to check it out.
So you think she saw it?
I don't know. Go ask her yourself whether she saw something.
- Can you laugh right now?
- Then should I cry?
I really feel like crying.
- Ah, Hurry up.
- Dammit.
I keep thinking about it and I'm going crazy.
Go to your seat and laugh.
But Gong Joo Yeong was worried. How much did you see?
Hey Ahn Kyeong Min. That's enough.
S-Sorry.
It must've taken three seconds for me to get back to the bathroom.
No, I think it was two seconds. Did she see it in those two seconds?
She couldn't have seen it, right? Right, our eyes met, so she couldn't have seen below.
How can I face Ja Rim from now on?
Where is he going?
And where is she going?
What's going on? Do you need to pee? Go then.
It's not like that.
Yeah, I can't avoid her forever. Let's face it head-on.
What head-on? Seems like you hurt your head pretty badly already. What wrong with you today?
- Where is Kyeong Woo?
- He left first.
Ah right, I have a gift coupon for chicken. Let's go have crunchy chili chicken.
♪ Byeong Hoon's beloved chili—
T/N: chili is a synonym for penis
I...I don't want to go. You guys go.
Why? Chili chicken is super delicious.
I won't eat it. You guys can stuff yourselves with it.
Is this a "try not to laugh challenge"? I'm going crazy.
I don't feel like it either. I just want to go home.
- Then I will eat their shares.
- Then pay that much money as well.
I don't have money. Is chili chicken that tasty?
The fragrance from the chili is so...
I...I...I am leaving now.
Bye.
What is this? Did you guys fight?
It's not like that.
Sweetie... Did you go home safely?
The... The thing you saw this morning, my...
To Wang Darling: Sweetie... Did you go home safely? The... the thing you saw this morning...
Hey, is our top gamer dead? Are you broken?
I know, right? I think my head must be broken.
Oh? Should I give you a head massage or something
so that you can focus well?
Yeah. Let's focus.
I have hypo-tension every morning these days so I couldn't see well due to my blurry—
Who are you waiting for, you fool?
- Hi.
- Where is Kyeong Woo?
- He wasn't here.
He keeps on leaving before us these days.
It's a bit awkward to go just the two of us.
- Shall we go?
- Huh? Yeah.
Since it's hot, let's go without holding hands.
- I think the same.
- Okay.
But it's too expensive.
- What?
- Hey, you know
your friend Bang... What's-her-name? Give me her phone number.
Last time, you said you didn't want to meet her.
No, well... Just give it for now.
Thank you.
What is it?
I don't know. They will take care of themselves.
Hi. I am Lee Kyeong Woo.
What? He contacted you? Why aren't you saying anything?
Be quiet. Be quiet.
For this creative experience activity, you'll have a special sex education class with an instructor from outside the school.
- Since she's not from the school, she's a guest so be good. Okay?
- Yes!
Teacher, into how much detail will she go?
We already know everything we have to know.
Quiet, quiet! Just know that we have to combine classes
because of the schedule. Class 2, come in.
Take seats as you wish.  The sex education teacher will be here in ten minutes so organize yourselves well.
Yes sir.
Hey hey, Mister Gong Joo, what are you doing?
- You should sit next to Wang Ja Rim.
- I'll just sit anywhere.
- Hey hey! Why take that—
- We all know you're together, no need to be embarrassed.
Okay, sit here.
- Hi.
- Yeah, okay.
In order to prevent unwanted pregnancies
when a man and a woman have sexual relations,
we need something, right? It's contraception.
There are many types of contraception.
First, we'll see contraception for men.
We'll learn how to handle and put on a condom.
I will teach you.
I need a volunteer to come up here.
- Gong Joo Yeong! Gong Joo Yeong, Gong Joo Yeong!
- Me, why?
Gong Joo Yeong? Who is Gong Joo Yeong?
Come here.
Okay, now open it and see how it looks.
- Hey, look at him.
- Why is Gong Joo Yeong's face so red?
Hey, enjoy being lovebirds!
Teach, looks like Gong Joo Yeong's ears are going to combust.
Oh Oh! It's absolutely not something to be embarrassed about.
Goodness. Where are you going?
Gong Joo Yeong ran and ran again.
If there was an end to the world, he wanted to run to that place.
But then he suddenly realized.
That he had to go back to the classroom anyway, and he just made it worse by drawing all the attention to himself.
And that he brought the condom along with him.
What should I do? It's not like we can continue to be this way forever.
Lee Kyeong Woo said he wants to have a meal with you?
Yeah. It's all thanks to you. Thank you.
No, it's nothing. That's good.
You also come along. I'll buy.
Why would I go along? You two should eat together.
Is it a bit weird? I thought it would be fine since you guys are close.
Should we meet separately?
Anyway, thanks.
S-See you tomorrow.
Hey, what is this indecent behavior in our sacred school?
Hey, if you leave like this I will never see you again.
Wow, you've got quite the skill  to incapacitate Gong Joo Yeong.
- Can you just leave?
- Why are you like this only with me?
I didn't see.
Lies. We looked each other in the eyes, right?
I only looked in your eyes, but your XX—
Did she just say XX?
Yes, she definitely said XX for sure.
I didn't see Wang Ja Rim like that.
Get lost, both of you.
Hey, I didn't see.
You don't remember? Ahn Kyeong Min covered everything.
- Really?
- Really. And even if by chance
I did see it, will you be like this forever without seeing me?
You really didn't see? You also kept being awkward.
Look at my eyes. Does it look like I'm telling lies?
No.
Let's go.
Actually, she saw everything
Stop playing with your phone. Eat something before.
Huh? Okay.
I'll just finish this one round.
When I look closer, you really seem like a baby.
Ye Seul what do you like about a guy like him?
At first, I liked him because he is handsome, but what he does is cute.
Cute? This small one keeps acting up.
My birthday is earlier. You want to die?
Sorry, Noona.
Cute. Min Ji, is he always this cute?
- By the way, Lee Kyeong Woo. At first, you said you weren't interested in Ye Seul, so why did you suddenly want to meet her?
- What?
It's just that when I first showed him your picture, he said he wasn't interested and left.
Who does he think he is?
Ah, it's because you weren't interested, that you didn't want to meet me at first?
Ah, yeah, I didn't like the picture. You look better in person.
Look at him talk. You make it so obvious that you have many girls.
What are you saying? What girl?
You want to watch a movie at my place?
Then shall we go to the convenience store and buy something to eat?
Okay.
It's 10,500 Won.
Oh! Wait a minute. I have 500 Won.
Ja... JaRim, this...
I...
I have plans at home, so...
Plans at home? B-But...
No it's a misunderstanding Ja Rim.
After that, Gong Joo Yeong developed a habit of
putting his clothes on before coming out of the bathroom no matter what.
Thanks for walking me home.
- No need for thanks. Go in. Text me later.
- What?
When you are being like this, it really seems like you're my boyfriend.
Then let's make it that way.
- Do you mean you want to date me?
- Why do you have to ask that?
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
Love Revolution
If that brat raises his average to 70,
even if you're last, the entire class will be exempted from after-school study. Okay?
Now what should I do?
- Let's start studying.
- Three times six?
Eighteen.
Shall I walk you home?
Then should we go to the station together?
What am I supposed to do if you need after-school class?
"How can I get to Changdeokgung palace?"
How do I go to Changdeokgung?
But why are you guys following me? I don't know such things either!
Hey Lee Kyeong Woo. You put the same answer everywhere and slept, didn't you?
We taught you so diligently. How can you do this?
Ah! Please, let's stop this. Please!
♫  I can do all this and more ♫