Pajama Party Guest Hostel
- Gong Joo Yeong, catch.
- Yes.
- More coming.
- Hey, Hey.
Are you not being careful just because it's not yours?
Gong Joo Yeong (17/ High school student) Moving Today
Just order some delivery food now.
Time attack mode on!
Lee Gyeong Woo (17/High School Student) Gong Joo Yeong's friend
Please stop.
Construction robot preparation complete.
Kim Byeong Hoon (17/High School Student)
- Next person, catch!
- Hey!
Jeez.
There's just the three of us.
Anyway, if anything is broken, one of you is the culprit.
Bull*. It's just clothing.
Hey, this is my favorite outfit. If you're going to do that, go home.
What?  Actually, we could totally be treated to jjajangmyeon and tangsuyuk in exchange for our work today. (Black been noodles and sweet-sour pork, eaten when you move.)
Are you kidding?
- Tang-tansgsuyuk?
Yes.
The cost-benefit ratio is dirty.
Hey. I am taking my first step toward independence by moving out of the nest.
But you kids are just looking for food.
Your parents pay your rent and living expenses. What kind of independence is that?
It's more like life is sweet for you.
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Gong Joo Yeong
What is this?  Did I draw this?
I'm sorry.
Yes.  I'm almost there.  I'm on the bus now.
This stop is Ilsam-dong.   Ilsam-dong.
What is this?  Why does it look like her?
princess_0 (Translation of his name)
Love Revolution:  Every first meeting is mostly fate.
kyungwoo @princess_0: "Actually, no."
ðŸ’ Episode 1 #Moving #First meeting #Fate
- What are you doing?
- Joo Yeong is sleeping.
Wow, you delinquent.  It's 8:30 now.
You're late on the first day of school.
Mom! Why didn't you wake me—
...up?
- Gyeong Woo, wait!
- Come quickly.
Wait a minute.
Gyeong Woo, I need bus fare.
Here.
Balance is insufficient.
Not enough?
Student, don't you have cash?
Ahjussi, can't you just let me ride today? Tomorrow I'll pay double.
How would I know that?
I will definitely ride your bus tomorrow, please?
It's my day off. Get off.
There are people waiting.
I'm sorry.
For two people. Him too.
Multiple fares.
Thank you.
Sir.
Kyeong Woo.  Isn't she beautiful?
Who?
Her.
So?
When we were moving yesterday, I saw her too.
I think she and I have some kind of connection.
- No ... I should grab onto something...
- Got you.
I got you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so embarrassed.
Welcome to Yisam Information High School
There are surely some of you who chose Yeesam Information  High School because you don't like studying.
Now that you are in my class, put aside any of those illusions you have in advance.
Dokgo Moon (45/single)
Joo Yeong's homeroom teacher/school principal
Kim Baeng:  Heol, I think our homeroom teacher is really harsh.
I heard he's like the dean of students. Shiver.
To Kyeong Woo's classroom during break time? Go Go?
Gong Joo: Go Go
There's no shortening of class because it's the first day of school so do your best.
I hope you won't do anything to wear me out on the first day of class.
Jo Yeon Sa (38/single)
Ja Rim's Homeroom teacher
He's sleeping?
Forget it. End of assembly.
It smells like rotten danmuji (picked raddish)! You didn't brush your teeth yesterday, did you?
I collected it all night for you.
Why are you stinking up some one else's class, you ass?
An Gyeong Min (17/High school student)
Alone since birth.
Are you still middle schoolers?
Went to middle school together.
Again? Again?  Hurry, hurry.
- How was it?
- Ah, it's hot.
It feels worse because it was hot.
Wang Ja Rim (17/High school student)
Was grabbed  by the collar
Crazy punk.
Yang Min Ji (17/High School student)
Was hit by the burp
Oh Ah Ram (17/high school student)
Blackbelt holder
You grabbed her by the collar?
- From the first day, you've done something legendary.
- I said it was an accident!
Would Wang Ja Rim agree? It probably looked like you were asking to fight her.
- Wang Ja Rim? Is her name Wang Ja Rim?
- That's what I heard.
Why didn't you tell me in advance that she's in your class?
I was sleeping.
Because of you, the goddess looked at me with contempt.
Hey. But isn't it total destiny?
Seeing her two days in a row, being in the same school and in the same grade.
On top of that, she paid for my bus fare, and I even grabbed her by the collar.
Does grabbing someone by their collar also count as fate?
So are you going to confess with a knee kick?
Hey, listen.  Romance is supposed to start naturally when a man and woman meet by accident.
I heard her name is Wang Ja  ("Prince") Rim and mine is Gong Joo ("Princess") Yeong. A prince and princess.
Isn't that perfect fate?
My romance manhwa (comic book) has already begun!
Shut your mouth! Fate, what a joke. How can you fall in love when you only brushed past her?
I really want to goose you with a shigan.
(aka Finger Pistol, combat technique from the manga, One Piece.)
But we're fated for each other!
Thanks to you I finished unpacking quickly. Thank you.
Stop by my house.  My mom said she would make you some side dishes because you're living alone.
Really? I like jangjorim (Beef boiled in soy sauce).
Jangjorim is my destiny.
Shut up and just accept whatever you're given.
Yes.
What?
She must live in that apartment house.
Look, my house is there, and she lives here.
Total goosebumps. With this, you still say we weren't meant to be?
Red: Joo Yeong's studio - Blue: Kyeong Woo's house - Black: Wang Ja Rim's apartment.
Hey, my house is closer that way.
On top of that, I'm in her class.
Fine.  Then, if we meet again tomorrow at 8:30, it really will be fate.
Look.  Indeed, we are meeting her.  I knew we were meant to be.
Weirdo. You've been waiting for 20 minutes.
You almost made me tardy.
Then later at the snack bar if she buys the same drink, it's fate.
I knew it was fate.  Bananas are white;
polar bears are white, and polar bears like coke!
Do you want to get hit by a polar bear?
What!  When did you get here?
Banan
You don't have to know.
If Wang Ja Rim comes out wearing a skirt,  it's destiny.
Just say if she is breathing, it's destiny.
Hey, how could you rip your skirt already?
Exactly. Isn't that some sort of sign?
Your school life is destined to be eventful.
What are you talking about?  I don't believe stuff like that.
You're here.  Let's go to the internet cafe.
Hey.  Isn't that enough for you to be dating Byeong Hoon?   It's destiny.
- Why are you doing this to me?
- What have I done?
I'm going Mid. Someone come here.
Got it.
As you said, I guess it's not destiny.
- Should I give up?
- Stop whining and focus.
- Hey Lee Kaeng, come in and gank, gank! Now!
-  Push the line.
You are being slaughtered.
You were too late.
- Goodness...
- Let's just surrender.
If my level goes down because of you, what are you going to do?
- Life is more important than games.
- Lee Kaeng, Gong Joo!
A moment ago I told you to enter and gank.
I need to drink some cola, this is frustrating.
Hyung, a coke please.
Order it.
Hey, Hyung. Of course, the coke is on the house, right?
You crazy bastard.
You were simply too scared to take action, so you waited, calling it fate or whatever.
If you really had feelings for her, you should have approached her.
How should I do that though?
I totally ruined my first impression. I don't even have anything to talk to her about.
The bus fare.
Didn't you borrow the bus fare from her?
You've got to pay her back.
Right, there was that. I should get going right this instant!
Do you even know her apartment number?
Can't you just get close to her quickly and help me out?
Why don't you ask me to date her in your place as well, while you're at it?
This dating dummy.
What is that supposed to mean?
With a face like this, I basically have a Ph.D. in dating.
Move it before I smash your head in. Let's just start with the basics.
- Just try and talk to her properly.
- Piece of cake.
I thought it was a piece of cake?
It's awkward because you're always by my side.
Tomorrow, you go first.
- Yes, yes.
- From tomorrow.
Day 1
She's coming. She's coming!
Day 2
Excuse me?
Day 3
Gosh.
Hey! Do you want me to set you up with a guy?
- No!
- You don’t have to answer this fast.
- Won't you see who he is, at least?
- I'm not looking.
- Can you arrange a date for me, then?
- You can't.
- Why not?
- Why would I risk him hating me by introducing you?
You're an asshole! By chance, do you like m—
- Are you crazy? Look at you in the mirror, you'll see why.
- Gosh!
Hey. That aside, I think someone's been stalking me these days.
What? Really?
Since a few days, every morning the same guy follows me.
- Did you see his face?
- Not really,
but he has a bowl cut and wore a red sweatshirt, today.
His height is average.
- What?
- Hey! Wang Ja Rim just told me that she's being stalked every morning.
What?! What kind of pervert would do something like this?
But wait, I follow her every morning and I’ve never seen anyone stalking her.
You're stupid! She's talking about you! She even knows what you look like and how you’re dressed.
A bowl cut and a red sweatshirt.
- What are you doing?
- Ah!  Ahn Kyeong Min.
Wait a second.
What are you doing?
- What? Are you giving this to me?
- Yes! My God! It looks better on you.
What are you doing?
All right. Perfect!
Yeah, it would be perfect if I hadn’t been here.
This is the stalker Ja Rim told us about, right?   Kyeong Woo, what this is all about?
No! I've been following her,  but I'm not a stalker!
What nice and fresh bullshit. That's what a stalker is.
I have my reasons.
I want to pay her my bus fare,  but it's hard for me to talk to her.
You like Ja Rim, don't you?
What? No!
What are you doing?
You can't!  I recommend you give up quickly!
- Why?!
- That scared me!
So you do like her!
But it's a pity. Ja Rim totally dislikes boys like you.
Then, what's her style?
I don't know. She's never dated anyone before.
She's never dated anyone before?
Wow, unbelievable. She's so pretty...
Wait a minute. What the heck?
Then you wouldn't know whether I'm her style or not.
I know that at the very least, she doesn't like people who are as forward as you.
Instead of getting hurt, just quit. I'll be going now.
Who does she think she is?
Who do you think you are?
Did you try to make me a stalker just now?
I mean... about that... Yes.
So disappointing.
Hey!
You need to give back my jacket.
- Hey, wait!
- Hey.
Forget it.
Just pay her back by tomorrow.
- The longer you drag it out, the more difficult it'll get.
- Okay.
Okay. Today I will surely!
Where are you going? Who are you? Why do you keep following me?
Huh? Oh... T-To pay you back.
- Pay me back?
- You paid for my bus fare.
I accidentally grabbed you by the collar that day.
Yeah, that's me.
You don't have to pay it back. It's only 1000 won (~$0.85).
No, I have to pay you back!
Then pay me back.
Here.
Why the envelope? The envelope looks more expensive than the fare.
Um... I'm Gong Joo Yeong. What's your name?
Wang Ja Rim.
Your name is pretty.
I live in a studio just over there. Let's be friends.
Sure.
5 Days Ago
The most fabulous day of my life has been decided, and it won't ever change.
That's the day that I first met you.
My eyes were made to see you, my hands were made to give you this letter,
and my heart was made to flutter for you. I'm sure of it.
We don't know each other well yet, but that's not the case for our names.
Wang Ja Rim, Gong Joo Yeong. These two words, prince and princess, are always paired together.
If it's for you, I will happily become a princess.
To my handsome prince.
Please accept the feelings of your princess...
Love Revolution
Love is all about timing.
Can you tell me your phone number?
- Well, right now is not the time.
- Why?
What in the world is this?
Don't people usually give up at this point?
Except for him...
I do think he's a bit special.
Wang Ja Rim didn't bring an umbrella.
Why would I use your umbrella, you crazy buffoon?
Isn't this Ja Rim's? Doesn't she need her keys?
Hey!
I picked it up on the way here.
Wang Ja (prince) and Gong Joo (princess). Even their names are a perfect match!
Starting from their names, they're a match made in heaven!