Ghana
Mild Chocolate
- What am I doing?
- What are  you really doing?
What is it?
- Go.
- Why?  Is something wrong?
Don't worry about it.
I heard about Ja Rim fighting with Gong Joo Yeong's ex-girlfriend.
Because of them, you and I have had a hard time all the while, right?
Right.
I was the one who did it all.
Hey, what can you say you did? You were busy dating.
What? Do you have a complaint?
Don't sneakily try to take credit.  It's my doing.
- Where are you going?
- The bathroom.  Why?
Just that we're talking and you're suddenly leaving.
Then, do you want me to do it while talking to you?
Please don't say that.
Kaeng! Kaeng! Kaeng, Kaeng!
Kaeng. I have a favor to ask of you.
You're here too.
I guess it's something I shouldn't hear.
Anyway, I was leaving.
- What I'm asking is—
- Is it another surprise event?
What?  How did you know? I haven't told anyone. How can you?
The tone of your voice. It's different when it's to prepare an event than when it's for a game.
What event is it?
It's not her birthday. And it's past your 200 days.
Wow.  Do you remember all of our anniversaries?
You talk about them all the time.
You said "it's been 100 days" on your 100th day and the same thing on your 200th day.
I bet no one knows what tomorrow is.
Because it's our very own special anniversary that I created myself.
When Ja Rim finds out, she is probably going to be so touched. Help me a little, please.
I don't want to! I'm not helping.  I have no intention to! Go back now!
- Where are you going?
- I don't want to. I have to pee!
princess_0
Love Revolution DRAMA
Episode 30
#AnAnniversaryOnlyIKnow #IndescribableSecrret #SurpriseEvent
prince_rim @princess_0: Let's be happy
- Shall we take a picture together? This weekend.
- Why?
My cousin is opening a studio and needs to take pictures to display.
If I bring my friends, he'll take friendship pictures for us for free.
Then pictures of our faces will be hung there.
That's true. What's wrong with that? You're pretty. You should use your face.
I'll get him to take our ID pics for free too. We need it for our IDs anyway.
My cousin is a damn good photographer.
Free ID pics is icing on the cake.
Oh, Min Di Min Di.  Let's take friendship pictures this weekend.
Jin Hui's cousin will take our pictures for free.
Really? Well, sure.
But, just among us?
Who else? Song Hae and Bae Ji?
No. I think Gong Joo Yeong would want to do it if he knew about it.
Oh, the boys too?  I'll ask in the group chat.
Gong Joo Yeong will want to do it for sure.
I know. He'll go crazy about how it's practice for wedding photos and all.
Don't say something like that. He's really going to do that.
Yes! We're practicing wedding pictures for free! Yahoo!
How come you never do something different from what I expect?
I'm happy. Tomorrow we have a date.
The day after, a wedding picture. It's a perfect weekend.
It's not wedding pictures.  It's just a picture.
Why are you even more excited than usual?
Day of the Event
Sorry? It's already sold out?
Yes.  It's a very popular product.
I placed another order, but I'm not sure when it will come.
Yes, I understand.
This is bad news from the start.
- Yes?
- Hey. Where are you?
On the way to the internet cafe. Why?
Great! Ja Rim is near the waterside shopping center. I need you to be with her for ½ hour.
What? What are you doing?
It's been a mess from the start.
I was going to buy a cake but they are all sold, so I have to look elsewhere.
Then tell Prince to come to where you are.
Are you nuts?  Then she will catch on to the event.
Damn. Why me? What about the other guys?
They're at my place, but I think both of them are asleep.
You're the only one who answered. Please, I don't have anyone else.
Never mind.  Just tell her to wait.
Why should I be with her?  Is she a kid?
Time goes more slowly when you're made to wait alone. For sure, she will get mad.
You, you can play that game together. There's that game you both play.
Meet her and do that.
Where are you?  I'll get the cake.
You can't bring it with you anyway.
I'll just pay for it and go right away. I'll tell the others to bring it later.
All right.
Thanks. I'll be there right away.
Okay. I get it.
I'm really sorry. Kyeong Woo will come to you. Stay with him for a little bit.
Huh?  Why Kyeong Woo?
All right for now.
I'll be right there.  I'm really sorry. Yeah.
Why did you come? You didn't have to come.
I was on my way to the internet cafe anyway.
Then go. I'll be fine alone.
No ... well ...
Aren't you thirsty?
That punk ... what the hell is he doing?
What? He prepared something again, right?
No ... I meant, what is he doing that's taking so long?
How many days has it been for you two?
It's 244 days.
It's been a long time. It feels like it was just yesterday he grabbed you by the collar on the bus.
You sound like you saw it.
What the?  I was there too. You didn't know?
I didn't.
Is it that you have poor memory, or ...
that you only had eyes for him since back then?
It would have been nice if I'd liked him since back then.
Right. That's true.
Are you going to take those pictures? What we talked about in the chat group?
Yes.  Aren't you going to do it?
It would be better to leave me out.
What are you saying?
Never mind.
It's time for him to arrive. I'm off.
Bye.
Darling, I'm so sorry.
It's okay.  Why did you run?
No.
If we're going to see a movie, we should eat now. Shall we go?
Okay.
What about Kyeong Woo?  Didn't he come?
- He just left.
- He grumbled a lot, I'm sure.
I'll make today a perfect day to make up for being late.
The first course is a famous restaurant I've found in my research.
This place doesn't accept reservations and—
- But it's closed.
- What?
We are temporarily closed due to interior renovations. See you next week!
It can't be helped.
Are there good places to eat around here?
There's another place I've found. Wait. There's one 20 minutes away.
Twenty minutes to get there? It's tricky if we want to be on time for the movie.
Shall we just eat what is sold at the movie?
But I wanted you to have something nice to eat.
We can eat that next time. Let's go.
Of all days, why is this happening today?
When did I fall asleep?
Dude, wake up!
- Do we have to go out now?
- No.  Not yet.
What the hell are we doing?
I'm spending my precious weekend helping Gong Joo Yeong for his surprise event.
So what did you have planned, sweetie?
Don't call me "sweetie."  It's disgusting.
I guess the movie isn't over yet.
He told us to pick up the cake later.
Then we have time for one round before we go.
The person in front was annoying.  Did he come for the movie or to use his phone?
That's true. But the movie was fun.
I'm sorry.  I should have chosen better seats.
For what? The seats were fine. We were just unlucky with the person in front of us.
I just keep having the worst luck.  Why do these things keep happening?
Even so, that much should go well at least ...
- They're coming down, hurry up!
- Be quiet!
- You're distracting me!
- Now!
New message from Gong Joo
- Go now!
- Be quiet!
New message from Gong Joo
Hey. It's time.  It's H-hour.
You should have listened!
Why haven't they come yet?  I told them over and over...
Get ready when I text you around 4:30!
- Okay.
Hey. It's time. It's H-hour.
What are you doing? Hey. Hello? Reply, you nutcases.
Save me
(T/N: all the messages show as unread)
- Sweetie. I have to go to the bathroom.
- Sure.
Something must not be going according to plan again.
You can get a penta kill here. Do a penta, go!
- That was so close!
- You couldn't even do that?
He's calling.
- It's already that late?
- Yeah.
Joo Yeong, we're on our way.
What are you doing? The movie ended long ago. Don't you check your texts?
We're almost there.
- Where are you guys, honestly?
- Well...
Your place?
Today has already been ruined. Come on, please help me.
Got it, dude. We're setting off.
Let's go.
Gosh, and we still have to get that cake.
Hello?
- You're done?
- Yes.
- Then let's go now.
- Yeah. What?
- Where are we going?
- Follow me for now.
Let's take that bus.
Follow this bus.
"This is a bus."
If you shake that, you're dead.
A stomach earthquake? "I'm hungry to death"?
Take a taxi. I'll give you the fare.
He says to follow him and he'll pay us back the taxi fare.
Darling, I'm sorry.
All my plans fell through and today was ruined.
What do you mean, ruined? It's only the beginning.
What? Beginning of what?
You idiot. Why do you think we came here?
Huh? Weren't we going home?
This is where we first met.
- What became of your habit to attach meaning to everything?
- What?
Actually, I...
[To him, they first met in front of his place when he moved in.]
I guess if I tell her, it'll completely destroy the mood.
Close your eyes.
Open your eyes.
It's a present for our 244th day.
This wasn't part of your plan either, right?
You also knew?
I couldn't figure out why, but you wrote it all over your profile.
♥︎♥︎♥︎ D-Day ♥︎♥︎♥︎ Our very own anniversary ♥︎♥︎♥︎♥︎
Teehee.
I thought you would've prepared something again, so I did something too.
So what is special about our 244th day?
The first time I met you, we took bus 244 together.
You really go beyond anything I can imagine.
- What are you doing, Lee Kaeng?
- Can we go now? When they're like this?
This fool can't catch the right timing! What is he doing?
Ja Rim. Thank you so much. I'm super touched.
I would never have imagined you would have prepared something like—
What's that?
This is something I p-prepared.
I told you not to come!
Enjoy your time together!
I'm the idiot for asking them to do that.
It's been shaken.
This is...
Take them following the numbers on them.
In March, the day I first met you, you were so pretty when you paid for my bus fare that I fell for you.
In April, at the school retreat, I practiced dancing and sang a song to make a good impression on you.
In May, I finally confessed to you and it was a big mess.
But we started to date and I was so happy.
In June, because of my foolish mistake, we fought.
In July, we went on a trip together for the first time and I talked nonsense after getting drunk.
In August, I got to know you better and I was happy I could comfort you.
In September, I was really touched by your heartfelt efforts to make me a delicious lunch.
And in October, we had our unforgettable first kiss.
I was extremely happy and I will continue to love you very much in the future.
I love you, Ja Rim.
♫ Then it will always be paradise  ♫
♫ My dear ♫
I think we must really be a match made in heaven.
I prepared a silver ring. It's a set!
♫ You are my one and only ♫
Darling, why are you crying?
I'm not.
♫ Are you all right?  ♫
Thank you.
♫ How are we? ♫
♫ I know this above anything else:  ♫
If you're thankful, give me a peck.
♫ I love you ♫
A peck, come on.
How the heck can I do that here?
♫ I will be able to say it now ♫
- One more time, one more time.
- Stop it.
Okay. From today on, it's one kiss a day. It's an obligation.
Why would I?
Not you. I'm the one who'll do it.
I don't want to. From today on, it's zero kisses a day. It's an obligation.
I'm going to do it anyway.
I love you, darling.
Thank you to the entire Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Who is it?
Who told you to suddenly appear behind me?
Hey. Are you okay?
Go away.
- Do you like me, Ja Rim?
- No.
Then I guess you love me?
You're so shy.
Thank you to Channel Manager: Klore6
Hey! Look at this, a couple ring and a couple necklace. Aren't you envious?
People would think you've been dating for years.
With your couple ring, couple necklace and idiotic nonsense.
That's true. There's someone else who has been dating for a few years.
- The homeroom teacher is coming!
- He's here, you punk!
Why do I smell class 2 here? Come out.
Sh*t, he scared me!
There's one more.
I apologize.
Thank you to segmenters: pilar_velasquez, cgwm808, josselinelino, aaazmm, hana_860, bianoctua, and Klore6
Thank you to Korean to English subbers: emilyazel, laks_727, cgwm808, ccxkiu, eun_jeong_you,  zohra_29, leehye, anniexsn
Thank you to editors: cgwm808 (Chief), Emilyazel (Translation) and Joysprite
♫ I like you ♫
Love Revolution
♫ I’m being sincere ♫
♫ I hope this song can be our beginning ♫
♫ I don’t want any more breakup songs that sound like my own story ♫
Please stop me if it looks like I'm going to cross the line.
Seok Ho
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com