- It's a draw.
- No, it's in.
Yeah, stop the crap.
What's that? Panchigi?
(T/N: game: flipping coins over by hitting the book they are placed on)
Ah, that? It's panchigi using chicken coupons. They call it chicken-chigi.
All the guys are playing it.
Okay, nice! Thanks for the food!
Gosh, I only needed two more of these coupons.
It's so noisy! Why are you guys like this? Please get caught and have these taken away.
Let them be. They'll get caught sometime.
Do the teachers still not know? The guys in the other classes are all doing that too.
If we also get scolded because of them I will get really mad.
Oh, okay, nice!
- Your boyfriend doesn't play that?
- He probably doesn't. If he's thinking straight.
What if Gong Joo Yeong is also like that?
I think I'll start to dislike him if he also plays that—
Hey, Ahn Kyeong Min! Prepare to cough my twenty coupons back up.
Did you start disliking him?
Oh Ja Rim! One minute!
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Love Revolution: Ram's Fleeting Glory
Episode 22: #Chicken-chigi #Gambler #TheDescentOf #Tazza
kyungwoo @Arong_fighter: Share some of your winnings...
No wonder you were sending fewer texts than usual. Is this what you were doing?
- Were you looking forward to my message?
- No!
Also, where did you get this?
I borrowed this from Kyeong Woo—
Uhm, this... don't worry.
Once I win my coupons back from Ahn Kyeong Min, I'll repay everything at once.
Look at the way you're talking. It's no different from an addict.
Right. I am an addict.
A Ja Rim addict.
Hey. I'm not in the mood to crack jokes, you know.
Just for today. I'll only play today.
If I don't repay Kyeong Woo his coupons by tomorrow, I have to give him three game items.
What if you lose more this way? Then you either end it with this game,
or end it with me!
I got it.
- Gosh.
- How is he so good?
What will you do? You lost everything.
Can you lend me ten more again?
- Not for nothing. Put up collateral.
- Collateral?
Write your name and the item you'll put as collateral here.
Do we have to go to this extent?
Of course. How can I trust you enough to lend to you just like that?
Admitted. Are strength stones okay?
Do you have some between levels 81 and 89?
Yisam Information HS
MaKaengPo Lee Kyeong Woo (moneylender)
Number of coupons in possession: 120+
Coupons loaned: ca. 150
- Gosh!
- Nice!
- Hey, I also want to join.
- Okay, come in, come in.
What? You also want to join?
How do you play this?
Do you even have a coupon?
- This?
- If you want to join, come. It's a "one-in" game anyway.
(One-in: Beginner's match where each bets only one coupon.)
Here we go, we got one more dupe joining the game.
- What the? You're also playing "one-in" games.
- Let's decide who goes first.
Not playing is losing. Rock, paper, scissors!
Well, everyone starts by donating, after all. Getting into debt on the way.
- Then these are all mine, right?
- Huh?
- Yeah.
- Wait, what are you?
One Bang... She's One Bang Man!
One Bang: Flipping everything at once.
That's going too far. Does this make any sense?
Hey, did you hear that? There's a girl in class 3 who's winning all the coupons.
Yup. I heard she takes it all as long as she goes first. One Bang Man has appeared.
Oh shit. I'm never playing her.
Five chicken for today's lunch...
It's her.
Oh Ah Ram, Oh Ah Ram. Help me out just this once, okay?
I got those from Kyeong Woo by putting my game items up as collateral.
Save me just this once, okay?
Lee Kyeong Woo? Collateral?
Huh? Yeah. Lee Kyeong Woo has more than 200 coupons.
More than 200? Twenty chickens!
Hey. Where's Lee Kyeong Woo right now?
Yisam Information HS
One Bang Man Oh Ah Ram (One shot one kill)
Number of coupons in possession: 122
Lee Gwang Ju, ten coupons. Yang Ju Yeong, eight coupons.
Let's see...
You got a lot.
Since you're going around taking all those, my business is doing great.
- What are you doing?
- Let's do a "20-in" game.
(20-in: Expert's rule where each bets 20 coupons.
We're playing with the one-on-one rule.
(One-on-one rule: Playing 1 vs. 1, with three main coupons on the board.)
We can't play against each other! Don't you know we should help each other? There's an unspoken rule here.
Are you scared? Afraid you'll lose everything?
Let's go for thirty coupons.
Okay, I'm putting five coupons for the next game.
Okay, this is all mine.
Hurry up and play.
You guys are all dead today.
Why can't you do this, seriously?
- Hey.
- No but—
- Oooh!
Uhm, Ja Rim...
Hey, where are you going?
Where are you going?
Ja Rim. I'm sorry, I shouldn't have done it. I won't play again, forgive me.
Why is this so hard to stop?
What are you going to do in the future if you're this weak to addiction?
In the future? So you're worried about my future. As though you're going to marry me.
Hey. Why would the topic change to that? You're trying to sneakily skirt around it again.
No, don't worry. I'm not addicted. This is also all for you—
What the hell are you saying? You want to feed me chicken using this game? No thanks.
No but, before, you said...
Huh? Why is Bonajour on here?
- What's that?
- The makeup brand I use.
It says they'll give me a Bonajour set if I collect 30 coupons from '232 Chicken'. What a random collaboration.
Really? But why with 232 Chicken...
Exactly. How funny.
But, is it okay for you to use cosmetic products? You said you have sensitive skin.
I use their moisturizer.
I like their Green Tea Water Bomb but it's hard to get.
What. I just said that in passing but you actually remembered?
Of course. I remember everything you say.
If you were my teacher, I would probably be the top student in the school.
Anyway, that's why you did that?
Yeah. It turned out to be kind of fun,
so I might have become a little addicted.
But it's too bad. I was winning everything on that game just now.
- Rock, paper, scissors, set shoot!
- Darn it.
Sure enough, the rumors about her being One Bang Man weren't for nothing.
If she goes first, Oh Ah Ram wins no matter what.
Instead, if I go first, I have a chance to win.
- Rock, paper, scissors, set shoot!
- Oh, sh...oot! Hey, won't you do it right?
Sorry, sorry. My voice grew louder because I was excited.
- Damn, what a crook.
- That was wrong.
- Good game.
- Fucking bastard, what did you do?
Hey, I just used my head. You can't play games if you're dumb.
You should use that great head of yours to study.
Whatever. Keep your boyfriend under control first.
Gong Joo Yeong's not doing it anymore. And he actually had his reasons.
He's not like you.
I'm even seeing Wang Ja Rim defend Gong Joo Yeong?
Am I dreaming?
What's his problem...
Gong Joo Yeong's not doing it anymore. And he actually had his reasons.
He's not like you.
I'm hungry. Let's eat quickly.
- Do you want chicken?
- What? We said we'd go to the popular place I found.
Did we? I won a lot of coupons today, so let's have chicken.
Ye Ye Chicken, Gunnae Chicken or 232 Chicken? What do you want?
Well, whatever you want.
Okay then. Let's go to Ye Ye Chicken. I've got many of their coupons, so I have to use them.
Noona, what's wrong with you today?
You're acting weird. Did something happen?
I'm tasting the bitter aftertaste of defeat.
Wow. You can lose at something? Was it those gamers' IRL fight?
Who did you fight with? A guy?
Shut your nonsense. Why would an athlete fight?
You're dead.
Damn it! I can't do this.
For a long game, I need to be able to flip just one at a time.
So you lost at panchigi? What's the big deal?
You try losing 12 chickens.
Should I teach you? I'm the ace in my school.
If there were a nationwide competition for this, I would take gold.
Really? Try it.
Sh*t! Hey, how do you manage to flip just one?
I can do them all at once, but not just one.
Look. It's a game of refinement. If you have to flip this one here,
you pick the right position and, rather than power, use a clean tap.
Control your strength! Look at my hand carefully.
Damn it!
Why do you keep using your strength? You don't get it at all.
Do you want to get hit with that strength? Speak nicely.
Why are you threatening me? Whatever, I'm not teaching you anymore.
- Teach me please.
- No.
Hey.
Lee Kyeong Woo. Let's have a revenge match.
What, you want to lose again? I don't like to knock a weak person's mental state down.
- I don't want to be hated.
- Don't you know about the courage to be hated? Shut up and let's decide who's first.
I was going to protect your last bit of pride, but well. Deal.
- Rock—
- Not playing is losing, rock paper scissors!
From now on, if you don't put anything out then I'll assume you lose and go first.
What's this? Her vigor is completely different from yesterday.
- Rock, paper, scissors!
Fighting, go for it!
Dammit, it's freaking cold.
Two, four, six, eight.
Here you go. I've repaid my debt now.
Yes, thank you.
Nothing's changed. Oh Ah Ram can still do 'one bangs' only.
It's getting tiresome. Let's finish things off quickly.
Hey. Looks like this won't finish today. What about an 'all-in' for this round?
What nonsense is that? You don't even have half as many as I do.
This is my ledger. I have over 200 coupons loaned to the others.
I'll make it my duty to get them all back. Deal?
Deal.
- It's an all-in game!
- How many are there in total?
Isn't it 400? This is crazy.
My coupons are probably in there as well, right?
I figured out your pattern.
Oh Ah Ram putting out a fist on the first round has a probability of 80%.
I suffered huge loss until now just to check this,
but let me turn things around with this one game.
Even if she puts out scissors, I can insist we're following the 'muk-jji-ppa' rule.
You dunce, who only knows to use one-bangs will be finished in this fight of probabilities.
Not playing is losing, rock paper scissors!
I won. I can flip four coupons maximum.
Oh Ah Ram. You'll do a one-bang for sure.
Then on my turn I just have to flip over four of them.
The victory of refinement.
What was that just now?
- Wow, this, this!
- Incredible!
As expected of you. To think that you're repaying the humiliation like this.
What? How did you do this? Weren't you unable to flip them over one by one?
What are you, how did you do it?
What's wrong with you? So undignified.
Kyeong Woo. Want me to lend you some coupons?
You're supposed to perceive the feeling for this.
But I have no way to teach that to you, it's frustrating.
A way?
- Stand up.
- Why?
Stand up. Sit down here.
Give me your hand. Hit it while holding my hand, so you can communicate the feeling to me. Come closer.
One...
Okay. So it's this kind of feeling.
Whoa, it's amazing.
- Wow.
- Whoa, that was...
The news leaked!
Give this.
Give it to me!
My calculations were perfect. What was that smile earlier?
Was it her plan? No way, that makes no sense. How could a muscle piggy like Oh Ah Ram design a plan?
Green Tea Water Bomb
- Oh, what's going on? You bought a new one?
- I didn't buy it, it was given to me.
Ah, it's the one you use all the time, right?
But you said it was all sold-out. Where did you get it?
Gong Joo Yeong got it for me.
Whoa, really? He's such a sweet loving boy.
- I'm so envious.
- Don't touch it.
Why? You've got three.
You've been using this a whole lot without me knowing, haven't you? The ones I bought before were out in no time.
Come on. Let me use just this one. I have to use this if I want my makeup to apply well.
Just buy your own. I don't even have enough for me. Buzz off.
- Hands are faster than eyes!
- Hey! Bring it back!
Five, four, three!
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
Love Revolution
Awesome! I won!  Go for a double date with Bang Ye Seul?
Four of you? People like you would like to hang out only the two of you, right?
I can hold hands with Ja Rim to my heart's content, link arms, and when we're in front of the merry-go-round we'll ki—
It's annoying. How did things become this way?
Whoa, then what about your progress?
Right, we can't not speak about this!
We did kiss.
- Ohhh. When?
- Where?
You also want to do it?
I'll give you three seconds.
- Three.
- What?
- Two. One.
♫ I miss you so much!  ♫