Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
- I'm washing up first.
- I put my foot in first!
Unni, you need to learn to give in to the younger one.
How convenient for you to treat me as an older sister at times like these.
- Let's do rock, paper, scissors.
- Rock, paper, scissors!
Don't you dare let water splash on the toilet seat!
My butt got all wet again yesterday!
That's right. The love letter was a little impulsive. It's actually a relief that she didn't see it.
Love...
is about timing.
Love Revolution: "Giving up" is just for counting cabbages.
kyungwoo @princess_0: Give up... (TN:"Give up" is the homonym for counting unit for cabbages.")
Episode 2 #White Day (T.N. when men give women candy) #Confession #Candy
We see each other often nowadays.
It's because our homes are close.
Hey, I'm blocked here.  Can you solve it for me?
Wow, you've reached quite a high level.
Wow, that's how you do it?
Don't talk to me. This is a hard part.
Hey, there's a bomb here.
- It's done.
- Thank you.
Do you play Daijo? I'll let you win  a round in exchange.
I don't play that.
Hey, Ja Rim.
Will you let me know your phone number?
- We haven't been able to get each other's numbers yet.
- Sure.
Did you know it was White Day today? I prepared it for you.
Look in the bag too.
Don't talk to me.  This is a hard part.
Here.
What about your number?
The bus is here.
Okay. I'm halfway there.
Halfway where? Is that the thing you prepared?
It's White Day, how could I just let it pass? Hey, the bus!
Mister!
I'm too happy!
Put them down. They're not yours.
I won't eat them.
As expected. I knew you'd receive some.
There's more here.
Amazing. There's so many.
Gong Joo Yeong is so pitiful. He doesn't know you don't like sweets,
nor does he know you won't eat them.
How did you know it was Gong Joo Yeong?
Huh?
That's... Didn't you tell me?
I didn't tell you.
How do you know Gong Joo Yeong?
- What did you mean by you knew I'd receive some?
- Hey, wait a second.
- Why are you being like this to me?
- Hey, it seems he must really like you.
He only picked out and bought the most delicious ones, strawberry and chocolate. He's so—
not devoted.
At the bus stop, I poured lollipops on top of her head.
Hey, you're screwed.  Come quick.
- Huh?
- Quickly, quick!
- What?
- I slipped up, sorry.
That worked out well. I was going to confess to her anyway.
Now I can tell her frankly.
Right now isn't the time.
She doesn't intend to date anyone.
Why? Why doesn't she intend to date?
Because... uhm.
That's... I don't know.
- Anyway, until I give you the signal—-
- Then you don't know.
This is all for you...
With Ja Rim's personality, you'll be ignored now.
Why?
Oh, Ja Rim!
I didn't get your phone number this morning.
But,
is Ja Rim avoiding me?
Don't get too shocked.
Then, I can just approach her!
Don't get too not shocked either...
07:02 AM
Wow, you came out early today?
How long has he been waiting here, seriously?
Since around 6 a.m, I think? Yeah.
I wasn't asking you. Will you not talk to me?
I fell for you.
What are you doing?
You said not to talk.
I'll split you in half.
Wow, you're playing along! (TN:  They were both signing homonyms for what they wanted to say).
Then,
could you give me your number, please?
♫ 01065218066 ♫
♫ Please call me on this number ♫
♫ Please call me on this— ♫
- Hey!
Give me a break.
Then... ♫ 0, 1, 0—♫
I said stop!
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
- I'm okay.
- Let me see.
What's your number? (upside down)
What's your number?
Hey Lee Kyeong Woo. You give him my number.
- Okay. Hey. I'll send it to you.
- Hey, don't send it!
- It's the same whether you receive it from me or her.
- It's different.
- I said it's the same.
- I said it's different.
Hey. What can you do if she is this hell-bent on not giving it to you?
- You should know when to give up.
- Give up? Give up?
"Giving up" is just for counting cabbages.
(T/N:"giving up" is a homonym for the counting unit for cabbages.)
I sent it. Whether you save it or not is your problem.
This jerk, I said I'd get it myself, darn it.
Alright. Tell me about your symptoms.
I can't express this with words.
Then express it with your body.
When I just think of that girl, my chest feels tight
and my heart bounces.
I feel like I'm going crazy.
Your symptoms are much more serious than I expected.
As I see it, your ailment right now seems to be this.
Don't be shocked.
Bullsh*t disease
Doc! You're being too much to a sick student. What happened to the Hippocratic Oath?
The Hippocratic Oath? Do you know about the Fibbocratic oath?
It's "I swear to make unwell the one who fibs about being unwell." I should just!
Doctor! How can you do this to a sick student?
Please give me some sort of medication or something.
Alright, just a moment.
- Here.
- A ruler?
Go, quickly. Are you not leaving? Get going!
Will you please not talk to me?
Let's date.  (T.N. He's signaling 4 "sa" -ear "kwi" - ruler "ja" = sakwija/let's date.)
Hey. It's raining outside.
That's right, like my heart.
Stop bullsh*tting and listen up. Wang Ja Rim didn't bring an umbrella.
So what?
- That's right. We can just use an umbrella together!
- That's right.
- Lend me yours.
- Why mine?
You're going to the internet cafe with the others anyway. You can share with them.
- Genji is with you.
- Hanzo at your service.
Kyeong Min: Genji / Byeong Hoon: Hanzo  (T/N: Overwatch characters)
Oh, but what if her friends also have umbrellas?
- I don't want to.
- Hey, you thought of it. You have to be responsible all the way.
Damn ...
Darn... the rain will probably stop later, right?
Use my umbrella with me. I knew you wouldn't bring one, so I prepared for us three.
Let's have a look.
Huh? I definitely packed it though. What is this?
- Do you not have it?
- No.
Don't worry, because I have an umbrella too.
Right here! Tada!
Huh? It was here, but it's not anymore!
Hey! Which jerk stole the umbrella that was here?!
Shall we just get a taxi?
It's fine. The bus stop is only a short walk ahead.
Go.
Shall we use the umbrella toge…?
Hey, Wang Ja Rim!
Okay.
- It's you then, the umbrella thief?
- Bag.
Ah Ram, go.
Round 1: Ah Ram VS. Kyeong Woo
Fight!
Will you approach? Or should I go?
Hey. We can just use it together.
I said I don't want to.
- At this rate, you'll catch a cold.
- Never mind.
- Oh! Wait!
- K.O! (Knockout)
Oh, nosebleed!
Hey!
Oh no.
Ouch, oh my goodness.
Get a hold of yourself.
Hey, hey, hey.
I get it, so just use this and go.
I won't bother you anymore.
Why would I use your umbrella, you crazy jerk?
I'm saying just use it! You'll catch a cold.
I don't want to!
Seriously, you're so stubborn.
Hey, won't you bugger off? Why would you follow me here?
I'm just avoiding the rain for a moment.
Is that not an umbrella in your hand? You can just use that and go.
It was thrown to the ground so many times, it's ruined now.
Mind your business and go home.
Code keypad out of order
Oh!
- This is Ja Rim's.
- Shoot!
Excuse me... if you're cold, would you like to go wait for a bit at my house?
You can charge your phone, too.
Are you crazy? Why would I go there?
- Hey, at this rate you'll catch a cold!
- I'm fine, so go.
You're bothering me.
I'm going, I'm going! Whether you catch a cold or not, do what you want.
So good.
- It's good, right?
- So good.
That's right. Since I made a mistake toward you girls, it's my treat. I'll treat you...
but what are you guys doing?
- The most unseemly thing to do is complain after you offered to pay.
- Right, you spend money and get cursed.
I said I'm not buying for you guys!
- It's uncool, Kyeong Woo.
- It's thoughtless.
Don't we need to go give her the keys?
- Would that be disturbing them?
- Disturbing? Disturbing what?
Ah, don't tell me...
Oh my! I don't have a key!
Dear me! There's no one at home.
What? That means you can't go home despite all this rain...
I'm cold and hungry.
Won't you be catching a cold at this rate?
What to do? Then, Ja Rim,
come to my house.
- Hey!
- What the heck.
No, it's nothing.
What? Why?
I picked it up.
- Why did you come?
- I was worried.
Isn't that obvious? Your face is pale.
At this rate you'll really catch a cold.
What about you? Aren't you cold? Do you not have an umbrella at home?
That's right, I don't have one.
I must have not packed it when I moved.
Quickly, at least dry your hair.
Let's go, to your house.
Hey. Are you not coming?
Wait here for a bit.
Wear this.
I'll wash yours and return it to you.
What are you doing? Put it on. You have three seconds.
Okay.
Drink it. Three, two, one.
- Go now. Three, two—
- Okay.
Hey.
If you catch a cold I'll kill you.
Ja Rim's scent...
You're back?
Unni, was the person in the lobby your friend?
-Has he not gone yet?
--He's gone.
But... that's my hoodie, you rude-ass witch!
Love Revolution
- Have you decided what to do for the retreat?
- Retreat?
What the hell are you doing?
- These punks say they'll participate in the talent show at the retreat.
- Of course we will.
It's an opportunity to appeal to Ja Rim.
Wang Ja Rim says she has zero interest in you.
Dammit, I almost forgot...
Will you marry me?
Wow, how sweet!
Everyone, raise your hands above your head! Close your eyes!
Open your bags and wait.
I didn't bring it.
They're going to check again?
Hey, we don't need to. Looks like it was Gong Joo Yeong.
♫ I like your smiling face the most ♫