Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
- What? I'm busy.
- Doing what?
- I'm getting ready to go out.
- Really?
You didn't forget!
- Forget what?
- We said we would meet today.
- Did we?
- On the day we came back from the valley, we said we had to meet.
I'm pretty sure I said I would see.
No, we have to meet today.
I really can't. I have plans today. I have to go help Min Ji and Ah Ram.
With what? What do they need help with?
They have to clean the school because of their volunteer hours.
- If we have to meet, let's just meet tomorrow or something.
- But it has to be today...
I'm hanging up.
Love Revolution: On the day I miss you.
Episode 12. #AllOfASudden #ADate #ForReal?
princess_0 @prince_rim: Ja Rim, I love you today too.
Wang Ja, you don't have to come today.
I'm in front of your house now!
What did you tell Min Ji again?
Don't worry, I sent replacements.
The replacements are you guys?
What's with that reaction? Who else could Gong Joo Yeong send?
It's just that he said he was sending Byeong Hoon.
It was my fault for being at the internet cafe with him. Hey, will you treat us to a meal if we help you?
- We will, but...
- Didn't Gong Joo Yeong promise to do something for you?
There's no way you two would come here if you're not getting anything out of it.
Oh, that...
This is just how loyal guys are. But where's Ahn Kaeng?
Hey.
What the heck are you doing this early in the morning? Disgusting.
Whoa, you're seriously doing all sorts of things now.
Now that it's vacation, you're doing crazy sh*t. Who would've expected to see Ahn Kyeong Min like this?
Did you actually spend money on that wig?
You can't even use it when school starts, so why are you throwing your money away like that?
Just shut the hell up. If I get a girlfriend before that, it'll be worth it.
- You won't get one.
- He's the type girls hate the most, isn't he?
That's just your preference. While I was coming here, the girls' eyes were already...
glued to me.
Aren't you hot? Hurry up and take it off! I can't breathe just looking at you.
You'll get all that taken from you.
Seriously, why are you picking a fight with me when I'm trying to be a bit more awesome?
- Who in the world are you talking about?
If anyone takes it away from me, I'm going to report it to the office of education.
No one can stop me now.
Oh, Mr. Dokgo Moon! Hello!
That seriously looks horrible!
- Oh, Joon Yeong! You're here!
- Hi,  Hyung.
This hyung is the boss here. I always buy my clothes here. This is my girlfriend.
- How pretty.
- Hello.
Hi! Hey, you punk, why haven't you been coming? I almost forgot your face!
I've been shopping online lately.
You are contradicting yourself.
- Don't you know I run an online shop too?
- Oh, really?
I didn't know. Since when?
Wait a moment.
Are you tired already? Don't you like shopping?
It's tiring so I just choose clothes quickly.
All right. I'll pick really quickly too.
- How is it?
- No good.
Give me more sincere comments.
You look like a carrot.
Carrot?
How about this?
You look like a Monami pen.
(T/N: Monami is a Korean stationery brand)
How's this?
It yells out, "Come to our correctional facility"!
What? I'm giving you comments like you asked.
Even so, you're speaking so brutally. My feelings are hurt.
♫ On this night when the darkness thickens ♫
- Here.
- What?
What? Try them on.
♫ Yes, I know very well it won’t ring ♫
♫ But tonight, for no reason, I find myself waiting ♫
I've come out.
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
Not bad. It's cute.
Yeah, it's cute. It's perfect for me.
My sweetie indeed has amazing fashion sense.
It seemed like it would look good on you.
Thank you, Ja Rim.
You said you were thankful. Move it.
What about Ahn Kyeong Min and Lee Kyeong Woo? Where did they go?
They said they were going to clean the mop. Are they not back yet?
What's with them?
If they're going to slack off, then they shouldn't have come to help.
- Where are the other plants that need to be watered?
- The infirmary and the school office.
Okay.
Here you go, your tiramisu and frappe.
Thanks.
I'm treating you because you specially chose my clothes for me today.
How is it? It's delicious, right?
Yes, it's flavorful.
Ja Rim, did you listen to IU's latest album?
No.
- Then, what singer do you like?
- Pink Floyd.
Is that a singer?
I see, that's a singer. I don't know him.
- What dramas do you watch?
- Stranger Things.
- Oh, the American TV series!
- Japanese.
(T/N: "Tales of the Bizarre", long-running Japanese series)
Isn't it an American series?
- Hey, so—
- Ah!
- Hey, what are you doing?!
You startled me! What were you doing?
You overreacted. I'm all wet now.
Hey, it's your fault for startling me! What were you doing here?
I was lying down for a bit. Taking a ten-minute break.
Everyone else is working while you're shamelessly resting. If you were going to do this, you shouldn't have come at all.
Don't be nagging me so much when I'm helping out of my goodwill. You'll get all the volunteering points anyway.
Okay, thanks. Ah, but what were you going to ask me earlier?
Whether you gave your number to Sang Hoon or not.
No, I didn't. How's that any of your business?
Come on, just give it to him.
- Or do you want me to give you his?
- I said forget it.
What the heck? Is he that unlikable? You're putting up one sturdy iron wall here.
Why are you behaving like Wang Ja Rim?
Freaking annoying.
Which mic has the best vision among all—
A microscope.
Ah, you know it.
Then, what is the reason why GD shouldn't do a headstand?
Because he'll be a Dead Guy.
(T/N: DG sounds like the slang for "die")
- Want to die?
- Ah, so you know it.
Then, what is it when you fall down on the left side?
I don't know.
A downfall. Look. Down-fall.
- And—
- Is this funny for you?
But I don't know what to talk about with you.
I heard that a good relationship is actually when you feel comfortable even if you have nothing to say to each other.
Then, are you not saying anything because you're comfortable being with me?
I'm not uncomfortable.
When it's just the two of us like this, it feels like we're really dating. Right?
Are we fake dating, then?
That's true.
Then where should we go now?
It's hot outside, so let's stay in one place.
Why? Sweetie, can you do as I ask just for today?
Why should I?
Well, that's because it's our first date.
Is it a date only as long as I do as you want?
That's true. You're always right.
Ja Rim, look at this.
You nutjob, where did you get this? Was it Min Ji again? Give it to me.
If you do me a favor.
- Want to die?
- Not today.
- I'll give it to you if you catch me.
- Hurry and hand it over. Hey, you're done for!
Ta-da! I have another one.
Hey! If you aren't going to work properly I'll just sweep you out of the school building!
- Okay, we'll work, just one minute!
- We're really done in one minute, just a sec!
Hey. What's more important, the game or your life?
Get up. Stand up.
Hey. I shouldn't have said that earlier.
But if you don't feel like dating him, that's all. Why did you get so angry?
Drink this.
♫ I like your smiling face the most ♫
♫ But the picture you posted today, where was it taken? ♫
♫ Why does it make me so anxious when you are somewhere I’m not? ♫
♫ I like you  ♫
♫ I'm being sincere ♫
♫ I hope this song can be our beginning ♫
♫ I don't want any more breakup songs that feel like my  own story ♫
So what are we going to eat?
Can you buzz off? I'd be embarrassed to eat together with you. Don't you agree?
Yes, totally.
Hey, take this wig off. Am I supposed to be able to eat anything while looking at that hair?
Absolutely not, never.
Hey, as if that'd stop you from eating.
- Hello, Teacher.
- Hello.
I told you not to joke aroun—
Hey, Ahn—
- Ahn Kyeong Min.
- Yes.
Make sure you return to your original look by the start of school.
Yes, Sir.
- Here.
- Move it.
You paid for everything today.
You don't have to do this. All the things we did today were things I wanted to do.
- Do you have a lot of money?
- Yes, I do.
- I'll treat you at the next place.
- What? Where else do you want to go?
For dessert.
Have you seen the time?
Sorry. It's because I was too happy today.
Let's go now.
We're already here. What a pity.
We've been together all day, so how is it a pity?
Take care on your way back home.
Whoa, are you being worried about me?
Just go home.
Ja Rim.
Before I go...
What is it again?
Uhm... that is...
If you've got nothing to say, I'm leaving.
Just once!
Can you...
Hug me just once?
What the...?
For my next birthday, it'll be a peck.
Go in safely.
Don't tell me it's your birthday today?
Yes.
One hour ago
What? It's Gong Joo Yeong's birthday?
Yes. He told us not to tell Wang Ja Rim no matter what, so we didn't.
But you're just out here? You won't do something for your friend?
Letting him be alone with Wang Ja Rim is his present. What else should we do for him?
And we decided helping you guys out would replace getting him a present.
But still,
- you should get him a cake at least. I don't understand you guys.
- I agree.
I'm the one who doesn't understand you.
The one concerned decided on that, so why would we do anything more?
I agree with Ah Ram.
When you guys forgot about my birthday—
Then let's go quickly. We need to buy a cake first.
- Okay.
Okay. With seventeen candles.
- Stop eating, girl.
- Ah wait, wait, just that one bite.
Why didn't you tell me?
I was afraid you'd feel preoccupied by it.
Today is your birthday, but you spent the whole day with me?
What about a cake? And seaweed soup?
(T/N: seaweed soup is traditionally eaten on birthdays.)
It's fine.
I don't even have a present for you.
I already got a birthday present from you.
You got one? What was it?
You bought me food, spent the entire day with me,
and you hugged me.
It's the best present I've ever received up to now.
But that wasn't me hugging you.
Wasn't it you hugging me as you pleased?
Sorry.
What are you doing? Come in.
Happy birthday.
Thank you, Ja Rim. I'm really happy. It's my best birthday.
I got it, so go now.
I'll leave first.
- What is it?
- Do you have a danso at home?
Yes, I do, why?
Byeol Rim asked me to borrow it for her. Let's go.
What's taking him so long? What the f*** is he doing?
They're going to make single-for-life Kyeong Min cry tears of blood. What the hell are they doing?
Hey. Don't pretend you aren't the same as me.
Gong Joo Yeong must be making the most of it since it's his birthday.
I sent Ja Rim a message. They'll come.
Hey, they're coming. Get ready. Hide, you moron.
Hey, where do I go with the cake?
- Just hide somewhere!
- Hide!
Here you go. But my house is a bit mess...
- Surprise!
What the f*** are you guys doing right now?!
♫ Your name I used to call so often  ♫
♫ Only now do I long for it ♫
♫ Whenever I felt sad sending you back home ♫
Love Revolution
Don't you guys have girlfriends to call over?
Gong Joo Yeong, you said your girlfriend is pretty. Call her over.
No.
Hyeong, do you know Ja Rim?
Long hair suited her better.
Anyway, now I understand why you said you couldn't have physical contact with her.
- She's got a super strong iron wall put up.
- Wait!
I want to ask you something.
Do you know hyeong Choi Jeong Woo?
Why don't you say anything to Gong Joo Yeong?
You have to tell him what happened to prevent any misunderstanding.
So did you break up with Wang Ja Rim?
But if you don't tell me anything, like this...
- Should we just break up?
- Right!
Wang Ja Rim?
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com