Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Wake up. You said you wanted to go together.
♫ I wonder about every single thing about you  ♫
♫ May I ask? May I approach you? ♫
Hello birdies!
♫ I keep on getting excited  ♫
Hi to you also, tree! Hi to you also, stairs!
Hi to you too trash!
Hello! It's a very good morning right?
- Hello, Ajumoni!
- Hey!
We're late. If you are done with this, let's go.
Hi to you too, Darling!
It's hot. Stay away.
Okay.
You didn't miss me? I missed you a lot.
- We saw each other yesterday.
- But we didn't see each other in our dreams.
What did you do yesterday? Were you very busy?
It's your fault that I didn't come in your dream.
Ah, so it's like that. I'll invite you more often then.
Where is the bracelet? Did your love cool down already?
It will be confiscated in school.
Ah right!
You thought that much about this? I am touched.
Then let's wear it till we reach school.
It looks good on you. Now, merge!
- Only till we go to school.
- Okay.
Love Revolution: Discount date
Episode 15.  #Collecting #JaRim's #Love #GrainAfterGrain
glasses @princess_0: Collect grains, you beggar
We have to go separate ways already? How can I wait till recess time?
Why am I not in the same class as you?
- It would be nice if we were together.
- We decided to go on a date this weekend, right?
- Lets watch a movie.
- Yes, we did.
- I will book the tickets.
- Go quickly.
Okay.
The bell sounds so sorrowful today.
It sounds better than the sound of your life ending because you're late on your first day.
Ja Rim!
Thankfully it looks like you guys all came through the holidays unscathed.
Yes!
Raise your hand if your homework has been left unscathed as well.
Who is the class president? Is it you?
Sorry? No, sir.
Teacher, it's me.
Ah right, it's you.
That was a bit too much...
Write down the names of those who didn't do their homework. Each will get two penalty points.
- Come on, Teacher!
- Be quiet.
Hey, that was too cruel.
Insufficient balance?
Ticket purchase - You have insufficient balance
Wait, what the?
Remaining Balance: 4,168 won (≈ $3.5)
What? Why do I have only this much left?
Did I get hacked?
Spending over the past few days:
100th day celebration couple bracelets - ₩80,000 (≈ $70)
Good mood on 100th day, bought snacks for friends - ₩31,000 (≈ $27)
Played the claw machine until I got a plushy to give to Ja Rim - ₩23,500 (≈ $21)
Bought lettuce under the insistent look of the street vendor grandma - ₩30,000 (≈ $26)
So I did use all this money.
What are you doing? You look like someone who's just been hit by reality.
Look at my remaining balance. I'm a total beggar this month.
Hey, so you have ₩4000.
- It is perfect for you to buy us each bread.
- Shut up.
I have to go on a date with Ja Rim this weekend, but I'm screwed right now.
- Ask your parents for pocket money.
- I can't.
I already feel bad about living on my own.
If they know I used up all my money I'll get scolded.
Part time job.
What kind of part-time job pays in advance?
- The date is this week.
- Ask Wang Ja to pay.
- It's damn simple.
- Hey I can never do that! So embarrassing.
Won't you help out a pitiful friend of yours
who is short on money for his date?
Just 40,000 won will be enough. Please lend me just 40,000 won, respected hyungnims!
(T/N: hyungnim is a respectful term for an older male)
If you only help me with 40,000 won (≈$35), I will treat you my whole life as my respected—
Where did they go?
- Did you book the tickets?
- Huh?
Oh, uhm. No, not yet.
- Shall I do it?
- No no no, I'll do it.
Hey, aren't you hungry? Should we go eat ramyeon at the convenience store?
- Shall we? Do you also wanna go?
- Huh?
Ra-ramyeon?
Remaining balance after eating convenience store ramyeon at ₩1500: ₩2668.
I should go and book the tickets quickly. What if they get sold out?
Ja Rim I'll contact you later.
You can just book the tickets with your phone, right? Why does he go home to do it?
- I'm so hungry.
- Me too. Let's go.
Last year I hid 10,000 won somewhere.
In this very book.
The bookmark...
Seoteve Jobs
Hyung thank you, I'll use it well.
Your loving brother Gong Jae Min
You're dead when I go home.
I'm out of rice too.
How will I manage?
What happened to this? Is it broken?
I don't even have money. I'm going crazy.
Father
Son, what is it this late in the night?
The air-conditioner is broken.
Oh no. Oh dear.
Call after-sales services asap tomorrow.
It hasn't been a year since we bought it, so it will be free of cost.
Really?
Then right now...
Right, it's too late.
Are you sick?
Why do you look so terrible?
I stayed up all night because my air-conditioner is broken.
On top of that, I'm out of rice so I couldn't even eat one meal.
Now it is not Prince Wang Ja and Princess Gong Joo, it should be Prince and Beggar.
On this note, Kim Baeng... Could you lend 20,000 won to your pitiful friend
- out of the kindness of your heart?
- Yeah no, I'm a beggar too.
I'm so hungry.
Is it far till lunchtime?
The monitor at that internet café was, and I'm not even kidding, this big!
What are you doing? Are you out of your mind?
This... Sorry.
Hey Gong Joo Yeong! Let's go to the snack bar.
- Snack bar?
- Yeah let's go.
N-No. I-I'm fine. I think I ate too much this morning, I don't feel too good.
What is wrong with him? Usually, he won't stay away from you for even one second.
Hey! He looks like he has starved for quite a few days.
- What are you guys watching?
- Gaming broadcast.
I know that much. I meant to ask what game it is.
- LoL.
- Who is playing? Let's watch it together!
Pfft. Would you understand anything from watching?
Hey, I also like LoL!
Really? What's your tier?
Uuh, what was my tier again?
If you're that uninterested in it, then you're definitely Iron.
Does it mean you're good if you're Iron?
No, if you're Iron, Gosh...
If you don't know that also can you just get lost?
How about an iron-fist?
Hey Yang Min Ji. If you play LoL, want to come to the internet café this weekend?
This weekend? Shall I?
Okay. Then I'll contact you this weekend.
Okay.
Are you good at LoL?
I'm in power save mode, please don't bother me.
Hey! Help me!! I've helped you a lot all this while, right?
Plat 4 Support. Main chara Karma.
Does it mean you're good?
Well, to some extent?
Really? Then help me out please.
Thousand won per ten minutes.
Hey! Are you saying you are going to take money from your friend?
Three hundred won.
Customer, there is something called the market price. If I do it for this much, rumors will spread.
Five hundred.
Deal.
- Tell your mother thank you for dinner.
- It's 10,000 won.
Are you crazy? I couldn't even eat properly.
Thinking about how I'll have to see Ja Rim without money, I couldn't swallow the food.
What are you saying when you even ate my share of the food?
Hey, stop wallowing in self-pity. You have many nice clothes.
Sell a few on second-hand goods sites. It should get you enough money for your date.
Oh! You are a genius!! Thanks, friend!
By the way, what is your mom making for tomorrow's breakfast?
You even want us to feed you breakfast too?
This is the t-shirt I wore on my first date with Ja Rim.
This is the one that Ja Rim selected for me.
This is the one I wore when I saw Ja Rim for the first time.
I had this?
Okay. I choose you.
Okay.
I wore this twice. It's in best condition. Bought it for 70,000, selling for 40,000, in person.
I'll buy it.
Remaining balance: ₩4,168
Remaining balance: ₩44,168
(Youth tickets at 10,000 - discount of 2,000) * 2 = 16,000
Balance: ₩44,168 - ₩16,000 = ₩28,168
It's the air-conditioning repair services!
Yes.
- Hello.
- It is there.
- Ah yes.
- It's over there?
- Yes.
I got it.
Let me have a look.
Ah, customer, I'm sorry but the model mentioned and this model
- are different.
- Pardon?
The model mentioned is L and the model here is N.
- It's not possible.
- Take a look.
Ah sorry. Maybe I saw it wrong.
What to do? The free repair period for this model ended three days ago.
Then how much would it cost to repair it?
Well, I'd have to open it but it'll probably be at least 50,000 won.
What would you like to do? Should I try to fix it?
Money left from buying the movie tickets: ₩28,168
No, I don't want to fix it.
Pardon? Will you be alright? When the room
- is this hot?
- Ah. Well,
I was born on a hot day so it reminds me of my youth, I like it.
Ah, yes. Is that so? Well, all right then.
You just have to pay for my travel expenses then.
- Sorry? Travel expenses?
- Yes.
The travel expenses fees are normally waived during the free repair period, but that just ended.
- It's 20,000 won.
- 20,000 won?
Spending for travel expenses without having fixed the air-conditioning: Balance ₩8,168
Popcorn and cola are a must when watching a movie, but I'm too tight on money. If I buy only one cola—
What time does the movie start?
At 1:10.
We still have a lot of time. Let's just simply eat something and go.
- Food?
- Yeah.
Aren't you hungry? Didn't you say you skipped breakfast?
I am fine though.
Do you want your stomach to gurgle out loud during the movie?
Let's eat and go.
Did you already start?
Ah, you came? You also join quickly. Loser buys lunch.
Deal.
Seafood risotto, please.
Did you choose?
Carbonara, 9000 won. Seafood pasta 22000 won. Pizza margherita 25000 won.
Sh*t. It would be cheaper if I go to Italy and eat it!
You still didn't choose?
Uh, no, just...
- Give me one kids meal set.
- Pardon?
This one. The kids meal set.
I'm sorry, but we can only sell the kids sell for preschool children.
I've had a problem with herbal medicine...
- Give us rose pasta for him.
- Yes.
You like rose pasta.
Yeah, I do like them.
Wow, did you show off even though you're unranked?
I told you earlier that I created a new id because I forgot my password.
And such a high-ranked person lost to a minion? How many meals do you plan on buying me?
It's because I haven't warmed up enough yet. Let's get to it some more.
Leave it. I have to leave because I have an appointment.
Huh? You're leaving? We played only one game though.
Not to worry. The next contestant is waiting.
He's right on time.
Hi.
Then I am passing the lunch I won to Sang Hoon.
Hey Sang Hoon! You can just let Yang Min Ji buy you food.
- What?
- No it's fine, you don't have to buy food.
- Ignore Kyeong Woo.
- You guys figure it out.
I'm off.
Sorry. I came because Kyeong Woo called me, but I didn't know that the situation was like this.
Are you uncomfortable because of me?
- Shall we just leave?
- Ah, no.
It's not like that. It's okay.
Then shall we play together?
Shall we?
Gosh you're damn bad at this. Stop playing you crazy cow.
Hey you f***ker! You have a death wish!!?
- I want to use the restroom.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
Could you make me credit and I pay later, please?
If I leave this with you...
- No. The payment has already been done.
- Pardon?
The girl already paid.
Thanks for the meal.
You bought the tickets, it's a given I should buy lunch.
Still...
You're out of pocket money, right?
- Uh?
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Because I was embarrassed.
- Why is this a thing to be embarrassed about?
Do you really like me? In a relationship where both like each other,
there shouldn't be any secrets, don't you think?
Sorry for making you concerned.
Just tell me next time. This makes me more concerned. And I am buying the popcorn and cola.
- You were the one who bought our food so I'll feel too bad—
- Shut up.
- I'm buying everything today. I have only been receiving from you all this while—
- Thank you, Ja Rim.
It's hot.
Ah but earlier didn't you say that it is a relationship where we like each other?
Then do you mean you also like me?
- Did I?
- Yeah.
So you also like me now?
I don't know. Think whatever you want.
Anyway, having no money is nothing to be embarrassed about. So don't hide it from me.
Okay. Then...
What does Ja Rim think of as embarrassing?
Walking like this right now.
Our Ja Rim even talks in a fun way.
Where in the world is that fun?
♫ I like your smiling face the most ♫
♫ But the picture you posted today, where was it taken? ♫
♫ Why does it make me so anxious
when you are somewhere I’m not? ♫
♫ I like you  ♫
Love Revolution
Wang Ja Rim and Lee Kyeong Woo will
take pictures with the customers.
Hey you're totally pulling for us to be slaves!
Where is the handsome guy from your class?
Are they talking about Lee Kyeong Woo?
Exactly how many pictures are they going to take?
If I get some of the guys going to class 3 to come here instead,
there'll be fewer guys hanging around Ja Rim.
Ja Rim, it's a concept, a concept! It's not for real!
- What are you doing?
- Can you set me up on a blind date?
Don't set him up on a blind date.
- Why?
You like Lee Kyeong Woo right?
- What?!