Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
Happy now? F***, you really can't take a hint.
- Aren't you on weekly duty? Why are you so late?
- What?
- Yeah...
- What are you doing? Hurry up inside.
Wait...
What?
Sorry about yesterday.
What are you talking about?
If not, then forget it.
Oh, so cute. Why are you so cute?
What are you doing, making me shy? Put them side by side.
- Ta-da.
- I want to take a pic of this.
- Then we set this as our backgrounds?
- I'm all for it.
Let's also do it like this next time.Okay?
Love Revolution: Talk kindly to others and you'll get looked down upon
Episode 8 #My_only_crime #Is_having_loved_you #Too_much
kyungwoo @princess_0: Whose crime is it?
- Hi!
- Where's Ja Rim?
- I think she went to the washroom.
What are you doing?
Hey, I think you better not look at that.
No, I just want to see her screen background.
Incorrect pattern
Hey! What are you doing right now?
- No, I...
- Are you nuts?
- Why are you touching other people's stuff?
- What? Ah, well...
Sorry. I was just thinking we could get couple backgrounds.
Who do you think you are to touch my phone?
What do you mean who do I think I am? I'm your boyfriend, after all.
So what if you're my boyfriend?
I can at least touch your phone as your boyfriend, right?
- Plus, I didn't even unlock it. Why are you already getting mad—
- What kind of nonsense is that?
I can't even have my own personal life if we're dating?
That's not it, but
we can at least share our things, right?
And I still don't know if we're actually dating.
Then, let's break up.
Hey! Why are you being like this?
What are you doing here? The bell rang.
Hey. Why is he like that again?
They broke up.
- What? Why?
- Be quiet.
Many of these conditions
can be satisfied that way.
First one...
having found that, as the last,
Don't tell me you really meant it?
You just said it out of anger, right? I was wrong.
I'm really sorry.
New text message.
Don't tell me you really meant it?
You just said it out of anger, right? I was wrong.
I'm really sorry.
Hey you nutcase. Cut it out! You'll get dizzy at this rate.
Let go! That's what I want.
It's my first time seeing someone trying to get drunk with caffeine.
Just keep going crazy.
It took me so much effort to date her...
She still hasn't read his messages?
You idiot! Are you just going to wait for her messages all day?
Just go find her first!
It's like you only have fingers and no legs.
But I'm scared to see her face.
Is that really the punk that sang a confession song in front of the whole school?
Hey! Why are you discouraging our Joo Yeong?
It's alright, you're okay.
Hey, go and talk to her.
Whatever you want to say, say it to her face directly.
Yeah.
What did I even do that was so wrong?
Hey, Wang Ja Rim!
You!
Check your KakaoTalk.
That was the wind.
Ja Rim, please answer me.
I was wrong for touching your phone.
Let's talk.
You didn't mean it, right?
Ja Rim!
Hey, aren't you going home?
I don't have the energy to go.
You've gone nuts because of a girl.
You go home first.
Come on, let's go.
No.
I said let's go!
- Give it back.
- Hurry and come out.
Hey, Wang Ja.
Honestly, Gong Joo Yeong didn't make that serious of a mistake, did he?
- Did you have to go as far as breaking up?
- Then, you...
What would you do if he secretly accessed your game account and took all your equipment and money?
- I'd  beat him up, of course!
- Exactly.
- Ah, no wait, that's not it!
That's for if he actually took them.
Has Gong Joo Yeong ever caused any harm to you? He didn't.
Is criminal attempt not a crime?
Isn't it common sense to get someone's permission first before touching their stuff?
- That's true.
- Are you Gong Joo Yeong's lawyer?
If he has something to say, tell him to talk to me in person.
Is it your hobby to justify a guilty person's behavior?
If I'm guilty, then you are too.
Guilty of the crime of theft for stealing my heart.
You're stealing it right now too!
You're still able to make jokes right now?
Sorry.
Hey, just make up with him already.
I'll self-reflect. Let's make up.
- You can at least hear what he has to say.
- I don't want to hear anything or say anything to him.
- He's the one who's at fault.
- That's right.
Gong Joo Yeong really was wrong. But you weren't expecting that, were you?
Well, it doesn't matter anyway.
I'll self-reflect. Let's make up.
Ja Rim!
- At least take this.
- I said, scram.
I'm really sorry. I really wasn't trying to check your phone.
I just wanted us to have couple backgrounds—
Hey. Just knock it off.
Why would we have couple backgrounds? Are we in that close a relationship?
I just said okay to dating you to be nice. To be honest, I...
No, never mind.
Ah, f***.
F- what?
My hand slipped.
Why are you so surprised? I also know how to swear.
- Are you crazy?
- No, I'm completely sane.
Anyway, finish what you were saying just now.
It's because I'm like this that you what? You hate me to death?
Why are you dating me if you don't like me?  Are you doing community service?
- That's because you kept—
- Oh, gosh. Thank you!
You were so magnanimous as to agree to date this lowly boor.
It is such an immense privilege! My apologies for annoying you all this time.
- Hey, listen to me!
- I don't want to!
Why do I always have to listen to you? I also know how to speak!
People can make mistakes.
Isn't that the process of getting to know each other?
You have to touch other people's stuff to get to know each other?
Whatever. You think I don't have other girls other than you?
Don't you remember the senior who likes me?
Oh, so you're even bringing that up now?
All right. Is this who you are?
So, this is what the real you is like, isn't it?
Then, what? What are you going to do about it?
For a person who says he won't change, you sure changed fast.
No, this is what the real you is like, so I guess you didn't change, right?
It's possible to act like this when you're mad.
But actually you're the one who wanted to say this all along, isn't it?
Then, you should've been like this from the beginning.
Why did you keep making caring gestures and confusing me?
I won't even wish for much.
Can't you at least treat me like a human?
Do you hate me that much?
- It's not that I hate you...
- That's what I mean!
Don't talk like that! Just directly say whether you hate me or like me!
Yeah, I hate you. I hate you.
"Hate you" ; "Hate you"
I freaking hate you.
"Freaking hate you"
- Are you done?
- Yeah, I'm done.
Why not swear, too? You're good at swearing, aren't you? F...
F... F- Foot, what do you think about my foot? My f-foot.
These look like flocked shoes.
- Hey, Gong Joo Yeong.
- Yes? I didn't swear.
Clean up the banana milk.
Yes.
We said we would meet tomorrow. What time should we meet?
Did we say that?
- I'm not going.
- Me neither.
This is awkward. I hate this!
- Then, perhaps we shouldn't meet either?
- Sure.
- Why not? Let's just hang out ourselves.
- Yeah, true,
the survivors should keep on living, and the ones who can hang out should hang out.
It's better if I'm not there, then.
I'll also head off now.
What should we do about them?
I don't know. I can't get involved in this anymore.
I'm sure they'll handle it themselves.
So, what time are we meeting tomorrow?
Can you not read your surroundings?
That crazy punk.
Is he seriously insane?
Rumors spread quite quickly in schools.
Please go, I'm not in the mood to talk.
Oh dear! But I came to comfort you.
To be honest, you two broke up much faster than I had expected. I was surprised.
I told you she never really liked you.
It's a relief you're finally free from her claws now.
Just consider it a good learning experience and move on.
Let's go, I'll buy you something.
I'm okay, please just go.
What? Don't tell me you're planning to try again with her?
Are you really that oblivious?
From the start, she agreed to date you with the intention of dumping you.
What do you like about that bitch?
Don't insult Ja Rim.
What?
What does it matter to you what she does or doesn't do?
You think I didn't know?
I'm the one who liked her and was dumped of my own accord, so please just drop it.
I was happy when I liked her.
Wow, you sound like a total loser.
You can go if you've figured it out. Because I'm going to keep living as a loser.
Sure. I'm not that interested in losers like you.
Crazy ass.
Ja Rim should've seen that just now.
I was kind of cool.
I'm damn charismatic.
This is driving me crazy.
What should I do?
She saw
We're not going to have fun today.
We're not going for fun, either.
We're going to Wang Ja Rim's place.
We're going to Joo Yeong's. He went home first again.
We figured he shouldn't be alone.
We thought we should speak to Ja Rim, too.
Why did those two have to fight and make things difficult for all of us?
Let's go.
What are you doing here?
What are you up to now? Do you have more swearing left to do?
It's not like that.
I was just walking mindlessly but when I came to my senses I was in front of your place.
Damn.
Are you writing a song?
Sorry.
I was just so mad, I spoke too harshly without realizing.
I know you didn't like me back.
Thanks for dating me.
Sorry.
Keep your head down.
I wasn't serious when I said I hated you.
I don't really hate you.
I wasn't messing with you, either.
I just don't really know, either.
I'll go.
Hey, why are you crying?
I thought you would never see me again.
That was my original plan, but we go to the same school and live near each other.
So that's how it turns out.
Then, are we dating again?
I guess.
Ja Rim, I really like you.
I know.
What about you?
Okay.
I'll wait until you like me back.
Do whatever you want. Now I really have to go to the market.
- Wait for me.
- Why would I?
The way to the supermarket is dangerous.
♫ Even if I keep telling myself it’s not real ♫
Okay, from now on I really won't do anything you dislike.
I don't like this stuff.
Can't you reconsider linking arms?
Why don't you just grab my collar?
You still remember that?
How can I forget?
They're practically filming a drama together.
Why are we here?
He's not worth worrying over.
Anyhow, it's good that it went well.
I'm hungry. They're going to the supermarket, right?
- Hey, hey!
- Hey!
- Let's go.
- Go where?
Where do you think you're going?
♫ But the picture you posted today, where was it taken? ♫
I don't care, let's go.
I said let's go with them. Hey.
♫ Why does it make me so anxious ♫
♫ when you are somewhere I’m not? ♫
♫ I like you ♫
Love Revolution
Exclusive News, Exclusive News!
"Let's go surprise Kyeong Woo"? You could just tell me you want to celebrate my birthday, why make up an excuse?
- How can I help y—
- Hi!
Did you need me for anything again, dear customer?
Some water.
Could you give me your number?
Everything else
is just so trivial compared to my Ja Rim.
Guys... Thank you.
Happy birthday to you!
- Don't tell me...
- You crazy morons, why would you eat that?
It was reserved by a customer to use for a celebration. How are you going to fix this?