Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
- See you after class.
- Study hard.
Right back at you.
I guess they are finally dating.
If he was going to be like that, then why did he play hard to get at first?
Don't talk behind people's backs first thing in the morning.
Well, it's because Ye Seul is totally out of your league.
- Congrats on getting a girlfriend.
- Thanks.
You guys also should do something that is worth congratulating.
I'll put my heart and soul into giving you congratulations then.
What the hell? Annoying first thing in the morning.
Wait and see. I'll receive your congratulations with all my heart and soul.
Hey Lee Kyeong Woo! I have something that is worth congratulating.
Oh really? Did you get a boyfriend?
Yeah. A boyish friend. Whom I'll beat up now.
Jerk.
The midterm exams are coming up. You must be very worried.
You need to avoid your class getting last place at all costs, this time.
I don't want to judge my students based on their grades only.
Education should aim to be well-rounded.
Yes, that's true. What you're saying is right.
It would be great if the principal had the same outlook as you.
I'm worried about what he'll say if you come in last again.
You are already worrying like this. You will be embarrassed if our class's average increases.
That won't be something to be embarrassed about. It will be something to congratulate.
Look, Teacher. For these midterms,
what about the teacher of the class with the lowest average treats the other to pizza?
Do you guys know that it is exam time? Are you guys studying properly?
No.
And do you know how severe our class' average is?
We don't know.
How would you feel if we place last again?
Comfort from finding our place.
I wonder if you know that you'll have to take after-class study if you come last again on these midterms.
What?!
- After-school study?!
- This is not right!!
- No way!
No sir, no sir.
Do you know who plays the biggest part in smashing our class average to the ground?
I am sorry, I was in the restroom.
He's come. He's here.
The punk who pinned our class average to the ground.
Let me make you a proposition.
If that brat raises his average to 70,
even if you place last, you are all exempted from after-class study. Okay?
Get ready for class.
Gosh, we're doomed!
And he's sleeping again!
Love Revolution: When Kyeong Woo studies
Episode 20. #Full-blown #NoAfterClassStudy #Project
glasses @kyungwoo: Use the time you write this stuff to study instead
What should I do now? Should I drop out?
Friend. Don't despair. Let's all gather at room 101 and study together.
Hey, but that's my place.
- I am going to the library with Ja Rim today—
- We know the password, do you think we don't even know that?
- Yeah, but it's my hous—
- Lee Kyeong Woo, you are going to study with us right?
What are you saying? You guys study hard yourselves.
It's because if it doesn't go well, our whole class will have to attend after-class study.
Right! You absolutely can't have after-class study.
Then there'll only be the weekends for Ja Rim and me to go on dates.
Lee Kyeong Woo, you need to study no matter what.
Friend, don't worry.
For the happy future of our class, I brought a tutor.
The most sought-after tutor of Yisam Information High School, Kim Byeong Hoon!
Hey! Who do you want to teach? Aren't your and Lee Kyeong Woo's grades almost the same?
How can you say such an upsetting thing? My average on the last finals was no less than 75!
Oh really? It's totally unexpected.
Yeah! Then you guys can study hard and increase the class grade average.
Then I am going to meet Ye Seul.
Don't worry. I explained everything to Ye Seul. She wants us to make sure you study.
She also won't like you having night study.
Okay. Then let's all go to Joo Yeong's house and you guys can learn from me.
I am not looking down on you, but can we really get tutored by a guy who got 75 marks?
Don't worry. I recruited a real top student for us.
I should call him over to my home. You're eager to know, aren't you?
- The top student was Jeong Sang Hoon?
- Yup.
Hey! Do you really study well?
Well... yeah a bit.
This person lives in a totally different world from you guys.
He's one of the top ten students at Mowon High, the most prestigious school in the area.
He's basically a future Seoul National University student.
It is impressive, but why are you the one bragging?
Because he is my friend.
And he could become someone's boyfriend.
Hey, hey! Let's start studying.
I'm going to tutor you according to your level. Should we start with multiplication? Three times six is?
Eighteen! Am I a kindergartener? You think I don't even know the multiplication tables?
Okay, so you know the basics. We'll get into algebraic identities right away.
The simplest and most used algebraic identity is '(a + b) squared.'
When you resolve it, you get 'a squared + 2ab + b squared.' You got it?
No.
Okay, don't try to understand, just memorize.
You solved it well until now. For the next problem, you need to use an application.
Try to put it into the formula and solve it.
I'll let you know if there's any mistake in how you solve the problem.
Ooh! Jeong Sang Hoon, are you tutoring Yang Min Ji one-on-one?
No, it's just that Min Ji makes the fastest progress.
Don't pay attention to others, and focus on your own studying.
Should I also learn from Sang Hoon? He's being darn nice.
Hey! You're not on the level to learn from Sang Hoon. Just learn from me.
- Dammit.
- Next is the quadratic formula.
I freaking don't want to study. Aren't you guys hungry?
Yeah! Honestly a bit.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Then shall I make a night snack?
No! Uhm, j-just study. You have exams too, so you should concentrate.
- Yeah.
- Right, let's all pitch in and order delivery.
- Yeah, sure! Delivery!
- Delivery.
What a waste of money. Why order delivery? I'll cook. What's in the fridge?
No. Well... I didn't do any grocery shopping, so there's nothing in the fridge...
It's full, though?
Did my mom come or something?
Be honest. You're being like this because my cooking doesn't taste good, right?
No. If it is you who made it, I could even eat a rock.
Ja Rim, do you know how to make braised spicy chicken? There's chicken in the fridge.
Yes, I make a decent one. It won't take long. You guys keep studying.
Okay! Cutting up a chicken is difficult, so I'll help you. Hey, you can only improve if you cook more, you know.
You should've stopped her! Are you going to eat it all?
I stopped her but she said she would cook. It's because you said you were hungry!
But she said she makes braised spicy chicken well. Maybe we should trust her. Plus, Ah Rong is helping her.
She just said she's helping with the cutting.
Wow, that smells amazing.
Hey, I... think I have to go to the washroom.
Oh, I also have to go and wash my hands before eating.
Oh, right, my mom told me to call her. I totally forgot.
Wow, the soup tastes great too. It makes me want to eat a ton!
The meat is super fleshy too. Wang Ja Rim sure can cook!
It's really delicious.
Even Jeong Sang Hoon said that? Could it really be tasty?
Seriously... Does she really make good braised spicy chicken?
Why aren't you guys eating? Hurry and come to eat.
- Oh, okay.
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah, we should eat.
- Of course.
I think it really turned out well this time.
Yeah, totally.
So tasty. We have to clear everything.
Gong Joo, open up.
You should eat some too.
This is really delicious!
I'm going first because I'm late for the gym training.
- Have a safe trip there!
- Bye!
- We're leaving too.
- Kyeong Woo, go over what you learned today before sleeping.
Hey, the fate of our whole class depends on your brain.
- Adios.
- Go, leave.
I'm leaving too. Sang Hoon, you're good at teaching. Thanks for today.
No problem. I also got to study thanks to you, so it was good.
Sang Hoon, you should take her home.
- Should I take you home?
- Then shall we go to the station together?
Let's go.
Should we go too?
- I'm going to the internet cafe.
- What about studying?
- I can't. My brain is overloaded, it'll explode.
- True. You did all your life's worth of studying.
By the way, don't wait up for me to go to school tomorrow. Just go ahead first.
- Why? We should go together.
- Are you planning to go with Ye Seul?
Sure. I'm leaving now.
- See you.
Whose is this?
- It's mine. They're questions that may possibly appear on the exam. Make sure you look at them.
- Why should I?
Kyeong Woo, I summarized the key points of Korean class. Want to copy it? No wait, I'll copy it for you.
Do you know the scope of our English exam? Should I tell you?
That's okay, I'll figure it out myself.
Hey, Kyeong Woo, you haven't memorized the chemical symbols yet, have you? I'll teach you an easy memorization method.
"Little Nasty Kids Behind Maggie’s Backseat
Always Cause Silliness."
What do you think? Easy, right? Try memorizing it like that.
- What the hell are you guys doing?
- Where are you going?
- But it's simple!
- Hey!
For English, you just have to memorize the vocabulary.
Hwang Jin Yi's poem, "Long November Night," goes, "Lain under the blanket warm as the spring breeze..."
When you have two letters, if you look at the transformation of the algebraic identity...
Why are you guys following me? I don't know any of this stuff!
If you don't know, then you should learn. You just have to open up your ears.
- Just be quiet!
- No...
- Listen!
- The formula...
The bell for class is going to ring soon.
I have a headache, so don't talk to me.
Then let me tell you an interesting story. Listen as you rest.
After all, history is like a story. History. The main work of art of the Unified Silla—
Why are you like this too?
Your grades have to go up so that Ja Rim won't get after-class study. Then, I won't need to wait until she's done.
If your grades improve, you'll make your mother proud. Ja Rim won't have after-class study, so we'll both be happy.
Is that not killing two birds with one stone? Right. While we're at it, let's memorize four-character idioms too.
Similar to idioms like "killing two birds with one stone," include "best of both worlds," "killing two birds with one arrow"...
Please stop! Please!
Please is spelt "p-l-e-a-s-e" in English.
- Stop.
- Stop is "s-t-o-p" in English.
Stop please, you son of a gun!
Translation unavailable.
Every time I went to your class during break, you weren't there. Where did you go?
I hid to avoid everyone. They try to get me to study whenever they see me. I feel like I'm going to die.
Our little sweetie is having a hard time because of his friends?
I have to vent this out. Shall we go and sing karaoke?
- Shall we?
- Yeah, let's go.
What the heck? Why are you guys here?
Could it be...
Sorry, Kyeong Woo. This is better than playing now and ending up having after-class study.
What will I do if you have after-class study?
What are you guys doing? Let go!
- I said to let go!
- We're arresting you on the scene. Karaoke and internet cafes are off limits to you during the exam period.
Who do you think you are? It's my freedom whether I want to play or not!
Do you think it's okay if the whole class suffers because of you?
That's why you guys should be studying! Hey, Bang Ye Seul, seriously!
Hey, you! Seriously...
- At this point, you should give up and study.
- What?
Taking into consideration the effort they put in, shouldn't you at least pretend to study?
Keep resisting and you'll strain your friendships. If it still doesn't work after all this, we'll blame your brain.
- Do you want to die?
- Okay everyone, don't get worked up, and let's study.
Since we did math last time, let's do English this time.
Ok. Hmm.
Excuse me sir, how can I get to Changdeok-gung Palace?
How can I go to Changdeok Palace?
Hmmm. Let me see, take line number 1 and go for three stops.
Let me see, take line number 1 and go for three stops.
Thank you for being nice to me.
Math (9:00-9:50) / Science (10:00-10:50) / English (11:00-11:50)
Pass it back.
Lee Kyeong Woo. Show me your test sheet so we can check our answers.
There's nothing to even check. Lee Kyeong Woo, you put answer 1 for everything and slept, didn't you?
We taught you so diligently. How can you do this?
I don't know the answers!
We taught you everything! What's the binomial identity?
(a + b) squared gives a squared + 2ab + b squared.
So you know it! So what was the answer to question 1?
I think he memorized the formula, but couldn't apply it.
- You didn't teach him how to use the formula?
- Ah right, application.
Dammit, I only made him memorize them. What do we do?
You buffoon, so this is your fault. How do you expect him to apply it, with that brain of his?
Let's just let it go and assume we'll get after-class study. Teaching my puppy at home would be more worth it.
Are you going to say whatever you want when I'm in front of you?
No. I invested so many hours in him.
Our Kyeong Woo can do well. You just have to do well from now on, so let's go over the questions quickly.
Ah, please, let's stop this. Please.
Math (9:00-9:50) / Science (10:00-10:50) / English (11:00-11:50)
Little Nasty Kids Behind Maggie’s Backseat
Always Cause Silliness.
Silliness.
Math (9:00-9:50) / Science (10:00-10:50) / English (11:00-11:50)
How can I get to Changdeok-gung Palace?
Hmmm. Let me see, take line number 1 and go for three stops.
Thank you for being nice to me.
One week later.
Teacher Jo of class 3 is buying, so eat as much as you want.
- Yay.
- Yahoo.
Once you're done eating, the ones who played around with the short-answer question in math,
number 3, number 8, number 11, number 16, and number 19. Come to the teacher's room.
The midterm results are out.
What's this? I'm the one who had to buy pizza for the other class, so why are you the ones looking like you're in mourning?
We all know how Lee Kyeong Woo took the exam, that's why.
From when are we going to have night study, sir? Till what time will it be sir?
No. Lee Kyeong Woo's grades increased a lot.
The guy who usually gets a 30 point average got 60 points.
Looks like you guys helped a lot.
But not only did Lee Kyeong Woo improve, you all have increased your grades as a whole,
so in these midterms, our class got no less than...
third place in the entire first-year grade.
Wow!
Third place from last.
Anyway, we avoided last place. Quiet, Quiet!
So, we'll forget about after-class study.  Get ready for your class.
- Yay!
- Awesome!
I thought we would have to attend night study. What happened?
- I thought that only my grades increased.
- Me too.
I did study harder than usual just to teach Lee Kyeong Woo.
We killed it.
Kyeong Woo, want me to tutor you again for the next midterm? Looks like your brain isn't a rock, after all.
Have you gone mad? If you guys do that again, I'll drop out.
Okay, good job!
Go easy on us, Joo Yeong. I got scoldings from my mom today so I'm already annoyed.
Wah! Did you tell your mom about your grades? I lied that they didn't come yet.
Why isn't Lee Kyeong Woo coming? His mom must be very happy because his grades went up.
Now that it's all over, stop talking about the grades. My sugar level is dropping.
Darling, me too. Ahh.
It tastes sweeter since my darling is feeding—
Darling, really?
What is wrong with you?
Yes, Mom. No, nothing big. Just that my grades increased.
Sixty marks.
It's amazing?
Dinner?
What about you, Mom?
Then I want bulgogi.
Well, I studied according to the textbooks, and it turned out well. Yeah.
♫ I can never know what you are feeling ♫
Subtitles brought to you by Teenage Love Team @ Viki.com
♫ I'm curious ♫
Love Revolution
♫ About you ♫
Why does this one look better?
The picture looks good because the guy is taller.
Well, this much is average height.
It is in a higher place, so...
- What should I do to get taller?
- What, you punk?
Eat well and poop well.
Have you seen any movies recently?
Did you go through an old clothes collection box?
I just bought these.
- What's this? Are you guys dating in the end?
- No, it's not like that.
- Do well.
- Let's leave and not disturb them. Have fun.
Once we're all grown up and graduate, Ja Rim will wear high heels since she'll be an adult. Then she'll be the same height as me.
I don't really like tall guys.
♫ I can’t slow down. Take responsibility for it ♫