(Episode 11)
I feel so sorry for Su Ryeon.
She was too sweet
to be used by someone like you...
until she died.
Thank you...
for remembering me.
- What are you doing?
- You're Su Ryeon.
I know you're Su Ryeon.
Don't try to run away.
I'm sorry it took me
so long to recognize you.
Where are you?
Where are you, Cheon Seo Jin?
She's in the practice room.
How dare she go out
without my permission?
I asked her for a private lesson...
so that I can prepare for my finals.
You didn't just bring her here
to cook for us, right?
Let me take advantage
of my new stepmom.
- Tell her to come here after.
- Okay.
I told him that you're giving me
a private lesson.
He won't look for you
for a couple of hours.
(Ms. Cheon)
Chairman, please
have a look at this.
What is it?
Logan Lee?
You mean, Ae Gyo met with Logan Lee?
Yes. They secretly met
after the bid.
When did this prick come back
to Korea?
What is James doing? All he had
to do is watch his son.
- Where's Na Ae Gyo?
- She's headed to the cottage.
The cottage?
- It's me.
- Do you know this man named Logan?
Come to the cottage right now.
I need you.
All right. I'll be there.
Get my car.
Help me.
- Yoon Hee!
- How can I trust you?
I know it's hard to trust me.
Of course.
But why would I lie to you
at this point?
I came here, even knowing
I might go to jail.
So, what is it that you want to say?
On the day of the Cheong A
Arts Festival,
Eun Byeol struck Ro Na down
with the trophy.
Ro Na rolled down the stairs,
and it was Yoon Chul who put
the trophy in Seok Kyung's locker.
We were crazy. We were only thinking
of how we could save Eun Byeol.
And after finding that out,
Joo Dan Tae started blackmailing me.
He had Eun Byeol's necklace,
which she dropped on the site.
Are you looking for this?
He used your daughter's death...
to take Cheong A Group away
from me.
How does that change anything?
That still means Eun Byeol is
the one who killed my daughter!
No, it could be Eun Byeol,
or not.
Joo Dan Tae was there, after all.
Eun Byeol heard Joo Dan Tae's
phone ring.
Are you kidding me?
You want me to trust your daughter,
who can barely remember anything?
I can prove it to you.
Joo Dan Tae changed his outfit
at the festival.
Isn't it weird that he got changed
right before the awards ceremony?
There must be something.
Regardless,
Ro Na was very useful.
Just as much as Seol A.
Thanks to those tragic girls dying
right at the most opportune times,
I was able to swallow up...
Su Ryeon's and Seo Jin's fortunes
very easily.
So, you want to put all the blame
on Joo Dan Tae now?
You think you can expose him
with just a few photos?
There are plenty of reasons
to change his outfit.
I'm not doing this
to save Eun Byeol.
What I want right now...
is the truth behind what happened
that night.
Just help me...
kill Joo Dan Tae with my own hands.
Please.
Yoon Hee!
Then turn yourselves in.
Come clean on everything Eun Byeol
and you've done to my Ro Na.
(Recording)
Sure.
I will.
What do you think you're doing?
Who do you think you are?
Logan!
It's been so long.
I thought your father locked you up,
but I guess you were out loose.
- Joo Dan Tae!
- What brings you here?
No, how did you get here?
I think he followed me from the bid.
Are you still
not over Shim Su Ryeon?
Hey!
I was too nice on you
the last time, wasn't I?
Take him to the warehouse.
I'll teach him a lesson.
Let go! Let go of me!
Let go!
What did he say to you?
He keeps telling me
that I look just like Su Ryeon,
and keeps asking me
how we're related.
That lunatic.
The problem is,
he knew about Jung Doo Man.
What?
He seems to know
that we got insider information...
from Jung Doo Man and
used that to invest.
He kept threatening me
to come clean.
Maybe...
Shim Su Ryeon knew
before she died.
No, there's no way
she would've known.
Jung Doo Man wouldn't have
told him either.
Talk to that prick first.
You should be able to find
something out if you keep asking.
I'll call you later.
Mr. Hong, it's me, Shim Su Ryeon.
Let go, you jerks!
You brats.
Hey!
Logan!
You must've been quite happy...
when you thought Su Ryeon
came back alive.
But it's too bad...
that we've disappointed you.
How dare you mess
with another man's woman?
Su Ryeon died earlier
than she should've because of you.
You sided with her
and gave false hope,
you prick.
I guess you're wasting your time
obsessing over little things...
because you're so rich
and you've got lots of time,
but unfortunately,
your revenge ends here.
You prick.
Take the sack off.
What? What happened?
Wake him up.
Sir...
We've been fooled.
Logan's people followed us...
and already changed our driver
to one of his.
He knew that
we would take him in our car.
Who are those jerks?
Just go.
Just run them over!
Who are you?
You little...
Are you all right, sir?
You idiot.
You didn't even check
the driver's face?
Seriously.
Ae Gyo.
Darn it. Ae Gyo.
(Na Ae Gyo)
So?
What did he say?
What took you so long to pick up?
I went in to take a shower
and ran out!
What's your problem?
Do you think I'll put up with it?
Forget it. Let's talk later.
Why you...
This was your plan all along,
wasn't it?
If you were going to save me,
why did you call him here?
I had no choice.
I had to make him trust me.
He knew we had met...
and had started to suspect me.
We lived together for 20 years.
It's a matter of time
before he figures it out.
Why are you doing something
so dangerous?
Where were you all this time?
Why didn't you contact me?
If you were alive,
why didn't you contact me?
Shim Su Ryeon died...
two years ago.
She's alive and sitting before me.
You and I...
have nothing to do
with each other now.
I have something to do as Na Ae Gyo.
Until I finish it completely,
no one can know that I'm alive.
Not even Yoon Hee.
How can I ignore you?
You may fall into danger again.
Su Ryeon.
I regretted it...
every day during the past two years.
For not protecting you.
I couldn't forgive myself
for going to the airport first.
It drove me crazy every single day.
Dan Tae is on his way here.
You have to go.
I can't help you again.
I can't go.
Go with me.
I won't go alone.
You uncovered
what happened to Seol A.
You did enough.
This is my problem now.
Stay out of it.
Everything will be over
in two weeks.
If my plan falls through
because of you,
I'll be miserable
and resent you...
for the rest of my life.
So get out.
Promise me one thing.
That if it gets dangerous,
you'll ask me for help.
That you won't...
leave by yourself again.
You need to go.
Su Ryeon.
Thank you for staying alive.
We have to pay the balance tomorrow?
That's totally unreasonable.
It was hard to get that lot.
We even had to win an auction.
We can handle that much.
Our lots went up in value
20 percent today alone.
Even still.
How can I get 50 million dollars
in cash overnight?
Well... You can gather everything
that is valuable...
and put the penthouse up
as collateral and get a loan.
Definitely not.
I refuse to touch the penthouse.
Babe.
How about that new safe
that you brought in?
How much do you think is in there?
Safe?
Seo Jin.
We have to squeeze out what we can.
We can't blow the five million
we put down as a deposit.
Oh Yoon Hee complicated everything.
I'm sure Logan Lee is backing her.
They bought Hye In's land...
and is playing with us.
Then the more reason not to give up.
Are you going to lose the center
in Cheonsoo District to Logan?
That's enough!
Logan didn't come back?
And if he did?
You would've been notified.
Think of how many guards
you have on me.
Did he really like Su Ryeon
or something?
That leech is sticking to me
and getting in my way.
It's not like you can kill him.
He comes from
a rich American family.
That Shim Su Ryeon...
Dead or alive,
she is incessant.
Don't you agree?
I'll call you tomorrow.
(Hyeum Medical Center)
And if you take A...
(Accelerated High School Math)
Seok Hoon.
It's me.
Is it really you?
Where are you?
Seok Hoon.
Ro Na.
I've been awake
for about a week now.
They say I was really out of it.
I had multiple brain surgeries.
They say it's a miracle
that I'm alive...
and able to speak.
I see.
This is really great.
I thought you were dead.
Who brought you here?
Have you talked to your mom?
- No.
- Why not?
Imagine how happy she'll be.
Call her right now.
I can't yet.
But it won't take too long.
Before that, I have something
to tell you.
That's why I called you.
What is it?
The person who did this to me...
Is it...
my dad?
I hoped it wouldn't be him.
I desperately hoped
it wouldn't be him. Why...
Why does he keep taking away
people that are precious to me?
Why in the world?
I'll never forgive him.
- Seok Hoon.
- I'm going to kill him.
Seok Hoon.
Mom?
She's the one who saved me.
Mom.
I missed you, Seok Hoon.
I missed you too.
I'm sorry.
Seo Jin suggested that we team up.
She even confessed
everything she'd done.
I think we can trust her.
It'll be fine
as long as we use her well.
She's already cornered.
She has nowhere to run.
I'm supposed to sign a contract...
with Na Ae Gyo tomorrow.
Is it really okay
to hand over the land so easily?
Do it. Do as Na Ae Gyo says.
But everything's over if the land
ends up in Dan Tae's hands.
Don't tell me
you still trust Na Ae Gyo.
She's deleted the spy app.
We don't even know where she is
or what she's up to.
Do you think I put the land
up for sale...
without a plan?
I do have a plan.
How much?
50 million dollars.
I want it in cash tomorrow.
Are you kidding?
Who has that much money in cash?
If you don't, get it from somewhere.
Put your buildings up
for collateral, sell your diamonds,
steal your mom's money, or whatever.
Getting that much money
should be no problem for you.
If you don't do as I say,
I can't guarantee...
Eun Byeol's safety.
You have until tomorrow noon.
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
Thanks in advance.
(Seller Oh Yoon Hee
and Buyer Na Ae Gyo...)
Okay, I'll check.
Thanks for preparing
the money in time.
We just paid the rest
to her account.
I see.
You prepared that much money
in one day? Impressive.
Ma'am, you're lucky.
This is the highest price
you could possibly expect.
You made a good deal.
Could you excuse us for a second?
Sure. Now that the rest has been
paid, please take your time.
I'll put these together
and give them back to you.
You just bagged a fortune,
but you don't look so happy.
Do you hate to
part with the land so much?
The land meant so much to Su Ryeon.
To think that it ended up
in the hands of scum like you.
You got paid for the land.
You don't have to pretend
to be loyal to a dead person.
You almost fooled me.
Don't you feel sorry
for Su Ryeon at all?
She looked after your children...
like her own for 17 years.
What did you do
while impersonating her?
What is your relationship
with Jung Doo Man?
What do you have on him...
that made him hand over all
the development information to you?
Do you want to know?
Too bad.
I couldn't tell you...
after you installed a spy app
on my phone and invaded my privacy.
You look like a backstabber.
A betrayer.
What? Are you feeling guilty?
You're not taking revenge
because you feel sorry for Su Ryeon.
You're just upset
that Dan Tae betrayed you.
The moment Dan Tae reaches out,
you'll take his hand.
You know
what a despicable jerk he is,
but you still felt drawn to him
because he's rich and well-mannered.
Did you want a penthouse so badly?
You were jealous of Su Ryeon.
You have no right to lecture me!
I'm being cruelly punished for that.
Even my child died.
What more can I do?
Tell me how I can atone
for what I've done.
I'm ready to kill myself or him!
I have a question.
You said you were with Su Ryeon
when she died.
Then you must have heard.
What were her last words?
Did she leave any message?
There's no message
she left for you, so forget it.
What about for her children?
I just think I should know...
in case they ask me later.
She raised them after all.
She told me to run away.
"Run away"?
"Go."
"Run. Right now."
After what I did to her,
she told me to run away.
I betrayed her and wanted her dead.
And she told me to run away.
Yes. You're right.
I leeched off Su Ryeon
just like you did.
We have no right
to criticize each other.
All we can do is
wait for our punishment.
Yoon Hee.
It sounds crazy,
but can you trust me for once?
I have a great plan...
to finish off Dan Tae.
What did you just say?
You want to get back at him.
Then do it.
I'll take his money.
But you can't tell anyone...
about me.
What do you say? Deal?
Forget it. I don't trust you.
What if I leave this to you?
Protect your daughter yourself.
You must protect your child
at all costs.
Since you're her mom.
At times, isn't it okay for a mom
to become evil for her child's sake?
A mother should be ready...
to do anything for her child,
remember?
Call me if you change your mind.
(Golden Real Estate)
You must protect your child
at all costs.
Since you're her mom.
At times, isn't it okay for a mom...
to become evil for her child's sake?
I told you that mothers should...
do anything for their children.
(Golden Real Estate)
Su Ryeon!
Su Ryeon! Wait!
Su Ryeon! Look at me!
Su Ryeon!
Su Ryeon...
She told me to run away.
"Run. Right now."
(The Republic of Korea)
(My little sister)
(Ms. Yang)
Yes, Ms. Yang? Is something wrong?
Ma'am, Chairman took the kids
to his study again!
What do I do?
Who are you?
Na Ae Gyo?
Why did you come here?
What if Joo Dan Tae sees you?
I have to get going right now.
Our kids are in danger.
That's why I'm here.
I'll head into the penthouse.
Are you kidding me?
I told you over the phone.
The kids are locked in his study.
We don't know what Joo Dan Tae
will do to them.
That's why I'm saying
that I'll go instead.
Crazy people should be dealt with
by crazy people.
I don't have time to talk to you.
If anything happens to our kids,
I'll die.
Get out of my way.
I just want to see the kids.
I'm leaving Korea soon.
I won't ever come back.
I'm leaving to a place
where Dan Tae will never find me.
Please.
Let me see the kids one last time.
Be careful, you might get busted.
He's a suspicious man, after all.
Hold on.
The flight is at 8 p.m.
It's to the US.
There will be a man named Logan Lee
waiting at the airport.
Leave with him.
You can trust him.
He'll protect you somewhere safe.
What about you?
I'll stay with the kids.
Thank you, Shim Su Ryeon.
Thanks for letting me live as you.
If anything happens to me,
I'll scream, "Run!"
Then, don't look back...
and just run away.
You have to take care...
of Seok Kyung and Seok Hoon.
You're their real mom, after all.
Seok Hoon!
Seok Kyung!
How could you...
Chairman Joo, are you here?
Su Ryeon!
Su Ryeon.
I'll call the ambulance right now.
Just hold on.
Su Ryeon...
I can't hear you.
What are you saying?
Run.
That...
Su Ryeon!
A murder at a penthouse?
How can something like this happen
at our Hera Palace?
This must be a lie.
Is that really Su Ryeon?
My goodness!
What happened?
Isn't that Oh Yoon Hee?
No way!
So, Oh Yoon Hee killed Su Ryeon?
That witch! You don't even deserve
to be called a human!
- My goodness.
- How could she?
- I don't believe it.
- No way.
- Oh Yoon Hee killed her?
- I can't believe it.
Na Ae Gyo?
This can't be true.
Get her!
(Jung Doo Man)
You have to take care
of Seok Kyung and Seok Hoon.
You're their real mom, after all.
Thank you, Na Ae Gyo.
I will avenge your death.
More coffee, please.
The coffee smells
especially good today.
That's enough, Dad.
You think she should be here
in an apron like that?
Bring our maids back.
It's fine. I'm fine on my own.
I won't be eating at home anymore,
so you don't need to cook my food.
Sit down.
Did I teach you to be so rude
at the table?
I didn't learn anything from you.
You brat!
Joo Seok Hoon! Stop there!
No need to cook my food either.
Might as well go on a diet.
What have you been doing to the kids
that they've become so rude?
Is it so hard to cook your food
to their taste?
You have to care for them like you
would for Eun Byeol!
I'll try harder.
I've never done
anything like this before,
but once I get used to it,
I'm sure I'll do well.
Why have you become...
so obedient?
What made you change your mind?
As long as you promise me
that you won't mess with Eun Byeol,
I'll try to listen to you
as much as I can.
Acting like I'm happy isn't
all that difficult.
I won't see Eun Byeol
without your permission either.
Do you mean it?
Just let Ro Na's case close...
with Ha Yoon Chul taking the blame.
Then, as you have asked for,
I'll give you everything,
including Cheong A Medical Center.
I'll think about it.
Thank you.
See? There you go.
How beautiful is it to admit defeat?
I'm having a great morning,
all thanks to you.
Sure. Laugh all you want.
If I have to die to get out of here,
I'll kill you too.
Goodness.
Have you looked into it?
What are you doing? Tell me already!
This is confidential information...
from the Ministry of Land,
Infrastructure and Transport.
I think it's true...
that Cheonsoo District is
being redeveloped in secret.
When?
The plans may be announced
this week at the earliest.
This week? That quickly?
Hey, then...
who has Joo Dan Tae's back?
He's known Jung Doo Man
for a very long time.
Jung Doo Man?
That's some powerful string
he's got.
Mr. Jung politely declined.
Is he trying to say that this is
not good enough or what?
Or is he trying to cut ties with me?
Kyu Jin is here!
Where are your manners?
You can't just come in
without calling in advance.
I'm a busy man.
Why?
Because you need to go and buy
more land in Cheonsoo District?
My gosh.
What do you mean, buy more land?
I sold all my properties.
This house is all I have.
Don't make rumors.
No, you sold all your properties
to buy more in Cheonsoo District.
You hired a representative...
to buy lot 27
for 50 million dollars recently too.
You should've offered
a higher price if you wanted it.
The rich getting richer.
Isn't that how the world works?
Kyu Jin is a little disappointed.
Where is our Hera Club bond?
I hear that the redevelopment will
be announced this week.
Where did you hear that?
I'm Assemblyman Lee Kyu Jin,
in the district of Gangnam!
You think I don't have my sources?
Brother!
Just hand me over a few good ones.
I'll give you the best prices.
I'd love to do that,
but one must always be careful,
and not be so tied down by money.
And a politician must live
an honest life,
don't you think so?
You starved in protest...
of real estate speculation,
so imagine how betrayed
your people would feel...
to find out that you're drooling
over some properties...
and trying to participate
in real estate speculation yourself.
I guess you don't need
that golden badge anymore.
Hey! This is personal.
How can you use the public
against me? That's a betrayal.
You don't think I can buy any land
without you?
"Any" land?
If you're so confident,
go out and buy some yourself.
Why are you coming to me
and begging me for it?
All right. It's on.
If this is how it's going to go,
I'm going to buy as much as I can.
Don't regret it later,
you greedy pig,
no, you swindler!
Idiot. That won't happen.
The announcement is happening
in just two days.
The game's over.
Here. I've even brought my son's
gold ring from his first birthday!
Give me whatever is left
in the Cheonsoo District!
I'll take any land that's left.
There must be a garbage dump left
or something!
I'm going to suspend this place
if you don't give me anything.
How many times do I need
to tell you?
There's really no more land left.
That's why we're pleading you.
Talk to the landlords, Mr. Hwang.
You can't call him Mr. Hwang.
Call him Sir Hwang Geum Bong.
Whatever.
I'm Red Pants.
I'm the queen who's turned...
a mulberry field into
a 15-story condo!
Everyone in this industry knows...
that my mother-in-law is
the big hand here!
If you give us something good,
we'll make sure to return the favor.
We'll triple the brokerage fee.
Please!
Yes, please!
I don't know what to do.
Don't you ever tell anyone this.
You're the only one I'm telling.
- What is it?
- Come closer.
They're going to build
a sports complex on this land.
Nobody saw, right?
Don't worry about it.
I came in through the back door.
So, what's this land
that's up for sale?
It's a golden spot. They're building
a high-end mall here.
You'll never see a listing
quite like this.
Why is the landlord putting
this land up for sale, then?
She took out a loan
from a loan shark...
and got caught by her husband.
Really? That's unfortunate.
I'll buy all of this. Okay?
I heard that there's some good land.
Here. These are
100-percent gold bars.
This is the letter of guarantee.
Sell the land to me.
(Golden Real Estate)
I sealed the deal...
with the highest price.
Great work.
Please sell the rest
of the properties to them as well.
Everything under my name.
And please have them pay
upfront in cash.
(Gangnam Police Station)
Had she known that
her birth father killed her...
What are you saying?
Apologize to Ro Na sincerely
for just once.
I feel so bad for my daughter,
who never even got...
to be treated like your daughter.
You can do that much, can't you?
I found out after we broke up...
that I was pregnant with Ro Na.
You were already engaged to Seo Jin.
I couldn't go back to you.
I rushed to marry someone else.
Of course,
I told him I was pregnant.
He liked me a lot,
and promised to love my baby too.
But once he saw the baby
that wasn't like him at all,
he changed.
He never came home...
and wouldn't even look at her.
Poor Ro Na had a very sad childhood.
She never received any love.
No. It can't be.
Why... Why wouldn't I
recognize my own child?
She's lying.
She's lying. She's lying.
She's lying!
Hey, you.
Have some manners
for your cellmates.
- Hey.
- Have you gone crazy?
Stay down, will you?
Shut your own mouth!
- You jerk.
- Hey.
Do you have a death wish?
Yes, kill me.
I want to die like crazy!
Why you...
You...
You jerk.
- Step on him.
- Okay.
You jerk.
Keep it down!
Hit me more.
Hit me more, you jerks.
- You psycho!
- Hey.
Hey!
You jerk.
Hey.
Stop it.
- Separate.
- Let go!
Stop it.
Darn it.
You jerks.
Kill me.
Kill me!
Goodness.
Oh my gosh.
What's your problem?
Why are you here?
Don't you have a TV?
I'm too nervous to watch alone.
Today's the day, right?
You acted like
you were Oh Yoon Hee's friend,
but it was all one-sided.
See? There's no friendship
when it comes to land and money.
Fine. I agree. You're right.
I learned a lot from this.
You shouldn't be nice
to just anyone.
That's why I came back
to my old stomping ground.
- Be quiet.
- Include me.
Sorry.
The news is about to start.
Raise the volume.
Okay.
They officially announced...
the plans to develop a new town...
in Cheonsoo District.
Here's the Minister of Land,
Infrastructure and Transport.
Hello.
I'm Minister Kim Ki Song.
Today...
- Kyu Jin! Well done!
- Oh my gosh!
Let's celebrate!
Let's go!
- Here we go.
- Oh my gosh!
Hey! Do you know what this is?
Russo-Baltique Vodka.
Vodka!
It costs
1.3 million dollars a bottle!
Mom! We should drink stuff like this
to say we're millionaires!
- Me too!
- Yes!
I'm rich now!
The related industries
can't hide their excitement...
about the unexpected announcement
regarding the development project.
Cheonsoo District, which was
selected for the development...
I own 70 percent
of Cheonsoo District.
There were many speculations
and expectations.
Everything is absolutely perfect.
It was more shocking
because it was a surprise.
The construction consulting results
came out today as well.
The government plans to change
the permitted use of the land...
and had the consulting firm
examine deregulation as well.
Cheonsoo District will undergo
major redevelopment...
and is predicted to become
the new center of Gangnam.
The government plans
to build a new city...
that includes residential
and commercial areas...
The person you have reached is
unavailable.
- Please leave a message...
- It will be at the forefront...
The value of the real estate
in the district is expected...
to skyrocket...
following the announcement.
We expect
many people will be interested,
so we will keep updating you
as we receive more information.
What is it?
We have no reason
to see each other anymore.
I never knew
there would come a day...
when you actually help me.
What are you getting at?
I'm in a good mood.
I don't want to ruin it.
If you're bored
because you have no one to talk to,
your friend is in the kitchen.
Go talk to her.
I guess you weren't confident...
about the Cheonsoo District
development either.
How could you cancel the contract...
the day before the announcement?
I canceled the contract?
Didn't you know?
Na Ae Gyo suddenly
notified me last night...
that she was canceling the contract.
I know you wanted it for a while.
So I came to ask
why you changed your mind.
What are you talking about?
She said she needed the cash
urgently.
She seemed desperate,
so I didn't even charge her
the penalty.
Although it's for the best for me...
since they suddenly announced
the development plan.
No one can cancel the contract
without my permission.
I never canceled it.
Then did Na Ae Gyo deceive you?
(Golden Real Estate)
You must've trusted her
a great deal.
Enough to bet your all.
That was so unlike you.
The person you have reached is
unavailable. Please leave...
My money...
How dare you take off with my money?
I'll kill you, Na Ae Gyo.
Did you locate her?
She is at the real estate agency
in Cheonsoo District.
I instructed the guards
to keep her there.
Let's go!
(Golden Real Estate)
(Property Sale Contract
Cancellation)
(Na Ae Gyo)
What did you do?
How dare you sell my land
without my permission?
Why is it your land?
They're in my name, so they're mine.
Are you finally
showing your true colors?
You really did try to betray me
since two years ago.
Have you lost your mind?
Why did you do this? Why?
I trusted you.
I should be compensated for living
in Shim Su Ryeon's shadow...
for all those years.
I can't just rely on you.
Who knows what will happen?
I simply took care of myself.
Where's my money?
Idiot.
Like I'd tell you?
(Golden Real Estate)
Let go!
Get in before I mess up your face.
Get her!
Get on.
Catch up, you jerk!
(Stop)
(Danger)
Why are you here?
You could get caught.
He's dying to kill you.
I don't care.
I'll risk my life
to stay next to you.
No matter how hard you try
to push me away, I'm not leaving.
Why are you doing this?
What if something happens to you
because of me?
Think about what happened
to Na Ae Gyo.
Nothing matters to me...
except protecting you.
Take revenge...
as planned.
(Gangnam Police Station)
Wait!
Why did you kill Bae Ro Na?
Did you deliberately kill
your daughter's rival?
Did your daughter ask you to do it?
Don't you feel bad
as her stepfather?
- Why did you kill her?
- Can you say something?
- Did you apologize?
- Answer my question!
- Mr. Ha!
- Say something!
- Please say something!
- I'm okay.
- Mr. Ha!
- Say something!
Dad.
Dad. Wait.
- Mr. Ha!
- Don't you have anything to say?
Any comment at all?
(Gangnam Police Station)
- Don't push!
- Step back!
Dad!
Hello, it's me.
Tonight?
I'll be ready.
She hasn't come back
to the cottage.
Hey.
Would you go back there?
Are you an idiot?
- What about the airport?
- It's being watched.
You can't miss her.
If you miss her, you're dead meat.
Gosh, seriously.
The person you have reached is
unavailable. Please...
Pick up, Na Ae Gyo.
What took you so long?
I asked you to bring me drinks
ages ago.
Who are you
so desperately looking for?
Who is this Na Ae Gyo?
Why? Are you
going to find her for me?
Slow down. You'll get drunk.
Stop getting on my nerves
and get lost.
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
Darn it. Seriously.
Na Ae Gyo, that witch.
The cottage and the airport...
are being watched by Dan Tae's men.
I was prepared for that.
Bring the money to the storage
by 10 p.m. and I'll spare your life.
It's time.
Everything will be okay.
Don't worry.
Hello?
Joo Dan Tae is trying to kill me.
Save me.
Where am I?
Let me see.
(Power off)
(Chamsarang Pet Funeral Home)
Gosh.
How are you feeling?
What happened yesterday?
You blacked out
because you drank too fast.
Should I make some soup?
No, you don't have to.
My head is splitting.
Why can't I remember anything?
I didn't drink that much.
Where's my phone?
I couldn't find it in the room.
I haven't seen it.
Should I call it?
This is a search and
seizure warrant.
Dan Tae!
- Don't step on this.
- Dan Tae!
Dan Tae! Dan Tae!
Don't step on this either.
- Search the place.
- These people...
Joo Dan Tae, correct?
I am.
You are under arrest...
for murder and desecration
of a human corpse.
Cuff him.
What are you talking about?
- Whom did I kill?
- Stop it.
Are you people out of your minds?
Na Ae Gyo died last night.
Ae Gyo died?
Oh my gosh.
Let's talk at the station.
Wait.
Dan Tae. What's going on?
You killed a person?
You didn't right? Talk to me!
He has a soft heart.
He can't even kill a bug.
- There must be a mistake.
- Let go!
Can you confirm where he was
last night?
You know...
I came home early and went to sleep.
Tell them.
We use separate rooms,
so I'm not positive.
I know he was drunk...
and very upset.
That's all I know...
Wait. He kept calling someone.
Who?
He said, "Na Ae Gyo."
Why you... Have you gone mad?
Let go of me!
I did not kill her.
Show me proof!
I won't go anywhere until you do.
Call my secretary. Get my lawyer!
Darn it.
We found this in the chimney.
Oh my gosh.
A partially burned glove,
raincoat, and shoes.
- Take it as evidence.
- Yes, sir.
It wasn't me.
I've never even seen that before.
I saw muddy footprints...
by the door this morning,
so I thought it was strange.
Did you really kill that woman?
The kids' biological mom?
How do you know...
who Ae Gyo is?
Take him away.
Your car was clearly caught
on camera...
in front of the warehouse
and the crematorium.
You ran over the victim
and killed her,
took her to the crematorium,
and burned her body, correct?
The owner of the crematorium
already confessed...
to taking money from you
and letting you use it anonymously.
I did no such thing.
This is insane.
I got drunk last night...
and slept in my room.
I never went outside.
How could I have killed someone?
If you don't believe me,
ask my wife, Cheon Seo Jin.
Cheon Seo Jin said
she can't confirm that.
What?
She's lying.
I am innocent.
You're falling for
a ridiculous ploy.
I swear I never went
to the warehouse...
or the crematorium.
If you don't trust me,
check Hera Palace's cameras.
See if I left the building
last night.
Around what time did you discover
the muddy footprints?
I saw them when I went
to get the paper,
so it was probably around 5 a.m.
Then he did leave
in the middle of the night.
The strange thing is,
there is no record
of him leaving the building...
after 8 p.m. in any of
Hera Palace's security videos.
Is there another way out?
It's a murder.
You have to tell us the truth.
What did he do here?
This is where he punished
his children.
I only found out recently...
after we got married.
Photograph everything.
Yes, sir.
And here.
This is a way out
of the building...
without passing the fountain.
There's an elevator
that leads directly to the garage.
Then he may have used this
to leave last night.
Call the captain. Tell him
we found the secret passage.
Yes, sir.
He may have hidden important clues,
so search everything.
There's something in here.
It's an urn.
Oh my gosh! It can't be!
Send it to NFS right away.
Find out if there's any DNA left.
- Rush it.
- Yes, sir.
Hey.
Okay.
They found human ashes...
in your study.
Ashes?
What ridiculous gibberish is that?
Why would there be ashes in my home?
I heard you said
you'd kill Na Ae Gyo.
We have a witness.
What witness?
I slept all day. Who saw me? Where?
I'm a witness.
I heard you say
you'd kill Na Ae Gyo.
I heard it clearly.
Oh Yoon Hee.
What is this gibberish?
I met with him yesterday morning
in his penthouse.
He was extremely angry at Na Ae Gyo.
The look in his eyes was terrifying.
So I recorded it just in case.
My money...
How dare you take off with my money?
I'll kill you, Na Ae Gyo.
You have a clear motive,
and all the circumstances
point to you.
Will you still deny it?
Oh Yoon Hee. You...
Search thoroughly.
- Yes, sir.
(Police)
Hey. Move this.
Help me.
I'm sorry. Please don't kill me.
It's okay. We're the police.
What's your name?
I'm Shim Su Ryeon.
Were you locked in here?
Joo Dan Tae...
locked us in here.
How long have you been here?
What's today's date?
(The Penthouse 2)
Who's alive?
Shim Su Ryeon. She's back.
- It's payback.
- Don't give me that.
He lost his money, he was betrayed,
and he became a murderer.
You won't rot in jail alone.
What did we do wrong?
It's time to give back
what I received.
I want a divorce.
I won't go down alone.
Don't leave me again.
You must protect your child
at all costs.
Since you're her mom.