(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
Tae Han, we got a report.
It looks like Kang Soo stole from a claw machine store.
Nice one.
Hey, Tae Han. You're back.
Come out here.
Give me a moment. It's the last game.
I said come here!
Why are you yelling again?
Is it because you're a cop now?
You steal when your brother's a cop?
- What? - You promised,
that you wouldn't steal again.
It wasn't me, okay?
Okay.
Let's go to the police station.
It really wasn't me!
You're just the same.
Even if no one else believes me, you should.
That's family!
How dare you talk back at me?
I went there to win something.
I kept our promise!
Hey!
Hello.
Are you sure?
It wasn't Kang Soo?
Okay, bye.
(Tae Han.)
Tae Han. Congratulations on becoming a cop.
I'll buy you the real deal one day, not a fake.
I spent 10 dollars trying to win this.
- He looks badly hurt. - Oh, dear...
- He's bleeding badly. - Let's call 911.
- Is he dead? - We're at...
- I'll give you my number. - There was an accident.
Get here quick.
It looks bad. His helmet came off.
(Dark Hole)
(Episode 4)
Look at that.
The surgical ward was shut down.
(Help! There are survivors here.)
Wait.
Look. Isn't that your wife?
That's my wife.
Daddy's off to work. See you.
Take care!
My Ji Hye's up there!
No! Ji Hye!
What happened?
Why is your wife up there?
Our baby's almost due, so she said she'd see the doctor.
I couldn't reach her on her phone, so I assumed she was at home.
How do we get up there?
That ward was closed. It's surrounded by mutants.
It's too dangerous.
Should we leave his wife there, then?
What is it? Do you have a plan?
No. I'll figure one out as I go along.
Hwa Sun!
- Are you okay? - Yes.
Follow us to the school.
Let's go.
Were you the one who made the announcement?
I'm a teacher here.
He's our security guard.
Let's hurry up and go inside.
This way.
Go on. I'll be right behind you.
Hurry up and take the kid.
Come on.
Come on. Hurry.
Those who refuse to follow me will all die.
(Muji High School)
Are you okay?
What... What just happened?
- Are you okay? - I'm okay. It's nothing serious.
- Did you hurt your arm? - Yes, I think I sprained it.
- It's not a big deal. - Let me take a look.
It's okay.
- Let me see. - Mr. Choi!
What do you think you're doing?
What if they're all infected?
Sir, they're not infected.
They just needed help.
Then what about them?
What if they become dangerous because of these two?
Will you take responsibility then?
Mr. Choi, what are you doing?
Hurry up and kick them out!
That's enough.
You're starting to make me sick.
What did you say?
Don't act like you care about others.
You're just trying to protect yourself, Dad.
How dare you...
That's enough. The students are watching.
Let go of me.
I'm a cop.
Do you want to get arrested for assault?
I get that you're scared.
But unlike what you think, we didn't get infected.
How do you expect me to believe you?
Look at my eyes.
Tell me if these are the eyes of someone infected.
We'll have to see if that's true or not.
Meanwhile, let go of me. You might break a bone.
(Muji Hospital)
- Is everything okay? - Yes, it's fine.
Good.
What? Hey, look.
Everyone! Look over here!
The smoke is disappearing. Hurry.
- Really? - Seriously?
Gosh, it's really disappearing.
- It's gone. - My goodness.
Hyun Ho! Hyun Ho!
Officer Cho!
You could get yourself killed by going there.
Get off me!
I need to go and get my wife.
Calm down.
What about the mutants in the hospital?
Your wife was with other people,
which means she escaped to somewhere safe.
The rescue team will be here soon, so let's just wait.
Don't lie.
You know no one's coming to rescue us.
I'll go with you.
You know the hospital pretty well, right?
Just take us to the surgical ward on the fifth floor.
I haven't been working here for long.
Wait a minute.
Why are you heading to another ward?
We found other survivors on a different floor.
We're on our way to save them.
Would anyone like to help?
Wait.
So you're causing a fuss...
just to go and save those people?
Did you just call this a fuss?
You're obviously making a fuss.
What if all the mutants in the hospital end up coming here?
- What will you do then? - What if they were your family?
Would you have said the same thing?
Hey, listen.
What are you? A kid? Stop playing cop.
Who are you?
What do you think you're doing? You got fired for getting bribed.
(Investigation Team for Detective Crime 1)
How did it go?
What's there to ask?
I got fired.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Why are you sorry?
What? Well...
I don't know who did this, but wait until I catch this jerk.
Don't overreact. I can make a living doing something else.
Let's go for some drinks.
What? I'm only stating the truth.
Right, Officer Park?
Just stay quiet, okay?
Get out of the way if you're not going to help.
Is there anyone else who is willing to help?
Let's go by ourselves.
Soon Il.
- Gosh. - Where are you going?
Hey, are you still wearing that?
Let's go.
- Will they be okay? - My goodness.
- It's dangerous out there. - Gosh.
(Fire door)
Stay calm and take deep, steady breaths.
- Ma'am. - Yes?
Should we take her to the negative pressure room on the fourth floor?
What are you planning to do?
Hey, don't tell me you're trying to get out of here.
The mutants have just disappeared.
This is our chance to move.
Are you saying we're going to open the door?
What do you suggest then?
Should we all just die here?
Is it okay for us to move by ourselves?
I think we should wait for the rescue team or the police.
What do you think?
I also think it's dangerous to go out.
This lady's condition is pretty serious.
She needs to be moved to a safer place.
Gosh. No place is safe in this situation.
Isn't the negative pressure room safe?
You're right. There, we can control the air pressure...
so that the smoke doesn't get in.
Also, the inner and outer doors will keep the mutants out.
Listen. There's no way...
we can take that pregnant woman all the way there safely.
What if some mutants pop out on the way?
We'll figure something out.
I'll lead the way.
You guys protect the lady.
What should we do?
Look.
Let's stop thinking.
In a situation like this,
it's best to listen to a civil servant.
Goodness.
Fine, let's do that.
All of you, grab something that can be used as a weapon.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Thank you for your help.
It must not have been easy.
Don't mention it.
I just wanted to save as many people as I could.
Anyway, why do you think the black smoke and the mutants...
suddenly disappeared?
I think they responded to the strange, high-frequency sound.
A high-frequency sound?
I didn't hear anything.
Really?
Yes.
What could the sound...
that only you heard be?
I don't know anything for sure yet,
but considering how the mutants suddenly stopped attacking,
I think they're being controlled by something.
By the way, I haven't introduced myself.
My name is Choi Seung Tae.
I'm Detective Lee Hwa Sun from Seoul.
Move, you punk!
What on earth happened here?
What...
What happened?
Goodness. What is this?
This is bad.
The person you have reached is unavailable...
Darn it!
You little punk.
Didn't I tell you to keep an eye on this place?
- You did. - And?
What happened to the door?
Why are all my cows gone?
You stupid punk. What were you doing...
when all my babies disappeared?
You idiot.
Who are you?
You have been chosen.
You will soon meet the one who chose you.
How's it going?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Nothing seems to be happening right now.
I hope they can stay away from the mutants.
Doctor, I'll go check on the generator for a second.
- Sure, go ahead. - Okay.
Wait. All the mutants are gone from this place.
(Muji Hospital, 2nd floor)
Is there another way we can get there?
One second.
Hello?
Yes, this is the security office.
Let me see.
Turn the corner you're at,
and at the end of the corridor on the left is a staircase.
It's deserted at the moment.
- It's too dangerous to leave now. - Let me leave.
- You can't... - Listen.
The smoke's gone and so have the mutants.
How long must I stay here for?
Whether it's to an army base or another city,
let's do something.
You two are way too noisy.
Listen.
Why are you making a fuss, miss, when they want to leave?
Can a man get some sleep?
My wife and kid are waiting for me,
and you want me to sit here and do nothing?
You can stay here. I'm leaving.
Whoever of you wants to go, you can come with me.
We can't leave now.
- Not yet. - We can't go yet.
I'm leaving too.
- Let's go. - Us too.
Okay. Let's all go.
Dad.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Dad. Don't go.
Dad.
Dad, don't leave us.
Open the door quickly.
You can't leave on your own.
Let go.
Let go of me.
Honey. You can't leave us.
Dad, save me!
- Dad! - My gosh.
You're out of your mind.
- Take us with you! - No.
- You trash! - It's not true.
You can't leave us here!
I'm not your husband!
You all die if you go outside.
Who are you?
Then leave.
If you don't do as I say, you'll be severely punished.
You just have to show these people.
You're crazy.
How dare a shaman talk like that to me?
Come along.
- Let's go. - Okay, let's.
- Wait. - I'm going voluntarily.
- Don't. - Stay.
- Where will you go? - You can't leave.
- Stay here. - Oh, dear...
They're really leaving.
What rotten luck.
What?
It's nothing. Let's get going.
He showed me everything.
- Open the door! Let me in! - Get lost, freak!
- Open the door! The door! - Darn it.
Why won't it start?
Open the door! Open up! Let me in!
Open the door! Save me!
Darn it.
Why won't it start?
- They're dead. - They died.
My goodness.
Ms. Kim, you were right.
You said they'd die if they left.
They did.
- That's right. - She did warn them.
- This is so scary. - What is going on?
- What should we do? - I want this to go away.
That shaman is going to cause bloodshed.
- Oh, dear. - Will you look at this?
I'm sorry, sir.
It's not like the kids have ever hammered a nail before.
If they are poor at it, you should've taught them.
Must I tell you what to do in detail?
No, sir. I apologize.
Are you kidding me?
Jin Seok. Let go. We can talk it out.
Hey mister. Are you playing games with me?
You can have pickled radish if you want.
Eat it.
Hey!
You can't talk to a teacher like that.
Do you still think I'm a student here?
Hey. You guys expelled me.
You kicked me out and now you want to teach me?
Hey, rude kid.
What?
If you're not a kid, why are you such a picky eater?
Oh. Are you showing off because you're a detective?
Darn you...
Oh, no.
Don't do it.
Open your eyes.
Stand up.
What? What are you staring at?
Grandma told you to come and eat.
- Over there. Do you see it? - See what?
Over there.
We could play catch if we had that, right?
You're awesome, Do Yoon.
Good luck.
Hey! It's dangerous! Get back, quick!
Hey!
[VIU Ver] OCN E04 'Dark Hole'
"Inside the Black Smoke"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
Why did you go outside?
You know what happens if you inhale smoke.
Tell me! Why did you go outside?
If we're to fight the mutants,
you need a gun.
You're a detective.
Wait.
Your name's Do Yoon, right?
Gosh, you're amazing, Do Yoon.
You're really brave.
But don't do anything dangerous like this from now on.
Okay?
Why don't you go on inside?
I need to talk to Detective Lee.
Do Yoon.
You may be good at catching criminals,
but you're not very good when it comes to talking to kids.
What she did was reckless.
She knows that.
But even so, she chose to risk her life for you.
I know this may sound out of line,
but don't shut people out too much.
We all need to work together in order to overcome this.
Put some tripe on top of a perilla leaf.
Then add some glass noodles on top. What comes next?
- Garlic. - Yes, you put garlic on top.
- Then you wrap it up. - You wrap it...
and put it in my mouth.
Are you a pig? Why are you eating everything?
You guys are amateurs.
He actually tried to steal my food earlier.
Don't you guys know what Chapaguri is?
Mix it with your right hand
Mix it with your left hand
You're talking about Bibimmyeon, you dumb fool.
My gosh, seriously.
Hey, I told you punks to be quiet.
What are you looking at? What do you want?
Have you lost your mind?
Hey, quit being a jerk and just get lost.
You couldn't even say a word to that detective earlier.
Have you all gone nuts?
What? What do you want?
You just wait and see. I'll get back at you for this.
He should be embarrassed of himself. Why are you up? Lie back down.
Should we just go and beat the soul out of him?
- Should we do that? - Should we?
Shut it.
Kid, where did your mother go? Why are you here alone?
She isn't...
my mom.
My mom is...
It's okay. Don't bother.
You don't need to tell me anything.
Let's go eat with Chan.
What are you doing?
I bet you're enjoying this.
What are you talking about?
You think you know my weakness.
Go ahead and tell everyone.
Just go tell them so I can kill you.
I told you...
to tell me how you're going to kill me.
Let me know once you come up with a creative way...
to kill me.
Although I'm not sure if you're smart enough to think of something.
Do Yoon! Do as the detective says.
You must live. Okay?
Detective! Drive! Now!
My mom...
would always find me whenever I would hide.
It's okay now.
It's cold at night.
Thank you.
Kids become friends so quickly.
I'm sure you'll also become good friends with her.
I don't know how I should treat her.
When I look into her eyes, I can see how desperate she is.
But I'm not sure if I'll be able to protect her.
I'm scared.
Well...
I'm sure she just wants...
to be reassured...
that you're always going to be with her.
So you don't need to try too hard.
Gosh!
Be quiet.
This is Doctor Han Ji Soo.
Yes.
There's an emergency exit near the Cardiovascular Center.
I think it'll be best for you to exit through there.
Okay, got it.
(Muji Hospital, 3rd floor)
The police should lead the way.
(Muji Hospital, 4th floor)
What is it?
I think we're good.
Let's go.
- Are you okay? - Yes.
I should hang in there for the sake of my baby.
What?
Look over there.
What are they doing there?
That's the fourth floor.
They're heading to the negative pressure room.
The smoke can't get in there,
so they're heading there for safety.
Do you hear me?
The people on the fifth floor are on their way...
The people on the fifth...
What is she saying?
The people on the fifth floor are on their way...
to the negative pressure room on the fourth floor.
They're on the 4th floor, not the 5th.
Officer Cho, can you hear me?
The fourth floor?
What does she want us to do on the fourth floor?
I think she's telling us to go to the fourth floor.
My gosh. Give me that.
Can you speak more...
Can you speak more clearly?
Officer Cho, can you hear me?
What's wrong?
I think I've seen that guard somewhere.
What do you mean?
Never mind.
I'm probably just being paranoid.
Run!
Hurry up!
Did you see how I exercised my public authority?
Couldn't you shoot sooner?
I almost died.
Those who refuse to follow me will all die.
Those who refuse to follow me...
Tell me what you want.
I can make anything happen.
Accept me.
Then you can get revenge.
Who are you?
Why did you stop attacking earlier?
Because it's fun...
to make them do whatever I want.
Who did this?
Sir!
Wake up. Are you okay? Sir!
We should hurry up and move him to the shelter.
We can't move him there. We'll scare the people.
We could move him to the counseling office.
- Let's do that. - Okay.
- I'll carry him. - Be careful.
- Let's go. - Are you okay?
Be careful.
Let's hurry up.
Hurry up.
Move.
All right.
Do we have first-aid supplies?
To treat this wound, we need to get supplies from the nurse's office.
We can't enter the annex because of the mutants.
If he's not treated, he'll go into shock from blood loss.
I'll go get them.
Tell me where the nurse's office is.
It's too dangerous to enter the annex.
You two risked your lives to save me.
What do we need?
A suture kit, hydrocolloid bandages,
dressings, NSAIDs, and hydrogen peroxide.
Also, povidone-iodine and dry powder, just in case.
Grab as many painkillers and anti-inflammatory drugs as you can.
Okay.
Detective.
Do you think this is civil defense training?
We're at war.
Do not act up without my permission.
If he's not treated immediately, he might die.
Yes, he might.
We all might because of you.
I own this school. I'm in charge.
Everyone here is my responsibility.
If you can't take responsibility for one person,
how will you take responsibility for everyone here?
Isn't it funny?
Wherever you go, there's always one troublemaker...
who puts everyone in danger.
- What did you say? - That's why...
order and control are absolutely important.
We can't let the one troublemaker who popped out of nowhere...
ruin everything for us.
Tell the truth. What is it you really want?
Stay here under my control,
or in return for getting the medical supplies you want,
leave this school.
Fine.
I'll get the medical supplies, then leave.
Detective.
Oh, yes. I'm so forgetful.
You came with a kid. Leave with the kid.
Stop it, Father. Anyone who leaves will die!
To save everyone else, sacrifices must be made!
Is that not true?
Director Choi. Sending the child too is a bit...
Do you want to go instead, Mr. Song?
Dong Rim.
Wow, Han Dong Rim.
I have a plan.
What is it?
You can reach the nurse's office and avoid the mutants.
You're out of your mind.
Follow me.
The quickest way there is to take the pedestrian overpass.
(Pedestrian overpass)
But as we fled over here,
we locked all the doors to keep the mutants out.
Where are the keys?
The teacher who had the keys...
became a mutant.
You can get there without the keys.
- What? - This door is broken.
Sir, what are you doing?
I'm taking a look because they say this door won't lock.
I think this needs to be replaced.
- The whole thing? - Yes.
You lot are so frustrating.
What are you doing here?
Well... I came to help.
What are you up to?
A man's at death's door. Should I just sit and watch?
I'm not that much of a jerk.
And, like she said, if the doors open...
How are they to pass the study hall corridor?
We don't know how many mutants there are and where.
Do you three think you can fight through them?
Are you saying you have another plan?
I'm pretty smart when it comes to being sly.
Tell me. What is your sly trick?
Are you good at being a distraction?
Hey.
- Do you hear me? - What's that?
Where is it coming from?
- It's not mine. - Yes, Detective.
You won't believe me, but I saw something in the smoke.
The black smoke might not be the end of it.
What do you mean the black smoke's not the end?
Inside the black smoke,
I think is a being we don't yet know about.
Be careful.
Detective. Detective?
What detective? Who was that?
She's a detective from Seoul.
She said there's another being in the black smoke.
What?
(To be operated by medical personnel only)
We pumped his stomach and we found a pesticide.
He can leave after the IV drip's done and he wakes up.
Sir, it's me.
I think this idiot ingested some pesticide. Yes.
I'll bring him in after his drip is done.
What do I do?
- Check Room 503's vitals. - Okay.
Sir.
(All child actors underwent psychological therapy.)
(Special thanks to Lee Cheol Min.)
(Dark Hole)
The black smoke...
is watching us, not attacking us.
That's why you should not trust people. You must trust him.
It's the mark of the chosen.
Listen to me carefully.
Hey!
Do you think you can run from them?
Go, Detective. You'll end up in danger too.
There's no time to wait. Hurry!