♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I’ve never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫  I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I’ll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I’ll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don’t regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 3
Yesterday you were still fine.
And today you get hurt.
Did you meet you foe?
Eat something at least, brave man.
Then you can get recovered soon.
I've been wandering in streets since little.
And I've met all kinds of people.
I can conclude that
you must been in tough days recently,
or you have a blood feud.
Did you just have a tough fight with your foe today?
If you say one more word,
you will die.
No. No. No.
Brave man.
No. Master.
Though I don't know who you are,
you can't be an ordinary person.
Me, A'Dou, lives a poor life.
Even if I died someday,
I'm afraid that no one would realize it.
If I can follow you and do something great,
it would be worth even if I'd die.
Search carefully.
Master, why are soldiers here?
Finding this place from Rongen Temple,
they move too fast.
Rongen Temple?
I heard that soldiers guarding Rongen Temple
got poisoned.
Was that you?
I knew that I was right about you.
You even dare poison soldiers.
Master, you're indeed not ordinary.
Mr. Du.
It's so late now.
I didn't expect you're still investigating here.
Mr. Du.
Why are you here, Mr. Fang?
I heard that Pinxiang Store
[Pinxiang Store]
has the best cookie among Changan City.
My wife wants to taste it,
so I'm here on my own to see how good it is.
When I was downstairs,
I got stopped by soldiers.
After me inquiring,
it turns out Mr. Du is investigating here.
You're really well-informed, Mr. Fang.
Why is it on fire?
It looks like I can't buy cookies today.
Father.
Mr. Fang.
Do you really insist breeding the evil?
I don't understand, Mr. Du.
I'm confused.
Mr. Du. I have to go.
I need to go home now
to tell my wife about it.
See you.
[Pinxiang Store]
Master, why is it on fire?
Father, it's weird about the fire.
I'm afraid...
Please be assured, father.
I'll investigate it thoroughly.
No need.
Since someone wants to protect her,
he won't leave a trace.
Is it possible...
that Mr. Fang set it on fire?
Don't draw a conclusion so soon.
Pinxiang Store is empty today.
That person might not want to hurt innocent people.
Let's leave here.
Send people put the fire out first.
Master, the fire is too strong.
What should we do?
Run.
Master. Wait. Stop.
Master.
Why is it suddenly on fire?
And that ladder.
Looks like someone prepared it for you.
What's going on?
Master.
Why don't you say anything?
Remove the trace showing I was there with fire.
There won't be any evidence of my trace there.
Then that's a favor for you, right?
A favor?
My mother just died recently in Rongen Temple.
I won't accept that favor.
Rongen Temple?
So Lady Jin is your mother?
Knowing too much won't do any good to you.
Whoever you are,
you're my Master.
Pinxiang Store is burned.
From now on, I have no place to stay.
Master,
please let me follow you.
Let me say it again.
I'm not your Master.
Following me means you'll die at any time.
Leave me alone.
Master...
[Crown Prince and Prince Qi died. Kill all their followers.]
Fang Yi.
[Harmony Brings Serenity]
Yes, your Highness.
Go to battalion suburbs and send my order,
that the rebellion stops at Jiancheng and Yuanji.
I won't blame their followers.
Your highness, that's...
What happened in Xuanwu Gate was not what I want.
No more people should die.
Yes.
That was an unexpected storm.
I can't help with that.
I wish after the storm,
Tang will be fine
and people will be safe.
[Crown Prince and Prince Qi died. Kill all their followers.]
Changge.
Didn't you say that you'll accept
the 100 amulets that I prayed for your blessing?
You haven't got any,
and now you're missing.
Please be safe.
Bodhisattva.
Please.
Please make sure that Changge stays safe.
[Yining Fang]
[Prince Qin ordered that the rebellion stops at Jiancheng...]
Tegin, how is it?
Our effort was in vain.
Prince Qin has suppressed the turmoil among soldiers.
How can he be so quick?
I didn't expect him to be so capable and broad-minded.
He pardoned all followers of the two princes.
With only an order,
he eliminated the turmoil among soldiers.
I despised him before.
What should we do now?
Prince Qin isn't an ordinary man.
Even if we continue staying in Changan,
we won't gain anything.
Let's leave here now
and go to Youzhou.
Youzhou?
Why are we going there?
We can't gain anything here in Changan during this visit.
Father has been suspicious.
If I go back with no gain,
my dear brother will make a fuss.
Youzhou is like a gateway to Changan.
We can only search things there
to keep him quiet.
I understand.
Mr. Fang.
I'm on my way to meet you at your home.
Greetings to Princess Yongan.
Princess?
Princess might haven't heard about it.
During the meeting this morning,
Your Majesty has granted Prince Qin as Crown Prince.
Naturally Lady becomes Princess now.
Thanks to your Majesty.
[Great Mountains]
Why did Princess want to meet me?
Mr. Fang.
I want to ask for your help.
Changge?
I know that Mr. Fang cherished Changge most.
I also know that you won't catch Changge.
Today I come here
just wanting to know the truth from you.
How is Changge?
Please don't worry, Princess.
Princess Yongning hasn't been caught.
I knew it.
I knew Changge would be fine.
Please be assured, Princess.
She was taught by Your Highness and Wei Zheng.
I also spent a lot of time on her.
How can she be caught easily?
Just... it would be tough to her.
[Elegance and Serenity]
About your Highness' intention to pardon people.
I can understand that.
But I think your Highness can't pardon everyone.
What do you mean?
Leader of Tianjie Army, Luo Yi,
has been good friends with Li Jiancheng.
If he wants to revolt, it will be huge trouble.
Also, Li Changge, the daughter of Li Jiancheng,
will do harm to...
Keming.
The essence to make the country in harmony
is to win people's heart.
If officers keep suspecting each other
and I get strict and abuse punishment,
I'm afraid that I'll be like Emperor Yang of Sui.
Have you heard the saying?
Civilizing people after the turmoil
will be much more effective.
I'm too ignorant.
No wonder.
It's from Wei Zheng.
Xuanling just recommended him to me.
Your Highness.
Wei Zheng has always been stubborn.
And now your Highness wants to recruit him.
I'm afraid that it won't be easy.
Stubborn?
Wouldn't that just match your flavor?
Mr. Du.
[Crown Prince and Prince Qi died. Kill all their followers.]
It's about the safety of Changan City.
Be careful.
Don't leave any trace.
Besides,
it's special period now.
Send more people to guard every city gate.
Don't let any related person sneak out.
Please be assured.
I'll try my best to do it for your Highness.
[Tonghua Gate]
Does the officer from Eastern Palace
also need to hide in Changan City?
Move away.
You can even beat soldiers in the street in public.
What are you hiding from?
So it's you.
Why are you tracking me?
Tracking you?
It's you that ran into me.
What do you want?
You're from Eastern Palace
and you haven't pledged allegiance.
Why can you go in and out at your will?
Non of your business.
What are you doing?
Someone's coming.
Why do you look like this?
As if I'm bullying you.
From now on, soldiers will guard the city gate
and control those in and out.
Yes.
If it weren't for that guy,
we would have been out of this city now.
Let's figure out another way.
Go back first.
Let's go.
[Serenity is Wealth]
It seems that Retinue is determined to
keep sleeping until it's dark today.
I'm sorry for that, Mr. Du.
My father doesn't feel well recently.
It's not convenient for him to meet guests.
Your father doesn't feel bad physically,
but psychologically.
My father wouldn't listen to anyone.
I apologize on behalf of my father.
Shuyu, do you have siblings?
I have three brothers and one sister at hometown.
They're with my mother now.
Your father is so stubborn.
Just like a tall tree,
it'll get broken if it's too tough.
If your father has a bad ending,
can your family survive?
I'm just sorry for Family Wei.
Don't you understand the gains and losses inside of it?
I understand.
Good.
You're at the similar age with my foster son Hao Du.
He acts very properly.
You can communicate with him more often.
Seeing him is like seeing me.
Can you understand my words?
[Mansion of Wei]
Li Shimin's soldiers.
Is Mr. Wei...
Mr. Du.
Please wait, Mr. Du.
[Mansion of Wei]
I'll do my best to persuade my father.
Good boy.
Your Highness gives this Fish Token especially to you.
From now on,
you're with us, working for Mansion of Crown Prince.
You can use it to come in and out of Palace,
and meet your Highness and me anytime.
What's that?
There. Look.
Look there.
[Official Notice]
About the case that Li Jiancheng and Li Yuanji revolted,
since the head were killed,
Crown Prince asked Your Majesty for pardoning others.
As long as they pledge allegiance on their own,
they'll be pardoned and no more punishment.
That's really a kind Crown Prince.
Right.
With such Crown Prince,
it's our fortune.
Changge. That was really you.
You caught me.
And you can get promoted with that, right?
Why would you think of me like that?
I won't do it no matter when.
Then why did you surrender to Du Ruhui?
Answer me.
My father was Retinue for Crown Prince.
Things are wrong at Eastern Palace now.
Family Wei is in danger,
and it's gonna be ruined anytime.
If I treat Mr. Du indifferently,
how can I save my parents?
But Changge,
it won't last long.
Please trust me.
I don't trust anyone now.
Changge.
Your Highness has ordered that
anyone pledging allegiance will be pardoned.
Am I guilty?
I don't need to be pardoned.
You're not guilty.
Neither am I.
Everyone isn't guilty.
So you have to trust me.
I'll accompany you.
No one can accompany me now.
My mother died.
They all died.
Changge.
No. The Fish Token.
She probably wants to use Fish Token to get in the palace.
Why does she want to go back?
[Hongyi Palace]
[Gentle and Pleasant Breeze]
Tribe of Ashile has been very cunning.
They often betray their allies.
We can't reckon them like others.
I'm afraid the turbulence these days was also from them.
It's late now.
You can go back.
- Yes.
Your Highness!
It's me.
Congratulations!
Your Majesty let me send Seal of Crown Prince here,
your Highness.
Mother died. The Eastern Palace was in a disaster.
So many people's lives were for such thing.
Put it here.
If you don't have anything else,
you can go back.
Yes, your Highness.
Looks like something is wrong.
Changge. You can show yourself.
I knew I'm here.
You can hide from others,
but not from me.
I've let them record
that Princess Yongning has died.
You killed so many people in Eastern Palace.
Why would you like to let me go now?
Is it that you finally find your humanity?
So you can do me a favor,
and comfort yourself
because you suffered from a sense of guilt.
Or is it because
I'm just a woman without the status as Princess?
So I can't be a threat to you.
Changge.
Changge. Stop.
Even if I might die,
I'll revenge for my mother.
Changge. Just leave!
[Taoism Brings Peace]
Your Highness.
Your Highness' safety matters to the society.
How can you be in such a danger?
Traitor. You can't escape now.
Take Li Changge away.
- Yes.
Stop.
That dagger belongs to her.
I'll use this dagger kill the murder that killed my mother.
How dare you!
Someone here. Put her into the dead cell.
Wait.
Take Princess Yongning to the wing.
And take good care of her.
Your Highness.
You're breeding the evil.
Keming. I'm tired.
About what happened today,
you can't tell anyone else.
Yes.
Take her away.
- Move.
- Go.
Father. It's already well arranged.
I've set lookouts everywhere in Hongyi Palace.
Please be assured.
Father.
How's your Highness going to deal with Li Changge?
Breed the evil and cause lots of trouble.
Father, don't get too tired.
What should I do next?
Double the soldiers.
And let them secretly guard the wing at every corner of it.
Give her illusion that she's not well guarded.
If she wants to run away,
kill her at the spot.
Yes.
Why are they guarding me with so few soldiers?
Mother, what should I do?
Your Highness.
Mr. Fang. I can't fall asleep.
Play chess with me.
Yes.
How dare you!
I haven't started.
How dare you make your move?
Isn't your Highness waiting others to make a move first?
You can't know about me better.
Changge isn't a girl easy to deal with.
Your Highness is busy with official duties.
No need to bother with that.
Your Highness urgently summoned me here because of trusting me.
Your Highness. I'll deal with that.
She's your student.
You have to be responsible for her.
Yes.
[Assassination in Mansion of Prince Qin.
The assassin failed and got locked at the wing]
Assassination in Mansion of Prince Qin?
I didn't expect him to be so dauntless.
Tegin. Who are you talking about?
The guy that won us at the Cuju court.
So he's not an ordinary man.
Needless to say.
He's more than uncommon.
He also has an uncommon relationship with Prince Qin.
Prince Qin didn't put him into cell,
but let him live in the wing.
So we'll be friends with him.
Friends?
The enemy of our enemy is our friend.
What?
Changge was caught by my father.
And she got locked?
I heard servants talking about it this morning.
And they were seriously scolded by Commander Hao Du.
As for where's she now,
I didn't hear that.
Changge.
What should we do?
Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang must know
where they locked Changge.
Mr. Fang.
Princess.
I was going to visit you.
Mr. Fang is really like a prophet.
The rain tonight is the biggest assistant.
Are you really prepared, Princess?
I'm afraid.
Don't be afraid, Princess.
Think of every step that Mr. Fang has taught you.
And just do as he said.
Things will be okay.
I believe Mr. Fang.
Since little, it was Changge that protected me.
Now it's time for me to protect her.
Stubborn as her, Changge won't eat anything these days.
But your Highness ordered that
they should take good care of her.
Those guards are also worrying about that,
because no one can afford to neglect Princess.
Only your appearance will let Changge eat something.
The guards pretend to stop you.
Actually they wish that you can show up.
Only by this can they be off responsibility.
Remember. Don't get afraid.
The guards will definitely let you get in.
How dare you! That's Princess.
Mr. Du said that no one can get closed to the wing.
Please don't make things difficult for us.
I heard that Princess Yongning
hasn't been eating for 24 hours.
My father said that you should take good care of her.
If something bad happens to her,
can you afford that?
That's..
Princess just wants to send her some food.
She won't stay long.
Or are you doubting Princess?
Please, Princess.
Wait for me here.
Changge.
Chang... Changge.
I'm Leyan.
Why are you here?
Who sent you here?
Don't let Changge know that I sent you there.
She wouldn't accept this favor.
What you should do
is to show flaws deliberately.
Give her the information to run away.
Let Changge run away by herself instead of being rescued.
That's what Changge would accept.
It's raining tonight and suddenly becomes cold.
The guards the in backyard went home due to chill.
So I bring you hot soup and cookies.
Eat it when it's still hot.
How did you get in?
I'm Princess now.
They dare not stop me.
Your father killed my father.
You became Princess.
Princess Yongan.
Changge. It's not like what you think.
I don't care about being Princess or whatever.
From your room to this wing,
you won't pass the backyard.
How did you know there are no guards in the backyard?
Who taught you that?
Changge is extremely smart.
If she found out you're lying,
you don't need to hide anything from her.
Changge. Leave here now.
The door of the backyard is open.
The guards were also kept away.
Go as far as you can.
Don't ever come back.
How can I believe you?
Is it your father's trap,
or Du Ruhui's?
Then you'll declare that Princess Yongning
die from arrows when she was running away.
Yes or no?
Changge.
Do you really think that I'll do harm to you?
It's Mr. Fang.
Mr. Fang taught me that.
He said that you're stubborn.
Only by this can you run away.
Fang Xuanling.
Tell Fang Xuanling,
It's my business. I'll try to think of a way it on my own.
He doesn't need to have a pity on me.
I don't want to owe him anything.
The only thing can dispel her misgivings
is your sisterhood since little.
The only one can save Changge
is actually you.
Changge.
This is the amulet that I prayed for you recently.
Take it with you.
Then you'll definitely be safe.
Amulet?
You Mansion of Prince Qin
killed everyone in our Eastern Palace.
Your father killed my mother and father.
Now you want me to be safe?
I'm sorry, Changge.
I didn't know that.
I...
I'm sorry.
Princess Yongan.
From now on,
we two are foes and absolutely irreconcilable.
Changge.
We two are best sisters since childhood.
Sisters?
How can I be sisters
with the daughter of the man that murdered my father?
I'll count down from three.
Leave here now.
Otherwise don't blame me for being too cold.
Three.
Two.
One.
Changge.
I don't believe you really wanted me to leave.
If my death can relieve your hatred to my father,
I won't regret.
Changge.
Leyan.
Sorry.
Princess.
Why don't say anything?
Is it because Mr. Fang's strategy didn't work?
Your Majesty let me send Seal of Crown Prince here,
your Highness.
Anything abnormal?
Princess Yongan was here with some food.
I have checked.
Nothing abnormal.
Princess Yongan?
Right.
Princess?
- Somebody here.
- Yes.
Lock down Hongyi Palace.
The rest go after her with me.
Yes.
Princess.
Call the imperial doctor.
Your Highness.
Li Changge is the serious trouble of Tang.
We found Princess' maidservant
fainted outside of the study.
The study?
Hurry.
Back to the study.
Keming.
It's gone.
Someone here.
You have to catch Li Changge.
Yes.
Go.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There’s always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There’s always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There’s always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There’s always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad