♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫  I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 02
Father.
That "lad" who reversed the game today. It was you, right?
I didn't mean to break into the stadium.
But we were on a losing streak at that time.
So...
that's why I had to...
Well done.
You've brought not only the treasured dagger
but also honor for me.
Your Grandfather heard it and requested my presence at once.
He praised you very highly
and gave a rick reward.
I've never thought that a girl
could do better than your brothers.
Thanks for the praise.
Changge.
Where's Ashile Tribe's treasured sword?
Send it to my room.
I want to appreciate it.
I've already sent it to Second Uncle.
What?
How "good and dutiful" you are!
It's me who's raised you up
but how can you send the treasure to other people?
Second Uncle is also my family...
He's your family so what about me?
How dare you take his side?
Changge.
From now on,
I want you
to mention nothing about Family Qin.
Father.
You've misunderstood me.
- I...
- Please calm down.
Your Highness.
Mr. Wei.
[Wei Zheng]
Retinue Wei.
You finally come to see me.
Your Highness.
She's still young
so you need not flare up for it.
She's unfilial!
She only cares about Prince Qin!
I don't think she'll concern me!
Your Highness.
Wei Zheng!
Don't waste time!
Come with me!
Yes.
Leave here.
Go to Mansion of Prince Qi and ask Yuanji to come here at once!
Yes.
- Mother.
- Halt there!
You don't take my advice anymore, right?
Then what did I tell you yesterday?
I just...
You just went over the wall and dressed up as a player
to be in the limelight in front of the Ashile, right?
Mother...
I won the game.
Father said that
Grandfather praised me a lot.
You've never slapped me before...
You've been wild since your childhood,
always making trouble.
I'm to blame for not lecturing you well.
You've been spoiled by me.
How dare you fight for the limelight against men?
Why mention it?
Men and women should be equal.
Why do you always think
I'm not as good as a man?
I'm able-bodied.
I have skills.
I can go wherever I want!
You can go nowhere!
Mother.
Follow me.
Kneel down.
Mother.
Kneel!
Take an oath here.
From now on,
no matter what happens
and what you go through,
you must live with no hates forever.
Mother...
I've never hated anyone.
I need your pledge.
Okay.
I swear.
But if someone harms you,
I shall certainly hate the guy.
No one will harm me.
I only hope
that you can be happy and unfettered forever.
Stay away from disputes and mishap.
As long as my mother stays with me,
I'm the happiest girl in the world.
Do not forget what you've sworn here.
Okay.
I'll keep it in mind.
Fine.
Go back and pack.
You'll be sent to Biyong Hall tomorrow.
Read and repent there for 10 days.
You must never escape again.
Mother.
It's my decision.
Nobody can change it.
Mother...
Report to Tegin.
Li Jiancheng and Li Shimin balance in power but are discordant.
We don't know who will be the heir.
Li Yuanji will soon lead troops to Wucheng.
We know nothing about his power and plan.
What has he done recently?
Nothing special. He's been visiting Li Jiancheng every night.
It's said they're close.
He did nothing unusual.
Nothing unusual?
Conceal your whereabouts and spy on them.
Report to me about all the details,
including the things not unsual.
Yes.
[Li Chunfeng]
Abnormal astrology.
A new monarch.
The world will be changed.
Get the cart.
I'm to the Palace.
Yes.
[Eastern Palace]
Princess!
Princess.
Madam made you some pastries.
All your favorites.
And also,
she made you some clothes.
I'm out for a few days and I'll be back soon.
Why did she...
She stayed up all night.
She's worried about you.
But why doesn't she come to see me off?
She's...
tired.
By the way,
Leyan doesn't know that I'll leave.
Don't forget to tell her to wait for me.
You can be at ease.
You've been friends since childhood
so she won't get angry with you.
Well...
It's time for me to leave.
Take care of yourself
and my mother.
Wait for me!
Here you are.
Hold it.
Mother!
Mother.
You ask me to leave but also hate to part with me.
Changge.
Biyong Hall is different from here.
The servants there are not that meticulous
so can you take special care of yourself?
When meals don't agree well with you,
can you make yourself a few delicious dishes?
As your clothes are torn
and I'm not at your side,
sew it yourself according to what she teaches you.
Put on more clothes,
if it's rainy or snowy.
Mother.
What about not leaving here
and staying with you?
Can I?
No.
Set out at once.
Do not come back without my permission!
Mother.
Fine, I'm leaving.
Changge.
Could you...
call me "mother" once again?
Madam.
You hate to part but why do you...
Only in this way
can she live a good life.
The mission will depart tomorrow.
Shixin Sili,
lead a group and ride north
and report the situation to Khan.
I'll stay here
keeping on exploring.
Scatter.
[Xuanwu Gate]
Close the gate
and lock it at once!
Hurry!
Wait.
We're not driving northward to leave.
It's not the way to Biyong.
Is it the wrong way?
We didn't go wrong.
Princess, don't worry.
Madam has told me
to send you there safely.
She's been weird since yesterday.
Where is she going to send me?
Hurry!
Hold on.
She's never treated me in this way before.
She must keep something back from me.
[Eastern Palace]
Blood?
What's happened?
Where are they?
Why so much blood here?
Why?
Who can tell me?
Why is no one here?
Mother.
Please be safe!
Follow up!
Hurry!
Keep pace!
Go!
Hurry up!
Be quick!
How did it happen?
Mother!
Mother.
Second Uncle?
Report!
Li Jiancheng and his sons are all dead.
General Yuchi has gone to guard the emperor.
Anyone's here?
Master.
Ask someone and send it to Eastern Palace.
Be sure to invite Crown Prince to read.
Yes.
Hurry!
It's too late.
Too late.
Xuancheng.
It's late.
[Fang Xuanling]
You...
Leave here.
Xuancheng.
You've persuaded him a lot.
Is it useful to write it?
Why do you come here?
I'm here to save you.
I don't need it.
But why are you going to suggest him again?
The officials should be loyal to their masters.
I should fulfill my duty.
Let me tell you that
a loyal official cannot die with his master.
You've done your duty.
All your duty.
You!
I'm here to prevent you.
As I'm here,
others will think you're under house arrest.
So I can preserve both your reputation
and your life.
- I don't need it!
- Xuancheng.
Do not let me down.
Leave here.
Right now!
You and I cannot leave here today.
Anything strange happened
since last night?
Prince Qin went to Eastern Palace.
The emperor withdrew from court today.
Xuanwu Gate has been closed.
Nearly 300 cavalries appeared at the gate.
They left after a while.
Who gave the order to close the gate?
Crown Prince's subordinate.
General of Xuanwu Gate Chang He.
He controlled the entrance.
Tegin.
We found it outside Xuanwu Gate.
It's from Youzhou.
Li Jiancheng commands the army in Youzhou.
As Chang He guarded the gate,
why did he stop Crown Prince's army to enter?
Prince Qin is not that simple.
Chang He might have turned the gun round.
Mother.
What's going on?
Please wake up.
Mother.
Can you hear me?
Mother...
Please wake up. Don't scare me!
Please wake up and see me.
What's happened?
What's the matter?
Mother.
Please respond to me!
Mother!
Princess.
- Aunt!
- Princess...
What's wrong with you?
What's going on?
Mother.
Leave here, Princess.
They...
Who are they?
- They...
- Tell me.
They're...
- Who are they?
- They...
Princess?
Chang He! Save her!
Please save my Mother!
She's lying there!
Traitor...
Run! Princess!
Princess!
♫ Sing but no sounds, brandish but no noises. ♫
♫ No rest content with desires, so what can I expect? ♫
Uncle's taught me to ride and use swords since I was seven.
Thanks for teaching me skills and crafts.
Of course, I should send it to you.
♫ retrospects of memory, hope we can forget each other. ♫
♫ Sing but no sounds, brandish but no noises. ♫
Prince Qin's soldiers are all over here.
I'm afraid you cannot escape.
Leave now!
Princess!
- Princess!
- Princess...
All soldiers in Changan accept Prince Qin's assignment.
- Hurry...
- I can't violate. Don't blame on me!
Crown Prince is rendered powerless!
Princess!
Remember what Madam has told you!
You must stay alive!
STAY ALIVE!
Run!
♫ Memories haunt me. I can't get rid of it. ♫
♫ Where is my future? I don't know. ♫
Don't move!
Stay there!
Halt!
Stop!
Stop running!
Freeze there!
Halt!
Stop!
Stay there!
Where can you escape?
Release!
♫ Life is changeable. Everything is just like a dream. ♫
♫ Joys and sorrows don't try to control me. ♫
Su Yishe.
Call the scouts together
and ask them to spread it in nearby armies,
especially those which will soon go north to attack Wucheng.
Crown Prince and Prince Qin died.
Execute all their soldiers.
Soldiers in the army
are mainly their former soldiers.
As it's spread,
trouble may arise.
Then,
Khan could be at ease.
I'll do it at once.
Leave.
Lady!
Lady! Mutinous soldiers have been suppressed.
We're now safe.
Why are there mutinous soldiers?
What about Eastern Palace?
What's happened?
Something wrong with Changge?
Trouble arises.
But Prince Qin has suppressed it.
Crown Prince and Prince Qi
have been executed.
What are you saying?
What about Changge?
Princess Yongning escaped from chasing.
She's now missing.
How come...
She told me to wait for her here.
I won't believe it.
It's so weird. I want to see Father.
Lady.
I'm afraid he has no time.
[Mansion of Wei]
- Mr. Wei.
- How's going?
I asked the guards of Prince Qin
about Princess as ordered.
Princess escaped from chasing temporarily
but she's missing.
She's clever.
As she's escaped, she might be safe now.
Well... I'm afraid...
she won't give up revenge.
Keep watching on it.
Tell me as you get any news.
Yes.
Set out at once.
Do not come back
without my permission!
Fine, I'm leaving.
Changge.
Could you...
call me "mother" once again?
Mother...
I'm sorry...
I will stay alive.
Am I wrong again?
Are there mice in the building recently?
Thanks for saving my life.
That's very kind of you.
I wasn't to save you.
I was afraid I would be implicated.
Sir.
Do you hide here because you're homeless?
You can sleep on my treasured bed.
It's soft and aromatic, thick and spacious. No one disturbs you!
Is it the soft, aromatic and treasured bed?
You can have a try.
It's soft and thick
with the aroma of straws.
Smells good!
Remember not to snore.
It'll bring people here.
Come on!
Have a try!
Sit.
Sir.
What's your name?
Are you from Changan?
Or are you nonnative?
Why do you come to Changan?
Sir, do you dislike chatting?
Where did you learn your skills?
Why did you learn it? To help the weak
or dominate the world?
You'll lose your tongue
with one more sentence.
Sir. I have only one last question. Trust me!
As you're homeless,
I think you may have no money.
Shall we...
As you're good at skills,
shall we go to steal the funeral objects of Lady of Eastern Palace?
There must be countless treasures.
Whose funeral objects?
It's hearsay.
The Lady od Eastern Palace.
Where's the place?
Tell me!
Rongen Temple.
Sir.
Why are you so nervous?
What's the matter with you?
I heard Prince Qin was rewarding his soldiers.
Even the horse grooms.
We really have had luck
to be appointed here
to guard the body.
We're really simpletons
to seek refuge with Prince Qin.
It's already good for us
to save ourselves.
By the way, where's our meal?
No one comes.
Officers.
Here's the food box from Pinxiang Store.
Who can sign for it?
Pinxiang Store?
- Who ordered?
- I don't know.
Who asked you to come?
I'm on duty to deliver. Nothing addressed.
It's said that it's worth 20 liang.
Officers.
It can't be shelved for long.
If it's not yours,
- I'll send it back.
- Hold on!
It's worth 20 liang.
Shall we...
Be careful, be safe.
We can't go wrong again.
You! Try one!
Really? Can I?
I'd like this one.
No.
Eat this one.
Hold on! The former one.
Have you decided?
It melts in my mouth.
Smooth and tasty!
It's the best pastry in Pinxiang Store!
Pretty nice! Officer, can I...
No. It's enough.
Delicious.
High quality.
I think I'm eating money.
[Spirit tablet of Lady Jin]
♫ Traces of thoughts, glimpses of obsession, ♫
♫ retrospects of memory, hope we can forget each other. ♫
♫ Sing but no sounds, brandish but no noises. ♫
♫ No rest content with desires so what can I expect? ♫
♫ No fake, no truth. No love, no hatred. ♫
♫ No obsession, no relief. They're all up to your heart. ♫
♫ Exhaust all your life to pursue someone. ♫
Mother...
It's really you...
They left you in the wilderness,
parting from Father.
Mother.
How humiliated!
You wanted me to get rid of hate...
Had you predicted your end all before?
But Mother...
Father and you met a violent end
and servants of Eastern Palace were imprisoned
Grandfather pretended to be ignorant of it
and all the officials looked on and did nothing.
If you hadn't sent me out of the palace,
I might have been killed by them either.
How can I get rid of hate?
Let me break the chopstick and swear to God.
No matter how dangerous and difficult it is,
I will kill the murderer by all costs.
♫ It's a dream. ♫
♫ Sorrow and happiness wane and wax like a flash. ♫
[Crown Prince and Prince Qin died. Execute all their soldiers.]
Now the rumor has spread.
I'm afraid it's useless for Your Highness to swear
or ask His Majesty's help.
What a malicious rumor!
Someone must want to stir up troubles,
causing the friction between you
and the generals of Li Yuanji and Li Jiancheng.
You should make a decision as soon as possible.
Your Highness.
The suburban army is the main force to support Wucheng.
We can't move it so easily.
What about inviting the general to come
in the name of awarding?
Separate soldiers and their generals
and then handle them.
If they're to be malicious,
how could they come?
If they refuse,
it shows their wild ambitions.
It will only alarm them and trigger a war.
I think you'd better solve it at once,
strictly and rapidly.
I don't agree.
I think you'd better part and rope them in,
slowly and gently.
Let's wait and see.
Your Highness!
That will do for the present.
- Commander Hao!
Someone poisoned us.
Please forgive us.
Who did it?
A common man.
He's clean-cut and brought us pastries from Pinxiang Store.
We didn't eat it until he finished eating safely...
Please forgive us!
Anything else?
No... nothing...
We fainted after having it.
Commander Hao.
We've examined the sacrificial tablet and tributes
of Lady of Eastern Palace.
Nothing is missing.
Father.
Sorry for letting Father be startled
by the poisoning case.
It's not a normal case.
It's happened around Lady of Eastern Palace.
Father, here you are.
They're poisoned to faint after eating these.
Besides,
nothing was stolen.
The guy dares to poison the emperor's soldiers
but steals nothing.
It seems to be our old friend.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which frozes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which frozes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad