♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I’ve never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫  I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I’ll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I’ll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don’t regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 1
[The Long Ballad]
Go!
Li Changge,
you can't get away.
Just surrender,
follow us back to Changan and confess your sins.
Changan is indeed a lively city.
It's so much more fun here than our grasslands.
What you see is not necessarily the truth.
The prosperity for now may not last long.
How much is it?
Sir, it's 3 wen.
Come on!
Get out of the way!
Out of the way!
Look out.
Are you blind?
This is what you officers do?
Bullying around?
How dare you.
Are you seeking death?
Don't stir up trouble.
Let's go.
Is that how the guard in Mansion of Crown Prince behave?
I'm the guard there.
Prin...
Sir,
I... I didn't know any better.
Please, sir, have mercy on me.
Get lost.
Yes.
Let's go.
Go!
Are you okay?
You've got some nerve.
I can't believe you'd confront Crown Prince's men.
But given that he stirred up trouble first,
I'll let you go.
Next time,
you won't be so lucky.
Go!
If it wasn't for that boy,
I'd definitely kick their ass hard.
Don't forget why we come to Changan.
Do not spoil the ship for a half pennyworth of tar.
Yes.
Mom.
Changge.
Mom,
why are you losing so much hair?
Are you not feeling well lately?
I'm fine.
I'm just getting old.
Everyone gets old.
You're not getting old.
You'll never get old.
You'll never be sick.
And you'll stay fabulous forever
just like now.
You're so sweet.
Did you sneak out again today?
Yes, I did sneak out.
But Mom, don't worry.
I didn't cause any trouble.
Changge,
there's something I want to tell you.
What is it, Mom?
Why are you so serious?
Changge,
you're always running wild
and I've never been strict with you.
But this time, you must promise me
that you'll stay right in the mansion tomorrow.
Don't come out no matter who sends for you.
Why?
I heard that
Ashile Tribe sent out messengers
without being invited.
They've arrived in Changan.
They came from the grasslands?
Why are they coming to Changan?
In name, they're just messengers.
But they requested for a Cuju game
the instant they arrived.
Everybody knows it's just an excuse.
A Cuju game?
It'll be so much fun.
Changge,
when your grandpa just started the war,
he made a marriage contract with Ashile Tribe.
It was a stopgap back then.
But now, Wucheng is at war.
And there's only a few girls
of the right age in the palace.
I'm worried that
they'll bring it up this time.
Mom,
that was a long time ago.
I doubt they still remember that.
You're thinking too much.
Changge,
you're too young.
Some things are better left unsaid.
I want nothing
but your safety and happiness.
That you'll live carefreely in Changan, warm and fed.
Lady Jin,
you were looking for His Highness.
He's back now.
Mom,
you're going to see my father?
He just came back.
I suppose he has no time for me.
I'll go later.
Changge,
go back and stay in your room.
Don't upset your father again.
San Niang,
doesn't she always hate to see my father?
Why would she want to see him now?
It appears that
Shimin is waging a war against me.
Brother,
that's the last straw.
We need to handle it immediately.
Let's not talk about it here. Go to my study.
Chang He.
Yes.
Keep an eye on Hongyi Palace.
[Li Jiancheng]
And tell me everything
that goes on around Prince Qin.
Yes.
Brother,
we can't afford to wait around.
Li Shimin...
Jin.
Why are you here?
I thought you hate this place.
Your Highness,
I heard that Ashle Tribe has sent out messengers
to Changan without invitation.
If tomorrow they bring up that marriage contract...
It was His Majesty's decision.
It's not up to me.
And it's not for you
to worry about what happened in court.
Yes.
This is the dessert I made for you, Your Highness.
Is there anything else you want to say?
Nothing.
Alright. If so,
maybe you should keep away from this place.
Yes.
[Hongyi Palace]
Leyan,
You're so timid.
I can't believe you'd still fall for this trick.
What will you do when I'm not by your side later?
Changge,
stop messing with me.
Come on.
I'll take you to your Mr. Right.
I don't have "Mr. Right".
I heard that Wei Shuyu'd show up
in the Cuju game at the stadium.
Don't you want to see him?
Brother Shuyu...
Why would I want to see him?
Since he saved your from drowning years ago,
you'd flush every time you see him.
Leyan.
Are you okay?
You think I'm blind?
Oh,
this is for you.
It's so ugly.
What is it?
I even pierced my hand
just so I could make this.
Now you tell me it's ugly?
Forget about it.
Ugly it is,
I like it.
Let me see.
Where's your wound?
I'm fine now.
Let's hurry there before the game ends.
Oh,
I got something for you, too.
This is the amulet
I got from the temple.
One is for you,
and another one...
Another one...
is for Brother Shuyu.
You got this yourself.
You should deliver it in person.
I...
Come on, wear this.
What for?
So that no one can recognize you.
I need to protect you.
What about you?
Come on, I fear no one.
Let's go.
Please,
I'm begging you.
Please, don't kill me.
Don't kill me!
I didn't sell Prince Qin out.
It wasn't me who let out the secret.
Please,
please, let me go.
Please don't kill me.
Don't kill me.
Please!
Don't! Don't kill me!
I didn't sell Prince Qin out!
It wasn't me!
Please don't kill me!
Don't kill me! Please!
No!
Let's go.
Leyan.
Hao Du is definitely not a nice guy.
Stay away from him.
Don't approach him.
Brother Shuyu once told me that
he's a cold-blooded person.
Forget about it.
Let's go to cheer for Shuyu now.
Let's go.
Nice!
Great!
Nice! Nice!
Nice!
Come on.
What a large venue.
Nice!
Great!
Thank you.
Go!
Hurry up!
My amulet!
My amulet's gone!
I must've lost it on the way here.
Give this one to him.
No.
This one is for you.
You see me practically every day.
Next time you go to the temple,
you can give me another one.
Take it.
But after today,
you don't know
when you'll meet him again.
Nice!
Look.
What a pity!
16 points for Ashle Team.
Nice!
Changge,
it seems that
we're losing.
We mustn't lose this game.
If we lose,
it'd affect the morale in our forces.
Nice!
Team Tang scores 14 points.
Team Ashile scores 16 points.
Nice! Nice!
Yaro!
Hang on, hang on there.
Changge!
Hold on.
Your Highness,
don't you underestimate this dagger.
It can cut clear through copper, iron,
gold and jade.
It can kill people without a sound.
Do you want to try it out yourself?
You're so humorous.
To me, Cuju is just like a war.
What matters is one's courage, strength,
and weapons.
Your players seem a spent force to me.
The game is set.
There's nothing to see.
[Li Shimin]
The result is still an open question.
And you're talking so wildly in front of everyone.
Aren't you afraid that
you'll be proven wrong later?
You!
He's always so arrogant and wilful.
He shouldn't have said that.
Please don't take it personally.
Since it's so sharp,
why don't we make it a bonus
and award it to the best warrior?
I've heard a lot about Prince Qin's lofty goals and open mind.
Now that I finally see him,
I suppose all he has is a glib tongue.
You're the sensible one, Your Highness.
Both His Majesty and Your Highness want to
forster cordial relations between our two nations.
Back at that time, His Majesty
made a marriage contract with Ashle Tribe.
How about we take this opportunity
and settle it down?
What?
Whose daughter is that girl?
Sir,
you're seriously wounded.
You need time to recover.
Sir, you mustn't...
This game is about the honor of Tang Dynasty.
How can I funk it?
If you go back to the game, it might turn chronic.
Sir...
Doctor,
I'm well-built since my childhood.
I'll be fine.
Brother Shuyu.
Why are you here?
Does it hurt?
Lady.
It's just a minor injury. No need to worry.
See? I'm fine now.
This is an amulet for you.
If I had given it to you earlier,
you wouldn't get hurt.
Thanks.
Wh... Where's my suit?
I can't believe there'd still be a player
who'd volunteer to seek his doom.
No matter who you are,
we'll kick your ass.
Just ignore them.
You two, remember...
All I want is...
Victory!
Yes!
Array of echelon.
Interesting.
Nice!
Great!
Nice one!
Nice!
Great!
Nice! Nice!
Nice!
Nice one!
Great!
Nice!
Nice! Nice!
Great!
Nice!
Team Tang scores 17 points.
Team Ashile scores 17 points.
Your dress looks so nice.
Yeah, it took me a long time to get it.
There, there.
Nice!
Great!
We won!
Nice! Nice!
Nice!
Game over.
Team Tang scores 18 points.
Team Ashile scores 17 points.
Team Tang wins!
We won! We won!
He is...
She's Changge, of course.
Who else could mess with those Ashle guys?
Lady.
Prince Qin ordered me to
escort you back to the Mansion.
How could Father know I'm here?
Father...
I'm just following the order.
Leyan,
there must be something important.
Just go back.
I'll explain it to Changge.
I...
Don't worry.
You're the Lady.
Nice work.
Great! Nice job!
You won.
This dagger is yours now.
Give it to that lad.
Yes.
Nice!
You've worked hard.
Hold on.
You talked about that marriage contract.
We should give this matter further thought.
That girl you've just seen
is indeed a royal lady of our empire.
Would you mind coming to my palace
so that we can discuss it in detail?
Your sincerity really strucks me.
It'd be impolite for me to decline.
Nice, great.
You too.
Good job.
What you did back there is heroic.
The Cuju ball is so heavy.
If it really hit that kid,
the consequences would be unimaginable.
Come on.
As the old saying goes,
"It is a glorious failure."
You can't understand Chinese, right?
I can.
He's so mean.
The boy who made that kick.
Me?
Yes, come here.
What?
As per His Highness's order,
this dagger presented by Ashle Tribe
will be awarded to...
How could you still keep your mask on?
Just state your name.
Shixin Sili is here for Tegin Sun.
Tegin Sun, why would you get interested
and take part in the game personally today?
I wanted to test their ability.
And how are they?
If it was a real war,
they'd be annihilated completely.
But that lad who entered at the last minute seemed smart.
I wonder who he is.
He's from the Eastern Palace.
His ranking must be higher than eighth.
Tegin Sun, you're omniscient.
Speaking of which,
I brought up the marriage contract today
and Li Jiancheng really took the bait.
But shall we give Great Khan a notice in advance?
No need.
They're so eager to sue for peace.
I suppose their forces must be weak.
Great Khan has nothing to worry about.
Our convoy was expected to leave Changan tomorrow.
Shall we change the schedule?
No.
Leave as scheduled.
Leave as scheduled...
Second Uncle!
It hurts, Second Uncle!
Let me go!
Troublemaker.
Isn't the public dazzle you get today enough for you?
Why are you here?
Uncle,
I'm here today
because I got you a gift.
Gift?
Show me, then.
You've just won it.
Why are you giving it to me?
Since I was seven,
I started horse riding and swordplay with you.
You taught me martial arts and warcraft.
That's why I could pitch into the Cuju game.
I can never repay your kindness.
I won this dagger myself.
Of course I should give it to you, Uncle.
Yongning, you've grown up.
Today you managed to apply warcraft to Cuju
and set the formation for players.
Good job.
Nice dagger.
It's this dress.
If it wasn't for this suit,
I'd definitely win over you, Uncle.
You're wrong.
That loophole was the bait I left.
You were too eager to win.
That's why you'd fall into my trap.
But you're more powerful than me.
If I don't take the opportunity
and make a surprise attack,
how am I gonna win?
The strong attack while the weak defend.
If you aren't strong enough,
all you can do is to draw in your claws
and bide your time before you gain the strength
and can finally launch the attack instead.
Sounds depressing.
This is the price the weak ones must pay.
It's not easy but you must struggle through it.
It's the only way to survive.
Lie low and work hard.
Whatever you're fighting for, someone or the world,
it's always the case.
Changge,
remember this.
Okay.
I'll keep it in mind, Uncle.
Alright.
You should go home now.
I have business to attend to.
Okay.
Then I'll come to visit you next time.
Changge,
send my regards to your mom.
Got it.
[Du Ruhui]
Your Highness,
I'm sorry I'm late.
I got so many eyes on me lately.
Changge.
Father.
That "lad" who reversed the game today.
It was you, right?
I didn't mean to break into the stadium.
But we were on a losing streak at that time.
So,
I had to...
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There’s always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There’s always solicitude ♫
♫ which frozes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There’s always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There’s always solicitude ♫
♫ which frozes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ it turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad