♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 14=
Little missy, come with us.
Did you get the wrong person?
You can scram.
Can I beat them up?
Try not to kill them.
I know.
You can kill the guy.
Don't hurt the girl.
Boss Bu Le wants her.
Bu Le?!
Where is he?
Boss!
Where's the girl? Did you get her?
Boss...
That brat's Martial Soul
is the Blue Silver Plant.
He's strong.
So you're Bu Le?
She's even prettier up close.
Break all his limbs and throw him out.
Send the girl to my room.
You're this powerful without Martial Soul.
Are you a Mutant Soul?
If you are,
I can help you.
Like how you helped Nightfire Village?
So you are the one
who took Ma Hong Jun away.
In that case we can strike a deal.
Give me Ma Hong Jun,
and I'll give you the right compensation.
With our help,
your Martial Soul
might be able to mutate again.
It'll become even stronger!
What deal?
Who is she to you?
She is my sister.
That's great!
Then I can be your brother-in-law!
We'll be family!
Where's the medicine for Nightfire Village?
Hand it over!
I-It's...
It's there, beneath the stack of books.
What's wrong, Wu?
I think I'm fine.
Check her wrist.
If that green line reaches her heart,
she's done for.
You better think this through!
If I die,
she'll die too!
Give me the antidote.
I don't have it!
I... I'll tell you.
Release me... I'm about to die.
Release me, release me.
That poison was created by the headquarters.
A minion like me wouldn't have the antidote.
At most, she only has half a month left.
You're going to pay for it
if anything happens to her.
I know... I know where...
you can find people from the headquarters.
Tell me now!
Get to
the town near the Star Forest after three days.
Someone from the headquarters will be there.
How do I meet that person?
Get that thing out from the box.
Don't worry, I've used up all the poison.
After three days,
take this letter
to Star Town.
Someone from the headquarters will find you.
Where's the medicine for Nightfire Village?
I've already distributed them.
I can't have prepared a letter in advance
just to lie to you!
You're both really going to Star Town?
It's stated here.
Wait on the street
with this letter.
Someone will reach out t you.
Looks like we have to go to Star Town.
That town is extremely dangerous.
The law does not exist there.
I heard that they have people guarding
at the town's entrance recently.
Those guards are the townspeople.
If it's so dangerous,
why didn't the townspeople leave?
If there's no law, there are no taxes.
Many Soul Masters gather there too.
They can do business.
Plus Star Town
is near Star Forest.
There's always Soul Beasts ambushing people,
making Star Town full of desperadoes.
They kill to rob, and prey on the weak.
No matter how dangerous it is,
I will go there.
Wu is my sister.
I can't just let her die.
But I'm still worried.
How about this?
We'll bring them along.
We'll all go together.
Let's bring that girl
from the Martial Soul Hall too.
Hu Lie Na is smart.
She'll be able to track
Bu Le down sooner or later.
If she finds out,
then the Martial Soul Hall will know too.
That's why we must bring her.
Will she be willing to come with us?
I have a plan.
Plus, we must not tell the other students
that it's for Wu.
For me?
That's right.
The school
is organizing a trip to the Star Forest.
We are going to find a Soul Beast
for Ou Si Ke.
For his Soul Rings to advance.
He wants to advance to Triple Soul Rings too?
Is there a problem?
How old is he?
He just advanced to Double Soul Rings.
If he doesn't master his Soul Power first,
he won't be able to advance.
Here, take this.
Don't drop it.
It's very expensive.
Use your Soul Power to activate it.
Full Soul Power?
That's impossible.
It's probably broken.
Do you really have full Soul Power?
So, no problem, right?
Even if you have full Soul Power,
you should be training often
to boost your Martial Soul
to the best condition.
Only then could you try to advance.
He already achieved full Soul Power last year.
Since it's been a year,
the timing is just right.
Can I not go?
You cannot.
I mean
that Star Forest
is where wild Soul Beasts lurk and gather.
Legend says there's even
top-level Soul Beasts in that forest.
What do you mean by that?
You coward, you're scared.
Who's a coward!?
W-who says I'm scared!
Rong Rong.
I... I am fearless.
I'm only afraid...
I'm afraid that you girls will be scared.
You should be careful and
think about what you just said.
Girls from Shi Lan Ke School are the most valiant,
a-and are not weaker than any of us here.
Of course!
Even the girls are going,
and you're not?
Dad!
I heard there are two Beast Kings in the forest.
Strongest in the world.
Only the Grand Soul Land Master
with Nine Soul Rings
have a chance against them.
What if we encounter
and can't defeat them?
It's been a while since anyone saw the Beast King.
The Beast King is lurking
in the depths of the forest.
Beast King?
Accurately speaking, it's the king of the forest.
One of them is the Titan Giant Ape.
Then what about the other?
No one has ever seen the other Beast King.
I don't know what that is.
But I've always thought
that it's a flawed statement.
Two Beast Kings in one forest?
How can they live in peace?
Because they're friends.
The Beast Kings are friends?
The second Beast King is the Azure Bull Python.
How did you know?
I... I...
Like Ou Si Ke,
I just heard of it.
Hearsay.
Ou Si Ke, do you have any more questions?
I'm really not suited to become a Soul Master.
Pack up, everyone.
We'll leave early tomorrow morning.
I still want to be an artist.
In your dreams!
But
doesn't our school emphasize
on letting the students have freedom,
and the option to choose?
Sure, I'll give you two choices.
One,
you'll come with us to the Star Forest.
I'll take the second choice.
That's to burn all your costumes and books.
Fine.
Alright, alright.
I'll go pack up.
What's more,
Tomorrow, Tang San and Wu
will go with Master first.
The rest of you, follow me.
We'll meet up at Star Town tomorrow.
Alright, that's all.
I can't believe
that your Soul Power is advancing faster than me.
There are lots of people stronger than you.
You don't have to be so mean to her.
She's not suitable to be in Shi Lan Ke School.
You...
I'm actually not strong at all.
I...
I... I'm really weak.
Really, Rong Rong.
I'm really very weak.
Don't worry, I think we can make it.
Don't you worry.
I'll definitely cure you.
I believe you.
Why do we suddenly have to go to the Star Forest?
Wasn't it mentioned just now?
It's to help Ou Si Ke's Soul Rings advance.
Ma Hong Jun is still battling in the arena,
and Bu Le has yet to appear.
Is it really an urgency to
help with his Soul Rings advance?
Perhaps you've already met Bu Le?
Or you know
that Bu Le will appear at the Star Forest.
Did I guess it right?
Hand Bu Le over.
The Martial Soul Hall will reward you well.
We don't need rewards.
Many people desire to hunt and kill Soul Beasts
for instant success.
They're considered lucky.
There are many Soul Masters that never returned.
Then why do people still go?
Aren't they afraid of death?
Hope can blind your eyes.
Look!
The Fire Flamingo.
Once a Soul Beast dies,
its aura dissipates and returns to the void.
Where did the corpse come from?
Of course it's a fake.
All the so-called ancient weapons,
remains of the Soul Beast,
and the inheritance of the Martial Soul
are just lies.
It looks really real.
Heads down, don't look upfront.
Seven Soul Rings?
Let's go.
Keep your heads down.
Follow me.
Let's find an inn to stay the night.
Alright.
We don't have enough funds.
We'll have to make do with this.
It's inconvenient for Wu.
I'll find a screen for you.
We'll sleep on separate beds.
Actually, it's OK.
Master,
I saw it on the street earlier.
How did you get Seven Soul Rings?
What is this?
The Headmaster gave me this.
He said it's a drama prop made by Ou Si Ke.
If necessary, we can use our Soul Power
to generate a
Soul Ring effect that looks real.
Ou Si Ke made this?
He's amazing.
Yeah.
It's a pretty good way
to scare people away.
But if we really get into a fight,
does that mean we're screwed?
That's why you should never be alone.
There are all types of people here.
Now you're cute.
Let me see your arm.
Sir.
You showed that you have Seven Soul Rings earlier.
Everyone who saw you
would know you're a Soul Saint.
It will be
inconvenient for you to go out.
Why don't I
bring that letter instead
to wait for that person?
You're right.
Be careful.
I'll be watching from afar.
I should go too.
You see...
If you leave me alone here in the inn...
It's pitiful.
I'm scared.
You're usually afraid of nothing.
You're scared?
I just want to go with you.
Don't... we look a little silly?
Well...
Why don't you wait for me inside?
I can stand here by myself.
No!
Even if it's silly,
I want to accompany you.
Why are there so many people
here to hunt Soul Beasts?
They are all Soul Masters.
Do you think
humans and Soul Beasts can have a peace talk?
Soul Beasts don't have intelligence.
How can we have a peace talk?
Then if Soul Beasts have intelligence
like humans do,
does that mean we can co-exist in peace?
Probably not.
Why?
What's the point
for a 100,000-year-old Soul Beast
to develop to the human form?
These Soul Masters
will still swarm here
to hunt for them.
So long as Soul Masters
continue to rely on killing Soul Beasts
to advance their Soul Rings,
humans and Soul Beasts
will never be able to co-exist peacefully.
Master has said
that demands will determine the stand.
But there has to be an exception.
Perhaps there will be one or two exceptions,
but there won't be any drastic changes.
Then what if lots of people want to kill me?
Why would lots of people want to kill you?
I'm just asking what if.
What if one day...
I'll be here to protect you.
If one day
over a million Soul Masters
want to kill me,
I hope that you'll pretend you don't know me.
Protect yourself.
No one
can ever harm you
unless
they trample my dead body.
Sir.
The poison in Wu's body is still progressing.
Don't lose hope.
Let's wait again tomorrow.
What if he doesn't appear tomorrow either?
If no one appears after three days,
I'll go to the Martial Soul Hall.
What for?
You don't have to know.
I'll have a way.
-Alright.
-Tang San.
Why aren't you sleeping?
I will protect you too.
If one day
over a million Soul Masters
want to kill you,
I will stand with you forever.
Of course.
What's this about?
It's nothing.
Sir, you should rest.
Here you come, bro.
Have some water.
What's going on?
Soul Beasts are rushing out of the forest.
Luckily I'm a fast runner.
Otherwise, I'd be dead by now.
I'm telling you,
I got really lucky.
A group of students were running to town too,
but a Soul Beast stopped them.
I don't think they'll make it.
What students?
How would I know?
What did they look like?
From far,
it seems like one of their
Martial Souls is the White Tiger.
Dai Mu Bai and the others
must have run into trouble.
Both you and Wu go back to the inn.
We want to go too.
Soul Beasts are rushing out.
This is a serious matter.
Both of you will be a burden.
Listen to me, wait for me at the inn.
Let's go back to the inn to wait for Master.
Let's go back first.
The elder that was with us earlier
is a Soul Saint with Seven Soul Rings.
We know.
We saw.
If we didn't see him leave,
we wouldn't be stopping you on your tracks.
We are just poor students.
We don't have any money.
You don't have money,
but that Soul Saint has.
You're both important to him.
If we take you as hostages,
we'll be sure to get paid a lot.
Our school is very very poor.
Who'd believe you?
She's telling the truth.
Why don't you ask around and find out?
Shi Lan Ke School is famous for being poor.
Men, get them!
Wait.
What school are both of you from?
Shi Lan Ke School.
Shi Lan Ke School in Suo Tuo City.
Did Bu Le send you?
You're the one from headquarters.
Brat!
Stop creating trouble for me.
If you're smart,
get out of here now.
This young brat
is already a Soul Saint with Quadruple Soul Rings?
It's just a bluff.
Useless piece of shit.
You useless brat!
Go to hell!
Why aren't my legs moving?
My legs!
Big Brother!
It's rare to see
the Blue Silver Plant mutates.
You killed them?
It's them who wanted to kill me.
I asked Bu Le to meet me.
Why is it both of you instead?
Poisoned.
Bu Le said you can cure her poison.
Yes, I can cure it.
But why should I cure it?
You...
Did both of you come with that Soul Saint?
You knew we were here?
What's your name?
What do you want us to do for the antidote?
I'm asking for your name.
Tang San.
I am Ye Zhi Qiu.
Piece of advice for both of you.
Neither the royal family
nor the Martial Soul Hall...
can cure this poison.
So...
I am your only hope.
Why?
Do you think you can defeat me?
I'll fight you anyway.
If you make any move,
I'll kill her first.
If you want me to cure her,
you'll have to work for me.
Cure her first.
You have no right to bargain with me.
Alright.
What do you want me to do?
We're lucky that it wasn't a head-on fight.
It'd be a huge problem if it was.
It's normal for Soul Beasts to appear
near the Star Forest.
We've finally arrived.
This trip is tiring me out.
Ou Si ke is the one carrying all your things.
Why are you tired?
You...
No no no.
Brother Dai.
I'm happy to.
This is practice for me.
Practice.
Workout.
What's up with that observer?
She didn't say a word.
She...
Perhaps she...
I have no idea at all.
Brother San? Sister Wu?
Didn't I tell them to go back to the inn?
Headmaster, Sir.
What happened?
The one we've been waiting for appeared.
Alright.
Let's talk back at the inn.
Let's go.
Ye Zhi Qiu's Martial Soul has no form
and kills people eerily.
His Martial Soul is really strange.
We absolutely couldn't see
what form it was.
Do you know anything?
Never heard of it.
Even you don't know.
Then that must be a brand new Martial Soul.
Or...
Mutant Soul.
Is this
the mission he gave you?
What are the details?
Tomorrow, there'll be
a Soul Master called Du Gu Yan
heading for Star Forest.
Her objective is to hunt Soul Beasts
to advance to Triple Soul Rings.
Your mission
is to find her,
and break this bottle in front of her.
What do we do next?
There is no next.
You only have to do that.
What does Du Gu Yan look like?
She wears a cherry blossom on her head.
You'll recognize her once you see her.
The Star Forest is vast.
How are we going to find her?
She will choose to hunt for
poisonous Soul Beasts.
What's inside this bottle?
Didn't he tell you?
No.
Two illogical points.
Why is a secret organization that is
widespread across the Douluo continent
targeting someone about
to advance to Triple Soul Rings?
Next,
if this is truly an important matter,
why isn't he doing it himself?
Why did he ask both of you to do it?
Perhaps it's because it's really dangerous.
That's why he won't do it himself.
Either
that he can't appear in front of Du Gu Yan
or
that the contents in this bottle
will harm him as well.
Maybe it's the same poison.
I'll research it.
Tang San.
Leave with Wu for now.
I'll research it with Master.
And also,
don't tell anyone else about this for now.
Understood.
Let's go.
Do you need anything?
Earlier you said
that the one you were looking for had appeared.
Was it Bu Le?
Tell me what you know.
This matter concerns Wu's security.
Before Wu is safe,
I won't let anyone else get involved.
Sir, how is it?
It's definitely poison.
But it's hard to determine the amount inside.
Is it the same poison used on Wu?
It's different. This is even more dangerous.
If you give me a month's time,
I can probably develop the antidote.
If we wait any longer.
I will die of anxiety.
If you really break this bottle
in front of someone,
then it's likely that everyone else in the area
will die too.
I'll make sure no one is nearby
and find alone time with Du Gu Yan.
Think this over.
Do you want to save someone,
or kill someone?
Give it to me.
I'll enter the Star Forest alone tomorrow.
You're willing to kill another person?
What else can I do, Sir?
I don't have a choice.
If I don't do it, Wu will die.
I'm not a good brother.
But I know
that I want to protect her.
No matter...
No matter what it takes.
Brother.
I'm a little scared if you're like this.
I scared you, Wu.
Don't be scared.
Sit down.
Who says you don't have a choice?
Good news!
I asked around and found out that
someone
has seen a Soul Master
that wears a cherry blossom on her head.
She just
entered the Star Forest tonight,
which means
that even if we only go tomorrow morning,
we'll be able to catch up with her.
Good news always comes along with bad news.
Tell us.
What's the bad news?
The bad news is
that accompanying her is
someone with Eight Soul Rings,
and another with Seven Soul Rings.
This bottle is filled with a potent poison.
Even if we find Du Gu Yan,
defeat the Grand Soul Master
and the Soul Saint with her,
we'll still have to face
the choice between saving
and killing a person.
That's why there is a second choice.
Know your enemy and know yourself,
you'd never be defeated.
Since Ye Zhi Qiu is targeting Du Gu Yan,
both of them must be related to each other.
If we are able to
find Du Gu Yan,
then perhaps we can find out
Ye Zhi Qiu's history.
But what's the point
of knowing Ye Zhi Qiu's history?
Tang San.
Everyone has a weakness.
No one is really a single independent entity.
Ye Zhi Qiu is no exception.
Your weakness is Wu.
Ye Zhi Qiu knows that you will save her.
That's why he blackmailed you.
Likewise,
Why don't we
give him a dose of his own medicine?
Once we know Ye Zhi Qiu's history,
we'll know what he's afraid of.
If we take his weakness,
we can force him to give us the antidote.
Tang San.
The school
will never give up on Wu.
Don't worry.
Alright.
Leave the bottle with me.
We'll enter the Star Forest tomorrow morning.
We told everyone
that we're helping Ou Si Ke
to advance to Triple Soul Rings.
But our real motive
is to find Du Gu Yan.
It's not to kill her.
Sir.
How can I find Du Gu Yan?
Wait for an opportunity.
Then what do I need to do?
We'll act together.
Help Ou Si Ke to hunt
a Millennium Soul Beast.
The blood of a Millennium Soul Beast
will attract nearby Soul Beasts,
including poisonous Soul Beasts.
According to my research,
the corpse and Soul Rings of
a Millennium Soul Beast
will not dissipate for at least
Fifteen minutes.
There are so many Soul Beasts gathering together.
Won't there be danger?
As long as Ou Si Ke can absorb the Soul Rings
before a large group of Soul Beasts gather,
it will cut off the smell of blood.
Even if a lot of Soul Beasts came,
the other kids here can still manage
the beasts well.
If it still doesn't work,
there's always you, Headmaster.
Will she appear?
Even if there's a Grand Soul Master
and a Soul Saint with her,
and no matter how powerful they are,
they will still need a few days to track
before they can find out
the poisonous Millennium Soul Beast.
When they realize that Soul Beasts have gathered,
they might follow us.
Let's just try our luck.
Alright.
Let's all rest here.
This forest is really big.
This place is almost as big as a kingdom.
We'd need more than a few days to pass through.
I thought there's
supposed to be a lot of Soul Beasts here?
Why haven't we seen any yet?
This is just the outskirts of the forest.
There won't be strong Soul Beasts here.
So it's still quite safe.
Our objective this time
is to help Ou Si Ke
hunt and kill a compatible
Millennium Soul Beast.
That's why we must continue to proceed.
Be careful, everyone.
The deeper we go, the more dangerous it gets.
Then... are there any normal animals
in the forest?
Of course.
For instance, at this height,
we'll be able to see large lizards.
These lizards don't have Soul Rings in them,
but there are many Soul Beasts
that like to eat lizards like that.
In this forest,
the strong
preys on the weak.
This is the predatory law in the forest.
I've heard the villagers talking about this.
Big fish eats small fish,
small fish eats the shrimp,
and the shrimps eat the mud, right?
Mud can't help you up the wall.
[*A Chinese idiom]
Are we playing Idiom Solitaire?
I'm really good at it.
You're talking too much, Ou Si Ke.
Let's go.
Let's maintain our pace.
Don't get left behind.
And also
be careful of what you step on.
Vines and pit holes.
We must pay attention.
There is a Soul Beast called Araki,
which has a unique trait.
It looks like a dead tree.
When it's not hunting,
you won't be able to see the difference.
Vines?
Save me!
Hold on.
Release your Martial Soul.
Your Evil Phoenix
is the strongest against plant type Soul Beast.
Are you alright?
I was frightened just now.
Your Martial Soul is part of you.
Sync your body with your Martial Soul to
build your instincts.
Got it.
I really never expected this Star Forest
to be so dangerous.
That's right.
You've all witnessed how terrifying
this forest can be.
So let me give all of you
a piece of advice.
Make sure you are fully focused,
and face this forest
in your best condition.
We've already run a few hundred miles just now
How can we maintain our best condition?
Easy.
You just need Ou Si Ke.
Me?
None of you have seen
Ou Si Ke's Martial Soul, right?
We really haven't seen it.
Display your Martial Soul, Ou Si Ke!
I don't think it's necessary.
I'm not even ready.
You're the only one who can let
everyone regain
our physical strength and spirit.
You don't want anyone here to get hurt, right?
Are you doing this on purpose?
I am doing this on purpose.
Actually, your Martial Soul
is really special and impressive.
It's unique!
Well... alright then.
Hold on to this for me.
You even changed into a costume?
Well... I...
I...
Is this your Tool Soul?
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪