ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
SEOMYUNG CHARITY MARATHON
I completed the race, right?
I can't believe I did it.
-I'm so excited.
-Me too.
-Is the race over?
-Yes.
What about you?
Did you finish soon?
Gosh. They're so mean.
They could've waited for me.
But I did.
I waited
until I could see you.
It's my first time finishing a race.
I often made you wait.
And every time I did,
you always waited for me.
I'm more fascinated by this moment.
I've made a wise decision to wait for you.
I'm glad I waited.
Me too.
Did you watch E.T.?
-Did you watch the movie?
-No, I didn't.
I see.
I actually practiced a lot
so I'd be able to finish the race.
-I wanted to surprise you.
-I don't believe you.
I kept a record every time I ran.
I have evidence. Do you want to see?
My gosh, seriously.
I'm so proud of myself
for becoming a runner.
What? You're not going to believe me?
My gosh.
Catch me if you can.
Why aren't you coming? Seriously.
-What? I was--
-Come and catch me.
-Try and catch me, okay?
-Okay, fine.
All right. Go on.
-Catch me if you can.
-I'm going to catch you.
-I'm seriously going to catch you.
You offered to drive me home.
I didn't know he'd be here.
Then who was supposed to drive?
You told me you don't drive.
And I was too tired to drive.
If I knew he was going to join,
I would've taken the bus.
Mr. Jeong, stop the car.
He wants to get off.
I felt awkward in the hallway
because you didn't let me inside.
Why would you come inside?
You were neither the doctor
nor the patient.
I wanted to be there for you.
You let Mr. Jeong inside.
-Should I stop the car?
-Take me to my house.
Stop yelling. It's giving me a headache.
You secretly watched me sleep.
So why can't I do the same?
I just watched you.
I didn't do it secretly.
Will you shut up?
Ms. Seo.
Was that too vulgar of me?
I'll pretend I didn't hear that.
Take care of yourself.
I'll get mad if you get sick.
You should go on inside.
Mr. Jeong, please take good care
of Ms. Seo for me.
What's with that guy?
-Mr. Jeong.
-Yes?
Am I doing the right thing?
-With what?
-With this.
How am I supposed to end it well?
Why are you thinking about ending it
when you've only just started?
What? Does that mean you support me?
I thought you couldn't support me.
I feel like I should since you're not
even supportive of yourself.
Every time I liked something,
it always came to an end.
The same happened with soccer.
I never liked something
knowing it'd have to end someday.
So you're scared that what happened
with soccer might also happen
with Mr. Lee?
No, I'm sad.
Cheers.
Cheers. You did great today.
DRIED FISH MIX
It's so nice and cool.
This place sells good beer.
Are you memorizing the menu?
Hurry or I might finish this.
I'm not good at choosing what to eat
with alcohol.
-You know I'm an LW.
-Choose whatever.
No, not that.
Dried pollack goes with beer.
Soup is for soju.
Dried pollack it is.
I thought you wanted me to choose.
You're talking back again.
What exactly is talking back?
-What you did just now.
-It was just a question.
Ma'am, can we please get
a dish of dried pollack?
Sure.
There's actually something on my mind.
Ma'am, can we also have jjamppong soup?
-Sure.
-There.
Are you ready to listen?
You're scaring me.
I'll try not to sound too scary.
I met my dad, and he told me
I'm free to date whoever
as long as I marry Ms. Seo.
So,
you can date anyone
as long as you marry Ms. Seo?
There's no telling what they're thinking.
-Can we have another glass of beer?
-Sure.
My dad thinks he's doing me a favor.
Does Ms. Seo know about this?
I heard this today,
so I didn't get a chance to ask her.
-But I'm sure she feels the same.
-What if she doesn't?
That crazy woman is full of surprises.
My gosh.
Should we just go
and apologize to your dad?
That's what he wants
and it's not that hard to apologize.
I won't let you how easy it may be.
Why would you?
You've done nothing wrong.
That's a very relative matter.
People have different viewpoints.
And your father thinks
I'm doing something wrong by dating you.
Don't ever say that again.
I'm not okay with it.
Gosh, you're such a straight arrow.
Thank you.
Okay, let's stop talking about this.
Let's talk about us.
How's work?
Woo-sik has gotten a lot better.
He might even be doing
better than before in some aspects.
Then will he be able to run again?
I really wish him the best.
I'm currently trying to find
a team for him.
One of them seems optimistic about it.
Then will he enter a race right away?
He needs to wait until spring
for the next season to begin.
You guys have seasons?
My first goal is to get Woo-sik
back on track
and see him start the race.
Once I do that,
I'll think about what to do next.
I think I finally get how you live life.
You told me
there was no one in front of you
after you outran each player.
You just focus on what's in front of you
and do things step by step.
I realized that's how you do things.
You even smiled at me for the first time
when you almost made a nine-second record.
If I timed myself today,
it might have been
a little over nine seconds.
Nine seconds? Is that good?
Gosh, of course. Totally.
I really loved your smile.
But for some reason,
it also made me feel sad.
I just felt that way.
It was the first time
I ever told anyone about that.
Nine seconds is a big record
and a huge barrier for us.
But you were there
when I said it out loud.
And you were there
when I could actually say it.
So what about that?
That's what the nine-second record
means to me now.
Gosh, you're making me blush.
My goodness.
If I keep going,
you might make a move on me.
I'm not going to
since you're looking forward to it.
What's the matter?
-Are you upset?
-No way.
I'm not upset at all.
-I'm full.
-Me too.
Thank you for celebrating
my first marathon race.
-No problem.
-Thank you.
To be honest,
there's something that worries me.
Something's worrying you?
And you're going to tell me?
You get better day by day.
This is how it must feel to raise kids.
Do I still look like a kid to you?
Yes, and that's exactly why
I should keep you close at all times.
What's worrying you?
Director Dong offered me a job
at the agency as an agent.
Hey, this is like Jerry Maguire.
-"Show me the money."
-It's Ki Seon-gyeom.
Then it's "Seon-gyeom Ki."
Gosh, I'm tipsy.
I think I'm easily getting drunk
thanks to the long run.
I think it'd be safer for Woo-sik
to have an agency supporting him
instead of just me.
You should also think about
what's good for you.
It's also your life.
Right.
Will you be okay working with Ms. Seo?
You guys have different values and goals.
I'm sure we'll butt heads
for the same reason.
Not everyone has what you have.
Your family is famous, you're handsome,
and you always got
the second-highest record.
But what about Woo-sik?
What does he have to offer?
His talent, of course.
In the end, the team just wants
the best record and a medal.
If it's because Ms. Seo doesn't know,
I just need to show her that he can do it.
She quickly accepts things
when you show her results.
Just a second.
Speak of the devil.
MS. SEO DAN-AH
Why is she calling you
at such a late hour?
"Dan-ah, I'll prepare everything
for your wedding.
Just show up to the ceremony."
Who sent you this?
The chairman. My father.
How am I the only one not to know?
Exactly. What kind of nonsense is this?
Seon-gyeom, did you know?
I think he planned this with your dad.
He said I could date anyone
as long as I marry you.
That's all I know.
What does Ms. Oh think?
She's not totally irrelevant
since you're seeing him
and are close with me.
Since when?
Are you guys seeing each other?
No.
Should we just get it over with
and tell them we will?
-Will you get lost?
-This is my office.
Why don't we just live together?
It will be much easier that way.
I can't believe this. That'd be the most
uncomfortable thing on earth.
Okay, fine.
Seon-gyeom, do you have a plan?
Isn't that why you brought her?
We clearly don't want to marry each other.
I don't really mind, but I bet she does.
So let's just say I don't want to.
How grateful.
My dad's probably going to focus
on the election.
Our marriage was never the issue.
He just needs Chairman Seo's support.
So let's just buy some time
and back out last minute.
You make it sound like
it's a really big plan
even though it's not.
All that negotiating
made you turn a bit cheeky.
It's nice and simple.
I won't have to waste my time.
Okay.
What are you looking at?
-Am I beautiful?
-No.
How would that make me feel?
Do I not look beautiful?
Don't you have more to say?
Next time. I'll see you.
Let's go.
Aren't you going to tell her
that you're going to apply as an agent?
There are principles.
So I should apply first.
I see.
I'm glad you started writing a diary.
You can use that
when you write your cover letter.
-You know what that is, right?
-Yes.
Where are you off to now?
Are you going home to work?
You can go without me.
I actually need to talk to her.
I don't know what it's about,
but don't hit her.
-I'll try not to.
-Go easy on her.
Okay, I will.
-Bye.
And you say we're not close?
I tried not to let this bother me
because I didn't want to seem petty.
But why did you say that?
I can't help it.
It's been ages since he liked someone.
And how do you know that?
I was the last person he liked.
You provoked me that day.
Ms. Oh.
That was ages ago. Why are you still--
Because I'm a loser.
I just stated the truth.
I don't know how to provoke people.
I guess you were
just born with it, my lady.
"My lady"? Why are you calling me that?
Don't you know The Handmaiden?
Lady Hideko.
"You will eventually love him, my lady."
I don't know any of that.
Anyway, I'm asking you
why you talked as if Seon-gyeom
once had feelings for you.
Even if he was just
a track and field athlete,
he would've gotten offers
from many other agencies.
But he chose to sign a deal with me
among all those agencies.
That's what I meant.
That's what you meant by that?
You should've listened until the end.
You were the one
who took it the wrong way.
I couldn't help but take it that way
considering your tone
and the timing.
See? It wasn't my fault,
but you're blaming me again.
Regardless of the process,
you still played a part in
bringing us together.
You're like Cupid.
There's no need to thank me.
But why didn't you also call Yeong-hwa
to discuss the marriage issue?
He can't contact me for personal reasons.
You could've called him.
You're right.
Why didn't you tell me this earlier?
Because I just thought of it.
Oh, and one more thing.
Stop calling him late at night.
Bye then.
Seriously?
The moral of this story is,
don't trust people.
Just trust the situation.
The situation.
So let me ask you something.
Why don't we work together?
Why are you shaking so much?
You're pretty even when you sweat.
Do you have hyperhidrosis?
-Hey.
-Yes?
I'm a cop.
So,
don't trust the person,
but the situation.
I have hyperhidrosis.
It doesn't change the fact
that you're a cop.
A cop with hyperhidrosis.
Where did I put my gun?
I'm doomed.
"Name, date of birth,
work experience…"
Work experience?
What has you all serious today?
-My resume.
-I see.
My work experience though--
There's not much to write
having been an athlete all my life.
All I've been is an athlete
on a national team.
Annoying jerk.
Just stick on a large photo
and you're golden.
It should be the appropriate size.
I know that much, you know.
You don't know what really matters.
Your face, right?
Stick on a large photo.
I gave you my advice, okay?
Don't you forget it.
I gave you my advice just now, okay?
Seon-gyeom, a huge photo of yourself!
I'll get going then!
Don't forget it, okay?
Do you feel that bad for me
because I came in second?
Why pity me like this?
I don't feel bad for you,
so why would I pity you?
This isn't like you though.
I earned money in a secondhand sale
for the first time.
I did sell it at a low price,
but it's better than keeping it with me.
I feel elevated in a way.
What did you sell?
Textbooks and mock tests
for the state exam.
You've been studying?
Yes, I even took classes
at the academy run by Seong-geun.
I'll never come in second place again.
-As if you can promise that.
-It's my determination.
It should be yours as well.
Sure thing.
Also, don't pay today.
How dare you offer
when I'm way your senior?
It'll be on me, so eat up.
Can I order more? Like a pizza?
-Excuse me!
-Hey.
We need to talk.
How dare you come here. Are you insane?
I have nothing to say.
Hey.
Stop playing hard to get.
-I told you to stop.
-Ye-jun.
And who may you be?
Did my son cause you trouble?
No.
-Excuse me?
-Mom.
-Mom, you see--
-Don't explain.
Starting this weekend,
you're coming to church with me.
-Mom.
-Don't!
I'm gay.
No. I doubt it.
You can deny it all you want,
but this is who I am.
So much for being his mom.
I was preoccupied with other kids
to realize what was happening.
Are you crying?
Seriously?
I like men too, you know.
What?
What's so special about liking men anyway?
I wanted to come out properly,
not get caught like this.
-You didn't have to bring one.
-It was in my pocket.
Did I blow my nose with that?
Anyway, it's cold. Let's go.
If Mom gets mad with you,
I'll take your side.
Why have you been nice to me?
Because it's annoying
when you're sulking all the time.
Can I blame my CSAT score on you?
-No.
-Exactly. So start walking. It's cold.
What a loser.
REASONS FOR APPLYING
Will I not be able to fulfill my dream
yet again this year?
Can you ask how much a gas stove is?
Seon-gyeom?
Seon-gyeom!
A gas stove. Ask how much one costs.
I can tell what you're thinking
because of your eyes.
It's your lack of attention
that made me this way.
How much is the gas stove?
A decent one would be
50,000 won to 100,000 won.
I never had enough money
after paying rent and expenses.
Yet you have enough to buy booze.
Why do you need one though?
It'd be nice to grill
some pork belly on the rooftop.
Wouldn't Mi-joo have one?
I should get all cute and ask her.
Why would you get cute with her?
Don't. I'll do it instead.
-Are you busy?
-Well, I was working.
Do you perhaps have a gas stove?
A gas stove? Probably.
Why do you ask though?
Yeong-hwa wants to grill
pork belly on the rooftop.
What? No way.
I'll lend it to you if you let me join.
Sure.
-Come on.
-Welcome!
-I'll take that.
-Hey, it's me.
Gosh, your hands are frozen.
It was all worth it
with you and the pork waiting.
-It wasn't necessary though.
-Oh, please.
The other one.
-It's frozen too.
-Your hands are warm.
I'd love to invite Ms. Seo over too.
It's your house, so do as you please.
We're only allowed to talk
about my paintings.
What's wrong with you?
What about that incident
in your hometown then?
I'm not allowed to call her yet.
Then just talk about the paintings.
-Why don't I give you a tour?
-You're a genius.
This is the sleeping area.
I sleep on the couch
while Yeong-hwa sleeps over there.
-Doesn't it get cold?
-It's all right.
Ms. Seo.
No, please don't hang up!
-He drew this.
-Don't pick up just to hang up.
-This is a first for me.
-It's about work.
-He's quite good.
-I'm done now,
so come by the house.
-Right this moment. That's right.
-Goodness.
Are you finished? Is this it?
No.
Then you lied to Ms. Seo?
I'm "almost" done.
I just chose to omit that.
Then that makes it a lie.
No wonder she tells you off.
So when will we eat? I'll grill the meat.
I once worked part-time
at a barbecue joint.
It's time to go shopping.
We'll go together.
You should have had everything ready
before calling me!
You two can go.
The walk over here was tiring.
Rest over there where it's warm.
-Bye.
-Should I? Okay, then.
Why keep buying booze in bulk
when you don't even drink much?
That's how I always buy alcohol.
Don't they have cases of soju here?
Cases? A whole case?
Who drinks all that?
They will if it's there.
What the hell?
Seon-gyeom, no. Are you kidding me?
How much meat are you willing to buy?
We're a party of four.
And two packets of meat will be enough.
Jeez.
They'll eat it if it's there.
Who is this "they" you're referring to?
-My colleagues.
-Your colleagues?
You mean athletes?
Oh, athletes.
They sure must eat a lot.
Well, who am I to complain?
What about pork neck?
Will this be enough?
-Right?
-Right.
It's Ms. Seo!
-What's going on?
-Hi, Ms. Seo.
Isn't it obvious? We're having a barbecue.
So where's my painting?
One, two…
Ta-da!
Picturesque, right?
This is a barbecue. I want my painting.
In my heart.
Are you willing to take it out of there?
This is the only thing
I have in my heart though.
Yeong-hwa, cut it out.
-I'll hold Ms. Seo back.
-The painting's nearly done.
I just wanted you to--
Sue me. The settlement will be generous.
-Goodness.
-Exactly how much?
-What your pain is worth.
-Ms. Seo.
Please calm down.
You'll only hurt yourself.
How is that the issue?
Okay, then.
I'll push him instead.
We'll say he slipped and fell.
Are you with me, Seon-gyeom?
As if it's that easy.
What if it is?
What if I break an arm from the fall?
-I won't be able to paint.
-Just your arm?
You have my blessings for once, Ms. Seo.
Though I really don't want to.
Just have some barbecue.
Burning it will be a waste.
-Help Ms. Oh, will you?
-Hurry.
Your hands must be cold.
I'd rather have soju or beer.
Why mix the two?
My temper sure has dwindled.
Come join us and stop distracting us.
This isn't a standing party.
-You should listen to Ms. Oh.
-Exactly.
And sit on that dump of a chair?
-It's cooked well.
-We're seated just fine.
If you had told me,
I would've bought my own drink and glass.
You never asked me
before dragging me to the East Sea.
Leave if you're going to complain.
Mi-joo, why are you being mean
when she actually showed up?
Why are you yelling at her
when it's your fault?
He's right. Be more attentive toward her.
If my putting up with this
will make things better,
that's what I'll do.
This is my first time trying pork belly.
My friend.
Didn't you call her here
to enjoy this with her?
Why aren't you making her a lettuce wrap?
It should be self-made
to fit our preferences.
Wait, stop.
That'll be a waste of booze.
Here. I'll drink that.
My dear athlete, you make one for me.
Don't you dare.
Stop calling him as if he's yours.
His contract ended ages ago.
Can you even remember his name?
-You've got to be kidding me.
-Do you? What is it then?
Wait, I really can't remember.
Hold on. I know.
Don't play games with me.
Let me look it up online.
You need to know my name
in order to look it up.
Your last name is Ki,
so I might luck out
with search recommendations.
Ms. Seo, what about my name?
I want to verify that you know.
You're Vending Machine.
-What about my name?
-It's Oh Mi-joo.
My heart just skipped a beat.
Actually, I think I'm offended.
A runner on the national team.
-Ki Seon-gyeom!
-Here you go.
-After--
-Open up.
What's with him?
-How was the pork belly?
-Are you bundled up?
-It wasn't bad.
-We'll eat it again sometime.
Sure.
-May, what are you doing here?
-Hi, Mi-joo.
All of you were present
during that mess at the cafe.
Hello.
It's been a while, roommate.
-What are you doing here alone?
-Actually, I'm with someone--
Where did he go?
Ji-hyun.
Jeong Ji-hyun.
Jeong Ji-hyun? I know that name.
It's Mr. Jeong's name.
You don't know
because you never call his name.
-I see.
-What the--
Ji-hyun?
What were you doing up there?
Well, you see--
Well, I always wanted my first date
at a playground with a slide.
This wasn't in your schedule today,
Ms. Seo.
Ms. Seo? The one who called you that day?
Your mean boss.
Mean?
May, when did I ever say that?
What?
Ms. Seo, you see--
I'll explain everything.
At that moment,
something in me exploded as well.
Thinking of that makes me--
Then don't think about it.
You really did startle me that day, May.
This is what you call a natural encounter.
Oh, I see what you mean.
I'm glad it was romantic for someone.
I was returning to the office
when he followed me.
Excuse me.
Here.
My name is Jeong Ji-hyun.
Sorry?
I know it's rude to ask a stranger this,
but--
But--
Are you perhaps seeing someone?
Sorry?
Are you perhaps married?
I guess I should've asked you this first.
Are you okay with dating men?
Sorry?
Roommate, didn't you say
that you were an asexual?
I'm not against romance though.
I cover a wide range on the spectrum.
-She's not against dating people.
-I see.
And that was before I met you, Ji-hyun.
May, please. People are watching.
I'll hold back on calling you
on weekends, Mr. Jeong.
I should respect your personal life.
Please do.
He's just too sweet
to say anything that could upset others.
Sorry?
How did he make this image for himself?
It's none of your business.
If you lie to me like this again,
I'll dangle you from the rooftop.
You say that like you mean it.
Are you saying I don't?
Is this you saying you'll be back?
Maybe I should move here.
Not my place. Seon-gyeom's there.
To be honest,
I called you to give you these.
You better stop lying to me.
I'll give you a gift
on your real birthday too.
I support your long-lost dream.
Then will you be giving me a soccer ball
next time?
Well…
You better pretend
like you didn't expect it.
Look completely surprised.
Promise me.
What?
Am I too beautiful?
This is such an unexpected sight.
You underneath the streetlamp.
Who are you to judge?
I would have never imagined.
But even if I did,
my most beautiful imagination
would've never compared
to what I'm seeing right now.
I'm truly happy that I could witness this.
Me too.
I have
a new goal.
You need my cooperation again?
You can stay where you are.
I'm going to keep some distance
so that I can always see you.
If I'm too far, I can't see you.
If I'm too close,
you'll block my field of vision.
So I do need to cooperate.
Why isn't she picking up?
Pick up, please.
Where are you?
Me? I'm home, working.
Don't you know who's here?
Code Name Candy.
Hurry over.
Goodness. Could you wait a bit longer?
Sure. I'm the one who came unannounced.
May I sit down?
I was too out of it
and forgot to offer you a seat.
-Please.
-Here?
Thank you for the snacks.
If you're bored,
could you sign a poster for me?
Sure. As many as you'd like.
Thank you.
Why are you dressed like that?
I had no time to put on makeup.
-Do I look weird?
-You look suspicious.
Take them off unless you've had surgery.
You're right.
Should I just say that I did?
Choose either the hat or the glasses.
No, I didn't wash my hair.
You're her fan. She's going to adore you.
Go on.
I've been thinking hard.
"Fair as milk," right?
From that film festival.
Yes, you're right. I can't believe it.
This is unbelievable.
You're truly fair as milk these days.
I was so proud of myself for remembering.
Oh, Ji-woo.
I thought you'd bring up some other topic,
so I was quite tense.
Why would you be tense
about chatting with me?
Do I make you nervous?
That too.
And I thought you knew before coming here.
Of course, I did.
Tae-ri told me that thanks to Director Han
and your subtitles, she went abroad
and walked down the red carpet
numerous times.
She's so kind to have said that.
We're in the same agency.
At times, she feels even closer
than my own family.
I see.
When will you send the coffee truck?
Can I do that?
Of course. You and Seon-gyeom
should send one.
I'm not sure if he can chip in
since he's jobless right now.
He's not jobless.
Then?
Haven't you heard?
No.
He's--
I'm nervous right now,
so I forgot the word.
He's-- What was that word again?
It was Jerry Maguire's job.
You know-- Oh, God.
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh.
Oh, an agent.
Gosh, I'm so stupid.
TO: OH MI-JOO
BE HEALTHY
I don't need any snacks with my drinks.
This feels so fulfilling.
What did she say?
Ms. Yook didn't ask you
to break up with him too, did she?
No, she just thanked me
for subtitling her movie
and said she liked going abroad as well.
We didn't talk for that long,
but it was evident that
they're mother and son for sure.
Haven't you heard?
No.
For a brief moment,
she reminded me of Seon-gyeom.
Since you've seen Candy in real life,
I'll expect you to be more efficient.
Of course. Cheers.
Cheers to our honey's love life.
You haven't dated in a while.
We're not dating.
Ji-hyun is just following me around.
He is? Why?
Do you really not know?
No.
You still don't know? Let's break up.
That's so awful.
Honey.
You acting cute is just terrible.
They all ran away.
Where will you go now?
I don't know.
This place wasn't bad.
I was at least fed once a day.
It wasn't bad?
They treated me like I was homeless.
We are homeless.
Right.
You know how to kill people?
She must be experienced.
I killed them before they could get to me.
What will you two do now?
We'll find a similar place
or starve to death on the streets.
Nothing changes the fact
that we've been abandoned.
Then would you like to join me?
I'll give you everything
you've ever wanted but never got.
-For example?
Let's see.
They always need time to think.
-Don't scammers do that?
-Yes.
First, since I now have two daughters,
why don't you call me Mom?
I could see a sequel
coming out in the future.
This is a cliffhanger.
Did you stay up all night?
May, I think Code Name Candy
will have a sequel.
In the final scene, Candy finds some kids
that she needs to protect.
Why are you spoiling it? I'll kill you.
In the sequel, she needs to strive
to protect what's dear to her.
A sequel is a must.
This movie hasn't even been released.
I hate you.
I'm sorry.
Did you read the news?
-About what?
-You probably didn't.
KI EUN-BI AND ASSEMBLYMAN NO'S AFFAIR
-Gosh.
-Is this true?
Probably not. It seemed like
she was dating someone younger than her.
People have gone berserk.
Why are you so emotional?
This is linked to Ji-hyun's workplace.
Isn't she in their agency?
You're right.
You're so thoughtful.
I just remembered
that she was Seon-gyeom's sister.
Thanks to what you've done to him,
he's now about to ruin
my daughter's reputation.
It can't be.
No, right?
Poor Ji-hyun.
He'll probably work overtime today.
I should call off our date first.
Seon-gyeom, where are you?
Do you want to come over when you're done?
Okay, see you. Bye.
Gosh.
I should be of help
since we've exchanged numbers.
Ms. Ki, this is Oh Mi-joo.
If you ever need to talk,
feel free to come over anytime.
No one will suspect that you'd be here.
Okay. I'll call you back later.
Didn't I say that
we should ask her ourselves?
Mr. Jeong, where's Eun-bi?
She's not at the hotel.
I'm on my way to her parents'.
Okay.
For today, let's tell them
that we're waiting for her reply.
If we still can't reach her tomorrow,
we'll claim that it's groundless.
I will request an exorcism this year.
At all costs.
-Hi, Mom.
-Did you read the news about Eun-bi?
What news?
Don't ask any questions.
Just go and comfort her.
I'm currently out of town due to filming.
If you weren't,
would you have gone yourself?
You sure know how to make me feel guilty.
No, I still wouldn't have been able to go.
I need to film
and memorize my English lines
for the audition in Hollywood.
Take good care of yourself.
You have such a busy schedule.
Am I being too selfish?
She must be troubled
by that ridiculous article.
And yet, I'm still here.
If you were to leave,
your fans would be disappointed in you.
PRESIDENT SEO DAN-AH
I'm sorry.
We kind of have an issue right now.
Don't worry. It's okay.
Is it because of Eun-bi?
So you know.
Don't worry too much.
It's our concern anyway.
I'm afraid Ms. Seo is still
having a meeting outside
and will be late.
I'm not here to see her.
Then why are you here?
As soon as I greeted you,
you told me to wait here.
How silly of me.
I automatically thought
that you were here to see her.
You don't look too well. Are you okay?
No. I've been bombarded
with a lot of bad news.
So why are you here?
I'm here to apply for that position.
You offered me the position,
so I thought I should submit it myself.
This is quite thick.
-You must've put in a lot of effort.
-Yes, I put my heart into it.
I'll take a thorough look.
You should work. I'll go now.
I hope to see you during the interview.
Hello?
Of course, it's not true.
Did you read the news?
Yes, on my way here.
I can't reach her either.
About those photos--
Eun-bi was the one who let me in on it.
You two met?
She visited me.
She probably wanted to warn me in advance.
She must have liked you a lot.
I'm honored.
According to what she told me,
it seemed like your father kept an eye
on his family members
and even had files on you.
Is this true?
I'd say there's a possibility.
I'm not sure
if I understood him correctly.
He could have just said it out of spite,
but what he said bothered me quite a bit.
She must be here.
Who?
I wanted you guys to talk in a safe space.
Ryan won't pick up my calls.
You've always found him no matter what.
I'm scared that he'll stop running away
and just break up with me.
-Would you like some more water?
-Yes, please.
Thank you for inviting me over.
I have no one to talk to
since I have no friends.
Since you invited me,
I decided to come here brazenly.
-Would you like some alcohol?
-I don't drink.
I don't think I'll be able to stop myself.
I did have tea with him.
But we were waiting for my father.
Am I truly innocent?
Will he trust me?
I can't live without him.
-You've lived well without him.
-You're wrong.
Did you know him since you were a baby?
You should be completely honest with him.
He must feel the same way
you're feeling right now.
How can I be honest with him
when he won't even pick up?
You could text or email him.
I didn't think of that.
It never crossed my mind.
What if this affects Father's election?
At a time like this,
you should put yourself first.
Let's be selfish for once.
You've changed a lot.
I should tell him myself
that it's not true, right?
Oh, dear.
Should I tag along?
And make things worse?
Thank you for the water.
Don't worry too much.
Swing by if it's too much to handle.
I'm always home.
Thank you.
It's not true.
I would never cheat on my boyfriend,
let alone with a married man.
Of course.
If I don't trust my own daughter,
who will?
You are more-- No, a million times
more famous than that nobody.
This was the best way for him
to make himself known.
Trust me. I'll take care of everything.
Okay.
Right, I should stop by my agency.
I'm sure it's chaotic.
Yes, you should.
Focus on training.
This is a crucial time for you.
All right. I'm sorry.
I feel like I dragged you into this.
Don't say that.
Thank you for believing me.
Did you get in touch with her?
We've given our reply for now.
Once the dust settles,
we should make a formal announcement.
How dare they call my athlete
a gold digger?
Do they seriously want to call someone
as successful as her a gold digger?
We're collecting the malicious posts.
We'll do everything we can
to see that they're punished.
She must be troubled as well.
Let's wait until tomorrow.
Check with Seon-gyeom just in case.
She must have talked to him
since he's her brother.
I'll try to find her myself.
Yes, ma'am.
I wish you weren't too invested, sir.
You're tormenting yourself.
This is my fate.
I should give it my all
no matter how big or small the matter is.
Should I rearrange your schedule?
You're barely sleeping these days.
Say that once I even have
enough time to sleep.
At times I feel
that this is too much for me to take.
I'm tired of forcing myself to smile.
My body just can't take it anymore.
Ms. Seo, good shot.
How did you find me?
I thought you'd be training
amid all this drama.
Is the scandal true?
What do you think?
We dealt with this issue once before
but here it is again.
My father wants me to be patient.
He'll take care of it.
I'm sure our agency doesn't need
to listen to him.
Or is he your agent?
I'm happy as long as you're okay.
Don't tell me
you came because you were worried.
I just came to golf.
She didn't go easy on me even once
although I'm not even an athlete.
Are you sure about that?
I see.
I'm done with the painting.
Come take a look.
I'm really done this time.
This hat totally ruined my hairstyle.
Would I still look beautiful?
I'll bring out the hair styler
from the car.
If he's lying again,
I don't think I'll let him live.
Should I bring this just in case?
Wouldn't this hurt?
What? What's that in your hand?
-I brought it just in case.
-I see.
All right. It's finally done.
Here we go. You can look forward to it.
One, two,
three. Ta-da.
It's
very noisy.
You hear noises?
Has technology advanced that much?
You're still too young to hide it.
Students tend to vividly reflect
their feelings or disposition
in their drawings.
You must have met many students.
That's just a theory.
This is just screaming, "I love you."
I love you, Ms. Seo.
You're right. That's what I felt
while working on this piece.
"Piece"?
Don't they usually say "work"?
I want to call this one a piece.
But then again, it should be called so
only after I die.
Until then, this is just a work of mine.
I'd love to see your piece.
You're not telling me to die, are you?
You should live a long life.
You're too young to say such a thing.
Gosh. You're unbelievable.
How could I display this
at an art museum? It's embarrassing.
I have no choice
but to keep it for myself.
-I need to take this.
-Sure.
Yes, Mr. Jeong.
What?
What did you say?
Wait.
Are you serious?
Okay. I'm on my way.
What's wrong?
Did something happen at work?
Or do you feel dizzy again?
-Ms. Seo.
-Yes?
Oh, it's related to work.
I should go.
Are you sure you can drive?
Yes. I'm the only one here who can.
Go back inside. It's cold.
You'll call me,
right?
Not all children
mourn the death of their parents.
And not all parents
love their children unconditionally.
Yeong-hwa.
Yes?
You should live a long life.
They say geniuses die early.
Subtitle translation by: Hye-lim Park
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs