watch on kisskh.me
HICCUP:
This is berk,
the best kept secret
this side of, well...
Anywhere.
Granted, it may
not look like much,
but this wet heap of rock
packs more than
a few surprises.
Life here is amazing,
just not for the faint
of heart.
You see, where most folks
enjoy hobbies like whittling
or needlepoint,
we berkians prefer...
...a little something
we like to call...
...dragon racing!
♪ ♪
Whoa-ho-ho!
Ho-ho!
I'm sorry, Fishlegs,
did you want that?
oh, snotlout, that was mine!
Here you go, babe.
Did I tell you that
you look amazing today?
'Cause you do.
Ugh!
Come on, barf.
It's starting
to stink around here.
Nope, still hates you.
Let's blow this place, belch!
SNOTLOUT:
Aah!
All right!
MAN: Come on!
Oh, yeah!
Ah, ha-ha!
That's nine for the twins!
Astrid lags with three!
Fishlegs and snotlout
trail with none!
And hiccup is...
Nowhere to be found.
Hmm.
Scared him off with the big
talk, didn't you, stoick?
What are you doing, snotlout?
They're gonna win now.
She's my Princess-- whatever
she wants, she gets.
Ruffnut? Didn't she try
to bury you alive?
:
Only for a few hours.
MAN:
Look at 'em go!
HICCUP:
Now, dragons used to be
a bit of a problem here,
but that was five years ago.
Now they've all moved in.
And, really,
why wouldn't they?
We have custom stables,
all-you-can-eat
feeding stations,
a full-service
dragon wash...
Even top-of-the-line
fire prevention,
if I do say so myself.
Ah, it's time, gobber.
Righty-ho.
Last lap!
The black sheep!
Come on, Stormfly!
We can still win this thing!
Come on, barf!
Let's go!
Go, meatlug!
let's go, let's go!
Ha-ha!
This is your
big moment.
Have a nice flight.
Up! Up, up, up, up, up!
Good job, meatlug!
FISHLEGS: Here you go, darling.
Mine's worth ten.
Yeah! The black sheep!
You guys are fighting
for Ruffnut?
I'm totally winning!
We're winning together.
Oh, no!
Whoo! No one can stop me now!
Except for me.
We're attached, genius.
Quit trying to steal
hey!
All my glory!
Get them, Astrid!
It's my glory!
Always ruining everything!
No, sheep, no glory!
ASTRID:
Gotcha! Ha-ha!
Whoa!
Astrid!
Well played!
That's my future
daughter-in-law!
Whoo-hoo!
Uh, excuse me.
ASTRID:
Stormfly!
Whoa!
Aah!
That's 13!
Astrid takes the game!
HICCUP:
Yep, berk is pretty
much perfect.
All of my hard work
has paid off.
And it's a good thing, too,
because with vikings
on the backs of dragons...
...the world
just got a whole lot bigger.
♪ ♪
yeah!
so, what do you think, bud?
You want to give this
another shot?
Toothless!
It'll be fine.
Ready?
Aah...!
Yeah...!
Whoo-hoo!
♪ ♪
yeah!
whoa!
♪ ♪
Oh...
Whoo-hoo!
Whoa!
Yeah!
Whoo!
This is amazing!
No longer amazing.
Toothless!
Oh, no!
Oh! Aah!
Aah! Whoa!
Whoo!
That really came out of nowhere.
We-we got to work on
your solo gliding there, bud.
That, uh, locked-up tail
makes for some pretty sloppy
rescue maneuvers, hey?
♪ ♪
ah!
Looks like we found
another one, bud.
Oh...!
Oh, what, do you
want an apology?
Is that why you're
pouting, big baby boo?
Well, try this on!
Oh, you feeling it yet? Huh?
Picking up on all
my heartfelt remorse?
:
Ah. Yeah. Oh, come on, come on,
you-you wouldn't hurt
a one-legged...
Uh... Y-you're
right, you're right.
You win. You win.
whoa-whoa-whoa...
he's down!
And it's ugly!
Dragons and vikings...
enemies again...
Locked in combat to the bitter...
Oh...!
You know that
doesn't wash out.
♪ ♪
so, what should we name it?
"Itchy armpit" it is.
What do you reckon, bud?
Think we might find a few
timberjacks in those woods?
The odd whispering death
or two in the rocks?
Who knows, maybe
we'll finally track down
another night fury.
Wouldn't that be something.
:
So, what do you say?
Just keep going?
Afternoon, milady.
HICCUP: Where have you been?
hi.
Oh, winning races.
What else?
The real question is,
where have you been?
Avoiding my dad.
Oh, no.
What happened now?
Oh, you're gonna...
You're gonna love this.
I wake up,
the sun's shining,
terrible terrors are
singing on the rooftop,
I saunter down to breakfast
thinking all is right
with the world, and I get:
:
"Son, we need to talk."
: "Not, now, dad.
I got a whole day of goofing off
to get started."
:
Okay, first of all,
I-I don't sound like that.
What is this character?
and-and second...
What is that thing you're
doing with my shoulders?
Yeah, that's-that's a really
flattering impersonation.
Anyway, he goes...
"You're the pride of berk, son,
and I couldn't be prouder."
Aw, thanks, dad.
I'm pretty impressed
with myself, too.
: When have I ever
done that with my hands?
You just did!
Okay, just... Hold... still.
Very serious.
Mm-hmm.
:
"You're all grown up,
"and since no chief could ask
for a better successor,
I've decided..."
To make you chief!
Oh, my gods!
Hiccup, that's amazing!
oh...!
Y-you're gonna wear
out the spring coil.
The calibration
is very sensitive.
Yeah, so... this is
what I'm dealing with.
What did you tell him?
I-I didn't.
By the time he turned
around, I was gone.
Huh.
Well... it's a lot
of responsibility.
The map will have
to wait, for sure,
and... and I'll need
to fly toothless, since
you'll be too busy, but...
I-it's not me, Astrid.
All those speeches and planning
and running the village,
that's his thing.
I think you're
missing the point.
I mean-- chief.
What an honor!
I'd be pretty excited.
I-I... I'm not like you.
You... know exactly
who you are,
you always have, but...
I'm still looking.
I know that I'm
not my father,
and I never met
my mother, so...
What does that make me?
What you're searching for
isn't out there, hiccup...
It's in here.
Maybe you just
don't see it yet.
Ugh. Ugh!
Maybe.
But, you know...
There is something
out there.
Hiccup... ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
:
Wow...
Stay close.
♪ ♪
:
What happened here?
♪ ♪
all right, e-easy, bud.
hiccup!
MAN: Fire!
Astrid, look out!
Aah! Hiccup!
Watch the tail!
Tie those legs up!
Huh?
Is that what I think it is?
HICCUP: Stop!
ASTRID:
Stormfly!
What are you doing?!
OTHERS:
Ooh!
back again!
Soil my britches.
That is a night fury.
Thought they were
all gone for good.
Looks like our
luck's had a turn
for the better, lads!
Don't think drago
has one of those...
In his dragon army.
Dragon army?
Look, we don't
want any trouble.
Hah! You should
have thought of that
before you stole
all of our dragons
and blasted our
fort to bits!
MAN: That's right!
MAN 2: Yeah, look it at!
HICCUP:
Wait.
What are you
talking about?
You think we did this?
Hah! Dragon trapping is
hard enough work as it is
without do-gooder dragon riders
sneaking in to rescue them.
What do-gooder...?
There are other dragon riders?
You mean
other than your thieving friend
from last night? You tell me.
You may have
an ice-spitting dragon
on your side,
but we still have
a quota to fill.
How do you suppose
we explain this mess
to drago bludvist?
Drago what-fist?
Does anything you
say make sense?
He's expecting
a new shipment of dragons
for his army by tomorrow.
And drago don't
take well to excuses!
This is what he gave me
last time I showed up
empty-handed.
He promised to be far less
understanding in the future.
All right, look, we don't know
anything about a dragon thief
or an ice-spitting dragon
or your lunatic boss
and his dragon army, okay?
Just give us back our dragon,
and we'll go...
Strange, hostile person
whom we've never met.
Oh, where are my manners?
I'm eret... Son of eret.
Finest dragon trapper alive.
OTHERS: Yeah.
After all...
It's not just anyone
who can capture a night fury.
And this is toothless.
He says we're going. Now.
Hah!
They all say that.
Rush 'em, lads!
ASTRID:
Stormfly, come on!
Go! Go!
You will never hold
on to those dragons!
You hear me?!
Drago is coming for them all!
Come on, meatlug!
Whoo-hoo!
Yahoo!
Hey there, stoick!
Hey, how are you?
Beautiful day.
Hello, spitelout. Great race.
Yeah...
Oh! Sorry, Mrs. ack.
: Any sign of him?
Eh! He's probably flown
off the edge
of the world by now.
You sure you want that kid
running the village?
You can still delay
your retirement.
Oh, he's ready.
You'll see.
there he is!
Huh?
The pride of berk!
Who finally decided
to show up for work. Yay.
Sorry, got held up.
Hey, uh, dad,
could I have a word?
Something you're
itching to tell me?
Uh, not quite the itch
you're thinking of, but, yes.
Oh, good man!
NOW, LESSON ONE:
A chief's first duty
is to his people, so... 41!
Well, can we just
talk in private for...
Forty...
MAN: That's me!
That's me! I'm next!
MAN 2: Hey, I was
ahead of you!
If we could just talk...
Excuse me.
I've been here all day.
Okay, okay, I want one
of those high seaters
with lots of spikes and a
big storage compartment!
Absolutely! You got it, sir.
Dad, this is actually
a little more important
than building saddles.
AH, LESSON TWO:
No task is too small
when it comes
to serving your people.
But, dad...
Oh, excuse us, grump.
Can we just talk...
Yah! Grump!
You let the forge
die down again!
Ah...
GOBBER: That's it, grump!
You're going up for adoption.
Okay, uh...
There you go.
Dad... yeah, but seriously,
go on. Have away.
I really need to tell you about
this new land we came across.
Another one?
Any new dragons?
We didn't stick
around to find out.
These folks weren't
particularly friendly.
GOBBER:
Oh, really?
Your night fury
and deadly nadder
didn't bring them
cheering to the rooftops?
No, this was different.
Not the standard
run-for-the-hills hoo-ha
I've come to enjoy.
These guys were trappers.
Dragon trappers.
You should have seen their fort.
All blown apart and stuck
in giant spikes of ice.
It was weird.
I've never seen
anything like it.
A-and worst of all,
they thought we did it!
You know, you two are gonna get
yourselves in serious trouble
one of these days.
Not everyone appreciates
this way of life.
Aye, gobber's
right, son.
Best we keep to our own.
Besides, you'll have more
important uses for your time.
Huh-huh?
Once we make
the big announcement!
They are building
a dragon army.
Or-or at least the guy
they work for is. Uh...
"Dargo... bloody fist"
or something.
I'll bloody his
fist with my face
if he tries to
take my dragon!
Or mine!
Ugh! You're such a moron.
A beautiful moron.
Yeah.
Bludvist? Drago bludvist?
Uh, yeah. Wait... You know him?
Ground all dragons!
HICCUP: What? Why?
STOICK:
Seal the gates!
Lower the storm doors!
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait, wait.
What is happening?
GOBBER: Come on!
You heard the man!
Lock it down!
STOICK: No dragon or viking
sets foot off this island
until I give the word!
Wait, because some guy you knew
is stirring up trouble
in some faraway land?
Because drago bludvist
is a madman
without conscience
or mercy.
And if he's built
a dragon army,
gods help us all.
Get them into
their pens!
Quickly!
Aye, stoick.
Then let's ride
back out there.
We'll follow those
trappers to drago
and talk some
sense into him.
No. We fortify the island.
It's our duty to
keep the peace.
Peace is over, hiccup.
I must prepare you for war.
War?
Dad, if drago's
coming for our dragons,
we can't wait around
for him to get here.
Let's go find him
and change his mind.
No, some minds
won't be changed, hiccup.
Berk is what you need
to worry about.
A chief protects his own.
STOICK: Secure the stables!
Latch every stall!
Hiccup, don't.
I have to.
STOICK:
This way!
Quickly!
Hiccup!
Come on!
Aah!
♪ ♪
ERET:
Keep your eyes peeled, lads!
With this wind,
we'll reach drago by daybreak.
So best we fill this ship up
with dragons, and quick!
It's no time to be picky!
Uh, eret?
Not if we want to keep our...
...heads!
Off the port quarter!
Net them, lads!
Take them down!
MAN: There's two of them!
Up on the left!
ERET: You're not
getting away this time.
Fire!
Reload!
Come on, reload!
Incoming!
MAN:
Steady yourselves, mates.
ERET:
And here I was,
worried we might turn up
empty-handed.
Nope.
It's your lucky day.
We give up.
That's one night fury,
uh, one deadly nadder, and...
Two of the finest dragon
riders west of luk tuk.
That ought to make the boss
happy, right?
Excuse us.
:
What are you doing?
HICCUP:
Toothless, stay.
HICCUP: Uh, the dragons
don't really care
for cramped spaces, so they'll
just hang out with you.
They won't be any trouble.
Unless you do that.
You know, wooden boats,
big ocean...
H-how is your swimming?
Not good.
Oops. Almost forget.
Can't have armed prisoners.
Give me that.
:
How is this a plan?
Just what every
dragon trapper needs.
One end coats the blade
in monstrous nightmare saliva.
The other sprays
hideous zippleback gas.
All it takes
is a spark, and...
HICCUP:
Oh, yeah, there you go.
HICCUP: Once they see you
as one of their own,
even the testiest dragons
can be trained.
Right, bud?
ERET:
Give me that!
What game are you playing?
HICCUP: Uh, no game.
We just want to meet drago.
why?
Because I'm going to change
his mind about dragons.
He can be really
persuasive.
Once you've earned his loyalty,
there is nothing a dragon
won't do for you.
you won't be changing
any minds around here.
I can change yours,
right here, right now.
♪ ♪
uh, may I?
Waah!
Watch it!
ERET: Dragon riders!
HICCUP:
Put me down!
Snotlout,
what-what are you doing?
See how well I protect
and provide?
TUFFNUT:
What is with all the nets?
RUFFNUT:
Hey, watch it! That was...
Close.
Oh, my.
Me likey.
Take me.
Hold your fire!
Um, what are you guys
doing here?
We're here to rescue you!
I don't need to be rescued.
STOICK: Enough!
Well, didn't you just pick
the wrong ship, eh?
I am eret, son of...
: Eret...
I...
Get this thing off me.
Anyone else?
Hmm, that's what I figured.
You, saddle up.
We're going home.
No.
Of all the irresponsible...
I'm trying to protect
our dragons and stop a war.
How is that irresponsible?
Because war
is what he wants, son!
Years ago, there was
a great gathering of chieftains
to discuss the dragon scourge
we all faced.
Into our midst came a stranger
from a strange land,
covered in scars and draped
in a cloak of dragon skin.
He carried no weapon
and spoke softly,
saying that he,
drago bludvist,
was a man of the people,
devoted to freeing mankind
from the tyranny of dragons.
He claimed that he alone
could control the dragons,
and that he alone
could keep us safe,
if we chose to bow down
and follow him.
Stupid.
Ah, good one.
Aye, we laughed, too...
Until he wrapped himself
in his cloak
and cried out,
"then see how well you do
without me!"
DRAGO: ...See how well
you do without me!
The rooftop suddenly burst
into flames,
and from it,
armored dragons descended,
burning the hall
to the ground.
I... Was the only one to escape.
Men who kill without reason
cannot be reasoned with.
Maybe.
Hiccup!
I'm still going to try.
This is what I'm good at,
and-and if I could change
your mind,
I can change his, too.
Come on.
Let's go.
No!
Lead the others back to berk.
I've had enough mutiny
for one day.
Ooh, I like that.
STOICK: Ruffnut!
okay!
Ah.
Don't worry, bud.
I'm not gonna let anything
happen to you.
I promise.
Aw, come on, dad.
Really?
Okay.
No sudden moves.
♪ ♪
hold on, hold on.
Toothless...!
♪ ♪
hey!
You left my dragon back there!
He can't fly on his own!
He'll drown!
Hey! Uh...
We have to head back
for my dragon!
Who are you?
The dragon thief?
Uh... Drago bludvist?
Do you even understand
what I'm saying?
Toothless!
Oh, it's okay,
it's okay, it's okay.
I'm glad to see you,
too, bud.
You really had me worried there.
Uh, uh...
:
Oh...
Hiccup?
Uh...
C-could it be?
After all these years?
How is this possible?
Uh, should I...
Should I know you?
No.
You were only a babe.
But a mother never forgets.
Shh, shh.
Come.
STOICK:
Boar-headed!
Just like his mother!
Aye, she could never
stay put, either.
GOBBER:
Eh, he's just 20,
and a viking.
I mean, could there be
a worse combination?
Heh! When I think
of how stubborn and senseless
you were back in the day.
Oh.
Well, not much
has changed, actually.
Ah, you know what he's like.
He won't give up, gobber.
And if hiccup finds drago
before we find him...
Ah!
Nothing can hurt hiccup,
so long as that
night fury's around.
It's a night fury!
Huh?
Find them, skullcrusher.
Find them.
Uh, h-hold on.
Wait just a minute.
This way.
Come back here.
Come.
You can't just say
something like that and run off.
You're my mother?!
I mean, what the...?
Do you... do you grasp how
insane it sounds?
Come quickly.
I have questions!
where have you...
Been all this time?
What-what have you been doing?
But they-they said
you were dead!
Everyone thinks
you were eaten by...
This is where you've been
for 20 years?
You-you've been rescuing them.
Unbelievable.
You're not upset?
What?
No. I-I don't know. I...
It's a bit much to get
my head around, to be frank.
It's not every day you find out
your mother
is some kind of crazy, feral,
vigilante dragon lady.
Oh...
Well...
At least I'm not boring, right?
Well, I suppose there is that...
One specific thing.
Do-do you like it?
I... I... I... I-I
don't have the words.
C-can I... Oh, he's beautiful.
Oh.
Oh, incredible.
He might very well be
the last of his kind.
Oh... and look, he's your age.
Wow.
No wonder you get
along so well.
Oh, yeah? Oh, yeah?
And retractable teeth.
How did you manage...
I found him in the woods.
He was shot down
and wounded.
This snafflefang lost his leg
to one of drago bludvist's
iron traps.
This raincutter
had her wing sliced
by razor netting.
And this, oh, poor hobblegrunt
was blinded by a tree snare
and then left to die alone
and scared.
And what of this?
Did drago or his trappers
do this, too?
oh.
Yeah.
Well, crazy thing is...
I'm actually the one
who shot him down.
Hey, it's-it's okay, though.
He got me back.
Right, bud?
You couldn't save
all of me, could you?
You just had to make it even.
So peg leg.
uh...
What did your father think
of your night fury friend?
Oh, he-he didn't take
it all that well.
But then, he changed.
They all did.
Pretty soon,
everyone back home had
dragons of their own.
If only it were possible.
No, really.
Believe me, I tried, as well,
but people are not capable
of change, hiccup.
Some of us...
were just born different.
MOTHER:
Berk was a land of kill
or be killed,
but I believed peace
was possible.
Stop!
You'll only make it worse!
MOTHER:
It was a very
unpopular opinion.
Hiccup!
MOTHER:
Then one night,
a dragon broke into our
house, finding you
in the cradle.
I rushed to protect you.
But what I saw was proof
of everything I believed.
This wasn't a vicious beast,
but an intelligent,
gentle creature,
whose soul reflected my own.
Valka, run!
No, don't.
Oh... Hold on!
No! Aah! Stoick!
STOICK:
Valka!
Stoick!
Valka.
VALKA:
You and your father
nearly died
that night.
All because
I couldn't kill a dragon.
Eh, runs in the family.
It broke my heart to stay away,
but I believed
you'd be safer if I did.
How did you survive?
Oh, cloudjumper never meant
to harm me.
He must have thought
I belonged here
in the home of the
great bewilderbeast.
The Alpha species.
One of the very few
that still exist.
Every nest has its queen,
but this is the king
of all dragons.
With his icy breath,
this graceful giant
built our nest,
a safe haven for
dragons everywhere.
Wait, that's the ice-spitter?
He's responsible for
all that destruction?
He protects us.
We all live under his
care and his command.
VALKA: All but the babies,
of course...
...who listen to no one.
Aw...
I've lived among them
for 20 years, hiccup,
discovering their secrets.
he likes you.
Wow.
You must be hungry.
Uh, yeah, I could eat.
Good.
It's feeding time.
I don't like it.
They should've been back
with hiccup by now.
I don't like it, either.
eret, son of eret,
was the man of my dreams.
My everything!
But, baby,
I grew facial hair for you.
Me, too.
What if drago shot them down?
What if they need our help?
We have to find them.
Wait, wait, what?
No, but stoick said...
It doesn't matter
what he said
if they've all been captured.
Come on!
NO-NAME:
Do we go back?
ERET:
We've nowhere to go,
nothing to sell, and no heads
to call our own.
Uh, eret...?
If we don't turn up
with dragons and fast...
Careful what you wish for!
Do something!
Eret, son of eret!
We'll miss you, eret!
What is this?
A kidnapping.
Yay, can he ride with me?
Can he?
:
Can he...?
You're gonna show us
the way to drago.
And help dragon riders
sneak into drago's camp?
Just kill me now.
That could be arranged.
Stormfly, drop it.
Huh?
Good girl!
Stormfly, fetch.
All right!
Okay! I'll take you to drago!
Works every time.
Hey, I-I thought
we were going to eat.
Oh, we are.
And then, from dragon island,
I found this archipelago...
There.
whoa.
♪ ♪
VALKA:
Oh, when I'm up here,
I don't even feel the cold.
I just feel... Free.
This is what it is to
be a dragon, hiccup.
It's all well and good
to call yourself a
dragon, but can you fly?
Oh, no! Aah!
Man, almost!
we just about
had it that time.
Incredible.
Well, not bad yourself.
All this time,
you took after me.
And... Where was I?
I'm so sorry, hiccup.
Can we start over?
Will you give me another chance?
I-I can teach you
all that I've learned
these past 20 years.
Like...
Wow.
Now you can make
those tight turns.
Did you know about this?
every dragon
has its secrets. And...
I'll show them all to you.
We'll unlock every mystery,
find every last species--
together, as mother and son.
This gift we share,
hiccup, it bonds us.
This is who you are, son.
Who we are.
We will change the world
for all dragons.
We will make it a better,
safer place.
Yeah, I mean, that
sounds amazing.
Oh, this is so great!
Now you and I can go talk
to drago together.
:
What?
There's no talking to drago.
But we have to...
No.
We must protect our own.
come on.
We should be getting back.
Hmm?
Okay, I got you here!
Now get this thing off me.
Never take a toy from a dragon.
Don't you know anything?
Why does this
keep happening to me?
What's down there?
Large diameter bubbles,
massive lungs,
cold water deep dweller,
I'm thinking
class five leviathan, maybe six.
ERET: Yah!
Meatlug, what's wrong, girl?
Hookfang!
Come on!
Don't move!
Uh...
♪ ♪
ERET:
Drago!
Get off me!
Always great
to see you, my friend.
Keeping warm up here?
Well, as you can see,
I am right on time
with a new batch of dragons,
just like I promised.
He's waking up!
Drop the ropes!
Give me some backup here!
Watch out!
Drop the ropes.
SNOTLOUT: Hookfang!
RUFFNUT: Hey!
What are you doing?!
You belong to me now.
ERET:
And as an added bonus,
I also caught you
their riders.
No extra charge.
What?
Are you kidding me?
Aw!
But you were so perfect!
Turns out there's a whole bunch
of them out there.
they attacked...
How many?
Drago doesn't have them
after all.
How many?
ASTRID: Hundreds.
A whole island full.
I wouldn't worry about it.
: My men are
hunting them down as we speak.
They won't know
where you're hiding.
I promise you that.
Oh, yes, they will!
They know we're missing,
and they have
tracking dragons.
If you so much as touch us,
hiccup is gonna kick...
Hiccup?
He's not a problem.
Really, trust me.
He's only the son
of stoick the vast,
his heir to the
throne of berk,
and the greatest dragon master
this world has ever seen.
"Dragon master"?
I alone control the dragons.
Nope, mm-mm.
Sorry!
And unless you let us go
right now,
he will blast through here
on his night fury
and blow your entire
fleet of ships
to splinters.
Then they'll be crying
like babies.
funny and beautiful.
Good one, babe.
Yeah.
Like babies,
they always cry.
Real tiny ones.
First there was one rider,
and now all of berk?
And you led them to me!
drago...!
Stop all preparations!
We must attack
the dragon riders' nest at once!
We will take down their Alpha.
Then we will take berk!
Drago!
And get rid of him.
drago, please, I...
ASTRID:
Stormfly!
No!
Well, bud...
We can't wait around for drago
to attack this place.
We've got to find him first.
Let's go.
Easy now.
Are you kidding me?
How did you get in here?
The same way we're
getting you out.
"We"?
All clear.
Toothless, come.
Uh, wait, uh, wait...
Okay, uh, dad,
there-there's something
you need to know.
Yeah, yeah,
tell me on the way.
Well, this isn't an "on the way"
kind of update, actually.
I've heard enough, hiccup.
More-more of
the earth-shattering
development variety.
Yeah, just add it to pile.
HICCUP:
Yeah, I, uh, uh,
dad, unlike most surprises
I spring on you,
this is one you'll like,
I promise.
You just have to
handle it delicately.
So... Uh...
You might want to take this one.
Huh?
Oh, boy.
Oh, uh, dad,
could you put
the sword away, please?
Oh.
I know what
you're gonna say, stoick.
How could I have done this?
Stayed away all of these years,
and why didn't
I come back to you?
To our son?
Well... What sign did I have
that you could change, stoick?
That anyone on berk could?
I pleaded so many times
to stop the fighting,
to find another answer,
but did any of you listen?
This is why I never married.
This, and one other reason.
I know that I left you
to raise hiccup alone,
but I thought he'd be
better off without me,
and I was wrong.
I see that now, but... Oh!
Stop being so stoic, stoick.
Go on, shout, scream,
say something!
You're as beautiful
as the day I lost you.
♪ ♪
DRAGO'S MAN:
Move it.
SNOTLOUT:
Could this day get any worse?
TUFFNUT:
Uh, let me see.
We're gonna jump
into freezing cold water
and then die from drowning.
ERET:
Looks refreshing.
Please, ladies first.
You are a steaming heap of dragon...
Duck.
Warn the others!
Get them, you son of an eret.
TUFFNUT:
Take that!
Okay, I love you again.
oh, pathetic.
You can still jump.
So, are we going to save
your dragons
and get out of here
or not?
Mm.
Check every trap.
They're here somewhere.
Meatlug?
Anyone coming?
I don't know, you just keep
doing what you're doing.
keep cranking.
Thank you for saving my life.
Now let me return the favor.
Mom, you'd never
even recognize it.
Where we used
to make weapons,
we now build saddles,
wing slings...
We-we even fix dragon teeth.
You-you wouldn't believe
how much everything's changed.
Aye, your son's changed berk
for the better.
I think we did well
with this one, val.
Thanks, dad.
Stoick :
I got it.
I'm, uh... A little
out of practice.
Well, you know,
I didn't marry you
for your cooking.
GOBBER:
I hope not.
Her meatballs
could kill more beasts
than a battle ax.
I've still got a few knocking
around in here.
And once you move back in
with all your dragons,
old drago won't even
stand a chance.
Everything will be okay.
slow down, son.
It's a lot to take in.
HICCUP:
Oh, gotcha.
Oh, I love this one.
Remember our song, val?
♪ I'll swim and sail ♪
♪ on savage seas ♪
♪ with ne'er a fear
of drowning ♪
♪ and gladly ride ♪
♪ the waves of life ♪
♪ if you will marry me ♪
♪ no scorching sun ♪
♪ nor freezing cold ♪
♪ will stop... ♪
♪ will stop me on my jour... ♪
♪ ...ney. ♪
sorry.
♪ If you will promise me  ♪
♪ your heart ♪
♪ and love... ♪
♪ And love me for eternity ♪
♪ my dearest one ♪
♪ my darling dear ♪
♪ your mighty words ♪
♪ astound me ♪
♪ but I've no need
of mighty deeds ♪
♪ when I feel
your arms around me ♪
♪ But I would bring
you rings of gold ♪
♪ and even sing you poetry ♪
whoo!
Oh, would you?
♪ and I would keep you ♪
♪ from all harm
if you would stay beside me ♪
VALKA: ♪ I have no use
for rings of gold ♪
♪ I care not for your poetry ♪
♪ I only want your
hand to hold ♪
♪ I only want you near me ♪
BOTH: ♪ to love and kiss,
to sweetly hold ♪
hey!
♪ for the dancing
and the dreaming ♪
come on, hiccup!
♪ through all my sorrows ♪
♪ and your lights, I'll keep
your laugh inside me ♪
♪ I'll swim and sail
the savage seas ♪
♪ with ne'er a fear
of drowning ♪
♪ and gladly ride
the waves of life ♪
♪ if you will marry me! ♪
♪ I'm still going... ♪
gobber...
I'm done.
I thought I'd have to die before
we'd have that dance again.
No need for drastic measures.
For you, my dear...
:
Anything.
Will you come home, val?
Will you be my
wife once again?
We can be a family!
What do you say?
:
Well...
Yes...
Great!
I'll do the cooking.
Thank Odin you didn't
listen to me, son.
we never
would've found each other.
toothless?
What's happening?
Oh...
:
Oh, no...
Val...
Val, it's all right,
it's all right.
We're a team now.
Now, what do you
want to do?
We have to save the dragons.
Aye, you got it.
Come on, son!
MAN:
Reload!
Fire!
MAN:
Fire! Fire!
Whatever comes,
keep hitting the mountain.
DRAGO:
We need to draw the Alpha out.
Ready the traps!
♪ ♪
TUFFNUT: Surprise!
Yeah!
What?!
Waah! Waah! Oh!
You really are
full of surprises.
Astrid :
Let's go.
TUFFNUT:
Dragon riders coming through!
Fire!
:
Oh, yeah!
MAN:
Look out!
Cut them down!
Eret, son of eret!
Aah...!
♪ ♪
up, girl!
Lean left, eret!
That's it!
ASTRID: Look out!
♪ ♪
HICCUP:
Yeah, baby!
Take them down!
Heads up!
Dragon master.
Welcome aboard,
dragon rider.
Thanks. I think.
Where have you been?
Oh, you know,
catching up with mom.
♪ ♪
That's your mother?!
Well, now you know
where I get my dramatic flair.
The Alpha!
Now we have a fight!
Come on, toothless.
Show them what you got, bud.
Attaboy!
♪ ♪
I've waited
a long time for this.
You cannot take our dragons!
They are controlled
by the Alpha!
Then it's a good thing
I brought a challenger.
Another one?
FISHLEGS:
That is a class ten! Class ten!
Look out!
No... no...
DRAGO: Come on!
Take down the Alpha!
Thank you.
For you, my dear... Anything.
Val, do you think
you can stop them?
I'll do my best.
Come on, cloudjumper!
you!
I watched you burn!
It takes more than
a little fire to kill me!
♪ ♪
Stoick!
No!
no!
We've won.
Now... Finish her!
No!
Hold on!
Skullcrusher, go!
Come on, gobber!
Right behind you, stoick!
♪ ♪
HICCUP:
Stop!
: This...
Is the great dragon master?
The son of
stoick the vast?
What shame he must feel.
All of this loss...
And for what?
To become unstoppable?
To rule the world?
Dragons, they-they are kind,
amazing creatures
that can bring people together.
Or tear them apart.
You see,
I know what it is
to live in fear, to see
my village burned,
my family taken.
But even as a boy...
Left with nothing,
I vowed to rise above
the fear of dragons...
...and liberate the
people of this world.
Then why a dragon army?
Well, you need dragons
to conquer other dragons.
Or maybe you need dragons
to conquer people...
To control those
who follow you...
And to get rid
of those who won't.
Clever boy.
The world wants peace,
and we have the answer
back on berk.
Just... let me show you-- no!
Let me... Show you!
What in...
Hiccup!
STOICK: Come on, gobber!
Okay, change of plan.
No dragon can resist
the Alpha's command.
So he who controls
the Alpha...
Controls them all.
Toothless?
T-toothless, you okay,
bud? What's going on?
DRAGO:
Witness true strength.
The strength
of will over others.
DRAGO:
In the face of it,
you are nothing.
Uh... what did
he just tell you?
Toothless, come on.
What's the matter with you?
No, no, no, no, come on,
what are you doing?
Knock it off.
:
Stop! Snap out of it!
toothless, no!
Toothless!
Don't!
Hiccup!
Stop...!
Son!
Dad!
No!
Hmm.
No...
Dad!
stoick...
Dad?
No. You...
No.
No, no, no. No.
♪ ♪
HICCUP:
No! Get away from him!
Go on! Get out of here!
get away!
VALKA: It's not his fault.
You know that.
VALKA:
Good dragons
under the control
of bad people...
FISHLEGS: No, wait. Don't go.
...Do bad things.
DRAGO:
Come on!
Gather the men
and meet me at berk!
Toothless!
No, don't.
♪ ♪
GOBBER:
May the valkyries welcome you
and lead you through
Odin's great battlefield.
May they sing your name
with love and fury,
so that we might hear it rise
from the depths of Valhalla,
and know that you've taken
your rightful place
at the table of kings.
For a great man has fallen.
A warrior.
A chieftain.
A father.
A friend.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, dad.
I'm not the chief that...
You wanted me to be.
And I'm not the peacekeeper
I thought I was.
I... don't know...
You came early
into this world.
You were such a wee thing.
Oh, so frail, so fragile.
I feared you
wouldn't make it.
But your father...
He never doubted.
He always said you'd become
the strongest of them all.
And he was right.
You have the heart
of a chief,
and the soul
of a dragon.
Only you can bring
our worlds together.
That... is who
you are, son.
♪ ♪
I, uh...
I was so afraid
of becoming my dad.
Mostly because
I thought I never could.
How-how do you become someone...
That great, that... brave,
that... selfless?
I guess you can only try.
A chief protects his own.
We're going back.
Uh... with what?
Uh, he took
all the dragons.
Not all of them.
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
FISHLEGS:
I don't want to die!
We can't fly things!
FISHLEGS:
Yeah, no kidding!
whoa...!
But won't that
bewilderbeast
just take control
of these guys, too?
: They're babies!
They don't listen to anyone.
Yeah. Just like us.
This is-- whoa!--
Very dangerous!
Some might suggest
this is poorly conceived!
Well, it's a good thing
that I never listen.
Whoa!
GOBBER:
So...
What is your... Plan?
Get toothless back
and kick drago's...
Heads up!
And that thing.
Whoa... Ow!
Oh! Oh... Ah, that's a good boy.
Uh... W-w-watch the furniture!
Where are you going?
Your chief... is dead!
Stoick?
No!
Not possible!
No one can protect you now!
♪ ♪
HICCUP:
No.
He took all the dragons.
Distract the Alpha.
Try to keep his focus
off of toothless.
Uh, how?
Have you forgotten
who you're riding with?
There isn't a dragon alive
that I can't wrangle! Aah!
Except for this one...!
Snotlout :
Amateur.
Hey, look! It's hiccup!
♪ ♪
What?
Ruffnut :
Keep 'em coming!
Black sheep, baby!
SNOTLOUT:
Ten points!
uh-oh.
I'm okay!
You certainly are hard
to get rid of, I'll say that.
Toothless... Hey.
:
It's me, bud.
It's me.
I'm right here, bud.
Come back to me.
He's not yours anymore.
He belongs to the Alpha.
But, please,
o great dragon master,
try... to take him.
He will not miss a second time.
It wasn't your fault, bud.
They... made you do it.
You'd never hurt him.
:
You'd never hurt me.
How are you doing that?
Please.
You are my best friend, bud.
My best friend.
Attaboy! That's it!
I'm here.
DRAGO: Enough!
Yeah!
Hang on!
Almost there, buddy,
almost there.
DRAGO:
Do something!
We need to get those two apart.
♪ ♪
We gotta block him out,
toothless.
Do you trust me, bud?
We can do this.
You... and me... As one.
That's it.
Now let's try this
one more time!
ASTRID: Take him down, babe!
Go get him.
Take control of it!
Shut it out, toothless.
Stop them!
Now!
Huh...?
Not again.
Toothless, it's now or never!
Come on, bud!
Hold on!
Ya-ha! We did it!
♪ ♪
Hold him there,
toothless.
It's all over now.
Or is it?
Uh... Oh, no!
No!
no!
Hiccup...
He's challenging
the Alpha!
To protect you!
♪ ♪
No, no, no, no, no! No!
Fight back! Fight!
Fight!
What's the matter with you!
Hold your ground!
Hold the line now!
Now do you get it?
This is what it is
to earn a dragon's loyalty.
Let this end now.
Never!
Come on!
Huh?
Fight!
♪ ♪
The Alpha... protects them all.
You never cease
to amaze me, bud.
thank you.
Toothless, you know
that doesn't wash out!
I knew you'd come back!
You're back, my beauty!
Oh! Oh!
ASTRID:
Stormfly!
Oh, give me a cuddle, grumpy!
Oh!
Who's my little Princess!
Don't you ever leave
again, hookfang.
Oh, you are. Yes, you are.
I missed you...
Oh, barf... Not you!
ERET:
That was some
pretty fine dragon-
wrangling back there.
You'd make a good trapper.
Whoa.
You know... skullcrusher
is gonna need somebody
to look after him now.
Me?
I'd be honored.
Oh, your father,
he'd be every bit
as proud as I am.
thank you.
I'm really glad
you're here, mom.
And here I'll stay.
See?
I told you it
was in here.
Ah, ha, ha.
You're still doing
that one.
That's hilarious.
Come here, you.
Mm!
Ooh!
♪ ♪
the chief has come home!
MAN:
Yeah!
Villagers :
Long live the chief!
♪ ♪
Yeah! Ha-ha!
Ah... Yah-ha-ha-ha!
HICCUP:
This... is berk.
A bit trampled and busted
and covered in ice,
but it's home.
It's our home.
Those who attacked us
are relentless and crazy.
But those who stopped them?
Oh... even more so!
We may be small in numbers,
but we stand for something
bigger than anything
the world can pit against us.
We are the voice of peace.
And bit by bit,
we will change this world.
♪ ♪
:
Wow!
You see,
we have something they don't.
Oh, sure, they have armies,
and they have armadas,
but we...
we have...
Our dragons!
♪ ♪