♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 15=
Who is that?
Come out!
Why can’t these youngsters do some
good deeds?
What a pity!
It’s such a cruel thing.
(Human Traffickers)
Yeah. Is he not afraid of retribution?
You should be sentenced to death.
What? What’s going on?
Look! Baldhead is tied up!
Make way! Step aside!
Official business!
Step aside!
-Make way!
-Sir!
We’re wronged, sir!
We’re innocent!
Innocent? You’re Baldhead Xu, right?
The trafficker has confessed
that you were going to sell him a girl.
I… I…
Sir,
I’m the girl he kidnapped.
I’m wronged.
Yuxiang!
I did all this for you!
You still dare to threaten others
when there is clear evidence?
Guards! Take him back and have him
flogged for 20 times!
Yes, sir!
Not like that!
It’s not like that! Sir!
Let her go.
Yuxiang!
Sir, it’s not like that!
(Human Traffickers)
-It’s not like that! -Go!
It’s not the truth!
Let me go!
Yuxiang.
-Father.
-Are you alright?
I’m fine.
What on earth happened?
I don’t know!
On my way home,
suddenly,
I got caught by a demon!
Demon?
But…
How could there be a demon?
Yuxiang.
Do you know who got us here?
I remember!
He is Qingqing’s brother!
I met him once in the market.
He… He…
He is a demon!
The demon is in Qingqing’s house.
Maybe
Qingqing is also a demon!
What’s going on?
Why do I feel a danger is coming?
It even makes my feathers bristle.
Something is wrong.
The invader is not friendly.
I have no powers now.
I can only escape.
My sachet!
You demon!
Let’s see where you can go.
Of course…
The back door.
Demon Rope!
Let go of me!
Dragon King!
Looks like she is already caught by me.
This demon is quite strong.
It’s a good material
for refining the elixir.
Ouch!
I haven’t touched your wound.
Really?
Ouch! It hurts!
If you continue yelling,
I’ll muzzle you.
My Lord…
You just can’t be quiet for a moment.
No…
I just wonder
why you came
after I cast the Three-call Spell
of Dragon King.
I changed it when I unsealed you
last time.
-It’s not a right thing…
-Don’t move.
Why did you make decisions
for me without asking me?
I saved you. And that’s your attitude?
Alright. Thank you for saving me.
But, I got hurt
because I went back
to take the sachet you gave me.
You care about that sachet?
Of course not.
If you don’t,
I won’t care about it either.
You can go now.
You’re no longer my maid.
Really?
I, Xue Qianxun, never tell lies.
Thank you, My Lord!
My Lord.
You don’t like eating osmanthus cakes.
Then these
must be for me, right?
Thank you!
My Lord! You’re so sweet! I’m leaving!
It’s done!
Why am I dizzy again?
Firefly.
Go and bring Yuchi here.
Yuchi! You’re here.
I need to give something back to you.
What is it?
I see the dragon on your handkerchief
is half embroidered.
So I finished embroidering it on my own.
Do you like it?
If the Star Halo shows up again
in three days,
you need to give me a token as well.
Finally I get your token of love.
It’s worth the wait.
You don’t like it?
I like it.
I like it so much.
This little dragon is for you
in exchange.
So exquisite!
Can you teach me to make it?
Let me take you to a place first.
Yuchi, where are we going?
We’ll be there soon.
But,
you have to close your eyes first.
Why so mysterious?
You can open your eyes now.
Amazing!
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
Yuchi,
how did you find this place?
Maybe you have been here before,
but you forgot.
No way!
It’s such a beautiful place!
How could I forget it?
♪Bright or dim♪
So many flowers!
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
Yuchi.
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
Why do I feel that
I have really been here before?
♪As if all feelings♪
♪Were for you♪
You remember it?
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
Maybe, it was in my dream.
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
So many butterflies!
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
Yuchi, look!
These butterflies can perceive
human emotions!
Come and play together!
Look.
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
It should be God’s favor
and surprise to you.
Yuchi,
every time when I’m with you,
the world will become so wonderful.
♪Like stars shining for the travelers♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I wanna stay with you♪
Ayu!
Yuchi.
Do you feel better?
I don’t know what’s wrong with me
these days.
Yuchi,
I fainted in such a beautiful place.
Sorry for spoiling the fun.
Have you been dizzy a lot lately?
Not very often.
Maybe I didn’t get enough sleep.
Yuchi, there are only two fireflies left
that you gave me.
It’s OK.
I’ll give you more.
Thank you, Yuchi.
But you have to promise me
to have enough rest.
Don’t worry.
You still have old scars and new wounds.
What is this thing
you are wasting your energy on?
These fireflies have a connection
with me.
As long as Ayu takes them with her,
she can call me
anytime she misses me.
Give me some, too.
Then I can also call you
when I miss you.
You always come without being invited.
Then, do you want to know
a thing about Ayu?
What is it? Go ahead.
If you don’t give me fireflies,
you have to give me other benefits
for it.
What?
I also want to be served with chestnuts.
Are you breaking me tooth?
Say it.
If you don’t say it now,
I will break all your teeth.
Alright.
I’m just here to remind you
that you’d better
keep a distance with Ayu.
Ayu is just an ordinary people.
Now you’re lack of energy.
You’ll automatically absorb the
mortal energy from Ayu.
What will happen?
Human and demon are different.
She will die.
Why was this not the case
when I was with Liuying?
You had enough energy back then.
And, you didn’t stay together for long
before she married Xu Zhiyuan.
Now Ayu always falls in a faint.
It’s because of you.
So,
you’d better leave her
as early as possible.
Qingqing!
Qingqing, they say you’re a bird demon
and you got caught by a demon hunter.
If Qingqing is a demon,
what about Yuchi?
Firefly, go tell Yuchi
that I have something important
to tell him.
Why hasn’t Yuchi come yet?
Is he caught by the hunter as well?
Yuchi,
you must come back safe and sound.
Qingqing has Three-call Spell
of Xue Qianxun.
You don’t need to worry.
Who is speaking?
Yuchi!
Where are you?
Did anything bad happen to you?
Yuchi!
Stop yelling.
-Yuchi…
-Don’t come over.
You’re all right. It’s fine.
Yuchi,
you are…
This is the Fallen-flower Valley
with many butterflies we came last time.
Yes.
Yuchi,
you’re really a demon?
Yes.
Run away now!
It’s dangerous here!
A powerful demon hunter
is finding you everywhere.
People in town said
Qingqing has already been caught.
I’m a demon.
Aren’t you afraid of me?
Who says demons are all bad
and people are all good?
To me, you and Qingqing
are way better than those
who bullied me.
Yuchi,
I saw the little dragon
on your handkerchief…
Are you a dragon demon?
Yes.
Then, fly away now!
Fly to the sky
and then the hunters can’t catch you.
Don’t worry about me and Qingqing.
We’ll all leave here.
Then, can I see…
Her again?
She can’t come to see you.
Neither can I.
Human and demon are different.
Then, you won’t come to see me
even if I free the fireflies, will you?
No, I won’t.
Yuchi.
I’m a demon.
You can’t get close to me.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
Let’s pretend…
♪Memories make me miss you♪
…we’ve never met.
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
That’s good.
Then
you and Qingqing will be safe.
♪It lingers around♪
Yuchi.
I won’t miss you in the future.
Don’t think of me either.
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
Ayu, take care.
Remember to take good care of yourself.
Don’t look back.
Don’t stop Yuchi from leaving.
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
So many butterflies!
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
Don’t look back.
Ruan Ayu.
You can make it.
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
(Xing)
Roast duck! Delicious roast duck!
Have a look!
Delicious roast duck!
Here.
-Roast duck.
-Have a look.
Here you are.
-Thank you!
-My roast duck
is delicious and fresh.
I want to go.
OK, welcome next time.
Flowers!
(Love with Dragon)
-Flowers! -Roast duck!
Have a look!
Miss! Your book!
Delicious roast duck!
(Love with Dragon)
Really?
Have a try?
I’ll buy one.
OK. Let me pack it up for you.
Ayu,
what are you looking at fascinatedly?
(Love with Dragon)
This man looks so handsome.
I don’t like this kind of book.
Really?
He has a nice face.
Roast duck! Delicious roast duck!
Flowers!
Fresh beautiful flowers!
Flowers…
I’m trying hard to forget you,
Yuchi.
But you’re everywhere in my life.
Why is it asymmetric again?
How I wish I have Lord’s hands.
It’s unfair!
He is a man!
Why is he so good at making
peach makeup?
It’d be good if he can help me make up
every day.
Or,
if I can have a lot of headwear
and headbands like Xiahou Xue,
I won’t be so upset about it.
This... looks too plain.
This?
Is it too flashy?
Will she like
this color?
So many!
Headwear!
Headbands!
Are these all for me?
Do you like them?
Yes! I like them!
Wait.
He just
dislikes my meteor mark.
Is it really that ugly?
Thank you, My Lord.
But, I don’t want these.
Why do you refuse my gifts for you?
I just don’t want these.
I’ll go to sleep now.
What’s that face?
If you think my meteor mark is ugly,
you can just say it directly.
Why bother to give me gifts?
Not jewelries and headwear?
What Qingqing wants most
is to get rid of the meteor mark
on her forehead.
But…
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪