♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 16=
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Was I being too mean
just now?
He is the Lord after all
and he also gave me so many headwear
to cover up my mark.
Does it mean he cares about me?
It’s all your fault! You annoying mark.
You made me become as annoying as you.
He
may never talk to me again.
(Lady Divine made timely rain in dream)
(Appoint Lady Divine as concubine)
Is there
really a Lady Divine who can bring rain?
You know what?
That Demon Hunter Wang is really great.
He used Demon Rope and Magical Gourd
to catch the demon Qingqing
at a stroke.
So great!
Well, if Qingqing is a demon,
and Ayu always stays with her,
Ayu may be a demon as well.
Nonsense!
It’s not nonsense!
She is a demon!
Demons appear in our town.
How can we live in peace?
Right?
Yeah, how?
My daughter is not a demon!
If so,
you grew up with her,
then you’re a demon, too!
We are different!
Her birth got her mother killed.
And she got Zhiyong killed as well!
That fire burnt Zhiyong
to ashes,
but Ayu is safe and sound.
What is she if she is not a demon?
-Yeah, she must be a demon.
-Demon girl.
My Ayu is not a demon!
She is…
What is she?
-She is…
-Go ahead!
She is Lady Divine!
The Imperial Notice says that
Lady Divine comes from the Southeast.
Ayu is Lady Divine!
Who is Lady Divine?
Make way! Make way!
Make way! His Excellency is here!
(Order Silence)
Who talked about Lady Divine just now?
He!
He said his daughter is Lady Divine!
Your Excellency,
please let me explain.
I just said it casually.
How dare you talk casually about
the Imperial Notice?
Guards! Arrest him!
-Yes, sir!
-Your Excellency!
Please spare me! Your Excellency!
-Wait!
Ayu is here! Ayu is here.
Father!
Why do you arrest my father?
Who are you?
-I…
-Your Excellency,
she is his daughter.
She pretends to be Lady Divine!
It has nothing to do with her!
I said it myself.
Please just punish me alone.
Take him away!
Wait!
My father is right.
I’m the Lady Divine His Majesty wants.
How could it be?
-That’s ridiculous.
-Yeah.
You are Lady Divine?
Yes.
The Imperial Notice says
the Lady Divine is needed to pray
for rain.
I can bring rain.
How do you plan to do it?
Let my father go first.
OK. Let go of him!
Ayu!
Father, don’t worry.
Your Excellency, please set up an altar.
I’ll pray for rain.
Go set up the altar.
Yes, sir!
Pray for rain?
Ayu brags too much this time!
Although you can use your power
to make some rain as Dragon King,
you can’t
make it rain in such a big Yuchi Town.
I will go to Thunderstorm Terrace
to borrow the Rain Wand.
Borrow?
You will only grab it.
You shall not come in!
I need to draw my magic charms.
It won’t work if I’m bothered.
Then, we will wait for you right here.
Let’s go.
Ayu, I got you in trouble.
I shouldn’t lie!
Look at me! I should get punished!
Father.
All our money is here.
They will only focus on me.
Go rent a carriage and leave later!
Here.
No!
What about you if I leave?
We should leave together!
Father!
No! I should be the one to die first!
I’ll stop them! You leave first!
Father! I haven’t got married.
I won’t die.
I heard the altar
is set up by the river.
Go wait for me at the dock
down the river.
I’ll find a chance to pretend to fall
and meet you soon.
We can go to our uncle.
Have you finished drawing?
Almost!
You have to come!
Father, trust me.
OK.
My Lord! My Lord! My Lord!
What’s wrong?
The Three-call Spell always worked!
Is it…?
No way.
Xue Qianxun! Xue Qianxun!
Xue Qianxun!
Good.
Now you know to call my name directly.
Hurry up!
Go to help Dragon King get
the Rain Wand with me!
Ayu is praying for rain.
She will be in trouble
if it doesn’t rain!
Come on.
You don’t want to help her?
Ridiculous!
If you interfere in human affairs with
immortal power,
you’ll get punished by thunder!
Dragon King is strong enough to
withstand thunder strikes.
What about you?
Only one bolt of thunder
can blow you to ashes!
But…
I can’t do nothing and watch Ayu die!
If you don’t go, I’ll go alone!
You stay out of this matter!
Go back to Luofeng Pavilion with me!
No! I…
Xue Qianxun!
Xue Qianxun! Let me go!
You! You big bully!
(Luofeng Pavilion)
I need to help Ayu!
Xue Qianxun! Xue Qianxun!
(Spell for Rain)
Keep pretending.
I’d like to see how you will cheat us.
Start now.
Your Excellency,
it’s not the right time.
Let’s see what trick you’ll play.
Guys! Watch carefully!
Don’t let this liar escape!
Quiet! It has nothing to do with you.
How long do you have to wait?
Father should have left by now.
I should hold on a little longer.
A burning joss stick.
The duration of a burning joss stick.
That’s a long time.
If the time is not right,
it will fail to rain.
Alright,
I’ll give you the time.
But I also have to remind you
that if your praying fails,
that’s a crime of deceiving the Emperor.
Bring her the joss stick.
Why hasn’t she come yet?
Ayu.
God,
please show mercy
and help my Ayu.
Let me kowtow to you. Please.
Time is up. You should start now.
Wait.
Can you do it or not?
If not,
just kowtow to everyone and confess
your mistake.
But the crime of deceit
is inevitable.
God,
I apologize to you
on behalf of my father and myself.
I shouldn’t brag about
being the Lady Divine.
But Yuchi Town has been dried up
for long.
If this continues, there will be famine.
Please show mercy
and rain a little.
You! You… Don’t come over!
Xuanming, Immortal of Rain,
please lend me the Rain Wand.
No!
I managed to get this job
of making rain from God.
You dragon demon don’t try to grab it!
I don’t want to fight.
I just want to use Rain Wand
to let it rain in Yuchi Town.
I have already made it rain
in the human world as God ordered.
Nonsense!
It didn’t rain in Yuchi Town at all.
I’m not that stupid to believe you.
You guys! Stop him!
Mr. Shen,
it’s already been hours.
There is not even a dark cloud,
let alone a drop of rain.
I can’t wait anymore.
This is a capital crime!
Enough!
Guards! Arrest her!
Yes, sir!
Arrest her!
Arrest this liar!
She is a liar!
Why do you cheat us?
Where is the Rain Wand?
Stop it!
Ziyang! Help me!
Dragon demon, it’s you again!
You disturbed me while
I eliminated Blood Devil last time.
Now you come here
to bully Immortal of Rain?
So what?
You…
Immortal of Rain has taken the order
from God about the rain.
I was also there during the process.
It’s true that there is
a long drought in Yuchi Town.
There hasn’t been
a drop of rain recently.
I have told him just now.
I have received the request from
the Emperor of the human beings
and it rained yesterday.
Unless…
Someone holds up a big umbrella
over Yuchi Town.
Star Halo should appear after the rain.
But there was no rain.
Maybe Yuchi Town is really
sheltered by something.
Sheltered?
We will know if we go and see.
Who is interfering with my rain?
Please wait. I’ll try again.
The result will be the same.
Who set up this huge barrier
to block the rain?
Do you remember
there was a light when Blood Devil died?
That might be his last grievance.
Yuchi Town is the place where he died.
He’s trying to turn this place
into a wasteland
for his burial.
Xuanming,
it’s of no use to try.
Come with me to report to God.
Yes.
Criminal Ruan Ayu
deceived all people and His Majesty.
Now,
sentence her to death
to worship Immortal of Rain.
Demon girl! I finally avenge Zhiyong!
Don’t talk nonsense!
Ruan Ayu,
do you have any last words to say?
Yes.
I have something to say.
Go ahead.
I want to admit my fault.
But it’s not to His Majesty.
I made a mistake
in giving hope to
my neighbors in Yuchi Town
and then letting you down.
Dear neighbors,
I
apologize
to you right here.
Father,
I’m unfilial.
I’ll repay your love and care
in the afterlife.
It smells so good!
Here. Eat it.
Have some more.
I know you.
You are Yuchi. You saved me.
Yuchi,
see you in the afterlife.
Is it finished?
(Order)
Behead her.
Stop wasting your power.
The barrier of devil
seems to obey only the commands
of its owner.
We have to command in the name of
Blood Devil.
How could we know
the name he made himself?
(Chenyu Xiaojun Brave Eternal Master)
Brave Eternal Master.
What are you doing?
(Brave Eternal Master)
Brave Eternal Master’s order!
Break!
It rains! It’s really raining!
Hold the execution!
Lady Divine! Please stand up.
Lady Divine, sorry for my ignorance.
Please forgive me. Please.
It’s OK.
Untie her!
Yes, sir.
It’s raining!
Let go of me!
She is not Lady Divine! She lies!
She is…
Demon girl! She is a demon girl!
Let this crazy woman shut up.
Lady Divine, please have a seat.
Don’t bother.
Liu Yuxiang,
you’ve been calling me jinx for
more than a decade.
Have you ever thought of a day
like this?
Have you ever thought of this
when you asked Baldhead to kidnap me?
Lady Divine, how will you deal with
this crazy woman?
Let me think about it.
Ayu.
Ayu, please show mercy.
You…
Wait. Dear Lady Divine,
please show mercy
and let go of my daughter.
She has been
relying on her identity
as Miss Liu these years
to bully us ordinary people.
If I let her go,
isn’t it encouraging bullying?
Lady Divine, you make sense.
The wicked should be punished
in evil ways.
In my opinion,
we should flog her to death
and parade her body through streets.
Lady Divine, how do you think?
Lady Divine! Please no!
Alright.
During the next 16 days,
you can parade through the streets
wearing this turtle makeup.
Liu Yuxiang,
if you have a habit of teasing
and bullying others,
you should also experience being
teased and bullied.
I hope you will be able to change
after you feel
other people’s strange eyes
and be able to show kindness
and compassion to others.
Take her away.
-Yes, sir.
Lady Divine, you’re so kind.
That really makes me admire.
Mr. Shen, I’m flattered.
It’s getting dark.
My father is still waiting for me.
I’m going home now.
Lady Divine,
don’t worry, His Majesty
has made arrangements.
Your father has now entered the Palace
to be well served.
Then, thank His Majesty.
And, thank you, Mr. Shen.
It’s my pleasure.
Lady Divine, when will you
enter the Palace?
I should go there, too?
Thanks.
You’re the Dragon King.
But you always hurt yourself
for an ordinary girl.
Is this love
really worth your sacrifice?
My little suffering
can get her life happiness.
It’s worth it.
Looks like you don’t know the truth.
His Majesty ordered
(Imperial Notice)
that if the Lady Divine is found,
she will be awarded with silks,
gold, silver and jewelries,
and also becomes concubine.
Concubine?
That’s right.
In my opinion, we can’t let
His Majesty wait.
How about entering the Palace now?
Congratulations to Lady Divine!
But now, she is marrying the Emperor.
You also want that?
That’s the best result.
Ayu was affected by me before
and got her spirit hurt.
Being the concubine
can make her enjoy the high position
and great wealth.
Also, the noble spirit can cure her.
She could live safe and sound
and pass away peacefully.
That’s what I want her to be like.
That is to say,
deep love
sometimes is sweet
and sometimes is painful.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
I’m so anxious.
Lord just locked me up here.
I don’t know how they are doing now.
You’re back! How is Ayu now?
How did you get hurt like this?
It’s no big deal.
I just need to rest for several days.
Go to Immortal of Fate for medicine.
Yes.
How can I go with this?
You locked Qingqing on the chair?
It’s for her own good.
I’ll find a chance to try
the equal treatment you said last time.
What happened?
Look at you! Your old wounds
haven’t been healed
and now you got new wounds!
Come with me.
Let me heal you.
I went to ask for medicine.
But Immortal of Fate
asked to come to have a look.
In front of our beloved,
we are not the Dragon King or Lord.
You should put these thoughts aside
and simply get along with her
equally in the way a man
treats a woman.
What’s wrong?
Why do you look at me like that?
I won’t forgive you
for locking me on the chair
even if you look at me like this.
If you really mind it,
you can also lock me up.
Don’t bother.
I know you did that for my own good.
But you could tell me gently.
OK.
Do you want some tea?
You want tea? Let me help you.
No need.
Sit.
Over there.
Chat with me.
Have some tea.
What trick is it this time?
Drink it.
OK.
Qing…
Sorry! My Lord!
My bad.
It’s fine.
Just sit there.
Let’s continue our chat.
I… I…
I want to use the toilet
because of the tea.
OK.
My Lord, I’m going now.
Does this really work?
I feel my heart beat fast.
But,
she seems to be avoiding me.
Why do Lord’s eyes
make my heart beat so fast?
What? Say it again.
I say
I want Qingqing to accompany Ayu
in the Palace.
I’m the one she should accompany,
not your Ayu!
I mean
I managed to make Qingqing
sit down, chat
and have tea with me now.
But now you want her
to enter the Palace.
Then we can’t…
Don’t act like
you can’t see each other again.
Qingqing’s power has been
sealed for long.
Now she is just like an ordinary person.
She can freely enter
and leave the Palace.
You are the Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
Heavenly Generals guarding the Palace
will never stop you.
You can see each other anytime you want.
But, it’s not same with me.
If I want to see Ayu now,
I have to have a tough fight
with the Generals.
I can’t see her as I wish.
That’s why I’m making this request.
I want Qingqing to take care of Ayu
in the Palace.
In this way, I can keep in touch
with her.
Alright.
I accept it.
Go and see her
before she enters the Palace.
You mean I can go to see Ayu?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪