♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage
and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away all loneliness♪
=Miss Crow with Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 17=
Hello?
Thank God.
You finally picked up.
We got so worried
when we couldn't reach you.
Everyone is looking for you.
I left early.
That's okay.
As long as you're okay.
By the way, I have some things to deal with.
I won't be going to the office for a while.
Help me take care of things.
Chuan,
you don't sound okay.
How about I get Jiang Xiao Ning
to keep you company?
Or else I'll worry.
No need,
I'm fine.
If something happens,
I'll call you.
Okay then.
Wang Kai,
why would Boss skip work for no reason?
This is the first time.
He had even never
been late before.
You don't get it.
If you don't come to work, it's called
skipping work.
If Boss doesn't come to work,
that's just called...
just called not coming to work.
I'm just curious.
I'll ask around for you.
Xiao Ning,
you're on good terms with Mr. Gu.
Do you know why he didn't come?
No, I don't.
She doesn't know.
(Is it because of me?)
(Did he not come to work because)
(he didn't want to see me?)
Jiang Xiao Ning,
come over here and take notes.
Okay.
Tell me your thoughts.
She wants to do the exhibition
on the top floor
mainly because of the night scenery.
So I intend to turn the east-facing side
into a one-way mirror completely.
That way the inside is see-through
and the exterior is glass.
Yep.
This way, we can ensure privacy
and...
Jiang Xiao Ning,
did you take down
what we just discussed?
I...
Where was I just now?
Oh yes, about the direction.
Sorry,
Sister Wen Wen is calling me.
Can I take the call?
Of course.
Venture capitalist is calling,
of course you need to pick up.
Hurry up, don't make her wait.
Take the call, it's okay.
Hello, Sister Wen Wen.
Hello, Xiao Ning, are you busy?
Sorry to disturb you.
I have something to talk to you about.
How about we have lunch together
during your lunch break?
My treat.
Sure.
I'll bring you
the design proposal then.
Okay.
I'll send you the address in a bit.
See you at noon.
Chen Wen Wen asked you out?
For a meal.
Just you alone?
Without Chen Dong?
I want to eat with a pretty girl too,
but she didn't ask for me.
I'm not too sure either.
But don't worry,
I can explain our proposal
to her thoroughly.
Let's continue.
Okay.
So it's all about
the night scenery.
It's super beautiful.
It sets a certain kind of mood.
Sorry,
I got caught up
sorting out some files.
It's okay.
You'll improve very quickly
working at Gu Chuan's studio.
And I'm very confident about
leaving this project to you.
I can't compare
with you guys.
I'm sometimes still not used to
interacting, getting to know,
and working with you guys.
You have your own strengths.
You're warm and cheerful,
persistent and hardworking.
Everyone can see that.
I like you a lot.
I think you're very sincere
and cute.
From the first time I saw you,
I thought you were really pretty.
After spending time with you,
I think you're really outstanding.
Not arrogant
and very empathetic.
I'm a girl and I like you.
But if I were a boy,
I would definitely like
a girl like you too.
You want to talk about Gu Chuan, right?
You don't need to have your guard up against me.
I'm not your enemy.
Su Man Lin told you, right?
I don't want to comment
on people I don't know,
but I'm not sure why
she told you about something
that happened so long ago.
I'm Gu Chuan's ex-girlfriend.
I don't deny that.
But when I first met you,
I really didn't know about
your relationship with him.
I also never expected that
it would cause you trouble.
Sister Wen Wen,
you didn't cause any trouble.
It's my problem.
I can feel
your sincerity towards him.
I can't really get involved with the two of you,
but if you were affected
by me,
I hope to clear things up with you.
No, I'm not.
Should I show you the blueprint now
or later?
Let's go to the site later.
You can explain it to me while we're there.
It's easier to understand this way.
My imagination isn't great.
Maybe that's why I can
only do photography
and not design.
Okay.
Hello, your food.
Thank you.
Let's talk while eating.
See if the food here
suits your appetite.
Okay.
I initially didn't want to
take on your case.
Is it because of who I am?
I don't have animosity towards you.
I'm just slightly afraid to see you.
Simply put,
I'm running away.
I don't deny that I once loved him.
Actually, after so many years,
I still admire
and respect him.
I hope we can all find
our own happiness.
This is me being open with you.
I did once regret
leaving him,
leaving this city,
during his darkest days.
But now that I think about it,
maybe this was all meant to be.
We cannot accept
each other as we are right now,
do you know what I mean?
How's your relationship with your ex-boyfriend?
I don't have an ex-boyfriend.
I haven't dated anyone yet.
Then let me share a secret
with you.
Don't fall in love with a man
because he loves you.
What does that mean?
If a man, by nature, is
cold,
emotionless, and hot-tempered,
or has some flaws which
you cannot accept,
but he temporarily disguises them
because of you,
don't ever be with him.
If there's another guy,
whom you feel even if you're not
in a relationship with,
or if you were dating
and you went your separate ways,
but you still admire him,
respect him,
and don't regret loving him,
then that is a relationship
worth having.
Sister Wen Wen, you put it so well.
I almost fell for you.
I hope Gu Chuan
can find his happiness.
When I was in my 20s,
I didn't fight for my love.
It took me a while to
get over that.
But I don't have any regrets.
I hope you won't miss it.
Fight for what you want.
You're already doing great.
No one can stop you.
Hello, Lawyer Huang,
are you busy?
Yes, I'm sorting out the documents
you gave me previously.
I want to set up a fund.
For yourself?
There are a lot of
outstanding university students
who are unable to attend university
for various reasons.
I want to set up a fund
to help these underprivileged students
finish their studies.
Of course,
I know our country is doing a lot
on this front,
which is why I want to set up this fund
for the architectural industry.
Okay, I'll look into it for you.
Also...
my wills.
I've discussed this matter with you
every single time.
I already know that
you won't change your mind.
I'll follow your instructions.
I want to make some changes
to my wills.
You don't need to notarize it for now.
Let me think about it.
I'll give you a call
once I've thought about it.
Sure, contact me anytime.
Bye-bye.
Actually,
I've already confessed to Boss.
And?
And then he asked me to stop talking.
This is tricky.
It doesn't sound like him...
but it also sounds like something he would do.
But I think
you need to trust him.
Believe that the man you love
is someone who is mature.
He has his considerations.
When the time is right,
he will share his thoughts
with you.
Thank you, Sister Wen Wen.
Really.
I feel really lucky to have met you.
Well then,
cheers!
Keep pushing.
Absolutely.
Xiao Ning?
Xiao Ning,
we're here.
Sorry, Sister Wen Wen.
I didn't sleep well last night.
I'm too tired.
How could I fall asleep
while going to the site with a client?
I'm sorry.
That's so unprofessional of me.
It's okay.
It shows that
you really trust me.
For sure.
Let's go.
Okay.
This place
is going to be renovated too right?
Yes, it will be renovated.
I heard Sister Man Lin and Brother Dong
talking about it at the office.
Okay.
Be careful.
We're here.
I want to shoot
the night scenery here tonight
to give the designers a reference.
Their design
incorporates the night scenery here.
I think it's great.
Sure.
Need me to help you take pictures?
It's okay,
Even having you press the shutter
would cost a lot.
It's so high up.
I feel a little scared standing up here.
Are you scared of heights?
Not really.
Compared to heights, darkness is even scarier.
It's lit at night.
Okay.
Hello?
What happened?
Wait for me.
I'll head over to pick you up.
My cellphone is running out of battery.
Send me your location,
so I can tell the driver.
It's going to rain soon.
Wait for me.
Okay.
Xiao Ning,
my husband's car
got submerged under the bridge.
I have to go pick him up.
I'll leave the keys at the door.
Remember to lock the door
when you leave.
Sure, don't worry.
I'll lock the door.
Be careful.
Okay.
No way.
Such bad luck?
Hello,
the number you've just dialed is switched off.
Sister Wen Wen.
Is anyone there?
Is… is anyone there?
Pick up the phone, pick up the phone.
Hello?
Boss,
can you come over to open the door for me?
I didn't want to bother you initially,
but I really couldn't find
anyone else.
What's going on?
Where are you?
An Tai Building.
I came here with Sister Wen Wen.
She left first because she had something to do.
I… I'm stuck on the roof.
I can't get out.
You're on the rooftop while it's raining?
That's too dangerous.
Find a shelter and wait for me.
Wait for me.
Okay, I'll wait for you.
Hello,
the number you've just dialed is switched off.
The number you've just dialed is switched off.
(An Tai Building)
Hello, Sir. How may I help you?
Hello.
My friend is stuck on the roof.
Please go up and take a look immediately.
Are you sure it's this building?
I'm sure.
Follow me.
Where's the key?
It was at the security office.
But the roof was rented out,
it should be with the tenant.
Isn't there a spare?
That's at the headquarters.
But it's too far from here.
We can't deliver it here.
Hurry, call the police now.
We've already called the police.
They should be here soon.
We don't have enough time.
Could you please
lock the elevator on the first floor
and make sure it stays there?
Don't let anyone touch the elevator.
Sir, you're...
Every elevator
has a maintenance floor.
I can enter from the elevator shaft
and exit from the maintenance floor.
I can reach the rooftop
this way.
That's too dangerous, Sir.
If anything were to happen to you,
I can't take the responsibility.
If something were to happen
to the person on the roof,
will you take the responsibility then?
That's not what I meant.
What I meant was
the firemen are coming soon.
I can't wait any longer.
I'm sorry.
I'm an architectural designer,
so I'm very familiar with
the whole structure of this building.
As long as you keep a lookout for the elevator,
nothing
will happen to me.
The most important thing right now
is to save that person.
That girl
is very important to me.
Please.
Okay, Sir.
Be careful.
I'll keep a lookout for the elevator.
Thank you.
Jiang Xiao Ning!
Boss!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
The door is locked.
Get out of the way.
No, Boss.
You'll hurt yourself.
Stay away.
Now.
No.
Are you okay?
Boss.
I knew you'd come.
Jiang Xiao Ning!
This bag is for Jiang Xiao Ning.
Ask her to drink one
when she wakes up.
Now,
you know how important it is for me to stay with you.
Thanks.
Knock it off.
How is she?
It's all my fault.
She got scared and got an electric shock.
You saved her, okay?
If you weren't there,
the thunderbolt
might have struck her directly.
Strangely enough,
Jiang Xiao Ning always gets involved in accidents
when there is a thunderstorm.
You two
make quite a match.
I'm just kidding.
Are you thinking about
something weird again?
What weird things can I think about?
Once you're fully charged,
go back and reset.
I'll take care of her.
I want to stay with her.
Your body
won't be able to go on like this.
It's okay.
I know what I'm doing.
What are you doing?
Do you know what people need
the most when they catch a cold?
What?
Cold medicine.
Do you know
what you need the most right now?
Cold medicine?
You need me.
You stay with her.
I stay with you then.
I owe it to you.
(*in a sarcastic way)
Boss.
You're awake.
Boss, are you okay?
I'm okay.
Don't move.
You just reduced your fever.
The doctor said you need to rest.
I'm fine.
I told you not to move.
Why don't you listen to me?
Boss.
I just want to get up to drink some water.
I'll get it for you.
Have I been paralyzed
by the electric shock?
Boss.
Did you stay with me this entire time?
How do you feel now?
Does it hurt?
No.
I'm just a little weak.
You should rest for a couple more days.
Boss.
Do you have
superpowers?
What do you mean?
People around you will get hit
by thunderbolts when there is a thunderstorm.
Last time, He Sheng got hit too.
Maybe, I'm a human lightning conductor.
My body produces a greater amount of power.
Maybe
I swear too much?
You flatter more than
you swear.
♪His hair was for you♪
Thank you, Boss.
♪But there was nothing to do♪
♪You will throw away all your worries♪
(I'm at the hospital.)
(Which room is Xiao Ning in?)
You should rest a bit.
I'm going to get you some food.
Thanks, Boss.
You don't think
I intentionally
locked her up on the rooftop, do you?
I know you.
You wouldn't do anything like that.
I'm responsible though.
I shouldn't have left her
there by herself.
I was answering a call.
I don't remember too much detail.
But I'm certain
I didn't lock the door.
I also left the key
at the door.
It's okay.
Don't blame yourself.
Oh,
did you mention what happened to my heart
to her
when you were eating together?
No.
You should
tell her about
these things yourself.
Thank you.
You like her.
Right?
Right.
Then why did you turn her down?
She's a very simple girl.
You'll hurt her.
Don't say I'm overstepping.
I just want you to be happy.
But you
look
really terrible.
You isolate yourself by
running away from your true feelings
and hurting others.
Maybe I'm wrong.
But you look exactly the same
as you were ten years ago.
You want to leave this world.
Gu Chuan.
Don't let Jiang Xiao Ning
become a second me.
You need her.
You need this relationship.
You should trust her.
Trust that she'll stay with you
no matter what happens.
It has been ten years.
Although I'm still alive,
I'm just staying alive.
It's not that I want it this way.
It's because I just can't
live like a normal person.
I gave up all my hobbies
and even you
for this mechanical heart.
To live with it,
I can't laugh out loud when I'm happy.
I can't drink when I'm upset.
When I'm angry,
I can't touch anyone
or anything.
I've been controlling
my emotions all this time.
However,
it still
reminds me all the time that
I don't have the ability to love anyone.
Now,
this mechanical heart
is performing worse and worse.
The pain it brings me
makes me feel that
every day is so long.
I certainly had thought of
ending it.
What about Jiang Xiao Ning?
What about you two?
Jing Xiao Ning.
She is a real accident.
She interrupted all my plans.
The old me never expected
the next day
to come.
Ever since she came into my life,
I started to look forward to
going to work.
I look forward to seeing her.
I look forward to listening to her nonsense.
I look forward to seeing her following me around
and flattering me every day.
What will you do?
I'm
in a dilemma.
Ten years ago,
you insisted
on pushing me away.
Ten years later,
you want to do the same
to another girl?
(Passenger Elevator)
(Patient Zone No.1)
Yan Yan.
You're here.
Why are you here?
They both got hurt last night.
I'm worried.
I was going to call you,
but I was afraid you would worry.
The doctor said
they're both fine.
Then you should have called
me last night.
If you were worried,
we should be here together.
I didn't stay up all night for nothing.
So Gu Chuan climbed from the elevator shaft and
crashed through the glass door to save you?
It was super scary.
I'll still get scared even by thinking about it.
If anything happens to him,
I don't want to live either.
Stop it. What are you talking about?
You're all good now.
What he has done
has proved that
you're important to him.
This is different from
what you had told me before.
He still turned me down.
This is odd.
First of all,
he's not a playboy.
My playboy radar
didn't go off.
Also,
he hasn't been in contact
with other girls, right?
If he sees you as a backup,
he wouldn't have risked his life to save you.
Then why did he turn me down?
Maybe he's inexperienced?
He doesn't look that way.
He is the owner of a big company after all.
I think you should be more proactive.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
You've already done something?
Right?
No, don't just make a wild guess.
You lied.
I know every single
thought of yours.
Don't think you can hide things from me.
Confess right now.
Did you kiss him?
Hug him?
Or you guys have already...
No.
But this time
I learned one thing.
Just like what you
and Sister Wen Wen had said.
First,
he is someone worth loving.
So I need to work hard
to shorten the distance between us.
Even if nothing happens in the end,
that would be because I'm not the right fit,
or I'm not good enough.
It would have nothing to do with him.
But if I give up now,
I'll regret it for sure.
So I plan to
go with the flow
and deal with things as they happen.
Look at you.
Spewing out words of wisdom.
Looks like love
does make people grow.
What if he is a playboy?
Didn't you say your playboy radar didn't go off?
I... I...
I'm not omnipotent.
How can I be a hundred percent accurate?
Then you were wrong about Mr. Xu?
I wasn't wrong about him.
Let me tell you something.
Am I interrupting?
No.
Oh, right.
I have some work stuff to deal with.
I'm leaving Xiao Ning to you.
Do you want to eat something?
We will do one more examination.
If nothing is wrong, you can go home.
Thank you, Boss.
Going home?
I'll drive you home.
No, thanks.
Did you drive?
No.
If you want to call a cab,
you'd better go across the street.
It's hard to park in front of the hospital.
Bye-bye.
It's really hard to ask you out.
Why are you here?
Recently, I've been
out of luck.
Come with me.
Director Xu
just gave you money not long ago.
And his son almost found out about it.
My brother went to prison
for you guys.
He ought to
give me money.
Don't waste my time.
I'll leave
once you give me money.
It won't look good
if other people see us.
What now?
You don't want to give me money?
Alright.
I'll ask Director Xu.
Come back.
You cannot come here
anymore.
Do you hear me?
Okay.
I'll follow your orders.
Follow your orders.
Chen Ao.
If I see you here again,
things won't end well for you.
Get in.
Shouldn't I drive?
I'll drive today.
Boss.
Although I got scared a little bit,
I should still
do my job.
Just do as I say.
I'll drive today.
Get in.
Come on.
Take it easy.
Sit still.
(Chuan,)
(do you remember me telling you)
(that someone attacked me?)
(I was able to take a photo of that person today.)
(712 vicious hit-and-run offender Chen Yun
being sentenced today)
Hello, Lawyer Huang.
Please do me another favor.
What is it?
Look into a person for me.
Find out as much detail as possible.
This person
is the truck driver
who hit me
back then.
Didn't he die
in prison?
My friend took a photo of him.
What?
No way.
I'm surprised as well.
I'll send you the photo now.
Okay.
I'll look into him as soon as possible.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪