♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow
that fills up the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing,
please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth,
flying towards fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness
that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and
let's count down to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but to be
a little bit fragile♪
a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 18=
(Defendant Chen Yun)
(Chen Yun to be sentenced today for Hit-and-run)
(violated the Provisions of Road Transport)
(and fled the scene afterward.)
(Chen Yun to be sentenced today for Hit-and-run)
(His action resulted in two people dead)
(and one critically injured.)
(He shall be charged for his action,)
(and because the consequences are severe,)
(he shall be punished according to law.)
(The court)
(will sentence according
to Criminal Code of the PRC,)
(Section 133.)
(His sentence is as follow,)
(Chen Yun is guilty of hit-and-run.)
(He will be sentenced to ten years in prison.)
Hello.
Where is
the Chairman's office?
On the 45th floor.
Take the elevator,
there will be an escort waiting.
Hello.
Zhao Yan.
It's one floor up, right?
Thank you.
(Reindeer Group)
Not bad.
It looks natural.
Without checking the original account,
nothing is suspicious.
Director Xu.
I think
we will be in serious trouble
if our business partner
finds out about this.
Working for me,
you have nothing to worry about.
Great undertakings
requires unwavering will,
a great opportunity,
and strong endurance.
In my eyes,
anything that hasn't happened
is not a fact.
Is that clear?
Yes.
What conspiracy
are you two brewing this time?
Elder brother.
What brings you here?
You've barely come
after we relocated here.
You pay no attention to our family business
but waste your time
on your puny little
designing studios.
What's the point?
Whose family business?
Mine or yours?
Who knows you will
give the whole business
to me or your godson.
Elder brother.
You two carry on.
I should get going.
Thank you
for your contribution to this family.
You're an adult.
Stop talking
like a jealous brat.
So
what brings you here?
This person.
Do you know him?
No.
I told you,
this was the man who attacked me.
Are you sure?
Absolutely.
Alright.
If you're sure,
I'll send my men to investigate it.
Is that all?
My mother asked me to tell you
she is coming back next month.
She wants to know
your schedules
and see whether you need her
to attend some social occasions
to put up an act or not.
If not,
she will go straight to Hainan
for a vacation.
How should
I know about the future?
She can go
wherever she wants for a holiday.
She asked you to deliver one message in person?
She could've
just called.
She said she didn't want to talk to you.
She wouldn't let me call you either
insisted that I must come in person.
I think
she wants you to come here
as often as you can.
Your mother is...
Even now,
all her little wit
is spent on you and the company.
Silly.
I've brought you the message.
So long.
Why was he
at the company?
He gambled and lost again
so he came asking for money.
But I sent him away.
Ran Ran took a photo
of you being with him.
Don't be so sloppy next time.
At this rate,
we'll run into trouble.
Figure something out.
Understood
Well?
Am I not efficient?
The person in the picture you sent me
is called Chen Ao.
The driver who crashed
your car
was his twin brother.
The twins
were both involved in robbery and burglary.
The elder brother Chen Yun
ran away after he hit
your car.
But he was arrested soon.
He died from illness
in prison soon afterward.
This means that Chen Ao
has nothing to do with my accident.
It seems so.
I still need to collect
more evidence.
This guy Chen Ao
may not be involved in my accident,
but I can't let him
harm Xu Cheng Ran again.
Mr. Huang,
do you have Chen Ao's record?
(Verdict of Chen Ao from Court of First Instance)
His record, address,
and even his current lifestyle
(Verdict of Chen Ao from Court of First Instance)
are all here.
No one else must know.
Understood.
Well then.
I should get going if there's nothing else.
By the way, Mr. Huang,
how is the progress with the foundation?
There are some procedures
to follow.
Be patient.
I'll keep you posted.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Boss, why are you here?
I'm taking care of a patient today.
Did you drove here
to pick me up?
I'm feeling
much better already.
I can drive.
Are you sure?
Do you need another day off?
That's not necessary.
I'm lively and full of spirit.
Do I look like a patient to you?
Not to mention
you took a great risk for me.
The more I think about it,
the more I blame myself.
I barely slept last night.
Very well.
Get on the car.
Did you have your breakfast?
Let's go get some drink.
Did I hear it right?
You told me
a pleasant drink
brings a good mood.
Let's go.
Your fruit tea.
I must apologize.
The network is broken down.
We can't scan your code.
Could you please pay in cash?
Cash?
I have some.
There you go.
♪Like feeling the stars♪
Sorry.
I'll have to give you coins for the change.
♪Believe that good things will happen
even without luck♪
I like coins.
Thank you.
♪So empty♪
Let's go.
Thank you.
Have a nice day.
♪So empty♪
♪Their feelings♪
♪One, two, three, count with me♪
♪If youth is precious, then cheers♪
♪Those blazing dreams, follow my command♪
♪Four, five, six♪
♪Chase recklessly, long live the young♪
I want to buy something from you.
Such as?
Your smile for today.
♪Another written page on the diary♪
Deal.
♪The brilliant memory♪
What is it this time?
Your smile for tomorrow.
Deal.
The day after tomorrow.
♪Colorful rays of light♪
♪I can see everything♪
Your future smiles!
Yes! You should smile more!
I still have some coins.
You should smile more often,
enough with a long face.
See?
I carry all these coins
only to purchase your smile.
♪Chase recklessly, long live the young♪
♪You are the most perfect
when full of vitality♪
Xiao Ning, morning.
Good morning.
Xiao Ning.
You heard you were ill yesterday.
Why were you and Mr. Gu
both absent yesterday?
I...
It's nothing.
Don't worry. I'm alive and kicking.
Good morning, Sister Man Lin.
Are you sure you don't need more rest?
It's OK. I'm feeling very well.
OK.
I'll leave these to you.
(Chen Wen Wen)
(Xiao Ning,)
(I'm sorry for the other day.)
(Chen Wen Wen)
(Could we talk?)
(I'm at the coffee shop downstairs.)
Mr. Gu.
I need your signature on this.
OK.
You're in a good mood today.
Someone actually
bought my smile.
Bought...
your smile?
Sister Wen Wen.
I've explained
what happened that day to Gu Chuan.
But all and all,
I caused everything.
I must apologize to you again.
It's fine, Sister Wen Wen.
It wasn't your fault.
It was merely my bad luck.
A show of goodwill from me.
Never mind.
I said you don't have to apologize.
There's no need to send me a gift.
It's not exactly a gift.
Consider it
a souvenir.
A souvenir?
This album contains
some photos Gu Chuan
took for National Geographic
ten years ago.
There are also
some photos from his younger days.
I don't think I should
keep them.
I think
you should have it.
(July 21st 2008, Cuba)
(January 20th 2009, Spain)
He took all these photos?
I hope you can
know more about his past.
I...
Do I have the right?
Trust me,
no one is more qualified than you are.
I'm leaving
for Australia tomorrow.
Many animals there are endangered
because of the wildfire.
I want to be there
to capture their images.
It might not take long,
but maybe I'll take quite a while.
Why are you leaving so suddenly?
What about the film festival?
Are you giving up on that?
I'm not giving up.
When I'm back,
you still need to handle the design for me.
The best thing that has happened to me
since I came back
was meeting you.
Thanks to you,
I get to know Gu Chuan again.
So...
Jiang Xiao Ning,
take care of him.
Sister Wen Wen,
are you leaving
because of me?
Don't think so highly of yourself.
It was too sudden,
so I overthink a little.
Gu Chuan
is more of a
stubborn person.
Once he makes a decision,
no one can change his mind.
But I believe
you're the only one that can change him.
You two have something in common.
You both have a passionate heart.
I do hope
you can be happy together.
If you don't miss the chance,
you won't have any regret.
I've already found my happiness.
Don't forget to work on yours.
Thank you, Sister Wen Wen.
Thank you.
Enjoy your food.
We only ordered one can of wine.
Please...
Never mind.
It's not that strong.
I can handle it.
Don't drink too much.
Leave the rest to me.
OK.
Boss.
I thought you never liked having late-night meals.
I feel hungry at night lately.
The bill is on me to return your favor.
Eat as much as you want.
How generous of you.
The food here is incredible.
When I was working part-time,
the happiest thing for me
was to eat as I could here
on my payday.
The lady here is a great cook.
Her cooking is on par
with Michelin-starred restaurant.
I've never
been to one anyway.
But this restaurant
is Michelin-starred to me.
I'll give it three stars.
No.
Five stars!
They don't give out so many stars.
You have a point.
Let me ask you something.
Are you always
so optimistic?
I control my mind with my will.
Every day when I wake up,
I brush my teeth with positivity;
I finish my meals with positivity;
I work with positivity;
I even take showers with positivity.
I stack positivity endlessly.
This practice will surely
make you happy every day of your life.
What about when you're upset?
Do you force yourself to smile?
Not really.
Maybe I've got used to it.
I've always been
very unlucky.
I have had
many unpleasant memories.
After going through so much,
I somehow coped with it.
Just as my aunt said,
"Every day is a new day."
"There is no way for us
to turn back time."
When I think about it,
I feel much better.
Having some wine here
makes my life even more enjoyable.
Cheers.
♪Happy birthday to you♪
Honey,
today is your birthday.
Stand up, make a wish.
Make a wish.
Great!
Happy Birthday!
Great.
Your birthday is around the corner.
How do you know?
I saw your ID card
when I got you the boarding pass.
I see.
It's been a long time
since I last celebrated my birthday.
Why?
It's just a date,
another usual day.
It's not different
from other days.
What matters the most
is to live happily
every day.
Do you agree?
You're right.
Well,
I must try the food you treat me to.
(Are you home yet?)
(Wife)
Sir,
you have a phone call.
Sorry, sir.
(Missed call from Wife)
Did it annoy you?
It was my wife.
I'll turn off the phone.
It's all right.
Could it be
an emergency at home?
Perhaps, you should call her back first.
It's nothing serious.
Every night when she is going to bed,
she will call me.
She's been doing that for seven years.
I've got used to it.
You and your wife
are very close.
I think so.
People always joke about the "seven-year itch",
but I think
we are closer
than we ever were.
You know,
she is five years older than me.
I've never felt
there's actually an age difference between us.
Sometimes,
she would get all clingy
like a little girl.
Isn't that interesting?
Is that so?
It's just my opinion.
I think that
to maintain
a healthy relationship,
men should learn
how to give.
We must learn
to understand our partners.
If our girl
is interested
in anything,
we should try our best
to present it to her
and let her know we care
and that we're willing to give.
That's how we maintain
a healthy relationship.
But surely there are times
that we quarrel a little,
but I do my best
to cheer her up.
When we were
still dating,
we fought sometimes.
My solution
back then was to
give her a kiss and try to cheer her up,
or maybe give her a hug.
Do you know
what the best solution is
nowadays?
Clear out her shopping cart.
(I'm home.)
(Boss.)
(You paid behind my back again.)
(So I still owe you)
(a treat.)
(OK.)
Sir.
You can pull over for a while
and answer the call from your wife.
Don't worry.
I don't want to take up your time.
It's fine.
Answer the call first.
OK.
Thank you.
I'll pull over.
(You have one new message.)
(Ice-cream also wants Jiang Xiao Ning)
(to spend her every waking moment)
(happily.)
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Why are you
staying up so late?
Did you take a shower?
I'll go take a shower now.
Such a mess!
Let me clean it for you.
Don't put the scissors on your bed!
Brother.
Sister-in-law.
Xiao Ning is all grown up now.
She's become very sensible.
Don't you worry.
She is doing well.
But this young lady
misses you so.
Is she here?
Your hair is a mess.
Iced Americano. Thanks.
Darling.
Darling?
Take another bite.
No.
I'll get fat
and you wouldn't like me anymore.
No way.
No matter how you've become,
you're the most beautiful lady to me.
Good girl.
Delicious.
Thanks.
Naughty!
You and your fancy words!
You're such a nice guy,
not to mention you're rich and handsome.
How can I ever leave you?
If any woman is foolish enough
to ditch you,
she must be blind as a bat!
You're correct.
But not every woman
is as brilliant as you.
Someone simply doesn't know
how to cherish my love.
Is this fun, Xu Cheng Ran?
I'm dating, of course it's fun.
Sorry, you wouldn't understand.
I don't care if you're dating.
But mind your manner.
Keep it down.
You're repelling the other customers here.
Who's the repulsive one here?
Ran Ran!
Some single lady
is jealous of our love.
Let's go
somewhere else.
We...
should stay.
We don't have to hide from her.
We'll stay.
Drop the act.
Miss, do you study performance art?
We're not acting.
Darling, give me a kiss.
Muah!
That's all?
Fine.
Ran Ran.
How dare you kiss my boyfriend?
You study performance art, right?
That was a demonstration.
Carry on.
Fine! We'll carry...
on.
Let's save it for another day.
That's all for now.
I don't...
I don't want her to hurt you.
I'm not afraid of it.
I can handle
this woman.
Go on.
I'll leave you be then.
Be cautious
when you're out there.
Got it.
Bye.
I wasn't acting!
Put on a play if you want,
but don't drag the girl into it.
Who said we were acting?
Do you take me as a fool?
Even a little kid could tell.
A little kid can't have a date.
Hello.
The Chairman passed out.
He's in the hospital.
Come here now!
The hospital?
OK, I'll be right there.
What is it?
My father passed out.
He's in the hospital.
I can drive you there.
Thanks.
How is my father?
He pulled through.
He's having a rest.
What happened?
It was in a project negotiation.
We agreed he wouldn't be drinking.
But Mr. Xu
drank too much.
Then he passed out on the table.
What were you doing?
Why didn't you stop him?
I tried
but I couldn't.
You couldn't?
Didn't you know
what your job was?
Didn't you know he couldn't take it
with his health conditions?
Get lost!
We're in a hospital, calm down.
Drink!
Keep on drinking!
You were always lecturing me
but you can't even
look after yourself.
If you fail again,
hand in your resignation.
So Director Xu is your father.
Why didn't you tell me?
This isn't
something to be proud of.
You obviously care about him.
Why didn't you stay
to keep him company just now?
Maybe you should just
move back to your home.
Who cares about the old man?
I don't care what becomes of him.
You've shown
all your love back there.
What did I do?
You're frustrated when you care!
I'm not.
Whatever.
Trust me,
that is a hospital.
Mind your manner
when you're there.
Agitation can be bad
for patients.
Even if he wasn't a patient,
it wasn't right
to talk to him that way.
Fine.
I got it.
He will be fine.
Boss.
Sister Qi Hong needs your signature.
I need to answer the call.
Hello, Aunty.
Xiao Ning.
Grandma...
Grandma is missing!
She went missing again!
I've searched everywhere for her!
Aunty.
Calm down.
I'll be right back.
Wait for me.
Don't worry.
We will find your grandmother.
Chuan.
Xiao Ning's grandmother went missing.
Help us look for her.
OK.
I'm with Zhao Yan.
We'll go together.
What's wrong?
Xiao Ning's grandmother went missing.
Let's go there and help.
Hello.
Have you seen an old lady this tall?
Grandma!
I'll look over there.
How was it?
We've contacted the police station.
They will inform us
if there is any update.
Thanks.
Where could she be?
She doesn't have strong legs.
Right?
Well...
She couldn't
have gone too far.
Right?
Don't worry, Aunty.
Don't worry.
But
the old lady is out there all alone.
What if something bad
happens to her?
Don't worry.
Take a rest.
Thank you.
What is this?
Your parents' photo is gone.
I put it in this frame, didn't I?
When I was making lunch,
someone delivered us some daisies
and placed them here.
That's gone too.
Grandma is at the cemetery.
She must be at the cemetery.
Let's look for her there.
Someone must stay here.
What if she comes back?
I'll stay with Aunty.
No.
I must go.
I must find her.
Don't worry.
Leave it to me.
Are you sure?
OK.
I'll keep you company.
Well,
Xu Cheng Ran
can check with the police station again.
Please.
Go on.
Aunty, I'll go with Xiao Ning.
Are you sure?
We can handle it.
Gu Chuan, take care of her.
Sure.
Aunty, don't worry.
They will find her.
Take some rest.
Grandma.
Grandma, you scared me.
I was so worried I couldn't find you.
I...
I miss them
so I came by myself.
Grandma.
It's a two-hour trip.
How did you get here?
I've been
keeping this photo.
I know
I'm forgetful.
So
(Qinglongshan Cemetery)
I wrote the address on the back.
With this,
I'll always remember.
I'm sorry,
Xiao Ning.
I'm sorry
that I made you worry.
It's all right, Grandma.
I don't blame you.
This isn't your fault.
I miss them.
I'm worried that one day
I might forget them.
All right, Grandma.
All right.
Xiao Ning.
Grandma.
Guang Da.
Stay a few days longer this time.
Don't always stay at the construction site.
Your wife,
why isn't she back with you?
I'm here!
My signature dish, Dapanji, is here.
It's not spicy.
Xiao Ning's Dapanji is super delicious.
You're lucky today.
Guang Da.
See?
Xiao Ning is already a young lady!
Grandma!
He is my boss,
not your son
nor my father.
If we were to be related,
he would be my uncle master.
Grandma.
Who do you think
I am?
Xiao Ning.
Trust me,
no puppy love.
The school doesn't allow that,
OK?
Grandma.
He is Yan Yan's boyfriend,
not mine.
Don't be silly.
He is not my boyfriend.
He's more like
a baron's foolish son.
Good.
That is good.
Guang Da.
Xiao Ning is a good girl.
She is so nice.
Yes.
Xiao Ning
is the best daughter
in this world.
Here comes the last dish,
fish filets in hot chili oil.
Guang Da.
Your wife is such an incredible cook!
Mother, stop fooling around.
Give me a break.
Aunty.
This is too much food for us.
We don't really
need a feast.
That won't do.
See?
After Xiao Ning
met friends like you,
she's been so happy.
I'm glad for her.
And thank you
for helping us today.
Grandma is finally found.
Happy!
Come on.
Let's have a toast
to Aunty's feast.
Thank you, Aunty.
Stop!
I just remembered
that I forgot something.
I haven't bought it for ten years.
Today
is Xiao Ning's birthday.
Ning Ning.
I understand.
You feel upset
whenever it's
your birthday.
But you
must stop dwelling on
the accident from ten years ago.
Be grateful.
It was a miracle that you survived.
Grandma and I
got to see you grow up.
By the way,
it's been years
since your parents' passing.
Learn to move on.
I think that
your life
should have
a new start.
Right?
Come, Xiao Ning.
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
Happy Birthday, Xiao Ning.
Happy Birthday to my dear Xiao Ning.
Thank you, Grandma.
Don't forget about me.
My sweet Xiao Ning.
Happy Birthday.
Thank you.
Aunty.
Do you have a lighter?
Sure.
I got it ready.
Do the honor.
See?
I was so thoughtful
not to show your age by the number of the candles.
Make a wish.
♪Happy birthday to you♪
Always stay happy.
Come on. Blow the candles.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪