[English subtitles are available.]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 31]
Half of my divine sense waited for you
for ten thousand years at the Graveyard of Gods.
The other half guarded you for ten thousand years.
However,
you still only have her in your heart.
How are you able to use the First Voodoo Insect?
I have my own way.
The Night Fairy,
get the poison out of Yushi first.
Then let's sit down and talk.
I'll talk with you after she's dead.
Chu, fight back now.
I can't.
Yushi.
Sheng Xie.
Qin Lie.
I'm fine.
Your spirit artifact gave me power.
Because you are not powerful enough.
Unless,
you have the crimson flame to activate it.
I do have it.
The Sword of Sheng Xie
is a spirit artifact forged in the crimson flame.
The sword pledged allegiance to our family.
It is so aggressive.
It is a sword.
Of course, it is very aggressive.
Is the crimson flame stronger
or the murderous sword?
They benefit from each other.
Wrong.
You don't know its true form.
What is its true form?
If I return it to its true form,
can we leave it all behind?
You can go back and forget all about this.
Okay.
I know your sufferings
and your anger.
Sword, kingly way, and integrity.
Establish the gods' stateliness
and guard people's kindness.
However, benevolent as it is,
the kingly way vanquishes the demons.
It's inevitable.
The more demons it killed,
the more murderous it became.
Till its true form was lost in the end.
It couldn't tell right from wrong,
or good from evil anymore.
The great dignity of the king was gone.
It became a devastating weapon.
Even you can't do anything to stop it.
The earth is inclusive, vast and boundless.
With the power vested in me by the earth,
I remove its desire for blood
and return it to its true form.
You will be clean and safe.
Are you willing to do so?
You're born with two bloodlines
but they won't merge together.
The Sword of Sheng Xie
shouldn't have obeyed your commands.
But it happened to be lost in the desire of killing.
So, you were able to use it with your hostility.
From now on,
you need to expel the hostility in your heart
to fully utilize the great power
of this ancient spirit artifact.
I've returned it to its true form.
You can go now.
I want to know the whereabouts of my father.
You broke your word.
I only have one goal.
I'll never give up until I get it done.
You are the one who ignored my determination.
Yushi.
Li Mu.
It turned out that we had such a bond.
No wonder it felt like we're old friends.
My master.
Uncle Li.
What have I done to deserve it?
Please forgive me, my master.
Now Sheng Xie...
I have some loose ends to tie up.
I wouldn't be able to follow you anymore.
Now that you've been awakened,
why are you still so obsessed with it?
Duan Qianjie needs to
choose his own path.
You shouldn't decide it for him.
What?
What is all this?
Years ago, Qin Shan helped me to get enlightened.
At that time, he already told me that
both of you are spirit artifacts
to guard the Soul Suppressing Orb.
Sheng Xie woke up after ten thousand years for you.
Ten thousand years ago,
we met and got to know each other
in the Gongmu family.
When the family was destroyed,
we took up the responsibility
to guard the Soul Suppressing Orb.
Brother,
I don't understand.
When you learn about what love is,
we will meet again.
Our paths shall separate now
but they might cross again.
Take good care of yourself.
spirit artifacts don't have emotions.
Why so emotional?
After a journey to the human world,
how can I be emotionless?
I lived up to my loyalty
but failed you again.
Now that you have feelings,
you didn't fail me.
I never knew that the spirit beasts
understand things better than men.
Men have seven emotions and six desires
while beasts are different.
We only have one emotion.
I'll never forget that.
That's enough.
I hope when the master truly is awakened,
he still has humanity.
Since the bloodlines co-exist,
they wouldn't try to suppress each other.
But before that,
I can only guard the master.
There is nothing else I can do.
Please be careful, master.
What do you mean by co-exist?
What exactly is sealed in the Soul Suppressing Orb?
You and Gongmu Lie co-exist in one body,
and he is sealed in the Orb.
What should I do to be awakened?
When the Four Spirit Artifacts are all awakened,
you should be awakened.
How can you safeguard the orb inside me
while showing up in front of me?
Spirit artifacts are able to control their powers.
Father,
the Sword of Sheng Xie is awakened.
before the sword was awakened,
its murderous power must have leaked.
The Golden Force must have sensed it.
The murderous power isn't a big deal. It's just...
The second volume of
the Scripture of the Nine Hells is out there now.
This could cause some real trouble.
Right.
Go kill Yiyuan.
Father, well...
Go kill him,
and lure them to the Purple Mist Sea.
It's more convenient when they are together.
I'll go to the Su Luo Realm.
Understood.
[Su Luo Realm]
Your highness, this is Hua Tianqiong
from the Sky Mending Palace.
What is it?
Lately, I felt
a spiritual power that is particularly strong.
It's the Scripture of the Nine Hells.
Your highness sensed it as well?
The three volumes of the Scripture of the Nine Hells
were lost ten thousand years ago.
The first and the second volumes showed up successively
with the power of Chong Ming.
Chong Ming?
No wonder it disturbed your highness.
Any thought?
I've sent someone to look into it.
The Scripture is in the Scarlet Tide Continent.
It's taken by some nobodies.
The Scarlet Tide Continent?
The lowest creatures were able
to summon the Scripture of the Nine Hells?
It was just a matter of luck.
They obtained it by accident.
This is a good thing for your highness.
Now you can take back
the Scripture of the Nine Hells effortlessly.
Keep it quiet. No one needs to know about this.
Since they are nobodies,
I'll send someone to handle it.
You should supervise it.
It shall be as you command.
When will you stop following me?
Until you get to the Illusory Demon Sect.
Then I can rest assured.
You'll rest assured.
What about me?
I'm sorry, Qianqian.
I upset you.
But the last person
I want to hurt is you.
Then stop lying to yourself.
I don't want forced love.
You don't need to fake it anymore.
We can be honest with each other.
Don't say that, Qianqian.
I am not faking it.
Instead, I feel touched.
No one cared this much
about me before.
It made me feel that
I'm needed and wanted.
Well...
Can we still be friends?
I won't pester you anymore.
I'm leaving.
Take care on the way back.
I feel tired.
I want to stay at an inn tonight.
Where is the inn?
Right up ahead.
Come on.
Only one room left.
Did you set this up intentionally?
I swear upon my life,
there really is only one room left.
I promise I didn't collude with the owner.
It's fine.
I'm stronger than you anyway.
Yeah, yeah.
I don't have the nerve to do anything
even if I want to.
But you want to do something?
No, no, no.
I don't want to do anything.
I knew you don't want me.
You only have Lianrou in your heart.
You must be hungry.
What do you want to eat? I'll go get it for you.
Clever move.
You know how to avoid questions now.
You really know about women.
No, I don't. Not at all.
Back in the Purple Mist Sea,
people disliked me because I am dumb.
No matter how hard I tried to please others,
they wouldn't be friends with me.
Except you.
Now, this...
It doesn't work for me, either.
No, it doesn't.
I told you I am dumb.
Are you feeling homesick?
Look,
after I get back to the Illusory Demon Sect,
you can go back to the Purple Mist Sea.
I don't know why
I always feel that
I don't belong there.
However,
I kind of miss it.
Then go back there.
Yiyuan, Yiyuan.
No one from the Purple Mist Sea
can escape from this.
Yiyuan.
Who are you?
[Tong Xin]
Yushi.
Wu Chun?
Aren't you dead?
Am I dead?
Maybe...
Maybe not.
Who was that?
I don't know, either.
I was trying to fight back.
He just disappeared in a blink.
He said that
"No one from the Purple Mist Sea
can escape from this."
Qianqian, I can't escort you
to the Illusory Demon Sect.
I need to go to the Purple Mist Sea first.
I'll go with you.
What? Li Mu is not human?
He is a spirit artifact?
Li Mu and Duan Qianjie are spirit artifacts.
So, I deduce that
I must be a spirit artifact as well.
Otherwise, why did it feel like
we had been old friends the first time we met?
Besides, in the entire Terminator Sect,
I am the only one who masters
the Terminator Profound Bomb.
Is it because
the true form of me is
a Terminator Profound Bomb?
Brother,
this bomb will protect you.
We should all protect Qin Lie.
No.
He's Gongmu Lie.
No, no, no.
He is my master.
Why are you so quiet?
What should we say after you said that?
Master,
how can I help you? Just say it.
Will you stop calling me master?
Then what do you want me to call you?
The Night Fairy must have known that
Wu Chun expelled the murderous power in Sheng Xie.
So, she used voodoo insects on Yushi.
She wanted to make her weak.
Then, she wouldn't be able to suppress the sword.
So Sheng Xie gained the power back
and was awakened.
But what does she want?
She wants to awaken you.
Yeah. That should be it.
And she is not Song Tingyu now.
She is the Night Fairy.
So, the person she loves is Gongmu Lie,
not Qin Lie.
She doesn't want to awaken Gongmu Lie.
Why?
He might be more dangerous if he is awakened.
What do you mean?
Why did you say my brother is dangerous?
According to the second volume,
Gongmu Lie truly is a dangerous person.
Du Shaoyang, I...
He is right.
Maybe that's the reason
my grandfather put me to sleep.
The Night Fairy was stabbed by Sheng Xie.
We don't know if she's dead.
Everything we are saying now is pure speculation.
Only your grandfather
and the second volume know the truth.
I've been suspecting that
the person behind this
is not just the Night Fairy.
There's someone else.
Where is this coming from?
We suspected that her accomplice
was Ye Yihao.
Now that Ye Yihao is dead,
and the voodoo insect in Siqi has been dispelled.
But the voodoo insect is still in Yushi's body.
What's worse, she's in a coma.
So, I assume that
something might
happened in the Black Voodoo Cult.
Or worse,
someone dangerous appeared.
So, what do you plan to do next?
I'll wait.
Wait for the person to give himself away.
We should all protect Qin Lie.
No,
he's Gongmu Lie.
No, no, no.
He is my master.
Master?
Shaoyang.
Come in.
Even Saintess Xie became
a housewife for you.
She knew you don't like the food here.
Well,
she's now cooking for you in the kitchen.
What? You want a free meal?
I want to have a drink with you.
My pleasure.
Why do you suddenly want to drink with me?
It is because
I'm worried about the voodoo insect in Yushi.
Drowning your sorrows?
It doesn't sound like you.
Then what sounds like me?
If it's the old you,
you would fight your way
into the Black Voodoo Cult directly,
or go to the Graveyard of Gods again.
For the love of your life,
you'd kill whoever stops you.
Now that you think
Ye Yihao didn't place the First Voodoo Insect,
how do you want to lure
this person behind it out?
I have no clue.
Nor dare I do anything recklessly.
Yushi is still in a coma.
Song Tingyu became the Night Fairy.
Uncle Li is awakened.
Duan Qianjie has left.
All of these are because of me.
Those are their choices.
It's said in the second volume that
the Four Spirit Artifacts are among us.
But it was stopped by the Night Fairy.
I didn't think too much about it
until Uncle Li awakened
and Duan Qianjie left.
If I had a choice,
I wish they were just my mentors and friends
instead of some spirit artifacts.
Are you suggesting anything?
Do you think it is not enough that
Chu follows you around and calls you master
all the time?
Do you think I am a spirit artifact as well?
If I really were a spirit artifact,
what would you do?
It doesn't matter
what I want to do.
What's more important is what you think.
Spirit artifacts may be valuable.
But for me, friends
are much more important.
Alright.
I finally get rid of Chu Li's nagging.
Let's drink.
I don't know why
I feel that Du Shaoyang is not right.
But I can't put my finger on it.
He keeps everything to himself.
I want to know about him more
but don't know where to start.
Neither can I tell him the truth.
I am a little worried about him.
I only realized it now that
without you around me
to share and discuss everything,
I feel so alone and lonely.
When you were by my side,
no matter what difficulty I faced,
I felt calm and assured.
Yushi,
you must wake up.
Otherwise,
what should I do without you?
Who's there?
Yiyuan is dead.
I'll kill everyone from the Purple Mist Sea.
Yiyuan.
You saw him as well?
Yes, it was a man.
Yiyuan was killed.
That can't be true.
Then it's everyone from the Purple Mist Sea.
Who the hell was that?
He showed up in our rooms at the same time.
What's going on?
Let's go to the Purple Mist Sea.
There was no one on the way here.
They can't all be dead.
Don't worry.
Let's go inside first.
Yiyuan.
Lianrou.
Why...
Why are you here?
To collect some spirit herbs. I just arrived.
What's going on?
Why is no one here?
You finally reunited with her.
Congratulations. Bye-bye.
Qianqian, Qianqian.
Qianqian.
Don't you call my name. Go away.
Come on.
-Qin Lie.
-Yi Yuan.
-What's wrong?
You are alive?
I thought you were dead.
How did you know that I was dead?
What happened to my sister?
Qianqian.
Would you leave us alone for a moment?
Sister,
I'm sorry, sister.
I shouldn't have left.
Neither should I lie to you
about not remembering you.
If I hadn't left,
maybe I could have protected you.
Even if I couldn't,
at least I could be there for you, just like
when we were in the Ling Borough.
Sister.
Have you settled
the people of the Purple Mist Sea?
They are now
in a place where no one can find.
After all this,
they will wake up
without knowing anything.
Good.
Watch closely later.
If Yi Yuan is not dead,
go after him.
Father, what is it between
you and Yi Yuan?
Nothing.
Then...
People from the Golden Force
should be here soon.
Master Hua.
I have been waiting for you.
The task is simple today.
Just some kids from the Scarlet Tide Continent.
A piece of cake for you.
Rest assured, Master Hua. You have my word.
They would be dead
before they know it.
Yi Yuan came back from death.
People of the Purple Mist Sea are missing.
Why did he
lure all of us here?
Is it because
they want to lead all of us here
so he can finish us off?
With his power, why does he need to do this?
If he wanted to kill us all,
we would be dead already.
Yi Yuan,
if you are worried about Qianqian,
why not go in and check on her?
No, I am only worried about you.
What were you saying?
Careful, everyone.
Look at the embroidery on their clothes.
The Golden Force.
Charge!
I thought they were some random brats.
But it looks like you have some skills.
We have no feud with you.
Why does the Golden Force want to kill us?
Sister.
It's me.
Father.
They are not
the best of the Golden Force.
But they can't be underestimated.
Aren't you worried?
You think they are the weakest as well?
If,
they can't even defeat the Golden Force,
how could we expect them to fight
against the God Race in the future?
They might as well be dead.
I am now most worried about Ling Yushi.
Yushi.
Qianqian.
Yi Yuan.
Yushi, Yushi.
Let's go.
Qin Lie.
I can't control it anymore.
Don't.
Don't be afraid.
I will try everything to save you.
Don't go, don't go.
Stay with me.
Yi Yuan.
Yi Yuan, Yi Yuan.
What happened to him?
Yi Yuan
was killed by them to protect Qianqian...
Don't worry.
He will wake up.
That man killed him once.
He woke up last time.
Qin Lie,
don't you need to
take my sister to the Abyss?
You can just go.
I will be here for him.
Will he really come back to life?
He will.
I think he didn't really die last time,
not that he returned from death.
No.
He told me that
he even saw Wu Chun and a little boy
after he died.
Wu Chun and a boy?
Maybe Yi Yuan really can be resurrected.
Chu,
you stay here to protect them.
I'll escort Yushi to the Abyss first.
Rest assured.
As your spirit artifact,
I'll protect them
with my life.
Just go.
Girls,
don't be too sad.
Yi Yuan is a good person.
Even if he dies, he...
I will be watching out for you outside.