[English subtitles are available.]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 32]
I was carrying out a mission
by order of the Master of Heaven.
The mission failed due to my lack of competence.
Master Hua, you're my supervisor.
I'm willing to take any punishment from you.
This should be a simple task.
But you failed at it.
It is easy to take your own life but
difficult to find a remedy.
It looks like you need help from my people.
Xing.
Yes, sir.
Master Hua,
what're you doing?
Do you really believe
he can come back to life?
I don't have to.
I've already seen it once.
Don't worry.
He'll surely wake up.
He can't bear leaving you.
Maybe,
it's you that he is missing.
Do you know
what our sect are best at?
I know immediately who you're thinking of
as soon as I see you.
I've seen who's on Yiyuan's mind before.
It's you.
So, I recognised you at once.
One can change
who he loves.
Others might.
He won't.
Alright then.
Take a look at his mind for me
when he wakes up.
Where are you now?
Did I die again?
Where am I?
It's you, again.
Who're you?
You can grow herbs with your feet.
Awesome.
Can you teach me?
No wonder he is the Voodoo Master,
one of the Ancient Masters.
She was defeated, as the Mother of Earth,
just by his Supreme Voodoo insect.
It's my fault that I didn't take good care of Yushi.
I understand.
It's not your fault.
What matters most now
is to detoxicate her.
Once she wakes up,
I'm afraid no one can suppress her.
Off you go then.
We'll try our best to protect the Queen.
We'll wait for you.
Shaoyang and Siqi will stay here.
I'll come back as soon as possible.
Night Fairy.
I know you're here, Night Fairy.
Come out,
Night Fairy.
Are you so weak that
you can't even pull your body together?
Are you going to kill me?
Just now when Ling Yushi was going to kill me,
it was you that was behind
the spirit diagram?
I couldn't let her kill you
once again in front of me
after ten thousand years.
It's a pity
that I still couldn't do anything to help.
Thanks anyway.
You were the mentor of Gongmu Lie
and his only friend during his childhood.
Every time I think of this
as Gongmu Lie,
I feel that I owe you so much.
Him?
You're him.
You're Gongmu Lie.
I grew up with you.
But you hurt me over and again
because of Wuchun.
Do you have any idea
that I've been waiting for you
for ten thousand years?
No one knows
what this feels like.
I can't tell you about all my sorrows
just in a few words.
But every time when I realise that
Gongmu Lie is to me
as Ling Yushi is to Qin Lie,
I know
you deserve to be treated fairly.
Are you talking to me now
as Qin Lie, or
as Gongmu Lie?
I'm Qin Lie.
What do you want to know?
Now even the Golden Force is involved.
I want to know
what happened ten thousand years ago?
I won't tell you.
It wouldn't do any good to you if you knew too much.
Why are you desperate to
find the spirit artifacts?
I don't want you to find them first.
I don't want you to be the first to
awaken your bloodline.
I don't want you to know
what happened ten thousand years ago.
Given the current situation,
I won't tell you anything.
Kill me if you want.
I'm on my last breath.
You can easily finish me off.
Well,
can I ask a favour?
Let go of Yushi,
will you?
I can't help you.
Are you determined to kill her?
It's not me that
wants to kill her now.
Who is it then?
My biggest mistake is that
I thought I could
control Du Shaoyang.
It's him...
I'm calling the Ancient Voodoo Insects
sleeping under the land of the Nether Realm,
by order of the Voodoo Master.
Ten thousand years ago,
the Voodoo Master fought for the Human Race.
The Golden Force took the opportunity to persecute him.
In order to protect Voodoo Cult,
the Voodoo Master sent you to hide beneath this land
with his remaining power.
Now, it's been ten thousand years.
Time flies.
Your opportunity has come once again.
I'm the direct disciple of the Voodoo Master.
By his order,
you'll all answer my calling
and let the Voodoo Race be great again.
What's wrong?
Why?
What is it?
Why don't you answer me?
Siqi?
I've been looking for you.
Why are you here?
Too many things happened recently.
I just came out for some air.
Since you're here, let's go and grab a drink.
Sure.
What're you doing?
Our future is full of risks and uncertainty.
We don't know whether we can survive tomorrow.
Since we're here like good old times,
I want to be your lover once more.
What's the hurry?
Don't you want to see me
without the veil?
Since you've seen my face,
you're my man.
I need you to remember my face forever.
If our relationship can last ten thousand years,
I hope you can still remember me
after ten thousand years.
The wine is poisonous.
You want to kill me?
You found it.
You're so cruel.
I thought you really loved me.
It's because I love you
that I would rather you died in my hands.
Only if you die,
can Ling Yushi be detoxicated.
Your sins can be reduced.
What gave me away?
You've changed.
You're unaware of that.
But I can feel that.
Where're my earrings? You didn't
get them back for me?
I forgot.
You left them on the doorknob
just for testing me.
Did I?
Did I want to test you?
I don't know.
What I know is that
if you still love me,
you would surely bring my earrings back.
You've seen what I did just now.
Congratulations.
You've become the disciple of the Voodoo Master.
Qin Lie can never be your match.
Do you want to kill him
or me first?
Since you love me so much,
you won't regret it if you die
in my hands?
You shall run as soon as possible.
No one used to respect me
on the lands of the spirit realm.
I wanted to be friends with Qin Lie.
He looked down upon me.
I obeyed my father.
Even he abandoned me in the end.
You're the only
who never gave me up.
I'm not going to kill you today.
This is a way
to pay your back.
If you ever stop me
when we meet again,
I'll make sure to kill you.
Du Shaoyang,
you fought the war of the Light Pillars
for Nebula Pavilion.
You fought against me with
the Profound Heaven Alliance
for the Human Race.
Now I realise
you did all these just for your ambition,
just because you hate and envy me.
You finally took me as your friend.
You drank with me.
Now you've found who I really am.
Do you regret it?
Du Shaoyang,
let me tell you.
You're one of the four Spirit Artifacts.
I am what I am.
Don't assume that I am inferior to you!
It's our turn.
There we are, finally.
Shall we do with bullshits first,
or let's go ahead with fighting?
I can let you go if you let go of Yushi.
Nonsense.
Kill him and my sister will be safe.
Shaoyang,
stop it.
I should have finished you just now.
Won't you just stop talking?
Shaoyang.
Master,
I'm sorry that I underestimated them.
I thought they were just nobody.
It turned out that they were quite powerful.
All our people sacrificed there.
Those boys were finished off
thanks to Yang Yi who fought hard.
Good.
He shall be rewarded.
Thank you, Master. This is my duty.
Where's the second volume of the Scripture?
We didn't find it.
Isn't it in the hands of those guys?
They had no idea of what
they held in possession.
They thought it was just nothing.
We've interrogated them many times.
They didn't even know
where and when they had lost it.
We'll keep on investigating.
Off you go then.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Master Hua.
Go and get your reward, then.
Yes, sir.
Father,
Du Shaoyang has entered the underground
of the Nether Realm.
Tang Siqi followed him.
Besides, Duan Qianjie has returned.
It seems that he still cares about her.
How do we deal with them?
Kill Duan first.
Yes, father.
By the time you understand love,
we shall meet.
This is the end of our friendship, but not quite.
Take care.
[On the bridge of the Colourless Realm]
Qianjie,
I don't expect you to marry me.
I just hope you can forever remember me.
Why her?
Come out!
I'm the successor appointed by Jiang Yan.
I'm the new Master of Voodoo Cult.
I'm ordering you.
You shall all obey me.
The ancestors ordered you to forget about love.
You failed.
I'll kill her right away.
You never made up your mind
to kill Qin Lie.
You didn't obey the ancestors.
Why should we obey you?
I'll go and kill him.
I'll kill him right away.
I'll kill them all.
I really admire you guys
who were born with noble identities.
People like me
can't rely on anyone.
All I have is my ambition.
How can I achieve great things
if I don't give up love?
Love is something
I need to get rid of as much as I can.
You suffered so much for Qin Lie.
But he froze you here.
You loved him secretly and deeply.
He was always delayed by other things
to get to you.
Have you ever blamed him for that?
Aren't you tired of it?
You must be tired.
Give up love as I do.
As the Queen of the Nether Race
and the Mother of Earth,
you are brilliant
but you achieved nothing.
Your people can only hide underground
humbly and humiliatingly.
They don't get to enjoy the sunshine.
They don't get fresh water, Ling Yushi.
Don't you feel guilty
about that?
Wake up.
Wake up using the power I gave you.
Kill all those who are cruel to you,
who forbid you from rejuvenating your own race.
You're powerful enough.
You don't need the second volume
of the Scripture anymore.
What have you done to Ling Yushi?
I've removed the Voodoo Insect from her.
She'll wake up soon.
You've come to the right decision.
I didn't.
I just can't give up on you.
Shaoyang.
Come with me, alright?
Ok.
You're still guarding against me.
You should want to kill me?
I can't achieve great things
if I don't kill you.
Duan Qianjie.
Don't kill him.
They want to kill the Queen of the Nether Race.
Tang Siqi is the traitor. Kill her!
Shaoyang.
No, Shaoyang!
Follow me.
Let go of me!
Shaoyang.
Where's Qin Lie?
Yiyuan.
Where's Chuli? Brother Chu!
Brother Chu!
This is...
What's wrong?
This is
Ling Town.
This is Ling Town.
Who's there?
Stop! Don't hurt me!
You bastard, it's me!
Uncle Hua?
Uncle Hua.
Uncle Hua, you didn't die?
Don't curse me.
What's going on?
Why are we here?
Did you save us?
Why do you have so many questions?
Which one should I answer first?
She...
She's Xuanxuan!
Me?
Sir,
can you tell us
what's going on here?
What's this all about?
I didn't really die back then.
His grandpa saved me and took me away.
Where's grandpa now?
I don't know.
After he saved me,
he took me to
a nice palace and told me to stay there.
I agreed.
But he told me everyone died
in Ling Town.
I thought I couldn't return
if everyone was dead.
I thought I could never come back.
But then,
he suddenly came to me
and said you were in trouble.
The Golden Force was going to kill you.
He wanted to save you.
He pretended as if
you had been killed by the Golden Force.
He sneaked you into Ling Town.
He can't meet you at the moment.
He asked me to explain to you.
Do you get it?
Why would they want to kill me?
Dunno. He didn't say why.
Why won't my grandpa see me?
Dunno. He didn't say.
Where is he now?
Dunno. He didn't tell me.
Aren't you living with him?
He keeps going in and out.
He is very busy, very busy.
He's occupied.
What do you know then?
I...
I remember.
When I came here, he told me
he knew you would ask this.
He had a message for you.
What is it?
Dunno. He didn't say.
What?
Ah, yes. He took
my hand back then.
He let me hit you with this hand.
Grandpa.
Gran, I miss you so much.
I've been looking for you, Gran.
What's this all about?
Am I really Gongmu Lie?
You're born to be unique.
You have bloodlines of both
the Human and God Race.
But now
you're Qin Lie.
You belong to the Human Race.
I let you wake up as Qin Lie
because I want to
train your mind so that
one day
you can integrate into the God Race.
Integrate?
You mean
we share a body
but that isn't me?
You were born in the same body but
you're different people.
In that sense, he's not you.
You said I'm unique.
Who am I?
Why did you make me sleep?
You froze Yushi as well?
Are these all related to the God Race?
Wuchun was frozen by her mother.
In that sense,
they're related.
You sealed me
and Yushi was sealed by her mother.
Was it because we were so naughty
that we annoyed
our neighbour?
They indeed despise you.
However,
you're not naughty.
On the contrary, you're both good kids.
Who is our neighbour then?
Even you
and the Deserted Spirits Realm cannot defeat them?
They're from the Surah Realm.
Lie,
since you've opened the second volume
of the Scripture,
why don't you train yourselves first
before you go
looking for the answers you want.
The second volume of the Scripture
belongs to the royal family of the Nether Race.
What does it have to do with the Gongmu family?
Everything.
Lie, I know
you still have many questions for me.
But I gotta go now.
Maybe you should have the answers
by the next time we meet.
Maybe you will have an answer
in your own mind.
Where're you going this time?
Where can I find you?
You don't need to find me.
You have your own way.
You need to understand love.
Maybe love is the only thing
you have in common.
Only love can help dissolve
the hostility in your bloodline.
I'm not hostile.
My good boy.
You can't find another one
who is more reasonable than me.
Good boy.
Did you understand what he said?
What's so difficult about it?
He just told me not to ask anything.
Ask nothing.
He didn't say anything else?
He did.
He said I'm a good boy.
Shameless.
Your grandfather is just like this.
He can be too cautious about everything.
It looks like you know him well.
What're you implying?
I guess that
you know more
than you told us.
Uncle Hua,
who are you then?
Me?
I'm just an old man without a family.
Both my wife and son died.
I almost forgot him.
This guy lying here
is Yuxin,
but not quite.
What do you mean?
Qin Shan told me another thing
that made me so angry.
You know what?
In order to protect you,
your grandfather took advantage
of my wife and son.
Hua Yuxin is
and is not my son.
He isn't even human.
He was a magic stone your grandpa
had put in my wife's belly.
What do you mean?
Hua Yuxin is an artifact cultivated
by your grandfather.
He wanted to make an upright friend
who could grow up with you
and purify your mind.
But his mind was corrupted.
He couldn't make a pure artifact.
So, he looked everywhere.
In the end, he found him.
He extracted the most innocent part
from him
and cultivated Hua Yuxin.
No wonder
when I first met Yiyuan,
he seemed to behave like a fool.
But later,
he became normal.
Because Yuxi died then.
Therefore,
Yiyuan became normal.
So, you're Yiyuan.
And Yiyuan is you.
It's you that I've always been thinking of.
Yiyuan, come back.
Who called my name?
Yiyuan.
Qianqian, are you alright?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
So good that you come back.
Uncle Hua.
Where's he?
Uncle Hua, you can't leave.
Where's Chu Li?
He's fine.
Who the hell are you?
Why do you take me here?
Tell me.
Do you want to kill me or save me?
Just be honest with me.
What are you laughing at?
I said, show some respect!
Did you hear me?
Besides,
where's my Senior Brother?
Where is he?
Say something!
Are you deaf?
Damn it!
You won't say, huh?
I'll blow you up if you don't say anything.
So grumpy.
You're hostile.
Who the hell are you?
Father,
I brought him here by mistake.
By mistake?
I...
What do you mean "by mistake"?
This place has nothing to do with you.
Go back to the Terminator Sect.
Why should I listen to you?
I need to protect my Senior Brother.
Don't you know that I'm the spirit artifact for Gongmu Lie?
Go back to the Terminator Sect.
I'm
a spirit artifact!