Damn it.
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Mr. Oh Jeong-bae.
Hands up,
or I'll fire.
I didn't do it.
Mr. Oh sent us a text that you
abducted him and brought him here.
When you find yourself trapped in a swamp…
Stay still.
You're under arrest
for abduction and murder.
…you must get out of it
before you hit the bottom.
Gosh, that hurts.
Hold on. You bumped into me.
Be more careful…
Wait.
You don't live here.
Where are you going?
Who are you?
Answer me.
Gosh. Where do you think you're going?
Damn, you give me no choice.
Fine.
It's been a while.
All right.
BEST LAUNDROMAT
Jeez. What was that noise? A flat tire?
Gosh. What is it?
Let's go.
-Is something wrong?
-Let's go. Hurry!
Yes!
Running away?
You're still totally fine.
Come on.
Is it time for some jujitsu?
Fine, come at me.
Jujitsu it is.
I got you. I got you, you little rat.
Don't hit my face.
Keep doing that and I'll go mad.
Stop! That's enough.
Boss!
Did you get my beer?
Yes.
I got bottled beer, your favorite.
Then you should make use of it.
EPISODE 16
Shouldn't you go farther?
I'll see what's going on.
Can I borrow your phone?
Sure.
Here you go.
It was a setup, wasn't it?
It seems like Babel found out
I was controlling Mr. Oh.
Do you have a plan?
I need to prove my innocence.
I have to find the person who lured me.
"Lured" you?
-Gosh.
-I got hit again.
-My goodness.
-You startled me.
How could you?
You startled me even more.
You see…
I found a suspicious man and caught him.
You can pay me and take him immediately.
Are you listening, Mr. Cassano?
Look here.
There are more than 50 missed calls.
MISSED CALLS
He must've had an accomplice.
What are you glaring at?
You killed the CEO
of Daechang Daily, didn't you?
Who made you do it?
Didn't I…
tell you not to hit me in the face?
How many more times
do I need to hit you to make you talk?
By the way, how did you know it was him?
Goodness. I'm Park Seok-do.
Geumga-dong's nutria.
A superb hunting instinct
and a tenacious will to survive.
But nutrias are being wiped out.
You get paid 20,000 won
for every nutria you kill.
You're being too harsh again.
You cold woman.
Okay.
Call me as soon as you get him.
He must've gotten help
from someone outside the building.
Your turn.
I've asked the police to put out an APB.
Get back in the game and get him quick!
Things are only getting
more complicated, right?
It's because you worry
about others too much.
You're too nosy.
I guess you are Korean after all.
You see,
I used to be in a gang myself,
although I eventually mended my ways.
Why?
Why else?
I realized I was useless
in the eyes of the world.
Goodness.
Do me a favor.
Leaving the past behind
and becoming a new person…
Forget all that.
Do what you do best.
That's what you can do to help the world.
Are you having a picnic?
Why are you all here?
My goodness.
Is this the man who lured you?
He won't tell us who was behind it.
Let's go talk in the car.
Go easy on him, okay?
He needs his jaw to eat.
Wait, why my car?
I washed it yesterday. Go cover the seats.
Okay. Hold on!
So I twisted his neck right away.
He's still alive, right?
He told me where his accomplice is.
I'll get going.
I'll come with you.
-Me too.
-Me three.
Me four.
This isn't some back-alley dog fight.
I need to prove my innocence.
Let us all go together.
The more, the better.
-Let's go.
-I mean…
Hey, go clean the seats.
By the way, Mr. Cassano.
Once this is all over,
shouldn't you repay me in some way?
I'm the one who caught him.
What do you want?
Can you grant me a wish?
What's your wish?
I'll tell you tomorrow. Tomorrow.
Stop him. It's dangerous.
Where are we going, by the way?
Goodness.
He's growing on me.
Open the door!
Hey!
Gosh, these punks.
Here I am, Geumga-dong's nutria.
Do as we say from now on.
I'm not sure that's a good idea.
They don't seem to recognize
their predator.
How dare they? I'll teach them a lesson.
Hold on. Move out of the way.
-Gosh.
-Let me hit him once.
By the way, he does look like
a nutria, doesn't he?
Well done, nutria!
Be careful! Oh, my.
RELIABLE POLICE, SAFE COUNTRY
These three are the real culprits
in the murder of Mr. Oh Jeong-bae.
We'll summarize what happened
for you, so listen carefully.
Attention.
Someone had ordered these men
to wait for Mr. Oh to get off work.
They struck him with a blunt object
to kill him in front of his office.
After they killed him,
they removed his body from the building
without anyone knowing.
And…
DAECHANG DAILY
they brought the body to Geumga Plaza
and moved it to the rooftop.
They made a false report
to the police to frame me.
And they lured me to the rooftop
of the central building.
When I arrived,
they dropped Mr. Oh's body to the ground.
Can you prove they're the culprits?
This van right here
belongs to these bastards.
You'll find the cart
they used to move the body,
the weapons they used,
and Oh's bloodstains in the van.
This is from the dash cam in the van.
You'll be able to see where they've been
in detail.
We'll keep a copy of the dashcam footage
just in case.
So Vincenzo hasn't been caught yet?
I don't know. The cops haven't called yet,
and they won't pick up.
Can I help you?
Yes, please.
We're looking for Mr. Park Do-hun.
Park Do-hun… Mr. Park?
That's me.
-Right.
-Mr. Park Do-hun.
You're under arrest for
aiding and abetting Oh Jeong-bae's murder.
-What?
-I'll take your coffee.
You have the right to an attorney
and the right to remain silent.
Hold on. This is a misunderstanding.
Mr. Han. Ms. Choi.
-Ms. Choi.
-Come with us.
-Mr. Han.
BYEBYE BALLOON TRAVEL
Very nice.
I cleared my name thanks to you.
So what's your wish?
It's about our flyers.
Can you do it for us?
-Do what?
-Can you be our model?
What are you saying?
Our model.
I don't know why, but you somehow give off
this trustworthy vibe.
Forget it. I'll just pay you.
Please be our model.
Without my help, you'd be
locked up in jail by now.
I said no. I'll leave this here.
No! Wait!
You promised to grant him a wish.
-Are you going back on your word?
-No.
I paid him instead. Move.
You're one heartless capitalist monster.
-Good.
-What? Give me that.
-Delete it.
-Okay. Good.
-Give it here.
-You're too close.
Take a half step back.
A half step back. There you go.
Very good. That looks really nice.
-Give me that.
-Good.
I'll hang you off the balcony.
Put your hand on your tie.
Delete it.
Can you look up a little?
-Give me that.
-There you go.
Damn it. Give me that now!
Perfect.
Give me that now. Stop it.
Why is this so hard?
You said you set up a trap.
How come he hasn't fallen for it once?
I can see why he used to be
an ace member of the Mafia.
He's as elusive as a ghost.
He's not to be trifled with.
He's invincible.
Yes. Vincenzo Cassano.
What could be his secret--
Can we trust the lawyer who got arrested?
Yes.
I made sure he understood.
Why do you look so unhappy?
It's not like that.
I was thinking of something else.
I'm sorry, sir.
I transferred the case
to the Namdongbu office.
It'll be fine.
-Han-seo.
-Yes?
We need to go somewhere.
What? Okay.
Did you see how I dodged it?
I'm so…
Myung-hee.
Wusang isn't some contract killing agency.
At this rate, everyone will be
arrested for ordering murders.
This is why
we should have succeeded the first time.
Gosh.
Shouldn't you try to stop Mr. Jang?
This has gone too far.
Are you blaming me?
We're a law firm.
There are limits to what we can do.
Did you bring me here
to adhere to the limits?
Didn't you want us to be Babel's bidet?
Damn it!
Still, this is just not right!
Jang Han-seok is a total psychopath.
-Jeez.
-Han Seung-hyuk!
I know you're frustrated,
but you should know who your enemies are!
I don't think I'll ever forget this aroma
wherever I go.
You've finally learned to appreciate
instant coffee.
You knew Jang Han-seok would kill
Mr. Oh, didn't you?
To some extent.
Since Mr. Oh washed
Han-seok's dirty linen in public.
So you already had
the big picture in your mind.
We should get going.
I'll carry your bag.
Thanks.
You look gorgeous today.
You look even more beautiful
with makeup on.
Right?
Yes.
Where do you want to go first?
I want to have my portrait taken.
I have no portrait to use
at my funeral later.
One, two…
One more.
Relax. One, two…
Put on a little smile. One, two…
One last time. Put on a bigger smile.
There you go. One, two…
Great. Well done.
Hold on.
Please take one more with us.
Sure, go ahead.
Stand straight.
Look at the camera.
Good. One, two.
Relax a bit. Okay. One, two.
We're done.
-Thank you. Oh, wait.
-Sure.
Your outfits match pretty well.
-You should take a photo together.
-I'm fine…
Hang on. Come over here.
Wait. Why don't you sit here?
Yes, sit here.
Just one photo.
Put your arm around her shoulders.
Like this. Stick closer together.
That's nice. Just one photo, okay?
Yes, just like that!
All right, look over here.
Great. One, two.
Okay, look here. One, two.
You two look so nice together.
One more. One, two.
That's great. One, two.
The weather is really nice today.
You're right.
I need to make
an urgent business call now.
Take good care of her.
Drink this if you get thirsty.
Thank you.
I'll see you later.
I haven't taken a walk in a long time.
I thought I'd die
without being able to enjoy such luxury.
This isn't a luxury. It's just a walk.
This is
the happiest moment of my life.
Just tell me
whenever you want to go for a walk.
I will. Thank you.
Receive your treatment
and hang in there until the retrial.
I've never had
so much energy before in my life.
Never?
No.
Not since
I sent my beloved son away.
He was my everything.
What hope could I have
after losing everything?
Then why didn't you look for him?
I did.
I looked for him for several years.
But I couldn't find him.
I was too late.
You can still look for him now.
I can't face him now.
I'd only be a burden to him like this.
Don't think like that.
I'm sure your son wouldn't.
Do you think so?
Yes.
I'm sure your son
has been waiting for you his entire life.
And I'm sure
your son…
tried to grow up strong
so he wouldn't be ashamed
when he met his mother someday.
That doesn't matter.
No matter how he's grown up,
he's still my son.
What mothers cherish their entire lives
are the beautiful smiles
their children give them.
"Ju-hyeong."
When I called him,
he'd look at me with this smile.
There's something
I want to tell him if I meet him again.
"I'm sorry I couldn't keep my promise
that I'd come for you soon.
There hasn't been a single day
that I haven't thought about you."
I want to tell him that.
There's something
I just can't wrap my head around.
How did Oh Jeong-bae
find out about all your dirty laundry?
He was someone who'd use secrets
to cut a deal as soon as he obtained them.
You're right.
He wasn't someone
who'd keep any secrets to himself.
Then that means
he learned about it recently.
If Vincenzo was the one who told him…
Vincenzo may be using the Guillotine file.
Then he wasn't keeping it in that room.
If that really is the case,
He could stir up the entire nation.
Then we'll have to use
the most effective method.
If I can't have it,
I'll make sure no one ever gets it.
Sir.
Yes?
Why did you want to come here?
To cherish Geumga Plaza
as a historical building.
What do you mean?
I just recorded a piece of history.
YEONGHO SNACK BAR
I came for a gas safety check.
Did the other inspector quit?
She took a few days off
since her daughter's giving birth.
Oh, right. So she's giving birth already.
Business must be slow
because of the demolition and everything.
Right, but we should hang in there.
-Oh, the gas pipe is over there.
-Right.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
All right.
Get some rest.
You'll be able to get
a good night's sleep today, right?
Of course, I'm sure I will.
Get some rest, then.
Wait.
Thank you.
Stay healthy, okay?
Please keep an eye on her.
Yes, sir.
-Who is that?
-A guard.
Just in case Shinkwang Bank tries
to harass her about the retrial.
Right, Hwang Min-seong
made a fuss last time.
Mr. Cassano.
You two looked really nice together today.
You looked like mother and son.
Later, when you're ready,
you should call her Mom.
What's this?
Oh, my gosh! Is this real?
Then are you really
going to become parents?
Oh, my gosh. Congratulations!
My gosh!
I think I'm going to cry.
Finally, after making such a fuss
about not having a child.
Yes. These days, I've become confident
that I'll be able to be a good father.
Things won't be easy, but we'll
try our best and raise our child well.
-I hope they'll grow up well.
-Of course.
You're both strong,
so I'm sure your child will be healthy.
Shouldn't we have a drink to celebrate?
Everyone, gather at Arno.
I'll treat you all to a delicious meal.
-Nice!
-Yes!
Is there good news?
The pawnshop owners are having a baby!
Congratulations!
I can't believe it. Congratulations.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you, Mr. Cassano.
We're going to have a party
at Toto's restaurant.
-You should come too.
-Sure.
We should celebrate such a happy occasion.
You're coming too, right?
I don't think he'll come.
I'll join you, too.
-Yes!
-Nice!
-Cheers!
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-I'm so happy for you.
-No way.
-All right!
Que sera, que sera
-Que sera, que sera
-Vincenzo!
I heard that in Korea,
you can have someone
to do things for you at gatherings.
-A black knight.
Right, a black knight. Seok-do?
-Go!
This is crazy!
He seems pretty drunk.
GEUMGA PLAZA
YEONGHO SNACK BAR
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, my baby
Here.
-Thank you.
-Here you go.
-Eat up.
-Aren't you drinking too much?
Do you hear the sirens?
-What?
-Is there a fire?
-I drank too much.
-What?
-Where could it be?
Sirens?
Hey, wait.
-Wait up.
-What's going on?
-What is it?
-Stay here.
-Is this the smell of gas?
-What?
-Oh, my.
-I can smell gas.
We received a report about a gas leak.
You should all evacuate.
-What?
-We have to evacuate?
-Oh, my gosh.
-Honey.
-A gas leak?
-We have to go.
-Let's go.
-Come on. Let's go.
I think it's over here!
-Hurry. Let's go.
-A gas leak?
Come on, let's go.
-Hurry.
-You guys go ahead first.
-Mr. Cassano!
YEONGHO SNACK BAR
It's dangerous here.
The gas pipe was cut.
-Someone cut the pipe?
-Yes.
Sir, you shouldn't be here!
Get out of here!
But what's this?
It looks like it's working.
Hey!
Thank you.
It's pretty sharp.
It has to be her.
The woman who came for a gas safety check.
We'll tell that to the police
and find her.
If it weren't for you,
it would've been a disaster.
I never heard of such watches.
There's no question who did this.
Babel, those jerks. They're even trying
to make gas explosions now?
They blew up their own vacation home
to kill their researchers.
What would've happened to our baby
if it really exploded?
It's all right.
But who reported it?
-Was it you?
-What? No.
None of you reported it?
It seems so.
We were all drinking.
Don't dodge this.
I won't.
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect the firefighters
to be dispatched.
Can't even blow up one building?
Why? I don't get it.
It was just about to explode,
but 911…
Right. 911.
I'll think of another reckless way
to take care of it.
-Are you saying I was reckless?
-Yes…
I mean, no.
Who is it?
I have something urgent to report.
Hey. Get out.
Yes, sir.
HANJU SACRED HEART HOSPITAL
So we finally found
what Vincenzo cares about the most.
Everything in this building
could've turned to ashes.
I wonder who reported it, though.
Sir, I'd like some luwak coffee today.
It was such a hassle to brew it,
so I sold it online.
Why would you?
Don't you know how rare it is?
What's with your clothes?
It's as if you live in the '80s Koreatown.
I disguised myself in case
someone recognized me on the way here.
What?
Oh, this?
I actually came here
to tell you guys about this.
Let me tell you.
This is a battle scar
that I got for saving your lives.
What do you mean?
Yesterday, when this building
was about to blow up.
Who do you think reported it?
You see, my brother ordered me
to blow up this building.
And I made him think I was going to do so.
Then I called 911 at the right time.
It was really dangerous.
Are we supposed to thank you or something?
Of course, you should.
You could've been buried alive,
but I saved all of you.
My brother and Wusang know that
there's gold and the Guillotine file here.
You know that, right?
That's probably why he wanted
to blow this place up.
He won't stop here.
He could even launch a missile.
Don't you think this is enough for you
to do me that favor?
I've done enough, haven't I?
Fine, I'll do it.
We'll discuss the details later.
Organize them in an alphabetical order.
Alphabetical?
Second from the top.
First, we should set up gas detectors
and a security system.
You never know
what that psychopath might do next.
He won't have many chances left.
Things are going to turn biblical soon.
The Tower of Babel will finally collapse.
In addition,
I'll make sure everyone who tried to
build it will be punished.
But we're not God.
God will punish them.
We'll just deliver them to Him.
Villains know best how to deliver
the likes of them to God.
Tell me the details.
Translation.
"Catch a big fish with a small fish."
SEOUL NAMDONGBU DETENTION CENTER
You're Kang Ho-chul, right?
Who the hell are you?
Manners, you son of a bitch.
Are you refusing to obey me
now that you're out of jail?
-Run!
-Run! Hurry!
Damn it!
Right.
Hello, ma'am
Get in, you bastard.
It's still chilly,
so don't stay out for too long.
-I'll come back later.
-Okay.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Your son is extremely handsome.
He is.
CONSTRUCTION PERMIT REPORT
BABEL TOWER PROJECT PROGRESS
-Mr. Cassano, where are you going?
-Mr. Nam.
You must be elated to have finally
met him again after a long time.
Of course.
I'm sorry for yapping away
when we've just met.
How embarrassing.
Don't be.
Your story made my heart feel warm.
I envy you.
My parents and I never took photos.
Really?
My father never liked taking photos.
Oh, dear.
With such a handsome son like you?
He didn't love me
as much as you love your son.
Is your son precious to you?
Of course.
I'd give up my life for him.
I hope you regain your health.
Thank you.
And thank you so much
for chatting with me.
Make sure to make me feel
ecstatic tonight.
-I'm looking forward to it.
-Yes, sir.
ATTORNEY CHOI MYUNG-HEE
I promise to bring you good news.
You seem to be in a great mood.
Did you go somewhere nice?
That's none of your business. What's this?
Oh, this? You don't look too great
these days.
Your ears look humongous as well.
This is for your health.
After all you've done?
Also, my ears were always huge.
Really?
Wait. One pill is enough.
Are you really not going to tell me
where you've been?
Damn it. You could've told me
in return for the supplements.
BUNGEOPPANG
Yes?
-Where are you?
-I'm buying some bungeoppang.
Custard cream for me, then.
I'm visiting the hospital.
Why?
There's something I didn't tell her.
Good thinking.
Go to her and call her "Mother."
And give her a hug.
See you later.
See you.
45TH JUDICIAL TRAINEES'
GRADUATION CEREMONY
Here you go.
-How much is it?
-That'll be 3,000 won.
-Here you go.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
I was told to move Ms. Oh Gyeong-ja
to another room.
What's going on?
-Move aside!
-Coming through!
-What happened?
-Really?
-Are you serious?
-It happened in the room.
It happened inside the room?
-It happened here?
-It's terrifying.
Ms. Hong.
Someone broke into the room
and murdered Ms. Oh.
One of the nurses…
He's definitely not a staff here.
I'll call the police.
Please send this footage to my phone.
Okay.
I have a favor to ask you.
Please stay by her side
until I come back.
I will.
Make sure you catch him.
No.
Make him pay.
The facial recognition result is out.
CRIMINAL RECORD
He had committed assault and murder
and was recently released.
He was charged with attempted murder
but was acquitted during the first trial.
I'll send you his photo
and his registered address.
-Thank you.
-Is there anything else I can do?
I may need you to track someone later.
I'll call you then.
Who is it?
What the hell?
Who the hell are you?
Do you know who the woman you killed was?
No, I don't.
She was my mother.
Who gave the order?
No one.
After I was released,
I had a drink with a friend.
Then I got upset and…
So…
you just killed someone at random?
Yes.
Do try to be understanding of me.
After all, you killed my mother.
Who gave the order?
It's the truth.
I was in a bad mood…
All right.
Let's drink ourselves to death tonight.
Why are you in such a great mood today?
Because I killed Vincenzo's mother.
The one he was finally reunited with
after 30 years.
What?
He must be devastated, right?
Were you aware of this?
What's wrong?
Are you scared that I killed his mom?
No, sir.
I'm just worried
it might worsen the current situation.
I feel the same way.
No good can come out of provoking him.
Since you joined hands,
you must share the same feelings too.
"Joined hands"?
What are you trying to say?
Hey, Ms. Choi.
How dare you talk so impudently?
I'm not being impudent.
I'm just stating a fact.
That's not true.
He was just lending me a hand
because I lacked so much.
You've been meeting each other
a bit too often for "just lending a hand."
-Damn it.
-What?
Have you been watching me?
Wait. Then me too?
How could you keep tabs on your allies?
It's because you weren't
acting like our allies.
That's why we did it.
Hey! Who do you think you're talking to?
Show some respect!
What is this about?
Non-members cannot enter.
Hey.
You must be out of your mind
because of my brother
when you're a mere lawyer.
Maybe.
But I can still see through
your lousy plan to betray the chairman.
Ms. Choi!
Watch what you say.
He's still our client nonetheless!
Seung-hyuk, you of all people
should have been more careful.
How dare you betray the chairman's trust?
What did I do?
How could you frame me like this?
Frame, my ass.
You should've known better. How could you?
Do I look like a pawn now that you've
gained some wealth and power?
If it wasn't for me,
you'd still be Mr. Seo's gopher
back at the Namdongbu Office!
-"Gopher"?
-That's right.
Do you want to die?
I'm your senior! Show some respect!
Sir, I don't know what she told you,
but it isn't true…
Who is that?
Help me.
SPECIAL THANKS TO JEON JIN-KI
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim