(This is based on the Tale of On Dal
in Chronicles of the Three States.)
(Characters, incidents, and dates
do not match historical facts.)
(Episode 15)
You found it?
I told you not to be afraid.
It is the grace of the skies.
The skies must have helped.
No, they did not do anything.
It is because you called the Princess
out of Magnolia Hall.
That is not true.
You and I did this together.
Wait.
This is not my handwriting.
Are you here to exchange love letters?
That looks like my letter though.
What do you think
you are doing, Princess?
What about you two?
What is this discreet meeting
at this time of night?
What do you mean? Watch what you say.
The Princess must have gotten us wrong.
Stop right there, Go Won Pyo.
Princess, are you out of your mind?
You cannot speak down to him.
Why?
Are you upset that I called out...
your lover's name?
We met when you were
selecting the Princess' groom.
This is the first time
we meet in private.
Your father was a legendary swordsman.
He did not hide behind a woman...
to draw his sword whenever he pleased.
Do not dare mention my father
with your corrupt lips.
Do not fall for it.
He is taunting you.
You cannot prove
anything with a fake letter.
At times, something fake
reveals the truth.
Someone was given the
order to steal the letter.
Your nanny?
If it were your command,
she would willingly jump into
a fire with a handful of straw.
Who would believe her?
There is another witness.
Eight years ago,
someone witnessed
your discreet meetings.
You must see but not look,
and hear but not listen...
for your family to be at peace.
I regretted keeping
silent ever since then.
If I had told my mother a day sooner,
I could have prevented the disaster
that befell us and the Sunno Tribe.
I do not know what you saw...
Shut your mouth.
You are Queen, the mother of a prince.
But with your corrupt deeds,
you brought shame on us.
I cannot even bear
to speak of it myself.
Curse me all you want.
Or do you want me to bite my tongue
and take my life right now?
You do not know the sorrow
of a woman scorned.
If the King had just
looked at me even once,
if he cared for me
just one-hundredth of...
the time he pined for your dead mother,
then I would have lived differently.
But...
you two killed my mother.
Including the innocent Sunno people.
You should save your breath.
Instead of bringing up the past,
tell us what it is you want.
Leave the palace.
As soon as possible.
Make up whatever excuse,
but you must leave the palace.
Silently.
So no one suspects anything.
I am the Queen.
I will not be chased out like this.
You brought this upon yourself.
For the sake of your son,
Prince Geon Mu,
I am giving you a chance
to leave with dignity.
Do not cause a scene.
If you wish me gone as well,
do not dare ask.
I have no intention of leaving quietly.
You must hand over something else.
Princess.
I am a foolish woman,
and I did something terrible.
I know why you did it.
You wanted to protect
the royal household.
Perhaps...
Go Won Pyo threatened you...
by naming me or the Crown Prince.
So I will not blame you.
Princess.
Just remember two things.
Father can never find out
what the Queen did.
And...
if you deceive me again,
I will not be forgiving,
even if it is you.
I will see you in the morning.
Do you regret it?
Regret?
Using Lady Gongson...
to set a trap for Go Won Pyo.
No.
If I think about the corruption
they perpetrated,
I could have them quartered
and still feel no better.
I do not have regrets.
You told me that the letter was real.
That was...
because you cannot lie.
I do not mind.
Use me as much as you need to.
But do not do that to anyone else.
Do not hurt them...
or yourself.
Everywhere I step is thin ice.
I do not know who is a friend,
or who is a foe.
I was taken, and when I woke up,
Lord Kim Cha Seung was there.
Lord Kim?
Did he question you
about the missing girls?
Yes.
He was furious
because of his great loss.
How dare he?
For something that trivial,
he abducted the Sono Tribe heiress?
I will not let him get away with this!
You must.
He let me go because I
promised to cover his losses.
- But this is...
- The mind of a merchant...
is the same.
I will sort this out. Do not worry.
I am glad you are back safely.
Get some rest.
General.
Do not...
leave my sight ever again.
Even if you come to hate my guts,
do not ever leave.
I will not leave.
Also, do not try to deceive me...
with a lie like that.
You were taken because
of your fake reports.
If it were for that,
how could I have come back alive?
It was not that.
Okay.
Look after yourself.
To convalesce?
Why must you convalesce
and pray to Buddha?
I did not inform you for
fear of causing concern.
I have been feeling unwell for a while.
I had been suffering
morning and evening.
Oh, dear.
Then you must consult my physician.
Medicines do nothing but the same.
I heard that mineral water from
a spring near Hobeob Temple...
cures internal illnesses.
I would also like to pray.
So I would like to leave the palace
to convalesce for a while.
Please grant your permission.
I would allow it if it is
to cure an illness.
The prince is young.
Would he be able to handle the trip?
The prince should remain in the palace.
We do not know how
long the Queen will be gone.
We cannot let the prince leave with her.
I will take just a few maids...
and travel quietly.
I am sorry, Queen.
I have not been to
your chambers lately...
and had no idea you were ailing.
This is my fault.
I thank you for your concern.
Since you have decided to leave,
you should leave today.
This very day?
The sooner you leave,
the sooner you can recuperate.
Father.
Why did you ask to see me so early?
Do you rarely come home...
because I have fallen from grace?
A friend was in trouble
so I went to check.
Is it a friend I know?
No.
You need not know of this friend.
- This is...
- The Gyeru Tribe's military...
(The authority to manage the troops)
is yours to control.
Before I give it to you,
I need to hear what your plan is.
What on earth is happening?
You look fine on the outside.
Why are you sick?
Please...
look after the prince for me.
Do not worry about anything else,
and focus on healing
your body and spirit.
As your father,
all I have to say is that...
you must return stronger than before.
Mother!
Where are you going, Mother?
I am going to a large temple far away.
I will pray for you to be strong...
at all times.
I wish to pray too.
For Father and your health.
I will be away only for a few nights.
Be a man and guard the palace.
Can you promise?
No! I will go with you!
Do not be so weak.
Until my return,
you must study and train.
Do you understand?
Mother.
I will take good care of the prince.
Do not worry.
Mother!
Do not go, Mother!
Mother.
Mother! Do not go, Mother.
Did you see this?
Sunno Tribe's Sa Un Am...
seems to want to challenge
the exclusive rights to salt.
He should know that he is
challenging the wrong people.
Is there...
another issue on your mind?
We should deal with them one by one.
Oh, Lord Hae!
Gochuga.
It has been a long time.
I managed to stay alive,
hence we meet again.
You made a long, arduous trip.
It was incredibly and stupidly far.
But only Lord Sa came out to welcome me.
The Five Tribe council seems
to care less about manners now.
Take a seat, General Yeon.
Yes, let us all sit down.
Goodness.
I noticed on the way in...
that the palace seems to be busy.
The Queen left to
a temple to convalesce.
Oh, dear.
She seems to be void
of care and emotion,
how did she get sick?
The Capital Defense Army is very grand.
Are you returning from
escorting the Queen to the gate?
Those who did not
receive a title from the King...
cannot be armed in the Capital.
The Gyeru Tribe is an exception,
so do not concern yourself.
Put down your weapons.
You are a mere assassin
who was granted a position.
Do not cross the line.
I told you to put down your weapons.
You are nothing but a Gokturk.
Right.
Your brother who scaled walls with you.
I heard he was slaughtered in battle.
How dare you?
Stop!
Sheathe your sword.
Do as I say.
Take him away.
Are you out of your minds?
In the middle of town,
the Capital Defense Army...
fought like ruffians?
Not at a time like this.
The Gyeru fools broke the law.
So you drew your swords?
Pung Gae defended me...
I apologize!
I will be very, very careful so that...
this never happens again.
Your Highness,
the King has called a meeting.
Okay.
You may raise your head.
Even if I sound harsh,
it cannot be helped.
We are now in the Capital,
so we cannot act like
how we did in Ghost Valley.
They are fast learners.
I am the slowest and worst.
Princess.
Ga Jin has a lot on her mind.
You know that, right?
With that tiny head of hers,
she worries about
everything and anything.
It must be...
hard on you too.
What?
I will try to comfort her,
but I am not that good with words.
Next, a letter from the Sunno Tribe
that the exclusive rights to salt...
should be returned to the King.
Is that truly what you think, Lord Sa?
All members of the Five Tribe council...
have accumulated great wealth.
I believe there will be no harm
in your taking back...
the exclusive rights.
I think highly of your thoughts,
but that is for the Five Tribe
council to decide.
That is correct.
It should not take much discussion.
We could reach a decision right now.
Lord Jin.
Yes?
It is a good idea.
Of the five members of the council,
those who agree that the King should
have the exclusive rights to salt,
step forward.
Gochuga.
You are standing with those in favor.
I too...
am in favor of returning the
exclusive rights to sell salt...
to the crown.
I, Pyeonggang,
have something to tell the King
on behalf of the people.
The fees levied...
are but a small sum to those here.
But to the people, they are the
products of blood, sweat, and tears.
In order to build Jangan Castle,
it is unavoidable...
Why is it the people who
must bear the cost of that?
The nobles of the capital and
the leaders in the countryside.
If we levy the taxes on them,
we can certainly cover the cost.
The duty of building our country
does not lie on the people alone.
Enjoying all of the benefits...
and yet avoiding all responsibilities.
You should know that is
a shameful way to behave.
Princess.
I will be the first to pay.
I will pay in jewels and silver...
to support the construction
of Jangan Castle... No.
I am willing to give
everything for Goguryeo.
I support you a hundred times over.
If the Queen Mother had been alive...
I am sure she would
have said the same thing.
I too will follow the Princess.
Deciding the taxation in this country...
is not something that can
be easily done in a day or two.
- It is very...
- Gochuga.
What do you think?
This new taxation policy
the Princess has provided...
is very solid and well thought out.
We should implement it quickly...
to ease the suffering of the people.
An ill wind will blow.
He is not someone to fold that easily.
Go Won Pyo will be sharpening his blade.
You are overly concerned.
The Princess is here,
and you have a heroic
son-in-law to protect you.
He could never point his blade at you.
I shall pick them off, one by one.
Those who defy you...
and those who leech off
Goguryeo as its leaders.
I will pick each one off turn by turn.
Were you at the king's palace?
Yes.
I heard you got rid of
the taxes on the people...
for the construction of Jangan Castle.
Yes, I went to confer with
my father about that issue.
I bet the people will be
really happy about that,
though I am sure the
nobles will be displeased.
I am saying you did well,
though it was a difficult task.
Thank you.
Ga Jin.
I heard of a skilled fortune-teller...
and requested an impregnation ceremony.
I heard a talented fortune-teller
has set up shop in the city.
Shall I ask for you?
She knew all along.
Knew what?
Who did?
Jangbaek herb store.
What?
What a fool.
How could I have forgotten?
What is it? You can
leave the hard tasks to me.
It is all right. I can ask Jin.
Earlier...
I think he was a little hurt.
We overcame numerous
near-death experiences together.
What about Lady Gongson?
What is it you want to say?
Do not try so hard.
Do not worry too much
and do not work so hard.
Just do things one at a time.
Just do what you can take,
one at a time.
Do you think I am having fun?
It is hard for me too.
It is all painful and chaotic,
but I cannot help it.
"It was unavoidable."
"I had to do so."
People always say that...
but there is nothing in this world
that is unavoidable.
I will go get some fresh air.
Dal.
I do see the stars faintly,
but the moon is so large that
a dragon could come from it.
A dragon?
So, is the moon white or red?
I do not know.
It does look whitish.
I must be the insane one.
I am here trying to read the moon
with a child the size of a twig.
What is wrong with being small?
All right, I will serve you properly.
Come over here.
Pluck out some of my gray hairs.
My goodness.
Do not worry about Dal.
He has been made a general,
and he has the most
beautiful Princess as his wife.
What is it that concerns you?
When you get old...
you start to get many worries
as much as you get wrinkles.
What is it that worries you?
Goguryeo, Baekje, and Silla.
What is it that they are fighting over?
What?
We are all of the same blood,
living on the same land.
The three kings could
just get together and say...
"Let us stop fighting and
be one country from now on."
That is all they have to do.
My goodness.
Everyone in the world, listen.
Zhuge Liang has been reincarnated.
Everyone, come watch and listen.
Otherwise, I will never...
be able to return to my hometown.
Weol...
Do you wish to return to your hometown?
Yes.
I see.
I am sure that day will come.
Dal and the Princess...
will work hard to make a world
where that is possible.
You must be catching a cold.
Let us hurry inside.
All right.
Shall I brew a warm cup of
scorched rice water for you?
That sounds nice.
The city is filled with praise for you
and your husband, Your Highness.
That is nonsense.
Whenever I faced an obstacle,
you were always of great help.
I should be the one
who is grateful to you...
since you trusted me,
despite my insignificance.
I called you here to
express my gratitude to you...
and because I have something
urgent to discuss with you.
Something urgent?
Do you remember?
When you were brought here
to the Hall of Convenience,
you confidently gulped down
a bowl of medicine...
to prove it was not poison.
While thinking about the favors
you have done for me so far,
I became curious.
Back then, you obeyed
Go Won Pyo's orders.
At other times, you did me favors.
Whose side...
are you really on?
Why do you even have to ask?
I am, of course, on your side.
Back then,
I gave in to Gochuga's threat.
You had no choice.
Is that what you mean?
I do know that. But what about this?
You knew who Du Jung Seo was all along.
Your Highness.
- If I had other intentions, why...
- Quiet.
You are the one who brought
Du Jung Seo into the palace.
You did not arrange it
because you did not know.
You brought him in knowing who he was.
- Your Highness.
- Hae Mo Yong.
You cannot deceive me forever.
Tell me who you really are.
For the great cause
of the three empires,
I want you to return to Goguryeo.
And...
kill...
Princess Pyeonggang.
I told her to.
What happened is simple.
I wanted her to win your trust.
So I found her weakness
and forced her into it.
It must have been a tall order.
You did well.
But neither of us knew about
the chief of Cheonjubang.
Master Go.
What else would you like to know?
I can tell you anything.
Do you believe you know
everything about Lady Hae?
I know more about her than you do.
She is the woman I love,
and there are no secrets between us.
Hey.
What do you think you are doing?
I rushed over because someone
heard voices coming from here.
It was you.
My Princess, what shall I do?
What do you mean?
These two displayed affections
in the sacred Hall of Convenience.
As the Head of Capital Defense,
shall I slash both of them?
You are out of line.
Do you dare to slay the
Head of Bodyguards?
Then let us fight with our ranks aside.
We will see who is the better swordsman.
Wait, Dal.
Lady Hae.
I do admire your talent,
but I should have known
better than to trust you.
This will be the last time I summon you.
My apologies.
Master Go, you may also
stop serving my father.
You do not have to pretend
to be loyal any longer.
His Majesty would not have
trusted me if I had only pretended.
I did have a sense of loyalty to him...
for a short while.
As I did to you.
Leave.
Enough of your rudeness.
I will be looking forward to our fight.
Sure.
Just you wait.
Let us go.
Something is going on.
- What?
- Not only Master Go...
but also Go Won Pyo
may be involved in a plot.
I am sure of it.
Ga Jin.
Something does not feel right.
What is it?
Yeom Ga Jin.
Even if you do not
agonize day and night...
Goguryeo will not fall.
How can you be so relaxed?
You do not...
covet the throne, do you?
When you were little, you told me...
that even a woman could become the king.
No.
Never say such an
impertinent thing again.
That is a relief.
Is something wrong?
You should have stayed out of it.
- Should I have remained quiet?
- Yes.
Now that you have shown your hand
to the Princess, what shall you do?
You will lose His Majesty's trust
that you worked so hard for.
Still...
I think I won your heart.
So it was all worth it.
This is not the time for jokes.
I am the one...
who got Du Jung Seo out of prison.
How...
There is no turning back...
or hiding any longer.
Soon...
This palace will belong
to the great Family Go.
See this.
Is this...
what you want?
Or is it General Go's scheme?
What is the difference?
It is for the Gyeru Tribe all the same.
Still...
Commander.
Yes?
You would even risk
your life for our family.
I am well aware of it.
Much obliged.
Soon when the Gyeru Tribe
takes control of Goguryeo...
you will be taking
even more responsibility.
You can trust me, my lord.
General Go.
What is it?
Have you been getting close to
Lady Hae from the herb store lately?
Why do you ask?
I have an informant who tells me...
small things that happen in the capital.
According to him,
Lady Hae disappeared for a few days.
She did?
Rumor has it that...
she was taken to Silla and
barely escaped with her life.
I am doing a little
digging to make sure...
she does not become a nuisance to you.
I will have to ask around as well.
- I appreciate it.
- My pleasure.
- Commander.
- Yes.
This mission is of the
utmost importance.
The Gyeru Tribe is
being closely watched.
With their exclusive rights to salt
taken away and taxes raised,
they must be very unhappy.
They may even put their
grievance into action.
Watching Go Won Pyo's home
is not enough.
Watch his private soldiers as well.
Are you saying...
he may rise in revolt?
Even if he does not, his son may.
Keep a close eye.
Yes.
(Hwangju Fortress)
Look who it is. Is it not the Commander.
It has been a long time, my lord.
It must have been a long journey.
Please come in.
That was close.
This time, you try.
Stop being so sad.
You should keep your chin up,
especially in situations like this.
Stop crying!
I did not know there was a nice
archery field like this here.
Archery is fun. Why are you sniffling?
Your Highness, would you
like to make a bet with me?
A bet?
If I manage to split your arrow
within three tries,
you will never cry again.
You are going to hit
my arrow using your own?
How is that even possible?
If I lose, I will stand
on my head all day long.
- Fine!
- That is absurd.
What was that? You are so bad at it.
That was a practice shot.
What?
Wow! That is amazing.
How did he do this?
How did you train in archery?
I did not train at all.
I only learned by watching over
other's shoulders.
Really?
Won! Hurry over!
Okay.
Thanks to you,
Geon Mu is feeling much better.
Thank you, Dal.
"Dal"?
That is no problem! We are all family,
Won!
He is not the type to give in so easily.
Go Won Pyo must be waiting for revenge.
I am here, but you did not even notice.
- Did you just get here?
- Yes.
What is wrong?
I went to the residence
of the Sunno Tribe.
I wanted to make up with Jin,
but I could not even see her.
Do not be so impatient.
You told me that she
is your special friend.
Okay.
It must be heavy.
I should quit my post
if I feel it is heavy.
What is it?
Instead of being the head
of capital defense today,
let us just hang out.
- What?
- Follow me.
What? Wait!
Hey.
Lady Gongson will be worried
if she finds Magnolia Hall empty.
Come on! Do not be scared.
I want to have snacks
and buy some accessories.
But the ones in the
marketplace are of low quality.
You must own something
much better than them.
There is not one you bought for me.
Why are you yelling?
Follow me.
Come take a look!
Please come take a look!
Welcome.
Come by some arrowroot!
- Wow, is this arrowroot?
- Yes.
Where did you get this? It is so big.
From deep in the mountain.
- Look, this is arrowroot!
- It is a bellflower!
- It is?
- Hurry and follow me!
Wait a minute.
It is a rare herb,
so it is rather pricey.
Thank Lady Hae for me.
Sure.
Please make sure to keep us
updated on the King.
- How is this one?
- It is pretty.
- How about this one?
- That one is pretty too.
What was that?
Do you find everything pretty?
You should pick one for me.
Let me see. What will suit you?
How about this one?
Ga Jin.
Sorry.
Let us just pick one.
You have survived.
Now I get it.
You are on the same side as
Go Geon of the Gyeru Tribe.
You two are forming a scheme, I see.
You are the one who
went back on your promise.
You attacked the King
without discussing with me.
And you even tried to
harm Crown Prince Won.
So what?
There must be a reason why you saved me.
I will let you go.
And I will also give you
a chance to take your revenge.
Gather your followers...
and assassinate the King.
You want me to plot conspiracy?
Do not worry.
The Gyeru Tribe will
take care of the rest...
once you assassinate the King.
I will punish the King,
and you will justify your conduct
of dominating the kingdom?
I will support you with all the
weapons and funds you need.
What about afterward?
If I become useless,
you are bound to kill me.
I am sure there is
nothing for you to lose.
Hey. If it were not for me,
you would have died...
without ever getting your revenge.
So what will you do?
This will spread all over your body.
10 days later,
it will mess up your blood flow.
If you do not wish to
die by vomiting blood,
you will have to get
an antidote from me.
Without your petty game,
I will not run anyway.
Then show me.
I do not wish...
to fight with you.
Tara Jin, did you think you
will live after betraying us?
Stop it.
What does this mean again?
Did you forget already?
- What does this mean?
- I know what it means.
It is a token that says that
we are on the same side.
You are smart.
We are on the same side,
and we are married.
The Goguryeo you dream of,
the empire you want to build,
I will live there too.
So make your dream come true.
I...
only came here to become your sword.
Ga Jin is the King's
daughter, after all.
What matters to her is
her father and Goguryeo.
But you are not even from Goguryeo,
and you lost your only brother.
That is all because of Ga Jin.
I fought with her as her friend.
You are only being used.
That is not true.
I am the one...
who raised and taught the pair of you.
Are you saying you value
your friendship more than my grace?
You and I do not belong to Goguryeo.
Remember the spirit of Cheonjubang.
(Hwangju Fortress)
I am already very angry.
How could he make the governors...
pay more tax to win the people's favor?
The Princess and the King...
are both fools!
That is why Gochuga put you
on an important task.
Starting with Hwangju Fortress,
if governors of each region
oppose the proposal,
the Gyeru Tribe will
take care of the rest.
Go back and tell this to Gochuga.
I, Yang Chaek, will gladly
disobey the King's order!
Gochuga will highly praise...
your bravery.
I hope so.
(Hwangju Fortress)
If Hwangju Fortress rises in revolt,
the nearby governors will join in too.
As soon as he does,
the soldiers of the
capital will be dispatched.
How will you take care of that?
I talked with General Nam,
and he already discussed it with
the officers under his command.
Well done.
If you pull this off,
I will place you on the throne.
Father.
I will step back and
support you from behind.
My Goguryeo...
will become a great nation
that has never existed before.
I will bring Silla and
Baekje to their knees,
and I will rule over...
the areas which Gwanggaeto
the Great governed and beyond...
under the flag of Goguryeo.
I must live a healthy and long life...
to see your Goguryeo.
What did you just say?
You and your brother
wanted to go back...
to your country when you
were done being assassins.
To the plains where the Gokturks are.
So...
are you telling me I can go?
It is not for me to decide.
You should have done
however you wanted to,
but I naturally thought
you would stay by my side...
and help me.
I only thought about myself.
Ga Jin.
You must have had
a hard time after San left.
I have been too inattentive,
and I am sorry.
About the chief though...
Are you not worried about him
at all when he ran away like that?
I am sure he will show up one day.
I am waiting.
You are?
I should have killed him then.
I will make sure not
to lose him next time.
Why did she want to see
you so early in the morning?
Was it about the fight we
had with the Gyeru Tribe?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Pung Gae.
You are a great shot.
Who did you learn archery from?
Master Go.
I know my sister has
past affairs with him,
but please do not hate him so much, Dal.
We should have a match
among the three of us next time.
Why do you not try again?
Master Go deceived both you and Won.
Are you saying he was
abetted by Go Won Pyo?
He could have been,
but he could have acted on his own.
Those evil jerks.
I presume the Gyeru Tribe...
is scheming something.
Scheming something?
There is a spy...
planted by Gochuga who
is living in your chambers.
Are you talking about Head Eunuch?
I know about him.
Father.
I was in a fuddled state when I
was drunk on alcohol and drugs,
but now I can see clearly.
I know he is Go Won Pyo's servant.
But why are you keeping him next to you?
I am guessing he will
be useful to use as bait...
to catch Go Won Pyo.
Your Majesty, Governor Yang
of Hwangju Fortress...
raised a revolt with his soldiers.
What did you say?
(Yang Chaek,
the governor of Hwangju Fortress)
- I will go, Your Majesty.
- Dal.
It is not a matter for you to meddle in.
We have a separate troop
to subdue the traitors.
That is the only way...
the Princess will be at ease.
Dal, it does not have to be you.
Then who would else come forward?
I will go.
Trust me.
Please let me go.
Gochuga, are you out of your mind?
How could you plan a conspiracy?
It is not a conspiracy but a corollary.
I am only straightening
out the things...
the King and the Princess did wrong.
Hwangju Fortress has
less than 2,000 soldiers.
The most they can come up
with is a mere 3,000.
By the time the King's troop reaches...
The King's troop is on our side.
- What?
- The commander who is in charge...
of suppressing the revolts
is General Nam.
He promised that he will
not fight against them...
even if the King gave him an order.
Including General Nam,
the commanders under his lead
decided to follow my order.
Well done! Then I will be at ease.
Then what is your next plan?
If the other regions start to revolt,
I will honor their wishes
and raise an army.
I will invade the King's chamber
and bring him down.
- Lord Gochuga.
- We are in the middle of something.
Stay outside.
The King's son-in-law is leading
the troop to Hwangju Fortress.
What?
On Dal is leading the troop?
This is karma.
This is ill-fated karma.
(River Where the Moon Rises)
I, Princess Pyeonggang,
will be so bold as to accept
the role of Head of Bodyguards.
I will become like Go Won Pyo...
if I can only take him down.
I am fighting for you, so you can...
Are you saying you became my sword?
You said you did all that for me,
but you went against my will.
- Face the reality!
- He is dead.
If you want to save the Prince,
then be on the winning side.
The winning side?
I cannot just stand by and
watch my lady become evil...
like Go Won Pyo.
Your Majesty.
I will enter the palace
as his subject in daylight,
but I will become the King by nightfall.
I am sorry, Dal.