(This is based on the Tale of On Dal
in Chronicles of the Three States.)
(Characters, incidents, and dates
do not match historical facts.)
Is this...
Gochuga's will?
What does it matter?
It is for the Gyeru Tribe.
I, Yang Chaek,
will gladly disobey the King's order!
If you pull this off,
I will place you on the throne.
My Goguryeo...
will become a great nation
that has never existed before.
I must live a healthy and long life...
to see your Goguryeo.
Your Majesty, Governor Yang
of Hwangju Fortress...
raised a revolt with his soldiers.
I will go, Your Majesty.
The King's son-in-law is leading
the troop to Hwangju Fortress.
(Episode 16)
Commander.
Yes?
This mission is of
the utmost importance.
We must go.
What are you doing?
Once we are done at Hwangju Fortress,
kill Go Sang Cheol quietly.
Why would you... Why...
"A tongue that lost control
is the root of all evil."
That is General Go's message.
What do you mean Commander Go is dead?
I apologize. It is my fault.
I realized the Princess
had bribed him...
and was looking into it.
- He was bribed?
- Yes.
He would not do such a thing.
Did you corner him
with just a suspicion?
I meant to question him on our return.
He caught on and tried to run away.
He even fought our own men.
I apologize, Father.
If the Princess bribed
Commander Go as well,
that will affect our plan.
Rest assured.
I checked on the King and the Princess,
and fortunately, nothing got out.
One wrong step and we
will fall from a steep cliff.
There cannot be a single mistake.
I will remember that.
I took care of Commander Go
to avoid the worst.
But for a while, we must lie low.
For our mission and...
to keep you safe,
I must hold back even if I miss you.
If one prospers, the other will too,
and if crushed,
we will be buried together.
That is our future, General Go.
If it is by your side,
I would not even mind
if it is in a hole in the ground.
This came from Jangbaek herb store.
Nanny.
Yes?
Do not be so uneasy.
This is Magnolia Hall.
It is where you raised me.
I will...
do as you say.
I know you do not trust me,
but for one last time,
I will show you my loyalty.
I have located Du Jung Seo.
Princess, I will come in.
Do you have news from Hwangju Fortress?
It is not about that.
I got a report from a soldier
who is watching the Gyeru Tribe.
Commander Go Sang Cheol
was brought back lifeless.
Go Sang Cheol is dead?
He left a few days ago
on urgent business.
His destination was Hwangju Fortress.
I apologize for the past.
My lord's command comes first.
All her loyal subjects left for battle.
The Princess will come alone.
I will cut her down as soon as she does.
You will do what?
You will lose your lives before
you can even draw your swords.
Lie in wait,
then attack at once when
I spray the sleeping powder.
You have only one opportunity.
Lady Sa.
Lady Sa!
What did you dream of...
that you moaned so much?
It was nothing.
Go back to sleep.
Go to sleep.
What is wrong with you?
I will get some water.
Oh, dear.
Lady Sa.
Lady Sa. Drink this.
Do you feel better?
Show yourself.
Do you think she caught on?
The Princess is not
destined to die tonight.
You can leave.
General.
The Princess is here.
I know Go Won Pyo is behind this revolt.
Or was it Go Geon?
I know already, so answer me.
The Gyeru Tribe was behind it.
Confess.
We will reduce the sentence
as best we can.
Do you call a beheading...
instead of a quartering
a reduced sentence?
I will die anyway.
My remaining family...
has a better chance of survival
with Gochuga than the King.
- You fool.
- Stop.
I will sort this out.
Return to Pyeongyang Castle.
Sort what out?
Bring the governor's family immediately.
I will see how many lives
it takes to make you talk.
Yes, Your Highness.
Dal. Were you hurt?
You mean to just scare him, right?
You said that...
to make him talk, right?
No.
If he refuses to speak,
I might draw blood.
How can you do that?
Do not speak so innocently.
Go Won Pyo and his son
are prancing about like mad.
They could bring down
the whole royal household.
Whatever it takes,
I must prove their wrongdoing.
They are a traitor's family.
Even if they are lucky
to avoid a beheading,
they will become slaves.
You can stop that, as the princess.
I cannot do that
because I am the princess.
The laws are set in stone,
and what is right and wrong is clear.
How can I let them off?
I do not know about laws,
but I want to save the
innocent family members.
Making the governor confess...
and punishing Go Won Pyo and his son.
That is our only option right now.
I fought the traitors like crazy...
and was reminded of my childhood.
The Gyeru Tribe that
slaughtered my tribe.
Go Won Pyo's men.
But...
last night, I was Go Won Pyo.
I slashed, stabbed,
and cut down people to no end.
Do not do that.
I will do all the killing.
You keep your distance.
A princess can do that.
Before I was a princess,
I was a killer.
I went to unfamiliar places...
and killed people I did not know.
When I got home,
I had bad dreams every night.
Those dreadful memories are in here.
They plague me even now.
All this was brought on...
by Go Won Pyo.
The lives you took here,
and you and me too.
We are like this because of his greed.
So what?
You have no choice yet again?
That is right.
If it is to take down Go Won Pyo,
I will become like him.
My wife,
my woman...
wants to become evil, like Go Won Pyo.
I cannot let that happen.
Dal.
Dal!
- General!
General!
- General! No!
- General!
Giddy-up!
A revolt?
Juam Fortress rose up?
Muwon Fortress nearby
is also acting suspiciously.
I guess Yang Chaek is not...
the only governor who
participated in the plot.
Your Majesty.
A signal fire was lit at
Jangryeong Fortress.
What? Jangryeong Fortress too?
Hwangju Fortress was suppressed...
- and Yang Chaek...
- He lit the fire.
He did his duty.
I did not expect the Princess
would send On Dal to suppress them.
If things all went to plan,
it would be an ordinary revolt
and not a grand one.
By now, Juam, Muwon,
and Jangryeong Fortress too...
will have risen up.
Now, it is all about time.
I will arm our men in secret.
The Sono and Gwanno Tribes
will join you.
Nothing must go wrong.
Yes, Father.
I was waiting for your command.
Not yet?
It is taking a while.
Ga Jin would be angry.
Why did he kill the governor
without permission?
Dal messed up this time.
Dal is in charge.
Is he higher than the Princess?
Who do you think got him the title?
Did Dal join the fight to get promoted?
He fought against
his will for his country.
He volunteered because
he is the only person...
the Princess can trust.
Good for you.
What is wrong with her lately?
The King sent me here
with full military authority.
I am not here as the Princess
and your wife.
I am here in the King's place.
Poachers use something called...
a toothed noose.
Pins are set into a rope like teeth.
Deer cannot break free
once they are caught.
The more they struggle,
the deeper the pins dig in.
If you find a deer caught in one,
you must kill it.
Even if you cut it loose,
it can only limp until it becomes
a wolf or wildcat's prey.
Yang Chaek is not a deer.
He is a traitor who was
bought by Go Won Pyo.
And you...
disobeyed the King to kill him.
Just so you do not have to kill...
You became my sword?
You say it is for me,
but you go against me in public?
I did not do it with glee.
I feel disgusted.
I can still smell the blood.
Face reality!
Do you even know how precarious
Pyeongyang Castle is?
Stop talking about politics!
This is between us two.
What shall I do?
Tell me.
What must I do to appease you?
Please tell me, Ga Jin.
Dal.
You cannot do anything like this.
Return to the capital.
Leave things here to me.
We have a messenger
from Pyeongyang Castle.
Juam and Muwon Fortresses too?
Yes. He commanded you
to quell those revolts too.
Regroup and arm the men.
We leave tonight.
Before the traitors can join forces.
We must crush them separately.
Right. We will be prepared.
Come along.
What about General On?
He will return to the capital.
I agree.
He needs to rest.
He is very tired.
I will continue to lead our troops.
You hurry back to Pyeongyang Castle.
We are already finished discussing that.
I know I was wrong.
I am sorry.
I messed everything up
by killing the governor.
So you should hurry back to the capital.
We do not know what Go Won Pyo
and his son may be up to.
And you are the only person
who can stop them.
I am not asking you as your husband.
It is a suggestion I make...
as a general of Goguryeo
to protect the royal family.
It is not about us...
but the entire empire.
I, General Go Geon, am ready
to receive a royal command.
You may stand up.
Since the invasion of the Northern Zhou,
it has become even more
important to protect the borders.
Therefore,
I would like to appoint you
to an important post.
Are you sending me to the border?
A group of rebels...
is disturbing the empire.
In situations like this,
it becomes crucial to prepare
against foreign enemies.
Who will be...
in charge of guarding the palace?
Princess Pyeonggang at your service.
I am honored to be appointed
the Head of Bodyguards.
(Head of Bodyguards:
Commander of the king's bodyguards)
Welcome.
Put your status as
a princess aside for now.
As the Head of Bodyguards,
keep the palace and
the royal family safe.
As you wish, Your Majesty.
What are you afraid of?
I am not afraid. I am surprised.
Throughout the empire,
there is no place that Go Won Pyo's
evil influence has not reached.
General On Dal will successfully
suppress the rebellion.
Do not worry, Your Majesty. Also,
I will keep the palace
under close guard.
Once the bodyguards are reorganized,
the level of surveillance on
the Gyeru Tribe will be increased.
(Surveillance: Keeping a close watch)
I need rest.
Is there anything else that
you would like me to do?
No. You may leave now.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Is anyone there?
Your Majesty.
Look who it is.
What is that?
General Go.
Some say that a second
feels like three years.
But for me, it felt like ten.
I missed you.
You need not tell me...
what I already know.
Head Eunuch told me that...
the King asked for medicine.
Yes.
He kept away for a while,
but he suddenly asked for it today.
He must be terribly anxious.
Of course.
The royal family is in dire danger.
I prepared the medicine
much stronger than usual.
For the next few days,
he will not be able to think straight.
I heard that you are being
sent to a fortress up north.
Before that,
I will put my plan into action.
As the Head of Bodyguards,
the Princess will fight back.
But with On Dal away
and the King intoxicated,
she will not be able to do much.
Still,
never let your guard down.
In a few days,
Goguryeo will see a new king.
He will rise up in revolt soon.
You cannot hide a nail in a sack.
When he feels that he
cannot wait any longer,
he will take action
without waiting for a cause.
The Gyeru Tribe's private armies
alone are extremely strong.
With the Gwanno Tribe
and the Sono Tribe's help,
they will be hard to beat.
Uncle, have you sent a message
to the Jeollo Tribe yet?
I have.
But they are too far away.
Even if they rush here as soon
as they get the message,
it will take at least 10 days.
Ten days.
Until the Jeollo Tribe's
armies arrive...
and General On comes back
after suppressing the rebellion,
we will have to stall for time.
Do you think the rebellion
will be suppressed soon?
We have no choice but to believe so.
We must trust General On...
and wait.
- Charge!
Get them!
Lady Sa.
Lady Sa! You are coughing up blood.
Stop making a fuss. Bring me some water.
Should I go down to Ghost Valley
and get some medicinal herbs?
I do not need medicine.
- Weol.
- Yes?
As soon as you wake up tomorrow,
pack up.
"Pack"? Where are we going?
If you know where we are going,
you will not come with me?
I will be okay.
Vicious rumors have reached
even the people at remote temples.
They were worried that
our empire might be divided.
Do not worry about the imperial palace.
Go back to the temple.
How could I not worry?
If there is a bloodbath at the palace,
no one will protect my son.
Please promise me...
that you will do whatever
it takes to keep my son safe.
Before you give me your word,
I will not return.
When you were kicked out of the palace,
do you know why I did not
challenge the Princess?
It is because the King's days
are numbered.
When the new world has come,
you can take your time to
come back to the palace.
Then, my son will be safe. Right?
Are you not ill anymore?
Our empire is in confusion.
I had to do something.
Go Won Pyo will not
let Prince Geon Mu live.
That will be the case
for Go Geon as well.
They must know that the
Prince will be a problem later.
Why would they show mercy on the Prince?
I do not follow you.
They are stepbrothers,
but they are very close.
Crown Prince Won can pass down
the crown to Prince Geon Mu.
If you want to save the Prince... No.
If you want to see him
ascend to the throne,
choose the winning side.
The winning side?
Then,
are you saying the Gyeru Tribe
is fighting a losing battle?
Yes. They will lose.
Lord Hae of the Sono Tribe
has already sided with our family.
I am sure you know...
he is the best person to
calculate gains and losses.
Your petty trick will not work on me.
My trick may be petty or grand.
Think carefully about it.
General On.
Dal.
It is dead.
What?
I did not kill it, but this guy just...
No. Did I kill it?
Pung Gae. Did I kill it?
What are you talking about?
No, you did not.
It is chilly at night.
I am afraid you might catch a cold.
Nanny.
I cannot see the moon.
The moon is always in the sky.
It is just hiding behind the cloud.
Will it come back out?
It will, right?
A silver mine?
Let me get this straight.
You have found a silver mine...
from the territory you have gotten back?
Yes, that is right.
Given how widely it spreads,
the scale of the mine...
What did the Princess say about that?
Upon the discovery of silver mines,
it is required by law...
that they are returned to the empire.
I have not told her yet.
Our empire is on
the edge of a precipice.
I cannot tell who will come out
as victors of this fight.
(A situation that could
bring a disaster at any minute)
To be honest,
keeping our tribe safe
is our first priority.
That is true.
That is why...
I asked to meet you quietly.
You are the most experienced
in matters such as these.
If you want to dig
silver out of the mine,
you must think about mining,
transportation, and refinery.
It will cost a fortune
to take care of this.
That is why...
What do you think about...
keeping this between us and
proceeding with this business?
Lord Hae!
You are here too, Lord Sa.
Excuse me. I have things
to take care of.
- Bye.
- Wait.
Goodness.
It looks like you and
Lord Sa of the Sunno Tribe were...
having an important conversation
this early in the morning.
Important? No. We were just
talking about the weather.
Is this something...
Gochuga and I should not be aware of?
How could you ask me
something like that?
I am not some subordinate
of the Gyeru Tribe.
Must I tell him everything
when I am exchanging pleasantries?
I have my pride! Unbelievable.
"Pride"?
My Queen!
What did you find out, Father?
You were right.
Seeing how flustered Lord Hae was,
I am sure he is siding with the King.
We are in a predicament.
If we support the Gyeru Tribe,
our entire family might
face a deadly disaster.
(A disaster that could
wipe out an entire family)
What should we do?
You said the uprising
will happen soon, correct?
Whether it is the royal family
or the Gyeru Tribe,
we must choose one.
I hear the King wanted to see you.
I bet he is not in his right mind
as he must be high on drugs.
Why did he want to see you?
I guess he wants to die
faster than we thought.
We will carry it out tonight.
I will enter the palace
as a subject in daylight,
but I will become
its owner by nightfall.
Yes, Father.
Gochuga of the Gyeru Tribe
is here, Your Majesty.
Really? Is that what happened?
Oh, look. It is Gochuga.
Did you call for him?
Did you want to show him
the state I am in?
You told him to come see you,
Your Majesty.
I did?
That is strange.
Anyway, since you are here,
please take a seat.
Why did I tell Gochuga to come see me?
There must be a reason I called him.
If it is not something urgent,
you can take your time to tell me.
Why do you not take a rest,
Your Majesty?
Oh, I remember now!
There is a rat roaming
around the palace,
and I want you to catch it.
I caught the rat who told Gochuga...
that you were looking for some medicine.
You have been living off the money
Gochuga has been paying, right?
I am falsely accused.
That is not true, Your Majesty...
You must go back to your chambers,
Royal Consort Hyeon.
From now, I am going to
punish the traitor for his crimes.
What do you mean?
Are you saying Father is
in custody at the palace?
Yes, General. Head Eunuch
was beheaded on the spot.
General Go, what shall we do?
Inform the Gwanno and
Sono Tribes immediately.
Tell them to be armed...
and go straight to the palace.
Yes, General!
Mo Yong!
Did the soldiers of our tribe
depart already?
I dispatched them just now.
But it seems Gochuga...
fell into a trap.
It is okay as long as
General Go is safe.
He will lead the revolt to success.
Wait.
- Are you from the Sono Tribe?
- Yes, General.
- What about the Gwanno Tribe?
- I have not seen them yet.
- Let us go.
- Let us go!
You led armed soldiers
to the palace at this hour.
You could be punished for revolt.
This is not a revolt.
You are being harsh, Your Highness.
How can a son just sit back and watch...
when his father is being
detained within the palace?
He is having a conversation
with the King.
He will return home when it is over,
so take your soldiers away.
Since we are here anyway,
we will escort him home.
I told you to go away.
I will wait.
So General Go must be here
with his private army.
He is a filial son, you see.
You will only need to say a word.
If you tell them to give up their arms,
you will be able to spare many lives.
You should...
spare their lives yourself.
Do you covet the throne that much?
Enough to shed blood?
You have been...
on the throne for too long.
If you give up the throne,
the internal strife will subside.
(A dispute or conflict among
the members of a group)
I feel sorry for you.
Whose side...
do you think the Gwanno Tribe will take?
- Are you from the Gwanno Tribe?
- Yes, General.
- I see that you made it.
Get moving!
Royal Consort Jin is
from the Gwanno Tribe.
Did you think they would stand
against the royal household...
just because they are
afraid of the Gyeru Tribe?
Your Majesty,
the Gwanno Tribe has joined us.
Lord Sa.
The Gyeru Tribe is in terminal decline,
but I guess Gochuga is the
only one who cannot see that.
Go Won Pyo.
Either you and your son will die alone,
or your entire tribe will be massacred.
You should make your decision.
Dismiss your private army
and surrender immediately.
That was Gochuga's order!
He is lying! Do not be shaken!
- It is over, Master Go.
- No, it is not.
Only my father's plan is over.
My plan has not even begun.
Take up arms!
Give up, Master Go.
You will have to kill me
for this to be over.
I do not wish to do that.
Fine. Then I will finish this.
Come at me if you want to die!
I will slice...
even the last piece of your flesh...
and the last piece of your bone.
You should leave with Father.
What do you mean? What about you?
There is someone I need to save.
Are you talking about General Go Geon?
He is as good as dead.
What are you planning to do?
Please leave with him.
I do not even know
where we are fleeing to.
How can I just follow him?
I am only trying to pay you
back for taking me in.
Please trust me.
Hurry!
Mo Yong!
Let us go.
(Jangbaek)
Find him!
- Find Hae Ji Weol!
- Find him!
- Look everywhere!
Find Hae Ji Weol!
Find him!
- Keep quiet!
- Get me out of here!
- Quiet down!
- Shut it!
- Let me go!
- Get me out of here!
Let me go!
Quiet down! Be quiet!
Is this...
Is this mess...
what you really wanted?
You should have told us to fight
even if it meant death!
Even if the two of us die,
the Gyeru Tribe has to live on.
Father. You are the Gyeru Tribe itself.
Do you not get it?
I will not fail like you did.
You brought me into this world,
but I will decide...
how I die.
If you do not wish to
die by vomiting blood,
you will have to get
an antidote from me.
(Silla, Seorabeol)
The internal disturbance in Goguryeo
is getting more interesting.
When things are chaotic on the inside,
it gives us a good opportunity
to attack them.
This is a golden opportunity
to take back Adan Fortress.
Yes, Your Majesty.
The troops are already waiting
for your command, Your Majesty.
Dispatch the troops to
Adan Fortress immediately...
and drive out the Goguryeo people.
I will convey your order, Your Majesty.
Is he waiting outside?
Bring him in!
That is not necessary.
Are you Hae Ji Weol of the
Sono Tribe from Goguryeo?
That is right, Your Majesty.
Welcome to Silla.
I hear you are good at
calculating gains and losses.
You should use
your ability for Silla's gain.
You are too kind, Your Majesty.
I promise...
that you will be able to
come to Silla in glory...
when Goguryeo falls.
I am here to meet your chief.
A breach of prison?
You usually have good judgment,
but you are being foolish.
As I promised with Go Geon,
I only need to kill the King.
It is not my duty to get him
and his father out of prison.
When things change,
the promises can be altered too.
I need killers to bring to the prison.
Do you dare to give me an order?
It is not an order. It is a solution.
It is the only solution
that can save your life.
You need to take the
antidote in two days.
Otherwise,
you will die...
by bleeding from every
orifice in your body.
I can torture you until
you hand over the antidote.
I would love to see you try.
Let us see if I confess first...
or if you die before that.
Do not do that.
I reek of blood.
Ga Jin.
Am I...
a complete fool?
Who told you that?
I did.
Saying that makes you a complete fool.
It is okay as long
as you do not think...
I am a fool.
The water was...
so sweet and refreshing.
The water from the well we dug together.
It was as clear as morning dew.
Do you think it still is?
Of course.
This does not taste like
the water from the well.
Because it is stained with blood.
I am sorry, Dal.
I am sorry for everything.
Do not be sorry.
I will go if you tell me to go...
and stop if you want me to stop.
(River Where the Moon Rises)
Why did you...
Why?
Why did you betray me?
She said she is completely sick of us.
She is sick of all of us,
including Ga Jin.
I have chosen you as
the next chief of Cheonjubang.
Are you going to betray my kindness?
I know that you are a spy from Silla.
As soon as this is over,
I will behead you and send
your head to the King of Silla.
I hear you killed
more than 100 traitors.
How did it feel?
You want to know
what it is like to kill a man?
Have you decided on what to do
with Go Won Pyo and his son?
I have decided to execute them...
first thing tomorrow.
My goodness. My son.
Please allow my son, Dal,
to go back to our village with me.
I do not wish to go back
to the village at all,
so do not be ridiculous.
I am only trying to help you breathe...
because I am your mother.
Son, is that you?
Your Majesty!
I see that you are still alive.