♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 12=
Don’t be afraid.
I’ll protect you afterwards.
Am I dead?
Silly girl. You’re still alive.
Who are you?
I’m Qingqing’s brother,
Long Yuchi.
Yuchi.
You’re wounded.
Have some more sleep.
Yuchi…
My Lord,
no matter how wonderful
this world is,
your Luofeng Pavilion
is the best place.
It’s so complicated here
with many bad places,
and my place is the worst.
And I have nothing
to entertain you in my place.
My Lord, please go back.
It’s OK.
A pot of tea is enough.
My Lord! You…
Big surprise today!
As long as you can
finish my ten cakes
with the time of a cup of tea…
Osmanthus House!
You can take them home for free.
Miss, come and have a look.
We have pea cakes, kidney bean rolls,
sugar steamed cakes, lotus cakes,
chrysanthemum cakes,
crabapple cakes, green bean cakes,
soybean cakes,
rose cakes and glutinous rice rolls.
Anything you want.
Then, I’ll help myself.
Miss, let me tell you
the rule first.
If you can finish the ten cakes
within the time
of a cup of tea,
they will all be free.
You don’t need to pay.
But if you can’t finish them,
it’s OK, you just need to pay for
what you eat.
Is it a good deal?
It’s not a surprise at all.
You just trick her to buy your cakes.
If I can’t finish them, I’ll just write
my name,
Long Qingqing, backwards.
Good for you!
Long Qingqing?
Why is your surname Long?
Say it!
It was Yuchi Longyan who sent me
to Yuchi Town.
They asked my name,
so I told them I was surnamed Long.
Don’t waste my time. It’s almost up.
You’re my maid.
Why didn’t you say your surname is Xue?
I…
Stop! Time is up!
Miss,
you need to pay for the nine cakes.
I can give you a discount.
180 pennies.
180 pennies?
That’s too much!
Isn’t it a good deal?
You wasted my time.
I have no money.
My Lord.
My Lord?
Miss, seems that today
you need to write your name
Long Qingqing backwards.
Ask the one surnamed Long
to pay for you.
No! No! My Lord!
You can’t leave! Are you a deadbeat?
You know what? My shop has been here
for a hundred years.
There has never been a repudiation.
You want to dine and dash?
Silver?
This sir is so generous!
So handsome!
From now on, I’m Xue Qingqing!
This one, this one, and those.
Pack them up! Keep the change.
Thank you, Miss.
Xue Qingqing,
can’t you notice that the cup is empty?
My Lord, can you
not call my full name?
It sounds weird.
It’s not weird to be surnamed Long,
but it’s weird to use my surname?
No…
Then, is Bingxing also surnamed Xue?
Of course not!
How could everyone take my surname?
Then…
Why should I take your surname?
My Lord, I’m sorry!
I didn’t do it on purpose! My bad!
-Let me help you…
-Xue Qingqing!
My Lord, don’t worry!
I’ll clean your clothes.
-Please don’t be angry.
-Xue Qingqing!
It’s a silk garment woven by
ten thousand snow silkworms.
How should I punish you?
Again?
Sorry, I forgot that you said
I couldn’t wipe two places with
the same rag.
I will write this line for 50 times.
But please don’t take me back to
Luofeng Pavilion.
If you take me back there, you will…
You will see me every day.
That means
I’ll always make you troubles.
You just don’t want to go back?
Since you don’t want to serve me,
go to Ayu now.
Really?
My Lord! That’s so nice of you!
No one can be sweeter
than you!
Then, I’m going.
Don’t come back if you want to go.
Who are you talking about?
Why is Qingqing running so fast?
Where is she going?
None of your business.
And, remember,
she is now Xue Qingqing,
not Long Qingqing.
I’m OK with it.
Thank you for your help
on the mountain.
Don’t bother.
I just thought Qingqing’s crying
was annoying.
So I did her a favor.
Qingqing?
You do care about her.
Nonsense.
“Don’t come back if you want to go.”
It’s said to Qingqing, right?
What?
You must be upset
to see me instead of her.
You came to my home and said
you were just passing by.
But you did that so many times.
You say you don’t like her crying
and you gave her your last name.
You just like her.
I like Qingqing?
Impossible.
That’s duplicity.
The more you say it’s impossible,
the more it’s possible.
You must like Qingqing a lot.
You still run around
with internal injuries.
So brave.
I don’t have internal injuries.
Really?
I can cure myself.
I don’t need your help.
Now we are connected by power.
If you remove your hand now,
both of us will be hurt.
Now you’re too weak
to protect your beloved
who is always in trouble.
Don’t move!
Yes, right. Don’t move.
I just came back for the cakes.
I’ll leave right away.
Don’t worry.
I don’t see anything
and I won’t say anything.
You can keep on.
You can’t remove your hands while
transferring energy.
Yuchi.
Ayu, you’re awake!
Do you feel better now?
Yes, I’m fine now.
Qingqing,
how long have I slept?
I remember that
after I went to see the little wolf,
I had a dream,
in which you had a brother.
It’s not a dream. I do have a brother.
He just came back from a long trip.
Is he Yuchi?
What? You call him Yuchi?
He told you his name is Yuchi?
Yes, he told me.
I guess he was also born in Yuchi Town.
That’s why he has this name.
When I was a kid,
my father wanted to name me Yu.
Yes, right.
He was also born in Yuchi Town.
What a destiny.
Dragon King is so smart.
Liuying only called him Dragon King.
Now Ayu can call him Yuchi.
Qingqing,
how did I come back?
You went to the Hunter Cave
with Zhiyong to see the little wolf
and then the cave caught fire.
Luckily my brother passed by and
helped you out.
It was Yuchi who saved me?
Then…
What about Zhiyong?
Zhiyong…
He is dead.
Ayu,
the fire was too big.
When my brother got you out,
Zhiyong was already dying.
Now you are still weak.
You need more rest.
We can talk about
the other things later.
(Tomb of Zhiyong)
Yuxiang.
What’s wrong?
Bad news!
What bad news?
Big bad news! Zhiyong died!
What are you talking about?
I’ll beat you if you keep
talking nonsense.
It’s true!
There was a fire
in Hunter Cave yesterday,
and Zhiyong was in there.
Why did
Zhiyong go to Hunter Cave?
I heard that he went with Ayu to see
the little wolf which was just caught.
Then the cave suddenly caught fire.
Everything was burnt away
but Ayu is safe and sound.
What a jinx!
She got her mom dead
and now she got Zhiyong dead as well!
Yuxiang…
Zhiyong died.
What’s the point for me of living alone?
What should I do?
Don’t be sad.
I can make a lot of
delicious food for you.
Ayu is such a hoodoo.
She murdered Zhiyong.
I have to revenge Zhiyong.
Is this going to be a dragon?
Don’t be afraid.
I’ll protect you afterwards.
Is that a dream
or reality?
Yuchi…
Silly girl.
Of course it’s true.
What?
I feel like
I heard Yuchi’s voice.
You still recognize me.
Come and have a look! Fresh fish!
They are just caught today!
Let me see.
-How much is it?
-Only one tael and three pennies.
-It looks good.
-They are fresh. Have a look.
You evil girl!
You burnt Zhiyong to death.
And now you came to the market.
Are you going to murder someone?
And you daredevils!
You even dare to buy her fish!
Who are you talking about?
You!
OK, if I’m an evil girl,
I will burn you
with my evil fire tonight!
If you are still alive tomorrow,
that means I’m not an evil girl.
Don’t be unreasonable.
I’d like to see
who dare to buy your fish today.
Really?
All fish are on sale today!
Only one penny for each!
Really? Only one penny?
I want this one!
OK.
Line up, please!
This one. This one is good.
So ignorant!
You came to my home and said
you were just passing by.
But you did that so many times.
You say you don’t like her crying
and you gave her your last name.
You just like her.
How does it feel to like someone?
How come Lord of Luofeng Pavilion
has time today?
Have some tea?
No, thanks.
Immortal, I want to ask you
how it feels to…
You promised to look up my
punishment for me last time.
Any information?
It’s pretty weird.
I’ve looked through all the records
but still found nothing.
Then…
What else can I do for you?
Immortal,
I’m curious.
You’ve made so many fates.
Then…
How does a man know
which woman he likes?
Well…
In fact, very few people
don’t know who they like.
What if there is such a case?
Actually, love is a simple thing.
You just need to take actions
to woo the one you love.
If you’re not tired of it
and it’s even happier than
being an immortal after you get her,
then you must love her.
That’s the feelings of love?
Steamed buns!
Fried bread stick!
Cakes!
Steamed buns!
Woo her?
Then it must mean to give her presents.
What presents should I give her?
This one is pretty.
Then, let’s buy this one.
OK.
Thank you!
Do you like it?
It’s so cute!
Sachet! Sachet!
Sir, my sachets are the best.
Here is the new
Dragon Boat Festival sachet
with great embroidery. You can use it
yourself or give it out as a gift.
Pack it up.
OK!
Thank you, sir!
Here you are.
Welcome again!
Sachet! Sachet!
Dragon Boat Festival sachet!
Ward off evil spirits!
Bird demon, cat demon, fox demon,
all will be driven away!
Miss, have a look!
(Blessing)
Ward off evil spirits?
We…
Demons are not all evil.
What’s more,
bird demon is not like fox demon.
I don’t want it.
I don’t care what way you use,
you have to find a way
to deal with Ayu.
Just leave it to me.
Don’t be too angry.
It’s not good for your health.
Only you’re willing
to help me since childhood.
Yuxiang,
your business is my business.
As long as you ask,
I will always…
Help you at all cost.
What brings you here?
You know what?
I can’t go back with you now.
I need to accompany Ayu.
Luofeng Pavilion doesn’t need you
for now.
Take this.
What’s it?
Food? Or something to use?
Cosmetics?
What day is it today?
You even give me a gift!
It’s not a gift.
It seems to suit you.
So I bought it by the way.
As expected,
she is so surprised just like those
women by the stall.
Dragon Boat Festival sachet!
Ward off evil spirits!
Bird demon, cat demon, fox demon,
all will be driven away!
You do this on purpose?
What do you mean?
Yes, I’m an evil demon
and you’re a noble immortal!
Thank you, My Lord.
It’s so rare for you
to give me such a nice gift.
On such a special day,
how about having a drink to celebrate?
Osmanthus wine.
One pot for each of us.
Let’s see who’ll get drunk first.
My Lord, you first.
My Lord, you’re always so nice to me.
I’ll drink it up first to show respect.
I don’t believe that I can lose
with osmanthus water.
Good drinker! One more!
Cheers!
My Lord, have another cup.
What a good drinker! Come on!
Cheers!
You can make replications?
My Lord, don’t you remember?
My power is sealed. I can’t.
But I can hold grudges.
Dislike me because I’m a demon?
Let’s see how I help you to ward off
evil spirits.
Finished!
What are you laughing at?
Nothing.
I’m just happy.
I’m happy, too.
Let’s go to watch Dragon Boats Racing.
Now?
Let’s me clean these up first.
He’ll be laughed at if he goes out
like this.
Then I won’t be his maid anymore.
I’ll just go to the line and wait
for my reincarnation.
What are you waiting for?
Don’t waste time. Let’s go.
Wait! Wait.
Are you really going now?
Let me find you a hat.
Or an umbrella.
The sun is too hot.
This is the symbol of Bird King.
You’re the Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
This exalted status befits yours.
Sorry! My bad! I’m wrong!
I don’t dare to do it again. I…
Sorry!
You think
I’ll beat you just for this?
I’m this mean
in your mind?
Of course not!
Look at me.
I’m being childish again.
You’re the generous
Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
You’ll forgive me, right?
Now,
it’s my turn to draw.
I thought you would let me go.
It turns out to be
an idiotic idea again.
Come on.
Narrow-minded Lord
will definitely make me ugly
and take me out to the street.
How will I keep my image
if anyone recognizes me?
Or, I should just ask him
to make it as ugly as he can
until I can’t even recognize myself.
My Lord, I think…
Shut up.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪