♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 11=
She’s born. Liuying is back!
I miss her so much!
Hey, why would Liuying choose this place
to be born?
Yuchi Town.
What about it?
Yuchi.
Is it because this village has
the same name with you
that she chose to be born here?
One way or another,
Liuying chose me in the end.
Got it?
Does your wound hurt again?
You haven’t fully recovered.
I’ve told you
not to come until you get recovered.
But I have to be with her.
You have me here.
Moreover, her name is no longer Liuying.
Don’t worry. I’ll take good care of her.
How about this?
We can disguise as families
and live in this village. Right?
Yes! Yes! That’s great!
You’ll be my maid
for a century.
You and I
to be families?
Do you want to marry me?
No! No! I can’t do that!
Who would marry you?
To be siblings.
(18 Years Later)
(Yuchi Town)
Hope the osmanthus cakes
of this new restaurant
can be as tasty as that in the capital.
It’s you!
Why are you here?
You know Ayu is here,
so you come for her?
I’m here for my fugitive maid.
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Your Highness!
He...
He... He wants to take Ayu’s soul!
When did my maid have Three-call Spell
with Dragon King,
the demonic skill?
You come upon being called.
You. Come here.
Your Highness.
He must be here for Ayu’s soul!
I’ll count to three.
Come or I’ll take your soul.
One, two, three!
You...
Qingqing.
Go over there.
But I...
I am here.
Ayu will be fine.
You came by his order.
Now I don’t want you to come.
Go make Silver Needle tea for me.
No additives.
You are fooling me.
I’ll go then.
We worked together to mend the sky net.
It can hold for a century.
Why didn’t you tell Qingqing
you don’t need Ayu’s soul for now?
A century is a short time.
Things are unpredictable.
I didn’t promise
I’d never take your lover’s soul.
Besides, why should I tell it
to a maid?
You seem to
specially come for Qingqing today.
Heavenly Soldiers have been
going after Blood Devil.
I passed by
and thought of the maid.
I came to warn that bird demon
who can’t use magic.
She should keep a low key.
You come personally
for this trivial matter?
Do you love Qingqing?
How is that possible?
You must be jealous.
I’m sure you love her.
I’ve never known
how it feels to love someone.
It’s hard indeed.
Maybe because I’m intelligent.
It didn’t take me much time
to understand the mortal love.
Look.
I can teach you if you want to learn.
I don’t need an injured dragon
to teach me.
My injury is almost healed.
Alright. You’re good.
Keep waiting here
for your girl.
I will quit bothering you.
(Ruan Ayu)
Here. It’s fresh.
Thanks.
Thank you.
(Royal Notice)
I was worried about the drought.
A Goddess came into my dream at night.
Then the rain fell.
The Goddess is in the southeast.
If the Goddess of Rain can be found,
she’ll be rewarded with
gold, silver, satin and jewelry,
and conferred as a Princess.
Conferred as a Princess?
“Goddess is in the southeast.”
Our Yuchi Town is in the southeast.
Miss Yuxiang, that Goddess
is likely to be you.
(Liu Yuxiang Baldhead)
Who else could it be if not me?
Absolutely.
The last fresh fish!
Fish!
How much is the fish?
Three copper coins per tael.
It’s the last one.
A discount for you.
Okay. I’ll take it.
Okay.
Take care.
Here.
She’s known
as a jinx.
She got her mother killed.
Buying her fish,
you’ll be in bad luck.
What? Is it true?
Mrs. Sun. Don’t listen to her nonsense.
I’m telling the truth.
Her fish will make your family die
from sickness.
Aren’t you afraid?
-Sick!
-You...!
And the plants will wither.
Wither.
So lucky?
No, I won’t buy it.
-Mrs. Sun!
-No.
I won’t buy it.
You jinx,
no one will buy your fish.
Never mind. I’ll eat it myself.
Eat it yourself.
Excuse me.
Yuxiang, are you alright?
You poured water at me!
Your skirt is wet.
You smell fishy.
You’re fishy.
What’s wrong with you?
I...
Hey... Gentleman.
-Let’s talk.
-Get away.
-Watch out.
Are you alright?
I’m fine.
Come if you dare.
Yuxiang, I got a lump.
Who is it?
Zhiyong.
If you dare to bully girls again,
(Zhiyong)
I’ll break your baldhead!
Get lost!
What is it to do with you?
Baldhead.
Zhiyong asked you to leave. Go now.
Okay.
Thank you, Zhiyong.
You are welcome. Let me help you.
Father. I’m back.
Ayu is back.
Dinner is ready.
Father, let me do it.
Please sit.
It smells good.
(Ruan Yueshan)
Only my sweet girl
likes my salted fish and vegetables.
Father, I earned three more
copper coils today.
I’ll cook good dishes for you tomorrow.
You are a good girl.
I’m blessed
to have a good daughter like you.
Father, eat.
Ayu, eat the fish.
Eat, Father.
Let’s eat together.
Get away!
Watch out.
Right ahead!
This way!
More people are dead!
Here! Here!
Look! Look!
Plus these two,
five girls have been killed,
not for money or lust.
Only for girls’ heart.
There must be a demon in town!
It must be Father
who put the quilt on me.
It’s so beautiful.
Why do we pick flowers
at such a remote place?
It’s empty. No one is here.
It’s dangerous.
Flowers here are beautiful and big,
with so many categories.
Look, so beautiful.
These flowers are beautiful.
But I heard
many girls went missing lately.
There could be a pervert.
We are beautiful like flowers.
We’ll be targeted by the pervert.
Really?
-Ayu.
-Catch the pervert!
Ayu.
On your feet.
Let’s go.
Wait.
We get lost.
Someone is watching us.
Dragon King. Dragon King.
-Let’s go over there. Hurry!
-Dragon King.
Ayu! Run!
Dragon King. Dragon King. Dragon King.
Zhiyong. Why are you here?
Are you alright?
I... I’m fine.
Ayu.
Wake up, Ayu.
Ayu. Wake up, Ayu.
Ayu.
Crap. Dragon King is jealous.
Wake up.
You are a man.
Let me do it.
Ayu.
Zhiyong.
What brings you here?
I was hunting nearby.
This demon’s heart was pierced
by my arrow.
Did...? Did you kill...?
No.
That demon was stunned by Dragon...
Stunned by me...
By me.
You?
We must leave here now.
Ayu. Get on my back.
Hey...
Dragon King, don’t be angry.
I’m going to look after her. Ayu!
Well, I caught a wolf cub.
I’ll show you tomorrow
to calm you down.
Great. Thank you, Zhiyong.
Don’t mention it.
Your Highness.
How is she?
She had a soothing pill
and went to sleep.
And that... That person.
I’ve driven him home.
Don’t worry.
But
why did you hide away every time?
Isn’t it good
to help her openly?
The Immortal warned me
not to be close to Ayu.
Just because you can’t love.
They make up so many executes.
Those immortals
just don’t want demons
to be friends with human.
I’ve been with Ayu all the time.
Isn’t she very well?
Since you can’t care about Ayu,
why don’t you let Zhiyong do it?
No!
Hello, Uncle.
Where is Ayu?
Are you looking for Ayu?
She went to see the wolf cub
with Zhiyong.
I told her not to go.
She’s so playful.
Yes, she likes having fun.
Uncle, I’m off.
Won’t you stay for a while?
No.
Wolves are fierce,
but the cub is lovely.
Am I right, Zhiyong?
Here.
Eat.
You don’t eat?
Blood Devil, you’ve hidden
in human’s heart for 20 years.
You thought we couldn’t find you.
You can’t get away this time.
Your power improved quite a lot.
More than that.
I will be immortal.
Bah!
I’m not even immortal.
How dare you say that, my grandchild?
Barrier.
No!
Dragon King. Dragon King. Dragon King.
Hurry.
Your Highness. Ayu is in the cave.
It won’t work.
I just got the demon-slaying edict
from Heavenly Emperor to Three Realms.
One of the two barriers is here.
The other one is in the cave.
No one can break them.
What to do?
I don’t care about Heavenly Emperor.
I only know Ayu is inside.
Yes. Ayu isn’t a demon.
She’s innocent.
It’s the best time to kill the demon.
If we miss it,
Blood Devil will harm the world again.
Whoever is sacrificed at the moment,
Ziyang will not stop it.
If it won’t be stopped,
I will break it and get her out.
Your Highness.
Xue Qianxun, please help Dragon King.
You’re the Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
You must know how to break the barriers.
Ayu shouldn’t be killed
for slaying the demon.
These barriers
were made by 81 Heavenly Soldiers.
I can’t break them either.
If mortals are killed,
the Heaven will compensate
with blessings.
But...
But what?
Ayu’s soul is different from mortals.
It’ll burn with the demon.
The barriers can’t be broken,
but we can try other ways.
How to put out fire?
By water?
Can we make a rain?
Or find a cover
to shield the fire?
(Fire King)
Dragon King?
What brings you to my Flame Palace?
Lend me the fire shield.
Yuchi Longyan. The fire shield
is the treasure of my palace.
It’s not something you can borrow.
How dare you! Guards, stop him!
Yuchi Longyan.
I’m slaying the demon,
while you’re breaking the barriers.
Are you going against me?
My Lord. Please help Dragon King.
Stay out of it.
Yuchi Longyan. Stop it!
Immortal Ziyang, you misunderstood him.
Xue Qianxun, why are you stopping me?
He just wants to save the mortal
in the cave.
I didn’t see any mortal there.
Don’t be cheated by dragon demons.
You liar!
Are you blind?
Ayu is inside.
You said I’m a demon.
You are ugly.
I’m cursing you back!
Don’t you trust me?
Even if a mortal is killed there,
they’ll be compensated with blessings.
My mission can’t be interrupted.
Your Highness.
You... Since you want a fight,
why did you attack him from the back?
Stay out of it. Be quiet.
Blood Devil has been slain.
You can go back and report now.
Let go of him for my sake.
Okay. For your sake.
Blood Devil has been slain.
Go back and report
to Heavenly Emperor with me.
Ayu.
Ayu. Ayu.
Ayu. Take a breath.
Your Highness. What to do?
Ayu. Great!
Ayu.
Let me go.
Let go of me.
You are my maid.
How dare you be so rude to me?
Go back to my pavilion with me now.
Sorry. Sorry.
I... I didn’t mean to offend you.
I was in a hurry.
I was worried about her.
Please pardon this stupid bird.
You are really a stupid bird.
Yuchi Longyan didn’t want you to go
as well.
That makes sense.
My Lord, you are cold,
but you do understand him.
Don’t be afraid.
I’ll protect you afterwards.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪