Ms. O Sang-mi!
Who are you?
A safe house is for people
who are not safe.
The more beautiful the scenery is,
the more troubled you'd feel.
ORDINARY GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEE
I'm afraid you haven't been told,
but you can't use your phone here.
Okay.
The NIS agents will be here
for your protection.
Sir, when are you going
to interrogate O Sang-mi?
You'd better stop right here.
-Excuse me?
-Leave it to us.
You've done enough.
Damn, he has a weird way of
getting on my nerves.
Are you here for a tour?
If I catch you drinking at night shifts,
I'll kill you.
-Yes, sir.
-Stay focused.
Thank you for your hard work.
I feel like I'm bombarded, too.
Too much is happening all at once.
It's on you.
You're right.
By the way, what's happened
to my boss at the Blue House?
I mean, nobody was fired,
and the office is in total chaos.
-What are you doing here?
-Why else?
To protect your highness.
Wonder why I wasn't fired?
I told you I can't be fired
because I'm a special agent.
I'm that important.
What about O Sang-mi?
She's probably singing like a bird now.
Our very best is onto her.
Anyway, bravo.
Breaking into the Blue House
to meet the President?
Cha Dal-goen, thumb ups to you.
You know, the security guys came at me.
I managed ok with 15 of them,
but when it came to 30 guys,
all of them martial artists,
it wasn't easy even for me.
Wow, 30 of them?
That's right.
I didn't want to scare you,
but there were more.
-Really?
-Hell yeah.
Where are you, Go Hae-ri?
I'm coming!
Hey.
God of war.
Nice!
Hey, Hae-ri go, stop it.
Amazing!
She's been still like that for an hour.
She's being cautious,
meaning she's hiding a lot.
Hello.
-Hello, sir.
-Don't get up.
How's she doing?
Considering she's probably
never been interrogated,
she's surprisingly calm.
I didn't ask you, Gang.
She hasn't even moved her lips.
Have some.
You'll need some energy.
Why exactly did you bring me here?
You're here as a witness,
so relax.
The plane exploded and crashed.
Do you think
anyone could possibly survive from it?
You'll get two billion won in compensation
and five billion in life insurance payout.
Not to mention the money
for crashing the plane.
Even I couldn't have died,
leaving all that.
Okay, let's say he's alive.
It's nothing to do with me.
Your husband was on the phone
with the terrorist before takeoff.
You got it wrong.
He was on the phone with me.
Wanna know about what?
It was a very intimate conversation
between us two.
Your number was not in his phone log.
How would you explain that?
Answer the question.
If you talked to your husband,
you surely can speak Spanish.
Of course, there's no record.
Because we used a burner phone
to avoid loan sharks.
What? Didn't you check her background
before the interrogation?
-Did you not know she could speak Spanish?
-I'm sorry, sir.
I won't even bother with you,
but what happened to Gi?
He's supposed to be good!
Anyway, you said you'd do it,
so find out everything.
Do whatever it takes!
I clearly told him
she could speak Spanish.
What's up with him?
-It's his strategy.
-"Strategy"?
But, sir...
Are we keeping this
from even the Director?
There's a mole in the NIS.
We can't be too careful.
Really?
Have some.
Seems like you need it more than I do.
Kim Woo-gi is in Morocco, right?
He must be very anxious by now.
Not knowing what you might spill out.
What are you talking--
With more than 10 billion won
from John &amp; Mark.
I get it.
To take the money,
you need to protect him.
My husband is dead.
He's dead.
Let her go.
But, sir?
Do you believe her?
The time is not up yet.
I'll take full responsibility--
Director's orders.
Don't make a scene.
How does that matter?
It's not easy there, it's dangerous.
So it's dangerous for me,
but not for the other guy?
Who is it?
Who's the asshole that snatched my client?
They are deadly and very brutal.
-Done!
-This is pissing me off.
Thank you, sir.
How is this 1,200,000 won?
UNCLE
Yes, talk to me.
I've already started working on it.
Cha Dal-geon seems to be sleeping.
Let him be. He'll be up when hungry.
I mixed jajangmyeon for you. Dig in.
I had a late lunch, so...
-Ours, then.
-Good.
Who said I wouldn't eat? Don't!
Come on.
Man.
God.
Is it okay to have food delivered here?
Why not?
The delivery flyer was already here.
The security guys
also have them delivered.
It won't take too much effort.
Don't worry about the NIS bastards.
I'll only kill Cha Dal-geon.
Are you ready?
I thought you'd never ask.
Go get the empty plates.
Along with Cha Dal-geon's head.
I'm here for the plates.
-Wait a moment, please.
-Sure.
My head is killing me.
Maybe food poisoning?
You are...
Where are you?
I guess you didn't even have
a single bite of jajangmyeon.
Weren't you hungry?
You should've ordered jjamppong instead.
Is your head made of stone?
It's fucking hard.
Goodbye, stone head.
Is he dead?
Dal-geon.
Check if he's dead.
CALL HISTORY
UNCLE
Did I kill him? Really?
-Dal-geon--
-Be quiet.
Aren't you going to answer it?
Pardon?
Oh, right.
Okay, what do you have?
Did you get it done in time?
Answer me, you idiot.
What the heck are you saying?
The line is bad. Call me again.
Who was that?
Fuck.
He sounds exactly like Min Jae-sik.
Min Jae-sik?
M?
Who's M?
-Answer it.
-Hey, Go Hae-ri.
Yes, Chief.
-What are you doing?
-Texting to reassure him.
I KILLED CHA DAL...
You're such an amateur.
-Lie on the floor.
-What?
-Lie down.
-Hey. You're scaring me.
I'm not going to jump you. Do it now.
Why?
Is something wrong?
No.
GONG-CHEOL
He's dead. Cha Dal-geon.
-Are you sure?
-I have proof. Want to see?
Shoot, where are my manners?
It's too gruesome for a lady to--
What about O Sang-mi?
Don't worry.
She's acting exactly
according to the script I gave her.
How are you?
I heard you're fluent in Spanish.
It was you who Kim Woo-gi talked to
on the phone right before takeoff.
Who are you?
How should I explain who I am
for you to understand?
Well...
Let's say I'm from John &amp; Mark.
In here,
there's a set of very kind instructions
for you to follow.
Learn it thoroughly and do as it says.
Then you can easily get away with
the NIS interrogation.
Does John &amp; Mark want my cooperation?
It won't be cheap.
You can talk about the details later
with an expert on that subject.
Memorize it before going to the NIS.
It's no good putting it off.
I put in a GPS-tracking bug.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I hope we never meet again
for something like this.
Come this way.
TAXI
Where to?
-Just circle around the downtown nearby.
-Come again?
Do a lap around the nearest town.
I'll pay.
Yes, ma'am.
She suspects a tail.
She was quite something
in the interrogation, too.
Maybe she’s always been like that.
Or someone inside is helping her.
GO HAE-RI
O Sang-mi is getting in a cab again.
Give me the coordinates.
What?
Are you alone?
What's it about?
I think Min Jae-sik is the mole.
What do you mean?
Get it together and talk to me.
Go Hae-ri, listen very carefully.
Yes.
You got it, sir.
Get out of here with the body.
By myself?
These agents are Min's henchmen.
To deceive them properly,
I have to be here when they wake up.
Go out and meet Chief Gang.
You can trust him.
I'm Cha Dal-geon.
You heard from Hae-ri, right?
Min Jae-sik, you son of a bitch!
Do you know this guy?
You don't need to know.
Excuse me!
I've kept you afloat so far.
Shouldn't you let me in on this?
You want to play alone?
Okay, then.
I'm going to deliver this body to the DA.
Unkillable.
"Unkillable"?
It's a secret group of North Korean
defectors from the special forces.
What can we do
now that the economic deal is signed
between the two Koreas?
Unkillable is now like a cancerous tumor.
You should've dismissed them.
Why send them to get killed?
If word got out
about using defectors for black ops,
who'd take the blame?
You? Me?
The Director?
Come on.
North Korea's State Security Department
was apparently
very satisfied with the list.
To get closer to unification,
we need to offer a sacrifice.
Min Jae-sik regrouped Unkillable
after it was dismissed.
Then it's confirmed, right?
That asshole, Min Jae-sik,
is working with John &amp; Mark.
GO HAE-RI
What is it?
It's bad news, sir.
Cha Dal-geon has gone missing.
What?
What the fuck were you doing?
We kind of passed out
after we had some jajangmyeon.
When we woke up...
Oh, there's blood spatter here.
I think an assassin broke in.
Well done.
Get Hae-ri out of there,
and then delete the CCTV footage.
It's been all taken care of.
That son of a bitch knows what he's doing.
Make sure Hae-ri doesn't talk.
Tell her
I'll report to the Director myself.
Good.
This is how it should be done.
MR. KIM
-Yes, sir.
-What happened to O Sang-mi?
Her ass is right in front of me.
Don't waste any more time. Take her in.
You got it.
Turn left.
What the fuck?
Let me follow him and cut his throat.
Let him go.
He's one lucky son of a bitch.
How far to the target?
1.5 kilometers.
Something's not right.
-Go faster.
-Alright.
O Sang-mi went into a church
near Hagye station.
Connect me to her bug.
Yes, sir.
THE TRUTH LIES IN O SANG-MI'S HANDS
CAN SHE CLEAR THE SUSPICIONS?
THE NIS INVESTIGATING...
HE IS SUSPECTED TO HAVE USED...
GAIN THE SKIES
WITH THE PRAYERS OF OTHERS
Is it okay to call?
Aren't you under investigation?
Don't worry. Everything is taken care of.
What do you mean? How?
We're not the only ones
who don't want the truth out.
You don't trust John &amp; Mark, do you?
You know
I don't trust anything but money.
Did you get every penny
from John &amp; Mark?
Is this part recorded?
Of course. As clear as crystal.
I'll get the rest when the time's right.
Don't you turn your back on me.
You'll get the 5 billion
only if I'm alive.
Things have gone too far.
I need more than just 5 billion.
Hang in there.
The more we wait, the more we can get
because it makes them more anxious.
Get off me!
Shit.
What do you have?
I got a smoking gun
that can nail Kim Woo-gi.
Be more specific.
It's a burner.
They talked to each other
only through this phone.
Hello?
Gi Tae-ung?
Drag her out.
Hello? Gi Tae-ung?
Gi Tae-ung, what's wrong?
Gi Tae-ung! What's going on?
CHIEF GANG
Mr. Gang.
At the spot you were disconnected with Gi,
a car accident has just been reported.
A car accident?
Oh, no!
Give me the coordinates.
And find out where the Director is.
He's not home
and doesn't pick up.
-Hurry!
-Yes, sir.
Pull over!
Isn't that Cha Dal-geon?
GONG-CHEOL
BIG BROTHER
It's Unkillable.
Don't answer it.
The person you're trying to reach...
GONG-CHEOL
ANSWER THE PHONE, CHA DAL-GEON.
They know.
Answer it, then.
BIG BROTHER
What did you do to Gong-Cheol?
Answer the question. Where is he?
Where do you think a bad guy would end up?
In hell, obviously.
You son of a bitch.
Don't forget my voice.
I'll personally cut your throat.
Do Su!
You're Kim Do Su, right?
It's Gang Ju-cheol.
Fucking traitor.
UNCLE
Min Jae-sik?
Yes, Dal-geon just warned me
that Min may know.
Find his location.
-Oka--
-It's urgent. Hurry.
Okay, okay. Everybody's in a hurry today.
I've got him.
He's at the nightlife hot spot in Gangnam.
Send me the coordinates.
-Se-hun, are you okay?
-Please get out of the way.
Gi Tae-ung! Do you recognize me?
Tae-ung!
Chief...
Where is O Sang-mi?
Move over.
Come on, move him now!
Excuse me.
Isn't this O Sang-mi's burner?
You're right.
Those bastards didn't know she had it.
Fucking bastards.
-Yes, Mr. Gang.
-What happened to Min Jae-sik?
I found him.
How is Gi?
The ambulance took him.
Where are you?
In Gangnam.
Min will soon find out.
We need to arrest him before he gets away.
Can you do it by yourself?
Don't worry.
I have a gun.
I'll take full responsibility.
If he resists, just shoot him.
-Sir?
-O Sang-mi was taken.
What happened to Tae-ung
wasn't an accident.
Mi Jae-sik is behind it.
He's not even human,
so if it goes south, you may kill him.
Hey, Miss! You can't just barge in here!
I'm looking for my husband.
Get out of my way.
So, Mr. Director.
Did you blow off some steam?
The President called me three times today.
If I don't finish this case soon enough,
I might get the chop.
That's why I invited you
to a place like this, to cheer you up.
Have another drink
and get some rest at home.
Excuse me, sir. Let me get this.
MR. KIM
Damn.
Oh, Kim,
I'm busy now, so--
Gong-Cheol is down.
We're going to lay low with O Sang-mi.
You need to get out, too.
Fuck!
What the...?
What are you doing here?
You're under arrest
for covering up the B357 crash
and murdering by proxy.
What the fuck are you doing?
He sent a hitman to kill Cha Dal-geon
at the safe house.
What's she talking about?
On top of that,
he attempted to kill
Gi Tae-ung--
-Go Hae-ri!
-Don't move.
Or I'll shoot.
What? Shoot me?
I'm your direct supervisor.
What you heard is a fucking rumor.
You destroyed the video
and betrayed your colleagues.
How much did John &amp; Mark fucking give you!
God, what a pain in the ass.
You have three daughters.
Does your dirty money
make your family happy?
-Put the gun down and let's talk first.
-I'm not kidding!
I will shoot you, son of a bitch!
GANG JU-CHEOL
Yes, Gang.
Sir, where are you now?
Fuck.
Damn it.
Are you sober now?
Yes. What about Gi Tae-ung?
The doctor told me that he'll live
and that we don't need to worry.
Thank God.
What about Min Jae-sik?
He's disappeared. His phone is off, too.
The police are helping us find him,
so we'll know soon enough.
It won't be easy to find him.
Damn it.
Shit.
Damn.
Mr. Min?
You're Chief Min Jae-sik, right?
Who are you?
Here.
You want to answer it.
This is Min--
Min Jae-sik isn't as bold as he looks.
He'd never act alone
unless he had someone to count on.
Are you saying
he's under some kind of protection?
Let me lead the investigation.
I will find an answer to every question
from Kim Woo-gi to Min Jae-sik.
-What if you fail?
-You don't like me, right?
I'll quit.
I don't care about your quitting
because I'll get sacked before.
We found a smoking gun.
A smoking gun?
We can find Kim Woo-gi any time now.
From my experience, everything we do
from this point on is very crucial.
An unskilled hunter can fail to catch
even a trapped prey.
Okay, then. I'm giving you full power.
If you fail though,
quitting won't be enough.
Is he still unconscious?
He's asleep with an IV painkiller.
I got a cold wind in my eyes
while running.
Don't worry about Min Jae-sik.
He's on an APB. We'll catch him soon.
Excuse me.
You're not my type.
I like tall, intelligent,
fair-skinned men.
She's got no taste.
He looks like a weasel
with a bad temper.
Dal-geon, you must be hungry.
Oh, no.
I made too much fried rice.
Who is it?
Dal-geon, it's me.
Hae-ri Go?
Ta-da! I've got fried chicken.
-Why?
-Why else? Because I'm hungry.
Oh, something smells good!
What is it? Kimchi fried rice?
You must have read my mind.
I had a craving on my way here.
You should've given me a call.
This place is a mess.
It's good that I'm here.
You made a lot. There's ham, too!
TTOBONGEE CHICKEN
You're a good cook.
The seasoning is perfect.
I'm not sure we are close enough
for you to come here and eat with me.
-What about Mr. Gi?
-Hwa-suk is there now.
Here, have some.
You want some?
Okay, I'll drink alone.
I want a drink, too.
I don't have soju glasses.
Sip slowly with this.
Here...
you did good today.
What?
Hey, hey. Take it easy.
What's wrong with you?
I'm trying to relax.
Too many things happened today.
Wow, I can't believe she drank all this.
Hae-ri Go!
Where do you live? Let me take you home.
No, sir. I can go by myself.
She's plastered.
No, you can't. You're absolutely hammered.
Hae-ri Go, get up. Let's go home.
Do you hate me that much?
Do you really
hate me that much, Mr. Gi?
What is it about me that you hate so much?
Just tell me what,
and I'll fix it all.
Hae-ri Go!
Wake up. Let's go home and sleep.
Wake up, now.
-Let's go home.
-You!
You're mine.
What?
Hey.
Go Hae-ri?
Now you're mine.
Ms. Go Hae-ri?
Hae-ri... Hae-ri Go?
Hae-ri Go.
You shouldn't sleep here.
Hae-ri Go, wake up.
Come here.
A snitch?
It seems Min Jae-sik was bribed
by John &amp; Mark.
He has links with
a high-ranking government official.
-Who do you think the official is?
-We're looking into it.
Any evidence of it?
There's no other way to explain--
Come on, Director An.
Are you crazy?
You are reporting to the President
without even evidence?
I was told to report even a small thing.
Still, you need basic facts.
Don't you see
he's tired from so much work?
Just solve the case as soon as possible.
It gives me such a headache.
Yes, Mr. President.
Down.
I'm sorry.
The leash slipped through my fingers.
-You can go now.
-Yes, sir.
This dog is smarter than An.
You should've just bitten him real hard.
Sometimes you need to take the wheel.
I've been free from stain
during my term of office.
I don't need a bucket of shit on me now.
Take him away.
It's not that you haven't had a stain,
but that you got it cleaned well.
And I was a part of that cleaning crew.
-Master Hong.
-Wow.
I haven't heard that nickname for a while.
Use that special brain of yours
to let me know what to do.
I gave you the pictures of Park Man-yeong
for a time like this.
Use the Minister of Defense
as a scapegoat?
That's right.
He can be used as a shield
and he's easy to get rid of.
You should've been
the Director General of the NIS
rather than the Prime Minister.
Then the two Koreas
would've been united already.
REST IN PEACE
FUNERAL DAY 49 OF THE B357 VICTIMS
KANG MI-SEON,
WIFE OF PARK KWANG-DEOK
CHA HOON, NEPHEW OF CHA DAL-GEON
We officially propose to the government
to find out the cause...
PRESIDENT JEONG GOOK-PYO,
PLEASE KEEP YOUR PROMISE
and the truth of the B357 crash.
President Jeong Gook-pyo
promised to find out the truth
but he has done nothing.
And the National Defense Ministry
is working with John &amp; Mark
on the F-X plan.
Politicians are not doing anything
like having the national assembly
get to the bottom of it
or enacting a special law
for the investigation.
We don't want the compensation money.
We don't understand...
STAYING SILENT IS ALSO A CRIME
why we had to lose our loved ones
and we want this abnormal situation
to be made right.
No money can heal the pain
from losing a family.
We want to know
why we had to lose our loved ones.
Please get to the bottom
of the B357 crash.
Please make a special act
so that this kind of tragedy
will never happen again.
Call the NIS about this, anonymously.
You got it.
People of Korea
whose hearts are also broken,
please give us your support
although we couldn't protect...
SEONDEOK JUDO GYM
This is frustrating.
How is the NIS investigation going?
You don't talk to Hae-ri anymore?
She hasn't called me at all.
She must be busy.
I see.
Wait. That guy...
Hmm? What? Who?
I'm Jo Bu-yeong,
a reporter for Pyeonghwa Daily.
Mr. Jo!
He was dead.
Sorry? Who?
Dal-geon. Dal-geon!
Mr. Jo Bu-yeong!
Mr. Jo!
Subtitle translation by Jean S. Kim