BUILDING GA
ROW NA
Seolleongtang for breakfast,
gomtang for lunch.
What shall I order for your dinner?
How about sundaetguk?
I'll have dinner at home
because I'll be out soon.
You're mistaken.
You were also mistaken
when you crashed the plane.
That was reckless.
Don't accuse me without evidence.
You know Kim Woo-gi, right?
No, I never fucking saw him.
-What's with your arrogant tone?
-You started it.
You don't know Kim Woo-gi?
Now, I got you with one of your lies.
Only a few photos
can't put me behind bars.
Why do you think Michael is dead?
I don't need to know
why he killed himself.
Can you see the purple stain
on his right hand?
It's called a diphenylamine reaction.
It's from the nitrogen dioxide
emitted from the gun powder explosion.
Yeah, he shot himself.
You know he's left-handed.
But he used the right hand
to shoot himself to death?
Michael was killed.
You're very imaginative.
Let's say he was.
Then tell me why.
He wasn't cooperative with the attack,
or you needed to shut him up quickly.
You think I killed him?
Are you from the Stone Age?
Do you really think
this archaic method will work?
Making up a story to frame me?
A call recording between
O Sang-mi and Kim Woo-gi.
You know
I don't trust anything but money.
Did you get every penny
from John &amp; Mark?
I'll get the rest when the time's right.
Don't you turn your back on me.
You'll get the 5 billion
only if I'm alive.
This is the story I have so far.
You're welcome to correct me.
This little thing is your evidence
for arresting me?
You can't submit it to the court.
Don't you have more?
Something to catch me by surprise.
Let her go.
We need to hold her longer.
The Court dismissed the warrant
for lack of evidence.
They're warning us
not to touch her, right?
Have you figured out who's pulling
the strings behind the scene?
Something is up at the Blue House.
I couldn't figure out what.
Capturing Kim Woo-gi
would sort everything out.
Jeez.
Oh, shit.
Why am I seeing a drone here?
They must have changed the patrol time.
Run!
I found bottles of mineral water.
Do you see Kim Woo-gi?
Not from here. I'll go inside.
My teammates will be there soon.
If Kim's not there, we are both--
But if he is, it's a jackpot.
Dal-geon...
If you get caught--
I did this alone. Play dumb.
Shit!
Sorry, doors are always closed.
Are you the owner?
Yes, sir. I'm sorry I didn't hear...
Ok, sir. Go ahead.
I don't care who the tenants are
as long as they pay on time.
Take us to their apartment.
-Okay, sir.
-Let's go.
I collect money from the tenants
in the beginning of every month.
Come on, hurry up!
Who are you?
What are you looking for in here?
Can't we just talk in Korean?
Mr. Kim Woo-gi.
Let's have a look at that apartment.
Gosh! Get up!
Get the fuck up! You fucking bastard!
Get up! Come here, you bastard!
Please don't kill me.
You bastard!
Stop! Don't move!
Shut up!
What are you taking me for, too?
Get off me!
Isn't he Kim Woo-gi?
Yes, it's him.
-What's going on?
-You're just in time.
Get off me.
Ask them to uncuff me, will you?
He deserves to be fucking beaten!
I can't get them to understand.
Who the hell are you?
I'm one of the bereaved.
I was on TV, too.
Why are you here?
-Sorry?
-Who sent you?
I came to find my nephew's murderer
on my own.
You got a problem with that?
Take him to the police station.
Don't fucking touch me!
Tell them
he should be in our custody.
Let us take him. He's one of us.
It is crucial that we arrest
and interrogate him.
He said they needed
to interrogate him at the station.
What rights do you have
to do that?
Don't get smart with me
or I will arrest all of you.
He's threatening to arrest us, too.
-Seriously?
-I've done nothing wrong.
Tell them to uncuff me.
Come on! Move it!
-Just tell them!
-Move it! Now!
Come on! Hey!
Shut up and walk.
Get off me! Hey!
Don't! Uncuff me!
-I remember him now.
-Let go of me!
He's Cha Dal-geon.
He disclosed the truth
about the crash at the Blue House.
But why is he here?
TEAM LEADER GI
Yes, sir.
Come to the police station now.
Pardon?
Police station? Why?
Kim Woo-gi is in custody.
He's caught?
Yes, I'll be right there.
Good job, God of War.
Bruce Chan.
Wow!
Dal-geon!
What's happening?
Don't worry.
Mr. Gi is talking to the police chief,
so you'll be out soon.
I told you
if we worked together,
we could catch this motherfucker.
Here, give me a high five.
-Argh!
-Just a bit closer!
A bit more! You can do it!
Go! Go!
Is it
necessary to do it now?
Yes, it is.
because I'm over the moon.
-Come closer, a bit more!
-Go!
-Come on girl!
-Yes, come on!
Just a bit closer.
-Again, again!
-Come on!
Just a bit closer.
-High five!
-Yeah.
You're lucky to be here together.
Time is up. Give me my jacket.
What shall we do?
Let her go.
Yes, everything is fine.
We got a call from Gi Tae-ung.
-Put him through.
-Yes, sir.
What do you have?
We've got Kim Woo-gi.
Good job!
I knew I could count on you!
I didn't capture him.
What?
Then who did?
Go Hae-ri
and Cha Dal-geon, one of the bereaved.
Cha Dal-geon?
He followed you there?
Yes.
It doesn't matter who did it.
Things aren't going well here,
so make Kim talk as much as you can
before coming back.
You got it.
Well...
Jessica says she'll have dinner at home.
What shall we do?
Don't worry about external pressure.
Just do your job.
I'll report to the President personally.
Well...
You need to go back inside.
Why? Do we have unfinished business?
Yes, choosing your menu for dinner.
Come again?
Kim Woo-gi is captured.
Take her back.
What does it have to do with me?
-Let's go.
-Don't you touch me!
Do you know how much this jacket costs?
Maybe I should just rip it apart.
Let's go.
We got Kim Woo-gi
and no one is dead or even hurt.
I don't see anything wrong with it.
You don't know what mistake you made?
You said I was incompetent
without a sense of duty.
You were wrong.
I did it to prove that.
You're pathetic.
Let me be honest with you.
You're worried about how to report this
because I and Cha Dal-geon got him
while senior agents did nothing.
Right?
I wanted to see reliability,
not your ability.
Whether we could trust you with our lives.
You aren't qualified to be on my team.
You failed.
Sir!
I reported it was you who caught him.
You will surely get the reward
that you love so much.
Such a narrow mind for a team leader.
If you trusted her from the beginning,
everything would be fine.
Isn't it a bit hilarious
a team leader talks about qualifications
when he can't trust his own team?
Drop it, Dal-geon.
Do you always mind others' businesses?
I saved your ass,
but you're blaming me for it?
Without Hae-ri Go,
you couldn't have caught that jerk.
Drop it.
It was only a matter of time.
But you got in our way
and messed up the situation.
We got him, though
while you were fucking wasting time.
I'm warning you
if you cross the line again,
I won't let it pass.
Finding out why my nephew had to die
is what you call "crossing the line"?
When will Jessica be out?
Tomorrow morning at the latest?
Are you sure?
Shadow will personally see to it tonight.
Jeez...
I will be there by 8:30
to see the President.
Thank you, Secretary Kim.
I'm surprised you called.
Dinner?
Okay, see you there.
You seem to be in a good mood.
Do I?
I got nothing good going on.
You caught Kim Woo-gi,
which is a good thing.
However,
do you think the President will be glad
to hear the news?
What do you mean?
He always thinks
what's best for our nation.
I know that.
For the F-X plan, he thinks
working with John &amp; Mark
is good for our nation's interests.
"Catching a real culprit
who crashed the plane."
"The terrorist confessed
John &amp; Mark was behind the attack."
It'd be the worst news for the President.
What do you want?
The Task Force team
in charge of the investigation
must be completely changed.
Not only Chief Gang Ju-cheol,
but every one of them.
Which means
I should cover up the truth?
Because it's an inconvenient truth.
Look, Senior Secretary Yun.
Are you out of your mind?
A show can go on
as long as there's a villain.
For the President
and the nation's interest,
I will willingly bear a crown of thorns.
You're out of your mind.
You're utterly crazy.
So you're the last piece of
the axis of evil.
These documents are about your corruption
when you were Head of the Security Office
at the Blue House.
What?
You heavily extorted
defense industry companies
and took bribes from Dynamic twice.
Min Jae-sik!
The stocks your brother-in-law gave you
rose five times.
You got them for free in an expedient way.
You bastard!
If the documents are exposed,
you and your acquaintances
will be badly hurt.
The opposition party
aiming for the next election
will show a lot of interest.
Let me ask you the same question.
Do you think your shitty scheme
will make the President happy?
I've served him for 15 years
as his secretary
ever since he was an assemblyman.
Nobody knows
what he really thinks better than I do.
You are mistaken.
I'll do what I think is right,
so do whatever you want.
Jeez, he's being tough.
What if we get blamed for everything?
He's ready to see you.
I'll wait outside.
Is it something important?
We've just started,
so it might take a while.
It's something that you must know.
You're making me tense.
You're ruining this massage.
Mr. President, excuse me for doing this.
Sure, go ahead.
Yes, right there.
I'm really stiff right there.
I hear stress causes cancer.
How's your health, Director An?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Because the NIS Director General is fine,
the President isn't.
Your overworking
will help me work less.
My apologies, sir.
The review in Minju Daily
fucking bluntly criticized
the next generation fighter plan.
I support John &amp; Mark
not because I have an agenda,
but because it's a good deal
and it helps complete
the independence of national defense.
Come on, except for Cha Dal-geon's claim,
there's no evidence.
Am I wrong?
Well, as a matter of fact...
What?
You think I'm wrong?
How loyal you are.
You think you're a loyal subject
from the Joseon Dynasty?
No, Mr. President. You're right.
Then why did you allow
the shitty reviews to be published?
The press is
like a fucking foal.
It'll go wild
once you let go of the reins.
That's why
I'm getting weaker
like this
whereas you're robust.
Wait outside.
My head hurts.
Has anyone died of high blood pressure
while getting a massage?
No, Mr. President.
Wow, that's good.
To be a loyal subject is simple.
Doing a job sincerely like you
so that I can conduct the State affairs.
That's what a loyal subject does.
You beat me to it.
I've been thinking a lot on the way here.
You and I are doing this
for the sake of our nation,
but how we think is very different.
The President can be hurt
if things go wrong.
That's why
he doesn't know.
He's never been briefed about it.
Let me hear your plan, then.
What do you want to do
by changing the TF team?
What difference will
changing one team make?
Kim Woo-gi will be dead tomorrow.
We want a neat and quiet funeral.
In order to do that,
we need to change the chief mourner.
I guess we finally meet.
Nice to meet you. I'm Kim Do Su.
Forget it.
We are here to do nothing good.
Look.
Share with me
what you guys babbled on about.
What a pain in the ass.
I'm not here to interpret.
Such an amateur.
Didn't you hear
you need to work with us closely?
You're just here
to take a free ride from me.
What a parasite.
Hey, bitch.
Do you have a death wish?
How much is the NIS paying you for this?
How much is John &amp; Mark paying you?
I'll give you that money.
Just get the fuck out.
A crazy bitch is roaming around
in broad daylight.
"A crazy bitch"?
Fucking asshole!
I'm sorry.
Pardon?
I said I was sorry.
Don't be discouraged.
Cheer up!
Elsa.
He just gave me a finger, right?
Well, I think he meant something else.
Ready for the interrogation?
-Oh, yes.
-Good.
Mustang,
don't you have something to say to Elsa?
Well,
what would we have done without you?
Said Zombie.
What the...
No, actually...
I wish
I had a sister like Elsa.
Said Mustang.
My, my.
Good job. Go get Mr. Gi.
-Uh...
-Jeez.
What's got into their heads?
-Oh, man.
-What's wrong with them?
You're the heroin of this operation.
They're sorry
for how bad they've treated you.
We can't say much because of Gi,
but when we go back to Seoul,
we'll surely report--
Go inside.
We're ready for the interrogation.
Why is Cha Dal-geon here?
He's here as a witness.
We don't need him.
Get him out of here.
He's the only one who saw the terrorist.
We need him for cross-examination.
Who was behind
the attack on the plane?
"Attack"?
I saw the plane going down...
So I escaped for my life.
Who was behind the attack?
Jeez.
Who ordered it?
Cha Dal-geon?
-Whoa!
-You think it's a joke?
-You can't do this!
-Come on!
-No, let him go!
Get him out of here!
-Let's go.
-Let go of me.
Tell the truth.
The bastard with a scar on his face
confessed everything!
You're fucking bluffing.
If Jerome got caught,
you wouldn't--
Jerome?
You heard that? "Jerome"?
Is Jerome the terrorist?
What's wrong with him?
-What is this?
-Oh, God! Look at me!
Come on, man!
I'll go get the doctor.
What the fuck is wrong with him?
Did you take poison?
Wake up, man!
-Get off!
-Come on!
He's a fucking junkie.
Drug.
The painkiller you're taking
can prevent him from going into shock.
Give me the drug. I need the drug!
-Please!
-Don't fucking move!
-What is it?
-It has morphine in it.
What are you doing?
Tell us first who was behind the attack.
It's all over if he's fucking dead!
Get off me!
Get off me, damn it!
Crazy bastard!
Give him a shot!
Don't, Hae-ri!
It's an order! Do it!
Please, give me...
Argh!
Jeez!
He could die of shock. Give him a shot!
Who was behind the attack?
-Go Hae-ri!
-Who was it?
What the fuck?
Who was it?
Fuck!
I don't know.
Michael! It's Michael!
He's the vice president!
Michael?
Who is he?
The vice president of John &amp; Mark.
Are you sure he ordered the attack?
I can take it no more.
Please give me a shot first.
Give me the evidence that it was him.
Please...
A secret bank account...
"A secret bank account"?
Michael...
Michael
gave me
five billion won--
He's in shock.
Hurry!
You know he's left-handed.
But he used the right hand
to shoot himself to death?
Michael was killed.
The account number.
The account where you received
five billion from Michael.
Did I say that?
I don't remember.
Hey!
What did you just say?
I have the right to remain silent,
so don't bother me.
Fucking son of a bitch!
Hitting him won't help.
This bastard
is a murderer who killed 200 people.
My job is taking him back safely.
You'd better let me go.
We're ready to leave.
Can't you stop already?
You two will end up growing on each other.
You and Cha Dal-geon will come separately.
What an asshole!
He's an asshole alright,
but he's not a traitor like Min Jae-sik.
I don't like his eyes.
Taxi!
The car just drove past me.
It is headed towards you.
What is the problem?
Why is the road closed?
There has been an accident.
A tow truck is back there.
What's going on?
-There's an accident. We need to detour.
-Man...
Okay. Let's go, then.
Go! Get out of here.
We're going to the airport, right?
Yes, he said this leads to the road
to the airport.
What's wrong?
What is going on?
Road is closed.
Go back to where you came from.
-Why?
-Due to construction. Now, move it!
-Is it really necessary?
-Are you interrogating me? Go! Scram!
What are they saying?
It's under construction.
We can't go this way.
What are you waiting for?
We should take the other road.
What the heck is...
Take care of it. We might miss them.
Please, let the car pass.
The road is closed due to construction.
We don't want to be late for our flight.
I wonder if they're redeveloping the area.
It's pretty desolate.
Hey, where do you think you're going?
I'm late. I need to work.
What?
Okay. I'll pay you.
Wait here.
-The road is closed.
-You're not going to let us pass?
-Hey, why...
-What did he say?
-What's with the constructions?
-We are not looking for trouble.
We missed them.
Who do you think you are? Jacki Chan?
Let us pass through.
The road is closed.
Just us, please!
What about you, communist?
My, my!
Are you chickened out?
Kim Woo-gi's head is mine.
I won't let the crazy bitch
take the credit.
Pull out!
Whoa!
Don't say...
Get in the backseat.
-Get out!
-Huh?
Go!
No...
Get out!
Run!
Argh!
Mr. Gi!
Go with Kim Woo-gi.
What about you?
I can use the rifle there. Go now!
You go with him.
Mr. Gi! Sir!
Keep going, you bastard!
Get in!
Fuck!
I think the bullet hit his artery.
Let's go to the nearest hospital.
No, it can be dangerous!
How long to the Korean Embassy?
About 40-50 minutes?
It depends on the traffic.
He could die before we get there.
Hold on. I will be there
in 20, no, 10 minutes.
GI TAE-UNG
Yes. What about Kim Woo-gi?
He's shot on the leg.
He's bleeding a lot.
"Shot"?
We were ambushed.
We're on our way to the Embassy now!
I'll give them a call.
What about the team?
Except for Hae-ri and Se-hun,
everyone died on site.
BUILDING GA
ROW BA
The local police are also in on it!
It's going to be difficult to take
Kim Woo-gi back home.
I'll send some backup we can trust.
Stay put at the Embassy.
Don't do that. Huh?
What's going on?
Wait. What are you doing?
We're shutting down the operation.
Take their phones
and turn off the computers.
-Okay.
-Hang on.
Hang on a second.
Hold on. What are you doing?
Let me go!
Wait a moment!
Don't touch it!
-Get off me!
-Get off me, please!
What's wrong with you?
What the heck is wrong with you?
Hurry. You're leaving tonight.
Okay, thanks.
What are you doing?
Hey, Chief Gang!
You...
Now you will be arrested
for revealing a State secret
and profiting the enemy.
Therefore, I need you
to quietly cooperate.
Cuff him.
I'm sorry, sir.
We can just talk, please!
Stop!
Min will take over the TF team.
Cuff him.
For a fucking spy
and fucking traitor,
you're strong but brainless.
Who from above is pressuring you?
Take him now.
Who on earth made you like this?
Director General!
Director An!
Jeez.
You can lean on me.
I'm fine.
How do I look?
Fine.
Shadow
certainly knows what he's doing.
I told you
that you were making a big mistake.
Even Michael was once a CIA agent.
Drop by
when you can't find a place to work.
I could use your skill
for making up a story.
How did it go?
They went into the Embassy.
Hae-ri!
Chief Gang called you, right?
-Yes.
-Where's the doctor?
Nobody is willing to come, so...
we're still looking, but...
-Take him to the infirmary upstairs.
-Okay.
Let's go.
Doctor Lim.
Hey, what's with the video call?
I can't tell you in detail.
I need your help with a gunshot wound.
Over there!
They are outside.
Look for surgical tools.
-What?
-Now!
Grab him here, quickly!
Get your things.
For what?
Not for farming, obviously.
We'll go inside to kill him.
It's the Embassy.
So what?
I didn't come all the way here
to miss the target.
Wow.
What a sucker.
You know nothing about the basics.
I can gauge your eyes out
with this sucker's finger.
Darling.
If you're wanted internationally,
you have to stay low your whole life.
I can't work with this fucking amateur.
You just wait and see.
After killing Kim Woo-gi,
I'll cut open your throat.
Am I a beer bottle
for you to open? You fucking sucker!
How is he?
I need to see the artery first.
Did you stop the bleeding?
-You have to bear with it.
-Yes.
Open the wound wider.
Sir, we've got no scalpels or anesthetics.
Bring me whatever there is!
His wrist!
-Hold him.
-Gloves.
Sterilize it.
Are you going to operate?
He can do it.
He's a real special agent.
Pour the povidone-iodine.
Hold him.
Pour it more.
In there, you'll find
an artery as thick as a straw.
Stretch open the wound.
-Sir?
-Stay focused!
Se-hun, you come here!
Come here. Hold this.
That's okay. I can do it.
Wider!
That's it, right there! That's the artery.
Okay, luckily,
it's not completely severed.
Will you be able to operate?
Yes.
I'll give it a go.
Good, right there. Right there, stop!
Stay focused!
Cut it.
Gauze.
Bandage.
Here.
-Done.
-Good job.
Good job, sir.
What?
-What?
-What's wrong with him?
What's wrong?
Doctor, he's suddenly convulsing!
What's happening to him?
He bled too much.
Without a blood transfusion, he could die.
Kim Woo-gi, wake up!
-What's your blood type?
-It's O.
How do you know?
I read all about him before coming here.
Mine is O, too. Give him my blood.
Hang in there. Don't fucking die.
Take my blood now!
Jeez.
Subtitle translation by Jean S. Kim