SMALL HEART CONCERT
JOHN &amp; MARK MILITARY TECHNOLOGY
Can you give your word for it?
Hey, mister. Didn't you hear me?
The man at the repair shop said
that they did something to my car.
Did you see the car?
I nearly got killed!
As for the details,
Dal-geon will come out
and talk to you about it,
so don't go anywhere
and please wait here.
-Okay.
-Get me a picture. Something's up here.
This is chamomile tea.
It calms your body and mind,
so I got it from the Director.
You should drink up.
You need it more than I do.
How much did Dynamic pay you?
What kind of bullshit is that?
Things change
but some things never change.
Money means power
and the truth is crafted with power.
I'm telling you to stay out of this fight.
So,
for money
and power,
did you kill all those people?
We never did such a thing.
I don't even watch the news
because it makes me cry.
I know you killed Michael,
the vice president.
And Pyeonghwa Daily Reporter
Jo Bu-yeong.
It seems to me now
that you need treatment.
You are not strangled by the pain.
You are holding onto it.
Did you know you have to be smart
to have a conscience?
You people are stupid as hell.
You messed with the wrong guy.
Watch out.
I'll sip every drop of blood out of you.
Mr. Cha.
How can I help you?
I feel so sorry for you.
Bring Hoon...
...back to life.
The car is ready, ma'am.
You can head out the back.
What happened to
Pyeonghwa Daily Reporter Jo?
He had been investigating the case
and crossed the line.
-If we had left him--
-So you took him out without telling me?
Don't you know
we're on the edge of a cliff?
There is no room for trouble,
so don't worry.
-Bring the car to the front.
-You'll be hassled by reporters.
Avoiding them looks more suspicious.
I should act confident.
So you are saying that John &amp; Mark
is behind the B357 crash.
-Is that it?
-Yes.
Are there any grounds for that claim?
There is a video file.
The NIS has the video
that can prove my point!
If he's telling the truth,
this is shocking news!
Then you should check with the NIS
if that is true.
This is not the first time
our company has heard this claim.
But none of those accusations
were found to be true.
Excuse us. Let us through.
Excuse us.
-Just a moment!
-Sorry.
And when Mr. Cha's claim is found false,
please avoid running critical stories.
He lost his family member in the accident.
I deeply understand how he must feel.
Yes, this is 111 Call Center.
Yes, we've checked
and there is no such video file.
I have no idea
why that man is saying that.
It's not under investigation.
I'm telling you. That's a false report!
I told you to keep Cha's mouth shut.
What the hell were you doing
when he was chittering and chattering
in front of reporters?
But what he said
was not completely made up.
Since it came to this,
we should start investigating--
Did you grow guts in Morocco?
For crying out loud.
CHIEF MIN JAE-SIK
Yes, Director.
Yes, sir. Understood.
Damn it, why should I be the one
dealing with reporters...
This is all because of you, you idiot!
I'm going to send you off
to rebel groups in the Middle East,
so if you don't want to get shot there,
bring me your resignation letter.
Get out.
Get out!
You're one step away from being sacked.
What's your plan?
Once it gets on the news,
the police will be involved.
We have to take the lead.
Where are you going?
I'm going to die an early death
because of you.
Yes.
What brings you here?
Did you see the pictures I sent?
Yeah, sort of.
I think Michael's death
is somehow related to the plane crash.
So?
How long are you going to
let Chief Min push you around?
Just use our help and--
The incompetent one,
the loud one, and the toothless one.
-What can we do together?
-Um, Chief?
I can see who the incompetent
and the toothless ones are.
Am I...
You said there was something off
about Michael's suicide.
That and nothing more.
I was just curious
about my friend's death.
Off you go.
If we nail this,
you would get a two-rank promotion.
Promotion?
Let it go.
This isn't a case
a nobody like you can solve.
-Chief!
-Let's just go.
Since when did you become a chicken?
What? A chicken? You rude little--
This is not like you at all.
-I'm so disappointed!
-Come on.
-Don't touch me!
-Have a nice day, sir!
Let me go!
Michael was murdered.
A left-handed person never uses
his right hand when committing suicide.
Look closely into
Michael's schedule in Portugal.
Did you know the President
invited us to the Blue House tomorrow?
-What time?
-But it's not for all of us.
Only a few representatives are going.
I would've recommended you over me
if I knew this would happen.
B357 PLANE CRASH
Any articles?
Not one.
What?
But they were all so worked up back there.
Do you think
that woman got to them already?
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
Is it Cha Dal-geon again?
What can we do by ourselves?
You should just come clean with him.
The person you're trying to reach...
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
SIX MISSED CALLS
You have a friend in Inspection, right?
Was it Se-hun?
Not exactly a friend. Why do you ask?
I'm going to find the video file.
How?
UNEMPLOYED LIL BRO
-What?
-It's trouble, sis.
One of mom's fund members ran off
with the money
and mom has to pay for it
because she's the fund leader.
Why does she always mess up?
I don't know!
She needs five million won right now.
-Do you have any money?
-I don't have any money!
Tell her to sort it out herself!
You have a crappy life, too.
Jeez. Are you okay?
Do you still want me to meet Se-hun?
-Cheers!
Bottoms up, okay?
What? Again?
Why are you pushing me so hard...
Are you getting me drunk
so you can do stuff to me?
Why? Are you scared?
Scared of you?
You scare me all the time.
Oh god!
Stop jibber-jabbering and just drink up!
Oh, dear me!
Where are you off to?
Running away already?
I'm off to take a leak! You can't stop me!
Why do you even have a bladder
when it's so small?
What did you say? A small bladder?
You messed with my pride, girl.
When I come back from the toilet,
you are as good as dead! Okay?
I don't even know why I am doing this.
Thanks.
Wow. This chicken's so good!
-This is a fantastic chicken place!
-Yep, yep.
NIS
Hey, you. Stop.
Who are you?
Go Hae-ri?
What are you doing here
in the middle of the night?
It's not like this is a night school.
Do I need your permission?
I'm just asking
because you don't need to be here.
I came to write my resignation letter.
Happy now?
For god's sake.
That was just my temper speaking.
Hey, why do you have to be so dim-witted?
Don't you feel the air around here?
There's no point in working hard.
And you will get hurt
if you don't mind your own business.
You get paid for doing nothing.
What's better than that?
It's best to be average.
You'll only get this kind of advice
from me and no one else.
I'll take note, sir.
Yeah, you do that.
I don't hate you.
I feel bad for you.
GO HAE-RI
-What is it?
-I have something to tell you.
Where are you?
-Something urgent?
-Yes.
I need to meet you now.
I'll text you an address.
Let's meet there.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO DELETE THIS
VIDEO RECORDING?
DELETING VIDEO
Hurry up. This place is about to close.
Explain it to me.
The flash drive your team took.
Why is it infected with a virus?
-How do you know that?
-I saw it with my own eyes.
Then why do you need an explanation?
Are you covering this up?
The plane crash killed 211 people.
Director's orders.
We have to follow them.
"Dedicate yourself in silence
for country and people.
That is the duty and pride
of NIS agents."
Those were the words
you told me over and over again.
Why have you changed?
If you're confident enough,
you can expose it yourself.
Don't you think I can do it?
You can't.
You know you can't.
Ugh.
-Oh god.
-Did you drink a lot?
See me? I look wasted, right?
She completely fell for it.
Man, I should have become an actor!
Give this to Assemblyman Lee Sang-bok.
They will be more influential
than the Prosecutors' Office.
Lee's on a work trip to Japan
and won't come back before this weekend.
Mr. Gi.
Do you really need to do this?
You can back out if you want.
Not a nice thing to say to a man
who always carries a resignation letter.
What if Go Hae-ri decides
to leak it first to the media?
She doesn't have the guts or the ability.
Even if she does talk,
we can always deny it.
Hurry up. This place is about to close.
Explain it to me.
The flash drive your team took.
Why is it infected with a virus?
-How do you know that?
-I saw it with my own eyes.
GOOD-FOR-NOTHING
Yeah.
Where are you now?
Are you kidding me?
How can it be gone?
A virus infection.
You don't believe that, do you?
What if I don't?
Don't you remember what happened
after we came back to Korea?
A reporter died in front of me.
-They are trying to kill me.
-I know.
So what?
This means there's a mole inside the NIS
working for John &amp; Mark.
We have to find out who that is!
I don't have that kind of power.
What about O Sang-mi?
Who's investigating her?
There is no investigation.
Oh.
Shit.
You told me
that you serve the citizens.
You told me to trust you
because you are the experts!
Stop it.
Why do I need to be yelled at by you?
-What?
-I've done everything I could.
What am I supposed to do
when my bosses are covering it up?
Just be honest with me.
You were doing this for a promotion,
but now that you can't,
you're stepping out.
Find out the truth.
You get paid with our taxes.
Don't you have a sense of duty
as a civil servant?
My dad...
He died after saving eight lives
in the military.
He became a hero.
But it was so hard
for the rest of the family.
Civil servant?
Sense of duty?
I don't care about any of that shit.
I'm doing this just to get by.
If I get fired,
my family has to live without a roof.
You are not the only one having it hard.
HOONI'S ROOM
PLEASE KNOCK
Hurry up.
This place is about to close.
Explain it to me.
The flash drive your team took.
-Why is it infected with a virus?
-How do you know that?
SHARE
DELETE
I saw it with my own eyes.
Then why do you need an explanation?
...said that this event
could become the starting point.
Next up.
Families of the B357 crash victims
will be visiting the Blue House
to meet President Jeong Gook-pyo,
eleven o'clock this morning.
The families,
invited by the President himself,
will talk about their compensation
for the crash
and prevention of future accidents.
the Blue House hopes to console
the families through today's event,
and looks forward to opening communication
between the government and the families.
-Hello...
-It's me.
Why?
I'll tell you in person. Where are you?
No, I'll go to your place.
Hello?
What is she saying?
God, my head...
That was quick.
Wait up.
-Who is it?
-I just moved in next door.
Here are some rice cakes.
I see.
I came last night but you weren't here.
I'll leave them here.
Just a second, please.
Thanks for the food.
Who sent you?
Was it John &amp; Mark...
We have an emergency patient.
Excuse us. Please make way.
Dal-geon?
Shit.
Police operator speaking.
How can I help you?
Someone's been kidnapped!
He is in critical condition and suffering
from chest discomfort and dyspnea.
We'll be arriving in 20 minutes.
Hurry up. He's waking up any minute.
Hang on.
Let's see...
Don't you know how to drive?
Damn it.
Shit.
Get up if you're not dead.
Are you mad?
We don't get paid for murders,
you dipshit.
-Hop on!
-Get the needle.
Over here!
Are you okay?
Are you okay, sir?
Try to stay still.
The ambulance will be here any minute.
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
Then get in.
There's no time, get in!
You can't go. We received a kidnap call.
Hey, sir!
Listen.
You know about the the Blue House meeting
with the families, right?
Expose what you've just heard
in front of the President.
That piece of shit!
What if you get fired?
What about your family?
I'm the daughter of Colonel Go Gang-cheol,
Chief of the First Division,
and a marine hero.
Please don't look at me like that.
I'm so pissed off at myself, too.
Welcome.
This way, please.
Excuse me, sir.
What is your business here?
I'm a victim of the B357 crash.
You're late.
What is your name?
-Cha Dal-geon.
-Cha...
But I'm not on the guest list.
I'm afraid you cannot enter, then.
I'm with the NIS.
We really need to meet the President.
Let us in.
I'm sorry. Please leave.
Don't be sorry and just let us in.
I'm a victim, too.
How come they are allowed in and I'm not?
Open the gate.
Making a scene here
would only cause you trouble.
Trouble?
I'm a victim, too!
I need to see the President!
I want to see him!
-You can't.
-What?
-I understand.
-You are supposed to serve the people.
This is not acceptable! Let me go!
THE BLUE HOUSE TOUR BUS
Can you do it?
No matter how I try,
there is nothing on the news.
I have to do it.
Where are you going?
I told you to stay with mommy!
Here we go.
What have you got here? What is this?
Yes, good job.
Yes.
This is the script for today's meeting
with the families.
Is that necessary?
There are some who are upset.
In case of emergencies--
You should have filtered them out
from the list.
Accident victims
are not national heroes, are they?
Are they going to blame the government
if influenza breaks out?
Don't you think
this tie stands out too much?
I would prefer a plainer one.
Sang-min, come on. Smile.
Here we go. One, two...
Yes, thank you.
It looks nice.
Study hard.
Excuse me, where is the bathroom?
Did you not go, back at the Exhibit Hall?
I did but... My stomach hurts so much...
Follow me, please.
GUIDE MAP
CURRENT LOCATION
BLUE HOUSE MAIN OFFICE
The President of the Republic of Korea.
A tourist has gone missing.
This is control.
There is an intruder behind the annex.
Damn.
Follow him.
Stay here. And you go report this.
Stop!
Stop, sir!
Shit.
I'm a family member
of a plane crash victim.
I'm here to see the President.
-Arrest him.
-Stop.
I told you I'm a victim!
Let go.
Let me go, you bastards!
I need to see the President.
Tell him I'm here!
Let go of me!
-What's going on?
-Let go!
-He's an intruder.
-I'm a victim!
I came to meet the President.
Take him out.
-Let go!
-Let him in.
-We can't do that, sir.
-I'll take responsibility. Let him in.
That's a serious code violation.
Is anyone else here more serious
than that gentleman?
This is for us to decide.
-Even if you insist--
-How dare you disrespect the citizens!
This is exactly why they accuse us
of being authoritative.
-Please bring the gentleman in.
-Yes, sir.
Follow me, sir.
Chief, we have a problem.
As a person responsible
for the safety of the citizens,
I sincerely apologize to you once again.
Although the ICAO
is still examining the accident,
the government will also be taking
every possible measure,
such as performing its own investigation
and enacting special laws.
Sorry to interrupt you, sir.
A bereaved family member...
There seems to be another guest,
waiting outside this room.
Bring him in.
-Mr. President--
-It's okay. Let him in.
Do not be disrespectful.
Good to meet you.
We welcome your visit.
Yes, sir.
Did the guards hurt you or...
No, sir.
Take a seat.
Help him to his seat.
The plane.
It wasn't a failure. It was attacked.
What do you mean by that?
I mean, the co-pilot of the aircraft
worked with the terrorist
and took down the plane.
We have reporters in this room.
Even though you are bereaved,
you will have to take full responsibility
for making false statements.
I'm not making false statements.
A video file showing the terrorist's face
disappeared inside the NIS!
Is this true, Director An?
Well, that's...
This is a conversation recording
between NIS agents.
Hurry up. This place is about to close.
Explain it to me.
The flash drive your team took.
Why is it infected with a virus?
How do you know that?
I saw it with my own eyes.
Then why do you need an explanation?
Are you covering this up?
The plane crash killed 211 people.
Director's orders.
-Huh?
-What the...
What is going on?
Come this way, sir.
Dal-geon!
Ms. O. Where's your husband?
Where is Kim Woo-gi, the co-pilot?
Why are you doing this to me?
You signed a five-billion-won
insurance policy under his name
and you're the beneficiary!
What?
My...
My husband's death is killing me!
I...
Sang-mi, talk!
Don't pass out. Talk to us!
Mr. Gi!
I don't have to meet Assemblyman Lee.
Go Hae-ri loaded her gun
and pulled the trigger, just now!
That kid!
Breaking news.
It's been claimed that a terrorist attack
had caused aircraft B357
to fall on the Moroccan seas last month.
Cha is consistently arguing
that B357 was intentionally crashed
and the attack was led...
Call Shadow.
...by John &amp; Mark,
a global defense industry.
-He must be busy right now.
-Just call him!
The victims' families held
an urgent press conference and requested
to expel the NIS Director,
and organize a special prosecution team,
in order to find out the truth
about the B357 crash.
The opposition party announced a statement
regarding the crash
and expressed severe criticism
against the ruling party.
The government's incompetence
and corruption--
You made the right choice
choosing Cha Dal-geon.
...they are busy
protecting the President's reputation.
Lobbying is not about weapons.
...irresponsible in its role
of protecting the citizens--
It's about people.
Regarding pointed out
as the one behind the terrorist attack,
John &amp; Mark says
they want to check the facts
through a thorough investigation.
The NIS says
it will thoroughly investigate
the people involved in the case
and check the whereabouts of Kim Woo-gi,
the co-pilot Cha mentioned.
CO-PILOT MIGHT BE ALIVE
What was wrong with me?
RESIGNATION LETTER
You're insane, Go Hae-ri.
You're out of your mind. You're crazy.
RESIGNATION LETTER
Let's have a word.
I...
I'm quite busy.
That resignation letter--
As an NIS agent,
I don't regret what I have done.
When I resign
and return to being a civilian,
you can expect
a proper human-to-human apology from me.
Go Hae-ri.
Come with me.
I'll take full responsibility and resign.
What?
Take responsibility?
Are you a chief or a deputy?
Who are you to take the blame?
My resignation letter.
Did you think that a letter
would help you quit in peace
and go home just like that?
You are on your way to jail.
For leaking confidential information.
Excuse me?
J...
-Jail?
-You.
You've never met Cha Dal-geon.
-What?
-Just play stupid.
You've never given him the recording.
But Cha Dal-geon--
He wouldn't want you
getting fired either.
I'll try to take all the bullets,
so you can just...
Just stand there and act shamelessly!
I'm good at being shameless...
But if I do that,
Mr. Gi will take all the blame--
You are worried about Gi?
What about me?
If you admit your mistake,
I'm the one who has to resign.
Because of a nitwit like you!
Do you think I'm worried about you?
Man, you really can't make
heads or tails of anything.
Oh god.
Damn it.
Don't mind us.
-You're supposed to drink it.
-I'm okay.
I heard you were kidnapped
on your way here.
Yes, um...
They have been trying to kill me
since Morocco.
Who might you be referring to?
John &amp; Mark.
The co-pilot was working for John &amp; Mark
until a year ago,
and his wife used to be
their flight attendant.
And the one that benefitted the most
out of the plane crash--
I am very much impressed by Mr. Cha.
Despite the kidnapping
and the murder attempt,
you've mustered the courage
to expose the truth.
Please wait and see
while I find out what exactly happened.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Could I ask you for a favor?
Please go on.
As for the NIS agents in the recording,
please don't let them get fired.
Well, that is not up to me to decide--
If it weren't for those people,
we would never have known this much.
Please, Mr. President.
I think it's not a bad idea.
Everyone in this country
is paying attention to the NIS.
I don't think firing those involved
would look good.
I give you my word.
Let's hope we have smiles on our faces
the next time we meet.
Thank you, sir. Thank you very much!
Thank you.
Yeah?
We were ordered to escort Mr. Cha
to the safe house.
Whose order is that?
I asked the Chief
of the Presidential Security Service.
It seems dangerous
now that his identity is revealed.
That's fine. You don't have to--
No, let's do what Yun says.
You are a very important person
from now on.
Is the house guarded
by the Security Service?
The NIS will be there.
I'll take him to the safe house.
-Thank you, sir.
-Take care.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'll see to it that this gets fixed...
You already spilled the soup
and scalded my balls.
Fix what?
Please give me a chance.
I can fix this, sir.
Quit your job.
I made a mistake.
Please forgive me.
I took a water tester of Han River
that you were,
and made you Director of the NIS.
The least you could do is earn your keep.
Director An, get up.
Tell me, Prime Minister.
How should we take care of this crisis?
I mean, is there any other way?
We have to fix the root of the problem.
Who do you think should fix it?
The police? The prosecutors?
That's even more stressful.
I think our best option
is to let Director An deal with it.
If you give me one more chance,
I'll do the best I can
and sort out this situation.
Don't fire the ones in the recording.
It will only gather attention.
Yes, sir.
What a pity.
To let John &amp; Mark go to waste like this.
Are you serious?
What can I do? Look at the mess we're in.
Just because you gave An the task,
it doesn't mean you can't take action
from time to time.
The truth?
We can reveal it in the way we want.
What the hell are you saying?
Why should I take the blame?
If a child plays with fire,
the parents should take the blame.
Don't you see how Go Hae-ri humiliated
the organization?
Go Hae-ri.
Are you the one who leaked the recording?
I thought you didn't know it existed.
And you never even met Cha Dal-geon.
Answer me, Go. I know you're not the one
who gave him the recording.
-Sorry--
-I'm the one.
I recorded it
and gave it to Cha Dal-geon.
Gi! What are you talking about?
That's not true. Mr. Gi doesn't even know
Cha Dal-geon. It was me.
Are the two of you playing games with me?
Aren't you guys embarrassed?
Two hundred civilians were killed
and we are busy covering it up.
Is it normal for us
to be blaming these two?
This is why people blame us all the time.
They call us useless and irresponsible.
Hey, Gang.
We are not here
to listen to your complaints.
Want to get straightforward?
Who here believes
that the video was infected by a virus?
We all know someone deleted it,
yet we are turning a blind eye to it.
It's good that you brought it up.
Gi Tae-ung.
Is there any sign of hacking
from outside the NIS?
No, sir.
That means someone inside the NIS
personally planted the virus.
Even the security camera recordings
were intentionally deleted on that day.
You have to be a Chief or above
to enter the control room, right?
Was it you, Min?
Are you nuts?
I'm the one who got screwed
because of this case.
Fucking hell.
I thought it was you.
-What?
-You can't stand me being successful.
Weren't you trying to screw me over?
You bastard!
Excuse me.
The Director wants to talk to all of us.
Our President
has given us one more chance.
Starting with the B357 incident,
do your best
in doing your part for national security
and maximizing the benefit of our country.
-Understood?
-Yes, sir!
One, we always think and act
on the side of justice and truth.
One, we always predict and prepare
to guarantee national security.
One, we are always aware
that losing one's honor
is equal to losing honor as a whole.
Do you think we should run
a drug test on him?
How can he not fire you
for leaking confidential information?
You can say that I'm an unlucky person,
but I hit the jackpot,
when it comes to my career.
Hey, who do you think is the dirty traitor
who deleted the video file?
I don't know.
It can't be Chief Min,
looking at the way he acted.
It can't be Chief Gang, either.
Chief Park from Inspection?
-Or Chief Choi--
-That's right--
Hello, sir.
Hey, Hwa-suk!
I would like to formally apologize.
About the recording.
I didn't intend to pin it on you.
Things got out of control so quickly and--
It's true.
I didn't mean to cause you trouble--
Well done.
Close your mouth, girl,
before flies get in!
He just praised me.
I just heard this from Se-hun.
You weren't the only one
with the recording.
Mr. Gi didn't tell you but... Come here.
Why is he so late?
Did Shadow say he's coming?
Are you saying I'm hearing things?
It's just that he doesn't move easily.
Damn it.
How dare he mess up the face of an angel?
Cha Dal-geon, that bastard.
How should I shred him into pieces?
Yes, Mr. Hong.
What do you think?
I'm getting ready for a revenge match.
You can stop now.
What are you talking about?
Don't you want Cha Dal-geon dead?
Another team will take over.
Is this because...
you don't trust me?
Cha Dal-geon is going
to the NIS' safehouse now.
How does that matter?
It's not easy there, it's dangerous.
So it's dangerous for me,
but not for the other guy?
Who is it?
Who's the asshole that snatched my client?
They are deadly and very brutal.
Send him in.
Shadow himself is here at last.
You...
Want one?
Thanks.
Go get the empty plates now.
With Cha Dal-geon's head on them.
Subtitle translation by Daham Yoon