SAMAEL SENT A MESSAGE
Engine number three failed.
The cabin altitude is rising.
Do we have a hole somewhere?
Why isn't the panel working?
Latitude, altitude, airspeed.
Nothing's visible, sir.
Let's stand by and take control.
The stick isn't working. What's wrong?
That's the end
of the flight deck recording.
Fill it up, please.
My gosh.
I'm thirsty and hungry.
I'm sorry but...
Can you go in there and grab me some?
What?
-What's wrong?
-Get in the car!
HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT...
Presuming a terrorist attack
based on a call is a stretch.
It seems to me like codes.
But I don't get these times.
Miss Go.
More than 90% of the evidence
points to aircraft failure.
Please try not to cause confusion.
Okay.
I'll come back
with a solid piece of evidence.
Thank you for your help.
The times are identical.
Look. The first sign of malfunction
appeared at 13:15.
The panel stopped working at 13:20.
Why isn't the panel working?
The stick malfunction at 13:23.
The stick isn't working.
The time of the plane crash...
13:30
Help!
Where is...
Over here!
A gunshot... Oh!
He got shot!
He got shot! Understand?
For the sake of the innocent victims,
we must find out the truth.
Please help, Doctor.
The ICAO will never agree
without any concrete evidence.
I have a video clip of the terrorist.
I'll send it to you by e-mail.
Let's do this.
We'll dig up the truth about the crash.
Thank you, Doctor.
Go Hae-ri speaking.
Ho-sik got shot.
Huh? What happened?
I know the hospital.
I'll stop by my house and go there.
Wait!
You were right.
We found evidence from the black box.
The plane...
was attacked.
I'll fill you in later.
What?
Where did my laptop go?
Mask off. Now!
You... The hotel cleaner?
Tell them he's with the one
who crashed the plane.
Turn around.
Get down on your knees.
Who sent you?
I don't know.
I was offered 10,000 euros
for killing you and staging a suicide.
Even if I kill you right now,
it would be self-defense.
Talk if you want to live.
I'm telling you.
We only talked on the phone.
Take out your phone.
Call that person.
If you don't, I'll shoot.
Hello...
-Hey, say something.
-Dal-geon?
How come you have this phone?
Ho-sik is still in surgery.
Are you saying this is Ho-sik's phone?
You're the one who called.
Listen carefully, Dal-geon.
The person who owns this phone,
just tried to kill me.
What?
Catch Ho-sik.
He's with the terrorist.
If we catch Ho-sik,
we can solve this case.
Where is the guy?
The man who got shot!
That guy!
Ho-sik? It's Cha Dal-geon.
Do you know where Go Hae-ri is staying?
Why do you ask?
The video is gone?
Don't worry.
I sent a copy to my NIS colleague.
We'll identify the terrorist
by tomorrow.
That's a relief. I'll wait for your call.
Go on.
We have a problem here.
I'm listening.
-Don't come near me!
-Mr. Kim.
You see this?
One bite and I'm gone.
-Stop acting crazy.
-Crazy?
You are the crazy ones.
Stop the bullshit!
Why did you kill my nephew?
Why did you blow up the plane?
Let's cool down and talk.
Don't throw away your life.
Think of your wife and daughter.
To save my wife and daughter,
this is the only way.
Mr. Kim!
Stay with me, Mr. Kim.
Don't...
Don't do anything.
Those people...
They are terrifying.
-Mr. Kim!
-Hey. You!
Talk before you die. Who are they? Huh?
-Stop it.
-Talk, you bastard!
Who is it?
Who killed my nephew?
-Talk!
-Stop it now!
Christ!
Please hurry. It's an emergency.
I called the police.
-Give me the gun.
-What? Why?
Your hands are shaking. Give it!
Shut up.
You're a civilian and I'm a special agent.
I'm not going to let you die.
So don't worry and just trust--
Fuck.
Hey!
What a nutcase!
Come on!
-You wanna kill yourself?
-What about you?
Getting you shot will be the end of me.
Wait right here.
What are you doing?
Do you know how hard I trained
for a situation like this?
This injury is not-- Ouch!
What the--
Do you see that car?
Can you get there in three seconds?
He's using a bolt-action rifle.
He has to work the bolt after each shot,
which takes three seconds.
A moving target makes it harder.
We will have a better chance
if we get there.
It's out of range from the roof.
We have to make it in just three seconds.
Can you do it?
Four seconds.
Run!
-What?
-Do you want to get shot?
Even a slight scratch
will leave a hole under your chin.
Special gadget for special agents?
No one's here.
Where did he go? Shit.
Damn!
MEMORIAL TOWER
PLEDGE TO THE NATION
Security sweep.
Everybody stand up.
-Your cooperation is appreciated.
-Bear with us.
Why?
What is this? This is so embarrassing.
You're new, right?
Hey, watch your hands.
Stop groping me, you bastard!
For god's sake.
Do you have everything?
Let me take one video file.
We're from the same town. Come on, Kim!
Do you have something to hide?
It's a picture of me butt naked.
It'll hurt your eyes.
No worries.
My insurance will take care of it.
That idiot. I should gouge his eyes out!
What's this?
What the hell is going on?
There's been a security breach
in this room.
Does that mean you can sweep the place?
Who gave the order?
Mr. Gi Tae-ung did, sir.
God, damn it...
Where is that prick?
Hey, Gi Tae-ung.
Did you order a sweep of my office
behind my back?
You've grown some balls.
Seven years ago, today,
my colleague died.
I believe you know him.
Code name, Blaise Pascal.
When there's a security sweep
your predecessors always gave a heads-up.
That's how things work,
courtesy to your superiors.
The operation was a success
and he had time to escape but...
Do you know why he died?
Because the operation command violated
a small rule.
-Hey, that was--
-That's why...
my friend died for nothing.
I'll get rid of wrong traditions,
and stick to the rules.
Damn that cocky bastard.
Honorable Chief Gang.
Can I ask you a small favor?
Go Hae-ri sent me a video
but the Inspection guys took it
in a security sweep.
Your authority would...
Chief?
Chief, help me this once!
You know very well
Mr. Gi always listens to you!
Sir?
Come on, Chief!
Just this once...
Disgusting.
He must have drunk his ass off last night.
Oh, stuff it.
He has no authority at all.
Gross.
Don't...
Don't do anything.
Those people... They are terrifying...
Loss of secret intelligence,
use of unauthorized equipment, hacking.
There are 27 security breaches.
This is a 30% increase
on last year's first quarter.
Now, please turn to page five
of the report in front of you.
GO HAE-RI
The person you're trying to reach...
He's ignoring my call again.
Fine, you do that.
I'll make you regret so bad.
Any unauthorized equipment
found during a full inspection
will be strictly dealt--
Sorry, I'm late.
Don't bother coming when you're late.
Oh, you mean it?
How many times have I told you
to turn off your phone?
Sorry, sir.
Yes, I'm in a meeting. Bye.
The plane crash...
It was a terrorist attack.
What?
I just uncovered a grand secret
from the black box.
We have been a laughing stock.
But if you and I catch this terrorist,
we can shove a big one
to those who screwed us over.
Gang. What are you doing?
Turn it off and...
The B357 crash was a terrorist attack.
-What?
Chief? Hello?
The Director General is here.
Report directly.
GO HAE-RI
This is An.
What do you mean by a terrorist attack?
This is Agent Go Hae-ri from Morocco.
I found a phone call of the terrorist
from the black box audio file.
There is an accomplice.
It's Kim Woo-gi,
the co-pilot of the plane.
-Are you sure about this?
-Yes.
I checked it together
with Dr. Kevin of the ICAO.
I sent Agent Gong Hwa-suk
a clip of the terrorist.
I'll return to the HQ
with further details.
Go. Who said you could come back?
You should write up
a detailed report first and--
Return right now!
Right away, sir.
They're pulling me back.
We should hurry to the hotel
to get our stuff.
You go alone.
The terrorist and the co-pilot
are hiding here somewhere.
I'm not going home until I catch them.
Do you think we're at a zoo?
Are they going to show up on schedule
if you want them to?
They will show up again.
Because they want me dead.
If I get those two, I can end this.
You need to understand the situation.
They tampered with the airport cameras
in just two hours.
Isn't it obvious that some big shots
are behind those two?
Who are those big shots?
Why did they kill
all those innocent people?
Why did my nephew have to die? Why?
That's why we should go back to Seoul.
To find answers.
There's nothing we can do here.
And our life is under threat.
Your country has what it takes.
The NIS will be investigating the case,
so don't worry and come with me to Seoul.
No need to wait.
Who's taking charge?
I'll take it, sir.
Go Hae-ri is under my command.
I'll take it.
Six years ago, Mr. Gang worked
with the British MI6
and apprehended Abu Sayyaf,
a terrorist group.
-When it comes to terrorists, Mr. Gang--
-Min can take it.
Yes, sir.
Go's video must be
in the Inspection Team.
Let's check that first.
-What?
-It's not working.
What happened?
It's a virus.
How can you idiots
let a virus come through?
We're figuring it out.
I don't care. Just restore the video.
How long to restore?
An expert is coming.
We don't have time. Restore it today.
Min, keep this confidential.
Yes, sir.
Does that mean
I don't have to worry about the NIS?
By the way, when can I meet you?
Turning me down again?
You should treat me better.
Or else I may harm you--
Shadow.
I made it but it's a good nickname.
The way Shadow works
is just like a stealth jet.
Silent and precise.
I'll tell Dr. Kevin not to worry
about the NIS.
Tell him to conclude it quickly.
-Dynamic System's aircraft failure.
-Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Minister!
Who would have guessed?
I heard you're a great golfer.
Let's go for a round sometime.
I'll do my best to accompany you.
I don't fraternize
with defense contractors.
He's so stiff-necked.
Do you have the documents ready?
Lieutenant General Lim Pil-gyu,
Head of Policy Advisor for the MND.
He takes care of the F-X Plan business.
President Jang Dong-gyu
of the Institute for Defense Analysis.
He hosted the press conference.
Choi Sang-bae. He is the Policy Advisor
in the Ministry of National Defense.
These three are close aides
of Minister Park Man-yeong.
They're deeply involved in the F-X Plan.
Lim Pil-gyu was involved in corruption,
back when he was in Logistics Command.
Jang Dong-gyu received big money
for exempting military obligation
of an acquaintance's son.
When Choi was in service,
he was accused
of molesting a female officer.
Lim Pil-gyu's documents.
Send them to Jang.
Send Jang's documents to Choi.
And Choi's documents to Lim.
We need to think smarter
to trap Minister Park.
LIM PIL-GYU
There can only be one second-in-command.
So these three colleagues are also rivals.
MILITARY POLICE UNIT 1
PETITION
What can be more fun
than a rival's weakness?
Send them a call sign,
they will all come running.
What brings you here?
I'd like to ask the same.
So you all came.
Thank you very much
for accepting my invites.
Let them in.
Today's event is my treat for you,
so please enjoy.
What's the meaning of this?
Those who feel uncomfortable may leave.
But the rest of us
will have a serious discussion
about the one who leaves first.
What do you think you're doing?
Thank you for coming, Minister.
Where are they?
Come this way.
I whisper in your ears
And stay by your side
But I always feel so sad
Why can't you accept
My love
You are my Mona Lisa, Mona Lisa
You make me feel sad
What the hell is this?
Mr. Minister.
Get out!
Damn it...
If I were you,
I would think this is a good time
for us to have a drink.
Do you think I will surrender
to your dirty threat?
Do you think it's a threat?
But I haven't asked you anything yet.
You picked the wrong fight.
You can't take over the F-X Plan.
One for corruption.
One for bribery.
One for sexual harassment.
You didn't know that, did you?
The top of the stream is clean,
yet the bottom is filthy.
The moment you choose Dynamic System,
what happened here
and your men's wrongdoings
will be released.
The public is already all worked up
after the plane crash.
How will you deal with all the criticism?
I feel bad.
It's not my intention
to pick a fight with you.
I know a lot of dirty secrets
in the US Department of Defense.
I also have some information
that the Blue House might like.
In other words,
I have a ton of gifts
I can offer you.
Are you offering a deal?
A deal built on trust is easily broken,
but a deal built on weakness
is hard to get rid of.
I don't know any of your weaknesses.
If so,
let's make one.
I think...
you could become a great weakness for me.
I told you we should hurry.
Happy now?
We missed the plane.
I can't even turn my own lights on.
This is why
you should have a good partner.
Aren't you eating?
I'll eat all of it.
Don't whine about it later--
If the NIS starts investigating,
will you take part?
That question sounds borderline insulting.
Of course, I will.
I'm the one who uncovered it all.
Why? Don't you trust me?
I'm a promising agent, you know.
Once I solve this case...
By the way,
do you have trust issues?
I can read people like an X-ray machine.
You are full of doubts.
Quick-tempered and feisty all the time.
How about you?
You struggled to trust me.
That's because of my job.
But you have a problem.
Still, that crooked personality of yours
got us somewhere.
No claps for me?
I dug up something big today.
How did you come to raise Hoon?
You don't seem like a kid person.
Go to sleep. I'll be on guard.
Excuse me, Mr. Civilian?
Guard duties
are not for civilians like you,
but for special agents like me.
Get some sleep. I'll protect you.
Go--
Protect me like this?
You'll stand no chance against him.
I was off guard that time.
The NIS pays me for a reason.
I don't sleep with any girl.
Suit yourself. I don't care.
Excuse me. You're not my type.
I like tall, intelligent
fair-skinned men.
What? Any girl?
Do you need medication?
You're seriously delusional.
Jesus.
Fine. Let's see who falls asleep first.
When you snore,
I'll be sticking this up your nose.
Could you please keep your head straight?
I'm sure they are watching us.
Isn't that man acting weird?
You're the weirdest here.
Just look at him.
Two o'clock.
I am looking at him.
That's what the shades are for.
This is why I can't work with amateurs.
You are right. That is so weird.
I'm sure they are having an affair.
Good instincts, Mr. Cha.
I am not a traitor.
I was trying to find the co-pilot
and take matters into my own hands.
If it wasn't for Cha Dal-geon,
I could've taken him out.
Samael will take care of
Cha Dal-geon and the co-pilot.
No. Let me do it.
This time, there will be no mistakes...
The NIS will take care of Go Hae-ri.
What about Cha Dal-geon?
Obstacles are meant to be removed.
We're already on thin ice.
Find out where Lily is.
-She should be in the US.
-Call her now.
No one here is more reliable than her.
Gosh, you should've called earlier.
I was about to go on a vacation
to Miami Beach tonight.
Right now?
I'll have my vacation in Korea.
In return,
book me a first-class ticket, please.
Me?
I beg you...
-Don't kill me.
-I'm working.
Are you certain, sir?
NIS DIRECTOR GENERAL
AN GI-DONG
I understand.
Yes, sir.
How strange.
He's like a ghost.
He's on the plane,
but not on the passenger list?
Is that possible?
Something is up.
Am I right?
Maybe they got the wrong guy.
Passenger lists are never wrong.
Two people saw the video.
It's not likely
that both of them are wrong.
Is there any chance
of restoring that video?
-No, sir.
-Who knows about this apart from Go?
The ones who sat in the meeting
and a few Inspection staff.
Drop the case.
-Sir.
-The video never existed.
Min, keep Go's mouth shut.
Gi, take care of your men.
I'll handle the chiefs.
Two hundred people died in the crash.
One hundred and eight of them,
our citizens!
Just because a video was lost--
Just do as you're told!
We just lost conclusive evidence
of a terrorist attack.
Do you think we'll be fine
if word gets out?
We will be as good as dead!
The ICAO will conclude
that the aircraft malfunctioned.
Let's just wait and see.
We can start investigating
if they suggest a terrorist attack.
Don't tell Go Hae-ri the details.
It's risky because she's a rookie.
Yes, sir.
I don't get it. There could--
Stop sticking your nose in.
Look at us. It was all for nothing.
You blew my shot at a promotion.
Is that all you care about, right now?
What did you say?
You may not give a shit
because your family is rich
and you lead a comfortable life,
but promotion matters to me.
Raising three kids
is not a joke, you know.
Gi Tae-ung.
I'm curious.
The video...
Don't you think
it was destroyed on purpose?
I mean, the timing is so perfect.
A video file is confiscated
after a security sweep,
and a virus destroys it.
The only image of the terrorist
is gone, just like that.
Are you saying that it was me?
Just saying.
Who cares now?
We are dropping it anyway.
DELETE
Welcome.
Wow.
I guess you made some money, Jessica.
But you look old now.
She's a CEO. Have some respect.
Come on, there's no need for respect
between us.
Am I right?
You haven't changed.
You're still a bitch.
A bitch employee for a bitch employer.
I'm a bit tired, so let's talk business.
Cha Dal-geon. He's a stuntman.
A stuntman?
Did a movie investment go bust?
B357. His family member was on it.
You will have to pay a big one.
A big one? That's not what we agreed on.
You didn't know.
I charge regular prices for bad guys,
but there's a premium for good guys.
Hey, Lily.
Follow-up service included.
I'll finish the job perfectly.
-If you keep this up--
-Take it or leave it.
I'll just take a tour of Korea instead.
I like places with a lot of tombs.
Gyeongju is the place!
No guns.
No poisoning, either.
I'm saying you should never leave
traces of murder.
Meet potassium chloride cocktail.
When this enters a body through the veins,
the heart cannot take it.
The autopsy report will say
it's a heart attack.
So you are planning to inject that
into Cha Dal-geon's neck?
Can you bell a cat?
Are you trying to insult me?
I'm Lily.
Ten percent in advance.
The rest when it's done.
I usually get half in advance.
So, where is our dear client right now?
I'll have it if you won't.
So your appetite is back?
You had nothing since yesterday.
Excuse me.
Could you...
Thank you.
This will make you feel better.
-Let me prick your finger.
-I'm fine.
Just do as I say and give me your hand.
God, your hand is so cold.
I know how you feel.
You blame yourself.
I felt the same when my dad died.
Blaming yourself makes you
sad and angry.
But we will get the terrorist,
thanks to you.
You can stop feeling sorry.
Jeez, look at that black blood.
It's worse than I thought.
-I'm sorry.
-You should watch where you are going.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
-Dal-geon, what's wrong?
-Let me see him.
-Dal-geon!
-Are you okay, sir?
Looks like a heart attack.
Call the ambulance!
This is an emergency.
Please send an ambulance.
Incheon Airport Arrival Hall. Hurry!
Dal-geon, wake up!
AMBULANCE
We'll pick him up
and inject the potassium chloride
into his veins.
And the bell's on the cat's neck.
What do you say?
He's coming.
We just arrived. Where are you?
Let's start.
-I'm sorry.
-You should watch where you are going.
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Subtitle translation by Daham Yoon