We are collecting signatures
to find out the truth about B357!
WHAT HAS THE GOVERNMENT DONE
FOR THE B357 ACCIDENT?
Your participation matters
in finding out the truth!
Please participate.
We are collecting signatures
to find out the truth about B357!
Your participation matters
in finding out the truth.
Please sign the petition.
We are collecting signatures
to find out the truth about--
Those among the bereaved families
who don't play along with us,
they hate the government for everything,
just like the bloody commies.
It's not only them.
You know Gi
and those who follow Gang, right?
I'm watching their phones
and listening to their calls.
They are all on my radar around the clock.
So don't you worry, Yun.
What about Edward?
Of course, we are watching him, too.
We'll tap his phone
when the warrant is issued.
The civil trial for the bereaved
will be held on the 15th, next month.
Exactly.
If Kim Woo-gi doesn't show up until then,
it'll finally be game over.
What if he does?
I assure you,
he will never set foot on this country.
We basically own this country.
Do you think he has even a tiny chance?
Hell, no.
I'd love to see them try.
REST IN PEACE, GANG JU-CHEOL
Chief Gang is alive?
But the doctor announced his death
right in front of me.
How can he be alive? Is he Jesus?
There's no time, so listen carefully.
ONE WEEK BEFORE
This is Edward from Dynamic.
Don't talk. Just listen.
The phone you're holding right now
is synced to Chief Min Jae-sik's phone.
He can see where you are
and what you are doing.
As you know,
the situation here is disastrous.
If no one inside the NIS helps us,
he will never stand in court
even if he comes in.
I beg you, Mr. Gi.
You have to help us.
Soon, your phone will be tapped as well.
Be careful.
Put that in Gang's meal
and make sure he eats it.
What is it?
Nothing.
He'll just have a seizure
and then a fatal heart attack.
We can't have an autopsy.
He has no family anyway,
so just sign him out
for cremation.
What are we supposed to do now?
Hello, it's Bullet Chicken.
We deliver faster than a bullet.
Sorry, we're closed for today.
No delivery now.
-I'm sorry.
-This...
This is Gi Tae-ung.
Let me.
Thank you.
SOUP/POISON/CPK3061/VAGABOND
CPK3... What does it do?
It's a secret poison,
used only by a few Black agents.
Sir!
Please open your eyes!
Get off me! Sir!
If he doesn't take the antidote
within five minutes,
he'll never wake up.
You guys must be out of your minds!
What if it actually kills him?
Hae-ri will show up with Kim Woo-gi.
Someone has to help Chief Gang.
Why are you doing this to me?
What did I do wrong?
For crying out loud!
This really is a bad year for me.
Don't worry. Mr. Gi isn't a traitor.
How do you know?
If he were,
he would've killed us at the embassy.
Hang on a second.
If the government is in on it,
then this is beyond my ability.
I know you're not capable.
I wish it weren't you.
However, now you're the only one
I can entrust this grave task.
-070--
-070-1584-1779
-Codename Vagabond.
-Call that number before you return.
Welcome, Go Hae-ri.
Who is...
Gang Ju-cheol?
How dare you call me by my name?
Chief!
Where are you?
We're smuggling ourselves on a ship.
For now, give me the time and place
of your arrival.
On the 15th, at 9 a.m.
We'll be disembarking
at Incheon Container Terminal No. 1.
The container number, KHCH 35679-19.
15TH, 09:00, INCHEON CONTAINER TERMINAL 1
KHCH 35679-19
-You must be bored in that cargo ship.
-Excuse me?
Min Jae-sik is desperate
to catch you guys.
We need to come up with a diversion.
We found Kim Woo-gi!
What's going on?
Where is it?
Port of Tarifa, south of Spain.
They are on a ship?
-Yes.
-Where are they headed?
Morocco.
They just escaped from there.
Why would they go back?
Kim Woo-gi is here, too!
What? Where?
Charles de Gaulle Airport, France.
Is this feed live?
What are they, Doctor Strange?
He's here, too!
Port of Naples, Italy.
They're at Antalya Airport, Turkey, too!
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
That's Cha Dal-geon!
What's going on?
I appreciate your hardworking
day and night for the nation.
What the hell?
Even Mr. Yun is there.
Hey, Gi Tae-ung.
You pretended to be all righteous,
so how do you live with yourself?
What the fuck...
Min Jae-sik.
I won't even bother calling you names.
Son of a...
You're all...
...absolutely fucked up, assholes!
Because I am...
...soon going to destroy you.
Turn it off.
-Huh?
-Cut him off right now!
Yes, sir.
What's wrong, Yun?
How long does it take to trace him?
Five minutes at best.
But it might take even days.
Make everyone wear a receiver.
Prepare to welcome our guest again.
Do you think Cha will come back?
He showed up for a reason.
I'm sure.
He will come back.
Oh...
Everyone, stand by.
-Get your receivers.
-Yes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Gi.
What do you think Cha wants?
I think he wants evidence.
Evidence?
O Sang-mi's press conference
turned the tables around.
He must be thinking
Kim's testimony is not enough.
So he wants us to slip
and say something incriminating?
That bastard is trying
to pull a petty trick on us.
Cha Dal-geon and Go Hae-ri
are Kim Woo-gi's kidnappers.
Gi, tell them to turn themselves in
and stall time.
Yes, sir.
They cut us off first.
What are they playing at?
They're taking the initiative.
They also need time
to trace your current location.
But the NIS has the latest technology.
Are you sure we are okay?
Don't worry about that.
What in the world is
in that chicken place?
CONSPIRACY THEORY
You're doing it again!
I told you not to grab chickens
with that nose-picking finger of yours.
Okay.
-It's disgusting.
-Okay.
You can call them donkeys,
and call us stallions.
Anyway, you need to stay alert
when you're against Yun Han-gi.
Tracing your IP might not work,
but he can still catch you
based only on a couple of words.
It sounds dangerous.
Do we really have to play it this way?
Even Gi Tae-ung is being watched.
We need to sneak behind their backs,
or we'll never bring Kim Woo-gi
back home.
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
Get started.
Yes.
Pyramid, pyramid...
Code break...
They are back in!
Put it on!
I can't believe you guys.
How rude. We are valuable informants.
Informants, my ass. You are kidnappers.
Mr. Gi, you are so shameless.
How can you lie like this
when you already know the truth?
Stop committing any more crimes.
Turn yourself in.
What, crimes? Crimes?
Hey.
How dare you mention that word?
All those people died for nothing
and you're killing them
for the second time!
Is that what civil servants
are paid to do?
They are pissing me off.
Any progress on the trace?
The IP address is very complicated.
Hurry the hell up, you stupid.
I'm Senior Secretary for this country.
Did you say "for this country"?
Aren't you embarrassed?
The truth is for the government
to find out.
You only need to bring me Kim Woo-gi.
Hey, let me ask you something.
Are you the boss of all this?
Or...
Are you taking orders from the President?
I'm asking if the President
is ordering you to do this.
Wait, nope. I asked the wrong question.
If you say no, you become a traitor.
If you say yes,
that would make the President an asshole.
Well, my bad. I take that question back.
Edward Park is in custody.
Dynamic cannot protect you now.
Bring Kim Woo-gi to us,
and Mr. Yun here will do his best
to meet your demands.
You will meet our demands?
In that case,
I want all of you to come clean
in front of the whole country.
Then I'll turn myself in.
I said I'll turn myself in, bastards!
Why are you all quiet?
Yes, Chief.
-Finish it now.
-Yes, sir.
Edward's secretary. Was it Micky?
Don't tell her anything about Vagabond.
I suggest you repent...
...and live a new life,
you bunch of garbage!
Did you trace them?
Um, you should take a look at this.
What the hell is all this?
These are the IP waypoints
I managed to find.
Europe, Japan, China, Turkey, India...
There are 43 locations.
Damn it. Why is it so complicated?
Analyze Cha Dal-geon's video,
and get someone better than you
to trace that IP, okay?
Move it!
-Yes, sir.
Looking at the hacking skill,
Edward must be behind them.
What should we do?
We have to release him soon.
Darn it...
You may leave.
I believe you people enjoy eavesdropping.
Keep the watch as well.
I don't like using stuff
that someone else has touched.
Chief Min.
I'm mad with you,
but the person next to you...
...makes me more mad.
This is not only about the F-X plan.
It's a battle between truth and lies,
good and evil.
Lies cannot bury the truth.
And evil cannot defeat good.
Our history proves that. But why!
Why can't you see that...
...when you have power?
Senior Secretary Yun Han-gi.
What happened here?
I also just got here.
We are in the middle of the ocean.
He can't escape.
You two should stay together.
I'll look for him alone.
If you make a mistake
and end up killing Kim--
Don't worry. I don't make mistakes.
Hey, Kim.
Stop wasting time and show yourself.
Don't move!
Get a boat ready. A motorboat.
If you don't, I will kill this bitch.
No matter what you do, you can't escape.
Shut the hell up!
She's bleeding, you bastard!
Go on and move, you shit.
Let's see what happens to her.
After the trial,
do you think they'll let me live?
Even if I make it to Korea,
I will never testify on your orders.
I won't! It'll get me killed!
You shameless piece of shit.
Shame? Name someone who does have shame.
The Blue House? The NIS?
You are no different!
You're so obsessed with revenge.
You don't even blink an eye
for the people that die!
-Shut up, you prick!
-You little...
Just give him what he wants.
Get the damn boat already
and send him away!
Are you mad?
-Now that we finally caught him!
-He says he's going to kill me.
Don't you see the blood on my neck?
Hey, he won't kill you. Trust me.
What if he does?
Do you even care about my life?
Why are you so afraid?
You're a NIS special agent!
Do you think the government supplies us
a couple of extra lives?
Whatever. Just die, then!
What did you just say?
-You're worse than Kim Woo-gi.
-What was that?
What do you think you are doing--
Let me see.
I'm fine. It's just a scratch.
You're bleeding a lot!
-I'm okay.
-I might as well just--
Hey, don't do it.
Stop.
Should I just kill him? My gosh.
Let me see.
That was so close.
Don't you think
my shoulder throw was awesome?
The guy who taught me
must've been proud.
Here.
Ouch, wait! It stings...
Blow on it.
-What?
-Blow some air on it.
Oh, it stings!
-Is that okay?
-Harder.
Wait...
It hurts!
It hurts so much.
Why is your face so red?
Do you have a fever?
What are you talking about?
I think you have a fever.
You do!
Hey, I have no fever. No.
Maybe you got scratched by a nail
during the fight.
If you're infected--
No, I'm totally fine.
I didn't get hurt at all.
Nothing's wrong.
Even your ears are red.
Oh, this is because Kim pissed me off!
I mean it!
-That bastard...
-Well, if you say so...
Hey, um, I need to go to the toilet.
I'll put the ointment on myself.
Do I...
Do I know you from somewhere?
You look strangely familiar.
Do you take business trips to Europe?
How much do you get from Dynamic?
I can pay you tenfold.
Maybe even more. Double?
We have now met quorum.
From now on, for the purpose
of securing future growth,
expanding social overhead capital,
and introducing
next-generation fighter jets,
we will take a vote for the approval
of the revised budget plan.
Sir, we already know the results.
Why are you so nervous?
As a politician, I never believe it
when I'm told not to worry.
I'd rather trust a merchant
who claims he's selling at a loss.
I will now declare the results.
Out of 259 members...
A total of 194 were in favor, 55 against,
and 10 abstained.
I hereby announce
that the new budget is approved.
We got it!
Congratulations, sir.
Well done, Minister Park.
Director An.
You shouldn't forget Yun, too.
He had a major role.
Thank you, Secretary Yun.
You're welcome, sir.
This calls for a celebration.
Let's go and have a feast.
Make a reservation at Anilok.
I'm paying today.
Yes, sir.
-Minister Park.
-Yes.
Seal the deal with John &amp; Mark right away.
Our people are calling for it.
Yes, sir.
REPUBLIC OF KOREA AIRFORCE
PROCUREMENT AGREEMENT
MINISTRY OF NATIONAL DEFENSE
REPUBLIC OF KOREA
Now, for the tremendous success in
our future business, let's have a toast.
Yes.
Minister, would you like to do the honors?
-Me?
-You worked more than anyone for this.
To our future! Love! Work!
Missile launch!
You sure know how to propose a toast.
I've prepared something, too.
These are a few of my prized possessions.
I'd like to throw an auction.
-Did you say "auction"?
-Don't be afraid.
I'm not taking money.
You are to bet on these
by showing me some sincerity.
And how would you like us to do that?
Well...
You can write me a letter.
Or you can pour me a glass.
If that's the case,
I can bet as much as you want.
This is a 1910 drawing
by a painter named Anek,
an impressionist artist
known for his unique drawing style.
The separated colors emphasize
the purity of the tones.
The colors were not mixed on a palette.
They were both mixed and used
on the canvas itself.
This one was drawn
by Woldam Kim Seong-hun.
An extremely famous artist,
I believe you already know.
I think you are all wondering
about the market price.
On the black market,
it is traded for about 400,000 dollars.
Dear me.
Excuse me for a moment.
Mr. Hong will continue with the auction.
Let me introduce you to the next painting.
I'm listening.
Right now?
Don't get up.
How rude of you.
I came here as soon as possible
and you made me wait.
Let's talk business
before we start eating.
Can't we start with the eating first?
As for the agreed amount...
You can send it to this account.
You are so lame.
DEEP BLUE
-"Deep Blue"?
-It's a trading company in Singapore.
Hong, got the account number?
Send the money we prepared.
The President must be in such a hurry.
It'll obviously be a paper company.
But whose is it?
I mean, the President
can't possibly be the CEO.
You just need to send the money.
You know that five percent
of the bid is huge, right?
I worked my ass off
to get the money prepared.
Yes, I get it.
You want me to get to the chase?
But I am a bit disappointed.
I was hoping to hear
some kind of a compliment, at least.
Check the account.
Pick your food.
Can I order drinks?
Yes, but I don't drink when I work.
Please set me up a dinner meeting
with the President.
I have a business opportunity,
perfect for his taste.
What? A deal?
The MND and John &amp; Mark
already signed a deal.
They will announce it soon.
But the trial hasn't even started.
How rotten are you guys?
Can we trust the justice department?
Kim Woo-gi's testimony won't be enough.
We need a solid piece of evidence.
Darn it...
-This is...
-What are you doing?
Why did you lock yourselves in?
What's wrong with this door?
Did you lock it, Hae-ri?
Huh? Was it me?
We were about to eat noodles.
Would you like some?
How long have you been working for Edward?
I saw you earlier and...
You seemed to know how to use guns.
We get trained, all the lobbyists.
I guess you're right. It's like
a car salesman needs a driver's license.
I'm getting off this ship
at the next stop.
It wouldn't be good for the trial
if we arrive together.
Anyway, thanks for your help, Micky.
Hey.
Do you have any evidence?
I don't mean a testimony or hearsay.
Something we can submit to the court.
Did you know...
that Michael had a girlfriend?
I know he had a mistress.
What about it?
You asked me earlier,
about how I met Michael.
I met Michael through his girlfriend.
That woman...
was the one
who introduced Jerome to Michael.
-She was Asian.
-Her face?
Did you see her face?
Maybe?
Did you ask for proof?
There is one.
A good one.
What is it?
A video file
of me and Michael making a deal.
What's your agenda?
What do you mean?
Why are you being helpful all of a sudden?
I don't think he wants my help. Come on.
I'll just go back to being quiet again.
If what Kim said is true,
it will turn this country upside down.
I don't think he is lying, sir.
You're arriving tomorrow, right?
Give me the time and location again.
9 a.m. tomorrow,
Incheon Container Terminal No. 1.
Container number, KHCH 35679-19.
TOMORROW
Gi and I will be waiting there.
I thought Gi was under surveillance.
How can he come?
That's why we need a good finale.
You guys will need to set it up nicely.
Don't worry. I'm a pretty good actress.
Min has sharp eyes.
Be careful.
I need you to give this to Gi.
What about the rent?
I partly own this restaurant.
Seriously? You only paid two million won.
Wasn't that for my husband's funeral?
Come on. I'm in a hurry.
Jeez, it's bad enough that my husband
got killed, working for the NIS.
Move aside.
Jang-su!
Hey, Gye Jang-su.
Hello?
Yes.
Send this in code.
It's been a while. Can you do it?
Yes.
Thank you.
Gosh, whatever.
Tomorrow at 9:00 a.m. Incheon Container
Terminal No. 1. KHCH 35679-19.
Boy, he's happy.
35679, 1... 19.
This one.
TOMORROW
INCHEON
9:00 A.M.
CONTAINER
TERMINAL
Container Terminal No. 1.
35679, beep!
TTOBONG'S CHICKEN,
THIRTY PERCENT DISCOUNT FOR ALL MENUS
Mr. Gi received a text message.
Open it.
TTOBONG'S CHICKEN
Looks like a spam message.
Check if it's a real business.
We order food from here often, sir.
I swear I've never seen him
eat chicken before.
THE HISTORY OF KOREAN INTELLIGENCE
HYEHWA BRANCH: 02-6699-1552
TOMORROW
INCHEON
9:00 A.M.
TOMORROW, INCHEON, 9:00 A.M.
CONTAINER
TOMORROW,
INCHEON, 9:00 A.M., CONTAINER
NO. 1
TOMORROW, INCHEON,
9:00 A.M., CONTAINER, NO. 1
TERMINAL
INCHEON, 9:00 A.M.,
CONTAINER, NO. 1, TERMINAL
KHC
CONTAINER, NO. 1,
TERMINAL, KHC
YEAR 1967
KHC, H35, 67
9-19
TOMORROW, INCHEON, 9:00 A.M., CONTAINER,
NO. 1, TERMINAL, KHC, H35, 67, 9-19
Hey...
Let me see that.
"The History of Korean Intelligence."
If you read while you're in the can,
you might get constipation.
You.
You're talking to Go Hae-ri, right?
It doesn't really make sense,
no matter how much I think about it.
To see a skilled hunter like you
let a target go,
especially such an amateur as Go Hae-ri...
"A colleague behind your back
can become your worst enemy."
It's a quote from page 147 of this book.
That's exactly why...
...I'm always bothered by you.
I'm worried you might stab me in the back.
That means you think of me
as a colleague, at least.
Chief, Go Hae-ri is turning herself in.
Turning herself in?
Wait, um, there's Go Hae-ri.
I can't talk for long, sir.
-First, I'd like to apologize--
-Cut the crap and just answer my question.
Are you giving up?
-Yes.
-Where are you?
But I think it's only right
that you hear my demands first,
before anything else.
And what might those be?
Please take me back.
Okay, fine.
Where are you now?
And, um, since you're taking me back,
I'd like a two-rank promotion--
Why would I ever give you a two-rank...
Fine, you got it.
Just tell me where you are.
We're in New Delhi, India.
What? India?
New Delhi.
We cannot go anywhere
because Kim was shot.
If you get on the first flight tomorrow,
I'll be at the airport.
Was it Edward Park
who got you out of the embassy?
Shh!
It's Cha Dal-geon, I have to go.
First flight tomorrow!
Is her IP address in India?
We couldn't trace it, sir.
Damn it.
Get me a ticket
for the earliest flight tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
You guys stay here and keep guard.
I'm going there alone.
How was I?
It was just the right amount
of awkwardness.
Do you know how hard it is
to get that right?
Okay.
You recorded the video call, right?
Yes, sir.
Bring it to my room,
without Gi knowing about it.
Why do you need it?
I think I saw something.
Was it Edward Park
who got you out of the embassy?
Shh!
Stop!
Zoom in.
Turn it sideways.
It's five o'clock.
So the time difference is either
one hour or 13 hours.
But India is three and a half hours late.
Come on, Go Hae-ri.
Do you think you can fool me?
Look for the places with a time difference
of one or 13 hours.
Focus on smuggling brokers.
And don't let Gi's group find out.
Yes, sir.
I can't imagine Go Hae-ri coming up
with this kind of plan.
Even Edward Park
is not an expert in this area.
I wonder who's helping them.
What the hell?
Hey, it's nothing like that. I...
I was pulling down the shirt for you.
Then what was that look?
How are you...
How am I supposed to look
when I wake up in the middle of my sleep?
What do you take me for?
Why aren't you sleeping?
Are you worried about tomorrow?
You're not scared, are you?
No way...
Stop tossing in your sleep!
Why are you sweeping around the floor
while you sleep?
-You're keeping me up.
-Hey...
You must be insane!
Did you observe me?
Do you...
Do you know how many times
you slapped me in your sleep?
You're no better.
Stop snoring and grinding your teeth.
I wonder who is going to share
a bed with you later.
God help him!
I wonder who you are going to share
a bed with, gosh!
-I feel sorry for her already.
-You are hopeless.
I already feel so sorry for him.
Good morning, sir.
What is it?
We found Kim Woo-gi.
Where is he?
On a ship.
It's a Chinese merchant ship
named Poseidon.
It leaves Shanghai
and arrives in Gwangyang at 10 a.m.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
There is an informant in China
called Polaris,
and Go Hae-ri contacted him.
Don't arrest him.
Take him out at all costs.
NIS
NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE SERVICE
He's going to pass out if he finds out
that Polaris is Chief Gang.
Was it Incheon?
When are we leaving, sir?
Darn it.
I never go well with these revolvers.
Why do South Korean cops use this?
Stop blaming the tool, you amateur.
So tell me.
How much do you make?
Why are you so obsessed
with prying into other's income?
You're the one who's not answering
a simple question.
You'll never do what I do.
You can't speak English.
You can do that for me.
So you just want to hop on my ride?
Piss off, please. Okay?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Where are you off to?
Pissing off. Why do you care?
Hey!
Itaewon?
Why would Tae-ung go there?
Where are you?
Keeping a 10-minute distance from Gi.
Keep a close eye on him
until I get back to Seoul.
SPEED QUICK
He turned towards Hannam Bridge.
Stop reporting and just go after him.
Yes, sir.
We arrive in Incheon in an hour.
Min can't catch up on us, right?
Don't worry.
He's not smart enough for Mr. Gi.
Why are we crossing the bridge again?
Gi's heading to Gangbuk.
Son of a bitch.
Why is he going back and forth...
-Catch up to him.
-What?
Get close to that prick, you idiot!
Damn that piece of shit...
Get that guy. Get the bike!
Where's Gi Tae-ung?
Sir.
Son of a bitch!
What the hell are you saying?
What do you mean our information leaked?
We were only talking to each other.
Did you get caught tailing him?
Why can't you understand?
He knew that we were tailing him,
from the start.
So you don't know where he's going?
Okay. Just stand by.
If Gi wanted us to follow him...
Don't mind him. Our target is Kim Woo-gi.
I need to take a leak.
Is the rest stop close?
Something in there?
I found a monitoring system
inside your phone.
God, damn it, Gi Tae-ung!
Can we reverse trace it by remote?
Chamber 9 will be able to do it.
Tell them that we need Gi's location
as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
That cunning bastard.
He's making this harder than it should be.
Wait for now.
It's Chamber 9.
Where's Gi Tae-ung?
He's at Incheon Container Terminal No.1.
So it was Incheon, not Gwangyang.
You, take my phone and go to Gwangyang.
The rest, to Incheon. Hurry up!
Hello, sir.
Chief.
Nice work, you guys.
-What about Min?
-Here...
He's driving his merry way
into Gwangyang, sir.
Has the ship arrived?
It takes an hour to drop the container
and finish the paperwork.
Take your hands off.
What do you think you are grabbing?
Gosh, hey.
Get your hands off!
You like this, don't you?
Get off me, already!
My gosh. My goodness.
Thank you.
Mr. Gi!
Good job.
That prick...
Well done.
We can get to court in time,
if we move right now.
Let's go.
Get in!
-Go Hae-ri.
-Give it to me.
-Hey!
Assholes! I'm going to kill them all!
Kill them!
Subtitle translation by Daham Yoon