ORIGINAL NETFLIX SERIES
KINGDOM OF KIRIA, NORTH AFRICA
Hey, monkey! Do you hear me?
This is a bullshit mission, Monkey.
Hey monkey! Do you hear me?
I was in the Vympel Unit.
Best in Russia, best in the world.
However, I'm now here with baby monkey.
to clean his bottom.
Monkey, I have an idea.
I'm the main one, you help.
You clean my butt.
Monkey.
MKKS
Damn yellow skin monkey.
Radio check. You hear me, Sekaan Butt?
Three minutes until the target arrives.
Geon, you can shoot.
What are you waiting for?
Geon, shoot!
Geon!
Geon, shoot the target now! Geon!
Nice to meet you!
My name is Cha Dal-geon.
I've joined
on the Seoul representative taekwondo team.
AUDITION KOREAN ACTION CENTER
I'm ranked fifth in taekwondo
third in hapkido, and second in judo.
I also practiced kendo for a long time
and kickboxing, so ...
Including training, in total ...
at least 18 ratings?
Is that much your age?
Then, 15.
Ready.
Hey, wake up! Are you ok?
My ankle. Ouch
You're laughing?
What is this?
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
I'm fine. Gosh, that ...
Hey, Hoon. What's up?
Hoon, I'm fine.
I scared you?
It was just a brick breaking demo.
Your uncle is okay.
This is just a little blood.
It doesn't hurt at all. See
Right? Look at it
Don't cry, Hoon.
This is nothing.
This is not my child. He is my niece
My sister suddenly died.
So, I have to raise him.
to become a man.
Please let me.
got this job.
I'm good at whatever physical work.
Just give it a chance.
then I will show all my abilities.
Thank you!
You may leave.
- Scene one, record three!
- Fine, mark it. Ready!
- One, two, start!
- start!
He really attacked me!
- Hurry up.
- Keep bandaged.
- Can you see the two sides?
- Hurry up!
Don't record this, please.
Ready.
- Greetings.
Congratulations
- Come here!
- Are you all right?
Help him out Take a helmet.
Are you ok? Slowly.
- Good work.
- Thank you to all of you.
Excuse me, ma'am. Could you please move?
He is a genius in taekwondo, talented.
One...
Turn off the fire!
- Dal-geon, are you all right?
- Yup.
- Are we safe?
- Safe!
Come on
Why did you give him?
Let me tie it.
- I'll tie it.
- Hey, don't move.
Highlight the black belt. Come closer
"Cha Hoon."
- Correct. Cha Hoon.
- Come on!
Yes!
JESSICA LEE
DIRECTOR OF JOHN & MARK ASIA
Update stealth function
is a key element of the F-15 Eagle.
He can give enemy information
through an integrated avionics system
sophisticated
able to provide early warning.
Chengdu J-20 China,
Sukhoi PAK Russian FA,
Japan's Mitsubishi ATD-X Shinshin,
has a stealth function.
However, given the critical situation
on the Korean Peninsula,
MICHAEL ALMEIDA
VICE PRESIDENT JOHN & MARK ASIA
I'm sure to apply for the F-15 Eagle
as the only solution to domination
the aerospace power of Northeast Asia.
thanks.
The superiority of Fokker 70
is a long-range air-to-ground missile,
its ability to carry
12 tons of smart bombs,
and fly with a speed of Mach 2.7.
PARK MAN-YEONG
MINISTRY OF NATIONAL DEFENSE
F-15 Eagle John & Mark
spend about 200 billion
for one plane.
So, at a cost of seven F-15s,
you can operate
our ten Fokker 70s.
One of the most important criteria
that must be considered
is proven reliability
and the cost.
Presentation on fighter jets.
who will lead the Korean Air Force
was held this afternoon at the War Memorial.
Global defense company,
including Dynamic System, John & Mark,
and Flying Euro accompanied this presentation,
also defense officials, journalists,
and the civil community involved.
in a warm discussion.
Ministry of National Defense.
will disburse 11 trillion won in funds.
to buy a future jet fighter.
The government announced.
that they will be careful in choosing ...
What's a trillion?
I can't even pay dues
to the taxi company.
Out
- Really won't come back?
- Don't discuss anymore. I really stopped.
However, your ideals
become a martial arts director.
After all your difficulties,
will you give up?
I'm annoyed for wasting time.
If it stops early,
I might now have savings.
Damn it.
- Gosh.
Go. I don't want to be seen.
Dal-geon. We never
do it for money, right?
Dream. Hope.
Vision. Correct?
If I die on location,
will you take care of my niece
to be a visionary man?
- What vision?
- I mean is...
HOONI
- Yes, Hoon?
- Where are you?
Certainly on location.
Gosh, the drab here today.
They cut off water.
If tomorrow doesn't pay the bill,
the gas will also be cut off.
Don't worry I'll pay tomorrow
Pay with what?
What again? The replacement actor gets money
from dangerous scenes.
However, it is not yet payday.
In fact,
I got the role of dialogue this time.
The pay is more than usual.
- We start recording again!
- Well!
I will go home soon.
Cook rice. Bye.
Jeez. He asked a lot.
Borrow money. I'll change it next week.
- Next week?
- Yup.
I know I can count on you.
Save the change.
- Hey come on.
- Stop it.
- You cheapskate!
- I go.
- See you later!
Hey!
Gosh, he drank more.
I hope he stops drinking.
He is lame.
TAEKWONDO I TEXT BOOK.
HOLLYWOOD PEOPLE.
RETURN BRUCE.
DON'T GET. KEEP ADVANCED.
BRUCE LEE
STUPID UNCLE
ACTION CENTER
Hello?
Is this the Action Center?
Is there Mr. Cha Dal-geon?
Dal-geon has stopped working.
Is this Hoon?
I told you I would bring it
barbecued meat. Why do you want noodles?
This.
What do you need for your trip
to Morocco next week?
I did not go.
- Why?
- I do not want.
Do you know how extraordinary that is?
Other children dream of wanting to be with them
Taekwondo demo team.
And you were officially invited
by the Moroccan government.
- So it's all free, right?
- Only flights and hotels are free.
We have to pay expenses.
You think I can't?
You're only 11 years old.
Act like a child.
You should beg to be allowed to go,
don't worry about the money.
Then you have to be mature!
Why yell at me?
You don't know anything.
- What?
- You are stupid...
Stupid? What do I not know?
Hey, Hoon!
He underestimated his uncle lately.
Just you wait, kid!
I will make a lot of money,
feed you meat every day,
and buy expensive clothes.
I will follow along and buy you
anything until you're satisfied.
Isn't this great?
"Celebrating 50 years
diplomatic relations, Morocco! "
INVITATION
RESPONSIBILITIES: GO HAE-RI
MOROCCO, NORTH AFRICA
EMBASSY OF KOREA
EMBASSY OF KOREA IN MOROCCO
I will arrange each of his travel plans
while the demo team is here.
This is an important event to celebrate
50 years of diplomatic relations.
So, prepare yourself.
Well.
Good morning! You arrived early.
There was an accident outside.
A motorcyclist fell
in front of my car.
My heart is still pounding.
Miss Go.
This is the demo team schedule
and progress reports.
Should have been available earlier,
but Moroccans don't help.
REPORT PCharacter limit: 5000TRANSLATE NEXT 5000
ERAYAAN 50 YEARS
KOREAN-MOROCCO DIPLOMATIC RELATIONS
You already have it.
The meeting is over.
OK.
Sorry, Sir.
Answer it.
Mother, I'll call again later.
Moroccan journalists waiting outside.
If it's incompetent,
at least act wisely.
I just saw an apprentice who was so negligent.
Sorry.
You...
This is Elsa.
I'll take it and send it immediately.
Gosh, it's locked again.
What...
What are you doing alone locking yourself up?
My set is torn.
I will leave soon
after replacing it.
You did many things today.
Quickly replace and exit.
- Not easy?
- No, ma'am.
Our offer is one trillion won
higher than Dynamic System
and evaluation of Fokker 70's performance
better than our F-15.
So? How exactly
the Blue House response?
The President wants to support us,
but cannot ignore public opinion.
What are we lobbying for? Is not that
so they ignore things like that?
You know what kind of president.
He is too careful.
F-X COMPANY REPORT
That's not careful. That's sneaky.
He only cares about the benefits.
The Blue House is still impenetrable?
Yes ma'am.
We lost the offer, so we are finished.
Make it still accessible
until all of this is settled.
Michael, you know
why I made a normal seller
like yourself being vice president?
Because you work for the CIA.
I'm not fit to be a CIA.
That's why I was fired.
Not enough.
Not at all.
You just haven't gotten a chance
to prove who you really are.
Do you know
I have to go through to get here,
be me now?
Yes I know.
We have to get this agreement.
however.
If not,
our history is finished.
You and me, done!
Understand?
ONE WEEK THEN, SEOUL
Perfect! The egg yolk doesn't break.
Let's eat!
Do not want.
Eat it. I'll take you to the airport.
Nope. I took the team bus.
Hey, Hoon.
Why do you always scowl lately?
Because of sneakers?
I said I'd buy the best shoes
after you returned from Morocco.
Hey!
Raised you that
stressful enough.
- At least you can listen to me.
- I regret living with you too.
Then go back to the orphanage!
I mean ...
How do I know what the problem is
if you are reluctant to talk to me?
Look at you, shut up and grunt.
You can not hope
I know the problem. Stop.
I still don't understand, but I'm sorry.
So eat this before it gets cold.
Last chance.
If you don't want to eat,
just for me.
Do not want?
One.
Two.
OK.
It's hot!
Hey, Hoon!
Hoon!
Fussy kid. No wonder he is my nephew
I shouldn't have waited for her birthday
to buy him shoes.
LISBOA, PORTUGAL
Incheon International Airport Police.
Hello?
We received many calls.
Please call back.
There will be a plane crash.
- We received many calls ...
- Flight B357 to Morocco tonight.
Hello?
MONITORING
- One two!
- Follow the instructor.
Come on, kids.
- Where is your card?
- Drink lots of water, yes. Stand up.
Hello.
- How are you?
You will go far away.
- You can. See, you can do it?
- Yup.
STUPID UNCLE
Really? thanks. Yes!
I am worried.
Do not worry. I did not go alone.
This is a group tour.
Not you. I worry about myself.
How can I live without you
for several weeks?
Jeez.
Are you that happy?
I am pregnant.
- What?
- It's been five weeks.
I will be a father?
- Yup.
- Really?
I'm now a father!
- Put me down.
- Sorry.
- You make me blush.
- Why?
Hey, your passport. Seriously.
How did you get abroad
without a passport?
You really can keep up
all those children?
Shut up They can hear.
- I'm an instructor.
- Whatever. Pay for transportation money.
You yelp your brother? You are not playing.
I also asked for payment
for the provisions I prepared.
Yes please. You snatched everything
from your only brother.
Hey!
Gather, everyone!
Say goodbye to your parents.
Uncle, I'm on a plane now.
I doubt you miss me,
but if you miss,
check the cloud.
I will upload the video.
Yes, police
Incheon International Airport.
- You speak English?
- Yup. Can I help you?
OK. Flight B357 to Morocco.
Stop the plane now.
What? Sir? What did you say?
- finally.
- Your passport.
There are terrorists on the plane.
The plane will crash. See?
Can I know who this is?
There is no time. If you don't stop it
the plane now ...
Hello?
You are there? Hello?
- What happened?
- Is there a fire?
Where is the fire?
Fire!
Hello? I just received
suspicious call.
There will be a terrorist attack on ...
Sergeant Park!
Hang in there, Park!
- Call an ambulance!
- Good, Sir.
- Don't go to the naming place!
Hello.
We still don't know the sex of the baby.
Attention! Make sure who is sitting
next to you.
Pa feeexpensive phone calls.
So, send the name via message.
I will choose. Yes, just a moment.
You two, give me your cellphone.
The door will be closed, Hoon. Sit down
Sit and stay in place.
Stop it! Give and put the bag on top.
Come on, quickly.
- Stay seated.
- Pass it!
Come in
You pushed me first.
- Come in and sit down.
- You pushed me first.
Why are there so many kids?
They are a taekwondo demo team.
National team?
We must do our best.
- Can I accept?
- Of course.
Dear...
I'm waiting for your call.
Are you fluent in Spanish?
Do not worry,
he doesn't understand our conversation.
Please dont.
DERMAGA TANGIER, MAROKO
Miss Go Hae-ri!
It is such a coincidence.
Why did you come here?
There is a friend of mine who came from Spain.
- You haven't heard the news, right?
- What news?
National Intelligence Service
arrested our consul last night.
What? What did he do?
He took bribes from local drug gangs.
That's not a drug. Understand?
And the drug was smuggled into Korea.
No wonder I knew it
because his eyes always look sleepy.
He doesn't take drugs.
He took bribes.
- I see.
Damn it.
This means trouble for us.
Taekwondo kids are coming tomorrow.
I'm sure the leak from inside.
Do you know who the court is?
Why are your eyes looking at me like that?
Why is my eye?
These are my beautiful eyes.
Your eyes are beautiful. I mean ...
In essence, let's be alert.
We are contract workers. Who cares?
See you tomorrow.
What is your business in Portugal?
I see you
secretly call at the office.
Is there something in Portugal?
Maybe a lover?
What's wrong with men?
- What?
- Who wants to cheat on me?
He looks well,
but it turned out to be really crazy.
If only you had weapons,
I'll shoot his head before returning.
Jeez.
I just found out he was violent.
Cheer up, Hae-ri!
In this world,
there is also a nice man!
You must be tired.
Get enough rest!
I love the breeze!
I just returned from Lisbon.
Yes. Suicide with a gun.
An autopsy won't change anything.
Yes.
WOMEN'S BABY NAMES
A-a, Ji-yeong.
Ju-hui ...
Let me fill your cup.
- Please get a cup of coffee.
- Good, Sir.
WARNING
PASSENGER OXYGEN TOOLS
Please wear your seat belt!
Wear your seat belt!
- What is wrong? Reset main warning.
- Main warning, reset!
- What is this?
- Engine number three is dead.
- Cabin pressure increases.
- Is the plane hollow?
Hurry up and use masker!
Passengers, we are experiencing turbulence.
Please sit down again.
and wear a seat belt.
Passengers, we are experiencing turbulence.
Please sit down again.
and wear a seat belt.
Handle!
Hold tight, everyone! Sit down!
Wake up, hurry up. Sit down
Mayday!
Bravo 357, emergency drop
because of drastic decompression!
Why isn't the panel working?
Latitude, height, speed.
Nothing is posted, sir.
Standby and take control.
The lever doesn't work. What is wrong?
Bravo 357, control tower of Mohammed 5.
Report the situation.
Mohammed 5 control tower, Bravo 357.
Failed to control the plane
due to technical problems.
WOMEN'S BABY NAMES
A NEW MESSAGE AT STUPID UNCLE
Uncle, I'm sorry
FIRING RANGE
KIM HO-SIK
11 UNSWERED CALLS FROM HO-SIK
This is an emergency. To the embassy, ​​now!
Enjoy it.
We should have finished
after a second drink last night.
You brat.
I should have bought it earlier.
SELA NEWS SBC
What is that?
Excuse me, please increase the volume.
I repeat.
B357 aircraft departing from Incheon.
to Morocco last night.
fell into the Moroccan sea.
It was announced by the airline
that as many as 211 passengers,
including the cabin crew,
died in the accident.
The cause of the accident is unknown,
but speculation due to bad weather.
or aircraft failure.
Twenty children.
from the taekwondo demo team
who was invited by the Moroccan government
are on a plane.
to celebrate 50 years.
diplomatic relations with Korea ...
CHA HOON (MEN / 11)
Meanwhile, the Korean government
haven't issued a statement.
related to the accident.
President Jeong Gook-pyo.
just arrived from Busan.
Please wait a little longer.
Out of 211 passengers,
108 of them are Korean citizens,
including 25 children.
Because the accident happened outside the area,
difficult to understand the situation.
I need to talk to you briefly.
Please, Prime Minister Hong.
Please leave us.
The makeup isn't finished yet.
Look shabby more fitting
for this kind of situation.
They say, even leaves fall
can make trouble in the last year.
Look at all the problems I'm facing
in the remaining year of my reign.
The plane that crashed, B357,
supposedly the latest model
Dynamic System design.
Most likely cause of the fall
due to aircraft failure.
Are you sure?
Based on the control tower records,
we are 90 percent sure.
However, until it gets a report
from the investigation team,
I think it's good
we don't take formal positions.
I'm so thirsty.
They don't even get me water.
My fellow countrymen,
I've never heard the news
the more tragic of my life.
As president,
I have failed to protect my people
and maintain their safety.
Now,
I feel shy.
To those who lost
their beloved family members,
and to everyone
who shared the pain of this tragedy
with them,
I want...
condolences sincerely.
- Wear a seat belt. Sit down
- Yes, just a moment.
- Hoon, I said sit down.
- Someone's sitting in my chair.
Wait.
Stupid uncle, sorry I'm mad at you.
You're also mad at me?
I know that you throw away films.
CD, and your books.
You were caught.
I brought it home again.
It was all very heavy.
Why come out of the Action Center?
You said you wanted to.
became a famous martial arts director.
and went to Hollywood.
You said your new name is Bruce Chan,
a combination of Bruce Lee and Jackie Chan.
You're so cool when you act.
I want fried eggs when I return.
The delicious one.
I want two, huh?
Hoon ...
Hoon!
PRESS CONFERENCE
REQUEST FOR SORRY DYNAMIC SYSTEM
Who are you bowing to?
Dynamic System, manufacturer of B357,
holding a press conference.
Grieving families barge in.
and caused a commotion.
While an accident was suspected.
due to a plane failure,
controversy is clearly inevitable.
because of the Dynamic System.
is scheduled to provide.
the most sophisticated fighter jet
and received 10.8 trillion won.
LISBOA, PORTUGAL
Finally...
you prove yourself.
You saved us all.
Thank you, Michael.
Goodbye.
Continued news of B357 accident.
Some family members of victims.
heading for Morocco tonight.
with a chartered plane.
by Dynamic System
Because it's hard to gather.
the remains of the crime scene,
they decide.
holding a mass funeral.
on the beach near the accident site.
TANGIER AIRPORT, IBN BATTUTA, MAROKO
It must have been a tiring trip.
I'm Go Hae-ri
from the Korean Embassy in Morocco.
I'm Kim Ho-sik.
During his stay in Morocco,
you will stay at the Continental Hotel
in the city center of Tánger.
There are buses outside for you, so, come on.
Sorry, may I go to the toilet?
Then, I'll be waiting for you guys
after ten minutes at Gate One.
You sit there.
what? Hey you
Sit down. Wear a seat belt
- Hey you.
- Be quiet.
Stupid uncle ...
Catch him!
We will leave soon!
Free!
Hey!
Street!
The wheel rotates on its axis.
You.
But how do you ...
Who do you work for?
How do you live?
All of them on the plane were killed.
How can you live?
You are the culprit?
You killed my Hoon?
Why did you drop the plane, damn it!
Why?
- Come here.
- What is wrong?
Call the police, hurry up!
- Eight hundred.
- Here is the money.
Exit.
Get out, fucker!
- Miss Lee Pil-sun?
- Yup.
The table in the middle.
If you can wait a little longer,
Dynamic System representative
coming soon.
Mr. Cha Dal-geon isn't here yet.
Have you contacted him?
He did not answer.
He knows the location of his hotel,
so it's ok.