What's up with all those kids?
It's a taekwondo demo team.
Sit down. Put your seat belt on. Hey!
Flight B357 which departed Incheon
and headed to Morocco last night,
crashed down into the Moroccan seas.
It was announced by the airline
that all 211 passengers,
including the cabin crew,
were killed in this accident.
They say,
even the falling leaves
can cause trouble in the final years.
Look at all the troubles I'm facing
with only a year left to go.
It must have been a tiring trip.
I'm Go Hae-ri from the Embassy
of the Republic of Korea in Morocco.
This bastard is alive
from the plane crash.
What you're saying is...
-The plane crash was--
-An act of terrorism.
You were right. The plane was attacked.
Don't do anything. Those people...
They are terrifying...
Who are those big shots?
Why did they kill
all those innocent people?
There is an accomplice. It's Kim Woo-gi,
the co-pilot of the plane.
Where is Kim Woo-gi, the co-pilot?
Why are you doing this to me?
You don't trust John &amp; Mark, do you?
Did you get every penny from John &amp; Mark?
I got a smoking gun
that can nail Kim Woo-gi.
The estimated location of Kim Woo-gi
is a slum in the northwest region
of Tangier, Morocco.
Get ready and get moving.
What's going on?
Give me everything you know
about Kim Woo-gi.
Check your sections
and find out if an Asian man
has been buying lots of water.
I found them.
Can't we just talk in Korean?
Mr. Kim Woo-gi.
Kim Woo-gi is in custody.
Kim Woo-gi will be dead tomorrow.
We were ambushed.
It's going to be difficult
to take Kim Woo-gi back home.
Are you going to operate?
Dear Koreans.
Our nation has developed
by using its hardships and challenges
as a stepping-stone
to take a leap forward.
"Our people have been strong
in hard times,
and brave in challenging times."
Wow.
I love this sentence.
"We have overcome crises by joining hands
with one another
and that is a beautiful tradition,
only a few other countries have.
During the currency crisis,
we gathered scraps of gold
from our wardrobes
with our own hands!
It was those hands put together
that saved the Republic of Korea
from such crises."
Did you confirm this speech, Yun?
-Yes.
-What is wrong?
I can't find anything awkward
about this speech.
I say we revise all the verbs. Verbs need
to convey power but this is too weak.
For example, instead of "we will commit"
"we must commit" is more powerful.
The Quintilian method.
Isn't that too old-fashioned?
Do you think this is about the method?
No, I'm saying that you don't get
the target and the goal of this speech.
What are you suggesting
that I don't understand?
Who's the target of this speech?
It's the opposition party,
opposing the budget revision.
So what?
We don't convince those fellows,
we threaten them.
That is the goal of this speech.
This is just too weak.
It's not even enough for convincing.
The budget proposal will be passed.
Is it necessary to arouse the people
in this state of affairs?
It's the nature of the people to want
a powerful leader in difficult times.
But I see no sticks in your speech,
only carrots.
How will you control the public
when a more pressing time comes?
That's Goebbels' logic from World War II.
It might make the President
look like Hitler--
I think it's for the best
to fix the entire speech, sir.
You need to rethink the concept, Yun.
"We need to spend a trillion won
in this F-X plan,
or our national security fails.
Should something go wrong
and a war breaks out,
it will be because the opposition party
voted against the budget."
The public will be watching,
so the President should show
at least this much charisma.
You should fix the budget speech,
Prime Minister Hong.
Me?
You wrote my speeches
for my presidential election campaign.
If it gets a sophisticated touch
by someone like you,
I would feel relieved.
-Mr. President--
-Yes, sir. As you wish.
Done.
Good job.
Good job, sir.
What?
-What?
-What's wrong with him?
-What's wrong?
-What the...
Doctor, he's suddenly convulsing!
What's happening to him?
He bled too much.
Without a blood transfusion, he could die.
Kim Woo-gi, wake up!
-What's your blood type?
-It's O.
-How do you know?
-I read all about him before coming here.
Mine is O, too. Give him my blood.
Hang in there. Don't fucking die.
Take my blood now!
How is Kim Woo-gi?
He's touch-and-go.
Why don't you get some sleep?
Never mind me. You can sleep.
Those glaring eyes of yours
make me uncomfortable.
I know how to go without sleep
for twelve days.
You should've joined the circus.
Could've been rich by now.
Girl.
Don't be sarcastic.
Or I'll crush your mouth.
If there is a guy who can crush my mouth,
I'd propose to him.
Men these days.
They are a bunch of chickens.
I'm never touching your mouth, then.
We should stop now.
It's too risky for you.
Leave it.
I'm perfectly fine.
You die if you lose more
than two liters of blood!
Do I have a choice?
That bastard...
If he dies,
I will never know
why my nephew was killed.
Kim Woo-gi. Wake up!
He's not going to die,
take the needle out.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're not fine.
Let's get you laid down, okay?
You will need it.
Eat it. Come on.
I don't like sweet food.
We don't need another patient.
Eat if you don't want to slow us down.
He's right. Eat. Here.
The situation doesn't look good.
If a video suggesting Kim is alive
is uploaded online,
it will hit us hard.
I think you should stop
with such useless concerns.
This is a secret mission
that only a few know about,
and I control that team
so what is there to worry?
But you can't control Cha Dal-geon.
You can never guess
what that wacko is up to.
If you can't hide it,
revealing it can be another way.
Here comes Mister Shadow himself.
What do you mean by that?
We have a hidden card up our sleeves.
You must have forgotten.
A hidden card?
O Sang-mi is one of the easiest people
to control.
The greedier you are,
the easier you fall for temptations.
So use her to nullify all the evidence?
But there is one condition.
It won't work if Kim Woo-gi is alive.
It will be hard to get rid of him
while he's at the embassy.
Man, I can't keep quiet anymore.
I was going to take care of this
without sharing it with you guys.
Before Gang was arrested,
he did something very commendable.
He said he'll send a backup team
to the embassy.
The mercenaries can't get in there,
but our agents will be welcomed.
The embassy is the best place
to deal with it quietly, right?
Well, then.
-Could we bring forward the schedule?
-Yes, you should. As much as you want.
You can think of Kim as a dead man.
Mr. Min told us you'd come.
Come this way.
Wait for me here.
It must have been hard,
staying in this rough place.
You know me, right?
John &amp; Mark's Director of Asia.
It was you?
You kidnapped me and kept me here.
Do you really think
you can get away with this?
You make it sound
like you are an innocent person.
You're an accomplice
in the terrorist attack.
You people did it.
It was you people!
You were the ones
who talked my husband into it!
Do you know why humans have
only one mouth but two ears?
We are designed to talk less
and listen carefully.
I haven't even got to my point
and you're already running your mouth.
I don't care what you say.
You can try to persuade me all you want
but whatever it is you want,
I'm not giving it to--
Persuade you?
Don't be stupid.
I don't persuade.
I'm not that generous.
Listen.
If you leave here with me, you will live.
If you stay,
those beasts outside will come in here
and rip you apart into pieces.
So that there's no trace of you.
Those eyes are telling me
that you will die soon.
Spare me.
Please...
Find Chief Yang
in the Intelligence Division.
He will take care of everything.
An opportunity...
is like a bird sitting on a tree.
Catch it before it flies away.
Please,
please keep your word.
Please, please keep your word, too.
Ms. O Sang-mi.
SEOUL YEONGDEUNGPO POLICE STATION
Can we trust her?
I wouldn't if she was dumb.
But she is a smart woman.
Chief An, Intelligence Division.
What do you need him for?
I'm turning myself in.
I'm O Sang-mi.
What?
I'm probably on the wanted list,
for taking down the plane.
Oh, please come in.
There's a vehicle at twelve o'clock.
Eleven o'clock.
Ten o'clock.
And at two o'clock.
Three vans and a sedan.
If we count in the blind spots,
we have from 20 to 30 of them.
I bet they're all armed
with heavy weapons.
This is way too intense.
We can't even trust the cops here.
What should we do?
PRESIDENT
Yes, sir.
NIS DIRECTOR GENERAL AN GI-DONG
Gang briefed me on the current status.
How is Kim Woo-gi doing right now?
The worst is over.
I believe he is going to live.
Still confronting with the enemy?
Yes, we are completely isolated
from the outside.
When are you sending the backup team?
They are leaving soon. Wait for two days.
Chief Gang's not answering my calls.
Is something wrong?
He's busy working on Jessica's arrest.
You can communicate with me
until tomorrow.
Do not take any actions
until the backup team arrives.
-If something happens, call me right away.
-Yes, sir.
Argh, Kim Woo-gi, that bastard...
He is holding up for too long.
It would have been great for all of us
if he just died.
Any word from Yun?
Excuse me? About what?
No matter how I look at it,
going behind the President's back
and doing this--
What is up with you, sir? I told you
Yun will take care of everything.
To be honest, he is the one
who provides girls to the President.
Trusting the second-in-command
is a safe bet.
Don't you think so?
RESTRICTED AREA
The door is now open.
The Chief is here.
Hwang Pil-yong.
Yes, sir.
You know that I consider you
the best among the Blacks, right?
Thank you.
The fate of the NIS is now in your hands.
Kim Woo-gi and Cha Dal-geon.
Those two must die.
How should I deal with Gi
and the other agents?
Isn't it obvious?
Get rid of them if they get in the way.
Isn't that a basic rule of our missions?
Don't worry too much.
You will not be taking the blame.
The ones in charge, like me,
will be taking full responsibility.
Okay?
Yes, sir.
Do you know why
this operation is named "Silk Road"?
The journey itself is long and dangerous,
but when you get back,
there will be a big reward.
Good luck!
Got toilet paper in the toilet?
Even the world's worst criminals
are allowed to take a dump, guys.
Open it.
Why don't you come in and watch me?
Get on with it, sir.
Chief, there's a problem.
This is Bae Dong-chan
from Pyeonghwa Daily.
This is Gang Ju-cheol.
Are you at the Blue House?
Yes. What is going on?
We found Kim Woo-gi in Morocco.
But people are trying to kill him.
What?
Go on.
Gang Ju-cheol, that crazy nut job...
Hey, Gang!
What are you doing?
-Gang Ju-cheol!
-Can you pass that onto the President?
I'll make it happen.
Are you cleaning the toilet?
TEAM THAT ARRESTED KIM WOO-GI
IN MOROCCO
AT RISK OF BEING ASSASSINATED
You could always have your men
do the cleaning.
Aren't you too old to be doing chores?
Huh?
Hey! Stay back.
Shit.
Stop right there.
-Take the phone.
-Yes, sir.
You are a piece of work.
NO CALL HISTORY
Who were you calling?
Your mother.
I told her you're a bad boy.
Fucker!
Take this and find out who he called.
Who?
Bae Dong-chan from Pyeonghwa Daily.
He's a Blue House journalist.
Can't you even handle Gang Ju-cheol?
What the hell!
Ms. Seo.
That memo... Hand it over.
I need to give it to the President myself.
Give it.
-No, sir.
-Seo Yeong-ji!
What's going on?
What do you have there?
It's confidential information.
A Pyeonghwa Daily journalist
wanted me to deliver it to the President.
Let me see.
I said let me see it.
You're opening a Pandora's box.
Don't read it,
if you're not confident enough
to handle it.
It could become big trouble, even for you.
It seems that...
we are now sharing a secret.
I have so many worries thanks to you.
You arrested me
but there are no charges against me.
And releasing me would be too risky,
even with a confidentiality agreement.
Can you call it a shoe factory
if it has no shoe in it?
What do you mean, no charges?
This is a factory for charges.
Senior Secretary Yun Han-gi
is the one holding your leash, right?
What are you going to do?
Now that Kim Woo-gi is found,
that boat you're on is about to sink.
You are so stupid.
I wasn't going to tell you about this.
But Kim Woo-gi...
is not coming back home.
I sent a backup team to Morocco.
The team I had handpicked myself.
You piece of shit.
Um...
I already signed the agreement
on keeping my mouth shut.
That's the classified intel Gang shared
with North Korea's Security Department.
But why are you showing this to me?
Because you are the eyewitness.
There is a signature block
on the last page.
Stamp your thumbprint.
What's going to happen
if I stamp my thumbprint here?
You seriously don't know?
Gang will be punished for violating
the National Security Act,
and you will be considered
as one of my own.
Why? Don't like it?
I'm not forcing you.
There are plenty of people
who can do it instead.
Aren't you reading it first?
It would take me ages.
NIS NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE SERVICE
Escort Chief Gang, down to the basement.
And you.
You might have to take the stand
as a witness.
That's okay, right?
I have no other wishes,
but to keep my job for a long time
and work under you.
That attitude from my subordinate.
I love it very much.
If you liked it so much,
could you allow me a few days off?
Don't you know that we're short-handed?
Get back to your work.
Of course, sir.
You have to work to get paid.
Screw vacation.
Thank you, sir.
Jang Cheol-su, come out.
Where are they taking us, one by one?
They'll be made to sign an agreement
before getting back to work.
I'm the only person
that Min wants to take out.
Then what should I do?
No matter what they ask from you,
just do as they say.
That's the only way we can save
Gi Tae-ung and Go Hae-ri.
Thank you for listening.
Hoon, you're next.
In the future, I want to be...
my uncle.
Keep it down, kids.
Do you want to become a stuntman
like your uncle?
No.
Then?
My mother left me in the orphanage.
But my uncle took me in and raised me.
He swears a lot...
and spits on the streets...
but to me, my uncle
is the greatest person in this world.
So my dream is to be like him...
and take care of him when I grow up.
Jin-hee!
-Ji-su!
-Mom!
Hoon!
Hoon.
Hoon...
Hey, Cha Hoon!
Hoon?
Hoon...
Hoon!
Oh, you're awake. How are you?
-I'm good.
-I see.
Where is Hae-ri?
In the kitchen, cooking some healthy food.
Alright.
I'm sorry.
Don't be discouraged. Cheer up!
Elsa.
What would we have done without you?
I wish I had a sister like Elsa.
Don't interrupt her.
Let her deal with it alone.
That will make her stronger.
-Ta-da!
-Wow!
You must be hungry. Let's eat.
I cooked lamb because there's no pork.
I'm not sure how it'll taste.
Wow. It's so good.
This is amazing!
Mr. Gi has never failed his operations.
When the backup team arrives,
we are taking Kim back to Korea.
So don't you worry, okay?
You lost a lot of blood today.
You should eat and recover.
Don't worry about me and eat.
You should eat well
and get well, too, sir.
It's so delicious.
This is like a culinary revolution.
Why are there only three eggs?
We only had three eggs left.
You can have them. I'm fine.
Go Hae-ri.
Take mine.
That's okay. You should have it.
I'm allergic to eggs. You can have it.
Oh, dear.
You have egg allergies?
Last time you worked out,
I saw you eating so many boiled eggs.
The allergy must come and go or something.
I said I'm okay. I cooked it for you.
-If you're not having it--
-Mix it.
Mix it well, okay?
Man, look at this soup.
I've never seen anything like it.
AGREEMENT
I've signed it.
LIES CAN'T BEAT THE TRUTH
Thank you.
WE NEVER GIVE UP
I hope this agreement could bring
some comfort to your hearts.
How is the lawsuit going
against John &amp; Mark?
It will start this week.
I see.
I guess I'm late.
Coming early wouldn't have made
a difference.
That agreement...
will soon turn into a complaint.
Hey, how dare you come into this place?
Get the hell out.
Get out before I throw you!
Mr. Park!
O Sang-mi is holding
a press conference now.
Did you say O Sang-mi?
Why is she holding a press conference?
-A press conference?
-She's shameless.
Turn on the TV.
I bet it's going to be interesting.
This is ridiculous.
REPRESENTATIVE OF B357 BEREAVED FAMILIES
O SANG-MI
I am here today...
URGENT PRESS CONFERENCE
standing before you all
because I have a confession to make
with a heavy heart.
I solemnly swear
that what I'm about to say
is nothing but the truth.
My husband, Kim Woo-gi...
is alive.
-What is she saying?
-But he's dead!
Kim Woo-gi...
will die soon.
My husband
was accused of crashing the plane.
And it is true.
If he dies,
you will receive his five billion won,
which adds up to 10 billion in total.
The company that offered
ten billion won to my husband
for taking down the plane
was not John &amp; Mark.
If you say no,
you'll die here right now.
It was Dynamic.
-What the hell?
-Mr. Park, what is she saying?
Dynamic offered me
ten billion won to lie
and say that John &amp; Mark
had ordered the bombing
to my husband.
This is your last chance.
I will fully cooperate
with the investigation...
and the entire truth...
will be revealed in court.
Can you tell us who it was
that directly gave the orders?
Please give us the details!
Please tell us the truth!
O revealed in a press conference
that the B357 bombing
was orchestrated by Dynamic System
to win the Next Generation Fighter Plan.
Civic groups and the opposition party
have officially called upon
the government and prosecution
to investigate and find out
who exactly is behind the plane crash.
I'll never forget
the humiliation I faced...
at the NIS.
That was a surprising twist.
Bold and sophisticated.
But... foolish.
Do you still have a card to draw?
You're asking for an all-out war,
but you should know better, Jessica.
You've seen what happened to those
who crossed me.
Never have mercy,
but always take revenge.
That's right.
No mercy for you.
Glad I came.
I was actually worried
that you might give in.
But this is what I wanted.
To me,
this is much more enjoyable.
Good luck.
I mean it, Jessica.
I'm hungry.
What should we have for dinner?
The survivors must go on.
Lighten up, people!
-What do you want, Jae-yeong?
-Shall I order from the same place?
Aren't you sick of rice and soup?
This is my treat.
How do you like roast chicken?
Are you really paying for it?
For god's sake.
I just got out of jail, man!
Chickens are no big deal.
Hang on...
There is a great chicken place
around here.
Hold on.
Let's see...
TTOBONG'S CHICKEN
How many of Gang's minions
are left in the building?
There are five we are watching,
including Gong Hwa-suk.
Keep your eye on them.
Don't let them out of your sight.
Yes, sir.
This is Bullet Chicken.
We deliver chicken faster than a bullet.
Oh, hello?
Do you have the chicken I'm looking for?
What was the name? It was...
"Vagabond", I believe it was?
Yes, we have those. Place your order.
Two seasoned chickens
and two classic chickens, please.
I'll be paying with card.
How long will it take?
Okay.
Jang-su!
Don't you get sick of chickens?
Get out.
Okay.
I told you not to go in there.
You might get locked inside.
I like it dark.
If you like it dark, you should stay in
your room and keep your eyes closed.
It's a delivery.
It's not just a delivery.
It's a signal.
Wow.
Hey, that was so quick!
I'll take that.
Jae-yeong, take these upstairs.
Yes, ma'am.
How much?
It's 64 million won.
Sixty-four...
You mean 64 thousand, right?
-Yes!
-Here is my card.
-Signature.
-Yes, let me.
Your payment was successful.
-Goodbye.
-Yes, thank you.
"Bullet Chicken"?
What is that?
It's a secret base that only Gi and I use.
When Code Zero strikes,
call Bullet Chicken.
The codename is...
"Vagabond."
Hey.
Were you high on the plane as well?
Was it Jerome?
The terrorist.
How did you meet him?
Wow, you're so energetic.
Look at you, working out
after giving me blood...
That pisses me off, alright?
Giving blood and making porridge
for a scum like you.
It's all fucked up.
You said you're pleading the Fifth, right?
While you're with me,
I'm going to make you feel
like you want to die.
So let's see who wins.
Dal-geon!
The backup team's here.
They're finally here.
Are you out of your mind?
You told me you don't sleep.
You were dozing off all the time
like a sick chicken.
Doesn't mean you can tear off my skin!
The stakeout. It ends today.
What's up?
It's weird.
Why are they letting the backup team in?
Maybe they have no other choice.
They don't want to take the risk.
But they came at us
like there's no tomorrow.
Good to see you.
You've been through a lot.
I'm Go Hae-ri. Thank you for coming.
This is Cha Dal-geon...
I've heard about you.
You've done a great job
together with Agent Go.
The local government will be
sending support, by 9 a.m. tomorrow.
Do we have to wait until then?
I think a helicopter is all we need
to get away from here right now.
I understand your concern.
But now that we're here, don't worry.
-Where is Kim Woo-gi?
-Show him to the room.
Please follow me.
What's wrong?
-They are not Chief Gang's men.
-What?
Yes. What's the matter?
I have a message for you.
Did the backup team arrive?
Yes.
They're assassins.
TAE-UNG, BACKUP TEAM, ASSASSINATION
Don't die. This isn't part of the message.
It's from me.
Come for chicken when you get back.
PRESIDENT
Yes, Director.
Is the backup team there?
Yes.
Listen to me carefully.
They're there to kill Kim Woo-gi.
And Cha Dal-geon, too.
Cooperate with Hwang.
On whose orders?
I know it's not your decision.
Who gave this pathetic order?
Gi Tae-ung!
Think wisely.
Do as I say or you, Go Hae-ri
and the others will get killed.
What if I take out the backup team?
You'll become a traitor.
Min is back in the TF team
and Gang was arrested
for benefiting our enemy.
Mark my words.
This is your country's order.
What is happening here, sir?
We will use this room.
As for Kim, we will protect him.
I can't let you do that.
Until he stands in court,
I'm staying with him.
Then we'll have to share the room,
Mr. Cha.
It's our job to protect you, too.
I would prefer to be
under Agent Go's protection.
This is an emergency.
Should the enemies strike in--
That's exactly why I prefer Go.
She has amazing skills.
Mr. Cha...
-As long as we are here, you must follow--
-We have a room for you.
I don't think this room
is big enough anyway.
You can use a bigger room.
Get some sleep.
I'll be on guard.
That guy I talked with...
You mean Hwang?
I have doubts about him, too, but...
I'm heading out.
We have two targets.
Kim Woo-gi and Cha Dal-geon.
If anyone gets in our way,
no matter who they are,
we take them out.
Who is it?
Stay over there.
It's Go Hae-ri.
Do you need something?
You must be tired.
Why don't you take some rest?
-We are checking our gears.
-Oh...
We have cup noodles. Would you like some?
We're fine.
His pistol has a silencer.
A silencer?
They're trying to do something quietly.
But they're here to fight the men outside.
It doesn't make sense.
You should take Kim Woo-gi to Gi's room.
-What about you?
-I'm going to find out more.
Be careful.
We don't want cup noodles.
I'm Cha Dal-geon.
I want to talk to you about Kim Woo-gi--
Kim Woo-gi! Wake up!
-Get up.
-What the hell, are you mad?
Put your shoes on.
Yes, this is Cha Dal-geon's phone.
Ms. Go?
Who is this?
I'm Edward's secretary.
Oh, Dal-geon is out right now--
You must do as I tell you right away.
What is going on?
Turn on the timer on your phone
and move to a safe zone right now.
Tell me what's going on.
Just do as I say
or you're all going to die.
Drop your guns, bastards.
Have you killed a man before?
It's not as easy as it looks.
You'll never shoot me!
I can't kill men.
But I can kill those worse than animals.
He's not going to shoot me,
so just take the shot!
-Drop it, damn it!
-Shoot him!
Deputy, this is an order. You shoot.
Shoot!
What the hell are you doing?
-Are you going to watch and do nothing?
-We don't make decisions.
We follow orders.
They are all going to get killed!
I'm following the order of my country.
Subtitle translation by Daham Yoon