Was it you?
Why did you crash the plane, you bastard!
Get out, you piece of shit!
The bereft families called us again.
-I'm afraid keeping them waiting--
-I'll be down there in 30 minutes.
I'll get ready.
Do you know how long we've been waiting?
You're outright ignoring us.
They didn't run off, did they?
-Call them right now!
-What's going on?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
What the hell is this?
-What's going on?
-He should've come down by now.
-You can't do this to us!
-Why won't you answer me?
I apologize.
I'm sorry for being late.
I'm Edward Park,
Chief negotiator of Dynamic System.
-We've lost our children!
-Please stop.
You bastard!
Bring my child back to life!
Bring him back!
Bring my husband back!
Is this a joke?
You killed my little brother!
Bring my husband back to life!
You fucking murderer!
-Mr. Kwang-deok, calm down.
-Get off me!
Hey.
Throw it.
-What?
-Throw it.
Son of a...
Motherfucker...
You can call me names and hit me
all you want.
Show them your anger and grief
in the most expressive way.
What the hell are you talking about?
Dynamic System told me
to settle with you at the lowest cost.
Are you kidding me?
The death toll, 211,
is just a number to them.
But 211 is not only a number,
it's your dear husbands, wives,
and children
who should be smiling by your side.
They need to know this.
Aren't you one of them?
Well, in fact,
A plane crash five years ago...
took my wife and daughter's lives.
It was my daughter's birthday...
but her party was canceled
because I said I was busy.
If only we'd had dinner together
that day...
if we'd had that dinner,
my wife and daughter
wouldn't have been on that plane.
Mi-seon wanted her husband
to have his own Judo gym,
so she sold Gimbap at a joint
till late at night.
Kim Woo-gi, the co-pilot,
his dream was
running a horse ranch in Jeju-do.
He was more at home on land
than in the sky.
Pil-yong was Pil-sun's little brother
whom she raised
like her own son.
Ui-jeong,
Yong-jae, So-dam, Hyeok-jin, Jeong-su...
They were all precious people
who shouldn't be gone like that.
This is terrible.
My job is done.
How much longer should I be here?
I feel this is my last opportunity
to atone to my wife and daughter.
Please support me
in my fight against Dynamic System.
I'll make sure to get whatever you want
from them. I mean it.
Uh, Dal-geon?
-Gosh.
-Dal-geon?
There's a survivor!
This bastard is alive
from the plane crash.
You must be Mr. Cha Dal-geon.
I'm not quite sure what you're saying--
That bastard tried to shoot me!
I know it sounds fucking crazy,
but I clearly saw him.
I really did see him!
Dal-geon,
are you out of your mind?
I'm not crazy.
My head is clear!
I was chasing after him...
This is driving me nuts.
So...
What you're saying is...
-The plane crash was--
-An act of terrorism.
I'm sure of it!
Terror?
What does he mean, a terrorist attack?
The plane exploded when it crashed.
Nobody could survive from that.
That's why this is driving me crazy!
I saw him clearly with my own eyes!
Wait, walk us through it calmly.
-Who did you see and where?
-Right.
There's someone else who saw him
other than me!
She must have...
Maybe I shouldn't be here.
Wait!
Do you remember the guy I told you to stop
at the airport?
Excuse me?
Wait a moment.
Come here!
What?
LOG IN
Look, it's the same guy!
Remember him?
Well...
I'm not sure. It was so hectic
and such a brief moment.
Try harder, please!
I don't remember.
What do you have your head and eyes for?
Why are you yelling at me?
Check the CCTVs at the airport.
You'll believe me when you see it there!
-Okay, let's go.
-Let's go to the airport.
-I'll go.
-Okay.
-Sure.
-No way. What kind of nonsense...
Stop! That man right there.
It's not him.
No scar on his face.
You were mistaken.
Ask them to show us a different clip.
This one!
Right there.
What are you doing to us?
We're suffering enough as it is.
I think he made an honest mistake.
Shall we go?
Wait.
That bastard messed with the CCTV.
Mr. Cha Dal-geon.
I saw him with my own two eyes!
I can bet my life on it,
so please believe me!
We don't need your life.
How can you make such a mistake?
We're going through enough already.
These things can be manipulated easily,
don't you think?
They crashed a plane.
For them, this is a piece of cake!
"Manipulated"? Manipulated, my ass!
Forget it.
Fighting among us wouldn't look good.
We're on a tight schedule.
Let's go.
Hey,
I run a Judo gym.
Because of that I'm very patient.
They suffered enough from their loss.
Don't add to the pain, okay?
His name is Cha Dal-geon.
A member of his family died
on flight B357.
What is he?
FBI? NIS?
He's a stuntman.
A stuntman?
Samael is looking for you.
SAMAEL JOINED THE CHAT.
If you keep disobeying his orders,
you are as good as dead.
I value my honor over my life.
I won't go back until it is restored.
I can't help you.
Don't worry, Busra.
There's someone to help me.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO OPEN OR SAVE THIS FILE?
SAVE
SAVING FILE
Ho-sik? It's Cha Dal-geon.
Do you know where Go Hae-ri is staying?
Why do you ask?
I have to give her something
but she's not picking up.
Ms. Go Hae-ri!
Ms. Go!
-Go Hae-ri?
-What are you doing here?
Are you one of them?
-What?
-Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Answer the question.
Who are you really?
So...
you think I'm working with the terrorist?
Are you out of your mind?
What do you think I--?
Where is he?
-Cha Dal-geon, look.
-I'm not my fucking self!
Talk, or I'll blow your brains out.
Then shoot me.
-What?
-You're obviously crazy.
-Pull the trigger. Do it!
-Shut up!
I understand you've lost your mind,
but how can you treat me like a terrorist?
What are you doing? Let me go!
-You crazy bast--
-Don't move.
You want to be in big trouble?
You'll regret this--
-It hurts!
-Don't move!
Don't you know what serious crimes
you're committing?
Breaking and entering,
unlawful detainment, and intimidation!
Don't!
Don't you touch it.
What a pervert.
And now, sexual harassment.
Sheesh.
NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE SERVICE
What is this?
National Intelligence Service?
Now that you know, untie me.
I told you you'd be in trouble.
My gosh.
Blowing my cover will get me disciplined!
Untie me now!
-Plenty of props like this on set.
-What?
Want to see mine, too? I'm CIA.
I am a special agent from the NIS.
How special are you now
all tied up and disarmed?
I can speak three languages.
You think we only have muscle at the NIS?
Smart agents like me are more special!
Get your facts straight!
-Who's M?
-Don't answer it.
Or else, I'll be fired.
Answer it.
Hey, Go Hae-ri.
Damn it.
Hello?
Yes, Chief.
Ambassador O Jae-gwan
was arrested upon his arrival in Korea.
Good job.
By the way, when can I return
to the National Intelligence Service?
Stay there for the time being.
Things are working great without you here.
Sir, how can you say such hurtful words?
NIS CHIEF MIN JAE-SIK
Nobody could've handled
the ambassador case as well as me.
You didn't do it alone.
Only an idiot cannot finish
a job wrapped up in a bow.
I wrapped it up.
What others did was just cuffing him.
Anyways, I'm getting my ticket home.
Unless you want to be disciplined
for leaving your post,
stay put.
Hello?
Sir? Chief--
Now you know I'm not lying?
Let's call it even
although I got the short end.
Why did you come here?
You must have a reason
to look for me late at night.
It's the video
taken before the crash.
Watch it and try to remember the bastard.
You said you were smart.
Look, Mr. Cha Dal-geon.
I'm a busy person
and I owe you nothing.
You're responsible, too!
What do you mean?
Check this out.
Here, your precious name, Go Hae-ri!
STAFF IN CHARGE: GO HAE-RI
This is just
because I'm the staff in charge.
Exactly!
I need your help.
I beg you.
Stay seated.
STAFF IN CHARGE: GO HAE-RI
You're responsible, too!
Asshole.
Talking gibberish like that.
I know you threw away your books.
You got busted.
I brought them back home.
They were so heavy.
Why did you quit the Action Center?
Hae-ri Go!
I heard you scored big this time.
Hwa-suk, where are you?
Where else? At the office.
I sent a video to your personal email.
I want you to check it.
What video?
Is it X-rated?
CHECK THIS AUDIO PLEASE
What is this?
Open it.
Oh my.
Isn't it from the crashed plane--
Can you see a guy on the phone
behind the kids?
The one in a hoodie.
Find out what he's saying on the phone.
Why did you quit the Action Center?
You said you'd become
a famous martial arts director
and go to Hollywood.
It'll take a while to receive approval.
There's no time.
Just remove any trace of the email.
Gosh... Okay, girl.
You should be spending your energy
on good looking guys over there instead.
This call costs a lot.
I got to go. Thank you.
Hello?
You're not welcome at all.
SAVING FILE
DELETE
Hello, Mr. Prime Minister.
-I loved your press briefing this morning.
-Thank you.
-Where's Mr. President?
-In his office.
He's in a bad mood.
Okay.
F-X PLAN EVALUATION REPORT
MINISTRY OF NATIONAL DEFENSE
JEONG GOOK-PYO
PRESIDENT OF THE REPUBLIC OF KOREA
THE MOST PROMISING MODEL IS THE F70.
I can wait outside if you're busy.
It's okay. Come and take a seat.
HONG SUN-JO
PRIME MINISTER
The price aside,
in terms of performance
and technology transfer,
MINISTER OF NATIONAL DEFENSE
Dynamic's F70 is deemed to be superior
to John &amp; Mark's.
What about public opinion, Mr. Minister?
SENIOR SECRETARY FOR CIVIL AFFAIRS
Are you sure
you can handle public opposition
to the deal with Dynamic System?
Still, you cannot make a hasty decision
on such a long-range project.
After the crash, the approval rating
for the President is plummeting,
and you want to add fuel to it?
That's why I'm telling you.
If word gets out
that we wasted north of a trillion won--
What is this display?
Minister Park.
Let's think this way.
For this F-X plan,
a huge sum of money was allocated,
11 trillion won to be exact.
Where do you think it comes from?
It's the tax
from the citizens' hard-earned money.
What would you do
if that money makes them sad
rather than happy?
Our national defense is important.
So is the long-range plan.
But aren't they supposed
to make the citizens happy?
I'm just representing
the National Defense Ministry.
For the citizens,
please consider carefully
which is the right decision.
Alright.
I will make careful consideration.
You may go now.
What the fuck does he think he is,
telling me what to do?
It was you who appointed
a good Defense Minister like him.
Are you mocking me?
I told you when you appointed him
a surprising number of soldiers
are upright
but few are reliable.
Don't you remember?
How can I convince that bullhead
to be on my side?
You cannot change people.
It's better to sack them.
You think I don't know?
It's bad timing.
You're not the one to wait
for the right timing.
To clear my head,
let's play go.
The families are having
a memorial service in Morocco today.
So what?
What does it have to do with playing go?
Nothing. I'm just saying.
The black is yours today
since I won big last time.
I can do whatever I want
while at the Blue House.
I should report you to the FTC
for abusing your power.
If you lose today,
you'll be black next time.
Mom...
Jin-ho.
I bet you can't even rest in peace
but I can't even hold you.
I miss you so much, my love.
I can't believe you're gone.
It's daddy's fault, my son!
Honey, please!
I'm begging you, Honey!
Jin-ho!
Honey!
Hoon!
Hoon, I'm sorry!
Due to the crash of B357,
the Korean public is in shock and grief.
Some even argue that
Dynamic System, the manufacturer,
shouldn't participate in the bidding.
What do you say about this?
Avionics are like the head of a plane,
and an engine can
be compared to the heart.
The B357 manufactured by Dynamic System
had malfunctioning avionics,
and its engine exploded.
A soldier
with a malfunctioning head and heart
can never win a battle.
That's all I will say.
Hey, Chief Gang.
What a surprise.
What are you doing here?
Aren't you too old to play with planes?
Then are you here
because you played with a plane?
What's with the sharp comeback?
Oh, is it because of the transfer order?
What's wrong with
the Psychological Intelligence Department?
Monitoring the media
and checking typos on documents
are all you need to do.
Get your annoying face out of here.
Man. You stink of alcohol.
Drinking again during the day?
That's why the Director General
doesn't like you
because you're a disgrace to the NIS.
Get the hell out.
I'm telling you because I'm your friend.
How can I give you advice
when you're not ready to listen?
Stop being ma--
Oh, Mr. Senior Secretary Yun?
I went to our hometown last week
for an alumni union.
There, you were
as popular as an idol star.
It's because you're the first
in our tiny town
to become Senior Secretary
to the President for Civil Affairs.
Had dinner yet? Do you care for Sushi?
There's a place nearby I go often
and they specialize in wild fish.
It's really yummy. Let's go.
GO HAE-RI
Why do you want to see the black box?
I'll tell you
if you promise you won't get mad.
Then don't. I'll get mad.
Some say...
there's a survivor
among the passengers.
What?
Tell that bullshit to Chief Min.
Why call me
instead of your direct supervisor?
You said you knew someone at the ICAO.
-I'm going to hang up now.
-Don't do this to me, sir.
I went to Lisbon for you.
Do you know how hard it was,
soaking wet and everything?
One good turn deserves another.
Don't be a cold fish.
All right.
I'll see what I can do,
but don't get your hopes up.
Thank you, sir.
By the way,
any results from the autopsy yet?
He killed himself, right?
Something isn't right.
He wasn't the suicidal type at all.
I got to go.
Excuse me.
I'm Gang Ju-cheol. I called you earlier.
Right, nice to meet you.
You're a friend of Michael's, right?
That's right.
I have a question about him.
I can only spare five minutes
due to the tight schedule.
Michael's wife
hasn't been answering the phone.
Do you know why he killed himself?
It's not something I can share with you.
How well did you know Michael?
He helped me a lot
when he was with the CIA.
Michael had a problem...
with his lady friends.
Do you know who they are
and what kind of problems?
Well, to respect his privacy,
I can't tell you anymore.
I'm sorry.
Putting this on will help you
with motion sickness.
Thank you.
You said you have an upset stomach?
This is something I take,
and it works really well.
Take one now
and maybe another on the plane.
Thank you for everything.
Is everyone here?
I don't see Mr. Cha Dal-geon.
He decided to stay here
to catch the terrorist.
He went back on his own.
It's time to go.
Thank you for your service.
-Thank you.
-Goodbye, sir.
This way, please.
O-chan, it's me.
I'm sending you a video now,
spread it online.
What the...?
Mr. Cha Dal-geon!
What is it? What's wrong?
Hoon's videos from the cloud are all gone!
What?
Maybe they were accidentally deleted?
-What the...?
-Shit.
Dal-geon!
No!
Stop right there!
Get over here!
Who sent you? Tell me!
Why are you doing this?
I don't know anything!
Let me live! I don't know anything!
Plane!
What the fuck are you saying?
Get over here, damn it.
Tell me now!
Speak in fucking English!
Tell me now, or you're fucking dead!
Do you want to fucking die?
-Freeze!
-Let him go!
Let go of me!
Not me!
Arrest that motherfucker, you idiots!
Arrest him, not me!
Let me go!
Ah...
Can you hear something?
Give me a second.
You got busted.
-The person next to...
-I brought them home.
-I brought them back home.
-The person next to...
I can hear a bit...
-I brought them back home.
It doesn't sound Korean.
-Excuse me?
-I think it's Spanish.
-Give me that.
-Sure.
-Why did you quit the Action Center?
-Set your watch.
-You said you'd become...
-To the current time, 11...
-From the beginning.
-Okay.
-The person next to...
-I brought them back home.
Okay?
-Why did you quit the Action Center?
-Set your watch.
You said you'd be famous...
-...and go to Hollywood.
-Seven...
-Is it authorized to do--
-Hush. Hold on.
-Precisely in 14 hours and 37 minutes.
-You're the coolest when doing stunts.
-...sorry I got mad at you.
-And the gift?
Hello?
I got his phone conversation.
-What did he say?
-I can't understand at all.
The man from the video spoke Spanish.
Spanish?
I'll read it to you. Write it down.
Hwa-suk, text it to me. Thank you.
She's such a pain in the neck.
-Who is it?
-It's me.
What are you doing here so early?
Cha Dal-geon is in police custody.
What?
What did he do this time?
-Just follow me.
-I know the way.
-Good. Drive safely.
-Thank you.
Hoon hasn't spoken a word
for more than two months.
The doctor said that
it's not that he couldn't,
but that he wouldn't.
Couldn't you reach his mom?
No, that's why we called you, his uncle.
So...
you want me to take him?
-You're his family.
-Family, my ass...
I can't.
My life is hard enough.
I can't raise a kid.
-We're closing down soon.
-Find another orphanage...
Find another orphanage for him, then.
Do it yourself.
Hey. Hey!
Shit.
Lift up your arm.
Don't you miss your mom?
I'll find her soon
and you can stay with her.
My mom abandoned me.
Will you abandon me, too, uncle?
Who says you can't speak?
If you're going to abandon me,
then do it now.
Family isn't like a piece of junk
you can throw away or pick up.
Family is...
people living under the same roof.
Family, my ass!
Who told you to pick up bad words first?
Who told you to learn such a bad word?
-Stop it.
-Oh! What's this?
You want to fight with me?
Want to fight?
Oh, okay. I won't let you!
Okay, you win.
I surrender, I surrender!
Got you.
You are free to go.
We will now begin the interrogation.
Was anything else stolen
besides the laptop?
Tell them he's with the one
who crashed the plane.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Just tell them.
The man who crashed the plane
and this man are working together.
He went to clean your room
and found it tossed, so he got out.
Don't fucking lie to me!
He's mad because you punched him
out of nowhere.
You bastard!
Ah! you motherfucker...
Dal-geon, it's no use getting worked up.
This man is a cleaner at the hotel,
and they've checked his identity.
Then the hotel is in it together.
Mr. Cha Dal-geon.
Translate it, now!
I can't. Why don't you, please?
Damn it...
-Why are they uncuffing him?
-Dal-geon, because--
He's being released,
and you're going back to jail.
What are you talking about? No!
Shit.
Let me go!
Dal-geon! Hey!
What are you doing?
Translate it to him.
I have 18 degrees in martial arts.
It won't take me a second to kill!
So tell me now
that you're with that terrorist!
That's enough, Mr. Cha Dal-geon.
You want to rot your life away in jail?
She's right. This is not the way.
He'll shoot you on three
unless you let him go!
Still not talking?
Let's die together, then.
They don't lie about shooting!
Say it!
He says...
they'll shoot me, too.
You're gonna get me killed, asshole!
Damn it!
Yes, Chief.
Go to the ICAO secretariat,
and look for Doctor Kevin Kim.
He'll show you the black box.
He's a Korean American working with us.
Are you there?
I'm afraid that won't be necessary.
You asked me to jump
through hoops for nothing?
I'm sorry, sir.
I got no time to lose. Get me out of here.
I did everything I could.
I won't help you anymore.
What if I've been telling you the truth?
Then you're becoming an accomplice
to the terrorist. Understand?
Shit. He's driving me crazy.
Welcome.
-I'm Go Hae-ri.
-Yes, I know. I'm Kevin Kim.
We retrieved two black boxes
from the plane.
They have the voice recording device
containing the cockpit conversation,
and the plane computer data recording.
What's up with all those kids?
It's a taekwondo demo team.
Oh, a national team?
We'd better do our best.
-May I take this call?
-Sure.
Honey, I have been waiting for your call.
Can you speak Spanish as well?
Don't worry, he doesn't understand
what we're talking about.
Doctor, do you speak Spanish?
I got it translated.
He seems to be talking
with his girlfriend.
OK, hold on.
I've synchronized my watch.
The man from the video spoke Spanish.
Honey, I have been waiting for your call.
Don't worry, he doesn't understand
what we're talking about.
-Why did you quit the Action Center?
-Set your watch.
To the current time, 11:02 a.m.
Seven, eight, nine seconds.
Okay, one moment. I got it.
When can I see you?
Precisely in 14 hours
and 37 minutes from now.
-And the gift?
-It's ready.
You'll find it at the meeting point.
What about our date?
They are set for 13:15, 13:20,
13:23,
13:30.
I got it.
Anything else you need?
No, it's fine.
I love you, darling.
It seems like
they're talking to each other.
It surely does.
But if one of them is the co-pilot,
then who's the other one?
You are free to go.
-What happened?
-I spent 1,500 euros.
I could've got it down to 1,000.
-Did you bribe them?
-What else could I do?
This is my bank account,
so send 1,500 euros to here.
You'd better do it.
That douchebag was right.
Excuse me?
The B357 crash was...
an act of terrorism.
Why do you want to join the NIS?
My dad was a colonel in the Marine Corps.
There was a fire during training,
and he died saving eight of his men.
I want to follow his noble path
and serve my country--
Boring.
Excuse me?
Most applicants give me the same answer.
I'm the daughter of
a man of national merit.
Doubting my patriotism
seems an insult to my dad--
He was worried about you.
Colonel Go Gang-cheol,
Chief of First Division, the Marine Corps.
Do you know my dad personally?
I'm one of those eight
whom he saved.
Oh, I see.
What a coincidence.
I wasn't going to tell you this,
but my mom fell victim to fraud
when she bought a part of
a shopping center not long ago.
We only have a house left
which is put up for auction.
And my brother failed
to enter a university and decided--
We're done here.
I'm a young breadwinner.
You said my dad saved your life.
If I don't get this job,
my family has to be out on the street--
Subtitle translation by Jean S. Kim