Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 15
It’s time.
Or
I should send you off Zhaodu first.
After all, we don’t have enough
forces in Zhaodu.
What if…?
Though we have few forces in Zhaodu,
we have a friend.
However,
he hasn’t agreed to work with us.
When he received my gift,
he’ll definitely agree.
Let’s see
how powerful the Earth Fire will be
after it breaks through the Wall.
Xiao.
What’s that?
It’s Moon Guards’ flame path.
Moon Guards
are isolated in the Abyss.
Though they’ve stepped away
from the harassment on land,
they still need to be cautious
of the Evil Souls.
When it gets dark,
they’ll ignite two flame paths
to keep away from the Evil Souls.
No.
I know what they’re going to do.
Actually Zhu Xi doesn’t have any forces.
All these
are their cover.
What do you mean?
Zhu Xi
let you go to Zhaodu to
give the information on purpose.
The fish boat army is a cover.
The real purpose is to
transfer all Fei Tian’s
Moon Guards from Zhaodu.
Transfer them from Zhaodu?
As everyone knows,
to get Zhaodu,
you must get rid of the Moon Guards.
It’s not safe here.
Go!
Yin Zhuang.
Go.
It’s the same with
that of the Earth Fire.
Flammable Stones.
They’re from the Fire Tribe.
Weisheng Yan.
Chief Priest,
it’s all done.
Where do you put them in?
Tianqi Cemetery.
We must make sure Zhu Xi can’t
find Goddess.
Yes.
To save Goddess,
it’s time for us
to be bad guys.
Your Majesty.
Quick.
Send His Majesty in.
What’s going on?
The Moon Guards’ castles around Zhaodu
have all been destroyed.
Our tribesmen
have mostly died.
Send all people out
to save them in all efforts!
No injured ones shall be left behind!
Yes!
Wait!
Your job is
to save His Majesty
and the capital city.
Fei Tian!
I see.
You can be relieved, Minister Fei.
Now
no matter how many Moon Guards’ feathers
have been on fire,
I shall set on the same number of
fires of revenge to Pingting!
Zhu Xi.
It’s my vow of the revenge
on you!
It’s quiet in Zhaodu.
So weird.
Yin Zhuang.
Wait for us on the boat.
But…
It’s fine.
It will protect me.
Huotu.
Xia Ling?
This way.
How would you be here?
It’s a long story.
Huotu, Ling…
It doesn’t matter. Go ahead.
Linglong was caught by them.
Where’s she now?
I’ll take you there.
Okay.
Go.
Something bad may also happen
to His Majesty.
We can meet in the hall directly.
Be careful.
Let’s go.
Did Zhu Xi take you here?
Did they make things difficult
for our tribesmen?
No.
It’s me.
I wanted to be the hero
to kill the monster
for the tribesmen.
She’s left the Fire Tribe.
Why can’t you let her go?
It’s my fault.
But I saw it clearly.
Linglong is indeed the Goddess.
Huotu, let’s go.
It’s here.
Linglong was kept inside.
Why didn’t you tell His Majesty?
People here seem to respect Goddess.
But they try to hurt her secretly.
Linglong?
Father!
Father, I’m Linglong!
I’m here!
Father!
Linglong!
Don’t worry.
I’ll get you out soon!
Father!
Linglong!
Step back!
Father.
It’s alright.
It’s alright. It’s alright.
You hold me too tight.
I am almost strangled to death.
Father.
It’s such a thick wall.
It’s my fault.
It’s your fault?
Why is it your fault?
I will never leave you again.
You don’t know.
I feel proud of you.
When I was in Pingting,
so many people were following behind me,
trying to flatter me.
They even wished me to be their father.
Nonsense!
Alright.
It’s alright.
It’s too dangerous here.
We should leave quickly.
Father.
I can’t run away now.
I can’t leave Yuan Yi
alone here.
Do you think
I’m here to take you to run way?
I have
no more wishes this life,
I only want you to live
a healthy and happy life.
I didn’t want you to leave before,
because I’m afraid in this big world,
I can’t protect you.
But now,
you’ve grown up.
You know what you want to do.
I
can’t protect you forever.
But at least now,
look,
am I powerful again?
Such a thick wall.
I entered through it.
Alright. Alright.
It’s okay.
Go.
Huotu!
Linglong.
Xia Ling.
They found us.
We need to leave now.
Okay.
Go.
This is…
He had been careless.
So I took the chance.
It’s these people
who deluded me to Zhaodu
to identify Linglong as a monster.
I…
Never mind.
It’s gone.
Zhu Xi’s men have taken actions.
Is it Zhu Xi who kept you here?
I don’t think so.
It’s Tianqi Cemetery.
I think it’s Chief Priest
who hid me here.
But he will not hurt me.
So he’s trying to protect me.
But it’s unnecessary.
Zhu Xi won’t be able to
make trouble in Zhaodu.
Linglong,
Fei Tian’s Moon Guards
have been all injured.
What?
Zhu Xi’s men
will attack Zhaodu in any minute.
So Chief Priest hid me
first.
He must have known
Zhu Xi’s plan.
Can it be that
Zhu Xi and Chief Priest
are a team?
They did it together?
It’s impossible.
Chief Priest won’t kill me.
He won’t hurt Yuan Yi, either.
Moon Guards…
They’re going to kill Fei Tian!
Minister Fei.
Run!
The Moon Tribe held His Majesty!
Fei Tian was trying to kill the Goddess!
The evidence is conclusive!
The treason crime is unforgivable!
All Moon Tribe’s men
shall die!
Chief Priest,
are you insane?
Your Majesty,
you can sentence me later.
But today,
I’d rather give my life
to wipe out the criminals.
I should have figured it out.
To wipe me out,
you’re even willing to work with Zhu Xi.
Fei Tian.
It’s your death day.
You?
What are you doing?
You want to rebel?
The Moon Tribe plots treason!
Fei Tian shall be sentenced to death!
Protect His Majesty!
Fei Tian is arbitrary and domineering,
and blasphemes Goddess!
She’s committed a death crime!
People in the city all want
to kill her tribesmen.
Now the Goddess comes again.
Whoever kills her
will get the Goddess's redemption!
Who dares?
Yin Xiao.
Go!
Fei Tian, go!
They will not make it hard on me.
But losing you
will be my real desperate plight.
We can’t let Fei Tian go!
It’s been a long time.
Minister Fei.
It’s
you.
You never expected that
I can still fly, right?
Fei Tian.
No.
Your Majesty.
Someone!
Yuan Yi.
Your Majesty.
You can
become a
res...
pectable
emperor.
I’m so proud of it.
No.
Don’t say this.
Hold on.
Linglong.
Here.
I’m here.
Go.
Take His Majesty away.
Promise me
to take good care
of His Majesty.
I can save you.
Wait a minute.
Your Majesty.
Protect yourself well.
Fei Tian.
Fei Tian, I can save you.
Sword.
Do you have a sword?
Yuan Yi.
Stab me, Yuan Yi.
Yuan Yi!
What’re you doing?
What are you doing?
I need to save Fei Tian.
Why stab you with a sword?
-I’ll explain it later.
-Are you crazy?
No!
-I won’t listen! It’s late!
-Explain to me first!
Father!
-I want to save Fei Tian!
-No!
Explain to me first!
-Enough!
-Father!
I can save…
Fei Tian!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Fei Tian has died!
Moon Guards!
Surrender yourselves!
Yuan Yi. What are you going to do?
Don’t stop me.
Don’t be impulsive.
Let’s go first!
I won’t leave.
Calm down.
I won’t leave Zhaodu!
Listen.
If you are controlled by Zhu Xi,
who can exonerate the crime
for the Moon Tribe?
You want Fei Tian
to bear the accusation of treason
in the record?
The Moon Guards safeguard Zhaodu
and protect you.
But they’ll be called traitors
and cursed by posterity after they die.
If you insist on staying in Zhaodu,
the sacrifice the Guards make
will truly become a joke.
In the name of Goddess, I promise
we will be back.
Protect the Goddess!
Bring His Majesty back!
Linglong,
go.
What’s wrong?
Surprise?
I’ve told you.
Don’t touch
my man.
Father!
Go.
Get on the boat.
Fei Tian
finally can be with Master Fozhuan.
Don’t follow him!
Maybe
he just wants to cry alone
and don’t want us to see it.
The top priority
is to discuss
where to go next.
It’s not a solution
to keep flying here.
Yeah.
I’ve promised Fei Tian
to guard Yuan Yi for her.
When Yuan Yi comes out,
we need to prepare
a complete plan for him.
Alright.
Let’s discuss
the plan.
Before that,
we need her to tell us the truth.
Huotu Xin.
I saved
you and your daughter again.
What’re you doing, Huotu Xin?
If she’s not willing to tell the truth,
it’s useless even if you kill her.
You think you know me well?
What the heck do you know?
I didn’t say I want to know you.
If you still won’t tell us the truth,
you have no more chance to talk.
You like the truth that much?
Then your sister
does marry the right one.
Miss Wu Yuan,
if your grandfather knows
you are serving Weisheng Yan
for him,
he must feel uneasy.
I was the same, too.
I was so stupid before.
If I sacrifice myself to ask
Weisheng Yan to support my brother,
in the end,
it must bring misery to us all.
So I’ve made up my mind
that I must leave Weisheng Yan
to live my own life.
I hope
you can also leave him.
Even if I tell you,
do you know if it’s true or not?
Because you can only tell us the truth.
Why?
I remember when we were
in the Fire Tribe,
you said
you wanted to keep me to make a deal.
My father told me
you did that to save your grandfather.
But whatever Weisheng Yan
is plotting,
it can’t be a favor to me.
But I
am the one
who can save your grandfather.
If I’m willing to help you,
you must be able to
make a choice easily, right?
Yeah.
We’re different from
Weisheng Yan, right?
At least we wish your grandfather
to be good.
You’re different from Weisheng Yan.
If you were at least half cruel as him,
will you
be in this situation?
You remember how to use it?
I’m tired.
I’ll go to sleep first
before reconsidering it.
Well.
His Majesty
is not so well right now.
If something bad happens to him,
you must be blamed for it.
You know what?
This time my father
didn’t ask to take me away.
He promised that
he will find the evidence
of Zhu Xi’s rebellion
and help me complete
what I want to do.
He said for these years,
he’s the only one coming out
of the Fire Tribe.
He can’t embarrass our tribesmen.
If it’s not that you took us out,
which allowed him
and I
to have experienced all these,
he may never
say that.
Actually me too.
Before,
I always tried to
get more recognition from others.
But if you didn’t take me
to experience this,
I may never know that
even if all are denying me,
I can still be happy.
I’m so happy that
I can be by your side.
You’re back.
You don’t allow others to disturb him,
but you can’t help to do so.
If Yin Zhuang knows that,
she must laugh at you.
How is he?
Yuan Yi?
Why are you here?
Where’s Linglong?
You can take her away.
What did you say?
Now Zhaodu has been occupied,
I’m in exile with the emperor.
Zhu Xi must tell others
we are traitors.
Do you want me to go back
to the Bright Moon Island?
You can always figure
out what I’m thinking.
Sure.
We are related after all.
But I
never know
what you’re thinking.
So I make you
suffer a lot.
Xiao.
You’ve changed.
What?
Now you’re willing to show weakness.
You’re trying to ask me
my true feelings, aren’t you?
You don’t want
me to feel wronged for you anymore.
Right?
Yes.
I don’t want to guess it anymore.
Xiao.
I told you.
No matter I choose to
get married or run away,
it’s all my choice.
So later on,
whatever you do,
don’t push me away,
or
treat me scrupulously.
The future path
will be so hard.
So you mean
Linglong
will be assimilated
by the Goddess?
If she gets more mature,
in the end,
she will lose herself.
It’s like
she’s eaten by the Goddess.
It’s different.
What’s the difference?
Does
Linglong know?
When I know it, it’s too late.
I don’t expect your forgiveness.
But please trust me.
I don’t want to lose her, either.
You don’t
want your Zhaodu?
I won’t trade it with Linglong.
Brat.
It’s rare that we can get along well.
So,
do you have any solutions?
Not yet.
But she can’t transform anymore.
Or else…!
Do you know
till now,
Linglong has been
trying to figure some ways
to help you take Zhaodu back?
She’s doing everything to help you.
So,
should you
repay her in the same way?
I will.
Brat,
at that time,
you coaxed her out.
Now you can’t throw her back to me.
Be a man.
Take your responsibility.
Think it well
about how to tell her.
Remember
not to make her sad.
You’re telling me this. Does it mean
that you’re committing her to me?
You bastard!
What’re you thinking?
Well.
What are you doing?
We…
I told you to take care of your wound.
How can you even beat him?
-I…
-You even bully him.
I didn’t.
No.
You fell down yourself?
Yeah.
No.
Does it hurt?
Never mind.
Let me check.
I’m fine.
It doesn’t hurt.
I just applied the medicine.
Huotu Xin.
I’ve known that.
What were you arguing for exactly?
I thought
you were going to
cry alone.
Sorry to keep you worried.
I’m okay.
Have you figured it out?
What’s your plan?
Actually we have discussed it.
We weren’t discouraged.
We’ve decided
to find the evidence of Zhu Xi
and Chief Priest’s rebellion first.
And then…
Well.
I’ll also try hard
to learn how to control Goddess's power.
Goddess and the emperor
are destined
to fight together.
So,
don’t worry.
I will never lose you.
Why
are you
suddenly…?
Father.
What’re you doing?
I…
What are you doing?
I’m serious.
Aren’t you having a headache?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Forced love is not sweet.
Bring the boat around
to the Fire Tribe.
The Palace of Flames.
Okay.
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪