Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 18
Yin Jia.
Come.
Huotu Ke.
Decapitate him!
Execute him!
Huotu Ke of Fire Tribe
ignited the Earth Fire,
tormented the common people,
and enraged God.
Huotu Ke
of Fire Tribe
ignited the Earth Fire,
tormented the common people,
and enraged God.
-This is…
-Huotu Ke
of Fire Tribe…
the trial of Earth Fire.
ignited the Earth Fire,
tormented the common people,
and enraged God.
Huotu Ke
of Fire Tribe
ignited the Earth Fire,
tormented the common people,
and enraged God.
Stop!
He was framed.
Now,
decapitate him!
No!
Stop!
Vile spawn!
You’re still unrepented.
Do you want to die with Huotu Ke?
Father.
You know it clearly,
Huotu Ke was wronged.
I’m not your father.
The Yins
has no such a daughter as you.
I won’t
let you kill him.
Yin Jia.
We will always be together.
No.
I curse you.
I curse the Yins,
the Yuans.
I curse every one of you.
I swear,
ten years,
a hundred years,
or a thousand years,
till Suchuan is destroyed,
I must take revenge for Huotu Ke.
Where’s my father?
I’ve never hurt innocent people.
You saw it, didn’t you?
You make me dream.
It’s not a dream.
It’s my memory.
Where did your necklace
come from?
My mother left it to me.
What about yours?
Does it have anything to do
with my dream?
None of your business.
So,
was Huotu Ke
really wronged?
You saw it.
The Earth Fire trial was full of lies.
That’s what you want me to see.
How do I know if it was real or not?
Those are my memories
left by Huotu Ke.
Every bit,
every piece of it,
is an irreplaceable treasure to me.
It’s everything to me.
How dare you say it’s not real!
So you try to kill Yuan Yi
to avenge Huotu Ke’s death?
Yuan Tu was the real criminal.
In order to quench the Spirit Stone,
he didn’t hesitate
to ignite the Earth Fire,
plunging the Fire Tribe
into misery and suffering.
At last,
he and my father
let Huotu Ke
bear the blame.
What was the Earth Fire trial?
It was actually the sin
of the Yuans and the Yins.
But Yuan Yi isn’t Yuan Tu.
The descendants of the Fire Tribe
have been trapped
by Earth Fire for generations,
and they must
atone for the crime
that they didn’t commit.
We don’t fight against the Earth Fire
to atone for our crime.
That’s the glory of Fire Tribe.
What a surprise!
In the end, it’s a girl of Fire Tribe
that tries to defend the Yuans.
The necklace left by Huotu Ke
is to keep
the good memories
of you two.
It’s not used to carry the hatred.
What do you know?
I know a lot.
If Yuan Yi is killed today,
I must try to kill you
to avenge his death.
I won’t care if I must
give up my own life.
However,
Yuan Yi certainly
doesn’t want me to do so.
And my father,
if I give up my life
that he has prized above
his own life,
he’ll never forgive me.
In the past 500 years,
you’ve been
stayed at the deserted
Palace of Flames alone.
It must be
more painful than death, isn’t it?
If Huotu Ke knew it,
wouldn’t he be more miserable than you?
If you kill Yuan Yi now
and shout,
“Huotu Ke, I’ve avenged your death!”
Could he hear you?
If you shout,
“I’ve cleared your name!”
Will people of Suchuan know it?
Killing Yuan Yi
is to vent your own hatred
or to clear
Huotu Ke’s name?
No.
It only makes you
a king slayer.
And Huotu Ke
was still the criminal
who ignited the Earth Fire.
At that time,
there would be no one
to prove his innocence.
But if you keep Yuan Yi alive
and tell him the truth,
he will help you
to absolve Huotu Ke.
Yuan Yi is the emperor.
If anyone
can rewrite history,
it must be Yuan Yi.
Do you want me to trust
the descendants of the Yuans?
Believe me.
Yuan Yi isn’t Yuan Tu.
He is a kind and upright man.
Then I’ll let you know
how many lies the Yuans told.
See by yourself.
What is this?
Goddess,
can’t you recognize the Gods?
They were
the piously worshipped Gods
killed by the Yuans.
Didn’t His Majesty tell you,
the day you
become the real Goddess
is the day
you vanish completely as a human?
What are you talking about?
Being parasitic on young girls’ bodies,
taking young girls’ lives,
could it be called Goddess?
You’re just a
human sacrifice for them.
You’re not even a monster.
It can’t be true.
I have the power of the Goddess.
I saved my father.
Really?
Did you really save your father,
or was it the fate of the Yuans?
Goddess
is just the Yuans’ puppet,
and a faithful dog.
Honorable God,
the Yuans’ chosen throne,
and the great dynasty
is based on
the sacrifices of
countless young girls like you.
The myth went on and on
until the great Emperor Yuan Tu
ascended the throne.
Yuan Tu feared the truth
would eventually be revealed.
He feared all day and couldn’t sleep.
Finally,
he made
the craziest decision.
To kill all the Gods
and make it a myth forever.
Here
is the place where
Yuan Tu slaughtered the Gods.
Only the roaring flames of Earth Fire
could kill you completely.
Earth Fire
rose from the slaughtering,
and it will last forever.
This is the truth of Earth Fire.
Isn’t it pathetic?
As a Goddess,
you’re used by the Yuans.
In the end,
you’ll be thrown away
like garbage.
Yuan Tu wouldn’t think of it himself.
After 500 years,
they eventually reappeared.
Again,
they stand in front of the Gods’ tomb.
The Yuans
built a dynasty with countless girls,
and covered up their lies
with the faith of the Fire Tribe.
This
is the truth.
So,
Goddess,
do you think
I can believe a man of the Yuans?
When it lights up,
the Fall of God in Suchuan
which has lasted for 500 years,
will end in my hands.
After that, Suchuan
will belong to you and me.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Listen to me.
I’m here to help you.
Weisheng Yan.
Seeing you here
doesn’t surprise me at all.
I was kind of hoping
to see you here.
Huotu Xin.
I’m really here to help you.
Don’t hurt me.
Drop the act.
You know I can’t
do you any harm.
But I can see anger
in your eyes.
Where’s Linglong?
Linglong?
Yin Jia is taking care of her.
Weisheng Yan,
tell me.
How can I rescue Linglong?
I’m begging you.
I’ve fought with you.
I know I’m no match for you.
I don’t want to be your opponent.
As long as you can save Linglong,
I’ll do whatever you ask me to do.
It’s too late.
It’s not.
The secret here can
make one live for 500 years.
I’m sure it can save Linglong, too.
Right?
So you want to do business with me.
But you don’t have any capital.
I…
I can take Linglong away
from Fire Tribe,
and from Suchuan.
Don’t you want Zhaodu?
I’ll take Yuan Yi away, too.
He’ll listen to Linglong.
Weisheng Yan,
you can take everything you want.
I only want Linglong.
Huotu Xin.
You were a tough man who didn’t give in
to Zhu Xi’s cruel torture.
What happened to you?
I…
I can’t save my daughter.
I can’t…
I can’t let Linglong become a monster.
You mean Jin’er, don’t you?
Well,
Jin’er listened to me at the beginning
and went to Fire Tribe.
Because she knew
only the Palace of Flames
had a way to save her.
Who was Jin’er actually?
Did she
have anything to do with you
or with the secret here?
Whoever she was,
whatever she would do,
it doesn’t matter anymore,
does it?
She was dead.
But fortunately,
she left a daughter
in the world.
Linglong.
She goes even further
than her own mother.
Did you see?
Jin’er’s appearance.
Isn’t Linglong like her very much?
I’m begging you.
Look.
I’ve never been your opponent.
The reason Wu Yuan
brought you here this time
is because only Yin Jia
can save Linglong.
Didn’t Wu Yuan tell you?
I’ve been helping you.
Weisheng Yan, you know it.
I don’t believe
every word you said.
But,
only you can save Linglong.
So it doesn’t matter.
I don’t care even if you let me
work like a horse.
Whatever you let me do,
as long as you can kill
the monster in Linglong’s body
and give her back to me,
I’ll listen to you.
It’s a deal then?
Actually, as for Jin’er’s death,
I blamed myself, too.
I don’t want Linglong
to repeat her mother’s tragedy.
This place isn’t good for walking.
What did you say just now?
You would do anything for me,
wouldn’t you?
Why don’t you help me
pave a trail first?
♪Paint a picture of spring♪
♪Fragrant flowers fall to the ground♪
I’m in a hurry to save your daughter.
♪Sink in thought♪
♪Look afar♪
♪To the vast♪
♪Falling flowers♪
♪Fly like yellow sand♪
♪Idle the days away♪
♪Forget melancholy♪
♪Loyal heart♪
♪Has been exiled♪
♪Displaced Crystal heart♪
♪Is blown off by the east wind♪
♪Flying frost and snow
dyed my hair white♪
♪Gradually I’m indifferent to
years and to rise and fall♪
♪Crystal heart lay in pieces
at the ends of the earth♪
♪Love sinks in day and night♪
♪Fate brings us together♪
I ask you to pave a trail.
What do you sprawl on the ground for?
♪For whom I stayed for a moment♪
You’re good for nothing.
Oh, by the way,
stay away from Yin Zhuang
from now on.
Except for Yin Zhuang,
I don’t need you to do anything.
You’re useless to me.
I keep you alive,
but you don’t appreciate it.
I’ll never leave Yin Zhuang.
The body works very well.
I don’t want to give it back to you yet.
Then I’ll stay here
for the rest of my life.
What did you say?
Say it again.
I said,
I’ll stay here
for the rest of my life.
I’ll remain at my sister’s side.
I’ll try every means
to drag you out of
Yin Zhuang’s body.
Even if
I become a ghost
like you.
Xiao.
Xiao, don’t.
Xiao, forget about me.
Yin Zhuang.
It was so touching.
It gives me pain
not to let your sister hear it.
But your sister fully
focuses on the Fire Tribe man.
Even if I give her back to you,
one day,
she’ll still leave you.
Can you bear it?
But I can
let you and your sister
be together forever.
Do you want to see
Yin Zhuang’s body?
Stop it!
Get the hell out of her body!
Xiao.
What happened?
Yin Zhuang.
I…
Can you still slap her?
I’m begging you.
Don’t do this to her.
Help me,
and I’ll let you and your sister
be together forever.
Linglong.
Father.
Are you all right?
Did the strange woman do anything…
Why is your face so dirty?
I…
I’m fine.
I’m fine, too.
I’m very well.
You…
Why are you here?
When I was born,
it was shining, wasn’t it?
It’s called Pillar of Eternity.
There is another one in Zhaodu.
But it’s bigger than this one.
Yuan Yi said,
through the pillar, Goddess shows
its divine power to Suchuan.
If I turn into Goddess now,
it must shine.
Linglong,
there’s one thing
I must tell you.
I know.
All the time,
I’ve been trying to prove
my mother wasn’t a monster.
Me neither.
Do you know, Father?
Yuan Yi is like
a beam of light
that comes into my life.
I left Fire Tribe
for Zhaodu.
I tried my best to be Goddess.
Because I want everyone to know
what Yuan Yi said was true.
But in the end,
I’m still a monster.
No.
Linglong,
you’re not.
That night on the fish boat,
Yuan Yi told you all of it, didn’t he?
I wonder why he is so weird
recently.
He must want to tell me these, too.
Father, you did a great job this time.
You didn’t try to take me away
or go to beat Yuan Yi
in a rage.
You trust us.
It makes me happy.
Thanks, Father.
Don’t worry.
I will find a way.
I will.
I have an idea.
I have an idea
to bring Yin Zhuang back
as well as to save Yuan Yi.
What’s that?
Yin Jia is in
the necklace around her neck.
Yin Jia.
This is Memory Crystal.
It can keep all your
good memories.
Even if Heaven rends asunder
and Earth cracks,
everything is destroyed,
or we were both gone,
our good memories kept in it
will last forever.
Forever?
It
is our eternity.
Yin Jia.
Weisheng Yan.
Haven’t you left?
I have a present
that I forgot to give you.
I don’t need it.
The necklace around your neck
is too old.
It’s not secure.
You will go out of
the Palace of Flames in the future.
In case anything unexpected happened,
even the Memory Crystal isn’t lost,
it may fall to the ground.
It’s not good to get it bumped.
This necklace
is made of the best
hard gold in Suchuan.
It is anti-fire-and-water.
It can’t be broken by
hard metal and stone.
It not only represents
my good intention,
but could also help you
to protect the great
Memory Crystal.
Then come and put it on me.
Yes.
As the treasure of Fire Tribe,
the Memory Crystal was only
used to keep some memories.
But you actually use it to
keep your consciousness
in order to make yourself immortal.
It’s astonishing.
The power of consciousness
is the only thing of the Yins
that is valuable to me.
Unfortunately,
the Yins had lost
the great power in the end.
It’s retribution.
Yin Jia isn’t a ghost.
She is kind of some
memory
or consciousness in the necklace.
What do you mean?
I don’t know why,
but I’m sure,
if you destroy Yin Jia’s necklace,
you can save Yin Zhuang.
Do you remember?
Yeah.
Go to save her now.
Yin Zhuang is waiting for you.
Well, where’re you going?
Yuan Yi is waiting for me, too.
I just saw
you played tricks on Yin Xiao.
Although it was interesting,
it was a little frivolous
of you to do that.
Aren’t you happy?
After all, you’re using
Yin Zhuang’s body.
I don’t care.
The body
is not mine.
It’s just
a container to me.
Sure.
But
I care.
Even if Heaven rends asunder
and Earth cracks,
everything is destroyed,
or we were both gone...
I must memorize everything about you.
It is our eternity.
Yin Zhuang,
I’m sorry.
I did something wrong.
I hurt you,
but I regret it now.
♪Oh Forget it♪
♪What can I do♪
I didn’t know how much
I loved you before.
♪As a mortal I’m too powerless♪
But now I know.
♪So be it then♪
Though you don’t want to be with me,
♪Be opposite♪
I can’t afford to see you
disappear.
♪Against the world♪
Yuan Yi,
even if I’m a monster,
I must save you first.
Linglong.
What’re you doing?
Father.
I’m sorry.
Linglong!
Yuan Yi.
Get up!
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Fortunately,
I can still save you.
Linglong.
You’re back.
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪