Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 17
Here,
we must take care.
Come on.
What… What is up?
Nothing.
Take care.
Yin Zhuang.
I recommend
we touch the bracelets.
It is very dangerous here.
They can protect us
if the Earth Fire rushes in later.
Okay.
I…
suddenly
feel like pissing.
Okay.
Just wait for me here.
Don’t go away.
Yin Zhuang.
Yin Zhuang?
Wu Yuan?
Why are you here?
Did you see Yin Zhuang?
They have found the entrance.
Yin Zhuang is waiting for us in there.
Let’s enter right away.
Welcome back
to the world of mortals.
What’s up?
Are you lost?
Yin Zhuang?
How did you like the meal yesterday?
I didn’t eat it.
Why don’t you acknowledge it
if you ate it?
Okay.
You didn’t eat it.
Let me tell you a secret.
That meal was personally
cooked by Yin Zhuang for you.
Remember to thank her later.
Okay.
I know Yin Xiao
was a little too harsh on you before.
But you are also to blame for it.
You shouldn’t have kept offending him.
But it is his fault
to leave you this time.
We have blamed him
and Yin Zhuang has blamed him too.
Forget it.
I don’t care anyway.
When you meet him again,
talk to him peacefully.
Yin Zhuang.
Whose dress is it?
It is my dress.
But,
you were wearing another one.
Linglong,
she is a little strange.
Are you scared, Your Majesty?
Scared of me
or this place?
Goddess is enough to protect you
even if she is half as mighty.
Don’t be scared.
Yin Zhuang,
are you kidding me?
Kidding you?
Of course not.
I am lauding you.
I have never seen
a girl with such a perfect combo
of body and soul
in the past centuries.
You are almost comparable
with the God of Emperor Yuan Tu.
But
why is the Goddess in your body
suppressed?
Are you
afraid of its power?
You have many secrets
on you.
That is why we came to
the Palace of Flames for an answer.
Do you forget it?
Answer?
I wonder
how Your Majesty thinks about it.
Yin Zhuang,
what nonsense are you talking about?
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
It is up to you
how to treat your own Goddess.
I am sorry for that.
What is wrong with you?
I don’t quite understand
what you talked about just now.
Where is my father?
Why are you alone?
Go towards the fire.
Your father is waiting for you
at the Palace of Flames.
Where are they?
Linglong?
Yuan Yi?
Where are they?
I have come with you all the way here.
How can I know it?
Er…
Where is Yin Zhuang?
Yin Zhuang.
Yin Zhuang!
Why did you change your clothes?
They have gone there.
Just follow the light
and they will be waiting for you
at the Palace of Flames.
Then
won’t you go with us?
Yin Zhuang,
wait!
Yin Zhuang.
Stop!
Don’t go there.
It is a trap.
Wu Yuan,
what’s up?
What are you talking about?
That person
isn’t Yin Zhuang.
Who is she if she isn’t Yin Zhuang?
Wu Yuan, no more kidding.
Let’s go. Hurry up.
Silly.
What a silly man you are!
Yin Xiao is right.
Wu Yuan.
I know you are wronged.
We will all say sorry to you
when we are back.
Linglong is still waiting for me now.
Let’s go.
Save yourself first,
Huotu Xin.
Nobody can be saved.
All people will die except Linglong.
What do you mean?
Die!
They will die, don’t you know it?
They will all die here.
What happened?
Who is threatening you?
Yin Zhuang is dead.
I killed her.
Then…
who was that person?
I don’t know.
But Weisheng Yan
must be the person behind all these.
Everything,
including taking you here,
was arranged by him.
Huotu Xin.
Huotu Xin, don’t go there.
You can’t defeat Weisheng Yan.
Weisheng Yan?
Yes,
I have been working for him.
Why?
Because only he can
control Linglong.
Only he can help me.
Will Linglong be in danger?
No.
He will allow Linglong to survive.
Is there a way to save Linglong
at the Palace of Flames?
I am afraid
only Weisheng Yan knows it.
Why do you tell me about it?
I know you won’t believe me.
But I don’t expect you
to die without knowing the truth.
Huotu Xin.
Do you remember it, Huotu Xin?
When I was at the Fire Tribe,
I told you not to go back.
I…
I believe you.
But I won’t give up on Linglong.
Never.
If we can meet again,
maybe you will see
a different me.
Yin Zhuang!
Huotu Xin!
Do you hear me?
Are you lost?
Yin Zhuang.
Follow the light.
No.
You are not Yin Zhuang.
Although
Yin Zhuang looks strange,
she has pointed out the right way.
But where is my father?
This is the palace
of the deceased king of Fire Tribe.
The palace of Fire Tribe
are comparable with those of Zhaodu.
Yes.
But they were all destroyed
by Huotu Ke for the ruling of the state.
As the legend goes,
in the reign of Huotu Ke,
his Jinshi City
claimed half the wealth of Suchuan,
and was almost as rich as
Zhaodu of Emperor Yuan Tu.
But
his yearning for the Spirit Stone
finally destroyed him.
Is the pursuit of unlimited power
his way of ruling?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Actually,
I wonder if I am the same as Huotu Ke.
Is my previous desire for God power
the source of all disasters?
Am I wrong
in my pursuit of the ruling way?
Yuan Yi,
don’t you believe me anymore?
No.
I had believed I must make a choice
between Suchuan and you
even until yesterday.
But now I realize
the God power
shouldn’t be the thing I am pursuing.
Why are you all
saying something
I don’t understand here?
Are you hiding something
from me?
I have considered it for long.
Today,
I will tell you all the truth.
After that,
I will make a choice with you.
Then,
I hope you won’t be the Goddess.
Instead,
you will be someone more important.
What a perfect couple!
Yin Zhuang.
Linglong!
Yin Zhuang!
Your words are really touching,
Your Majesty.
If Emperor Yuan Tu
had shared the same feeling then,
these disasters
wouldn’t have occurred.
Why do you keep talking about the past?
What did you find
at the Palace of Flames?
There are too many secrets
at the Palace of Flames and
they have been covered for too long.
So long
that I almost don’t believe
they will be uncovered
one day.
I wonder which one
Your Majesty wants to hear first.
Have you really discovered anything,
Yin Zhuang?
Do you know the secrets of Weisheng Yan?
Weisheng Yan?
Compared with the things here,
Weisheng Yan is nothing.
What is it then?
Don’t worry.
Wait until all people are here.
My father…
He will arrive soon.
Your Majesty,
please take your throne.
This is Huotu Ke’s throne.
Yes.
If you don’t see everything here
from the eye of Huotu Ke,
how can you really
feel what he felt?
Yuan Yi?
Yuan Yi.
Linglong, danger!
Don’t get close to Yin Zhuang!
Stand up!
Linglong.
Don’t go there, Linglong.
Don’t go up there.
What’s going on?
Yuan…
Your Majesty.
Do you feel the pain
of Huotu Ke?
I have done
what you asked me to do.
Well done!
You should give me
what you promised me.
Don’t worry.
Let me tell you a story first.
What is the most touching love
you have ever seen?
The one I have seen
happened right here.
It is a story about a boy of Huotu
and a girl of the Yin family.
Your flowers,
your grass,
your mountains,
your sky and clouds,
your smell,
your voice,
the air you breathe,
I will remember everything
about you.
Yuan Yi.
Don’t touch him.
His Majesty is still alive.
But if you touch him,
he will die.
You…
Linglong, don’t go there.
Linglong!
I will never
allow Yuan Yi to die.
Die?
He deserves much more than death.
I want him
to see the land
ridden with his sins to suffer
from the scorching of Earth Fire,
and slowly
wither here
a few hundred years later.
What are you talking about?
Yin Zhuang,
what’s wrong with you?
I am not Yin Zhuang.
But the bracelet you wear
won’t tell a lie.
It is not easy
to remove the bracelet.
Will the same tragedy
happen again?
She isn’t Yin Zhuang.
No,
I am not Yin Zhuang.
I am Yin Jia.
Yin Jia?
A girl of the Yin Family
who loved Huotu Ke so crazily.
Huotu Ke
was a figure five hundred years ago.
This story
must be older than the Earth Fire.
And they are the same violent.
It
can’t even be extinguished today.
Yin Jia
is a name
that the Yin family wishes
to eliminate from its history.
To the Yin family,
it is a name
full of sins,
humiliation,
and dirtiness.
But to the Huotu family,
she is the only
and the holiest
savior.
Blood.
Yin Jia.
Who is Yin Jia then?
She was the ancestor of the Yin Family.
Ancestor?
No.
The Yins doesn’t have such an ancestor.
A girl of the Yins
who became an enemy of the family,
abandoned her noble blood and reputation
and even killed her father
just to follow Huotu Ke.
Wasn’t Huotu Ke
the person who
ignited the Earth Fire?
If the whole world believes
your beloved
commits an unforgivable crime
and only you know he doesn’t,
what will you do then?
-Kill him.
-Decapitate.
-Kill him right away.
-Kill him.
-Decapitate him right away.
Huotu Ke of the Fire Tribe
has ignited the Earth Fire,
harmed the living beings
and offended the God.
If all people
are murderers of your beloved,
what will you do then?
Huotu Ke of the Fire Tribe
has ignited the Earth Fire,
harmed the living beings
and offended the God.
Will you rival with the world
just for him?
Huotu Ke of the Fire Tribe
has ignited the Earth Fire,
harmed the living beings
and offended the God.
This little blood
isn’t enough.
It isn’t your blood,
nor your body.
Come out here.
Where is your power?
Can’t you move?
You lost the power of your ancestor.
And have no reverence to your ancestor.
The Yins
is really a miserable
and absurd family.
If your beloved
becomes a scapegoat of history,
what will you do then?
Who on earth are you?
Why do you want to hurt Yuan Yi?
Yin Jia,
a sinful girl
driven out by the ancestor
of the Yins five hundred years ago.
Five hundred years ago?
Nonsense!
How can a person
be five hundred years old?
Live?
It can’t be called “live”.
She is a phantom
living in the shadow of history.
Sinful girl.
Exactly.
I am a sinful girl indeed.
I have become sinful
as I am a girl of the Yins.
Like Your Majesty,
we are all the offspring of sinners.
I will never allow you to harm Yuan Yi.
Linglong.
Goddess?
She is just a crazy dog
of the Yuan family.
Let go of her.
Don’t come here.
I… I am coming to save you.
Linglong.
Linglong!
Release His Majesty.
Do you really want to harm your sister?
Yin Zhuang!
Do you hear me, Yin Zhuang?
Yin Zhuang.
What a pitiful person.
Your Majesty.
Do they know the great sins
they are trying to guard?
Huotu Ke is wronged.
He
was just another wronged soul
in the history of the Yuans.
The real source of the Earth Fire
is Emperor Yuan Tu,
the ancestor of Yuan Yi
and the greatest emperor of Suchuan.
Huotu Ke,
I have avenged for you.
You have made a long-term plan
just to
attract His Majesty here
and avenge for Yin Jia.
Why did you do it?
If I say
I was moved
by Yin Jia’s love story.
Will you believe it?
Do you know love, too?
Do I know?
Yes, I know.
But I have never seen it.
Why did you do it
on earth then?
Why?
Of course for a transaction
with Yin Jia.
Then,
what about the others?
Will Yin Jia kill them too?
Or
will you kill them?
It depends on their choice.
Do you know why I cured
your grandfather’s disease?
Because
I want you to have a weakness
in the world.
If you wish to get out of my control,
you need to refrain yourself
and don’t leave any new weakness.
Wu Yuan,
to people like us,
love
is just useless.
Your Majesty.
Congratulations!
You have taken revenge.
Please
honor your promise.
Is this the Spirit Stone?
Exactly.
This is the Spirit Stone that
has the power to kill the God,
and Emperor Yuan Tu
has tried his best to obtain even
at the cost of igniting the Earth Fire.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪