Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 16
Your Majesty.
Everyone’s here?
Father.
What’s going on?
Why are we
in the Fire Tribe?
Because
we’re fleeing.
Greetings to Your Highness.
Greetings to Chief Priest.
Weisheng Yan.
Good for your winning game.
I don’t understand
what you said.
Why would Wu Yuan help them leave?
Well.
I really don’t know.
I’m doing my best to support you.
My loyalty
is known by all.
Weisheng Yan.
Compared with your scheme,
your little humbleness
is ridiculous.
Looks like Marquis Pingjiang
only has
such ungrateful guys.
Listen, Zhu Xi.
All people in Suchuan
have known Goddess has come again.
His Majesty
is the chosen emperor.
The emperor who is blessed by Goddess
is not the one who
can be controlled by vassals anymore.
If you hurt Goddess again,
you are the enemy of Tianqi
and the world.
The enemy of the world?
After the birds were killed,
a fox is still left behind.
Such a trouble it is.
The situation is not stable yet.
You still need some friends.
You are right.
But this friend can only be used,
but not trusted.
If I guess it right,
all of you
will be sentenced to be
the wanted criminals who
created rebellion
and abducted His Majesty.
I will not
allow anyone to frame them up.
That’s my thought, too.
Don’t speak weirdly.
Just tell us.
I’m
not a smart guy.
But it’s better than him.
I don’t know
about the court or political tactics.
You smart ones
can analyze for me.
Zhu Xi and Chief Priest work together.
What’s their purpose?
To kill Fei Tian,
wipe out the forces around His Majesty,
and finally
control His Majesty
and the entire Suchuan.
Then why didn’t he
just kill His Majesty
and replace him?
Since ancient times, the Yuan family
has been the emperor
of the world.
God chose the emperor.
How can he be replaced?
You indeed belong
to the oldest noble family in Suchuan.
You think exactly the same
with Zhu Xi.
So,
Zhu Xi wanted to kill me
so as to get rid of the God
who chose the emperor.
But Chief Priest wanted to kill Fei Tian
to help me become Goddess.
Though they worked
together to kill Fei Tian,
their purposes
are totally different.
Smart girl.
But it’s a pity that
Suchuan can’t allow
such a smart Goddess to live.
But Weisheng Yan is different.
Weisheng Yan,
no matter what method you use,
the news that His Majesty is missing
can’t be leaked,
and His Majesty
can’t show up outside Zhaodu.
Bring His Majesty back
before the old fox does.
Aye.
I want to see the Goddess,
alive or dead.
But His Majesty
must be safe and sound.
Your loyalty
shall be learned by the world.
Weisheng Yan.
What’s this?
The throne.
Whose throne is it?
The emperor of Suchuan, of course.
Since it is a throne,
a man
must sit on it.
An alive one.
Though you put enough gold on it,
it can’t receive people’s reverence,
let alone to govern the country.
It’s indeed no use
of putting gold on the throne,
but when they are put
in people’s pockets,
they can drive them to do a lot.
As to that,
you and I
become friends because of gold,
don’t we?
Friends?
Weisheng Yan.
Remember.
Between the honorable and the humble,
there will be no friends.
There are
only usefulness
and uselessness.
It’s lucky that
you are a useful man.
Thanks, Your Highness.
The noble, God and throne.
They’re all Weisheng Yan’s enemies.
No matter which of them succeeds,
it’s the same for Weisheng Yan.
But he’s also a man
who won’t do anything unprofitable.
So
if he can work with Chief Priest
and Zhu Xi,
he must have a bigger plan.
If we can know
what Weisheng Yan’s plan is,
and make use of it,
maybe we still have a chance
to change the situation.
You are all smart.
It’s indeed not a good idea
to fight against you.
But
why are we in the Fire Tribe?
Because all secrets
are in the Fire Tribe,
related to you.
I don’t know what Weisheng Yan’s
purpose is,
and if His Majesty finding Linglong
has anything to do with him.
But I know
he has a thorough plan.
And Linglong
is an important part of the plan.
He’s the person who secretly drives
Linglong to go to Zhaodu to be the Goddess.
Since Linglong was born,
Weisheng Yan has been
paying attention to her.
Since I was born?
Yes.
Or even earlier.
To the time
when your mother came to the Fire Tribe.
My mother
was related
to all of this?
It’s possible that
your mother came to the Fire Tribe
to find the Palace of Flames.
If you say so,
everything can be explained,
no matter the monster girl
that Zhu Xi brought
or the thing that Tianqi followers
sent by Chief Priest to the Fire Tribe
died one by one.
All we have investigated in Zhaodu
directs to 17 years ago,
or actually
the Fire Tribe 17 years ago.
What’s in the Palace of Flames?
Why are you looking at me?
I’ve never been there, either.
Though it’s Weisheng Yan’s boat,
I feel
kind of reluctant to throw it.
The boat is too conspicuous.
Do you still hurt?
Much better.
Well.
Wu Yuan’s medicine
is quite good actually.
Sure.
The medicine
can grow flesh on the dead body.
Save it when you use.
It’s the only bottle.
I took it from Weisheng Yan’s.
I finally come back home!
So nice.
We’ve been out for long.
How come I never heard you said
you missed home?
It’s…
It’s because I’ve been with you
all the time.
Wherever you are is my home.
You clever girl.
It’s true.
Linglong,
I’m sorry.
I failed to give you
what I promised.
Not that.
You give a better me.
Let’s go home.
Go.
This way.
What’s in your bag?
Weisheng Yan’s gifts to me.
You’re not willing to
throw Weisheng Yan’s gifts?
They’re innocent.
Why throw them?
The boat,
the medicine,
and this.
How many stuffs have you taken
from Weisheng Yan?
Next time I’ll take his life.
Let’s go.
I’m starving.
She does recognize the way.
An old horse always knows the way.
Wait.
What’s the matter?
Someone’s there?
Why are you being so shocked?
Can you wait here?
We haven’t been home for long.
There must be a mess.
Let me clean it first.
Look what time it is.
There are so many of us.
We can’t be seen by the Leader.
Go, go, go.
No way.
Clean it up first.
Clean… Clean it up.
Wait a minute.
What are you doing?
Go.
I’m back.
I’m back, too.
It’s nice to be home.
It looks fine.
Not a mess.
I’ll go to call them in.
What?
Change your clothes first.
You’re right.
Change clothes.
Huotu Xin
is quite pitiful.
Why is that?
Could Jin’er marry him
for going to the Palace of Flames?
Could it be that
she had never loved him?
Yet Huotu Xin has kept the secret
alone for so many years
from Linglong.
If you think so,
don’t you feel he’s pitiful?
This is the responsibility
a man should take.
It’s not easy, is it?
I haven’t worn these clothes for long.
How’s it?
Do I look handsome with these?
Yes.
My father is the most handsome.
I’m not used to seeing you wearing
the clothes to clean the floor yet.
What?
You don’t want Yuan Yi
to see this?
After staying in the palace,
you hate our shabby home?
With guests coming,
I should clean it up.
Move away.
I’m cleaning the floor.
Have you
fallen in love with him?
I don’t know.
You… You don’t know?
How can you
not know it?
So…
So you like him?
Whatever you say.
You… You didn’t deny me!
Alright, Father.
Yuan Yi just lost Fei Tian
and Zhaodu.
Don’t talk nonsense before him.
Now
it’s not the time to talk about this.
Now it’s not the time?
So it means
there will be the time.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Where’s Wu Yuan?
She said she didn’t want to
go to your house.
You’ll see her in the Palace of Flames.
Well.
Didn’t she say she’s starving?
Why didn’t you watch her?
You seem to care about her a lot.
She’s been suspicious.
We should be
cautious, right?
Okay.
I’ll find her then.
Alright. It’s fine.
She’s not a noisy girl.
She’s not used to being treated well.
A hardy girl as she is.
Linglong has almost done
with the cleaning.
Let’s be ready.
And we can go to
the Palace of Flames soon.
Yuan Yi.
Follow me.
To where?
Let’s go to survey
in the Flame Chilling Wall.
Have you decided how to tell Linglong?
I will.
Why do you stop?
Come here.
I have something to tell you.
Do you see the necklace that
Linglong is wearing?
Yes.
Do you want me
to send some jewelries to Linglong
to please her first,
and then tell her the truth?
What are you thinking?
Is my daughter that kind of person?
So you are…?
Linglong’s power is controlled.
It’s related to the necklace.
It’s possible that
the necklace
has suppressed her power
inside the body,
controlled Goddess’ power,
and helped her retain her original look.
Where did you
get this necklace?
Linglong’s mother,
Jin’er, left it.
Who on earth is
Linglong’s mother?
17 years ago,
Jin’er came to the Fire Tribe
with the secret in her body.
It’s ridiculous that
though I stayed with her all day,
I never found
any difference inside her body.
And
once I also thought
she was a monster.
The Goddess you believed in
is indeed a monster
in Jin’er’s eyes.
She must have known some truth.
So she came to the Fire Tribe
to look for a way of removing the power.
So you’re taking them
to the Palace of Flames
not because of Weisheng Yan,
but for Linglong.
Both of that.
After all,
all these
seem to direct to Weisheng Yan.
I also want to help you.
Once you have no trouble,
Linglong has less to worry about.
But does Linglong
know it?
Linglong
never believed that
her mother is a monster.
So
she’s trying hard
to become the Goddess
to prove to everyone.
Sorry.
When Linglong was born,
Jin’er must have found
something weird in her.
So she broke into the Palace of Flames
at any risk.
If Jin’er told me
the truth at that time,
I can face it with her.
In that case,
at least Linglong
still has Mother now.
She must be afraid
that the truth will hurt you.
But we are family.
Families are supposed
to face difficulty
and help each other,
aren’t they?
But for 16 years,
you also haven’t told Linglong
the truth.
Jin’er and I both made mistakes.
I hope you
will not do that again.
I’ve told you
Linglong’s secret.
Are you
taking me as your family?
Honestly,
after going through all these,
I can also tell that
you
are a nice boy.
So I’ve made up my mind.
After all these are gone,
I will let Linglong
take you as her brother.
You can become sworn brother and sister.
Alright.
Go back.
Brother and sister?
Wait.
Aren’t we going to survey
in the entrance
of the Flame Chilling Wall?
There’s no need to survey.
I will take you in.
Your Majesty.
Why are you here?
Yin Zhuang was worried.
She asked me to have a check.
It’s my place.
What’s the worry for?
This is from Yin Zhuang.
Thanks then.
Thank Yin Zhuang, too.
How’s the entrance?
It… It’s good.
Is it right, brat?
Yes.
Go.
Huotu Xin.
We are men.
Whenever it is,
we should take the country
as a priority.
You stopped Gu Shi with your own power.
I respect that.
But now Zhaodu has been occupied,
and His Majesty is in exile.
In this moment,
you can’t give up your responsibility
for your own love.
Why are you
telling me this suddenly?
Nothing.
I just want to remind you.
Did you overhear my talk with Yuan Yi?
Overhear?
No.
What did you say about Yin Zhuang?
Yin Zhuang?
What’s wrong with Yin Zhuang?
Nothing.
Now many things are happening.
Don’t talk nonsense to His Majesty.
I didn’t talk nonsense.
Subordinates should share
His Majesty’s worry,
crack down the plots,
and help His Majesty take Zhaodu back.
I was just talking with him
about something between men.
It has nothing to do with state affairs.
I am talking with you
exactly about the things between men.
Yin Xiao.
You
are a good subordinate
and a good man.
All you said are right.
But I…
I don’t have so many wishes.
I only hope I can be like a common man
to manage my small home
and live my normal life
thoroughly and earnestly.
The others have nothing to do with me.
Common man?
You are
a quite common man.
I’ll take it as a praise.
That’s not what I mean.
I’m saying that
you’ve had a
cute daughter,
and a small home worth protecting.
Yeah.
But sometimes I will still think that
if it can be better.
Why are you still unsatisfied?
As to men,
though you have the world,
you also hope
when you come back,
someone is waiting for you.
When you open the door,
the dishes have been ready.
You’re back.
Come to have the meal then.
Why are you looking at me?
Sit… Sit down.
Why are you staring at me?
Sit down.
So many dishes.
You cooked them all?
Not at all.
Linglong said
she wanted Yuan Yi to taste
-the Fire Tribe’s dishes.
-Here.
Taste it.
It’s much better
than the dishes in Zhaodu.
When have you become so diligent?
Have your meal.
Taste it first.
Yin Zhuang made it.
The Bright Moon Island’s specialty.
Fried chili.
Taste it.
Is it from the Bright Moon Island?
I need to taste it then.
Is it good?
Yeah.
Is it hot?
No.
Taste it.
Let me have a try.
Brat, go taste it.
Is it hot?
I drink it first. I drink it first.
Give me, Father.
Water.
Come back.
Is it that hot?
Water. Where’s water?
Water. Water. Water.
It’s not hot at all.
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪
Why are there leftovers?
Yuan Yi, finish them.
I…
What’s the “ah” for?
How can an emperor waste food?
Father.
This is also made by Yin Zhuang.
Eat it.
And this one.
Taste it.
Is it good?
Yes.
Have you figured out
how to go to the Palace of Flames?
With my help,
you can just rest assured.
We…
Well…
Yuan Yi,
look at the flame.
You know what?
I’m kind of happy now.
Before,
here
hides the secret of my own.
But now,
the truth in the Palace of Flames
is connected with both of us.
It feels
like
the two destinies
are bound to be connected.
Linglong.
I have to tell you something.
I…
My father succeeded.
The guards were transferred away.
If you have anything,
tell me later.
Let’s go.
This is
indeed amazing.
Now the bracelet has nothing to do
with Weisheng Yan.
Do you still feel embarrassed
when using it?
I do.
It’s your dowry after all.
If some day you find
your beloved,
but I’m still wearing it,
your brother will cut my hand off.
Well.
If I have my beloved one,
you need to be careful then.
Go.
Father.
Good job!
Wu…
Where are the others?
I left her in your home.
I can’t trust her.
Just a few of us go in?
Didn’t you say it’s your place?
Brat,
when I fought
against the Earth Fire,
you were still a little kid.
Do you know what’s most important
to get inside the Wall?
The top priority
is to trust each other in the team.
Or we can’t do anything well.
Hope when we’re back
from the Palace of Flames,
I can be proven to be wrong.
No quarreling.
If someone finds us,
we can’t do anything then.
Don’t forget what’s
the most important task.
Alright, Father.
Let’s go in.
Be careful.
Xiao.
You shouldn’t have done that.
You come here in person.
I think
I should help you here.
If it’s not for the Fire Tribe
and the Flame Chilling Wall,
the Earth Fire
must plunge the people in Suchuan
into misery and suffering.
You are Suchuan’s heroes.
But how did
the Earth Fire be ignited?
Under the ground,
there’s a rich lode of Flammable Stones.
The Flammable Stones keep burning.
So the Earth Fire can’t be put out.
Why did the lode
of Flammable Stones be ignited?
It can’t ignite itself, can it?
No one knows.
Go.
Don’t tell him now.
Why?
To protect my father.
If he knows
the Earth Fire was set on
by our ancestors,
he may get crazy.
It’s too cruel
for him.
But you have made it through.
That’s because
you were with me.
But you dared to plan
on hiding from me.
I haven’t forgiven you for that yet.
Yuan Yi.
In the world,
except for my father,
I trust you the most.
So no matter what
happens in the future,
you can’t hide from me anymore.
So do I.
We can face everything together.
You two,
why are you so sluggish?
Quick.
Linglong.
It’s the place.
Be careful.
Mother!
I promised you
I would come to see you.
Here I am.
Linglong,
when did you get the Dormant Lotus?
When you were sleeping.
Whatever you want to tell your mother,
you can tell her now.
Do you want me to step away?
No.
I have something to ask you.
Do you know
Yin Zhuang likes you?
I know.
But I can’t believe that.
Do you like her?
I…
In front of my mother,
you mustn’t lie.
I dare not like her.
You’re lucky to have me
to be your daughter.
I’ll take care of it.
What are you taking care of?
♪The scenery is flowing silently♪
But you need to promise me,
well,
if you give birth to a boy
in the future,
you can’t be partial.
Sure. I won’t.
You promise.
♪Flying flowers♪
Promise.
♪Fly like yellow sand♪
♪Idle the days away♪
♪Forget melancholy♪
I promise.
♪Loyal heart♪
♪Has been exiled♪
Mother,
see?
We
♪Crystal heart lay in pieces
at the ends of the earth♪
are doing fine.
♪Love sinks in day and night♪
♪Fate brings us together♪
You silly girl.
♪For whom I stayed for a moment♪
Alright.
Let’s go.
To the Palace of Flames.
What’s wrong with your face?
Maybe it’s burned by the Earth Fire.
You Fire Tribe’s men
can endure the heat the most, can’t you?
Maybe I haven’t been here for long.
Alright.
Just take us to the Palace of Flames.
Where is
the entrance?
Didn’t I tell you?
I’ve never been there.
So I don’t know
where is the entrance.
What did you say?
The gate of the Palace of Flames
was destroyed by the Earth Fire
several hundred years ago.
If we go there,
we may need to climb the mountain.
I know a secret pass.
There’s really a road here.
Stay close.
I only brought one Fire Spear.
Your clothes.
It’s so beautiful.
It’s glowing silk.
I was so afraid of darkness
when I was little,
my father used Yetan’s silk
to make the clothes
for us,
so as to help me resist
my fears of darkness.
Yetan?
Where is it?
In the most northern place.
It’s far beyond Suchuan.
I haven’t heard it for long that
someone is coming from the place.
Follow up!
You two.
You two can glow!
Since they two can glow,
you two stay close to us.
Exactly.
It’s the way.
It’s exactly the same
with Huotu Ke’s description.
Let’s go, Father.
When we are in the Palace of Flames,
you can be so helpful.
Let’s go.
So amazing.
Do you wear the clothes
all the time as you grow up?
Every time when we got taller,
Juan would
pull the glowing silk out carefully
and put it on our new clothes.
Xiao.
What’s this?
Huotu Xin.
Yeah. What’s this?
This is…
It
looks like the Flammable Stone.
But…
It’s the Flammable Crystal.
What?
It’s the most valuable treasure
of the Fire Tribe,
and the source of energy.
In ancient times,
the ancestors of the Fire Tribe
used the Flammable Crystals
to get the unparalleled power
of quenching stones
in entire Suchuan,
and built the brilliant
Jinshi City.
It’s the treasure in the Fire Tribe.
You don’t know it?
He is not to blame.
Even if in the Fire Tribe,
only the noble were allowed to get in
to the Palace of Flames.
Even in ancient times,
common people were not allowed in.
What… What common people?
Our family name is Huotu.
Our ancestor
is Huotu Ke, the great Founding Father
of the Fire Tribe.
Yeah.
So now you are in the Palace of Flames.
It’s also the origin
of the Earth Fire, isn’t it?
Only if the Flammable Crystal
is burning,
the Earth Fire
can never be put out.
Be careful.
We are at the top now.
The Palace of Flames should be up above.
We’re really in.
Like I said,
the map of Suchuan
is all in Yuan Yi’s head.
Even so, I won’t accept him.
I… It’s weird.
How come there is such a road?
Huotu Ke built it
to escape from the Palace of Flames.
Maybe
since he quenched
the Spirit Stone,
he’s foreseen the Earth Fire disaster.
What do you mean?
Just gossips.
We can talk about it later.
Going to the Palace of Flames
is more important.
What’s the next step?
Your Majesty.
It’s a fork here,
like a maze.
It confuses us.
From here,
I don’t know the next move, either.
Just take the time
to find the way slowly.
We can surely find it.
Father is right.
How about we separate to find it?
It’s faster.
In case
we can find each other,
Yuan Yi and I
will be waiting here for you.
Yin Zhuang,
you and my father have bracelets.
You can take care of each other.
You two are a team.
Go to that way.
Yin Xiao.
You go that way alone.
Don’t run about then.
What’re you looking at?
Let’s go.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪