♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 19=
Yuchi!
Why can’t I see Dragon King’s
face clearly in my every dream?
Or, does it want to tell me
that Yuchi won’t come to me
but I have to go to find him?
General!
Come in.
General, bad news!
Dongluo is going to sneak up on us!
What?
Our scout reported that
in order not to leak their trace,
they destroyed five villages
and left no one alive,
even newborn babies.
Zhong Sheng was patrolling the border.
Unfortunately, they killed him.
Who is their leader?
You were right.
Our scout said it’s
Dongluo’s Crown Prince.
Han Xiyun!
Gather up for battle!
Yes, General!
Dongluo has come again and again
to invade our homeland
and hurt our people!
Today, let those beasts from Dongluo
regret stepping into our land!
Soldiers!
Live for war! Die for war!
Together! We’ll kill all the invaders!
Drive these jerks back to Dongluo!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
General!
Mr. Lu, what’s wrong?
Night attack is dangerous.
You shouldn’t go.
I can’t escape just because I’m afraid.
That’s not what a general should do.
Just because you’re the general,
you should know that
an army can’t be without a general.
If something bad happens to you,
who will be in command of our army?
You make sense.
General, so you’ve decided not to join
the night attack?
You won’t join.
Me?
But, General…
Uncle Zhao,
I’ll leave the camp to you.
Soldiers! Let’s go!
Yes, General!
Report!
Your Highness,
we encountered a surprise attack
in the rear by the Feng Army.
They are quick on their feet.
How is the situation?
Not too many injuries and deaths.
But most of our catapults
were burnt.
I’m afraid our plan…
Such a clean action.
It must be Feng Chenyue.
She just rushed right into the trap.
Give my order.
Kill all the sneak attackers.
No one should be left alive.
Tonight,
I want her head to be my bowl for wine.
Yes, Your Highness.
Han Xiyun!
Bow and arrow!
General Feng,
it’s been a while.
You’ve got good Kung Fu!
Which squad do you belong to?
What’s your name?
Fight!
What are you waiting for? Chase them!
Yes, Your Highness!
Kill them with the crossbow!
-Yes!
Carry your shields on your backs!
Hurry up!
Get up!
I ask you to send troops to the rescue!
No!
-General gave the order…
-You!
Mr. Lu, please let me explain.
I know you’re worried about General.
So am I.
But General gave the order
before she left for the night attack
that we can’t dispatch troops
until we receive their distress signal.
It can’t be disobeyed!
Alright,
seems that you’re pretty loyal
to General Feng.
Mr. Lu, we are Feng Army.
I have only one big brother in my life.
Without him, I wouldn’t have been here.
You’ve never seen
how General usually is.
So combative and majestic-looking.
Just like my big brother.
Of course I’m loyal to her.
I’ll take that as a compliment.
-General!
-You’re back!
Are you all right?
Can’t be better.
How was it?
We are slightly damaged.
But overall the attack was a success.
Dongluo Army turned and retreated.
Then we still need to take precautions.
They will turn on us at any moment.
We need to be on guard.
No, I propose to strike at dawn.
We should counter attack
and burn all their food and horses,
so that they can’t invade
again for now.
I agree.
Zheng, you have the same idea with me.
It seems that we are
on the same wavelength.
Then, now we…
To counter attack,
I want to go with you.
Uncle Zhao and I
each lead a group of troops.
You need to take care of the camp.
Alright. Chenyue…
No. General.
Uncle Zhao, let’s go out
and discuss the formation.
OK.
By the way,
there is a soldier with great Kung Fu.
He must be better than me.
Do you know who he is?
A soldier
has better Kung Fu than you?
No way. I won’t believe it.
You know what?
It was so amazing.
Dongluo’s catapults
were so close to me.
But not even a single arrow hit me.
Given their poor skill,
they should practice more.
General, you’re the strongest.
Let me take the water out for you.
How could you be that lucky?
It must be Dragon King’s help.
By rights,
I should have been shot by one
or two arrows at least.
Were you secretly helping me?
Are you
hiding around me?
Why does the feeling
of flying feel so familiar?
Hey, you!
Are you goofing off here?
Hurry to prepare the food cart! Move!
Be quick!
You will all get punished if there is
any delay in preparing
rations and forage!
Miss Qingqing.
You’re the Dragon King!
But now you’re a soldier serving here.
It will definitely scare him
if you tell him who you are.
They won’t know who I am,
especially Chenyue.
I hope that
we will only be strangers in this life.
Why?
I helped her to become Concubine Yu
through the rain in her last life.
Although she got a wealthy life,
her life ended miserably
because of missing me.
I don’t want such a thing
to happen again.
So, this time,
I just want to be a soldier
and protect her secretly by her side.
But, what if she falls in love
with someone else?
It’s fine as long as she is happy.
If I were her,
I’d choose a tall,
handsome and rich guy
who has no parents, brothers or sisters.
He is cold to everyone else
but only sweet and nice to me.
Are you talking about Xue Qianxun?
No way!
How could it be him?
Cold to everyone else
but only sweet and nice to me.
How could it be Xue Qianxun?
Right?
Not him.
It’s me.
Did you interfere in
human affairs with your power again?
Will you be punished
by the thunder again?
Thunder?
It’s just like scratching an itch.
Where are you going?
Take this elixir first.
You are the proudest Dragon King.
But you’re willing to be punished for
protecting that girl.
Look at how painful you are.
Why bother?
I don’t feel painful.
On the battle field,
death is a common practice.
Even if she dies in battle,
she will go to her next life.
Why bother to help her
again and again?
Isn’t it better to be together
with her earlier?
Do you know what love is?
Love?
I used to think that
love was as romantic as it was
in those stories.
But after I experienced it, I found that
it’s more than that.
Then, explain it to me.
Love is not icing on the cake,
but sharing weal and woe.
It’s not selfish possession,
but long-term protection.
Liuying and Ayu
never had any aspiration,
but Chenyue has.
So, I must help her
to realize her aspiration
and let her live happily
in this life.
I can’t win in arguing with you.
Anyway, take care of yourself.
The elixir just now can let you recover.
But if you use your power
within the next 49 days,
you’ll get hurt.
And,
when you’re lack of energy,
you can’t use your power.
Why didn’t you tell me?
If you hadn’t had it,
how could you still stand here?
Can you be grateful?
Will Chenyue be in danger?
Rest assured.
She has the Soul of General
to protect her.
Alright.
That’s good.
I’m so kind to you.
Shouldn’t you say something to me?
I keep what I owe you in mind.
I’ll pay you back in the future.
Your Highness, the enemy raided us
and burnt our barns and stables.
Let me use your knife.
Your Highness.
What are you doing here
instead of rescuing the provisions?
Feng Chenyue is coming with her troops.
I’m here to protect Your Highness.
I don’t need your protection!
Now get out to do what you should do!
Yes.
I’m waiting here for Feng Chenyue
to bring me her head.
I’m leaving.
I don’t know why,
but I just feel she is coming.
Look! We were just talking about you!
Give me
your head.
Kill!
Don’t move!
Order them to put down their weapons.
Weapons down.
Weapons down!
You will have to pay for your cruelty!
General Feng, you know I’m the
Crown Prince of Dongluo.
I’ve heard
that you don’t like slaughter.
I always hate wars.
But I have no other choices to do this.
It’s of no use if you capture me.
There is never an end of taking revenge.
In the end,
it’ll be the brotherly people
of the countries who suffer.
If I can go back,
I’ll try my best to persuade my father
to withdraw,
so that we can build our friendship.
You think I can let you go
only for your words?
I’m not that easy to cheat.
I didn’t mean that.
A promise is a promise.
I promise that from now on,
our two countries
will remain brotherhood
and peace for a hundred years.
Brotherhood and peace
for a hundred years!
Brotherhood…
In this case,
don’t rush to go now.
Come with me to our camp
to discuss the details of the
peace negotiations.
General Feng, please lead the way.
My eye!
Kill her!
Kill them!
Bros! Withdraw!
Catapults!
Again!
But if you use your power
within the next 49 days,
you’ll get hurt.
Kill!
Protect General to withdraw!
General! Go!
Let’s go!
The soldier I mentioned is him.
He blocked the arrow for me.
In last battle,
it was also him who covered us
to make us able to retreat.
I have an impression of him.
But I’ve never heard that
he has great Kung Fu.
A master always hides in the crowd.
The one who keeps low-profile
is the real master.
Bro,
thank you.
Chenyue!
Mr. Lu.
I heard you got hurt?
Where? Let me have a check.
Zheng, I didn’t get hurt.
It’s him.
He blocked an arrow for me.
Thanks for his sacrifice.
He deserves award for his
service to General.
Mr. Lu, don’t worry about this.
Our general will never treat
a meritorious soldier ungenerously.
Now he is already the Brave Sergeant.
General Zhao,
I asked them
to make some nourishing soup.
Go and have some, please.
Since you said that,
I do feel a little hungry.
Come on, let’s go together.
Mr. Lu, please.
Alright, let’s go have some together.
Come on.
“Zheng?”
That sounds pretty close.
When will my eye be cured?
Well…
I’m waiting for your answer!
I’m afraid your eye…
can’t be cured.
Really?
That means
your medical skills are not good enough.
That means…
You’re a quack!
Your Highness.
The Imperial Advisor is here.
You can leave now.
Yes, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Mr. Advisor, why do you suddenly
come to the army?
Your Highness,
I heard your eye got hurt.
You’d better go back for treatment.
Thanks for your concern.
But I can’t go back
before I win.
What if His Majesty wants you to?
Does my father know
that my eye got hurt?
His Majesty knows it.
I haven’t avenged yet,
but he asks me to retreat now?
Even if Your Highness’s not in the army,
we are still here.
We’ll fight till the end!
His Majesty ordered that
anyone who dares to start a battle
without his order
will be executed right away.
If I guessed it right,
father wants me to
submit to humiliation.
I understand that you feel unfair.
But you are the fiercest warrior
of Dongluo.
You got an eye hurt,
but the army suffered
heavier casualties.
The morale of the army is affected.
And most of the food were burnt.
We have lost the certainty of victory.
His Majesty asked me to remind you
to take the people of Dongluo
into consideration.
Looks like father has made up his mind.
Then, that’s it.
Mr. Lu.
Well…
Thank you.
General, have some as well.
You’re not thinking of pursuing
the retreating enemy, are you?
Yes, I am.
Report!
General Feng. General Zhao.
Mr. Lu.
There is a letter asking for meeting.
Let me read it.
What’s the letter about?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪