♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 20=
Mr. Lu. Well…
Thank you.
General, have some as well.
You’re not thinking of pursuing
the retreating enemy, are you?
Yes, I am.
Report!
General Feng. General Zhao.
Mr. Lu.
There is a letter asking for meeting.
Let me read it.
What’s the letter about?
The Imperial Advisor of Dongluo
asked for a meeting to make peace.
Well…
The war will be over?
The King of Dongluo
must be upset that his son got hurt.
Let him in.
-Hurry up.
-Yes.
Father.
Today, I’ve finally
beaten back the invader Dongluo
and accomplished your
long-cherished wish.
You can
rest in peace now.
(Deceased Father Feng Se’s Tablet)
Soldiers.
There can’t be peaceful borders
without your sacrifices.
I want to
thank you on behalf of our fellows.
The war
is finally over.
She got one of my eyes blind.
But I’m ordered to make peace.
Father
is just trampling
on my dignity.
Am I so worthless
in his mind?
Your Highness,
I know you’re angry.
But His Majesty did this
for the whole situation.
We can wait for a few more years
until you ascend the throne, then…
Ascend the throne?
How long do you think that old jerk
can keep me as the Crown Prince?
I don’t have much time.
My fate is in my hand,
not the heaven’s.
Jin.
Yes, Your Highness.
I must
take this revenge.
I’ll go kill her right now.
No.
Touch it.
I want her to feel my pain.
I want her to wish she were dead.
I’m leaving, Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Refill it.
Young man,
what medicine did you use?
I’ve been a physician for years
but never seen a wound
heal so quickly like this.
It’s just a small wound.
Then, have enough rest.
Long Yan.
Do you feel better now?
Mr. Lu.
Don’t bother to do this.
I came a long way from Wind City
with limited supplies.
This box of ginseng is a gift for you.
Thank you for saving General Feng.
It’s my duty to protect General.
Long Yan,
I’m not being grateful
as the Military Supervisor,
but as a man.
Thank you for saving the most important
person in my life.
The most important person?
I like her.
Not only like that.
I will marry her one day.
We have been childhood sweethearts.
I have been loving her since
the first moment I saw her.
And I have never forgotten her
for so many years.
When I learned that she and her father
were guarding the border here,
I volunteered to serve
as the Military Supervisor here
after I became the Top Scholar,
to get close to her.
You gave up a better career
for General Feng.
I admire it.
Thank you, Long Yan.
Then, please accept
this box of ginseng.
Thanks for your efforts!
Let me propose a toast!
General Feng! General Feng!
General Feng!
Cheers!
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
Enjoy your food!
General!
-Guys!
-General. General.
Thank you! Cheers!
-It’s what we should do.
-Thank you, General.
General is such a good drinker!
Have some more food!
-Sure.
-Thank you, General!
Come on, eat.
-Thank you!
-General! General!
-Please don’t say that!
-Come on! Cheers!
Cheers!
Thank you, General!
-Come on!
-Come on! Cheers!
-Don’t drink too much! Let me.
-General!
-Come on! Cheers!
-Thank you, General!
General, cheers!
Have some more food!
Chenyue!
Look at Lu Zheng!
Doesn’t he know how to treat a girl
politely?
Chenyue!
General Feng is really…
-Did you see his hands?
-An excellent woman and a good drinker.
Look at him!
But, as the Military Supervisor,
I’ll drink for her from now on.
Come on! Cheers!
Cheers! Cheers!
Together! Cheers!
Chenyue.
General Zhao,
does Mr. Lu
like our general?
Everyone can tell it.
Don’t say it out.
But,
Mr. Lu is well-educated while
General’s trained in military exercises.
I don’t think they are
right for each other.
You know what?
Our general is the chosen one
and one in a million.
And, Mr. Lu has
a good family background
and good character.
He looks weak, but he is still manly.
That’s enough. That’s a perfect match.
Then, are we going to have their
wedding feast soon?
Don’t talk nonsense!
General may hear you.
I’m just worried for Mr. Lu.
General is hard to handle.
-Enough. Drink.
-Come on.
Come on, guys!
Drink some more! Cheers!
-Cheers!
General is such a good drinker!
-Yes!
-She drinks like a fish!
Chenyue.
Mr. Lu.
Zheng, you can also tame a horse?
I trained this wild horse
to give it to you.
It must have cost you
a lot of time to tame it.
You’re really going to give it to me?
We are so close now.
Just take it.
My horse is great.
Why should I change it?
But, General,
this is a fine horse.
Look at it.
Its hair is black and bright.
And,
its hip. Look!
And its legs.
It’s definitely a fine horse!
Uncle Zhao, you like it?
I…
Since Uncle Zhao likes it,
you can give it to him.
Well… It’s…
It’s not appropriate.
General, it’s for you.
How could I take it?
Uncle Zhao, your horse
was given by my father.
It’s old now. You should change it.
Zheng, what do you think?
Alright. Alright.
Mr. Lu, thank you.
I’ll take it.
Chenyue.
Open it.
Nice bow.
The dragon’s head…
should be like this.
Chenyue.
Zheng, what’s the matter?
General!
Time for a facial!
Come here.
Zheng, let’s talk later.
I can’t stand Qingqing. See you!
Why are you running again?
Come back!
So, she likes dragons?
(Deceptions in War)
(An Evilly Charming Emperor’s Requite)
Nice shot! Long Yan.
Mr. Lu.
Don’t bother.
Long Yan, I have no friends
in the army.
But you and I feel like old friends.
Mr. Lu, I feel flattered.
You risked your life to save Chenyue.
I will never forget
your kindness.
It’s my duty to serve General.
I also want to do many things for her.
I gave her fine horse, nice bow,
clothes and hats.
But she doesn’t like
or use any of them.
But lately,
I just found that she likes dragons.
Dragons?
Yes.
You know,
dragons are not like lions or tigers.
If she likes those,
I can catch one for her.
Now I know that she likes dragons,
but I can’t bring her one.
Yes.
After all, dragons only fly in the sky.
I got an idea!
Great. Great.
Congratulations, Your Majesty!
We have won the war.
Then, Dongluo
will send their most beautiful
Princess Rui
to make peace by marriage.
Congratulations, Your Majesty!
Chenyue!
Look what I bring you for fun.
Dragon kite!
You must want to see
the dragon fly in the sky.
How do you know that?
There are some things
you don’t need to say.
We have connection in minds.
Right?
Connection in minds?
I’m a boy and I’m older than you.
You should call me Zheng.
I’m Qingqing’s brother.
I’m Long Yuchi.
I can always find you
no matter where you are.
Is Zheng implying to me
that he is Dragon King?
But, why I feel…
Chenyue?
Come on, let’s go fly the kite.
Sure.
Take it.
Let’s go.
It’s flying!
Press down the string.
Here. Have a try.
No. Not like this.
Downward. Down.
Downward.
Yes. Right. Down.
That’s right.
Great.
Yes, it’s like this.
Yes. And pull it.
Look.
It’s flying higher!
Yes.
Young Master!
Chenyue, I have something to deal with.
I need to go now.
-I’ll be back later.
-Go now.
Look at you. Dragon?
It’s a dragon!
You! Come here!
Yes, General.
Take it.
Is it really you?
Why did the dragon appear
as soon as Zheng left?
Is that a hint to me?
But, why don’t you tell me?
Are you being shy?
Dragon King! Please show up!
I won’t laugh at you!
He said he would never be jealous.
But, look at him now!
He can’t be with Chenyue.
So, he can only watch her happy
with another man.
Look at him!
He is jealous of the fake dragon!
Look how he is flying!
Dragon King is just a Jealous King.
Jealous King! King of Jealousy!
Why is the laughter
in my head so familiar
but strange?
Who is that person?
So funny!
Zheng!
I’m here.
Yuchi.
What did you say?
Don’t be shy, Dragon King.
I know you are him!
What? Dragon King?
Do you have anything to do with
the rebel, Duke Long?
It’s a misunderstanding.
Don’t talk about it again.
It will be bad
if this goes to Wind City.
No more “King”,
no matter what it is.
-But Dragon…
-Don’t say it again.
Alright.
I’m sure that
Dragon King is by my side.
Who is he?
If he is not Zheng,
why did he give me the dragon kite?
Why did a dragon appear in the sky?
The Feng Army is heavily guarded and
it’s difficult to penetrate.
It’s not so easy to deal with
Feng Chenyue.
We have to bribe the officials
in Wind City
to let Feng Chenyue go back there
before we can do it.
Father has sent Rui for the marriage.
I got it.
I will accompany Princess
to Wind City.
Rui has always been timid.
I’ll ask her to listen to you this time.
I’ll let Feng Chenyue go back to
Wind City
and kill her then.
Wind City is so beautiful!
After we are settled,
I must come here and find
if there is any food from our hometown.
His Majesty specially prepared
this cozy Xilai Pavilion
for Your Highness.
We can tell how much His Majesty
loves Your Highness.
Your Highness.
Eunuch Li,
a little gift for you. Please accept it.
Your Highness,
just come to me anytime you like
if you need any help.
I’m leaving now.
You may leave as well.
They finally left.
Did I do anything wrong just now?
Your Highness have done a good job.
Then, what should I do next?
According to the royal palace etiquette,
Your Highness should have more contact
with the Queen Consort.
Then, will Feng Chenyue
come to Wind City?
She will come
if we want her to.
if we want her to?
Your Highness, please take an
early sleep after such a long journey.
What’s this?
It’s called labyrinth casket.
Labyrinth casket?
It looks interesting.
(Yue)
Order General Feng to come back
for reward?
Young as she is,
it’s not easy for her to be able to
beat back Dongluo.
Your Majesty,
it was not easy.
I also admire it.
But she may grow frivolous
for enjoying success when young.
Now she is the only one on the border
who dares to ignore the imperial court.
I believe General Feng is not that
kind of person.
Your Majesty, a field commander
always decides
even against the King’s orders.
In my opinion,
we can take this opportunity
to see whether the Feng Army
has become arrogant
or they are still loyal.
(Imperial Edict)
General Feng Chenyue defeated Dongluo.
His Majesty shows concern
and orders General Feng to go back
to Wind City within ten days
for reward. That’s all.
Thank His Majesty. I receive the order.
Congratulations, General Feng.
But, ten days is short.
Please set off as soon as possible.
If there is any delay,
that’s against the imperial edict.
I see.
You have come a long way here.
Uncle Zhao.
Yes.
Take Eunuch for rest and food.
Please.
-General.
-Qingqing!
We can finally go back to Wind City!
What’s so good about Wind City?
I think it’s more free
and beautiful here.
Wind City is better of course.
Chenyue, you’ll be rewarded.
But you’re ordered to go back
within ten days.
The trip will be a torture.
There must be something fishy.
Don’t worry.
No matter how things change,
just roll with the punches.
(Xu’s Mansion)
I heard that His Majesty is calling
the female general, Feng Chenyue,
back to Wind City?
Feng Chenyue is like a queen
on the frontier.
All the soldiers there are
at her command.
She is really that capable?
The Former General Feng got his
daughter at an old age.
Of course the Feng Army
will all listen to her.
As a female official in Wind City,
she must obey the rules here.
I’ll find a chance
to teach her a lesson.
General.
You’re practicing
Xuantian Swordsmanship.
It’s famous for its speed.
I don’t know more than three people
in the world who can use it.
And it’s more difficult to master it.
I admire it.
I’m flattered.
Come on, let’s have a match.
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
General, I lost.
You didn’t do it seriously.
I’m going back to Wind City.
How about you be my Chief Guard?
Thank you, General.
But, I think you don’t need
a soldier like me in Wind City.
You don’t have to answer me now.
We’ll set off tomorrow
and you can decide it then.
Chenyue.
I knew you were here.
Zheng.
Mr. Lu.
I have something to tell General.
Excuse me.
I didn’t finish my word just now.
Actually,
I got a secret letter from my father,
saying that some ministers
are discontented with your achievement.
He asked me to…
Keep your nose clean
and stay away from me?
Of course I’m not afraid of the gossip.
But, Chenyue,
you have to be careful in Wind City.
As the Military Supervisor,
I’m afraid I can’t go back with you.
Returning to Wind City is more
dangerous than a war?
Without people around to help,
you have to be more cautious.
I got it.
Thank you, Zheng.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪