THE RULES OF PANTANA WITTAYA SCHOOL
[Nanno] It is said
-that there's a rule for everything.
-GENERAL REGULATIONS
And every rule is there for a reason.
A CHAPTER ON DISCIPLINE
But the rule makers always bend the rules.
HEADMASTER,
HEAD OF STUDENT WELFARE,
HOMEROOM AND CLASS TEACHERS,
DEPARTMENT STAFF
So the rules become oppressive
to all of us.
CHAPTER THREE
AUTHORITY OVER PUNISHMENT
And they keep us all tied down.
[shouting]
DETENTION, CONFINEMENT, IMPRISONMENT
It's time for that to change.
[tense music]
[music continues]
[theme music]
Hello. My name is Nanno.
It's nice to meet you.
[Teacher B] Go sit over there, Nanno.
Hi, I'm Nanno. What's your name?
[Teacher B clears throat]
Pay attention, Nanno.
You're already behind
the rest of the class.
[Teacher B]
Okay, turn to chapter four, page 128.
Hi, Nanno. My name is Mie.
[chuckles]
[tense music]
[Mie gasps]
What's going on?
Nothing, ma'am. I dropped my pen.
You need to be careful, Mie. You don't
want to be distracting your classmates.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Here, Nanno.
[door opens]
[suspenseful music]
We are here to do a random bag search.
[students] Yes, ma'am.
[grunting]
This outdated protocol of yours
is a violation of our student's privacy.
This is the best method.
And you don't have
any choice in the matter, understood?
According to the school rules
every single student must always do
as their teacher say.
[Teacher A] I'll be the one to decide
if it is unfair.
[grunts]
Now, have I made myself clear to you?
Yeah.
[eerie music]
Thank you, Teacher B.
You're most welcome.
[piano orchestral music]
[Teacher B]
The French Revolution took place
in the 1700s.
-The era was considered…
-Nanno.
…a time of change. The financial crisis
-left the royal treasury empty.
-Nanno!
[smacks lips]
Hello, my dear students,
our highly prestigious
Pantana Wittaya School
has managed to become
a pillar of society,
due to our ethics,
morals and guidance, so please
if you stay disciplined,
you will absolutely achieve everything
you have ever hoped for.
Why do teachers think
they can do whatever they want.
Hm… the teachers here are worse
than you can imagine.
Seriously, Nanno,
you should really be careful.
The teachers at this school despise
people like you.
People like me?
[Mie] Yeah. You're the type who asks
a lot of questions. They really hate that.
[snickers, laughs]
It's not funny, Nanno.
You saw that there are two
empty desks in class?
Wanna know why?
Are they sick?
[Mie] They belong to New and Jelly.
The other day, Jelly called out
Teacher B for something.
And Teacher B got so upset,
she threw an eraser at her head.
-[thud]
-[Jelly screams]
Sorry, it must've slipped.
Don't just sit there.
Someone take her to the nurse's office.
[Mie] New took a video of what happened
with his phone.
But, Teacher B caught him.
Do you know what happened to them?
The student welfare officer
locked both of them up
in the Repentance Room.
And they haven't come out
of that room since.
No one's heard from them.
Hmm.
Sounds kind of fun.
Let's go find it. Wanna come with me?
[Mie] Your crazy, Nanno.
That room is so scary.
Rebellious students come out of there
completely tamed.
No one wants to get put in that room.
[eerie music]
There she is.
[chuckles]
Are you Nanno?
Yeah.
[tense music]
[breathes deeply]
Are you aware that we have
very strict rules here?
[Nanno] I'm aware.
That's good to hear.
Since you're new here,
I'll let you off easy once.
You must memorize all 427 rules by heart.
[groans]
Thank you, ma'am.
You'll do it elsewhere.
THE RULES OF PANTANA WITTAYA SCHOOL
[suspenseful orchestral music]
[murmurs]
[murmuring continues]
-She's taunting them.
-Look at her.
-[student 1] Is she crazy?
-[student 2] She's insane.
[Nanno murmuring continues]
[laughs]
[music continues]
The rules of Pantana Wittaya School…
[laughs]
…established 1982.
[snorts, laughs hysterically]
Do you think this is against the rules?
There's no rule written in the book
against laughing at the rules.
[laughing]
She's laughing.
[Nanno] Rule number two.
[snorts, laughs]
-[Nanno] Rule number three…
-We should call Teacher A.
[Nanno laughing hysterically]
[music stops]
[clicks]
[murmuring]
She's totally crazy.
[breathes heavily]
[indistinct chattering]
-She's burning the book.
-No.
Damn.
I read through the Book of Rules.
In all 427, none of them say
that I can't set fire
to the book of rules.
[breathes heavilly]
Take her to the Repentance Room.
[both] Yes.
[Nanno] Oh, my.
[grunts]
[Nanno] This is so ominous.
Are you going to have me murdered?
[grunts]
[Teacher A] Mm.
-[clicks]
-[intercom beeps]
Hello, my lovely students.
Behaving?
Hello?
[breathing heavily over intercom]
[Jelly] Teacher, please get me out
of here. I promise I learned my lesson.
Please, teacher. Please, let me go.
We welcome those who do repent.
Since you've made amends,
we now consider you a valuable asset
to our school.
So, you are free to rejoin
all your classes.
Thank you for this chance, Teacher A.
[Teacher A] And you, New?
Have you learned anything?
I'm fine here.
[New] I didn't do anything wrong.
But you filmed the teacher,
which is not good, New.
It's Teacher B who didn't admit
her mistake.
And she hurt Jelly.
New, can you please just tell her
what she wants to hear?
-But this is not right.
-[gasps]
This has to stop.
We can't keep living like this.
If that's what you think,
then stay in there.
Then, I'm quitting the school.
[Teacher A] You'll quit?
Do you really think quitting
will solve everything?
You know, there is an easy way to deal
with a student like you.
[Teacher A] We'll put your name on a list
of undesirable people.
That will ruin any chance you had
of getting
into any university whatsoever.
But, you have no right to do that.
[Teacher A] I do.
And I have done it before.
[Teacher A] The world runs on nepotism.
What about you?
Are you prepared to face
the consequences of your choices?
[grunts]
Just apologize to her…
so we can get out of here.
[Teacher A] Tell me one more time.
Do you still want to quit this school?
No, I'm sorry.
Say that again.
[New] I'm sorry. I was wrong.
You were right.
I swear I won't hurt
the school's reputation ever again.
[clicks]
[creaks]
Thank you.
When New first arrived here,
he looked like you do right now.
[Teacher A] You may use this time
to repent for your choices.
You must memorize
all the school rules by heart.
[female voice over PA] The rules
for students of Pantana Wittaya School…
-[snorts]
-…AD 1982.
[yawns]
Rule number one,
all students shall respect
and strictly follow
the school rules.
Rule number two,
all students shall respect
and treat their teachers
like their own family members
and always be grateful
for their teachers' kindness.
[both] Teacher, there's a problem.
Nanno, didn't you get in trouble
for yesterday?
They just made me listen to all 427 rules
over and over again in a dark room.
Were you scared at all?
Yah, Jelly's like a different person now.
It's true.
New's still too sick to come back.
I didn't let her out of the room.
Why is she here now?
To be completely honest,
I find this whole thing…
pretty…
boring and stupid.
[sighs]
Are you a smoker, Teacher B?
It really wasn't scary at all.
If all of us break the rules,
we can have a pretty big party
in there together.
[Teacher A clears throat]
Okay.
Stand up.
[sighs]
Looks like I'll be partying
all by myself again.
I've memorized all 427 rules.
Rule one,
all students should strictly follow
the school rules as written.
Rule two,
students should respect
their teachers like they were family.
[Nanno] Rule three…
I'm going to ask you once,
who the hell are you?
My name is Nanno. I'm the new girl.
Have you forgotten?
[exhales]
I'd also like to know
how long you'll be able to endure this.
Welcome to the Repentance Room, Nanno.
[eerie music]
The atmosphere is so pleasant in here.
[music intensifies]
["Symphony No. 5" by Beethoven plays]
[laughing]
[all cheering]
[music continues]
[music stops]
[Teacher A] Who are you?
I'm Nanno.
You keep asking me the same thing.
Well, what do you want from us?
Hm… that's different.
Let's see, I want…
I want you to tell your students
that you were wrong,
admit that you were the one who planted
the cigarettes.
Admit the school is backwards,
and then, I'll be satisfied.
Such audacity from a young girl.
[Teacher A] Open your mouth.
[grunts]
Want to defy me?
[mumbles]
Laugh if you understand.
Don't get angry, Teacher A.
-[breathing heavily]
-[mumbling]
[mumbling]
[retching]
[screams]
[whimpering]
[laughing]
[snickering]
[dramatic orchestral music]
[grunting]
[panting]
[grunts]
-[door opens]
-[female student] Excuse me, ma'am.
I'm Yuri.
It's my first day at this school.
I'd like to be made
the head inspector please.
Can a girl like you be inspector?
The rules exist to serve the public.
I want to be of service by enforcing them.
[Yuri] I can give you my support.
I know Nanno. She and I went
to the same school.
I can help you deal with her.
What is this?
There is a rebel group of students
on a secret chat.
So, I joined under a fake name.
We can catch them before things get worse.
-[student 1] Come on.
-[student 2] You, come to the front.
Now, sit down.
-Hands on your head.
-Hands up.
Shit. How did they find out?
There must be a mole here.
Ah, yeah. Do we really have
to sit here all night?
You, name?
Sittichai.
-What class?
-[Sittichai] Class 6-5.
-You?
-Teerapat.
-Class?
-[Teerapat] Class 4-2.
Well, thank you, Yuri.
You did an excellent job today.
You can go rest now.
Let me put that file away first.
[suspenseful music]
They're ready for you.
[majestic music]
[principal] Do you regret your actions?
[students] We are sorry, Principal.
I asked whether you regret your actions.
[students] We regret them.
Sir, forgive us.
Thank you.
There's a place for those who do repent.
[principal] No more mistakes, or…
there will be punishment.
Without question, you must follow
the rules here very strictly.
Be strong and do not give in
to temptations.
Very well. You may go to class.
[students sighing, grunting]
[students groan]
[whispering]
[tense music]
Hello, Yuri.
Why do you keep dancing around
the issue, Nanno?
Why are you still a two-faced bitch?
I warn you, stay out of my way.
[scoffs]
[school bell ringing]
[machine whirring]
[Teacher A] Stop that, Nanno.
[sighs]
What kind of trouble are you up to now?
[Nanno] I want everyone in this school…
to see what hypocrites you teachers are.
[grunting]
[both grunting]
[classical music]
[splutters]
[screaming]
[Yuri] Look into the camera, please.
Stop that, Yuri.
-[grunts]
-Come near me…
and I'll send this clip to everyone.
Then, what do you want from me?
I want those documents.
Hm?
[chuckles]
These papers show the total amount
of donations
given to the school by the ministry.
How interesting.
Huh? Why does the school
look like trash then?
It's never clean
and the lunch here is disgusting.
We don't have computers either.
So, where did the money go?
Do not let Nanno's lies fool you.
Those documents
are actually all fake, Yuri.
[laughs]
If these papers are fake,
then it wouldn't matter…
if we threw them away.
[classical music]
Oops.
Look, she's up there.
[laughing]
You!
[student 1] She's over there.
Go get her.
[Yuri] You should probably start
running away right now.
[student 2] Over there. Hurry!
-Hurry up! Get her.
-[student 1] Go get her.
-[student 2] Come on.
-[student 1] Hurry.
She went that way.
[laughing]
[clamoring]
[suspenseful orchestral music]
[muffled laugh]
[music stops]
I'm sorry, Nanno.
But, to win at this game,
you must take one for the team.
[tense music]
Hello teachers of Pantana Wittaya School .
We hereby declare that…
we will no longer submit
to the rules of this school.
[cheering]
How dare you say that?
What shall we do now?
Well… should we torture them?
Should we make them write down
their confessions in statement?
Make them admit to all the horrible things
that they did to us.
We will expose how evil they are
to everyone.
[sighs]
Yeah.
-[student] Filthy animals.
-Yeah.
You heard what she said.
[New] Write down your confession.
[student 1] Move it.
-Let's go.
-[student 2] Come on.
[indistinct shouts]
[Yuri] Make them suffer.
Let's give them a taste
of their own medicine.
[student 1] Hurry up!
Come on.
[student 2] Write it!
[indistinct shouting]
[tense music]
CONFESSION FORM YOU SHALL REPENT
AND BE PUNISHED FOR WHAT YOU DID
[eerie music]
[snickers, laughs maniacally]
[New] Why can't you write it?
Why can't you write it for us?
I'll help you.
[New] See, it's not that hard.
Write that you hurt me.
Can't you write it?
Can't you? Let me help you.
[student] Stop fighting back.
Remember what you did, huh.
Write what you did to me.
-Write, you left me without anything.
-[gasping]
[New] Write that you made me lie.
That you left me.
-[gasping]
-[New] Write down everything
that you did to me.
Do you have regrets?
Write it down!
[New panting]
-[student 1] She's dead.
-[student 2] What do we do now?
[whimpering]
Shit, New!
You killed her with your chokehold.
How can you all blame me?
You and you and you did this.
We were just holding her down.
-We didn't choke her to death.
-She's right, New.
Honestly…
I didn't even agree with this shit.
I was afraid you'd think I was ignorant,
and then turned on me instead.
[student 1] That's your fault.
It's your fault. You killed her.
-[student 2] We should punish him.
-[student 1] Yeah.
You killed Teacher A.
-[students clamoring]
-[laughs]
[student] How could you do that?
You all had a part in this.
-Shut up!
-[clamoring]
[gun fires]
[sighs]
Okay, I'll give you one last chance.
If you stop, I will pardon your crimes
including the murder.
[dramatic music]
[clanging]
Hey, we can't give up yet.
Isn't this the path we've all chosen?
If we surrender, we will become
just like these teachers,
you know.
[breathing heavily]
[clangs]
I think it's over now.
[metals clanging]
Okay, capture the students
who've been bad.
[eerie music]
[principal]
Everything has returned to normal.
Very well, my dear students.
You know we've been living in peace
and harmony for some time now.
You've adhered to the rules for so long.
Then, one day…
a new student came along
to put ideas in your heads.
She threw the whole school
into a state of chaos.
Will we let
the new student completely ruin us?
Everyone, raise your hand
if you think we should kill her.
Okay, very good choice.
Since you have seen your errors,
I'd like you…
to take a step forward
and prove your loyalty to everyone
by weeding out the radical insurgents
who have disrupted
our peace and prosperity.
Make sure they never cause us
trouble again.
[clanging]
Use this knife to prove yourself,
and that you are
a true and worthy student.
You, I think yo should be
the first one to go.
[principal] Here, take the knife.
You wouldn't want to go to prison
for murder.
Have you forgotten?
It was Nanno who started all this.
You're lying. Nanno fell to her death.
How can you blame her for all this?
[tense music]
[clangs]
[claps]
It's time to get to work.
[clamoring]
[principal] Stop it. Everyone, stay calm.
[footsteps approaching]
[clamoring]
Hello, my dear teachers
and fellow students.
I sure hope you did.
[chuckles]
[students clamoring]
[overlapping chattering]
Listen, stop.
Let's go. Let's get out of here.
Let's go, come on.
It looks like
you're outnumbered, Headmaster.
[shushing]
Nanno.
Have you forgotten that I have a gun here?
I would like to know…
if your gun has enough bullets
to kill each one of me.
[tense music]
We also have weapons, Headmaster.
[student panting]
Right now, we are live-streaming
from the Pantana Wittaya School gym
and this is our headmaster.
[tense music]
[gasps]
[chuckles]
Oh, yes, it's me, the principal.
Come on, put your phones away now.
Listen, put your phones away.
[yells]
Put your phones away.
[principal] Put them all away.
Stop filming!
Yes?
Just shoot me.
[breathing heavily]
Shoot me!
You bitch!
[grunting]
Come on, say something to the camera.
Nanno, do you think you've won?
I've won? This is hardly a victory.
This is just the start.
[evil laughing]
[laughing stops]
Don't you see that your way doesn't work?
Are you really going to keep me in here?
I went to a lot of trouble
to get you that evidence.
Yuri, you're just too impatient.
[laughing]
[muffled laugh]
You might have trouble breathing in here.
That's right. I got locked in here alone
for the longest time.
There's no phone reception.
No food either.
Wait, what? Who said that?
There are so many of us here.
Let's be cannibals.
You're right. Who should we eat first?
Should it be the black sheep?
What do you say? Wanna be eaten?
-[grunts]
-[laughs]
[Nanno sighs]
[laughs]
Bye bye, everyone.
See you later, Yuri.
I'm sure you'll find a way
out of this place.
Hang in there.
[tense music]
Okay, what should we do next, Nanno?
It's up to you to decide what to do next.
Do you think we can fight
all those people out there.
[dramatic orchestral music]
[chuckles]
[eerie music]
Who knows how the rest of the story goes.
If things are black, white, or colored.
Who is right? Who is wrong?
And who is better than their friend?
Are we really the ones to judge…
in this greyscale world?
[lock clicks]
[creaks]
[panting]
[screams]
[closing theme music]