[eerie music]
[rustling]
[tense music]
[Nanno] The right to punish
the wrongdoers…
[sobbing]
…is given to those who are in charge.
But, what is going to happen
if the ones in charge
get persecuted themselves.
-[squishing]
-[sobbing]
[gasps, pants]
[theme music]
SCHOOL BUILDING
[foreboding music]
CONGRATULATIONS TO JUNKO JIRAIYAWAT,
THE NATIONAL BIOLOGY OLYMPIAD
GOLD MEDALIST
[theme music]
Are you starting to doubt
what you're doing here?
[female student] Junko, come decorate
with us. You can help us cut some paper?
-Yeah.
-Mm-hm.
Hi, I'm Nanno. I'm a new student here.
Are you Junko?
Weren't you the one who won
the Biology award?
Mm-hm.
[claps]
Good job.
It's nothing.
I can't go play outside
with the other kids.
So, I read instead. It's not fun.
Why are you in that chair?
Is something wrong with your legs?
I've always had this condition.
You've always had this condition.
What's wrong with you?
[dramatic music]
[groans, exhales]
[female student] Junko, you okay?
Take her to the nurse's office now.
[female student] Junko has hemophilia.
When she gets a wound,
it causes lots of bleeding.
It's dangerous.
And she needs to be careful.
It can be life threatening.
I feel bad for her.
This disorder has no cure
or treatment at all.
[female student]
Now that you know, you can donate to her.
There's info on this page here.
JUNKO THE POOR GENIUS
MAKE A DONATION TO KOMKRIT'S ACCOUNT
TO HELP PAY FOR HER TREATMENT
[man 1]
Here's 200 baht to help you, Junko.
[man 2]
Here's 50 baht, Junko. Get better.
[woman]
Do you think 50 baht can really help her?
[man 2] I give her 50 baht every day.
Stop insulting me. I don't know you.
A TRANSFER SLIP OF 5,000 BAHT
A 5,000 BAHT TRANSFER
MADE TO TEACHER WAAN
[Waan] You have to be extra careful
when you use scissors, remember?
Because, it's more dangerous
if you get cut, okay?
Hello, are you the new girl
in Junko's class?
Yeah.
I'm Nanno.
[Waan] What are you doing here?
I wanted to check on Junko.
I was there when she cut herself
and it was…
[Waan] Don't be afraid, dear.
Junko's always been very fragile.
That's why she gets injections everyday.
I love you so much,
and I'm not going to lose you.
Has Junko always been in that chair?
Yes, since she was little.
How unfortunate.
Yeah.
Junko is so strong but--
No, I'm talking about your life.
[sighs]
It must be exhausting for you
to look after her forever.
I've heard people say
that they wanna have kids so the children
will look after them when they get old.
But, for you, that day will never come.
You will have to watch Junko
your whole life,
and she won't be able to do that for you.
But, that isn't how I see it.
I wanna help my child.
And I would like her to be healthy.
[school bell dings]
[scoffs]
It's time for class. Come on.
[dinging continues]
[sighs]
[electronic music]
[inhales]
Here, eat something.
[doorbell rings]
[door opens]
[grunting]
You can put it in the corner.
Yes, ma'am.
Put it over there.
-[Waan] Thank you.
-[man] Sure.
[door closes]
[Waan] Are you full?
Yeah.
[winding]
[rustling]
[lullaby music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[music playing continues]
[eerie music]
[door opens, closes]
[foreboding music]
[door closes]
Who's there?
Is someone there?
Hi.
Mm. Feeling okay? Why are you in here?
[snickers]
I feel just fine.
Then why aren't you in class?
You know I'm the new kid in school, right?
Mm.
I actually transferred here
because I wanted
to meet a teacher who used to work here.
But she seems to have left.
I don't suppose you know
what happened to her.
[chuckles]
Oh, Supatra, you mean her?
-MRS. SUPATRA MEESIRI
-[Waan] She left school last semester.
-[Nanno] Really?
-[Waan] Yeah.
-Well then, where did she go?
-[Waan snickers]
I'm not too sure. She didn't tell me where
she went. We really weren't that close.
You weren't close,
but didn't you work together
in this office?
Ah, yeah. I texted her several times,
but she didn't text back.
It took me by surprise when she left.
She left without even saying goodbye.
[sighs, clicks tongue]
She didn't say goodbye.
Come to think of it,
I haven't met many teachers here.
[Nanno] For example…
Ms. Iriyachai.
-MS. KHEMAKA IRIYACHAI
-[Nanno] Doesn't she teach Biology?
What about Komkrit, Teetawat, Nalinna,
and Tawanwad.
-Have they all left as well?
-[Waan chuckles]
Mm. There's nothing strange about that.
Teachers at this school come and go
all the time. It's completely normal.
When they find somewhere
better to go, then…
[snickers]
…they choose to leave.
By better?
Do you mean somewhere
that's stuffy and salty?
[tense music]
I mean like a beautiful school
that's by the beach.
[chuckles]
Yes, I suppose so.
[inhales]
Everyone wants to move somewhere better.
Don't you want to move somewhere else?
[snickers]
I can't go anywhere.
You have to watch Junko.
Mm.
Okay, time to go to class.
Actually, I came here…
to return this to you.
You left it behind.
At first I thought
it was just Junko's desmopressin…
for treating her hemophilia.
Turns out, it's not.
[chuckles]
The teachers, this school…
it's all really so strange.
[breathes deeply]
[female student] Ms. Waan,
Junko slipped in the bathroom.
[gasps]
Junko!
[grunts]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[humming "Twinkle, Twinkle Little Star"]
[phone chimes]
[chimes]
[Waan gasps]
[Nanno] What have you been injecting
into Junko, huh?
[tense music]
And you killed anyone who knew about it.
Should I post about it all online?
Are you happy with your choices?
You're so disappointing.
If I were you, I would just kill her.
Isn't it Waan the person you saw
in your dream?
We're like two peas in a pod, Nanno.
You know that. Your blood is in my veins.
In a way, we're kind of like
mother and daughter, yeah?
[scoffs]
I don't think so.
You want to kill people.
Is that all you think about?
[laughs]
And that dream
is never going to come true.
You might regret believing that it won't.
[chimes]
TEACHER WAAN - LET'S TALK
No one is going to believe you.
All the evidence I need is inside Junko.
And you keep the bodies in your home.
Is it easy to make money
off of people's sympathy?
I'm warning you, you don't know anything.
What? About how…
you can't live on a teacher's salary
so you make your daughter sick for money.
Is that what you mean?
Maybe, the time has come
for you to be punished
for what you've done.
What are you going to do?
[grunts]
[grunting]
[Waan gasps, groans]
You don't have to worry.
I'm not going to hurt you.
There are so many others
who are willing to do that.
No!
SHARE
You don't understand. I raise that money
for the people's families
who were murdered, okay?
[snickers]
Yeah, by poisoning Junko.
I didn't poison her. I'm protecting her.
[Waan]
I did that to keep everyone else safe.
Junko is a monster.
[Waan] She killed all those people.
She has this disability.
She was frail and they bullied her.
-[screams]
-[laughing]
[laughing]
[female student 1]
Look at her! Get up if you can!
-Look at her.
-[Junko] Please help me.
What's going on here?
[whimpers]
They're hurting me.
[sobbing]
But we just wanted her, um,
to stand on her own two feet.
Junko, please don't be such a burden
to others.
[Waan] Junko hated everyone
at her school.
She asked to stay home
until her legs were healed.
She spent the whole day in her room
surrounded by the thing she loved most.
And that thing was…
Anatomy.
At first, I didn't think it was so bad.
Then one day when she could walk again,
I discovered that…
Why did you take me here, Junko?
If it's not cool, then,
I'm just gonna leave.
[Waan] I have some snacks.
-[gasps]
-[plate shatters]
Mom, it's so pretty?
[dark orchestral music]
[sobbing]
[Waan grunting]
[breathing heavily, grunting]
I tried to make everything go away.
[sobbing]
[Waan] I tried to protect her,
and protect everyone else.
That's why I gave her injection
so she would stop killing people.
[exhales]
I really tried to do my best
as her mother, okay?
Without me…
Junko could kill even more people.
Your responsibility…
as her mother…
is to cover Junko's crimes?
There isn't any justification.
Junko is a real monster.
[Yuri] Did you hear all that, Junko?
Junko.
I told you that your mother
can't be trusted.
And who are you?
I'm a friend of Junko's.
A friend?
[Yuri] I'm a close friend of hers.
I'm close enough to know
what you've been doing to her.
You know what…
[Yuri] We've both been victimized.
What right do they have to judge us?
Things are going to change
from here on out.
I'm sorry, but I had to.
I didn't want you to kill any more people.
Those people all deserve what they got.
They were just bullying me all the time.
[laughing]
Get your wheelchair, go!
Look, intestines.
The useless teacher…
who said I was a burden to the school.
I wanted revenge.
Yuri said I'm entitled to that,
and I agree.
How could you hurt me this way?
I never meant to hurt you, Junko.
I only did it to protect you.
Protect me?
We've been doing just fine
this whole time
until these people showed up
and disrupted our lives.
My life was so much better
when I was able to kill.
And you took that away from me.
I actually switched the medication
and replaced it with vitamins.
So, the weak and vulnerable Junko
that you saw was…
It was just an act.
[snickers]
Junko.
[tense music]
[Waan] Junko!
[screams]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[shrieks, groans]
Junko.
I'm your mother.
But, I don't care!
[screaming]
What do you think we should do?
Should we let the daughter
kill her own mother?
Or let her live?
[both grunting]
[screaming]
[panting]
If you knew Junko was a killer,
why would you help her then?
Don't you want to punish people
like I taught you to do?
We just use different methods.
[panting]
[Waan] Junko.
Please don't make me do this to you.
Junko is a victim just like I am.
[Yuri] All we wanted was to get revenge.
[snickers]
People like you and Junko…
can hardly call yourselves victims.
It's probably hard to judge
who's at fault here.
Is it Waan who crippled her own daughter
to stop her,
or is it Junko who got her revenge
for being bullied?
Can you really judge
who's the worst?
You should be thankful I let you live.
I protected you.
[sobbing]
You didn't have to suffer ever.
I'd go to jail for what you did.
You killed people, Junko.
Instead of showing me gratitude,
you try to kill me.
[both scream]
[both panting]
[panting]
[groaning]
[sobbing]
Junko.
Please stop. I'm sorry.
I love you, Junko, so much.
[Waan sobbing]
Junko.
[both crying]
Mom.
Junko.
[sobs]
[gasps]
Don't you like to call me a monster?
[Junko] Huh?
Prove to me that you are my mother.
A mother about to be killed
by her own daughter.
My… I can't let you… live the rest
of your life if I'm not there.
[both crying]
I'm sorry.
[sobbing]
[crying]
[humming "Twinkle, Twinkle, Little Star"]
[sobs louder]
[lullaby music playing]
[exhales]
[crying]
So, have you decided who is guilty here?
[gasps]
[slushes]
[theme music]
[laughing maniacally]
[grunts]
[dramatic music]
[slushing]
[orchestral piano music]
[panting, grunting]
You shouldn't have come here.
This was all supposed to be a secret.
-[Waan grunting]
-[slushing]
[Waan] You hear me?
[Yuri]
The wickedness of humans never ends.
Even love can be used
to do selfish things.
[slushes]
[sobbing]
I'm so sorry.
[Yuri] That's how it goes.
[music stops]
[sobbing]
[screaming]
[sobbing louder]
-[retching, groaning]
-[slushing]
[dramatic music]
Your time's over, Nanno.
[snickers]
I will give people the power
to destroy one another.
[grunts]
[theme music]
Bye bye, Nanno.
What will happen to the world now?
It's so exciting.
[Nanno] In a world…
where everyone thinks they are free,
and does whatever the hell they want,
am I really necessary anymore?
[theme music]
[closing theme music]