[ominous music]
"Any day now, we're gonna be classmates."
I really can't wait.
[ominous music continues]
[Nanno]
Teenage love is forever frowned upon.
Do adults forbid love
because they mean well?
Or because they can't accept the truth?
[theme music]
DRESS CODE FOR FEMALE STUDENTS
TIPNAREE WITTAYA SCHOOL
CORRECT PROSTRATION POSTURE
[epic music]
A VIRTUOUS LADY IS A NATIONAL TREASURE
TIPNAREE WITTAYA SCHOOL
We can't merge with the boys' school.
Just tell me what this is all about.
We have no other choice, Miss Naruemol.
Our school is running at a loss.
Our esteemed school…
is acclaimed for producing
highly virtuous ladies.
If you suddenly let those boys
swarm in here like pestering flies,
they will tarnish
our school's fine reputation.
We can keep our reputation,
but I won't have the necessary funds
to pay you.
Are you fine with that?
These male students are like termites,
you know that.
Once they start eating away our home,
they'll never ever stop.
And that fine reputation
that we've established?
It will all but crumble to the ground.
[scoffs]
Crumble to the ground?
So are you saying these boys are termites
or are they flies?
They're both.
Just read what they're sending
to our girls.
-Hmm.
-[Naruemol] I can't bear it anymore.
[scoffs]
Oh.
[laughs]
These boys are much more naive
than I had imagined.
Do you know that back in my day,
boys were far worse?
[laughs]
Laugh all you want
but I will not allow this.
[principal sighs]
I know you love this school very much,
but you seem to have forgotten
that I don't need your permission
to do anything.
I called you here
because as chief administrative officer
of the school,
you'll come up with our policies
to help prepare
our impressionable students
for the transition about to take place.
[principal]
Our reputation might be tarnished,
however, we'll earn the money needed
to keep the school running.
Are we clear?
I must say that I'm quite disappointed
by this decision of his.
I mean, our principal
practically opened the gate
for the enemy to take over our land.
Don't you think?
Hmm…
I actually don't think
it will do much harm at all.
Our students will have to meet boys
eventually one way or another, you know.
But this isn't the time in their life
to fight.
These girls are incredibly delicate.
[quirky music]
They are like beautiful flowers
in their first bloom.
We must provide them
utmost care and guidance.
They're at a very vulnerable age.
They're easily distracted.
The boys are also
at quite a precarious age.
They lack both maturity
and responsibility.
It's risky, you know.
We're putting our students at risk
of being demoralized.
[woman] I agree with you, Naruemol.
We must preserve our students' virtue
at all cost.
If we can't agree
that this is a real problem,
we'll never get through it alive.
Well articulated, Linda.
I've been here a long, long time.
I'm well aware of the fine reputation
that our school has achieved.
So, I'd like to volunteer as the leader
to help us get through this moral crisis.
But we all must join the fight.
I'll do all I can imposing policies…
going the extra mile
until with the victors.
And brave Linda…
I'll need your might on the battlefield.
It would be my honor.
But we must begin right away.
Because the students
are already talking about the merger.
How awful.
There hasn't even been
an official announcement yet.
It's already getting out of control.
Who would have leaked the news about this?
[girl 1] Hey.
I heard our school will merge
with the boys' school next door.
-Is that true, Nanno?
-Yes.
[girl 2] Will we have boys in our class?
How will that work?
-I won't know how to carry myself.
-[girl 1 sighs]
What will we do in gym class?
How will we manage?
What if we have to work
on a report together at home?
-Just the thought stresses me out.
-[girl 2] Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
[Nanno] There's nothing to worry about.
Boys are harmless.
-[girl 1] Really?
-[girl 3] Hmm.
[Nanno] Mm-hmm.
I went to a unisex school before.
Boys aren't as scary as you think.
How so?
One time, a group of boys dared each other
to slide down the stair's railing
while I was on the lookout for them.
When a teacher showed up,
they all just ran away.
-[girl 1 chuckles]
-It was fun.
-[girl 1 and girl 2 giggle]
-That's funny.
TIPNAREE WITTAYA SCHOOL
RULE NUMBER ONE,
GIRLS MUST NOT LAUGH
AT BOYS' LAME JOKES
TO APPEAR LADYLIKE
Have you guys ever heard what they say
about the girl's school uniform?
[boys] Don't skirt me now.
-[sighs]
-[both boys laugh]
Here they come.
[girls giggling]
So, hey there.
I'm Nanno. Nice to meet you.
I'm Punjan. These are Pob, Man and Yong.
These girls are Mind, Ploy and Khao.
It's so nice to meet you.
[Mind] Hmm.
How can they hear you
from all the way over there?
Why don't you come closer?
-Okay.
-These boys don't bite.
[pensive music]
I want to give you a tour
around the school,
but I'm also the new kid here.
I should let these girls do it.
Huh?
I don't think that's appropriate, Nanno.
But I remember
that a virtuous and well-mannered lady
-should always be kind towards others.
-[Mind sighs]
-[Khao] Mm-hmm.
-Am I right, Namnueng?
Yeah. She's right.
[ominous music]
Come on. I'll show you guys around.
[Mind] Mm-hmm.
This is the music room.
So, if this is the Tipnaree music room…
then I'm guessing there must be
a lyrics room somewhere else, right?
[girls giggling]
You see, I told you that boys
are really funny.
-[Nanno giggles]
-[Mind] Oh.
-Nanno.
-[girls chuckling]
[Namnueng] Let's move on to the next room.
[girls giggling]
[Namnueng] This is the art room.
-[Punjan] The art room?
-[Namnueng] Yes.
[Punjan]
Is this where you do embroidery and stuff?
[Namnueng]
No. That's home economics class.
[Punjan] What about this room?
[Namnueng]
This room? This is for girls only.
-Boys aren't allowed.
-[Punjan] I want to see it.
They stand so close.
[Linda]
What should we do about this, Naruemol?
[suspenseful music]
I think I have just a way.
Today is the day we welcome
the male students to our campus.
To make sure all classes
run smoothly and on time,
I'd like to inform you of one small rule.
We'll implement the practice
of social distancing.
Boys and girls must keep distance
from each other.
[Naruemol]
Starting with the morning assembly,
girl and boy students will be kept
in separate lines at all times.
The girls will form a line
on the left side.
The boys will form a line
on the right side.
You may proceed.
[ominous music]
[Naruemol] From now on,
-you will be put in separate classes.
-[students reading out loud in unison]
This isn't only to preserve
the purity of the girls.
We'll also raise boys to be gentlemen.
[students reading out loud
in unison continues]
Run. Run faster. Run faster.
Run faster. Come on.
This is good for you.
Exercise is good for you.
It will make you sweat.
You must distract your obscene mind.
Thank you so much.
Chocolate has hereby been banned.
It can stimulate sexual desires in men.
TIPNAREE WITTAYA SCHOOL
RULE NUMBER TWO
STUDENTS MUST SAY UHT DRINKS
OR PASTEURIZED DRINKS INSTEAD OF MILK.
-[boy 1] I'm exhausted.
-[boy 2] I know.
Don't you think this is a bit much?
Well, kind of, yeah.
[Ploy] I feel so bad for the boys.
Look at them.
Their hands shake so much,
they can barely eat.
[Mind and Namnueng] Mm-hmm.
[mouthing words]
I'm so tired.
-[Mind] Hmm?
-[Namnueng] What's he saying?
Mm-mmm.
[phone chimes]
Pob says he's really tired.
Hang on. Do you have his phone number?
It's normal for friends
to exchange numbers.
[Namnueng] Ah.
Would you like me to add you
to the group chat?
-[Namnueng] Mm-hmm.
-So you can talk to them too.
-All right.
-Sounds good.
[Nanno] Hmm.
[Nanno] I added you to the group.
-Accept my invite.
-[Namnueng] Okay.
MINT JOINED THE GROUP
POON JOINED THE GROUP
MINT: ARE YOU EATING
ONLY VEGETABLES? POOR YOU.
BALL: THEY ARE NUTRITIOUS.
NANNO: DO YOU NEED MORE NUTRITION?
BALL: CAN I HAVE YOUR MILK, THEN?
NANNO: OKAY.
[quirky music]
BALL: THANK YOU.
You know you can't use your phones
at lunch.
Who are you talking to?
What is this?
"Take you, take you, take you."
TAKE YOU
"Take you"?
I think you should look at the messages
more carefully.
THANK YOU.
BALL: CAN I HAVE YOUR MILK, THEN?
Oh, my goodness.
[gasps]
He asked for your milk?
He asked to have my box of milk.
What do you think he meant by that?
Can I have your milk, then?
Let's see.
[students exclaim]
I'd love to try that.
[intense music]
I must handle this.
TIPNAREE WITTAYA SCHOOL
RULE NUMBER THREE,
GIRLS AND BOYS CANNOT TEXT EACH OTHER.
YOUR ACCOUNT WILL BE SUSPENDED
IF YOU GET CAUGHT.
-[students chattering]
-[fanfare music]
[buzzing]
[girl] What's wrong with the internet?
[indistinct chatter]
[fanfare music continues]
-[crickets chirping]
-[wind gusting]
[tranquil music]
-Can I get one copy of the photo?
-Mm. Me too.
-[man] Sure.
-[chuckles]
-[Naruemol] Gosh.
-[Ruethai] Ah. Hey.
It's so cold.
So, have you thought about
what department you will apply for?
Hmm…
-I want to apply for Education.
-Mm.
And after I graduate,
I wanna come back to teach here.
Hmm? Right here?
-Mm.
-Oh, wow.
Then, I think Nareetip Wittaya School
should maybe crown you
as their most generous alumni?
-Wow. Thank you.
-[giggles]
[Naruemol and Ruethai laugh]
-[Ruethai] I'm going to cry.
-[Naruemol] Are you touched?
[Naruemol and Ruethai giggle]
[Naruemol] Aren't I sweet?
[Ruethai]
But I think you'll make a great teacher.
THE EDUCATION OFFICE PRESENTS
THE OUTSTANDING TEACHER AWARD
TO MS. NARUEMOL SRISIRIWIMOL
[tranquil music continues]
THANK YOU, MISS LINDA.
THIS WORK MUST BE TAXING FOR YOU.
ANYTHING FOR YOU, MISS NARUEMOL.
NAREETIP WITTAYA SCHOOL
RULE NUMBER FOUR
-[school bell ringing]
-[ominous music]
Hey, are you still chatting with the boys?
I am.
But I thought your account
also got suspended.
I have a new app now.
-A new app now?
-Mm-hmm. The app True Love.
It lets you talk to people at school
anonymously,
so teachers can't tell
who we're talking to
or see what you're saying to each other.
You never know, maybe, you might find
a friend or even find a boyfriend.
Hmm.
So, I can just download it
and use it right away?
That's right. You can download it
and get started.
Amazing. I'm going to download it.
ALIEN: WHO ARE YOU? GIVE ME A HINT.
SWEET LEMON:
DID YOU JUST LOOK ME IN THE EYE?
[girl 1] This is so exciting.
[girl 2] Yeah.
I want to know who I'm talking to.
SMILEY ELEPHANT:
ARE YOU MY JUNIOR OR SENIOR?
[Naruemol] This is way out of line.
Did you introduce your friends
to this obscene platform?
Obscene?
What does that mean?
This is a… a blind-dating app.
It's a disgusting platform
where you share private things
with strangers.
A disgusting platform?
It's just a chat room.
I think this app
lets us see people's inner beauty
and it may help us to find a true friend.
And who knows?
We might even find true love on this app.
[Nanno] What about you?
Did you ever fall in love with someone
when you were in school?
Watch it. Don't get nosy about my life.
Kids your age
should focus on your studies.
You should not be focusing
on finding love.
Just take it from me.
Love will bring you big trouble
and don't forget that.
Some girls might lose their virginity.
Some of you…
might even get pregnant.
[tutting]
I know that.
If things get out of hand…
students may do obscene things,
won't they?
[Naruemol] If you understand…
you must delete that app this instant.
Delete it?
But I think this app
might be useful for the teachers.
You can use it
to monitor the students here.
[tense music]
What are you saying?
Don't you think it's always better…
to be the one in the know?
I think you want as many students
as possible using this app.
This app keeps users anonymous.
But then again, you know,
you have names, birth dates
and passwords of every student.
You could use this app
to monitor everyone's conversations
before they stray too far.
No one will know.
But it's up to you.
Hmm…
It's all up to you.
Maybe you don't feel like
it's worth the risk.
Maybe you're afraid
you'll get carried away.
But don't worry,
you'll just be chatting over text.
No one will get pregnant.
You're right.
Please set up an account for me?
[quirky music]
[keypad beeping]
EMPTY VASE
EMPTY VASE:
I GET DISHEARTENED SOMETIMES
THAT NO ONE APPRECIATES MY HARD WORK.
DAFFODIL: I GET IT.
YOU JUST WANT TO BE APPRECIATED.
[ominous music]
[keypad beeping]
EMPTY VASE: IT'S LIKE I'M FIGHTING ALONE
WITH NO ONE BY MY SIDE.
DAFFODIL: PLEASE KNOW THAT
AT LEAST YOU HAVE ME.
[Naruemol] Ruethai.
I spent ages looking for you.
What is wrong, Ruethai?
You can tell me anything.
You know you're my best friend.
I can do anything for you, Ruethai.
[Ruethai] Hmm.
[sighs]
I really wish I had a boyfriend like you.
Of course, Ruethai.
-[Naruemol] I can be anything for--
-[Suer] Ruethai.
Forgive me.
I was wrong.
Please give me another chance.
[dramatic music]
[Ruethai sighs]
[Ruethai sobs]
NAREETIP WITTAYA SCHOOL
RULE NUMBER FIVE, CHANGE OF RULE
Here are the names of students
having dirty conversations.
Dear students,
unfortunately, we've discovered
that some of you
are acting in defiance
of our school's rules.
I have no choice but to impose
even stricter rules upon us.
I'm doing this for your own well-being.
From now on, female students
attend classes in this building.
And male students will take their classes
over there.
And for some of you who are here…
we'll be taking your phones away
immediately.
Teachers, you may proceed.
[suspenseful music]
[Naruemol] Hey, you two. Can you keep
your distance from each other?
Otherwise, I'll have boys and girls
use separate hallways.
-Good afternoon, Miss.
-Good afternoon.
[Nanno] Hello there.
I was worried that you might be tired
so I brought you something to drink.
Why are you following me?
How's it going? Did your plan to spy
on the students work?
When I read what students text each other,
I can feel myself start to blush.
I don't know.
Do you feel the same way too?
There's nothing interesting about it.
It's all nonsense.
I know, right?
It's a real shame, though.
Everyone's starting to suspect
that you are also using the app.
I don't care much about that silly app.
I just need to find a way
to keep boy and girl students
away from each other.
I'm sure you'll find a way.
Excuse me.
I think I heard some weird noises
coming from that room over there.
[girl moaning]
[gasps]
-[Naruemol] Ah. Oh. Huh?
-[Namnueng] Huh?
[Naruemol] Hey!
-[Namnueng stammers]
-[Naruemol] What are you two doing?
-What are you doing? What are you doing?
-[Namnueng] It's not what you think.
-[Namnueng and Punjan grunt]
-[Namnueng] Stop it.
Didn't I tell you
to stay away from each other?
[Namnueng and Punjan groan]
[ominous music]
[Punjan pants]
Let's go, Punjan.
[Namnueng grunts]
[panting]
[Naruemol gasping]
I have some bad news to tell you.
Ruethai isn't with us anymore.
She had an abortion
and lost too much blood.
[Naruemol sobbing]
The doctor couldn't save
her precious life.
I'm sorry to say, she's dead.
[crying]
[somber music]
[principal] Do you have anything
to say for yourself, Miss Naruemol?
I was trying to prevent horrible things
from happening to both of my students.
They have no idea
what could happen to them.
This happened.
Punjan and Namnueng
were apparently studying together.
They dropped this eraser on the floor,
so Namnueng bent down to pick it up.
Do you honestly believe them?
I wasn't there, so I don't know.
What I do know is, Punjan got ten stitches
for the cut on his head
and his parents may very well sue us.
Miss Naruemol…
for the sake of our school…
I have no choice but to fire you.
What did you say?
I'll help clear up the problem
you've caused,
but I must ask you
to leave the school immediately.
What will become of this school
if I leave?
We will go back to being
a straightforward unisex school
like it was supposed to be.
[dramatic music]
[indistinct chatter]
[dramatic music continues]
DAFFODIL: DON'T FORGET THAT
A VASE MAKES A FLOWER LOOK PRETTIER.
EMPTY VASE:
I GET DISHEARTENED SOMETIMES
THAT NO ONE APPRECIATES MY HARD WORK.
DAFFODIL: PLEASE KNOW THAT
AT LEAST YOU HAVE ME.
DAFFODIL: I GET IT.
YOU JUST WANT TO BE APPRECIATED.
EMPTY VASE: IT'S LIKE I'M FIGHTING ALONE
WITH NO ONE BY MY SIDE.
[principal] Attention, students.
This morning, I've asked Miss Naruemol…
to come say goodbye before she leaves us.
Therefore, I'd like you
to pay close attention.
Miss Naruemol has been a teacher here
for a long time
and was a student here herself.
I'm sure she has some words of wisdom
to share with you all.
The stage is yours, Miss.
Thank you so much.
Dear students…
our school is currently undergoing
quite a few changes.
I'd like every female student…
to maintain your virtue and chastity.
As for the male students,
please keep your distance from the girls.
Once you're out in the world…
you will all be happy and safe.
[ominous music]
[phones beeping]
[whooshing, chiming]
[Naruemol] Students.
When the right time comes,
you will all find so much happiness
in having a family, a family of your own.
I want you all
to maintain your virtue and chastity.
Are you listening to me?
[phone beeps]
[tinkles]
[whooshes, chimes]
Empty Vase.
Daffodil.
I get everything now.
What do you get?
I don't just look up to you.
I think I'm actually in love with you.
Love me?
I have feelings for you.
-[grunts]
-That's obscene.
[Naruemol] We're both women.
Love is the warm feeling
that fills up your heart.
You feel joy
when you're near the person you love.
Do you know that my heart feels warm
every time I'm near you?
What about you?
Do you feel the same way about me?
You're my very best friend.
I would do anything for you.
Naruemol, please open your heart to love.
Love is never wrong.
It's people who make it so.
[dramatic music]
No matter what form love takes,
isn't it still love, Naruemol?
I know you feel disheartened
that no one sees how hard you work.
But I see it. I do.
It's like I'm fighting alone…
with no one by my side.
Please know that…
you have me right here with you.
[students exclaim]
[students cheering, clapping]
[students mumbling]
[students chattering]
[phone beeps]
[tinkles]
[whooshes, chimes]
[theme music]
[theme music continues]