[English subtitles are available]
I'm sure you are tired of hearing this,
but I want you to listen.
It was three years ago.
Maybe we could've changed
something at that time.
(Three years ago)
Captain.
Two hours have passed since the advance
team landed, but no news from them.
Prepare survey units 2
and 3 for landing now.
Yes, sir!
The island of devils that defeated
our warrior unit and threatens the world.
We must bring back whatever information
we can get back to Marley.
Hold on tight!
The devil...!
Hello, ladies and gentlemen of Marley!
Welcome to Paradis island!
I am Hange.
I'm here to welcome our distinguished
guests who've travelled a long way here!
Please, come here and enjoy
some tea and relax.
By the way, I’ve become a friend
with one guest who arrived earlier.
Isn't that right, Niccolo?
Captain!
Don't mind me!
Just shoot these devils already!
Wha-!
-Just what are you saying, Niccolo?
-Captain!
He's clearly not interested in
playing along with your stupid skit.
Niccolo..!
Listen up, you damn devils!
Marley lean no ears to the words
of those with defiled blood!
We have no interest in drinking pig piss
with you tarnished bastards!
Ooooh!? Oooh!
Are you sure you want to
insult us like that?!
Can't you see the titan standing behind you?
We will not bend to the power of devils!
This is our greeting to you!
What're you doing, Yelena?!
Throw your weapon away.
You guys...
Do as she said.
Hange, we're honored to receive
your invitation.
Let's have that tea.
I've always wanted to meet you.
Eren.
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Angels planning disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
(#68 Volunteer)
That tall, skinny woman just shot
her own ally to death.
What did she do that for?
Beats me.
Be she's on our side nor not,
it's clear we can't trust her either way.
Sasha, don't sleep.
But we're fortunate to be able to
talk and gain intelligence from them.
-Yeah, we're really lucky.
-Tell me about it.
It was by pure chance that we
were able to stop them from landing.
If Marley were intended to send out troops,
it’d be a much more massive scale..
We must think of something about it.
Oh, I see.
So you can shoot multiple
times with this.
Those are Marleyan soldiers'
standard equipment.
Each Marleyan's army divisions
consists of about 20,000 soldiers.
There are 50 divisions in total,
making around a million of them.
In addition to that,
they possess three fleets
consisting of 21 battle ships.
They've also seen incredible
progress in new weapons R&D,
as well as in aerial military capabilities.
...Aerial?
Don't look so surprised.
They will look down on us.
I know that!
In other words,
mobile weapons that can go beyond seas
and walls, and drop the enemy from the sky.
They'll come from the sky?!
Hey!
Marley has all that wonderful power,
yet they haven't launched a proper attack
on us for almost a year. Why is that?
There are two main reasons.
The first reason is the Pure Titans
that they unleashed on this island.
Their existence makes it hard for them
to get here, even with the latest weapons.
It was originally a policy meant
to confine the Eldians inside the walls.
However, it ended up one of the reasons
that kept Eldian from Marley’s attack.
Seems like it.
Quite ironic, I must say.
However, the day is about to break.
The Titans should be active soon.
Yet, we're still leisurely drinking tea
here outside the wall.
That means you have killed
all the pure titans on the island.
Is that correct?
So what? Will you manage
to inform Marley of it?
No, it's wonderful.
Way beyond what I expected.
What's the second reason?
Marley is currently in a state
of war with multiple countries.
In other words, they’ve got
a bigger issue to deal with.
You guys have defeated Marley's
trusted Warrior unit.
You guys also took the Colossal Titan
and the Female Titan-their key weapons.
Marley is a country with many enemies.
So other countries came together in
a blink of an eye and then the war began.
So that means you guys are
seeking revenge for your defeat, .
so you infiltrated the army as
some sort of intelligence agent?
I’m right, aren’t I?
As I thought, you guys must have convincing enough
motive and backers to betray Marley like that.
Calling us an "intelligence agent"
would be an overstatement.
We lost our homeland to Marley and
joined their army as conscripts. We're weak.
We also start to lose hope of
opposing such a big nation.
It is until he became our leader.
Marley and the world fear
the Titans and regard them as devils.
However, I think differently of them.
They are Gods…
They gave us hope
when we were at our weakest.
We shot our superior under
the orders of Zeke Yeager.
We're the Anti-Marleyan Volunteers.
Our goal is to free the Eldian people.
That would be Zeke Yeager's request.
All of this would be done to rescue
the Eldian people who are in…
Nonsense!
Who would accept such a ridiculous offer!
We're talking about the Beast Titan here!
He turned the people of Ragako into Titans
and spread terror inside the walls!
He's the very person who nearly killed the entire
Survey Corps, yet he's sending out a request?!
Their objective has always been
to retake the Founding Titan.
If force doesn't work, they will
use any other means at their disposal.
Our enemies must be aware of our thoughts.
Why don’t we listen to Commander first?
According to Zeke, they have a "secret plan"
that can solve all Eldian's problems at once.
What he needs to carry out that plan are
the Founding Titan and a Titan with royal blood.
The world can be saved
if he has those two things.
However...
He can only reveal this secret plan
after those conditions are met.
I can't listen anymore.
They sure think of us as fools.
Eren?
That's true.
I remember.
There was one time I was able to activate
the powers of the Founding Titan.
It was in the moment I touched
a Titan with royal blood.
I’m sure that Titan was
my father's former wife, Dina Fritz.
Zeke is Dina's son, so he must've
figured it out somehow.
The means of overcoming
the vow renouncing the war.
The only hope left for us Eldians.
The way of trampling the world using
thousands of titans inside the walls...
The condition to activate the Rumbling.
You...
Why didn't you tell us that until now?
Because I was concerned about Historia.
I can't allow her to become a Titan
based on my uncertain information.
I admit it was a thoughtless decision.
We will talk more about that later.
But, if that's really true...
Zeke's secret plan would make sense.
Are you serious? You really trust them?!
That's right!
Who knows what would happen if we left
those enemy soldiers on the island!
We should hang them all to death!
No, we can't do that.
We need those volunteers if we want to
protect this island from Marley's survey boats.
Without their "wireless communication,"
then we....
This is survey fleet 1.
Come in.
This is survey fleet 2.
Thank goodness! Our boat ran aground...
We have been waiting
for help all this time.
We will head right away.
In that inlet, right?
Our numbers?
Rest assured. We're heading there
with two survey ships.
Hey, are you okay?
Everything is fine now!
The Colossal Titan!
Why?!
Hey!
That's the enemy!
Hurry! Jump into the sea!
Get out of there!
Jump! Now!
Welcome to our filthy island,
home to defiled devils.
We’ll receive you well!
As long as you like pig piss.
We won't mind if you refuse,
but we also won't let you come ashore.
I'm sorry, but you'll need
to swim back home.
It was fun back then.
We Eldians indeed are
feared and hated by the world.
By the people on the other side
of the sea who have never even met us.
But not everyone on the other side
of the sea is our enemy.
We find that the world is much
more complicated than we thought.
It's full of things we don't know.
By the way, why's your skin is
so dark, Onyankopon?
He who made us once thought,
“wouldn't it be interesting if there
were more than one kind of people out there?”
The same goes to the subjects
of Ymir like you guys.
All of us exist because
someone wanted us to exist.
Then who made us?
The being that granted power
to the founder Ymir.
It’s God.
There are those who think like that.
They have right to believe
whatever they want.
What is this food?
Is this stuff edible?
Looks raw.
First time having seafood?
Niccolo is a master of
Marleyan cooking.
Dammit.
If you don't like it, stop eating,
you Eldians.
There's no food for…
-Yum!
-That's unfair, Sasha!
Mr. Niccolo, you're a genius!
Watch your manners!
I've never had something like this.
There's more. Take it slow.
The port will be done soon.
The progress has been so fast ever since
those Marleyan engineers decided to help.
I'm surprised they would
agree to do so.
Sure, we both were suspicious of each
other at first and it didn't go so smoothly.
But once time passed and we started to
look at each other as a person, not title...
I'm sure we can understand each other.
Armin.
Did you see anything from
Bertolt's memory?
Eh? Well...
No, nothing useful.
We don't have much time.
Zeke only has three years
left to live.
Yeah, and about that.
Is it really okay for us to keep
carrying on Yelena's plan?
Is there any problem?
Is threatening the world with Rumbling really
the only way to protect the Eldian people?
That’d drag the entire world into a nightmare.
Can't we just talk it through
before that?
If we can resolve our misunderstanding
by speaking to Marley and the world...
Misunderstanding?
What misunderstanding?
You know, people think we're scary.
According to the world, we're monsters
who can turn into a titan.
That’s not a misunderstanding.
But there are Marleyans
who’ve become friends with us..
How many?
Most Marleyan soldiers are glaring
at us from the prison cell, no?
I'm sure if we have more time, we can...
Yeah.
We need time.
Yes.
And to buy that time...
...we must make sure they
can't do anything to us.
Is what we're doing
really the right thing?
Maybe there could be another way.
I can't stop thinking about that.
I thought I knew about Eren
more than anyone else.
Even more than Mikasa.
But... I don't know anymore.
Hey!
You're Marleyan, right?
What are you coming here for?!
What business do you have at
a graveyard of the Eldian killed by Marley?!
Please wait!
Please let us!
We will take care of him!
I beg you, please.
Don't get so close with an Marleyan!
Hey, Niccolo.
Are you okay?
Dammit!
Why?
Did Sasha really die?
Tell me.
Why?
What were you guys doing?!
They said she got shot by
a girl who snuck into the airship.
How could that possibly happen?
It was not just an ordinary girl.
She'd been trained.
A warrior candidate?
I also let my guard down.
I'm sorry.
Why are you apologizing to me?
All I did was cooking for you guys.
Thank you for feeding
her so much good food.
Niccolo.
How did you feel, Connie?
Sasha and I were like twins.
It's like I'm losing half of myself.
You are?
Thank you for taking care of my daughter.
Umm, sir?
I'm just a captive Marleyan.
But I have permission to work as a chef.
Your daughter enjoyed my food
more than anyone else did.
That's why...
If you don't mind...
Please come and taste my cooking.
For free, right?
Yes!
So your reports say you were victorious?
Ignorance sure is frightening.
I can kill you right now and send your
corpse to Marley in order to reveal your scheme.
I bet it will spell an end
to your grandparents.
But if this "secret plan" of yours is real,
I can wait a bit longer before
slicing you into pieces.
I don't mind either way.
I'm grateful for your generous words.
But shouldn't you let me meet Eren first?
Why the hurry?
I already prepared a high class
hotel for you to stay for the night.
You can take a nice rest there, first.
Say... can you stop glaring me like that?
This is all the Titan transformation
serum we stole from Marley.
However, duplicating them
will be difficult.
No, this ought to be enough.
We can't thank you enough for this.
You guys have done so much for us,
guiding us from ignorance to hope.
Only devils would doubt
their own saviors.
Over these past three years,
we thought we've done enough to
prove that we're friends with the Eldian.
But it's unfortunate.
Those guns we brought were meant
to bring freedom to the Eldian.
I'm sorry for our selfishness.
But please overlook our weakness
for the time being.
We have no choice but to put
shackles on Zeke.
I don't mind, Commander Pixis.
The day will soon come when
we can sit at the same dinner table again.
This is the hotel I'm staying?
Do you have any complaints?
It's the forest of great trees.
There's no better place than this for you to stay.
Looks like I can have a lot of fun
with vertical maneuver equipment here.
What do you say, Captain Levi?
I'd like to show Gabi and Falco
this vast wilderness as well.
Whether or not those brats get
to see this vast wilderness is up to you.
Eren... Yeager!
Eren was ready to do this,
even by himself.
Whether we help him or
abandon him...
it would have ended awfully
either way.
But now we've killed a lot of people.
We’ve got the battleship, soldiers,
and civilians involved.
And took everything away
from them out of nowhere.
However, if that military port
is still operating...
Marley would launch an
immediate counter-attack on this island any time.
We lost our hope for peace.
So we have no other choice but this.
Just like you guys that day.
Please, Annie...
Tell us something.
If we lose, we die.
If we win, we live.
We can't win if we don't fight.
Fight.
♫ In an instant ♫
♫ In an abandoned world ♫
♫ If you can’t fly, please tell him ♫
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes
I will be immortal ♫
There is no ally in the outside world.
That's why we must destroy all
of our enemy to survive.
No one knows whether that
is truly the right answer.
Next Episode: A Sound Argument