We'll bring our director,
Ms. Cheon Seo Jin,
to the stage to announce the winner.
A round of applause, please.
Where's Eun Byeol?
She took a lot of pills earlier.
Did she pass out somewhere?
- I don't see Bae Ro Na, either.
- Classical singing. Bronze award.
Seniors from Cheong A
Arts High School,
Noh Ji Ah and Cho Bo Mi.
Why isn't she picking up?
They're announcing the winners now.
Be quiet.
Everything is fine without her.
Would you please just shut it?
You were so good today.
It was amazing.
Here.
Thank you.
Do you want to get pasta with me
tomorrow?
I can wait for you
by the entrance after class.
I'm busy tomorrow.
I can wait.
I missed you too, Ro Na.
The highlight of the 28th
Cheong A Art Festival.
The recipient of the grand prize,
given to the singer who has...
the most-divine voice, is...
What I want is
the grand prize trophy.
So regardless of whose name
you find in the envelope,
just call my name.
Bae Ro Na.
(The 28th Cheong A Arts Festival)
Excuse me!
There's a dead body outside!
Someone is dead!
My goodness!
(The 28th Cheong A Arts Festival)
Min Seol A?
I'm sorry...
for taking your place.
Please forgive...
my mother.
Don't be sorry.
Over there!
Here!
Oh, my!
What happened?
- What's going on?
- No way!
Ro Na! What happened?
Ro Na!
Ro Na...
Ro Na, open your eyes!
What are you doing here?
Mom is getting scared.
Open your eyes!
- What are you doing?
- Honey!
Can you do something?
Ro Na isn't answering.
Ro Na, open your eyes!
Ro Na, can you hear me?
You have to stay with us.
What are you doing?
Call an ambulance!
- Quick!
- Okay.
Hello? Could we get
an ambulance here quick?
We're at Cheong A Arts High School.
There's a student injured.
Please, quickly!
- Ro Na!
- What?
Min Hyuk!
Ro Na!
Don't look. It'll be fine.
Don't look this way.
I can't find her pulse.
She's not breathing either.
Everyone, back up!
Ro Na!
This is...
a murder.
This a murder case!
Shut it! My daughter isn't dead.
Why would Ro Na die?
She's still warm.
My daughter is still warm!
Lock the gate right now.
Don't let anyone here leave
until the police arrive.
No one can step foot outside
until we find the culprit!
Don't just stand there.
Lock the gate!
Yes, ma'am.
What's this now?
(The 28th Cheong A Art Festival)
- Get out!
- Out of our way!
Stop! Don't run!
There's a person here!
- What's this?
- Stop! No!
No! No!
Did you see her?
Wasn't she with you?
You can't leave!
You need to stay inside!
No!
Yoon Chul.
I'll go as soon as
I take care of things here.
Go ahead.
She'll be okay.
Please leave.
(Ambulance)
Don't touch it.
It may be evidence.
What is it?
Aren't you hungry?
Want a snack?
I don't want anything.
Why did you lock the door?
Are you very upset?
I'm fine! I'm totally fine!
I need to rest.
I'm just tired.
Okay. I'll let you rest.
(The 28th Cheong A Art Festival)
She didn't die. She didn't die.
She can't die.
(The 28th Cheong A Art Festival)
What's her BP?
Get the defibrillator.
Charge to 190 joules.
Clear.
Open an OR.
Call Neurosurgery.
Take her to the OR now!
No... Ro Na! Please don't leave me!
Ro Na. Please just stay alive.
I'm sorry. I was wrong. Ro Na...
Ro Na. I'm sorry!
Did you find anything?
Too many people ran out.
It'll be difficult to find
footprints or evidence.
(Police)
Did she die?
How long will you keep us here?
We have things to do!
Would you say that if
it were your daughter?
You act like
she's your real daughter.
Why are you trying to escape
without being questioned?
- You're hiding something!
- What did you just say?
You're an assemblyman. Step in.
Hey. Let go!
What are you people doing
to an assemblyman?
Mr. Ha. Do you know what time it is?
Let's go home already!
Everyone here is well known
in their respective fields.
They're not flight-risks!
- And the police will...
- A child!
A child was hurt.
She's fighting for
her death right now.
I will catch the culprit myself.
Whoever it may be!
I will find them...
and punish them.
I won't let anyone...
step food outside of here
without an alibi.
So it's in your best interest
to cooperate.
I was in the auditorium
from the moment the festival began.
I went to the bathroom only once.
You can confirm
with the people here.
Me too. I was in the same row
as my husband the entire time.
Chairman Joo. You were
the first person on the scene?
Is it a crime to run well?
And strictly put,
the janitor was the one
who first discovered the scene.
I ran over when I heard him scream.
All of us...
saw each other in the auditorium.
- Am I right?
- You're right.
We had coffee together
while the judges deliberated. Right?
- Right.
- The entire time.
Jenny says Eun Byeol wasn't in
the dressing room.
Shouldn't you question her first?
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen Eun Byeol
this entire time.
She wasn't in the field either.
She wasn't feeling well,
so she went home early.
She went home?
She went home without hearing
the grand prize announcement?
Eun Byeol would never do that.
She was a strong contender
for the grand prize.
She'd faint before she'd leave.
Did Eun Byeol take
a drug again today too?
You all know, right?
That she relies on drugs...
whenever she performs.
She wasn't feeling well
because she was nervous.
Are you suspecting
Eun Byeol right now?
No one is excluded.
Not you, not Eun Byeol.
Don't worry.
I'll see how she's feeling
and have her go in for questioning.
Your daughter Eun Byeol too.
Satisfied?
Let's let people with
solid alibis leave first.
(Police Line Do Not Cross)
This is the wing of a trophy.
It looks like the weapon used.
Trophy?
There were two stab wounds from
the trophy on her head and shoulder.
She lost especially a lot of blood
from her head.
Where's the rest of the trophy?
We couldn't find it at the scene.
We plan to focus the investigation
on finding the missing weapon.
We'll have to shut down the school
for the time being.
I'll help you as much as I can
as the school director.
Is there anyone from the school...
who had a grudge against the victim?
Seeing how
they rang the fire alarm...
to eliminate the evidence,
it may be someone who knows
the school very well.
Can you think of anyone?
What do you take the great
Cheong A Arts High School for?
Are you saying we were behind it?
Well, that's not it, but...
Please cooperate with us.
We will.
Why are you so on edge?
Why are you doing this?
Are you a detective?
Are you Ro Na's real dad?
Fine, try and find
the culprit for Ro Na.
Search the whole place
all night if you want.
(Intensive Care Unit)
(Restricted Area)
This is Ro Na's.
How is she? Did she wake up?
(Intensive Care Unit)
Are you Bae Ro Na's guardian?
She just woke up.
Ro Na, it's Mom.
Open your eyes.
Ro Na, I'm here.
Do you recognize me?
Ro Na.
Who did this to you?
Who on earth did this to you?
Ro Na.
This is yours.
You won the grand prize.
Recover quickly
so we can celebrate together.
Hang in there, okay?
Hang in there.
The trophy is Seol A's.
Give it to her.
I know I've been mean to you.
I'm sorry.
Ro Na.
Ro Na, wake up.
Ro Na!
Help!
Ro Na! No!
Wake up. Please don't die.
- Please move.
- Ro Na, please.
Ro Na, please don't die!
Ro Na, I'm sorry. Please.
- Ro Na, please.
- We're ready.
I'm sorry. Please don't die.
- Please.
- Defibrillator!
- Yes!
- Yoon Hee.
- No!
- Defibrillator!
No! Ro Na!
Ro Na, please.
Ro Na, I'm sorry.
- 200 joules charged.
- Ro Na.
Ro Na, please.
No! Please!
Why are you still up?
I want to ask you something.
It's about Ro Na.
Did you do it?
What are you talking about?
Why would I do such a thing?
You're lying.
I know you have something
to do with it.
Both when Seol A and Mom died,
you were calm like now. But...
I know.
Both Mom and Seol A...
were killed by you.
You killed my mom!
Why did you do that?
To marry that horrible woman?
Or is it because my mom
gave birth to Seol A?
If you harmed Ro Na too...
I never imagined
my son would be so delusional.
What's this nonsense?
Let go of him!
We're not your possessions.
You have no right to hit us.
I'm glad you're here.
I need to ask you something.
Do you know whose necklace this is?
It's Eun Byeol's.
She was wearing it
during the festival.
Why do you have it?
I found it on the floor.
Go to your rooms now.
Don't touch it.
It may be evidence.
- Assemblyman Lee.
- Show some respect.
Do you even know how much
a bunch of spinach costs?
So this belongs to Eun Byeol?
Where did it go? I was sure
that I put it in my pocket.
Where is it?
You're back.
You came home pretty late.
Something came up.
Did Eun Byeol have dinner?
No. As soon as she came home,
she took a shower and went to bed.
She was probably too tired to eat.
It's late. You should go to bed.
By the way, I can't find
Eun Byeol's dress anywhere.
She was wearing it when she came
home, but it's not in her wardrobe.
It must be somewhere.
Why is that so important
at this hour?
I see. Good night then.
Could it be...
No way. Eun Byeol would never.
It can't be.
(Secretary Do)
Secretary Do, how is Ro Na doing?
What?
There's no chance that...
she'll wake up?
Did you...
really do it?
What are you talking about?
I was just upset that
I didn't win the grand prize.
Then what's that?
Why is there blood on the dress?
Tell me everything that happened.
What did you do to Ro Na?
Ro Na didn't die, did she?
No way. That's impossible.
She's made of steel.
No way. I don't believe it.
Pull yourself together
and answer my question.
Did you do it?
Answer me, Eun Byeol!
She kept taking things away from me.
She kept getting in my way
and badmouthed you.
That you slit her mom's throat.
That you lost to her mom.
But I had no plans to kill her.
I'm telling you the truth.
Believe me!
It's okay.
Get it together.
Calm down.
It's all over.
I'm a criminal.
The police will
come for me soon, right?
No. I should just turn myself in.
I want to just come clean.
It's all over for me,
college and singing!
No!
Your life won't be done.
I won't let it!
I'm going to protect you.
It doesn't matter...
whether Ro Na lives or not.
You don't need to get involved.
If anyone asks,
just say you don't know.
Do you understand me?
What if someone saw?
There are surveillance cameras
all around the school too!
I'll take care of it.
Don't you worry.
I can dispose of this dress too.
I can do that.
That way, there's no proof.
The trophy.
The trophy?
Your trophy from
Cheong A Arts Festival.
Where did you put it?
In my locker at school.
What?
Another unfortunate
incident occurred...
at the famous Cheong A
Arts High School.
During the Cheong A Arts Festival,
known to be one of the key events
happening at the school,
the student that won
the grand prize...
fell into a coma...
before she could even get
to hold the trophy in her hands.
The police think that this was
likely to be a hate crime...
by a fellow student who is
jealous of her.
They're going to investigate...
and go through each person
who was present during the incident.
Meanwhile, Director Cheon Seo Jin
of Cheong A Foundation...
announced that all classes will
be held virtually...
and that the school will comply
with the police investigation.
Her brain damage is severe.
It'll be difficult.
You should prepare yourselves.
Yoon Hee.
You can't stay like this.
I'll get you a room. Get some rest.
It's fine.
I need to find whoever did this
to my daughter.
What did the police say?
Have they still not found
any evidence?
They're looking into it,
but nothing so far.
The murderer was at school!
How can they not find anything?
I find it odd that the fire alarms
malfunctioned and went off.
I don't trust the police anymore.
I need to drive myself there
and see for myself.
You're too weak right now.
Let's just trust them and wait.
I've contacted someone I know
in the police to look after this.
I'll get a call as soon as they find
any evidence.
I can't trust anyone!
I'm going to find that murderer.
You think I'll just let them live
after hurting my daughter?
Yoon Chul,
what if something goes wrong
with Ro Na?
What if something bad happens?
I feel like I'm going to go insane.
What do I do?
What's going to happen to my Ro Na?
Yoon Hee!
Call a doctor!
- Are you okay?
- Get her an oxygen mask!
Su Ryeon, please don't take Ro Na.
You can kill me instead.
Please don't take Ro Na.
Please.
(Sleep aid)
Don't think about anything.
Just sleep.
Did you see my phone?
I destroyed it just in case.
I'll get you a new one.
Stay away from your friends
for a while.
Remember.
What's past is past.
Once you sleep, it'll all be past.
Eun Byeol had it all along.
The evidence
that you killed her grandfather.
Did you enjoy
the video I sent you,
Ms. Cheon?
Who is this jerk?
Stop hiding and just show yourself!
So, did it become nothing?
What happened to Grandfather.
What do you mean?
I missed him so much.
That's why I took pills.
What are you saying?
You're not making any sense!
(No SIM Card)
When did you come?
Today.
How's Ro Na?
Is she still unconscious?
Cheon Seo Jin and Eun Byeol are
acting suspiciously.
Please tell me what you know.
I took this at 5 a.m. today.
Where is she going this early
in the morning?
With a bag in her hands?
What's weirder is that
she came back empty-handed.
Not only that, she was with Seo Jin.
Could that be...
I need to get the trophy first.
If we get caught, that's the end.
The police have finished
the investigation of the site.
- Are you sure?
- The initial investigation failed,
so they're struggling to find
any evidence.
There's minimal manning
and most are gone.
Let's go.
- Cheon Seo Jin?
(Ha Eun Byeol)
Right?
Ms. Cheon.
What brings you here?
What are you doing here
at this hour?
Are you looking for something...
in this dark classroom
with nobody here?
Right. Something is fishy.
What are you
rummaging through like a thief?
Rummaging through? What?
What?
Those lockers behind you.
They look perfect
for hiding something.
- Get out of my way.
- That's right.
Let's open them up.
You start from the left.
I'll break the doors open
from the right.
Hold on!
I'll open Eun Byeol's.
What? There's nothing.
There aren't many left.
It's here!
Whose is it?
(Joo Seok Kyung)
Joo Seok Kyung! I knew it.
We have to get her!
Let's go. Quick!
What are you doing here?
Let me go!
Do you know who my mother is?
I'm not leaving!
Father, where are you?
Seok Kyung is...
being arrested!
What happened to your hand?
I was rushing to open the locker.
How did you know?
Eun Byeol called.
Were you the one who rang
the fire alarm too?
No.
I had no idea then.
Is it really Eun Byeol?
Did Eun Byeol really
do that to Ro Na?
No, right?
I don't want to believe it either.
Why didn't you tell me?
You should've told me first!
How was I supposed to tell you?
You're Oh Yoon Hee's husband now.
I don't believe this.
How could my Eun Byeol do this?
It already happened.
We need to accept reality.
No. This can't be.
This can't be true.
You're the one who put the trophy
in Seok Kyung's locker.
You didn't want Eun Byeol
to get arrested either.
You've always been
a disappointing father.
Are you really going to
watch her ruin her life?
It's going to be proven very soon
that Seok Kyung didn't do it.
So, get yourself together!
Yoon Hee won't give up.
She's going to keep digging
until she finds the murderer.
In the end, she'll find out
that it's Eun Byeol.
Then, Eun Byeol's life is over.
Save her.
You're the only one...
who can save our Eun Byeol.
You're Eun Byeol's dad.
What am I supposed to do?
I can't do this anymore.
I feel so bad for Yoon Hee.
I'm going to go crazy,
looking at Ro Na like that!
Ro Na...
has no hope, anyway.
I heard from Dr. Jung...
that everything should be
decided by tomorrow.
Shouldn't those who are alive, live?
What are you trying to say?
There's only one way to stop
Yoon Hee from keep digging.
While Seok Kyung
earns us some time,
we have to make someone else
the murderer.
Cheon Seo Jin!
Eun Byeol is the only person
on my mind right now.
I'll only think about her.
I'm her mom,
and a mother must protect her baby.
If anything happens to Eun Byeol,
my life is over.
Darn it!
Why did you do that to Ro Na?
Did you hate her that much?
You should've just hated me.
Why did you take it out on Ro Na?
She was innocent!
- Why?
- Are you insane?
Why would I do that?
- Why did you...
- What are you doing?
Who are you to accuse my daughter?
Stay out of it!
Seok Kyung tried to kill Ro Na.
The bloody trophy was found
in Joo Seok Kyung's locker.
We deduce it to be the weapon
used to assault the victim,
so we had to question her.
The trophy?
I heard...
there was bad blood between you.
That you bullied Bae Ro Na.
You threw paint on her too.
And you locked her in the bathroom.
- That was...
- They're completely unrelated.
Seok Kyung did not do it.
I can prove it.
Detective.
We got the fingerprint results
from the trophy.
(Analysis Report)
There were many prints on it,
but Joo Seok Kyung's prints
were not among them.
See? I said it wasn't me!
Someone put it
in my locker to set me up.
Who? Why?
Probably someone who's mad at me.
Seok Kyung isn't the culprit.
We took this picture
in the dressing room...
just before
the grand prize announcement.
Look. Seok Kyung is there too.
Is this enough proof?
Who's missing?
Ro Na and Eun Byeol.
We deduce the time of the incident
to be just before the announcement,
so Joo Seok Kyung wasn't it.
What do you people
take our family for?
This is defamation.
You'll have to answer for this.
Let's go.
Eun Byeol wasn't there.
Come to think of it,
Ms. Cheon picked up a necklace...
at the crime scene.
A necklace? What did it look like?
It was very fancy with a huge stone.
I think it was a sapphire.
I only took a glance at it,
so I don't remember.
Sapphire?
(I hope you win the grand prize.
Good luck. Dad.)
Didn't you know?
I assumed she gave it
to the police as evidence.
Yoon Hee.
Why are you so jumpy?
I didn't know you were here.
Didn't you go to the hospital?
I came to get some things.
Where did you go?
To the office.
I have a lot of work piled up...
since I haven't been going in.
How did things go
at the police station?
Seok Kyung's fingerprints
weren't on the trophy.
I see.
Any other evidence?
It wasn't Seok Kyung.
I think someone tried
to frame her for it.
Who would do such a thing?
I know.
I'm going to Ro Na.
Rest at home.
Okay.
Yoon Hee. Tell me if you're tired.
I'll relieve you.
It isn't you, is it? Yoon Chul,
you can't do that to Ro Na.
You can't.
Eun Byeol. Why did you do it?
Why did you do that to me,
Eun Byeol?
Eun Byeol.
Why did you do that to me?
Go with me.
Ms. Cheon isn't home yet.
It doesn't matter.
I'm here to see Eun Byeol.
She isn't feeling well...
How do you feel?
I heard you were sick.
I guess you are. You look terrible.
I'm fine.
But... What brings you here?
You heard about Ro Na, right?
- Yes.
- I wanted to ask you something.
Did you see Ro Na...
just before the announcement?
No.
They said...
only the two of you
weren't in the dressing room.
Where were you?
I wasn't feeling well,
so I was in the infirmary.
Really?
You saw Ro Na, didn't you?
Tell me the truth.
What happened between you two?
Tell me the truth now!
What are you doing?
What are you doing to a sick girl?
Why is Eun Byeol sick?
- What?
- She used that as an excuse...
to avoid police questioning.
That's why I came to ask her myself.
Ha Eun Byeol. Answer me.
You saw Ro Na that day, didn't you?
Tell me the truth.
What did you do to Ro Na?
Tell me now!
I don't know. I don't know anything.
Stop it!
Stop harassing my daughter
and get out of here now.
Get out!
- Get out!
- I know you're lying.
- Tell me what you did to Ro Na!
Get out!
Get off!
Are you going down the list
and suspecting all the kids here?
First Seok Kyung, now Eun Byeol?
Seok Kyung has a solid alibi.
The only person without an alibi
is your daughter.
That's for the police to decide.
Right.
Why hasn't Eun Byeol
returned her dress?
What?
I went to the dress shop earlier.
Eun Byeol's dress was the only one
that hasn't been returned.
Can I see it?
You're insane.
Why must I show that to you?
You're right. I'm insane.
My baby is lying in the hospital
like that. How could I not be?
I have to see that dress.
You have it, don't you?
Why? Do you think the dress
has blood on it or something?
You like being thorough.
Where's the dress?
Ms. Jin! Bring Eun Byeol's dress.
Yes, ma'am.
Here it is.
You're delusional and paranoid.
Why don't you spend this time
looking after your child?
Ms. Jin. Our guest is leaving.
(The 28th Cheong A Art Festival)
Make this exact same dress.
I need it by tonight no matter what.
Yes, ma'am.
Yoon Hee came to my house.
She even asked for
Eun Byeol's dress.
She suspects Eun Byeol.
What if she finds out the truth?
Please do something.
Find a way, okay?
The Cheong A Arts High School
incident is being investigated...
by Gangnam Police Station.
- The janitor turned himself in...
- Sang A.
- Sang A. Come here.
- And confessed to his crime.
- What is it?
- The janitor, Park, claims...
- Please stop yelling.
- That he had been insulted...
- I can't use the bathroom at night.
- By the victim continuously...
- The culprit has turned himself in.
- And committed the crime...
- I mean Ro Na's case.
- On impulse.
- What? Who is the culprit?
- Having worked for many years...
You know, the sharp-faced man
who is always smiling.
The janitor.
Do you mean Mr. Park?
No way. Why would a nice man
like him do such a thing?
This is why you can't judge
a book by its cover.
He probably has
multiple personality disorder.
Oh, I see.
I'm relieved that
the culprit has been caught.
Otherwise,
Yoon Hee and Yoon Chul
would have gone mad...
and grilled every kid
at Hera Palace.
The school really needs to be
more considerate of the seniors.
But it just can't be Mr. Park.
He was too scared
to even touch a dead bird.
He would never harm a person.
What was your motive? A grudge?
Or were you after money?
The kid looked down on me...
and insulted me continuously.
- So on the spur of the moment...
- Do you mean it was not planned?
What is going on?
Why is Mr. Park the culprit?
It's okay, Eun Byeol.
Don't worry about anything.
Why him, of all people?
He's always been so nice to us!
I feel terrible.
What am I going to do now?
According to Gangnam Police Station,
Park has confessed
to both his motive and method.
The investigation results...
- Mr. Park.
- Will be announced soon.
Stop drinking.
Leave me alone.
I can't stand being sober.
Why didn't you tell me
it was going to be Mr. Park?
I was closer to him...
than to my own father.
I know. That's why
I'm doing my best...
to reduce his sentence.
I feel like a monster.
I feel like it's all my fault.
It's driving me crazy.
Criticize me if you want.
I know you want to ask me
why I hid away Eun Byeol...
if I was going to end up like this.
Fine.
You may be right.
I can't stand myself.
I said, stop drinking.
This isn't going to change anything.
Every night, in my dream,
Ro Na wakes up.
It makes me so anxious.
If Ro Na wakes up,
all my efforts come to nothing.
Eun Byeol will be arrested.
I'm scared. I'm horrified.
It's killing me.
Neither Eun Byeol nor I
will be able to handle it.
Pull yourself together.
We must protect Eun Byeol.
- What are you doing?
- Are you sure...
you can protect Eun Byeol?
I'm going to protect her
with my life.
Even if that means you have
to kill Bae Ro Na?
Promise me that
you'll protect Eun Byeol.
That you'll do whatever it takes...
to save Eun Byeol's future.
If you can't, I will.
I'd kill Ro Na with my own hands...
- to protect Eun Byeol.
- Seo Jin.
All this happened...
because of the things
we did in the past.
Both of us are responsible.
Even if there is a 1-in-10-million
chance that Ro Na will wake up,
that chance might...
make both Yoon Hee and us miserable.
Do you want that?
(Yoon Hee)
(Serious Crime Team 2)
Mr. Park, I'll wrap up
the interrogation here.
Is that okay?
Yes.
Is it you?
Is it really you?
Are you the one who did that
to my daughter?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Why did you do that? Why?
What did Ro Na do?
- Answer me!
- Please leave.
What did Ro Na do?
Why did you do that?
I'll kill you, you jerk!
I'll kill you!
I'll kill you.
I'm sorry, Yoon Hee.
I guess...
this is it for us.
I didn't think I'd betray you again.
Never forgive a jerk like me.
(Restricted Area)
Unbelievable. Dad, check this out.
All the comments
are criticizing Ro Na.
Everyone feels sorry
for the janitor...
and thinks that
he must have had a reason.
Still, that's a bit too harsh
when the girl is dead.
Do you know what annoys me the most?
A powerless person
who bullies other people.
How dare she pretend...
to belong to the upper class?
After living at Hera Palace,
she forgot her place.
I can't believe she's being
criticized even after she died.
Just focus on preparing
for college entrance exams.
Are you following my advice?
Of course.
I already have...
more than 500,000 followers.
Isn't that incredible?
Can he really get into
Seoul National University...
by following your advice?
You don't trust me?
Why do you think I became
an assemblyman now?
Assemblyman Kang and I...
have been working hard to propose
this bill since last year.
Special admission for influencers.
It might disappear next year.
Min Hyuk,
you have to get in this year.
My aide is doing a great job
managing your account.
Just follow your mom around
and do a lot of volunteer work.
- Take good pictures too, okay?
- Got it.
After Ro Na's incident,
all the kids are in a panic.
This is Min Hyuk's chance
to get ahead of them.
They say every crisis is
an opportunity.
Exactly.
(Grand Prize Bella Voce)
It's Mom, Ro Na.
My poor Ro Na. You must be cold.
(Bae Ro Na)
It took some time
to go through your things.
I finished everything I had to do.
I'll come to you, my daughter.
(Bae Ro Na)
Are you in that big a rush to die?
Let go.
I'm going to Ro Na.
I can't let my daughter go
all by herself.
Do you think I saved you to do this?
I'll punish myself.
I'll take my punishment
for killing Seol A!
You can die,
but you need to find out
who did this to Ro Na.
The real killer...
is someone else.
The real killer?
Who is it?
Ha Eun Byeol.
Take a break and be back by 3 p.m.
Yes, ma'am.
Who are you?
Su Ryeon?
How have you been?
It's been a while,
Joo Dan Tae.
(The Penthouse 2)
I'm seeing red right now.
Can we start over?
No!
I know Seo Jin's weakness.
That's the only way.
I think I really like you now.
Who dares to insult Ms. Jincheon?
You need to work on
your personality.
Hello, I'm Shim Su Ryeon.
She knows
all of Joo Dan Tae's secrets.
Was it that rat Logan Lee?
Beg and beg! Get on your knees!