Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
That was awesome.
I feel like I'm a Mafia from the '60s.
Enjoy it.
See how it feels to be a real villain.
Keep it up!
Escort the chairman out
right now, you morons!
Are you okay, sir?
-Let's go.
-Be careful.
Be careful.
-Stop taking pictures!
-Come out!
-This way, please.
-Be careful.
-Coming through!
-Hurry up!
Move out of the way!
-Stop taking pictures!
-No pictures!
Stop that!
-Come this way.
-No pictures!
Make way.
Cover him properly.
Hurry up over there!
What are you doing over there?
-Gosh, seriously.
-What is it now?
Namdongbu Prosecution Service.
Mr. Jang.
You're under arrest
for leading anti-union activities.
-You have the right to remain--
-Cut it out.
There's no evidence.
What we saw back there is enough evidence.
That doesn't count!
There's no conclusive evidence.
Stop taking pictures!
Or I'll sue all of you.
I'll come with Mr. Jang.
You know me, right?
Let's go.
Hurry up, everyone.
Keep reporters under control.
Get moving! Get to work!
Gosh, why did they have to take pictures?
Why did you bring these two in?
You should lock up these punks.
They poured pig blood over him.
This is assault.
-It's not assault. It's a prank.
-Hey.
I pulled a little prank
on my beloved friend.
Between you and me,
a prank like this is no biggie,
right, Han-seok?
A "prank"? That's just nonsense!
Charge them now.
The video that played on the screen
is obviously fabricated.
Anyone could see that.
Shouldn't you have verified the video
before arresting him?
Right. If it's been acquired
in an illegal manner,
I'll raise an issue right away.
Just you wait. Let me see.
-Where is it?
-Even without the video,
the Vision Team's documents are
good enough evidence.
What's that?
Anyway…
what's the evidence
that the attorney for the union leader's
family brought?
Do you even have any?
Do you?
Here's testimony from the man
who ran over the union leader
under the influence.
Tell us the truth.
I was told
to run over the union leader while drunk.
They promised me 200 million won
and an early release with manslaughter.
Who promised you that?
Lawyer Seo Seong-wan of Wusang.
Why are you telling us this?
I heard about an old case.
Wusang had a man
run over a lawyer,
promising him a reduced sentence.
But he died in prison.
I don't want to be killed off like that.
Gosh, too bad for Mr. Seo.
He joined Lomborgheni
a couple of days ago.
In addition to anti-union activities,
all of you will be charged
with aiding and abetting murder.
-What?
-Me, too?
He said it was Mr. Seo.
Do whatever you want.
We have nothing else to say.
They say silence is golden,
but a villain's silence is
a warehouse of sins.
Shut up, you Mafia bastard!
-Gosh.
-Watch your mouth!
You rude brat. How old are you?
I was born in 1993.
How old are you?
Sit back down!
I was born in the Year of the Snake.
Me, too.
An Italian Mafia scumbag
is pretending to be a hero for justice.
That's ridiculous.
A hero for justice, my ass.
I'm just a scumbag who cleans up scum.
I can never stand scumbags
that stink more than me.
May we leave now?
Let's go, Ms. Hong.
Sure, Mr. Cassano.
What?
What? What is it? You little…
What are you smiling for?
I bet they never imagined they would
be investigated together.
I'm sure they'll be released tonight,
but it'll be a night to remember
for Jang Han-seok.
I'd say the smoke grenade
went off quite successfully.
Our target isn't the anti-union documents.
Then what is our target?
Once you obtain Vision Team's data,
in addition to the anti-union documents,
secure the evidence on Chairman
Jang Han-seok's paper company.
His paper company is
Mr. Jung's second target, right?
We'll use the anti-union case
as a decoy to divert attention.
"Make a sound in the east,
then strike in the west."
You really are a consigliere.
What does that mean?
Diverting the enemy's attention…
Oh, hello.
And attack when they least expect it.
That's clever.
Listen up.
Even with the most solid evidence,
anti-union activities can't send
Jang Han-seok to prison.
He'll make someone else take the fall.
Right.
Even if he is indicted,
his sentence won't be long.
Our goal regarding the union should be
to force Babel to fully recognize
their union.
If this goes well,
we can finish off Han-seok at once.
A prison sentence
and an astronomical fine.
I don't understand a word,
but I'm all for finishing him off at once!
Let's get things moving
before the smoke clears.
Okay.
Have him ready.
The Vision Team leader is
in the next room.
He'll be confronted with the chairman.
Mr. Seo of Wusang is
also being brought in.
My goodness.
Mr. Jung.
I'm the one who ordered
the anti-union activities.
My brother
knows nothing about it.
He took up his position
just a few days ago.
Until then…
I managed the whole thing
and gave the orders. I'm sorry.
Vice Chairman.
Why don't you calm down a little?
No, I'm fine.
Ask me anything.
I'll answer as thoroughly as I can.
Haven't you left yet?
What kind of investigation is this
to hold them up like this?
Do you have any idea
what's going on inside Babel?
Sir.
Are you intervening in our investigation?
That's not it.
I'm just here to give you information.
There's a group of Babel employees
who served the former chairman
and are unhappy
with Chairman Jang's takeover.
This is their plot against him
to kick him out.
Isn't it obvious?
-That's news to me.
-News to you?
How are you going to investigate
with so little information?
In that case, the Vision Team leader
might have been a part of the plot
all along.
Come to think of it,
Mr. Seo left the company
complaining about
his poor performance reviews.
Anyway, send these people home
and start the investigation over.
I can't do that!
These people
need to be investigated first.
The press will be all over you
for a botched investigation.
Start over.
Be thorough this time.
Mr. Nam, have you found anything?
Yes, I found a suspicious looking company.
It says, "Jason Fund needs
to expand its workforce."
It's located in Malta.
And it's called "Jason"?
Jang Joon-woo went by Jason at Wusang.
And if you look over here…
They have a branch in Korea as well.
It says, "establishing a security network
for Jason Fund Korea."
That must mean
that their accounting is managed in Korea.
That's all I could find. No locations,
no phone numbers, no nothing.
I wish we knew someone
familiar with paper companies.
Mr. Cassano.
Yes?
It's not an appealing idea,
but we might know an expert
who we can consult.
An expert?
You came to the right person.
Money laundering and tax evasion
are my expertise.
You used to run a mom-and-pop store.
My boss…
is second to none when it comes
to financial crimes.
He's number one.
Hey.
Is that even a compliment?
Should I be happy or not?
Even a mom-and-pop store
works the same way as a conglomerate.
I'm a bookkeeper
specialized in money laundering.
I can also cook the books.
You should give us a presentation
at Jipuragi soon.
Let me see if you'll be of any help.
Hold on.
What's in it for me?
Isn't Babel your enemy, too?
You almost died
in a freezer recently, right?
Jeez, that brings back terrible memories.
You're right.
It was horrible. How did I forget that?
I don't even want to think about it.
My toes were frostbitten.
Mr. Park, let's get back at them.
Let's do that.
They even took all my money.
What am I doing here?
Those Babel bastards…
-Good work.
-Cheers.
Those little rats.
The Chief Prosecutor sure came up
with a solid story for us.
He's worth every penny.
Hey, Brother.
-Yes?
-I appreciate your kind gesture,
but you shouldn't take the rap
for such a trivial charge.
Take the fall for paper companies,
tax evasion, illegal stock acquisitions.
That's when you can really prove
how loyal you are to me.
Of course, sir.
Back there, I got ahead of myself.
Don't worry.
I'll do anything for you.
My, this is beautiful.
I love the wine.
You should've told me first--
My heart really sank back there.
How could you do that
without discussing with me?
I thought that would be…
the best deal for me.
Did you think Chairman Jang
wouldn't see through that?
My goodness. You frustrate me.
The other charges include
tax evasion, illegal stock acquisitions…
They're too much.
Well, I agree with you.
I doubt that Mr. Jung has
any substantial evidence,
but if Vincenzo uses his tactics
and finds more evidence,
-it's going to--
-Mr. Han.
Yes?
I have a favor to ask you.
Sure, what is it?
Arrange a meeting with Vincenzo.
With Vincenzo?
Yes.
The sooner, the better.
A prosecutor's botched investigation
almost framed Chairman Jang of Babel
for leading the company's
anti-union activities.
But the truth was stronger
than negligence.
It turned out
that the plot was orchestrated
by Director Kim and Team Leader Park,
who were opposed to Chairman Jang…
I'm sorry things turned out
like this again.
It's fine.
The anti-union activities
were only a decoy.
We'll start looking for evidence
of paper companies.
Thank you.
All we need is a Pandora's box
to end all this.
What are you referring to?
Haven't you heard of it?
The Guillotine file.
I have.
It was revealed
when a meeting agenda was leaked.
That's right.
Right now, no one knows where the file is.
Once we get our hands on it,
all the corrupt politicians, lawyers,
and businessmen in the country
can be put behind bars.
-Is it that powerful?
-Yes.
It's beyond our imagination.
Mr. Cho.
You're here.
How could you make such a mistake?
It was finally time.
I'm sorry.
I was too flustered to think about
the iris recognition device.
Now, without opening the secret room,
we can't get the Guillotine file.
I'll…
come up with a solution.
For now,
let's leave it to Vincenzo.
He might be able to find a way.
Well…
Here.
Oh, my.
Is this for me?
This is gorgeous.
You wrote a letter, too.
Hold on. Not now.
Please read it at home.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Oh, right.
Let's give her our gift.
-Here.
-Thank you.
My goodness.
You brought me bungeoppang?
I love these.
Eat slowly.
Okay. I appreciate it.
You two should have some, too.
It's so good.
It's really tasty.
Right.
I'll tell you what.
Do you know the difference
between bungeoppang and ingeoppang?
What is it?
Bungeoppang looks
as if it's saying, "bung."
Ingeoppang looks as if it's saying…
"ing."
Isn't it funny?
Oh, I see.
I never would've guessed that.
Hello?
Hello, this is Han Seung-hyuk of Wusang.
Why are you calling me,
Mr. Han Seung-hyuk?
I have a very important appointment
tonight.
Can you come alone?
Keum Gwang-jin.
Here.
See? He's right here.
Mr. Keum Gwang-jin
is going to come to our plaza tomorrow.
-I see.
Then shouldn't we have to pay him?
Well, he usually gets two million
for each exploration.
But since we're almost like brothers,
he'll do it for free.
-Really? For free?
-Of course.
Would this really be okay?
If Mr. Cassano finds out, he'll be upset.
Right, with what happened last time…
Then this time,
just use me as an excuse.
Tell him I did it.
I guess that's a good idea.
Then we'll pretend we don't know anything.
We'll pretend we didn't know
and watch what he's doing.
All right.
See this article?
See how he found the gold? Where is this?
This is driving me crazy.
Sir, Mr. Cassano is here.
I finally get to talk to you in private.
Sorry for cursing at you yesterday.
Well, it was an understandable situation.
You can make up today.
Yes, let's bury the hatchet.
What do you want?
Mr. Cassano.
I know this is an informal meeting,
but you should still have manners.
I'm not here to show my manners.
If you don't like it, just leave.
I may look young,
but I'm much older than you.
Look at me.
He really is a Mafia member.
It's fine, I like this dark vibe.
Right. It's nice.
He's like a total gangster. My gosh.
Let me ask you something first.
Do you have to destroy me too?
Is your goal to destroy me
along with my brother?
If that's not the case,
then you can have him.
I'll help you kill my brother as you wish,
so just leave me and Babel alone.
Our vice chairman
has made a very tough decision.
Forget it. Just go.
You're the one who came here.
I never exploit betrayal within a family.
Why would you care about that
when you need to win?
Take care of your family matters
on your own.
I won't get involved in it. Okay?
By the way, why is it
that you don't do that?
Because if I exploit
a betrayal within other families,
my own family might betray me in the end.
So keep that in mind.
He's acting all cool, isn't he?
He's pretending to be a family man
when he's a Mafia.
Oh, he drank from this.
GEUMGA PLAZA
I will begin the presentation.
First, what is a paper company?
You, what is it?
A company that makes paper.
-You're so ignorant.
-Jeez.
"A company that makes paper"?
Seriously, honey?
-You should say "paper manufacturer."
-Oh, right.
This is ridiculous.
Well, many people think that.
But a paper company
is an inactive company
that only exists on paper.
A ghost company!
It's not a ghost company.
-It's not?
-It may seem like it,
but it's actually legal.
That's the key point.
So many company executives use them
for purposes other than just business.
They evade taxes
or buy stocks under borrowed names
to increase their shares illegally.
I have no idea what you're saying.
Anyway, it's something bad, right?
-It's very bad!
-Okay.
So they don't pay taxes,
and break the law.
And along with going to jail,
they'd have to pay a huge penalty tax.
It could be up to several trillion won.
If Jang Han-seok gets caught, he'll have
to pay at least a hundred billion won.
By the way…
he must've set up something in Korea
to launder and manage his money.
It wasn't on the files, though.
We only found evidence of tax evasion
and using illegal methods
to gain Babel E&amp;C stocks.
Babel E&amp;C?
Hang on.
I think I'm figuring it out.
What do you mean?
You know Na Deok-jin, right?
Yes.
He said he did some work
for a paper company before.
I see.
What's he been doing since he got fired?
Hello! I'm Singing Mr. Na!
Which is the answer?
SINGING MR. NA
Tapping chopsticks together
Let's make a rhythm
To the beat of tapping chopsticks
And sing a song tonight
If you have lingering feelings
Look at the passing time
And if your heart is burning with passion
Sing a song of love
Life circles round and round
-You've never been to places like this?
-What?
-You've never been to a place like this?
-Never.
This is a Korean style club.
Tapping chopsticks together
Hey, you!
Stop singing!
What did you just throw?
I'd sing better than you
even if I sang through my nostrils!
Jeez!
Don't throw stuff at him!
It's not illegal to be a bad singer.
What's with him?
I guess he's pretty drunk.
She's right.
You didn't need to throw stuff at him.
I made a resolution
while sleeping in my car for a month.
"I will achieve my dream.
I'll live my life to the fullest!
Where are you, my bluebird?"
So I was reborn
as a Trot singer, Singing Mr. Na.
You should try sleeping in your car again.
You may find another dream.
I can't. I sold my car.
By the way, who is she?
Remember the lawyer Hong Yu-chan
of Geumga Plaza?
I hated him.
You little…
I'm his daughter,
Lawyer Hong Cha-young.
Oh, that lunatic?
You better answer my questions honestly.
Yes, sir!
You know Jason Fund, right?
Jang Han-seok's paper company.
Jason…
How would I know that?
I do.
Tell us everything you know.
And everything you don't know.
ATTORNEY CHOI MYUNG-HEE
CHOI MYUNG-HEE
-Yes, Ms. Choi.
-I found
the easiest and surest way
to get rid of Vincenzo.
What is it?
"Yi yi je yi."
What is that?
I'm not good with Chinese idioms.
"Use other enemies
to get rid of your enemies."
Give me more details.
Yes.
One of the jobs I was tasked with
was sending development information
to the paper company office.
Where was it?
It was disguised as something else,
of course.
It was a place called Ragusang Gallery.
Through the gallery,
they're laundering money with art pieces
and buying Babel E&amp;C stocks
under the paper company's name
to increase the CEO's shares
illegally.
Then the financial documents
must be there, too.
Yes, of course.
Their accountant
works in the director's office.
I think the director is keeping her there
and managing the accounts herself.
MONTHLY EXPENSES AND FINANCE
What about security?
Mr. Vincenzo!
It's an art gallery.
Security is tight, of course.
There are guards lined up
in front of the director's office.
And to enter the office,
you need this.
The director's fingerprint.
Anything else?
Oh, I didn't know this either,
but I heard there's this art piece
inside her office.
I can't remember exactly,
but apparently it's really expensive.
I don't know the artist, but the piece
was titled Nothing.
No, not like that.
All right. You have to welcome him
with a big round of applause.
But why is he so late? It's already…
It's past eleven.
I'm sure it's because
he had prior engagements.
I guess he really is busy.
What will you do
if Mr. Cassano finds out about this?
We didn't call him.
It was Mr. Park who called him.
Seriously?
You all suggested calling him.
I'm disappointed in you.
No, it's not what you think.
If we really end up finding the gold--
That must be him!
Gwang-jin!
DOG FINDERS
ANIMAL RESCUE TEAM
Is that a person or a dog?
Are those dog ears?
-Seok-do!
-Gwang-jin.
Sorry for being late.
I was saving this dog on the way.
I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry, everyone.
-Hello.
Why are you…
I should've told you earlier.
I quit looking for gold three months ago.
-What?
-Why?
I've been looking for gold all my life,
but I've felt empty inside.
And one day,
I started raising an abandoned dog.
It just filled my heart.
So I quit everything the very next day
and opened an animal rescue center.
You can't imagine how happy I am
doing this job.
I understand.
Everyone,
real gold isn't in gold mines.
It's inside your hearts.
It really is.
So, look for it there.
I'll be off to find more gold now.
I'm sorry.
-Call me. I'll get going.
-Goodbye.
Bye.
It's inside our hearts.
Why are you looking so down?
You didn't do anything wrong.
It's all my fault.
The truth is, if I were you,
I wouldn't trust
a despicable Mafia member like me.
I understand.
It's not that we don't trust you…
You can do whatever you want.
This dirty, despicable Mafia member
will get going now.
Mr. Cassano…
Don't say that about yourself.
We're sorry. We didn't mean…
How could you do this?
Wait for me, dirty Mafia!
Wait for me, despicable Mafia!
What would've happened
if he hadn't become an animal rescuer?
It would've been the end
if he had found the gold!
Hey, guys.
Why don't we talk for a moment?
I don't want to hear
about the ghost underground.
-Me neither.
Let's go.
The secret basement.
You have no idea how scared I was
that they might find the secret basement.
What are you talking about?
I feel so anxious every day.
When are you going to get the gold out?
The person who made the security system…
for that room
is me.
The iris recognition program
and the demolition program.
I'm the one who made all that.
Hang on.
Why is everyone here so talented?
What was your job?
I was a security system programmer,
and a hacker before that.
But how are you still alive?
All the people involved were--
I didn't work at the scene,
so my identity wasn't exposed.
But when I heard that
all the workers involved had died,
I ran away just in case.
And fortunately,
Wang's men failed to find me.
How did you know
the location of the room, then?
I made the system, so I made sure
I could track it, of course.
And why are you telling me this?
Gather round.
The gold in the room.
Let's get it out together.
You can't open it since Wang is dead,
and if Babel takes this building,
it's over.
Plus, if you make one mistake,
the whole building will collapse.
Can you really open it?
Of course.
I can open it with the building intact.
Since it's come to this,
let's let her join our group.
I can open it if the monks aren't there.
All I need is one minute.
Ms. Seo. Even if you do open it,
it'll take a while to get everything out.
There's that much?
Just wait a little longer.
And make sure to keep this secret, okay?
I've kept my mouth shut
for the past two years.
Don't worry.
All my worries are gone now!
We'll be counting on you, Ms. Seo.
Ms. Seo, you're our savior. I mean it.
What is this?
I made some tteokbokki for you.
And here.
I made this dress shirt myself.
I'm a great tailor too.
Oh, you didn't need to.
We felt bad since all we did
was accept your kindness so far.
And we also brought this
on behalf of all the people in the plaza.
MEMORANDUM
THE PEOPLE OF GEUMGA PLAZA
WILL TRUST VINCENZO CASSANO
AND SHARE ANYTHING
THAT NEEDS TO BE DISCUSSED
There's no need to do this
for a dirty, despicable man like me.
That's not true!
We really mean what we wrote.
Please accept it.
We must have lost our minds
after hearing about all that gold.
We could have been kicked out of here
but you protected us all this time.
Stop it.
We didn't have any money
or any power.
We've been able to live decently
thanks to you.
We even got to help others
and teach those Babel jerks a lesson.
We'll now stop chasing false hope
and focus on protecting our plaza
with you.
All right.
I will join you again.
Gosh. Thank you so much!
There's something
we need to do together first.
It's an important matter,
so I'll tell you all about it
tomorrow morning.
All right. Thank you. Get some rest now.
I missed your tteokbokki.
Really?
-Let's go.
-Thank you.
It's no problem.
-Let's go.
-Shall we go?
Bye, then.
Thank you so much.
We're planning to
totally screw Babel over.
It's a very important job.
Then we must all join in.
-Let's do it!
-Yes!
All right, everyone.
This is really important.
We need good teamwork for this
above all else. Got it?
-Yes!
-Let's do this!
Let's do this.
-Yes!
All right.
-Geumga!
-Let's do it!
So he's secretly laundering
his money with all this.
Using art pieces to launder money
is pretty common.
"Ragusang." What's with the name?
-What does it mean?
-How elegant.
DIRECTOR'S OFFICE
There are guards
in front of the director's office.
Then there's probably no point
in forcing ourselves in there.
And there's a security lock
on the door, too.
We need to find a way
to get inside naturally.
What should we do
to get in there naturally?
This artist's piece is in Korea?
PRIVATE VENUE RENTAL SERVICE
LAWYER HONG CHA-YOUNG
I looked into the private venue
rental service,
but it's fully booked
for the next two months.
I see.
It really is fully booked.
It's not even that cheap.
Let's find another way, then.
I've hacked into the reservation list.
GEORGE ANDERSON
JESSICA BENING
They look like a couple.
Their reservation is in two days.
How about you two disguise as a couple
to get in?
Do you mean him and me?
He and I can't be a couple, can we?
Hey…
Gosh, that'll be so awkward.
Fine.
I'll do it.
Here.
Damn it. That was so close.
How will we hack
into the accountant's computer?
Right, there's a catch.
The director's office uses
Babel's own network,
so it's impossible to hack remotely.
I need to install a transmitter
on the computer
and hack from nearby.
Can you change the photos
on the reservation list?
That's a cakewalk.
GEORGE ANDERSON
JESSICA BENING
I brought some information
regarding Nothing as you asked.
It's an installation piece
by Jackson Martin, an American artist.
It used to be displayed in Milan,
then was sold to Ragusang Gallery.
It's worth around ten billion won.
Why would they keep it in the director's
office and not exhibit it?
It's an extremely rare piece.
Its former owner from Milan
kept it hidden as well.
Thus, there are no photos.
Then let's begin.
My partner would never dress like that.
I'm dressed like this because I'm not.
If you're going to put on an act,
you should do a proper job.
I'm too lazy to get changed.
Don't bother. Get in.
What is he up to this time?
Here is the product you ordered.
When did you prepare this?
You finally look the part.
Aren't you being too generous
for a single act?
They're not a gift.
I'm just giving them
to their rightful owner.
Hey!
Starting from 6 p.m., the gallery will be
rented as a private venue.
Please vacate the premises before then
for our next schedule.
Starting from 6 p.m., the gallery will be
rented as a private venue.
Please vacate the premises…
Our record said
that one of you is fluent in Korean.
That'd be me.
I'm extremely fluent in Korean.
I see. Then she can't speak Korean at all?
I can speak a little.
She has improved a lot lately.
You've been studying hard, right?
Right, darling?
-Yes, darling.
-Right.
I see. Please come in.
-Sure.
-Okay.
This way.
How's Anderson and his lady doing?
-They just started the tour.
-Good.
Pasta and wine.
Thank you.
Okay.
For the next three hours,
this building will be yours.
And I'll be by your side, guiding you.
First, you'll have your meal.
We've prepared a meal at Gallery C.
Actually,
we'd like to look at the art first.
When I was in LA…
Every time I felt that way,
I visited The Broad.
The art pieces touched my heart.
That's when I started to… Right. Study.
Study art.
The library sold some delicious hotdogs.
And the hotdogs… Gosh, I still miss them.
This painting is We, Forever by Ali Osman.
It expresses everlasting love.
Mr. Anderson prepared a surprise proposal.
Please come forward, sir.
-Me?
-Yes.
Me?
Yes. Come on.
Here's the ring you told me to keep.
The ring?
Yes.
Right, the ring.
Come on.
Mr. Anderson, now is the time.
-Come on.
-Right.
Please accept my love.
Say it with more love.
A bit more romantically.
I'm on cloud nine.
Here comes the highlight of the proposal.
Kiss.
-Kiss.
I'll do that later.
-Mr. Anderson?
-Yes?
You can't postpone a kiss.
Do you truly love her?
Yes, I do love her.
I really do, but…
But I feel a bit uncomfortable
doing it here.
That was so beautiful, you guys.
This is such a magical night
I will never forget.
I will never forget this night either.
-Congratulations
-Your wedding, love forever
-Don't fight
-From black hair to white hair
-Congratulations
-Your wedding, love forever
-Don't fight
-From black hair to white hair
What's up with your outfits?
Are you Go stones or what?
Have one each.
You'll be awake and happy.
It's tasty.
We're a team now, so you should chat.
You're so pretty.
You too.
What's your lipstick color?
I see. It suits you perfectly.
It's like listening to two ghosts talking.
What's taking them so long
to enter the office?
Gosh.
William Dayne
often portrayed the inner most thoughts
that people have in his paintings.
You must be tired.
You should sit down.
Yes, there's something we want to see.
There is one.
We heard
that Jackson Martin's Nothing
was in this gallery.
You're indeed art enthusiasts
who know your onions.
I'm terribly sorry,
but that piece isn't exhibited
for the public, so you cannot see it.
We were thinking about buying
some paintings today.
You sure have gotten better in Korean.
We can buy some at other galleries.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
What a disappointment.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Nothing is…
in my office.
This way, please.
Let's take a look before we go.
-Okay.
-This way, please.
Please stop this and leave.
I want to see the director.
Come back tomorrow morning.
No. One of the pieces displayed in there
has plagiarized my work.
I just need to get seomthing.
It won't take long.
What and where is it?
Tell us, and we'll get it for you.
It's very personal and is a secret.
-Just let me go inside.
-I can't.
I want to see the director!
-Please stop yelling.
-Is this how you do your job?
Which agency do you belong to?
I said I won't be long.
If she's not coming out, I'll go.
I'll call the police.
I've already called them. Move.
Stop her.
-Please stop.
-Stop her.
-My father…
-You trampled on my passion!
You cannot enter, ma'am.
This must be Nothing.
Ms. Bening, that's a floor lamp.
Ji-eun, turn on the floor lamp.
Turning on the floor lamp.
It's an AI.
How pretty.
Yes?
Your sense of humor has improved.
Someone must be living here.
Why is there a doormat here?
It's about my foot size.
This right here is
Jackson Martin's Nothing.
He has portrayed the emptiness
of material culture
through his sixth sense.
As soon as I saw it, I could feel
the emptiness from the footprints.
-You can, right?
-Yes, those heels.
It amazes you even more,
-the more you look.
-Right.
Ma'am.
How dare you barge in here?
What is it?
Some strange women are demanding
to see you.
They even called the police.
Nothing.
-Mr. Anderson and Ms. Bening.
-Yes?
-Please take your time.
-Sure. No worries.
All right.
-Oh, I'm so sad.
-Are you?
Let's see.
I mean, Ms. Hong.
-Okay. Put it in.
-Okay.
Hold on.
Hurry.
FATE PIANO ACADEMY, SEO MI-RI
We did it.
I've inserted the thumbstick.
CONNECTING TO REMOTE PC
How long will it take?
Anywhere between one…
or ten minutes.
Why is the gap so big?
Don't toy with my heart like that.
-Hit the glass.
-Drink.
-Here comes the alcohol
-Drink
Shot.
-Well done.
-One more.
What the hell are you guys doing?
Are you the director? Gosh, you're tall.
-Why do you have plagiarized art?
-Why won't you let me in?
Something that's mine is in there.
What is this nonsense?
Plagiarism?
What's that?
Over here.
Police.
We heard there's plagiarized art.
Detective Jeon, go on.
Who's the director here?
Why is it taking so long?
Let's be patient.
She did it.
Here you go.
Is it my turn now?
SHARED DOCUMENTS
Let's see.
"International transactions…"
Why are they all in English?
-Didn't I tell you to study English?
-What is this?
You know that advertisement.
"If you can't speak English,
come to Deoun School.
You too? Me too. Her too."
An accountant doesn't need
to learn English.
Here it is. "International transactions."
How long will it take?
Please wait one minute.
My thighs are drenched with sweat.
Please hurry.
My armpits are sweaty as well.
Don't rush me.
COPYING 4 FILES FROM MANAGEMENT TO PROJECT
Lee Song-baek's unique touch is
clearly visible in this painting.
Plagiarism?
-Do you want to see mine?
-Let's see it.
Ma'am, what did you leave behind in here?
There it is.
It's still sweet.
Why would you chew it again?
Look at my painting.
This looks nothing like that painting.
The lines, colors, feelings,
and the impression…
They're awfully similar.
It looks pretty much identical.
They're the same.
They pretty much duplicated her painting.
Why are you doing this to me?
Even my calves are sweaty now.
What's taking you so long?
COPYING 4 FILES FROM MANAGEMENT TO PROJECT
It's done. Remove the thumbstick.
Yes?
What are you doing,
Mr. Anderson and Ms. Bening?
Oh, no. I think she caught them.
I knew something was off.
How come my ominous feelings
are always right?
You're not a couple, are you?
What are you after?
We're caught.
What are you saying?
We're agents from AISE,
the foreign intelligence service of Italy.
We're looking into paintings
that have been smuggled from Italy.
We've received a tip-off
that some of them ended up here.
Get them!
Don't move.
Are you guys really agents from Italy?
Name, Jung Do-hee.
It says you graduated
from Parsons School of Design,
but that's been fabricated.
PERSONAL DETAILS REPORT
You also didn't win
the Giovanni Award in Italy
or the Emerson Award in the US.
How did you know?
Our Korean agent tipped us off.
Come in.
The two intelligence services
are working together.
Tell us the truth.
How many pieces have you smuggled in?
None of our pieces have been smuggled.
It's the truth.
-Don't lie!
-Tell the truth.
-Do you think we're joking?
-Do you?
-Talk, or I'll shoot you.
-Hurry up.
-Just one piece, sir.
-Which one is it?
The portrait of Antonioni.
Wait. One minute.
Everything will be fine
once I return the painting, right?
Can you give me your word
there won't be any trouble?
Yes.
Hand it over to him,
and he'll take care of the rest.
-Do you mean him?
-What is it?
Do you think I'd sell it?
A bit.
Split it seven to three?
Good work, guys.
Thank you, sir.
Make sure you erase
all the CCTV footage of us.
But that will take too long.
Answer me.
Fine.
If you ever need to flee the country,
call this number.
It's an affiliated company.
What?
"Byebye Balloon"?
"A trip just for you"?
We've arrived, boss.
I had such a blast acting today.
Me too.
There was even a kissing scene.
Right, there was.
I'm sorry if I caught you off guard.
It's okay.
Stop it already.
It's so embarrassing.
Ms. Hong.
Should we have a celebratory drink
on the rooftop?
Sure.
Should we order jokbal or chicken?
Or we could just buy some beef jerky.
What's wrong? Do you not like beef jerky?
Ms. Hong.
I'll go upstairs and prepare everything.
Can you go buy some beer?
There's not much to prepare.
You just want to send me on an errand.
When I went up two days ago,
there were boxes piled up there.
Again?
Gosh. Who is it this time?
Get some beer. I'll go up first.
There are boxes up there again? Jeez.
Did Paolo send you?
Perhaps.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park