Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles and
reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 3
Actually,
I've never seen her since I was a kid.
I don't know whether I'm sad,
but I think my dad must be very sad.
Otherwise, he wouldn't drink every day.
I think
my mom must be
a gentle and soft person.
That's why my dad has been
feeling sad over the years.
Alright.
I don't know why
I'm telling you all these.
Just listen to it as a story.
Don't cry.
I'm not crying.
Da Ming told me
everyone would die.
As long as you remember him,
he will live in your heart.
I guess
your mom
must be living in your dad's heart.
They aren't separated.
Young Master.
How is it?
We have searched all girls' dorms
but we couldn't find the girl yesterday.
We did search thoroughly.
Then, let's just wait here.
I'm sure she needs to eat.
No. Listen to me.
Wu is really
not who you think she is.
To me, Wu
is a kind-hearted girl
with a pure soul.
Her thoughts are simple and direct.
She's like...
She's like a child.
We understand, Brother San.
Anything you say.
You...
Don't make things too complicated.
We understand, Brother San.
We won't tell anyone about
what happened between both of you.
Brother Wang.
Sister Wu was stopped
by Young Master Xiao.
You really don't remember me?
We met at the entrance yesterday.
Wu.
Tang San.
Over here.
They said we can dine for free here.
It's you again, Brother Tang.
Do you know them, Wu?
He said we met yesterday.
But I don't remember.
You're Wu, right?
Why are you with people
from Dorm Seven?
I'm their boss.
You're their boss?
Yes.
You're good at telling jokes.
I'm not telling jokes.
That's because I defeated all of them.
Are we done talking?
I'm hungry.
Let's have lunch.
Wait a minute.
What again?
The food in the canteen is just average.
There's a restaurant
exclusively for the
Soul Master Association.
You can order anything you want.
I am the governor's son.
So I can take you there with me.
I wonder
if I have the honor to do so.
Your father is the governor?
Yes.
I thought you're from the Xiao family.
So what?
Think about it.
The governor is your father
and his last name is Cheng.
And yours is Xiao.
It doesn't add up.
You do have the courage, little girl.
How dare you tease the governor.
What does he mean?
What do I mean?
Young Master Xiao
is showing you some respect
by asking you to join him.
Come here.
Brother Tang.
I'm treating her to lunch.
It has nothing to do with you, right?
Wu.
Do you want to go?
Are you going?
I'm not from
the Soul Master Association.
I'm not going.
I'm not going, then.
Do you hear that?
She said she's not going.
What an ungrateful person.
You're so weak.
I gave you a chance, Tang San.
Why did you embarrass me
in front of so many people?
That's not my intention.
I'll give you another chance.
Move aside.
Hand her over.
You'd better think twice.
My third uncle is
the headmaster of the school.
Is his last name also Cheng?
If we're done here,
we shall leave for lunch.
Wu.
Let's have lunch.
Okay.
Let's have lunch, Wang Sheng.
Let go.
Give it to me.
Stop it.
How dare you cheat.
Wang Sheng.
What's wrong with you?
I said I won't tell you the answer.
How could you grab my paper?
I...
-Why is he lying?
-You...
What are you talking about?
Sir.
Yes, it's my fault.
I didn't manage to stop Wang Sheng
from cheating.
I'm willing to be punished.
You copied my answer.
Alright.
Sir.
He took Wang Sheng's paper away.
I can testify.
Are you
trying to make trouble?
What are you doing?
Zero mark will be given to
Wang Sheng and Liu Long.
Get out now.
Sir, I...
Everyone else should be seated
and carry on with the test.
Martial Soul Fight
is an extraordinary skill,
as well as an exquisite piece of art.
When you go to
the Intermediate Soul Master School
or the Advanced Soul Master School,
you will have a chance to train in a team
at the Soul Arena.
Now,
Xiao Chen Yu
will demonstrate for you.
Please learn from him.
I need an opponent in the combat.
Tang San is a good opponent.
Tang San.
Please cooperate with Xiao Chen Yu.
Yes, Sir.
Go for it, Tang San.
Go for it.
You can do it.
If you stay away from Wu,
I will have mercy on you,
so you won't be too embarrassed.
Let's start.
You didn't get a good look, did you?
We didn't. Do it again.
Yes.
Do it again.
Show us again.
I'll demonstrate again.
Xuan Tian Strike!
Sir, they took advantage of us
just because they outnumbered us.
Alright.
Get back to your position.
Martial in general
is just some physical activities.
Now, all of you
hit the sandbag in front of you
with your Martial Soul Shield Body.
You must feel your own Martial Soul
and make it
a part of your body.
When you are extending it,
imagine
you are extending your arms and legs.
You have an extra pair of ears.
Nothing else?
The speed will be slightly faster.
It appears that Sister
Wu's beast soul is a rabbit.
Since I'm going to school,
I've decided to officially
give my Martial Soul
an artistic name.
I'll name it as
the Flexible Charming Bunny.
Is it nice?
It's cute.
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon!
You're fighting? Count me in.
This is outrageous.
You started it first.
Liu Long, Xiao Chen Yu
got his clothes dirty.
Take him back to get changed.
Yes.
It's not over yet.
Xiao Chen Yu is obviously
bullying us.
I can't believe that the teacher
didn't stop them. It's outrageous.
It might look like the teacher
punished both of you.
But in fact,
not only did he stop Xiao Chen Yu
from doing something merciless
to Tang San in the class,
he also avoided
offending those rich boys.
Sister Wu,
are you okay?
I'm fine.
My clothes will dry in no time.
Brother San,
we have work to do in the afternoon.
We'll get going then.
Go.
Wu.
Let's go.
What's the matter?
Your clothes are wet and
you might catch a cold.
I'll dry it for you.
It's warm.
Why is your hand as hot as fire?
Don't you feel hot?
I practice some skills every day.
And I develop this skill over time.
Please teach me.
Do you really want to learn it?
Training
doesn't happen overnight.
Turn around.
Let me dry the back.
Does that work?
I've set traps
at the left, centre
and right side.
I even covered them with fallen leaves.
It's as if they aren't there.
I'm sure they won't be discovered.
-I...
-Now, let's wait for them to come
and step on
the firecrackers hidden
underneath the fallen leaves.
Then...
When exactly will they come?
It's getting late.
You better hurry up.
You're not allowed
to leave if it's not done.
I'll check it tomorrow morning.
He's annoying.
He doesn't even allow us to eat.
I'm so hungry.
Go get some rest. I'll do it.
You're the best, Tang San.
Are you crazy?
Are you out of your mind?
What are you laughing at?
When are they coming?
Soon.
Soon, Young Master.
It's done.
Tang San, Wu.
Come here.
It's getting late.
You better hurry up.
You're not allowed
to leave if it's not done.
I'll check it tomorrow morning.
He's annoying.
He doesn't even allow us to eat.
I'm so hungry.
Go get some rest. I'll do it.
You're the best, Tang San.
Keep moving...
Do me a favor, Wu.
Okay.
I will be done when you count until 100.
One.
Two.
Three.
40.
45.
Count properly.
Four, five.
Ten.
They're doing that right in front of me.
I can't stand it anymore.
Don't...
Calm down, Young Master.
You must calm down, Young Master.
Calm down.
Who's talking?
I am. I am counting.
Carry on.
Okay.
35, 40.
45.
50.
55.
Purple Demon Eye.
60.
65.
70.
75.
There's an explosion.
Let me check it out.
Wu.
Where were you?
75.
Stop counting.
Let's go eat something. I'm hungry too.
What do you want to eat?
Carrot.
Carrot?
Let's go.
Are you done sweeping?
Forget about it. Eating comes first.
Let's go.
Alright, let's go.
We can't go out now.
Luckily they didn't notice us.
Are you stupid?
They already noticed us.
He swept the fallen leaves
and the firecrackers here.
But I just can't let it go.
Just let it go.
I was right.
Martial Soul Hall wouldn't
give a recommendation badge
to a useless Martial Soul.
Young Master.
I think
he's just lulling us into
a false sense of security.
-Yes.
-He's...
He's even bullying us.
Yes.
No...
No.
That's not what I meant.
I mean
you are the governor's son,
Young Master.
You are a noble person.
Tang San and those attached students...
Who does he think he is?
He has been humiliating us
in public and in private.
It doesn't matter if we lose.
But you can't lose.
I am not capable of doing it now.
I am no match for them.
I can't teach them a lesson either.
I have an idea, Young Master.
Great.
They are disobedient.
I should teach them a lesson.
I'm sure all of you learned something
from the practical lesson yesterday.
Today,
I will give each of you
a one-on-one guidance
based on your condition
and I will grade you.
Let's start with you, Wu.
Okay.
It's great.
Your strength is on your legs.
Work on it.
You can choose a Soul Beast
that has strong leg power
like Lightning Rabbit and Jade Rabbit
as your first Soul Ring.
Must I kill a soul beast
to get the soul ring?
Yes.
Is there any other way?
There isn't.
It's your turn, Tang San.
Sir.
There haven't been any changes
with my Blue Silver Plant.
I can't launch any attacks with it.
I don't think that's Blue Silver Plant.
It's useless.
Can you guide me, Sir?
You did well in your written test.
And you are smart.
However,
I am inexperienced in handling
a useless Martial Soul
like Blue Silver Plant.
I can't be of any help.
I do not want to give up, Sir.
I want to be a soul master.
I suggest you to study
the theory of soul master.
Take a deep look at it.
When you have achievements,
you might be a master of theory
or a teacher
just like me.
I'm sure it will be useful someday.
Thank you, Sir.
What's with the blank look?
Let's practice, okay?
Stop thinking about it.
Come in.
I have a question, Master.
Why did you say the Blue Silver Plant
is not a useless Martial Soul?
You have 15 minutes.
Make it quick.
I have to guard the gate later.
Everyone says Blue Silver Plant
is a useless Martial Soul.
At first,
I think everything
has their features and purpose.
Even the most common
Martial Soul like Blue Silver Plant
is no exception.
But after training
for the past few days,
everyone's Martial Soul has improved.
But my Blue Silver Plant
is no different from the state
when my Martial Soul awakened.
Nothing has changed at all.
There's no useless Martial Soul,
there is only useless man.
Repeat after me.
There's no useless Martial Soul,
there is only useless man.
Speak louder.
There's no useless Martial Soul,
there is only useless man.
Inferior Martial Souls
have been a main topic
in my study.
Blue Silver Plant is one of them.
It's weak
but it does have its strength.
Blue Silver Plant has its strength too?
Have you ever observed
the form of this plant?
Alright. Here's an assignment for you.
Observe the Blue Silver Plant.
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
Ever since my Soul Master awakened,
the power of
Xuan Tian Strike hasn't improved.
Blue Silver Plant is also
just the same as it was.
Tang San.
I knew you are here.
Wang Sheng prepared
some hometown specialties.
Let's have dinner together.
Tang San.
What's so special about it?
Right. What's so special about it?
Yes.
There's nothing special
about Blue Silver Plant
in the first place.
You're a genius, Wu.
You are right.
Blue Silver Plant is too common.
That makes its power to puzzle
greater than any other Martial Souls.
I am satisfied with your answer.
Does it mean that I can get a soul ring
like everybody else?
Can I be a real soul master now?
Based on the analysis
of my study
on Blue Silver Plant,
you can be a Controlling Soul Master.
A Controlling Soul Master...
What's the power of
a Controlling Soul Master?
A Controlling Soul Master
uses his own Martial Soul
to restrict his opponent's movements,
in order to facilitate the attack.
You will learn this
in the class.
What I am going to say
is the theory from my study.
Do you want to hear it?
Come on.
Show me your Martial Soul.
Try to extend it.
I can't.
Empty your mind at all times
and get ready for
Martial Soul Shield Body.
Make it formless and shapeless
like water
and let it flow through your body.
You must coordinate
with your Martial Soul.
Then, it will become your ally.
If you fight it back,
it will become your enemy.
Try to adapt to your Martial Soul.
You must have faith in it.
Because a heart of faith
is your Martial Soul.
Have faith in it and
it will have faith in you.
Then, it will start to grow.
I really made it.
Don't get distracted. Keep doing it.
Other than
the commonality you mentioned earlier,
Blue Silver Plant has
three other strengths.
Firstly,
the usage of Blue Silver Plant
doesn't require much Soul Power.
It's even lesser than
Food Branch Martial Soul.
Therefore, you can use it
as much as you can
with your own Soul Power.
Secondly,
Blue Silver Plant is weak.
So it won't repel
Soul Ring of any other elements.
Thirdly,
I found out that
it's best for Blue Silver Plant
to develop into Controlling Branch.
This is because the plant is flexible.
It can be controlled
and turn into various forms.
The simplest of all,
it can be used as a rope
to tie down your enemy.
What should I do?
What was on your mind?
I got excited.
Think about something else.
I can't.
My mind is blank.
I can't think of anything.
Think about food.
What's your favorite food?
Braised pork belly.
Why isn't it working?
I never had it.
My friends in the village told me that
it's the best food of all.
Do something, Master.
I'm sorry, Master.
I still can't take control of it.
This is common
as you are still exploring.
It's getting late.
Let's continue tomorrow.
I made a mess in your room.
I'll clean them up before I leave.
When you leave,
bring this bottle with you.
What is it?
It's a medicine to treat bruises.
I don't think I need it.
I did it.
Are you okay?
Why are you still up?
What are you doing?
I'm practicing Blue Silver Plant.
So you keep falling
to train your pain tolerance?
No.
Master told me that
a heart of faith is my Martial Soul.
I'm trying to adapt to
my Blue Silver Plant.
But
The teacher told us in the class that
our Martial Soul coexists with us.
We are dependent on each other.
So,
I think
even if your Martial Soul
is awakened late,
it has been there all along.
Why is there a need to adapt to it?
Did Master say it wrongly?
At least with Master's guidance,
my Blue Silver Plant is growing.
I suppose this is a progress.
Training alone must be bored.
How about I train with you?
Okay.
It won't listen to me.
Don't go.
Now I know
why Master
gave me the medicine.
What is it? Is it sweet?
Can I taste it?
Don't simply consume medicine.
I've practiced with you for a long time.
My legs even got swollen.
Look.
Just one sip.
Okay.
It's sweet.
I wonder if my mood will get better
after taking something sweet.
You're not in a good mood?
Wang Sheng
told me over dinner
that they will elect the leader of Soul
Master Association tomorrow afternoon.
I registered as a candidate.
Tell me,
why is the leader elected by an election
and not by fighting?
You find it strange too, right?
Candidates have to prepare
a speech.
What should I talk about?
Actually the election
is not just about electing a leader.
It's about electing someone
who is willing to help others
and someone who is responsible.
As long as you are helpful,
I'm sure you will be elected.
I want to help others too.
Wang Sheng and I
will stand by you.
I'll buy you
a nice dress.
Okay.
Look at the ironsmith shop ahead.
The weapons they make are powerful.
I'm going to...
What is this?
It's sticky rice cake
with carrot filling.
I'll have one then.
How much is it?
Three copper soul coins for one.
You don't have money
but you want to eat.
Watch how I do it.
I'll be done soon.
Don't get too near.
Who taught you this?
My dad.
Uncle San.
Can you give me my wages
for this month
after deducting the cost of the iron?
I'll give you a pay rise.
Thank you, Uncle San.
We have money now. Let's go eat.
You're the best, Tang San.
Let's go.
You have it.
No.
It's okay. You can have it.
Just eat it.
I will eat it, then.
Wu.
This is for you.
What is this?
It's a sleeve arrow.
I invented it and...
It's a secret weapon.
A secret weapon?
It's amazing, isn't it?
How do I use it?
It's simple. Let me show you.
Look.
Just push the button here
and the little arrow inside
will be shot.
I love this gadget.
Let me put it on you.
Okay.
Rest assured, Wu.
There's a safety device here.
It won't hurt you.
Wu.
Put your hand down.
What's the matter?
Remember,
don't use it
on people anyhow.
Don't worry.
I won't use it
unless it's necessary.
Move aside.
Get out of the way.
Get up.
Are you okay, Ma'am?
My sticky rice cake.
Get up, Ma'am.
Get up.
Move aside.
Who are these people?
How could they leave
after they hit someone?
Have a seat, Ma'am.
My sticky rice cake.
Wu.
My stall is destroyed.
The governor of Nuoding City,
Xiao Chen Yu's father.
The governor?
A governor doesn't have
to apologize after hitting somebody?
He doesn't have to.
You told me that
the governor is more than just a salutation.
It's a status.
That's right.
What status is that?
He was born to be a governor.
It's hereditary.
But it's unfair.
One should achieve possession and power
with one's strength.
How could someone be born with it?
I don't quite understand, either.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination
is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways and
we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as
another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break
ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways and
we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as
another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break
ordinary rules in life♪