Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 5
Are you okay?
It hurts.
What happened?
Brother Tang.
You are really full of surprises.
Which one of you hit Wu?
It was me
You have a problem?
What do you both want?
This is the President
of the Soul Master Association.
Controlling Crane Catching Dragon.
How dare you...
Young Master.
I came here to hunt for a Soul Beast.
My guards tend to be
a little more nervous.
Coincidentally,
these trees were swaying,
so they thought it was an attack
by a Soul Beast
and made a move.
I never thought
I'd see you both here.
Miss Wu.
I apologize on his behalf.
We're not done
with yesterday's incident.
So, you were hiding in the forest.
No wonder I couldn't find you.
You were looking for me?
That's amazing.
I'm lacking for a pet rabbit
at home.
You...
He has advanced successfully.
We are very different
in terms of ability.
Let me handle this.
I was thinking that this must be fate.
Don't you think so, Brother Tang?
Young Master.
How did you know I was going
to make a move, Brother Tang?
People would normally ask me
where I got the warrant from.
How did we get
into the Soul Hunting Forest?
That's right.
I came here for the both of you.
What sort of grudge
do you have against us?
Nothing.
This is about
you embarrassing me
in front of others time and time again.
That was very rude.
Honestly speaking,
I've looked past it.
It wasn't anything serious.
But,
you were going against me
in front of everyone.
If I don't
teach you a lesson,
I'm afraid...
more people are going
to lose their respect for me.
Am I right?
No, I would not dare.
You want to go against me?
You'd have to pay the price.
Am I right?
Actually, I don't have a choice.
You have to forgive me!
What do you want?
You should know.
Hand over the girl.
And you
join my Martial Club.
What do you think?
Isn't that great?
Yes. Yes. Yes.
This Spotted Cat is badly injured.
You just got your Soul Ring.
You won't be able to advance anyhow.
They are useless to you.
Yes.
Everyone knows
it is very challenging
to catch a Soul Beast.
But,
it's really easy to catch a young one.
Especially when the mother
is dying.
Liu Long.
Teach Brother Tang San here
and this little sister
some manners.
You...
What modesty is.
All right.
All right?
Everyone else,
get the young beast alive!
Remember, I want it alive!
What Soul Beast is this?
Young Master, be careful.
Stop!
Young Master!
This forest is really large,
so both of you'd better follow me closely.
Don't get lost.
Thank you, Master.
You don't have to thank me.
This is just a deal.
The Spotted Cat is still there.
We have to come up with a way to help them.
No.
Why?
The time is not right.
Let's put up a fight then.
The winner gets to decide.
Young lady.
You don't just use your fist in a fight.
You've got to use your brain too.
Even if you can get past me,
how are you going to deal with
Xiao Chen Yu and the rest?
What about the Thorn Apple Snake?
Where is this Thorn Apple Snake from?
I think it came along with Luo San Pao.
According to the traces left on the fight scene,
I can determine that the Spotted Cat
was bitten by the Thorn Apple Snake.
Then, I found
the nest of the Thorn Apple Snake
and got Luo San Pao to provoke it.
That's how the Thorn Apple Snake came.
No wonder Spotted Cat
was injured severely.
It was injured
and even poisoned by the Thorn Apple Snake.
Thorn Apple Snake is poisonous?
That's the snake poison's numbing effect.
Based on its pattern,
this Thorn Apple Snake
is about 400 years old.
It's the most suitable choice
for your Soul Ring.
Tang San's Martial Soul is Blue Silver Plant.
What does it have to do with snakes?
Blue Silver Plant is an exception.
As a Plant Branch Martial Soul,
Blue Silver Plant may be weak in strength,
but its mild nature and non-exclusivity
could be out of the norm
and let it assimilate
any ability of Martial Soul
and turn that into its own.
This is the Theory of Martial Soul Mimicry.
Based on my theory,
this snake suits you best.
Has your theory been proven before?
Few people chose to believe me.
I trust you.
At Nuoding School,
your guidance was really helpful to me.
My Blue Silver Plant
could grow and withdraw freely.
Tang San, don't listen to him.
That was the result of your talent
and effort in training.
Don't forget that this deal
is to prove
that my theory is right.
If you kill the Thorn Apple Snake,
its Martial Soul
will definitely be stronger
than other ordinary Soul Masters.
Thorn Apple Snake is invulnerable...
With Xiao Chen Yu and his men,
we could exhaust
the Thorn Apple Snake's power.
We just have to wait
for them to exhaust themselves in the battle.
Retreat. Quick!
Young Master.
Try harder and we can kill it.
That's too great a loss.
Tang San might be waiting
for us to suffer.
Retreat.
Retreat!
They got away.
Go after the snake!
Let's take a look at the mother cat.
It's about to die.
That cat is no help to you.
I...
Even if we hurry there right now,
we can't defeat Xiao Chen Yu
and his guards.
Look out!
Take a look at Master.
He's poisoned.
Kill it.
My theory can't be wrong.
Leave me alone.
Kill the snake.
Ghostly Trace!
Purple Demon Eye!
How is Master doing?
It's just a minor scratch.
The poison is mild. He will be fine.
All right.
Yellow. More than 100 years.
If Master is right,
it's the Soul Ring of about 400 years old.
It suits me best.
That's a theory he came up on his own,
how could you believe that?
I think Master wouldn't harm me.
You saw it too.
This snake was coming for me,
and Master defended me.
He saved me.
But what if he is wrong?
With a Soul Beast that is too strong,
you are likely to fail to advance.
This is a deal.
He did help me.
It's all about the deal.
All this Master has said
along the way is about the deal.
What if you die?
My understanding of a deal
is exchanging herbs for Soul Coins.
This is fair.
But your deal with Master
is that you have to prove his theory
at your own peril.
I'm not considering
the consequences and risks in the future.
All I know is
that Xiao Chen Yu has many guards.
If I have no way
to get the strongest Soul Ring,
I'll not be able to beat them
and protect you.
For someone like Xiao Chen Yu,
even if it weren't for you,
I'd be going against them too.
You killed the Thorn Apple Snake
to fight me?
You're so good.
It means that you see me
as a worthy opponent.
Is that right, Brother Tang San?
I have no other options.
I wish what Master said is right.
It's really hot.
-Something went into my hand.
-Tang San.
Hold on.
Tang San.
He is overconfident.
Since you won't listen to me,
I'll let you kill yourself.
Take him away.
You...
Aren't you the one
doing chores at school?
You're helping them?
Get away? How can they get away?
Break wind like striking thunder.
What did you say?
Rumble the heavens and split the earth.
I guess he has gone nuts.
Luo San Pao!
Run!
Young Master.
Catch him.
Brother Tang!
I will wait for you at the school.
If I don't see you
before sunset tomorrow,
I will chop off his head on a charge
of attacking the son of the Governor!
Tang San.
You're awake. How are you feeling?
I made it.
I have my very first Soul Ring.
Although there was a lot of pain
throughout the process,
I didn't feel any kind of rejection.
What about right now?
I feel energized all over my body,
and my body feels lighter
and comfortable.
Although your Martial Soul is of a plant type,
you are able to absorb
the Soul Ring of a beast type.
It seems like what Master said is true.
Master can be trusted!
Where is Master?
The snake poison got worse?
Xiao Chen Yu caught Master.
That...
But,
while you were
absorbing the Soul Ring just now,
I found
the antidote for
the Thorn Apple Snake's poison.
I saved the mother cat.
Vermillion Lotus can cure
the Thorn Apple Snake's poison.
We have it in our village too.
Xiao Chen Yu said he would
be waiting for you at the school.
If you don't show up
by sunset tomorrow,
they'll kill Master.
By sunset tomorrow?
Why were you helping Tang San?
I told you. It was just a deal.
You've discovered
a new Theory of Martial Soul.
Do you think I would believe that?
It's up to you.
I don't care.
Do you want to die?
Fine.
Young Master.
Do you think we can ask Headmaster
to get them...
No. No.
Your uncle.
Ask your uncle, Headmaster,
to get them expelled.
I can't make the decision.
But matters regarding students,
as the President of
the Soul Master Association,
I still have a say in this.
We said we were going
to wait for Tang San at school,
we can't break our word.
He will not come.
Liu Long.
Young Master.
Inform the Office of Administration
that the Soul Master Association
is having an event tomorrow,
and the school will be closed.
No one is allowed to stay in the school.
All right.
After that,
bring me the documents
about Tang San and Wu.
I want to take a look.
Young Master.
This Tang San
dared to absorb the Soul Ring
of the Thorn Apple Snake.
I guess he is probably dead by now.
If he isn't dead,
how powerful can he be?
This... This is impossible.
Moreover, this weird Master
isn't related to Tang San.
Even if he survives,
will he come here for someone like him?
Liu Long.
What kind of person
do you think Tang San is?
I think he is a good man.
Yes. A good man.
A good man would definitely come back.
Go.
As detailed as the documents can be.
All right.
I'll go now.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Blue Silver Plant got bigger and wider.
The changes are quite big.
It seems a lot tougher than before.
What about the Soul Skill?
How do you do a Soul Skill?
Focusing on the Soul Ring will do.
You did it!
It is gone.
Is it possible that there are no special skills
even after Blue Silver Plant
got a Soul Ring?
There is another possibility.
Your Soul Skill
can only be used on humans.
But I can't go around
to get someone to try it either.
Try it on me.
It is numb!
How is it?
It is poison.
Your first Soul Skill
inherited the poison
from the Thorn Apple Snake.
Any wounds? Is it bad?
Do you need an antidote?
It should be a temporary paralysis.
Your Blue Silver Plant
can't possibly have poisonous fangs.
Are you really all right?
When I'm injured in the future,
it might help alleviate the pain too.
Don't say that.
As long as I'm around,
I won't let you get hurt.
So, your first Soul Skill is mild poison?
I think it is the constraint.
First Soul Skill, Constraint?
Sounds a little common.
The name isn't important.
What are we going to do next?
Rescue Master at the school?
Actually,
I'm not very close to Master.
Moreover, Xiao Chen Yu
is the son of the Governor of Nuoding City.
He has many guards.
Isn't it suicidal
for us to go back like that?
I'm the boss.
I can help you.
You?
You don't even have a Soul Ring.
How are you going to help me?
Moreover, it's just the two of us.
Xiao Chen Yu must have set some traps.
What are we going to do?
We will go our separate ways here.
The school is definitely not an option.
You should go home.
Remember.
Don't ever come back
to Nuoding City anymore.
What about you?
Me?
I'll return to the Saint of Soul Village.
I need your help.
Young Master!
Young Master.
There is finally news
from Martial Soul Hall.
Say it.
Martial Soul...
They said
Officer Su Yun Tao from Martial Soul Hall
wasn't close
to Tang San.
But I heard
Su Yun Tao was the one
who helped Tang San
with his Martial Soul Awakening.
He also
took the latter seriously.
I understand.
Take a look at this.
Wu's letter of recommendation?
Wu was initially
arranged to live in Dorm Seven.
These people
at the Office of Administration
had a problem?
Having a girl live in the dorm for males?
Go and investigate
who wrote Wu's letter of recommendation.
And the entire process in this matter.
Check it out.
Sure.
Young Master.
What about Martial Soul Hall?
The fact that Su Yun Tao admires Tang San
is actually a good thing.
Good thing.
Bring Wang Sheng here.
What does this have to do with Wang Sheng?
All right. I'll go now.
Why did you come back?
We're going to save him together.
You don't have a Soul Ring.
It is too dangerous.
Century Soul Ring?
How did you do that?
When did you become a Soul Master?
Right after you left.
I knew you wanted to save him on your own.
So,
I can't be a burden on you.
Which Soul Beast did you kill then?
I just killed a random one.
A random one?
Anyway,
I have a Soul Ring now.
What is your Soul Skill then?
Watch this.
All right.
A stronger waist.
I call it Arched Body.
You two...
You are rescuing him?
Master was caught by Xiao Chen Yu?
No wonder
the school is closed tomorrow.
You shouldn't act rashly
because there are guards
from the City Main Office
all over the school.
It will be easier if we know
where Master is locked,
but the school is really big,
with many guards there.
It's not easy.
What should I do?
You're a student.
The guards will not take notice of you.
If you discover
any heavily guarded places,
don't barge in.
Come back to tell Wu and me.
All right.
I'll ask everyone
to look around tomorrow.
Great. Thank you.
How am I suppose
to get in touch with you tomorrow?
School entrance.
See you by the spring.
All right.
You should go.
Actually, I really envy you
that you can go against Xiao Chen Yu.
We don't want to be his enemies,
but he doesn't want to let us go.
He is here.
Master is locked up
in the practice court.
Are you sure?
I saw it.
All right then.
Thank you.
How about I join you both to rescue him?
It's fine.
We're really grateful to you.
You should hurry and leave this place.
It's fine.
We know what to do.
Amazing.
Master.
We're here to save you.
You're awake.
Go! It's a trap!
It's fine. I can just bend it.
Don't touch the cage!
Wu!
I was thinking.
If I were you,
I'd ask for help.
But who should I ask?
First of all,
this person has to be a close friend.
Next, he has to be someone
who doesn't like me.
After all,
he is the only suitable one.
I'm sorry, Brother San.
He captured my father.
I have to cooperate with him.
Come on.
Century Soul Ring?
We really made it!
Yes.
Your theory has been proven.
Great.
You really got
the power from the Soul Ring
of the Thorn Apple Snake.
But, don't be nervous.
If we had wanted to hurt you,
we could have caught you last night
when you were looking for Wang Sheng.
I went all the way to get Wang Sheng
to lead you to the practice court.
Then, I purposely
set this cage up
just to avoid a fight with you,
so we could have a good discussion.
Avoid a fight?
You think I'd believe you?
The situation is different now.
Martial Soul Hall has confirmed
that Su Yun Tao admires you.
You know Su Yun Tao's identity?
Officer of Martial Soul Hall.
There are thousands of officers
in Martial Soul Hall.
It isn't a great position.
But Su Yun Tao is different
because
he is a direct disciple
of the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
Brother Tang.
You don't know
about the chief of Martial Soul Hall?
Let me explain it to him then.
Martial Soul Hall
is all over Douluo Continent.
There are many talented people
and different Clans that are powerful.
You should know this.
The person who leads Martial Soul Hall
is the chief, Her Majesty.
Everyone calls her
Head of All, Lord of the Endless.
Her power
is above the Sovereign of the Empire.
So...
So, I think
we can actually become friends.
I can release Wu
and return her to you too.
Moreover,
didn't Wu want to be
the President of
the Soul Master Association?
I can fulfill it.
For me,
I'm only asking for a small favour.
That is,
introduce Su Yun Tao to me.
You want to join Marital Soul Hall?
A janitor like you
has quite a bit of sense too.
That's right.
Martial Soul Hall
is very influential right now.
Even if I inherit my father's position,
I'll just be
a little Governor of Nuoding City.
What do you think, Brother Tang?
Release her first.
I can't release her for now.
When I finally see Su Yun Tao,
I'll release her.
Release her!
How about...
How about this?
I can hand Wang Sheng over to you.
You can do as you wish.
Wang Sheng.
Actually,
I was going to take my time
to make you obey me.
But I thought about it.
Since I captured your father
and threatened you,
you might hold a grudge
against me in the future.
So,
once you're dead,
I'll send your father to accompany you.
Xiao Chen Yu!
What do you say, Brother Tang?
If you can't do it yourself,
I can help you out.
I can do you a favour.
This has nothing to do with him.
Release Wu.
You're really protecting her.
Do you know
she is actually a liar?
Give me.
This is Wu's letter of recommendation
from the Gujie Village.
I checked it.
This letter of recommendation
was originally given by our school
to a young man
in the Gujie Village.
So,
the arrangement
a dorm for males.
It seems like
she didn't tell you about this.
If you had asked me,
I would have told you.
Cheating and stealing.
Would you believe the words
of someone like that?
I would not.
I didn't steal.
I bought this letter with Gold Soul Coins!
Tell me then.
How many Gold Soul Coins it took?
About a few dozens.
He took the Gold Soul Coins
and said
he could go to a better school.
He was quite happy.
A few dozens of Gold Soul Coins
could definitely get him
to the best Soul Master School
in the Capital.
Why didn't you go there yourself?
Why would you want a recommendation letter
just to come to our Nuoding Beginner School?
Why should I tell you?
Look.
You can't explain it anymore, right?
Brother Tang.
That's the truth.
She is
nothing but a malicious liar!
Let her go.
You are really giving me a headache.
Your personality
makes you really hard to talk to, right?
Let me put it this way.
I'll make it clear.
You have no choice.
Even if you beat us all,
they can't get out!
I don't think so!
Don't move, Wu!
Wu!
Have you made up your mind?
I just have to take you to Su Yun Tao?
That's right.
You let us go after that?
Of course
not.
All the Governors and Martial Soul Hall
appear united,
but they're actually not on the same team.
I can't let the news
about my intention to join
Martial Soul Hall spread out.
Look.
Everyone here is my guard.
My people.
He is different
because
he is going to be a dead man in a while.
As for you,
you're going to be my confidant
after this whole thing.
I don't have any intentions to join you.
That's not up to you.
Also,
don't even think about escaping
because
I've investigated you.
You're from the Saint of Soul Village.
Your father is
a blacksmith.
Don't worry.
In the future,
I'll bring your father to Nuoding City.
He won't have to worry
about his life anymore.
As for you,
you don't have
to work at the ironsmith shop,
getting hard-earned money.
Think about it.
It is a good thing.
Wu!
Are you crazy?
The person who set this cage
is a Soul Honour.
A Soul Honour.
He is a genius with three Soul Rings.
Even if you choose
to electrocute yourself,
you'll have no way of escaping.
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'm going to save you.
What are you trying to do?
I told you.
This is the power of a Soul Honour.
You... Brother Tang.
You're a smart guy, aren't you?
You have only one option right now.
Why are you hesitating?
I won't take the option you gave me.
In that case,
there are no other options.
Then, I'll just have to make my own way.
You fool! What are you doing?
It is useless!
Martial Soul can't stand it either.
Tang San!
Don't be afraid.
I'll get you out soon.
Let go!
Your Martial Soul will be ruined
if you continue!
Let go!
Without blood and sweat,
how can I make a way of my own?
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪