Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles and
reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
Douluo Continent
Episode 4
What status?
He was born to be the Governor.
It's hereditary.
But it's unfair.
Everyone should gain dominions and power
with one's own strength.
How could someone be born with it?
I don't quite understand either
Wu,
the Soul Master Association's election
will be held this afternoon, right?
I think so.
Stop picking things up. Let's go.
With the sleeve arrow,
I'm invincible!
Be careful.
What's wrong?
What took you so long?
What is it?
The election is over.
Isn't it supposed
to be held in the afternoon?
Young Master Xiao
brought the election forward
to this morning.
They outnumbered others,
and he is now the President
of the Soul Master Association.
This is the new timetable
for sponsored students.
Look.
He's obviously targeting both of you.
From now on,
not only do you need
to work in the afternoon,
but also in the morning.
If this continues,
you will have no time for class.
You can't attend Soul Power training,
so you won't have a chance to advance.
It's fine.
We can sneak in the class.
No, Brother San.
Nuoding City and the School
are under the control of the Xiao family.
You can't fight against them.
How about this?
Both of you run away.
Why should we run away?
Young Master Xiao is
more terrifying than he looks.
He will do anything.
It sounds like you know him very well.
Look.
Who did this?
My dad works in the mine.
It belongs to the Governor.
On the day my Martial Soul awakened,
Young Master Xiao asked his men
to beat me up.
I got no Soul Skill.
There was nothing I could do.
He told me to bear in mind
that even if I become a Soul Master,
I still belong to Nuoding City
and the Xiao family.
Drink this.
Your wounds will heal quickly.
It's fine, Brother San.
The wounds were caused by Martial Soul.
They are harder to heal,
and they can't be treated
by ordinary medications.
Don't worry.
If that jerk beats you again,
come over and tell me.
Sister Wu will protect you.
We can't let the election
slide so easily.
I'll go to the Soul Master Association now.
Keep an eye on it.
Don't let anyone come in.
Even the Soul Master
from the City Main Office is here.
Again.
I'm counting on you.
Who is it?
Hurry up!
Adapt to your Martial Soul.
You must have faith in it.
Because the heart of faith
is indeed your Martial Soul.
The heart of faith is the Martial Soul.
Is it reliable?
Of course.
Officer Ling Feng did it himself.
There won't be any problem.
Don't worry.
Young Master.
It's Ghost Wolf.
It's the most suitable Soul Beast for you.
Officer Ling Feng
had it under control.
You only need to kill it.
What is the white circle?
Too bad, it's just a white Soul Ring.
If this Soul Beast is
more than a hundred years old,
it's easy to kill,
but hard to capture.
You're right.
What about Martial Soul Hall?
We'll get an update soon.
Tang San is just a bumpkin.
There's no way that he is connected
to Martial Soul Hall.
Make things clear before you carry on.
Okay.
You did it.
Young Master, you did it.
Finally, I'm a real Soul Master.
Tang San,
I'm going to teach you a lesson soon.
What colour was it?
White.
A white Soul Ring?
It's less than a hundred years old.
If what you said is true,
as Xiao Chen Yu hates you so much,
he hasn't done anything to you
because you were recommended
by Martial Soul Hall.
That's why he is being cautious.
I have nothing to do with
Martial Soul Hall.
He will find this out soon.
What are you going to do then?
What was he doing?
Obtaining a Soul Ring
marks the beginning
of the practice of a Soul Master.
Why did he have to kill it in person?
The Soul Master
must kill a Soul Beast
with his final hit
to absorb its Soul Ring.
I guess his father's men
captured it for him.
Actually, what he wants is Wu alone.
You should stay away from it
and don't get involved.
Thanks for telling me these things.
There's one last option for you.
I can help you to get a Soul Ring
and become a real Soul Master.
Wait for me here tonight.
Why are you helping me?
It's a deal,
so you'll have to help me too.
What can I do for you?
You'll know that later.
If you really want to protect that girl,
remember,
tonight will be your only chance.
The School is just an illusion.
The life of a Soul Master
is full of blood and danger,
along with endless exciting things
to be discovered by you.
Are you ready to welcome
this whole new world with me?
Why are you helping me?
A Soul Master shouldn't get used to slaughters.
The strong must protect the weak.
Your philosophy differs from the others.
To be honest, it's quite silly.
I know.
But that's what I believe.
They say I'm silly too.
Well, I guess fools should work together.
Come with me.
Let's look for
your Soul Ring together.
Look, it's not bad.
Boss, look at this.
This is nice.
Ten silver soul coins.
Right.
The craftsmanship is bad.
Master, what are we waiting for?
Wait for them to close.
Why?
In order to help you obtain your Soul Ring,
we need to capture a Soul Beast.
To look for a wild Soul Beast
near Nuoding City,
we can only go
to the Soul Hunting Forest.
What does it have to do with the shop?
The Soul Hunting Forest
is guarded by Law Enforcement Corps
of Martial Soul Hall.
We can't enter
without a clearance warrant.
Martial Soul Hall dominates the forest.
The forests where most Soul Beasts live
are guarded by Martial Soul Hall.
There are many Grand Soul Land Masters
in Martial Soul Hall.
They are powerful,
especially the current chief of
Martial Soul Hall.
She is known as the greatest Soul Master.
What is the chief's name?
Her name is
Bi Bi...
Anyway, everyone calls her chief.
They won't call her by her name.
We need to get the clearance warrant
in order to enter the Soul Hunting Forest.
So, Martial Soul Hall owns this shop?
No.
But we can get
the clearance warrant here.
Why do we have to wait
for the shop to close?
The warrants here are ill-gotten,
so they can't sell it openly.
It's almost time.
Master,
is the warrant expensive?
I know you're poor.
I'll pay you back.
I'm working in an ironsmith shop.
I can earn seven to eight
silver soul coins per month.
It's too late.
Thank you in advance.
I'll pay you back
when I've saved enough money.
There's no need to thank me.
I don't have money either.
How are we supposed to buy it then?
You haven't seen
my Martial Soul, have you?
No.
This is my Martial Soul,
Luo San Pao.
Well...
Is this a Tool Soul or a Beast Soul?
Neither.
It is a Mutant Soul.
I can't believe
that it has mutated into a pig.
It's a dog.
It can run outside your body.
Isn't your Tool Soul, Blue Silver Plant,
staying outside your body as well?
So there are three types of Martial Soul,
Tool Soul, Beast Soul,
and Mutant Soul.
The formation can be divided
into two types,
within the body
and outside the body.
You're good at summarizing
and studious.
Practice makes perfect.
I have so much to learn.
We're closed.
A deal for the Soul Hunting Forest.
We want to get in there.
One hundred gold soul coins.
One hundred gold soul coins?
Are you robbing us?
A clearance warrant
from Martial Soul Hall is hard to get.
Take it or leave it.
We don't have money.
Get lost.
But I have a living Soul Beast.
One gold soul coin is worth
ten silver soul coins,
which are worth
a hundred copper soul coins.
It's enough for
my dad and me to use
for several months in the Saint of Soul Village.
A Soul Beast is worth
a hundred gold soul coins.
Soul Beasts are extremely proud.
They would blow themselves up
if they lose in a battle,
so a living Soul Beast is priceless.
Didn't they capture a living Soul Beast
for Xiao Chen Yu to get his Soul Ring?
It was stunned by some special means.
He's the son of the Governor.
They have resources and men,
yet they could only capture
a Ghost Wolf
that's less than a hundred years old.
It's very difficult to capture
a living Soul Beast.
But the one you used to trade
for this warrant,
it's not a Soul Beast.
It's your Martial Soul.
He can't tell.
Mutant Souls are rare.
Can you get your dog back?
I can take it back anytime.
We were lying to him.
Why do you think
I asked you to walk faster?
That's not good.
Hurry up.
This is the Soul Hunting Forest.
Look.
Law Enforcement Corps from Martial Soul Hall.
That's a Soul Honour
who has got his third Soul Ring.
He's strong.
If anyone tries to break into
or sneak into the forest,
it's almost impossible to succeed.
I understand it.
All I want to know is,
why did you tell me
to carry so many radishes?
That's for Luo San Pao.
Luo San Pao?
Isn't Luo San Pao a dog?
It eats radishes as well?
It's related to its means of attack.
Come, let's go.
Wait.
What are these for?
Dog food.
Fine, fine, enter.
There's no time limit.
Life and death are your own business.
I guess he ran away.
It's not a bad thing.
Staying here would do him no good.
Make way.
I don't think he ran away.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Whose baggage is this?
Brother San's.
Thank you.
Your father is doing fine lately.
The guards are
staying with him every day.
They're monitoring his every move.
If anything happens,
we'll inform you immediately.
Wang Sheng,
study hard.
So when you return to your family,
all of you can come together again.
Right?
Boo!
Anyway,
thank you
for helping me to take the first step.
Don't mention it. It's just a deal.
Absorbing the Soul Ring from the Soul Beast
is a transformation of energy.
There's a limit to the Soul Master's capacity
to withstand the Soul Ring.
I think I've heard of this.
I read it in a book at school.
There's a precise number for the limit.
For example,
if a person wants to get
his first Soul Ring like you,
the age limit of the Soul Beast
to be hunted is 423 years old.
The closer it is to that limit,
the more obvious
your improvement would be.
But if it exceeds the age limit,
your body won't be able to contain it,
and then you will fail to advance.
Four hundred and twenty-three years old.
It's not mentioned in the book.
It's calculated theoretically.
Amazing.
But how do we know
how old the Soul Beast is?
Luo San Pao's sense of smell
is extraordinary.
It can tell its opponent's
strengths and weaknesses.
With its guidance,
we can find you
the most suitable Soul Beast.
Young Master.
The Governor mentioned
that the Soul Hunting Forest is dangerous.
You can't go there in person.
Do you know the reason
why a family would decline?
They take away the rights
of their descendants
to move forward
in the name of protection.
If they always protect their descendants,
it will only make them weak.
Well, what if Tang San and the others
have really run away?
Liu Long.
Didn't you notice his eyes?
What is it?
People like him
will never run away
before being crushed completely.
Why don't we check again?
There are people who saw him leave the city,
but we can't confirm
that he went to the Soul Hunting Forest.
I've cut off
all the assistance
from the school to him.
Under the circumstances,
if it were me,
I would be left with only one choice,
which is to kill a Soul Beast
and obtain a Soul Ring.
He's no match for you.
I never belittle my opponent.
Back at the school,
everyone was watching.
I would look bad if I hurt him.
But now it's different.
I will track him down
and destroy his pride and hope
with my own hands.
I will snatch his girl away
and crush him.
That's more interesting.
But we haven't
confirmed his relationship
with Martial Soul Hall.
I'm not going to kill him.
I only want to make him give in.
Here you go.
Thank you, Master.
Get some rest.
We'll depart after Luo San Pao
has enough rest.
Master, we didn't get very far.
It gets tired easily.
It's not moving at all.
Did it pass out?
It is actually awake.
This...
Luo San Pao is a Martial Soul.
Yet it can eat too?
This is indeed a way to get energy.
So, maintaining it
consumes little of my Soul Power.
Here, San Pao.
Have a radish.
San Pao.
Why isn't it eating?
Have you ever seen
a dog that likes eating radishes?
Then why did you
make me bring so many radishes?
Be careful!
Luo San Pao!
Break wind like striking thunder,
rumble the heavens and split the earth!
Ghost Wolf.
White Soul Ring.
It's less than a hundred years old.
The same Soul Ring appeared
after Xiao Chen Yu
killed the Ghost Wolf.
What is this ring exactly?
It is just a kind of energy.
Soul Ring of a Decade Soul Beast
is white in colour.
Soul Ring of a Century Soul Beast
is yellow in colour.
That of a Millennium Soul Beast
is purple in colour.
Soul Ring of a Decade Millennium Soul Beast
is black in colour.
Soul Ring of a Century Millennium Soul Beast
is red in colour.
A hundred thousand years.
Is it possible
for a Soul Beast to live that long?
If you have the chance
to go to the Star Forest,
you might see one
if you're lucky.
I killed it.
Others can never absorb it.
Aren't you going to absorb it?
What a waste.
My Martial Soul is ruined.
It's meaningless for me.
Why did the corpse
and Soul Ring disappear?
Generally, if the Soul Master
doesn't absorb it,
the Soul Ring and the corpse
will disappear within two hours.
This Ghost Wolf
was less than a hundred years old.
That's why it disappeared soon.
Do you absorb the Soul Ring
by touching it with your hands?
You'd better start your Martial Soul first.
You'll need it when you absorb the Soul Ring.
San Pao did a great job.
Why did you say it was ruined?
We're merely making a deal.
I don't have to explain it to you.
It was San Pao's Soul Skill, right?
It was amazing.
It...
It just looked a bit...
Right.
Its means of attack
is quite special.
Indeed.
Didn't you say it didn't eat radishes?
Luo San Pao can only launch three attacks.
After that,
it needs to rely on radishes
to replenish its energy.
Only the radish?
It's the most effective one.
Tang San.
Wu?
You're from the City Main Office.
Please go in.
Excuse me.
Has anyone else gone inside today?
Yes.
Was he about my age?
More or less.
Were they a man and a woman?
Are you done?
Do you want to enter or not?
Be care of your attitude!
Last question.
They're still inside, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
Come out first.
So this is San Pao?
It's chubby and adorable.
Is it because it can only
launch three attacks
that it's called San Pao?
But it's weird.
Why is it a pig?
It is a dog.
Wu.
Why did you follow us here?
Well, that's because you didn't ask me
to come along.
But why were you in the basket?
When you bought the radishes,
the boss was moving
the baskets at the back,
so I sneaked in.
I'm smart, right?
That's not the point now.
We're in the Soul Hunting Forest.
There are Soul Beasts everywhere.
Do you know how dangerous it is?
Well, I'm already here.
You can't tell me
to go home alone, can you?
Can we send her
out of this place first?
It's easy to go out.
But how do we get
another warrant to come here again?
I'll follow you,
and I'll run if I'm in danger.
The most powerful part
of a rabbit is its legs.
I can run really fast.
I have the sleeve arrow as well.
I promise I won't cause you trouble.
Young Master.
Look at his attitude.
If you hadn't stopped me,
I would have used Black Tiger Heart Digging
on him.
They are Law Enforcement Corps
from Martial Soul Hall.
Do you dare to attack them?
Martial Soul Hall is too much.
It's like
they own the Soul Hunting Forest!
Besides, they're just a Sect.
How dare they treat you
so disrespectfully?
Liu Long.
Remember.
You can only be domineering
if you're strong.
Yes, yes.
Young Master.
Young Master,
there's a wheel track here.
It goes that way.
Entering the forest with a trolley.
I wonder who gave them the warrant.
There's no hurry.
We have time to question them
when we catch them.
Follow it.
Sure.
Are you hungry?
We only have radishes here.
We don't have time.
Why?
We need to run.
Run?
What do you want to do?
I heard
you killed a Ghost Wolf.
Right.
Ghost Wolfs live in packs
in the forest!
A pack of Ghost Wolfs.
It'll be tough.
Run!
It's impossible to escape.
Let's fight them.
We have to distract them.
Who will do it?
Luo San Pao.
Okay.
Let's change...
Tang San.
What are you doing?
I overheard your conversation.
He was lying to you.
He lied? What did he lie about?
He said 423 years
was the age limit
for the first Soul Ring.
There's no such theory.
How do you know?
I've read all the theoretical books
in the school library.
Do you know?
An advanced Soul Master once said
that if your first Soul Ring
came from a Soul Beast
that's more than 300 years old,
you would fail to advance for sure.
Maybe he wanted me
to challenge the limit.
If you fail to advance,
it would cause severe injury or death.
Master was obviously trying to harm you.
If that's the case,
he could just hand me
to Xiao Chen Yu.
All he wants to do
is to validate his theory.
He doesn't care
if this method
would cause you harm or not.
No.
I've thought about it.
His plan for my Blue Silver Plant
is right
and reasonable.
Do you really want to get a Soul Ring?
Xiao Chen Yu has advanced.
I'm running out of time.
Are you going to kill a Soul Beast
even if it doesn't harm you?
I don't want to.
But for all these years,
this is what the Soul Masters
have been doing.
Okay.
Let's find a fierce, evil Soul Beast.
Then it will be alright.
A fierce, evil one?
I think it's Earth Rat. It's adorable.
Let's get another one.
I've always wanted to ask you.
Why are you
so fond of reading theoretical books?
I came to the school to figure out
the essence of Martial Soul.
Have you figured it out?
Not yet, it's complicated.
It takes time.
What is it again?
The territory of Ghost Wolfs.
The interesting thing is,
almost all Soul Beasts
have avoided that place.
How do you know?
We didn't see any Soul Beasts along the way.
I saw their tracks.
And there's the odor.
It's obvious.
How can you tell all these?
I grew up in a forest.
Let's go.
I'm sure there's something huge.
Here.
What is it?
The tracks of Soul Beasts.
You can even notice them.
It's ahead of us.
It seems like
it was torn by something.
Two Soul Beasts fought each other.
It was an intense fight.
Both of them might be injured.
It's Spotted Cat.
Its claw attack is very strong.
It seems to be injured.
Can I use it
as my first Soul Ring?
Although it's injured,
it's still very strong.
Not to mention that you have no Soul Skill.
Let's give it a try.
Purple Demon Eye.
That's so pitiable.
Aren't you going to kill it?
Forget it.
The forest is large.
We'll find another one.
Great.
You don't want me to kill it?
Why didn't you stop me?
If I stop you
just because I like cats,
it'll be unfair to you.
I can't
just ask for anything I want.
Next time, you can tell me
whatever you want.
I saw that your eyes were
glowing purple just now.
Was that the power of your Martial Soul?
Sort of.
That was pretty.
But,
isn't Blue Silver Plant blue in colour?
Why was there purple light?
The cat must have passed out
because of excessive blood loss.
Its wound is still bleeding.
The injury must be severe.
Tang San, are you in a hurry
to look for a Soul Beast?
Do you want to save it?
If we don't save the mother,
the kitten is going to die too.
But how do we save them?
I'll look around.
I guess there are herbs
that can stop the bleeding.
I'll be back soon.
I'll go with you.
You don't know what it looks like.
Stay here and keep an eye on them.
I'll be back soon.
You even know what kind of herb
can stop the bleeding?
It's because I grew up in the wild.
I'll get you some fruit on my way back.
Okay, hurry back.
I'll wait for you here.
Okay.
Wu!
Are you okay?
It hurts.
What happened?
Brother Tang.
What a surprise.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination
is where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways and
we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as
another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break
ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways and
we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide, take it as
another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break
ordinary rules in life♪