Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 6]
Recently, it's true that some bad things have happened at Ling Group.
Thank you for all your trust in me.
I will definitely take on the responsibility of the president.
Lead Ling Group to the future.
I do not agree!
- It's Ling Yue!
- Yeah, it's him.
- It's really Ling Yue!
- It's second brother!
Dad, he is alive.
Second brother, you're really back.
You scared us!
Father.
There's not a big problem with your leg, right?
No. The doctor said some rest will do.
You just said... you do not agree.
Exactly.
Everyone thinks it's good. Your opinion is useless.
Aren't I right, little brother?
There's enough supporters of me here.
Your disapproval is useless. You can't take me down.
My little brother, broke his leg,
and even broke his head. This is laughable.
Why did you just day that you do not agree?
Because this kind of business is destined to lose money.
Funds cannot be returned. Not only is it a failed plan,
in the end, it will also affect the development of the head office.
What nonsense are you talking about?
- You're just a—
- Let him finish talking.
Luocheng does look like fertile land at first glance.
It is located in the East Asian monsoon region
At its southeast corner, there's a heavy metal industrial field that's been established for decades.
Normally, there isn't anything going on.
But every winter,
the factory emits large amounts of hazardous gas.
And due to the wind, it drifts towards Luocheng.
If you purchase this land, what the outcome will be,
I think everyone is clear about it.
If that's true, then wouldn't the estate rot in our hands?
- Yeah.
- Yes, that's right.
Ling Fang, why is it that in your plan,
the environmental monitoring report says that
there are no problems?
Don't listen to his nonsense.
I've checked for miles radius around. There wasn't even a factory in sight.
You can't have what he says goes, right?
He has no evidence. He does e-commerce, what does he know about this?
What a coincidence. I just happen to have evidence.
Many years ago, when President Ling was looking for a location for the logistics warehouse, he considered Luocheng.
This report not only shows the environmental monitoring report for miles radius, but even tens of miles.
Dad, listen to me explain.
Why would I listen to your explanation?
You're eager for success. Desperate for an achievement.
You don't even have foresight when making decisions.
What right do you have to be the president of the group?
Sorry, shareholders.
We took up too much of your time.
Regarding the issue of Ling Fang,
becoming Ling Group's president,
- I vote against.
- What are you saying, Dad?
I disagree too.
- Me too.
- I'm against.
- Against.
- I'm also against.
- Me too.
Okay. The votes stand.
Meeting is over.
Luckily Ling Yue made it back in time. Otherwise, we wouldn't even be able to measure the losses.
That's right. Luckily we found out quick.
You did this on purpose.
You purposely chose this time to come back to purposely make me look bad.
- I did do this on purpose.
- Why do you have to get in my way every time?
Enough.
Do you need me to find the best doctor to take a look at your leg?
It's fine. I won't need it.
Stop being cynical.
Who knows what true intentions you have.
I believe the one having other thoughts is you, big brother.
I just happen to want to ask, why do you always want me to die?
This was found from someone else's dash cam.
How will you explain this?
- How?
- Dad, this is fake.
I dare you to bring the vehicle owner here.
Shut up.
Regarding this issue, Dad will give you an explanation.
What have you been doing all this time?
Why was there no news?
- I had some things to take care of.
- What,
is more important than the company?
Dad, you shouldn't worry about this.
Isn't the most important thing that Second Brother came back safely?
Since he's back, let's let him continue to be the pres—
Shut up you little brat
Let the spot of the president
be empty for now.
Ling Yue, take this time
to rest up.
I will do as you say.
Ling Fang, those old men and you are secretly
doing those small tactics behind my back.
Don't think I don't know.
So you better behave during this time.
You're on your own.
Do you think you've won?
It doesn't matter if you mess up my work. We're both the vice presidents right now.
We sit on an equal footing. Who knows about who will finally win？
Elder Brother, you're not my match.
Who are you looking down upon?
I don't care who the successor is.
I just don't want to be controlled by you.
So you want to control me?
- Elder Brother!
- You don't care about the position as a president?
- Elder Brother, we're a family.
- Ridiculous! Come over here!
There may be a misunderstanding. Calm down.
Calm down.
You brat.
You're amazing.
You're definitely going to make me be the scapegoat.
Elder Brother, you know if you're the scapegoat or not.
Let's see who's lying then.
Your legs are paralyzed right?
You really can't stand up anymore?
What? You don't trust me?
That girl is named, Gu Anxin, right?
Don't look at me like that.
Why are you suddenly interested?
Don't think about doing anything to Anxin.
You care about her?
- It's none of your business.
- How is this none of my business? Did you forget?
Ever since you were young, I always wanted to steal whatever you liked
or ruin it.
- You wouldn't dare to.
- Why wouldn't I?
Unless you won't ever meet her again
or I will definitively be able to find her.
Second Brother, are you fine?
I'm fine.
Ai Li, did you borrow my car last time because you knew that
my dashcam showed what Elder Brother and them
did to Second Brother's car?
On the day of President Ling's accident, we didn't see Director Ling Fang in the parking lot monitor.
But it just so happened that your car was there too.
So I thought it might be a lead.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I didn't even know my car had such a thing.
That was my idea. It doesn't concern you.
I just didn't want to drag you into this.
Second Brother, we're all brothers.
Elder Brother just lost himself for a moment.
He doesn't want to do harm to you.
You don't have to worry.
I will handle it.
President Ling, is your leg okay?
I didn't think that bastard would go so far.
Should I send you to Miss Anxin's house?
We can't go back there.
Now that Ling Fang has a lead, he won't let it go so easily.
Since you've already been followed,
if we go back to Anxin's house, then she won't be able to hide.
I'm sorry. I failed my duty.
For the time being, protect Anxin.
Don't let Ling Fang become aware until the matter is over.
Understood.
Excuse me, what is your friend's name?
Next time, invent a name before you come.
I have some issues on my end. Once I've dealt with them, I'll come find you.
Xiao Ba?
Hello, is this Miss Gu Anxin?
Congratulations! You've won a prize.
The prize is to enjoy a set of undergarments worth 288 yuan.
Please provide your chest, waist, and hip measurements.
I don't like to wear undergarments.
But my good friend You You likes them.
You can send them to her. Her chest measurement is 36A.
Hey! I'm clearly a 36D.
Gu Anxin! You've ruined my good reputation.
I'm not in the mood to talk.
Let Xiao Ba come and cure you. Where is he?
Xiao Ba! Say something!
Don't hide on the side in silence. I know you're there.
He—
Xiao Ba!
I didn't hear anything.
♫ Haven't separated yet, already started to miss you ♫
♫  Hugging you like owning the whole world ♫
♫  You are so beautiful that I am afraid the time won't be enough ♫
♫   Promises are superficial  ♫
You're so big, but that's all wasted. You're afraid of cockroaches.
Why are you looking at me?
No reason.
How about I gift them to you?
In the future, I'll help you with physical tasks like opening cans.
Stop fooling around,  give it to me!
What do you want to do, leaning so close to me?
♫  Let the eyes of time be our witness  ♫
♫   of that sentence, I do  ♫
Fine.
Then it's a promise. Seal it.
Anxin? Are you still listening?
Is the connection bad?
He left.
[Text messages with Anxin]
President Ling, the meeting with President Chen is at 10am.
Got it. Go ahead and arrange it.
[Express Delivery Service]
Anxin, you're still here?
You should go home. The company's new system doesn't allow overtime.
I'll be done very soon.
You're taking the company bus, right? It's available before 10pm.
When did the company become so generous?
I don't know either. It's like there's a new person in charge.
- I'm going now. Bye.
- Bye.
Anxin!
How come you're here?
I came out for a walk.
You can't stand and you still want to go for a walk?
Let's go home.
♫   Just got used to it that you give me first ♫
♫   Those tears I wanted to wipe away  ♫
♫   Those touches yet not touches  ♫
♫    There are never right or wrong in love ♫
♫ Gaze at me, don't avoid me ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Let me try to touch your hard shell ♫
♫ Hugging the fragility ♫
♫ Hold me gently ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Having never walked through it, ♫
♫ how would you understand? ♫
♫ Gaze at me, don't avoid me ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Let me try to touch your hard shell ♫
♫ Hugging the fragility ♫
♫ Hold me gently ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Having never walked through it, ♫
I have already increased the security there according to your instructions.
♫ Hold me gently ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Having never walked through it, how would you understand? ♫
President  Ling, I'm worried Miss Anxin will blame you.
At least she doesn't have to tread into these muddied waters.
Xin'er, look! Who's that?
I heard Ling Yue just escaped death
and is already burying himself with work. He's really going all out.
I heard his leg's crippled.
Let's not talk about this. Xin'er, how is your company coming along?
-How much does Uncle Gu decide to invest?
-It's his own daughter!
She'll get however much she wants. Right?
Angela, let me out at that intersection there.
What's wrong?
I might have caught a cold and don't feel well. I don't want to drink today.
It's not safe so late.
Don't worry. My driver will come pick me up immediately.
You two go ahead and have fun!
Then send me a message when you're home. Bye bye!
Bye bye!
Do I have the honor to be the driver for such a lovely fairy lady?
What a coincidence!
It is a coincidence and also isn't.
I was planning to meet you coincidentally anyways.
[Weibo]
How about it? Are you getting on?
You're awake?
Why did you bring me here?
Whenever I feel down,
or have something I can't come to terms with, I always come here to get some air.
And then I feel better. You can also try it.
I look like I'm in a bad mood?
Do you think you look like you're in a good mood?
How am I that ugly?
You're prettier when you smile.
Thank you.
It feels so nice.
You'll never go wrong listening to me.
Someone like you who always looks optimistic and carefree also has frustrations?
I only look carefree.
Think about it. I have two brothers who fight everyday.
How carefree can a fish in a pond like me be?
I heard...Ling Yue came back?
The net must be going crazy with news about my Second Brother.
The media has yet to actually catch a photo of him.
But everyone says he...says his leg-
Says my Second Brother's leg is crippled, right?
Don't listen to their nonsense. My Second Brother's leg is certainly injured,
but he's been recovering. It will definitely get better.
Xin'er, don't worry.
Second Brother can always turn ill luck into good fortune. This time will be no different.
His injuries...are they serious?
I'm actually also not clear.
Ever since Second Brother came back, he's locked himself inside the house.
He doesn't interact with anyone and devotes himself wholeheartedly into work.
I think this matter really impacted him greatly.
Someone as prideful as him...is now like this.
But I believe...he will definitely get better.
Because he is Ling Yue.
There is nothing that can knock him down.
Xin'er,
you still care about my Second Brother that much?
How can I just easily forget...so many years of feelings?
[Express Delivery Service]
Alright, then I will place it in the To-Be-Received cabinet for you.
Your welcome.
Thank you for your call. If you have time, please rate my service.
Alright-
So handsome!
Thank you.
Brother?
I'm sorry. I'm late.
-What sort of charm does Gu Anxin have?
-I know right...
The pond's so large, but why does she get to be the mermaid?
Perhaps that's just fate.
Today we're all lemon fairies*.(Feelings jealous)
Brother, why did you suddenly come back?
I should have come back earlier.
You've experienced so many things, yet why didn't you tell me?
What things?
How long are you planning to keep the fact that you dropped out of school from me?
How do you know?
We've video called so many times and sent so many emails.
You've always told me things are good, everything is good...
Look at you now? I can't help but worry for you.
I'm alright, Brother. I'm actually living great right now. You don't have to worry.
Give me your hand.
Look at my eyes.
How could I not know you? You're always like this.
Whenever you are bullied or experience bad times,
you just like to keep it all to yourself.
You're afraid of making trouble for others by telling.
I'm not others. I'm your brother.
Your brother is back. From now on, you won't ever feel wronged.
You don't need to pretend to be strong in front of me,
or pretend to be sensible. Alright?
This ice cream has my teeth hurting.
Alright. Don't cry. Your brother is back.
From now on, I won't let anyone bully you.
Oh, right, Brother.
I only asked for a half-hour off so I need to go back soon.
Okay, I'll drop you off. We have time.
You insisted on eating ice cream. Now you're cold, aren't you?
No need Brother! I am very strong.
You, strong?
Look at you, you look like a small penguin.
From now on I'll be by your side, so you won't have to suffer.
Look.
You've always been next to me, always been by my side.
I dreamed that a strange Aunty was in my room.
Don't cry, I'm here.
What is this?
It's a nightmare eating bracelet.
As long as you wear it, it will eat all of your nightmares.
Thank you, Brother!
- Alright. Let's go.
- Let's go.
[Express Delivery Service]
Stop working here.
Work at the Manga company that you brought up to me.
Don't you like to draw?
Just like Aunt Jin.
If I can't draw well, then what do I do?
I will help you then.
But I eat a lot. When the time comes, you can't blame me for that.
You have lost so much weight.
You have to eat more from now on.
The chubbier the better, okay?
Brother, don't you know that if you eat too much you will get eaten?
Since you were little, you've always been strong.
I came here to tell you that I'm back.
Go.
Yes?
Mom.
I'm going back now.
What are you doing here?
Yesterday, he drank at my place.
I didn't feel comfortable getting someone to drive for him, so I sent him home.
When I have time, I want to properly meet that girl, Anxin.
What kind of women,
is even able to crack this hard nut.
This is the main lead?
She is pretty.
Who is the guy next to her?
He's good-looking! A new date?
Given his way of avoiding a problem by walking away from it,
If I was her, I would do that too.
Which eyes did you see that he is good-looking?
He's very radiant.
At least he's better than some rocks.
Girls like guys like him.
Why aren't you going back?
Are you waiting for me to ask you to eat dinner together?
I will leave soon before you poison me.
Go do some digging on that guy.
Okay, I will do it right now.
[Weibo]
[Cherry Blossom Festival]
Anime convention recruitment.
If you send your work to our inbox,
your work will have a chance to appear at our anime convention,
letting more talent scouts discover you.
- Sister Chang'an has to go! Quickly, submit.
Exactly! Guru Chang'an, you have to participate!
We will support you!
Let's go Chang an!
Can I really do it?
[Send]
[Your email has been sent]
Does it hurt here?
I'm asking you a question, does your leg hurt?
Can you please respect the doctor in front of you and tell me if your leg hurts?i
Sister Chang'an has to go?
When did you become so effeminate?
And you have become Yuan Yuan?
Why aren't you called Fang Fang or Bian Bian?
Give it back to me.
I don't even want to see it.
Why is Sister Chang An?
It's President Ling's people.
Then it looks like
are a lot of interesting things happening.
Silly, don't you know to block it.
Sister wipe yourself and don't get cold!
Thank you!
Sister, use this umbrella.
Then how do I give it back to you?
No need to! My bus is here, good bye!
President Ling, the anime convention has already been arranged.
Let's go.
Later when we see their piece
-Do you understand what to say?
-Yeah, I understand.
Please.
Hello teachers.
Sit.
Thank you.
You see, it is raining.
You are all wet, please wipe yourself.
Drink some hot water so that you don't get sick.
Drink more.
What is going on?
Gu Anxin. Right?
-Did you bring your piece?
-I brought it.
I'm sorry, I forgot to bring it...
No worries, you can tell us
about your previous projects.
In the past, I have serialized
Big Bad Wolf and the Little Sheep.
Also-
-Then...
-That's good!
I have saw your piece before and it was really good.
It can be directly published.
-Really?
-Really!
Is it that good?
What nonsense are you saying?
You're going a little overboard. Pull it back.
Anxin, you have been selected.
Selected?
Just like that?
There is no 2nd or 3rd interview?
No need.
It's an exceptional hiring.
You can start working tomorrow.
Tomoorroow? I'm not ready to begin tomorrow, sorry.
Then if you have any conditions
No worries, you can just tell us.
No! It's not a condition.
To be honest, it's because I haven't quit
I have to pass over the work.
So I can't work tomorrow.
Then no worries.
I know this good news has come too suddenly. I understand it may be hard to accept.
After all we are the Chuangshi Company!
Right, right, right.
You just consider it after you leave.
Once you are done considering, you can contact me.
- Mr. Zhao Lei.
- That's right, Zhao Lei.
- Me too. My name is Wang Li.
- And me as well.
- My name is Chen Hong.
- Hello, Chen Hong.
Then, I leave now.
Alright.
-Do you need me to see you out.
-See her out.
-No need.
-Need not.
-Shoud do that.
- I'll send you.
- Oh, no need.
Go slowly. This way.
- Auntie.
- Son!
- Mom.
- You're finally back.
Have a hug.
Let mother see you.
Why you lose so much weight.
Is the food abroad not to your taste?
Not at all.
Come, quickly.
Let's try the food I prepared for you.
Your favourite dish.
Just sit down.
In the few years I haven't been back,
your cooking skills have really improved too quickly.
- Eat well.
You didn't order food to fool me, did you?
You always know how to sweet talk.
All you have left is your sweet talk.
Father.
Your mother is always wishing to the moon and the stars for you to return.
First thing you do since you come back isn't seeing her.  You think I don't know that.
You've spent the whole day with an outsider.
Dad, Anxin doesn't count as an outsider.
She isn't related to me, Gu Yuanchao.
How could she not count as an outsider?
Dad, look,
I am not your biological.
You love me still.
What sort of nonsense, how could it be the same?
Yuanchao, did you finish your phone meeting?
It gave me a headache.
Let me press there.
You are just too tired.
Yuanchao, stop blaming our son.
They grew up together.
- Naturally, their relationship is good.
- That's why I'm afraid he'll be provoked by her.
Dad! I always feel like there's something secretive going on.
Anxin is so kind since little, how could she have hurt someone.
You think you understand her.
Look at her shameful behavior.
She is made of the same mold as her mother.
Whatever bad thing she does, I wouldn't be surprised.
That's enough, stop fighting. Our son just came back.
However you look at it, Anxin is a child of our Gu family.
You also promised Sister Jin Guan that you would take good care of her.
This child was indeed too headstrong in the past.
But I trust that she now knows she was wrong.
Oh right, Yuanchao.
It's your birthday in a few days. How about we welcome her over to get together?
You can organize it.
Trust me.
Son, eat more.
- Here.
- Thanks Mom.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up a lifetime ♫