Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating a beam of light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breath brushes up against my cheek ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage,
happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up a pitiful youngster off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up
one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr. Ling]
[Episode 5]
Anxin. I like you.
Y-You stand there. We can talk from there.
I really like you.
Stand there! Don't come closer!
Listen to me! Give me a chance.
- I– No, don't come closer.
- Anxin.
Listen to me.
- D-Don't come closer.
- Give me a chance, okay?
Anxin!
Listen to me! Give me a chance. I like you, really!
You hurt me? Anxin... Anxin!
Anxin! Anxin, open the door!
Anxin, open the door! Open the door!
Why won't you open the door? Is it because I'm not as rich as that man?
Anxin, open the door! Are you women just this vain?
Open the door, Anxin. Anxin! Open the door!
Aren't you scared of the dark?
Anxin!
Are you afraid? Anxin!
Open it. You can't escape.
I'll get you the moon.
The moon can't come.
I can get it. Trust mom. I'll get it for you.
Mom!
Open the door, Anxin. Anxin! Open the door!
Anxin!
Don't be afraid. I am here.
I saw that you didn't come straight home,
nor did you send any message, so I went looking for you at work.
Thank you.
I won't let that man off.
Don't be too aggressive.
Your injury isn't healed yet.
It would be dangerous.
Resign from your job, I'll take care of you.
If I resign, are we going to make a living as street performers?
Don't worry, I won't let you suffer.
Oh right. The office is so far from home.
How did you get there?
I called a taxi. With your phone.
$125.00
How do you know my Alipay password?
I used your fingerprint to pay.
$125.00
What's wrong? Are you feeling unwell?
I'm okay.
I just feel like my heart is choked up with anxiety.
Your heart is on that side.
[ Sudakuaidi ]
Anxin, I like you.
You're drunk.
I sincerely like you. You have to give me the chance.
- No, don't come closer!
- Anxin, listen to me.
- Sister Anxin.
Sister Anxin, give it to us.
Oh, it's okay.
No it's okay. I can do it.
Manager Du is here.
Anxin, don't you know? Dujin has been fired.
The boss got a letter reporting him.
It was filled with evidence of him making false accounts and taking sales commissions.
The boss got very angry and made him leave immediatly.
When did it happen?
Not long after we arrived at the sales department today, we received notice from headquarters.
[Anxin, I didn't understand in the past why you opposed me]
Take this home. I can't take it home. Yours too, I can't take it.
- You have to take it.
- Oh right.
It's not easy to find work right now. I don't want to get fired.
What do you mean, "get fired"?
I mean... in any case, you have to take my token of gratitude.
Take it, Sister Anxin.
- You're back?
- Yeah.
How come you bought so much? Did you get a bonus?
I'm telling you, it's even stranger than getting a bonus.
As soon as I got to work today, all of my coworkers were nice to me.
Even the people I don't usually interact with stuffed gifts in my cabinet.
Do you think my boss has taken a liking to me?
But he's over fifty years old!
Stop dreaming. You should go to sleep.
Good night.
Is the matter settled?
Yes. We have already bought Express Delivery Service.
President Ling, are we just going to let Du Ming off so easily?
Just leave it at that.
Hey,
it seems like you slept well last night.
I used the aromatic Xiao Li gave me. I slept really well.
[File Folder]
Yours?
You didn't hide some
embarrassing photos in here right? So nervous.
What are you thinking about?
You're a little different today.
♫ From that day in the rain ♫
What's different?
♫ Fate is odd ♫
Help me up.
♫ The unforgettable past receives a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly skips a beat ♫
♫ Using the hand of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Clearly caring more and more ♫
♫ Flip the coin of happiness, It's you anyways ♫
♫ Our story has only begun ♫
♫ Longing already can't be stopped ♫
♫ Even breathing is hot enough to make my face burn up ♫
♫ Our story seems familiar ♫
♫ Destiny has hinted many times ♫
♫ Looking for the address back to your side ♫
♫ From when we met on that rainy day ♫
♫ Hints of memories wet from rain ♫
♫ Fate is odd, the unforgettable past receives a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly skips a beat ♫
I-
You...don't need to s-say anything. I know you didn't do it on purpose.
I'm also pretty busy! I-I still need to go to the bathroom to wash the dishes I just ate.
♫ It's you ♫
It's alright...
♫ Our story has only begun ♫
♫ Longing already cannot be stopped ♫
♫ Using love to spin open the door to love for life ♫
Why are you suddenly eating ice cream?
Because it's hot?
Did you finish washing the dishes you ate in your bathroom?
[Application Resume]
You must really want to know why even though your resume is exemplary
why you can't find a job anywhere, right? Manager Du?
Who are you?
I am someone who can help you.
-Hello, You You?
-Anxin,
I saw your weibo post. Did you make progress with that handsome boy?
-Tell me the truth.
-What progress? I just posted randomly.
Stop trying to trick me! Who posts love messages randomly?
If you tell me the truth, I'll let you off easily. If not, it'll be bad for you! Choose for yourself.
Perhaps...I...
-I might like him a little bit.
-My God!
-Isn't that super obvious?
-It's obvious?
You can tell?
T-Then if you can tell, can he tell too?
Of course he can tell! And he also likes you.
No way. How do you know?
I haven't been fascinated with imaginary couples for nothing!
Then do you think...do you think he has a girlfriend?
That's true...He looks so handsome.
There's no way he doesn't have a girlfriend.
Right...
Don't scare yourself though. Maybe he's been single his whole life?
Single his whole life doesn't seem possible. He's so great.
Isn't there a lot of male protagonists like that in novels?
Your meeting is so legendary, so anything is possible!
Maybe he's your perfect male protagonist.
-Right? Xin Xin?
-You You, I'll talk to you later.
Manager Du?
There is further news today about the crazed stalker causing alarm everywhere.
The police is currently conducting investigation according to the security cameras that recorded the suspect.
We also encourage citizens to actively provide evidence.
Hello, the phone number you called is unavailable at this time. Please dial again later.
Hello, I am Anxin's boyfriend. Is she at the company right now?
I haven't been able to get into touch with her. Can you let her know?
Oh...Anxin? She isn't at the company tonight. She doesn't have a shift tonight.
She left work right in the morning.
-What time did she leave?
-I think it was 6?
Oh, ok. Thank you.
President Ling, what are you...
Come inside to talk.
-Why have you come?
-Things are urgent, and I only found out now.
Look at this.
[Ling Group: Chairman Position Draft]
Tonight, President Ling Fang will secretly meet with the stockholders.
-When?
-10 pm at Michelle Hotel.
President Ling, if you don't leave now, I'm afraid it'll be too late.
Time goes by so fast.
I remember when you first arrived at the company,
you were still an intern who didn't know anything.
That's right. Time goes by so fast.
Actually, what happened last time,
I've always been very guilty.
I want to find an opportunity to apologize to you.
Whenever I get drunk, I act like a jerk.
I troubled you.
I'm really...sorry.
Manager Du, you actually don't have to apologize to me.
Just let things in the past pass.
I believe that you didn't do it on purpose either.
You believe me?
President Ling, Du Ming disappeared.
Keep looking. What time is it now?
9:00 PM. President Ling,
if you head back now you can still make it.
Leave finding Miss Anxin to me.
Let me down over there.
Okay.
I believe you.
Because I've also hurt someone before.
I was desperate for their forgiveness.
So, I understand you.
If you understand me,
then why are you doing this to me?
That does that mean?
If you understand me, then why did you harm me?
Why did you drive me into a corner?
I don't really understand what you mean. What do you mean by
driving you into a corner?
You look so innocent.
Anxin.
If I didn't know what you did to me, I'd be deceived by your pitiful face.
Even now, I still can't accept what you did to me.
Manager Du, I don't know what you're talking about but I think there must be a misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding? Wasn't I fired because of you?
Wasn't it because of you that I fell to this state?
It's not like that.
- I...I don't have to capabilities to do that.
- You don't.
The person behind you does.
Why do you have to force me?
Why won't you let me be?
We can just all go down together. What else?
- If you keep this on I'm going to call for someone.
- Call.
Call. Call. You call.
Call.
Anxin.
Run. Run.
Why do you have to force me?
Why, why do you have to force me?
Say it.
Anxin.
How are you?
Are you okay? Don't worry, I'm here.
You didn't hurt yourself, right?
You leg.
My leg is fine. Here, I'll help you up.
Here.
Come.
Are you okay?
Careful.
Xiao Ba.
Come here.
What? You feel sorry for him?
Xiao Ba.
Should we take him to the hospital?
I examined him. It's nothing serious.
You should get on the car. I'll take you home first.
- Do you know each other?
- Yeah.
You should get on the car.
What should I call you?
You can just call me Ai Li.
You're Anxin, Right? I heard Xiao Ba mention you before.
So you guys are...?
Not what you think.
That's what I thought.
How can you like him.
Don't say it like that. He is my savior.
What I'm doing is my responsibility.
Do I turn right ahead, or?
Anxin.
Do I turn right ahead or keep straight?
Keep straight and turn right.
Okay.
Oh, left turn.
How come I'm here?
Ai Li brought you back. Shouldn't you thank her?
- Thanks.
- It's nothing.
I met you coincidentally anyways.
It's getting late. I also have to take that person to the police station.
I'll get going.
Be safe.
How did your leg suddenly get better?
It's probably a sudden spurt of activity before collapsing.
After I heard you yelling so loudly, I stood up out of desperation.
What do you mean?
It's my instincts that triggered my potential, you know?
I was just hit by that Winter Melon Du. Now I can't stand up again.
Sorry, I know it was because of me.
If you really are sorry,
then how about you massage me a few more times.
When did you learn to be so cunning?
I didn't teach you that.
Where's the wheelchair?
I was in a hurry so I forgot it there.
- I'll go find it right now.
- There's no need.
Ai Li said she'll buy me a new one, as thanks.
After all, I helped her before.
But she saved your life today.
How will you thank her?
That's right too, why does she treat me so well?
Do you think she likes me?
How is that possible.
Ai Li has such good skills,
she might be a police.
I don't know either.
Let's go.
Let's go home.
Take it slowly.
It's already 11pm.
Do you need to do something?
It's fine now.
I won't let him appear in front of you again.
Then what if he still does?
I won't let this sort of thing happen again.
But what if it does?
I'm here for you.
Okay.
Then that's...
It's a pinky promise. Seal it.
Seal it.
This is how you do it.
Get some sleep soon.
Keep watching Ling Fang, let me know if anything happens.
[Security, High Efficiency, Convenient, Privacy, Energy Saving. Beautiful View]
Come in.
You're here.
Father, what do you think of this proposal?
I had a look already. Not bad.
The idea is quite unique.
Then how much money are you planning to invest into this?
Your father hasn't finished speaking yet.
If you want to go with this
You'll need spend some time to consider it yourself.
After all there are risks involved.
All in all, it seems that you don't want to invest in this.
You...you should leave this tough work to the men.
- You shouldn't waste your time on this.
- I can do it too.
Since you are not interested in this proposal,
then I will take this away.
I heard that you've been looking for the Ling family's son.
Which one?
The daughter of mine
has plenty of admirers.
You don't have to waste all your time on him.
If he doesn't come back, I think that's for the better.
Understood, father.
Director Ling, about the shareholders that Director Ling Feng saw previously,
some of them have been seeking the chairman recently.
I fear that they may be discussing about the shareholders' meeting.
Do you think that Director Ling Feng may be...
Those old things won't be easily bribed.
But since it's been a while since I last made an appearance, they will waver a bit for sure.
It's understandable if they are looking for someone for backing.
Then, when are you thinking to return?
A bit longer.
It's everything sorted with Du Ming?
Rest assured, the crimes combined won't let him live comfortably.
Also, Du Ming has said.
He only chose Miss An Jing
because someone made sure he can't back out so he had no other choice.
-Who was it?
- Not sure yet.
But he's saying that we did it.
Then it seems that someone is trying to frame us.
Could it be Director Ling Feng?
No way. Knowing my brother, if he knew i'm still alive,
he wouldn't be so quiet.
Then who could it be?
Don't worry. They will show up soon.
Find out for me whether the time of the shareholders' meeting has been decided.
Who are you on a call with?
It's Ai Li, she said the wheelchair she bought for us has arrived.
Ours?
She bought it for you.
Then I'll retrieve it for you after I get off work.
No need, she says that it'll be delivered to the door.
That's quite thoughtful.
She quite good to you.
Yes, not bad.
Have a look, this one's not bad. It's quite nice.
You can choose a few more to complement each other.
- Oh this purple one is quite nice.
- Hello, did you want to purchase some flowers?
[Director Ling: Shun Jun Hotel, Room 1205]
[There's someone tailing you, lose them first.
No, what's this situation? Going to the bar during the day!?
Who knows? Let's just wait for now.
Hello, this is for 'Cutie'.
- Okay, thank you.
- No worries.
Sorry, non-hotel residents cannot go up,
No, I know him. I need to speak to him.
Then may ask what is his name?
Next time, make the name up before you try again.
Is there a need for me to make up a name?
I really know him that's why–
Fine.
Thank you.
Hello, I made a reservation.
- Can I confirm your name?
- Ai Li.
'Ai' as in wormwood, 'Li' as in bamboo hat.
Your room key card has been retrieved by the man you are staying with.
He just went up in his wheelchair.
Didn't you realize that you were being followed?
Why are Ling Feng's men suddenly following you?
Sorry, it must be that the movement of acquiring of the Express Delivery Service was too big.
-  We can't hide it anymore.
- There has been an update with the shareholders' meeting as well.
It's about the changing of CEO.
The chairman was considering all this time.
But today, it was suddenly announced that there would be a meeting tomorrow.
It will be to give Director Ling Feng the position of CEO.
Director Ling, you must return to the family immediately.
Let's go. It's about time I gave them a surprise.
Then do you want to tell Miss An Xin?
If you leave without informing her, she would be worried.
So you two are...
It's not what you think it is.
Do you think she fell for me?
[Something came up for me.]
[I'll look for you when I'm done.]
[What's wrong?]
[Are you with Ai Li?]
Recently, the Ling Group has encountered some unhappy incidents.
To be entrusted at such a critical moment, I have also felt the pressure.
However, I really appreciate the trust everyone here placed in me.
I will take on the responsibilities as CEO.
I will lead us into the future!
I do not agree.
Director Ling! Director Ling is back. It's really him!
It's second brother! Father, he's alive!
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Soaking the memory wet ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats out of normal ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Obviously, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness,
for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the reminiscing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up ♫
♫ a lifetime ♫