Who is it?
It's me.
Why are you here?
I miss you too much.
So, I came here to see you.
This is for you.
How do you know this place?
When I first saw you in the game,
I was here at this building.
I know that you are this company's
CEO.
So, I came here to see you.
You are all wet.
Let me get you something to change into.
This is our company's event T-shirt.
Change into it.
I'll wait for you outside.
Sit tight.
I drive very fast.
(Exit)
=Love Crossed=
=Episode 15=
The city at night is so beautiful.
The rain has stopped?
You love the rain?
I've seen it in movies before.
How do you feel about the real rain?
It's quite fascinating.
The feeling of it
falling down on my face
is very comforting.
I like the breeze after the rain.
It's warm and clean when
it breezes on my face.
I once read a book.
That book is about
the life after death.
So, how is it like?
After we die,
everything will stay the same.
But we won't be able to feel
the breeze on our faces again.
I didn't know how it feels in the past.
But now, I can understand
why humans are so sentimentally
attached to this world.
There are a lot of things that
people are attached to.
The morning dew on the petals.
The warm sunshine in the afternoon.
The chirping of cicadas in summer.
And the first snow in winter.
You should experience them all.
After hearing that,
you've really piqued my interest.
You are not afraid of
the outside world anymore?
It's not that I'm afraid.
But compared to fear,
the urge to see you is stronger.
(Kele, you've been asking for)
(a car of your own for a long time.)
(And I think that)
(it's really inconvenient for you
to take the train to work.)
(Use the money in this card)
(to buy a car that you like.)
(Kele)
I know. In this situation,
the man should cut the steak
for the woman
and then give it to her.
But I think that you are
different from other women.
You are more independent.
That's why I ate the steak myself.
Just now, I was still thinking about
how to reject you kindly
if you cut the steak
and gave it to me.
You've done well.
It's more comfortable to just
eat our own food.
Today
is our first date in the outside world.
Can we drink some wine?
Sure.
I'll pass.
I'll drink water instead.
I know.
You have to drive, right?
So, you know about that.
Looks like you'll be able to
adapt to the outside world soon.
So comfortable.
Is this firm enough?
Yes,
can't you be gentler?
Okay.
If you feel sore anywhere,
tell me about it.
I feel sore everywhere.
Let me massage you more then.
Actually, my heart
is the one feeling unwell.
Kele.
Is something weighing you down again?
It's because of you.
Let me ask you.
If your mom is going to pass away,
what will you do?
I will accompany and
take care of her all the time.
See? Even you can understand that.
Why can't he understand?
Are you talking about
the person who looks like me?
Yes. Him.
When I told him that his mom is sick,
he scolded me for being a busybody.
I don't want to get involved anymore.
But my dad came back today.
And suddenly, I realized something.
You can't leave behind regrets
in your life.
Kele, you are doing something good.
You can't give up
just because you failed once.
I think you should advise him again.
He'll understand.
Okay. I'll advise him again then.
But to be honest,
what if he scolds me again?
If he scolds you again,
you can come and scold me.
Then, you'll feel better, right?
If I see him one day,
I'll definitely scold him for you.
I knew it. You are the best.
(Lu Xiao)
(Xu Nian)
This is the first time you see yourself
in the real world, right?
Is this our images in the game?
Actually, it's not
that different from you.
But you have to know.
No matter how real
the person in the game is,
he's still not the real you.
The real you
should live in the real world.
(Su Lie)
(Luo Ke)
We are here.
When can we meet again?
Will you come to Bay House to find me?
But I'll wait for you
in the office every night.
If you want to see me, come out.
See you tomorrow night then.
I'll show you
more of the outside world
tomorrow night.
Okay. I'll get going now.
I'll really go now.
Go.
Bye.
(There are a lot of things that)
(people are attached to.)
(The morning dew on the petals.)
(The warm sunshine in the afternoon.)
(The chirping of cicadas in summer.)
(And the first snow in winter.)
(You should experience them all.)
(The colorists in operation)
(Lu Xiao)
(Crush On Love)
Cheng Jun!
Son!
Wake up, son!
He's a jinx.
No wonder no one
is willing to adopt him.
Son!
The dean shouldn't have pitied on him.
Look at her now.
They just recently adopted him
and her own son is dead because of him.
That's right.
(Family Medical Guide)
What are you doing?
Good morning.
You haven't eaten breakfast, right?
I had.
It's okay.
That breakfast is not good anyway.
Look at what I've brought.
This is only for you.
I don't want to eat it.
Let me tell you.
This is not a normal cake.
This is a birthday cake.
It's not my birthday.
Why do I have to eat this birthday cake?
I know it's not your birthday.
It's not my birthday too.
This one
is my mom's birthday cake.
Didn't I tell you
not to be a busybody?
I'm not being a busybody.
This is really my mom's birthday cake.
Although my mom
passed away when I was very young,
every year,
my dad and I will
celebrate her birthday.
Your mom passed away?
Yes, when I was very young.
Why are you celebrating
her birthday then?
Shouldn't it be her deathday?
My dad and I
think that deathday is too depressing.
So, every year,
we'll mourn for her.
Every time we celebrate her birthday,
I'll think that
it would be nice if
my mom was still alive.
I really miss her.
So, Lu Xiao, don't be mad at me.
I told you as soon as possible
after I found out that your mom is sick,
because my mom passed away from illness.
I don't want you to have any regrets.
Kele.
Thank you for what you did for me.
But, please don't tell anybody about
my mom being in the nursing home.
For the rest,
let me decide by myself.
So, you are not mad now?
Let's eat some cake then.
Okay.
Are we still going to film the MV of
"Better to dance than to fall in love"?
Guan Qianya has refused to
be the leading actress.
Of course we do.
Let's just find an actress
who looks like Guan Qianya.
Won't it be against the law?
Guan Qianya has no right to sue me.
What I mean is
won't it be a breach of copyright
of the Love Boys,
if you dress up as Xu Nian?
Xu Guanghan has even
fewer rights to sue me.
He took away so many of my songs.
So what if I use one of his characters?
Moreover,
it'll attract more attention
if we are going to court.
I just don't understand.
Why do you have to dance
Xu Nian and Guan Qianya's dance?
Is it for the sake of
the theme of
"Better to dance than to fall in love"?
Or is it because you want to
promote yourself with its popularity?
Both.
But this is the postmodern art.
You don't know anything
about being an artist.
Look at this...
Isn't this place too small
for Y4's concert?
It's not small. Qi Chuan will be
holding his concert here too.
Qi Chuan?
Then, it's quite small.
What is he going to do?
A farewell concert?
No.
His first concert for his world tour.
First concert.
So, there'll only be one concert.
It's a farewell concert then.
This is strange.
After he left Yao Inc.,
he can't write new songs anymore.
What songs can he use
to perform in a concert?
Don't be like this.
Contact them later.
Give them a discount
so that he can still use
his previous songs.
How much is the discount?
Is someone asking us about the price?
Tell them that
it'll be 10 times the market price.
You just got your compensation, right?
I'm sure you can afford it.
Of course I can.
Mr. Xu, are you here today
to give me support before the concert?
I forgot.
He's here to scout out the place.
He wants to hold a concert for
the four virtual characters, right?
Are you afraid now?
But don't worry.
Our concert date
will be far from yours.
About two months after yours.
First,
we don't want you to jinx us.
Second,
if we hold a concert,
no one will go to yours.
Mr. Xu.
Our tickets have already been sold out.
But don't worry.
I'll keep one
VVV VIP ticket.
Remember to join us on that day.
You can keep one for me.
But I won't attend it.
Qi Chuan, when have we
sold out all of our tickets?
Moreover,
if it'll cost us 10 times the price to
buy our previous songs,
we'll lose a lot of money.
It's okay.
I can sing
"Better to dance than to fall in love"
for several times.
It'll take up more than 10 minutes.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
One and two, three, four, five, six...
What's wrong?
The new game has
additional dance moves now.
And they are so difficult.
Yes. Even Lu Xiao got it wrong.
Let's practice it for twice more.
And then, we can rest.
No.
I can't dance anymore.
Xu Nian. How about we stop for today?
Okay. We'll do it again tomorrow.
Go back and rest.
Let's go.
(TAILG)
I never thought that
I'll be buying a motorbike one day.
(New Arrival)
(TAILG)
Miss, are you interested
in the motorbike?
May I ask
is there any promotion for this?
I'm sorry.
This is our new arrival.
(TAILG)
One charge can last your 150km.
For now, there's no promotion for it.
Anything on sales?
What about this?
This is our classic motorbike.
It's not on sales as well.
Do you sell second-hand motorbikes then?
TAILG only sells new motorbikes.
We don't sell the second-hand ones
or refurbished ones.
Looks like this is not for me.
Miss.
How about you take a look at this?
This one is on sales.
But this is the last one.
If you want it,
I can apply for more discounts for you.
(Sale, 75km per charge)
(Crush On Love)
Ms. Guan.
You are still working?
I'm going to stay here
for a little bit longer.
There are files that
I have to go through.
I heard that Mr. Zhang asked you
about the acquisition
but you rejected him.
Why?
We are the ones who founded
Crush On Love.
Even though we are in
a bad position now,
I won't give it up.
I know.
But have you found
another solution to it?
These are the certificates of
my house and my car.
(Real Estate Certificate,
Automotive Registration Certificate)
Mortgage them for me.
I've calculated it.
The mortgage money
will last us a while.
Ms. Guan, you can't do this.
This is everything you have.
If the company survives,
I'll be able to get them back.
Don't worry. I'll find a solution.
I'll get it done.
(Crush On Love)
Wait, Mr. Cui.
Do you have an iPass card?
No. Ms. Guan.
During the mortgage period,
you can still use your car.
You can stay at your house too.
There'll be no changes to your life.
I know.
I need it for something else.
I just topped it up. You can have it.
Thank you.
I'll get going then.
(Crush On Love)
(iPass)
What happened?
Why is the electricity off again?
Don't panic.
I'll look for the emergency light.
Hurry up.
Who is it?
Jiang Kele!
Be careful!
It's dark. Be careful!
Who went out just now?
Jiang Kele. Look.
Jiang Kele?
When did she become so tall?
What do you mean?
That person is not Jiang Kele!
Why are you still standing here?
Chase after him!
Stop right there!
I'll make sure that
you have no songs to sing.
You'll have to sing one song on repeat.
Hello? What is it?
What?
Fix it now!
What's wrong?
The Maintenance Department said that
Bay House is suddenly out of power.
They are fixing it now.
What are they doing?
Why is it out of power again?
Can they fix this issue already?
Why do you stop?
We have to go back to Bay House.
Mr. Xu, it's a red light.
Riding on my lovely motorbike.
I won't be stuck in a jam anymore.
Where's my helmet?
Did I leave it in Bay House?
No. I have to go back to take it.
Or else, I'll be doomed.
He's running at night with a helmet.
So dramatic.
Isn't that my helmet?
Who are you?
Why did you steal my helmet?
It's me, Kele.
Who are you?
I'm Lu Xiao!
Lu Xiao, why are you out here?
No time to explain. Let's go now.
Stop right there!
Bro!
Did you escape to go to the hospital?
Yes! Speed up!
Okay. I'm speeding up now.
(TAILG)
Hold on to me.
Can you hold on to me properly?
Mr. Xu, we've restored the power.
Where are the security guards?
Someone sneaked out just now.
So, they chased after him.
Mr. Xu, why are you here?
Where are the other three?
They are resting in their rooms
because they are too tired from dancing.
Ask them to come out.
Wait.
Go and get the other two.
I'll go and get Lu Xiao.
Mr. Xu, why are you here?
Get out.
I have something to ask all of you.
Who sneaked out when
the power went off just now?
The power went off just now?
Yes.
I didn't know because I fell asleep.
Why would the power go off suddenly?
Shut up.
Xu Nian, tell me.
Who sneaked out just now?
You are the one who
sneaked out just now, right?
Keep it a secret for me.
Nobody went out.
I think you know
the consequences of lying.
I'll ask you again.
Who sneaked out when
the power went off just now?
Nobody.
I was watching a movie
in the living room just now.
They were resting in their rooms.
And the power went off suddenly.
But then, the power restored.
I don't know what happened.
But the security guards said that
a person who's wearing a coat,
jeans and helmet
ran out from the building.
Lu Xiao, don't you think
that their descriptions
sound a lot like you?
Don't you think so?
Why did you shake your head?
They are not exactly the same.
Lu Xiao is not wearing a helmet.
Search the place.
Get down.
Why did you take me here?
Am I going to go to
the hospital by metro?
I have no time to explain it to you.
(Xiang Hua Qiao Lu Station)
(Please do not follow
the dangerous activities.)
What kind of place is this?
There's a tunnel in front.
You can go back to Bay House from there.
Bay House?
Why am I going back to Bay House?
Our pursuers have left.
I can go to the hospital.
Now is not the time for you
to go to the hospital.
You've attracted
too much attention.
Mr. Xu might have already
found out about it.
The only thing you can do
is to go back now
and act like nothing happened, okay?
I'll find a chance to
get you out next time.
But does this tunnel
really lead to Bay House?
Trust me. Let's go now.
Mr. Xu, there's no helmet.
What about upstairs?
Okay.
If you cover up for him,
you'll be committing the same crime.
The power is back?
Mr. Xu, why are you here?
Good evening.
Why are you here so late at night?
I bought a candle.
Candle?
Yes.
Aromatic candle.
The power went off just now.
You don't know
how far I went to buy this candle.
But it looks like
we don't need it anymore.
It's okay.
We can keep it for next time.
So, you ran out when
the power went off just now?
Yes. It was me.
Why did you run when
the security guards asked you to stop?
♪You're in my embrace
when I open my eyes♪
♪You reassure me♪
♪Your care and attention
make me feel important♪
♪Every day I want your attention♪
♪I can't stop throwing tantrums♪
♪It's your fault that
I'm so spoiled now♪
♪You promised to hold my hands
and to spend the life together♪
♪So let's enjoy the current moment
and the future♪
♪Your love and sweetness
filled my heart♪
♪I long for you all the time♪
♪The music of missing you
is on repeat in my head♪
♪If only time could slow down♪
♪I don't want to be separated from you♪
♪No obstacles in our path♪
♪You're in my embrace
when I open my eyes♪
♪You reassure me♪
♪Your care and attention
make me feel important♪
♪Every day I want your attention♪
♪I can't stop throwing tantrums♪
♪It's your fault
that I'm so spoiled now♪
♪You promised to hold my hands
and to spend the life together♪
♪So let's enjoy the current moment
and the future♪
♪Your love and sweetness
filled my heart♪
♪I long for you all the time♪
♪The music of missing you
is on repeat in my head♪
♪If only time could slow down♪
♪I don't want to be separated from you♪
♪No obstacles in our path♪