So you're saying you ran out
when the power went down just now.
Yes. That's right. It was me.
So why did you run
when the security guards called you?
Mr. Xu.
If you hadn't asked about it,
I would've never told you.
I've been keeping this to myself
for a long time now.
From the first day they saw me,
those two security guards
were after my beautiful look
and body.
One time,
they even pushed me to the ground.
Lei Na saw it too,
but she didn't do anything.
So I could only run when I saw them.
Mr. Xu, if you are a fair man,
you should fire them immediately.
But if you want to cover for them,
it's all right. I can bear with it.
But I can only do nothing
but run when I see them.
Mr. Xu, I found the helmet.
The helmet.
Rest well.
Why do the three of you look
as if you just got away with something?
=Love Crossed=
=Episode 16=
-Mr. Xu!
Someone ran out earlier, right?
Yes!
We chased after that person
for a long way!
Especially me.
I hurt my arm too.
Mr. Xu, would this count
as a workplace injury?
It would be great
if we could get a raise.
Trying to get a raise, right?
Both of you...
You couldn't keep them in. You couldn't
catch the person who sneaked out.
And you even had the wrong person.
What did you do right?
All I see are mistakes.
Actually, Mr. Xu...
We're fine without a raise.
We're strong and healthy, you see.
That's right, Mr. Xu.
My arm is just fine.
I'll just put a band-aid on it.
Away with the both of you!
Yes, sir!
Mr. Xu,
why didn't you fire them?
We can't let more people
know about the Bay House.
Besides, you're one I'd like to fire
more than them.
Well, the helmet
was a moment of carelessness.
But I noticed something
even more important!
Lu Xiao and Jiang Kele
were wearing couple outfits earlier,
did you see that?
Say, don't you think
it's thanks to my quick-thinking
and my super speedy motorbike
that we got out of this?
I'm telling you,
if we got caught, we'd be done for.
You don't know how scary it was.
Last time,
when I was caught by Lei Na,
they almost injected me with poison.
But thankfully,
she didn't know how to use it,
so it all went to waste.
I know.
You do?
Did they try to inject you too?
No, they didn't.
But I was interrogated in the pool once.
Oh, I got it now.
You sneaked out last time
to see your mother too, didn't you?
Then along the way, you kissed me.
They found out, and you were caught
and taken back here.
So that means I saved you twice.
Twice!
Thank you.
What was that?
I can't hear you.
Never mind then.
Thank you.
See.
Wouldn't it be great
if you had just been honest?
If you had been honest with me sooner,
I could have taken you out
through the tunnel.
You could go to any places
whenever you wanted.
Well, who would have known
that there was a secret tunnel?
I'm sure even Xu Guanghan himself
doesn't know about it.
That's true.
You've been staying here all the time.
Of course you wouldn't know about it.
But that's all right.
You have me now.
I'll arrange
our future escapades.
I was just "almost" caught today.
Do you have
to look down on me like that?
No, I'm not.
I just want to make
a pinky promise with you.
(Crush On Love)
When will we be able to meet again?
Will you come to find me
at the Bay House again?
If you want to see me, come outside.
Then... I'll see you tomorrow night.
What are you doing here late at night
with the lights off?
Did you think the power went out again?
Here. I'm giving this back to you.
Thank you for today.
You're welcome.
You went out because you had
something important to do,
right?
So you've sneaked out of this place too?
You know about that tunnel too?
When did you find out about it?
Recently.
Did Jiang Kele tell you about it?
Why did she tell you about it first
and not me?
Because I had something important to do.
That's why I went out.
But don't worry.
She and I are just friends.
I trust you.
As for that tunnel...
A secret between us.
Where did you get this motorbike?
I just bought it.
You're home late. Where did you go?
On a ride!
What about you?
I... I...
I worked overtime.
Okay, I can't hold it in anymore.
I'll talk first.
I made up with Lu Xiao.
He promised me that he would go with me
to see his mother.
Then I won't hide this from you either.
Xu Nian and I made a promise.
We'll go on dates in the outside world.
I want to show him
the outside world before having him
make the decision.
But he never came.
Oh, I know what happened.
What happened?
Here,
why don't we find a place
to get a drink and talk?
I'll get the car.
Wait.
Come with me on my motorbike.
We'll take a ride.
Your new motorbike?
Brand new!
Let's go.
Morning, Kele.
Morning.
Here for work, eh?
Don't talk to me!
What's gotten into you today?
You seem unfriendly towards us.
Don't both of you know?
Why did you chase after me
when I went out to buy candles
last night?
Oh, that.
Mr. Xu already gave us a scolding.
I promise I won't mistake you
for someone else again.
Before this, I thought both of you
might have bad eyesight too.
But now?
I can't tell if that's the case
or if you guys are after my beauty.
No, no, of course not!
Absolutely not!
I swear. Both of us
do not have any sort of
intentions towards you.
Right. I swear to the heavens!
Never mind.
I wouldn't know even if you broke it.
Only the heavens would know.
Anyway,
I've reported the damages you caused me
to Mr. Xu.
You'd better
watch how you treat me from now on.
Please come in, Ms. Jiang!
What was that?
Sorry!
Why didn't you knock?
I... I thought you would get
used to it by now.
Well, I'd still like some privacy.
Sorry. My bad.
I came to tell you
that we'll make our move tonight.
One, two,
three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Two, two.
Seven, eight.
Stop.
Luo Ke,
why is your body so stiff today?
Su Lie, help him stretch his body.
Stretch? That's painful!
I don't want to do it!
What is it? Tell me.
I have something important
to do tonight.
I have to go out.
If anything happens,
cover for me.
Okay. I'll go out after you come back.
Cover for me then.
Okay. No problem.
Change.
Oh my god.
Hurry. Hurry.
Hang on.
Pass it over.
Why are you so slow today?
Must be because of the stretch earlier.
I haven't recovered from it yet.
Maybe you'll feel better
after playing a few rounds.
Get the food out. Faster.
I'm already doing that.
Hang on, hang on.
The plate is over there.
Oh, just cut the vegetables.
They've been playing for over an hour
and they're still playing it.
I can't stand it any longer.
I'm going to get them
back to their rooms right now.
No, you can't be violent.
But they...
Leave it to me.
Hurry, hurry.
It's counting down.
Get the plate over here.
Hurry up.
Xu Nian, what are you doing?
We were just about
to complete that level.
Playing games, huh?
Have you learned the dance?
We practiced together
this afternoon, didn't we?
Right. We stretched together too.
There are still a few moves
you guys haven't perfected yet.
-I...
-That's enough.
Come with me. We're going to practice.
Hurry up.
Come on.
Let's go.
Do you want to give it a try?
Here?
♪Sweet strawberry flavored jelly♪
♪That's what I think of
when you smile back at me♪
♪I feel my heart stir
when we accidentally touch♪
(Please don't follow
the dangerous activities.)
♪Let love explode and bombard you
with sweetness♪
♪I'll take your entire world by storm♪
Hold on to me tightly.
♪I'll follow you wherever you go♪
♪Like a tail you can't get rid of♪
♪I'll bombard you
with the sweetest words♪
♪And you receive them with a smile
I'm so glad I didn't mess up♪
♪Life is too short.
Let's grasp the moment and fall in love♪
♪Stay true to your feelings♪
One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight. Two...
Su Lie, why did you stop?
I still think it's weird
that it's just the three of us here.
He's right. Why isn't Lu Xiao here
getting his moves checked too?
Do you want to check his moves?
Go and get him then.
Su Lie, why don't you go?
I think you should go, Luo Ke.
I think it's better that you go.
I think
we're good with just the three of us.
Right.
Su Lie, count the beats.
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Over here, Lu Xiao.
Can I help you?
We're here to visit a patient.
Name?
I'm Jiang Kele.
Not your name.
I'm Li Zhenyu.
I meant the name of the patient.
Jiang Wenyue.
She's in the ICU.
How is her condition?
Not well.
She was resuscitated again this morning.
I don't think she can hold on
for much longer.
Where is the ICU? I want to visit her.
It is past the visiting hours.
Come again tomorrow.
No, I mean...
She doesn't have much time left
and you won't let him see her?
Then why are you wasting our time
with all those questions?
If I hadn't wasted your time,
how would I have known that
you were here to visit an ICU patient?
I'm sorry.
I went through
a lot of difficulties just to get here.
Could you please let me see her?
Just one glance.
Not even a single glance.
Do you have any sense of compassion?
I'm telling you,
if you're the reason
that a son couldn't even
see his mother in her final moments,
I'll have you pay for it!
The rules are put in place
for ICU patients
for the sake of their welfare.
You are only allowed
to visit for two hours each day.
From 2 p.m. to 4 p.m.
It's way past that time now.
The patient needs to get rest.
You can come again tomorrow.
What if we have to see her today?
Then I'm afraid
I'll have to call security.
Never mind.
We should go.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, Lu Xiao.
It's my fault for not checking
the visiting hours ahead.
It's my fault that we ended
wasting this trip.
Kele, it's fine.
I'm grateful that you're here with me.
We'll just think of this as a chance
to get familiar with the route.
Then let's go back now.
Xu Nian is still waiting for you.
We'll come again tomorrow.
But we have rehearsals tomorrow.
I might not be able to come out.
Don't worry. Leave it to me.
I'll think of a way for sure.
Don't give up. We are the best.
We can do it!
(Crush On Love)
(General Manager Room)
I'm sorry I'm late again!
I know.
Kele told me
that you were held up.
But I was late again.
We never fixed the time
of our dates.
Did you run all the way here again?
Yes. I didn't want to keep you waiting.
Take this card.
You can use it to grab a ride.
(iPass)
That way, you won't have
to run all the way here anymore.
Xu Nian, are you asleep?
We got too excited from dance practice,
and now we can't sleep.
We finally got the hang
of the hardest moves.
Come out and see them.
Yes, come out now.
Or we'll forget them again tomorrow.
He might be asleep.
We'll know when we get inside.
What are you guys trying to do?
Dancing so late at night?
Do you really love dancing that much?
Then why don't I have you guys
dance until the morning?
No, no, no. That's okay.
We'll dance tomorrow.
Sorry to bother you, Xu Nian.
Good night!
We'll be going then, bye!
They won't notice you with this on.
Do you want that?
I gave you a card, right?
Use it to buy whatever you want.
You can get anything you want.
Give me the bag. Go on now.
A serving of popcorn, please.
Thank you.
You bought it?
Here, try some.
How is it?
Tasty.
What are they doing?
They're feeding their "boyfriends".
Boyfriends?
Where are they? I don't see them.
You might be one of their "boyfriends".
Or Lu Xiao, Luo Ke, and Su Lie.
This is your game, Love Boys.
These girls can choose
from any one of you
to have date, go shopping, have a meal,
and watch a movie with them.
Anything.
I understand.
It's just like how we were before.
So that's how it looks like
in real life.
They're different from us.
There is no real human being
behind their games.
True. You're the only one
who got the one-on-one service.
We met and fell in love with each other
through this game,
and that's how
we got to where we are now.
Holding hands
and strolling along the streets.
But for them?
They won't have anything to speak for
at the end of the day.
It's just a game.
Is it necessary to expect so much?
At least, they're happy right now.
They seem to be enjoying themselves.
Isn't that enough?
Don't you think you're fooling yourself?
If this game never existed,
those young women
would be able to look for a partner
in their real lives.
They'll try to understand each other
and learn how to compromise
and how to change for the better.
And they'll be able to acquire
true love and happiness.
A real lover, Xu Nian.
Not a virtual character.
Yes, you have a good point.
But,
these girls couldn't
find a partner in real life.
And that's why they ended up
playing the game?
To find a partner,
a companion,
to love, to understand
and to rely on each other
among this sea of people.
Isn't that something
everyone has to go through in life?
But them?
They're addicted to the game.
They've given all their time and money
to a bunch of data.
That'll only make them
grow further and further away
from reality.
Only one end awaits them at the end,
a life of loneliness.
Qianya. Look.
Some people might really
want to find true love
and a partner in real life.
But there are those
who are happy to stay
in their happy world inside the game.
As long as
they aren't hurting anyone,
it's their right to choose
to do what they love.
Isn't that right?
Well, then do you know
just how many couples and families
have been torn apart in real life
because of this game?
I've never been in love
with anyone before,
but I've read a lot of books.
In the books, it's written
that cracks of a relationship
and marriage
begin to appear for internal reasons.
Perhaps we shouldn't place the blame
for such a complicated phenomenon
onto a game, hm?
That's because you've been
staying inside the Bay House
for over 20 years!
You've never been outside!
Everything you know
are from books!
But things are different in real life,
Xu Nian.
Are... Are you angry?
No, I'm not!
I just think that you're just
the same as Xu Guanghan.
You twist words and use false logic!
Qianya...
Don't touch me! Eat your popcorn!
(iPass)
(Xu Guanghan)
(Guan Qianya)
(Xu Guanghan and Guan Qianya
meet in a debate on live-stream.)
(It's true that there is nothing)
(for me to say in this situation.)
(Given all of your intelligence,)
(I think it might be better)
(for me to show it to you.)
(Guan Qianya, women's last hope,)
(and the leader of the opposition
against Y4.)
(Based on the video,)
(it's safe for me to say)
(that Guan Qianya)
(is a heavily addicted player
of Love Boys herself, isn't she?)
It's so hard to change
someone else's mindset.
Did I rush into things?
Maybe I should've given him more time.
It was only his second time
coming outside, after all.
To find a partner,
a companion,
to love, to understand
and to rely on each other
among this sea of people.
Isn't that something
everyone has to go through in life?
But them?
They're addicted to the game.
They've given all their time and money
to a bunch of data.
That'll only make them
grow further and further away
from reality.
♪Every night I see you in my dreams♪
♪Dreams and reality become entangled♪
(Guan Qianya sells off assets
to save Crush On Love from bankruptcy)
♪I can't tell them apart♪
♪You and I have different memories♪
♪As if we're searching
for the intersection♪
♪Piecing together the
secrets of the future♪
Aunty.
How did you get in here?
Didn't I change the door
and the password?
Let me tell you something.
Your password is super easy to guess.
It could only be four numbers!
Your birthday, your father's birthday,
your mother's birthday or my birthday!
But I didn't use any of those this time.
Yes, you didn't.
So I was especially careful this time.
I entered the date of "her" birthday.
And it just...
Slowly opened.
It was amazing!
I never thought
that you were such a pure-hearted man.
She had already left the entertainment
business for so many years.
And she married off to another country.
She formed a new family in Canada.
And you still can't let her go.
Aunty,
I must clarify something with you.
I didn't use her birthday
as my password
because I couldn't let her go.
It's because
I thought no one knows her birthday.
How did you know about her birthday?
Don't forget.
She almost became your wife back then.
We went out for meals
and went shopping together.
We did our nails and lashes too.
We were such good friends back then.
So both of you
did so many boring things together.
These may sound boring
to all of you men,
but to us women,
these are precious moments
of companionship.
Perhaps...
She thought
I was the only closest family you had.
And that's why
she tried to butter me up.
That woman did everything she could
just to get what she wanted.
How many times have I told you this?
Mind your words.
Be kind.
If you could have
changed your personality,
she and Qi Chuan wouldn't have left you.
I spent so much time and energy
making them into who they were.
Did they just leave?
No. They betrayed me.
I take back what I said earlier.
If you could've been kinder to them,
they wouldn't have betrayed you.
Is it my fault that they betrayed me?
They betrayed me
because their moral code's gone awry.
But losing them
is your loss.
It's their loss!
Look at Ge Yilan.
She could've been a megastar.
But she ran off to Canada
and became a housewife.
And Qi Chuan?
He doesn't even have enough songs
to open a musical concert
to earn some money.
How could that be?
I was
going to buy a ticket for his concert
to go and see him.
Don't waste your money.
He saved me a seat.
You can have it.
But I advise you
not to go and listen
to him singing that one song on loop.
Well, you'd better remember
to save me a ticket
for Y4's concert too.
Y4's concert?
You never attended any of their
previous concerts when I invited you.
Why are you asking for a ticket now?
It's different now.
The previous concerts
aren't fun at all.
Those were all projections. Fake.
But it's different this time.
They said I'll get to see
and touch them.
Actually, I'm really happy.
You changed.
Have you really figured it out?
That you'll put the four of them
under the sunlight again?
Don't worry.
All will be revealed
at the concert.
He didn't come yesterday.
Is he not coming
to practice today either?
You're actually badmouthing Lu Xiao.
I wouldn't dare say it to his face,
but behind his back...
Let's go.
Lu Xiao, are you ready?
What's wrong?
I think I have a fever.
A fever?
You're burning up.
How did you catch a fever?
Was it because of last night?
Last night?
Could it be that he couldn't sleep
because we were too loud?
That doesn't have anything to do
with catching a fever, right?
What are you guys doing?
-We...
Are you all right?
He has a fever. He needs to rest.
Let's go outside.
Okay.
♪I'm sorry I admit♪
♪Every night I see you in my dreams♪
♪Dreams and reality become entangled♪
♪I can't tell them apart♪
♪You and I have different memories♪
♪As if we're searching
for the intersection♪
♪Piecing together
the secrets of the future♪
♪I'm falling hard♪
♪Draw a circle to encircle our hearts♪
♪A heart for a heart♪
♪Your favorite melody begins to play♪
♪In my mind♪
♪Beautiful memories
that belong only to us♪
♪Draw a circle to encircle our memories♪
♪Surrender our feelings to each other♪
♪Humming your favorite melody♪
♪Reminding you♪
♪Of the memories we shared♪