ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
WOOHYUNG ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
What was this?
HAN TAE-SAN
Tae-san…
-What is it?
-I can't do this.
-What's wrong?
-I dropped this last time.
The film keeps getting stuck now.
I told you to just get a digital camera.
Nobody uses film cameras these days.
No way. Decent digital cameras
would cost as much as a car.
And didn't I tell you?
Digital cameras don't have that warmth.
How should I put it?
It lacks the human touch.
It's about humanity, you know?
Hello? Anybody in there?
That's a machine too, you know.
My gosh.
All right.
All right, it's done.
Okay.
Yes! Tae-san! Look, it's working!
-It's working!
-What? It's working?
Yes! Let's get a digital camera now!
It's really working, right?
Was that really you, Tae-san?
100 MISSED CALLS
JANUARY 22, TUESDAY
UNKNOWN CALLER
What?
Mr. Han Tae-san.
Mr. Han!
Yes?
Why weren't you picking up your calls?
You heard about me, right?
It's me, Mr. Park.
Well, the phone was off.
Did you arrive okay?
Pardon?
Oh, yes.
Then you should've called me.
Where did you fall, then?
Well, the reed field in Gimpo.
Goodness.
That must've been pretty rough.
There have been download errors
these days.
Everyone keeps falling over there.
You're not injured or anything?
Oh, and what about the Control Bureau?
Oh, it's all right.
That's a relief.
So, did you bring it?
Well, yes. I did bring the stuff,
but what exactly do you mean?
I guess it's natural to forget.
I mean the key!
Did you bring the key?
The key?
Yes, I have the key.
Are your limbs all there?
What?
Are your limbs all intact?
Yes.
Good. Your health is the most important.
All right. Let's meet.
Bring the key.
Where should I go?
No, it's fine. We'll come pick you up.
Where are you now?
I'm at an acquaintance's house.
An acquaintance?
You said your limbs are all intact, right?
Yes.
But let me ask you something.
What's the number
written on your right arm?
Hey. You're not Han Tae-san, are you?
What was that?
The number you have dialed cannot…
Damn it.
SEUNG-BOK
-Hello?
-Why weren't you picking up?
I'm on my way.
Oh, right. The meeting. It's over, right?
I'm sorry about that.
I'll make sure to attend next time.
Hello? Seung-bok?
You're angry at me again.
Why do you always get angry at me?
Just come home right now.
What's going on? You're scaring me.
Hello?
FORENSIC INVESTIGATION
Who are all these people?
The security alarm went off.
What about the security camera?
Nobody was caught on camera.
I don't know what happened.
Has any of your belongings gone missing?
I'm not sure.
Look carefully.
It looks like the culprit
made a huge mess.
-No, it's just the way it was when I left.
-Pardon?
Well, it may look messy,
but it's actually pretty organized.
-So it was like this…
-Hang on.
Something's different.
It's fine now.
It seems like a simple
breaking and entering case.
Did you see anyone suspicious
when you left the house?
The drawing.
It was always like that.
No, I hung it upside down on purpose.
Mr. Kim, take that down.
"Don't look for your brother.
If you do,
you'll die"?
What?
This is crazy. How did they get in?
I've requested officers to be placed here
and got all the guards to come.
I'm canceling all your schedules for now.
But by "brother," did they mean Tae-san?
What did they mean by not looking
for your brother?
I have no idea.
Hey, this isn't something
you can just forget about.
Stop saying you don't know
and think about it.
Have you done anything weird recently?
Mr. Han Tae-san.
Did you bring it?
Did you bring the key?
Strange. I'm sure I saw it before,
but I can't remember where.
It's not here.
Is this it?
This must be it.
Why is that locked up?
Is this it?
I give up.
What?
Mr. Han, I'm going home now.
Not now! Come over here.
Come on.
Hurry!
Oh, gosh.
-Darn it.
-Where to?
What is this?
-Over here. Put it here.
-On the floor?
Put it down.
-What are you doing?
-I'm making a darkroom.
Bong-seon, there's a red safelight
in the storage room.
Go and bring it for me.
-And get a cup of coffee on the way back.
-Okay.
-Iced coffee.
What's with all these photographs?
Did you take them when
you were birdwatching?
Yes.
They're not birds.
They're not.
Could it be a stalker?
Maybe.
Hey.
Who's that?
My brother.
Didn't your brother…
He died.
They look like photos that were taken
after he died. What is all this?
This is impossible.
-What is it?
-Hey.
-What?
-The date…
It's today.
What?
What about this?
This is crazy.
The conference. It's in two days.
No way.
Did you get married?
What are you talking about?
Hey, I don't even know this woman.
You married someone you don't even know?
Shut up.
I don't know what's going on, either.
What is all this?
Seo-hae.
Damn it.
Is it the girl or the world?
You can only choose one.
No.
Don't breathe.
Everything is poison.
I only took it off for a while
to tie my hair.
What about you, dad?
I'm fine.
SEYANGWON
That damn thief.
If I catch you, you're dead.
Darn it.
Where did it go?
It must be tough working in the heat.
Was there a burglary or something?
Yes. But we're not open yet.
We're open at 11.
I'm not here to eat.
What is it, then?
I'm from the Immigration Office.
HWANG HYUN-SEUNG
We don't have any illegal immigrants
working here.
I got caught for hiring one last time,
so I almost had to close the shop.
Now I never hire anyone who seems
the slightest bit suspicious.
It's not about that. We received a report.
It's the police, right?
Some strange woman entered our restaurant.
Please calm down,
and tell us exactly what's going on.
She doesn't seem to be a foreigner.
She speaks Korean.
But something smells fishy.
That's Sun's voice.
That lousy jerk.
I knew he'd cause trouble.
The man who made that call
works here, right?
Yes, he works in our kitchen.
But he isn't here yet.
His name is Sun? Is he a foreigner?
No, not at all. He's absolutely Korean.
I just call him that.
It's like a nickname.
His name is Choi Jae-sun.
He's not an illegal immigrant.
Did he do something wrong?
It won't cause us any trouble, right?
Could we take a look around inside?
Well, you should at least tell me
what this is about.
Check this place.
What are you doing?
We have signs of contact.
Where were you last night?
I was at home.
Are there any other security cameras
besides that?
No, that's the only one.
Were you with friends or family
last night?
No, I live alone.
This will get complicated.
Complicated? What do you mean?
Anyone who's come into contact
with them has to be quarantined.
Who are you guys? You're not
from the Immigration Office, are you?
Where are you from?
Sir, what's important
isn't "where."
Take care of him.
ON GOVERNMENT DUTY
I told you I don't have any.
I'll wire you some when I get paid!
I don't have a single penny
on me right now.
I'm hanging up.
This…
Damn it!
Hey! Do you have a girl
living in your house?
No.
Don't lie to me!
Then who's that girl over there?
Damn it.
Why is she out there when she's sick?
You have to pay extra
if you have a roommate!
Don't try to fool me!
Hey! Kid!
Darn it.
You shouldn't be out here
when you're sick.
You're here.
Let's go.
-That bag…
-I got it from your closet.
Let me borrow this.
Gosh, that's expensive.
-But where are you going?
-Busan.
Like that? Why?
If Han Tae-sul opened the suitcase,
they're going to kill him.
-Who?
-You don't have to come.
Just get me a ticket.
No way. You have to pay me first.
You said you'll give me the numbers
if I made the call.
I never said I would.
What?
Hey. I let you stay the night
and even fed you.
Plus, you're taking my bag.
That's worth a lot.
I didn't report you,
even if you seemed a bit strange.
And you do this?
I could just report you.
Give me back my bag.
Oh, sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I said I'm sorry.
What?
Who are you?
Are you a ghost?
You're a ghost, right?
Please spare me. Just this once!
I have an elderly mother
and a younger sibling.
My family will starve to death without me.
Please don't kill me.
Please, have mercy.
I'll tell you the rest
when we're in Busan.
Why would I go there?
I told you,
if Han Tae-sul opened the suitcase,
they'll kill him.
What does that have to do with me?
Are you coming or not?
Darn it.
Give me that.
I need clothes.
It's the only female clothing I have.
It's our restaurant uniform.
I don't know why it's here, though.
You wear that.
What?
Don't be ridiculous.
No way. This is a luxury brand.
It cost me a fortune.
Darn it.
This jacket's expensive.
That too.
-And your pants.
-What?
Gosh.
She's so annoying.
Let's go.
Right now?
Yes.
Hang on.
I need to call my boss first.
You can't get to Busan that quickly,
you know.
Hang on. I need to take the day off.
Why isn't he picking up?
Why isn't he answering?
Is he still not at the restaurant?
He's never this late.
Hang on one more minute.
Let me call once more.
Those kids? They're in there.
It's the Control Bureau.
What?
Put on your silencers.
There are eyes watching.
What?
Don't pull out your guns
in a cramped place like this.
Come on out!
That's enough.
Let's not do this. Come on out.
-We have to go.
-Go where?
Over there? No way.
They'll kill you since you were with me.
I'm not going.
They're not on the other side.
You can go by yourself.
Wait! Don't shoot! I didn't do anything!
I really didn't do anything.
-Please just let me go.
-Run!
Get up!
Unbelievable.
Illegal immigrants running around
in broad daylight?
Are you that desperate to die?
All right, then.
I'm not going to die today.
They're on a dump truck.
License plate, 92…
No need.
They can't last long without a broker.
Okay. We got a call from headquarters.
They found something.
Han Tae-sul. Don't open the suitcase.
Han Tae-sul? The Han Tae-sul?
Yes. The CEO of Quantum & Time.
She called with that man's phone.
Is Grandpa in there?
DECEASED, HAN TAE-SAN
Oh, the ashes got switched.
It must be tough for you.
I hope your loved one can rest in peace.
What a weirdo.
Gosh. You startled me.
What's this? A DNA test?
Wait. Damn it.
It's a paternity test.
I told you not to go outside.
Sorry, I forgot.
I'm going to go back home.
But why are you two always together?
What's going on?
Are you two dating?
Are you?
You guys…
Are you really…
I was just kidding, but I guess it's true.
It says there's a 99.9 percent chance
of not being a match.
Lucky you.
You two look great together. You did it!
Congratulations.
But…
is it really possible for someone
to fall from the sky?
I'm not sure
if it's scientifically possible.
I don't know, either.
Then what now? Should I take you home?
I guess.
By the way, how did they
get inside your house?
The house is technically impenetrable.
It's built like a safe.
-How did they get the door open?
-A safe…
You're a genius!
Hey! Go to Jeongan-myeon 21-2,
Paju, Gyeonggi Province.
I just remembered what that key is!
It's for a safe!
How did you even think of that?
You're so adorable.
Bong-seon.
Wait here, Bong-seon.
What is this place?
This place?
It's my first lab my brother built for me.
AUTHORIZED PERSONNEL ONLY
Come on.
It was around here somewhere.
Who took this?
WHAT MODEL PLANE DID HE RIDE?
FUND MANAGER KIM DONG-HYEON
YOO EUN-JI NAMED DEPUTY PRESIDENT
HAN TAE-SUL DISCHARGED FROM HOSPITAL
HAN TAE-SUL
QUANTUM & TIME CEO
What is this?
What took you so long?
What is all this?
This is the key to the safe, right?
Where's the safe?
Why did you deceive me?
Why did you pretend you were dead?
How…
How could you do this to me?
Answer your phone.
-Hello?
-Mr. Han Tae-sul?
Are you the famous Han Tae-sul?
You should've told me. It's an honor.
The safe was really heavy.
Who are you?
You have the key, right?
Come on, don't shout.
Shouting won't get you anywhere.
We should meet
and talk it out heart-to-heart.
What happened to my brother?
Let's take our time to talk.
You have the key, and I have the safe.
It takes two to tango, you know.
We should meet up and talk.
And it seems everything inside
will be destroyed if you force it open.
That's pretty smart.
How do you know my brother?
Your brother?
Well, we're business partners.
Just tell me one thing.
Was my brother alive all this time?
Of course!
-Why?
-"Why?"
My gosh. He's alive because he isn't dead!
What about the plane crash?
How did that happen?
You said you were going to ask one thing.
Question time is over.
All we need is that key.
We'll come find you,
so take care of yourself until then,
and keep that key safe.
Since we're making a deal,
let me offer you something as an extra.
Take a look outside.
ON GOVERNMENT DUTY
You see men in black uniforms, right?
Hey, Bong-seon.
Sir, some strange people
are heading that way.
Yes, I know. Hang on, don't hang up.
Okay.
Who are those guys?
The Control Bureau.
Are you
on their side?
Those guys are ruthless.
Once they catch you,
you'll never get back home alive.
If you want to know what's going on,
just do as I tell you.
I'll tell you what I tell all my clients.
"Run."
Darn it.
-Bong-seon.
-Yes, sir.
Get the car started.
Move in. We're going to capture him alive.
Go.
Darn it.
-Bong-seon!
-Yes, sir!
Bong-seon.
Bong-seon!
Bong-seon, let's go. Bong-seon!
You'll lose your breath
if you keep running like that.
Come with us.
Bong-seon.
Forty-eight kilometers
until your destination.
Turn that off.
Sorry, sir.
IMMIGRATION CONTROL BUREAU
"Immigration Control Bureau"?
Aren't you going a bit overboard
with immigrant management?
They're dangerous.
IMMIGRATION CONTROL BUREAU
NO SIGNAL
Damn it.
Pardon us for what we did to you.
I can't get a signal.
-It's for security purposes.
-What is this place?
The Immigration Office?
No, we've become a bureau since last year.
We're the Immigration Control Bureau,
Team 7.
Excuse us for a moment.
What are you doing?
Have you met this woman before?
No. Who is that?
Where is the suitcase?
Let me ask you again.
Who are you guys?
I told you
that we're the Immigration Control Bureau.
Managing immigrants coming from where?
What does that have to do with me?
Mr. Han, the important thing
isn't where they come from.
We don't want to harm you, Mr. Han.
Normally, we should've
taken care of you already,
but because of your social status…
You know what government business is like.
Please cooperate.
I'll ask you one last time.
Where's the suitcase?
I don't know.
All right.
You seem to be quite a playboy.
It's best to stay out of trouble
in these unsettling times,
don't you think?
There will be a "Me Too" article
released tomorrow.
What?
I guess your stock prices will drop
about ten percent.
And for the day after tomorrow…
Yes, this will be nice.
Retinol, diazepam…
Habitual use
of illegal psychotropic drugs.
If there's an article
about the CEO Han Tae-san
being a drug addict,
you'll have to give up your position.
Shall we meet again after that?
If you sit in that chair
after you become a normal citizen,
you won't be able to say things
so confidently like
"I don't know, I don't remember" again.
Whatever you want.
Everyone starts out as confident as you.
But they all act the same eventually.
They say "Please let me live,
I'll tell you everything.
Please just kill me."
Like your brother, Han Tae-san.
What did you just say?
Say that again!
Take him home.
You jerks! Come over here!
Mr. Han!
We're keeping an eye on you.
Watch your back.
Let me go. Let go of me, you punks!
Mr. Han!
Are you okay?
Mr. Han, are you sure you're okay?
I think you should get some rest.
After I regained consciousness,
I got a call from them.
They said you'll be out in a few hours.
They told me not to call anyone
and to wait for you at your house.
Then I found you unconscious
at the front door.
Who were those guys, though?
The Control Bureau.
Controlling what?
I don't know, either.
They wouldn't tell me.
I think you should really stay home
from now on.
That threat you received,
-and what happened yesterday…
-Let's go.
Where?
Busan.
Two tickets to Busan, please.
The 10:30 KTX Train arrives the earliest.
-How much is it?
-It's 119,600 won for two tickets.
Gosh. What about a Mugunghwa Train?
There's one that leaves at 10:20.
-How much is that one?
-It's 57,200 won.
I'll get two tickets for that.
If you're using your card,
insert it in the device here.
No, I'm paying with cash.
Here's 56,000 won, and…
Here. 1,200 won.
Two executive car seats
for a KTX Train to Busan.
What happened, Tae-san?
Bong-seon.
Do you think I've lost my mind?
I'm not sure.
I just…
miss my brother.
That's all.
Wouldn't it be dangerous?
-If they come to the conference…
-What if they do?
Maybe they're the ones
who wrote that on the wall.
The Control Bureau or something.
-No, they're not.
-How would you know that?
If they wanted to kill me,
they'd have done it yesterday.
-Then who…
-How would I know?
By the way, you're riding a train
instead of a plane…
Would you want to ride a plane
after a plane accident?
Gosh, those thieves. They always try
to make you buy the expensive ones.
Isn't it funny?
Look at the screen over there.
The KTX Train leaves ten minutes later
than the Mugunghwa Train,
but it arrives three hours earlier.
Doesn't that resemble our lives?
People who have wealthy parents
get to ride KTX Trains
and arrive earlier than other guys
even when they leave later than them.
Life is so unfair.
What? Is that blood?
Yes.
But who were those guys?
They said they were the Control Bureau.
Are you an illegal immigrant?
None of your business.
-Hey.
-What?
Who were they? They even had guns!
The Control Bureau.
What kind of government bureau
carries guns around like that?
My gosh. I almost died, you know.
I can't die. I told you.
I'm the breadwinner of my family.
If you don't tell me the lottery number…
I can't even go home,
and my boss isn't picking up my calls.
I don't even have money for the trip back.
-Just report me.
-What?
Jeez. What do you take me for?
But why are you looking for Han Tae-sul?
Do you know him?
Or is there money involved?
Or is it a love affair?
Is he really going to die?
Is he an illegal immigrant too?
Or is he in the Control Bureau?
-No.
-Then what?
I'm going to the bathroom.
What?
What the…
Damn it.
Hey! Are you in here?
Hey!
Damn it!
Damn it.
Hasn't this ever happened to you?
Seeing a photo of something
that hasn't happened yet, for example.
The future is already here.
It's just not widely in use yet.
The company decided not to give in
to the kidnapper's demands.
But how, when Tae-sul is still missing?
We still have you.
We need to make a move now.
You almost had us killed!
Who put you up to this?
Are you stalking me?
Is this like a one-night stand?
As if.
I'm the owner of Asia Mart.
What we do here is…
We're like the unofficial embassy.
We take care of people who came here
from other places.
Welcome to the future.
Subtitle translation by: Ju-young Park