ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Seo-hae, wake up.
Seo-hae.
Dad.
Time to go. It's your turn now.
Anything that weighs over 30kg
is not allowed in.
Microbial substances, living creatures,
and explosive materials are not permitted.
We assume no responsibility
and shall not be liable
for any injury, death, and accidents
that occurs during your trip.
-Form a line.
-You must get tested before you board!
-Move forward!
-Put your belongings in your suitcase.
-You may go.
-Move forward!
Let's meet again, alive and well.
-Move forward.
-Move forward!
-You, over there. It's this way!
-Hey, move it.
Let's go together, Dad.
I don't think I can go with you.
Tell me what I told you.
First, when you arrive.
When you arrive!
"Start running."
Do not let anyone catch you,
no matter what.
If you get caught,
just don't say anything.
Just pretend you can't talk. Okay?
Yes. But let's go together--
Second.
Hurry up!
"Do not trust anyone."
You never know who's your ally
and who's your real enemy.
Don't trust anyone. No one. Okay?
-Okay.
-Good.
What was the third thing?
Come on.
-Number 250811!
-Coming!
Quick. What was it?
"Han Tae-sul."
Han Tae-sul.
Stay away from him at all costs.
You must not cross paths with him.
Don't even talk to him, okay?
Then what about Mom?
What if she dies?
We all die in the end.
But I can't leave you alone here, Dad.
When you get there,
you'll find lots of good food
and all of your favorite fruits.
Real fruit, not the canned ones.
So just go.
Eat everything you want.
And do whatever you want.
Just enjoy your life.
Promise me.
-Number 250811!
-Coming!
Promise me.
If you don't, I won't let you go.
Let's go.
Catch her!
Darn it.
Hey! You, come here.
Yes, sir. How can I help you?
You call this ramyeon?
Are you blind? Look at this.
The noodles turned completely soggy.
How dare you make me eat this trash?
You eat this.
What? You can't either, can you?
I want you to scarf it down
and make me a new one. Okay?
Hey.
The new one will taste the same.
Where are we now?
We're 10,000m above the ground.
The low air pressure
lowers the boiling point.
That's why your noodles taste bad.
Didn't you learn in science class?
Who are you?
HAN TAE-SUL, QUANTUM & TIME
They took my picture
when I was at the lab,
so I don't look that good.
Next month, you'll see
my Hawaiian-themed photos.
If you give me your contact information,
I'll send them to you.
Have you been to Hawaii?
No.
Me neither.
-Why do you ask?
-You know…
If I ever fall in love with someone,
I want to take her there.
Just saying.
So just thank her for the noodles
and finish it.
Hey!
I don't want to.
In that case,
this evening or tomorrow morning,
"rude ramyeon guy"
will be all over the Internet.
Are you blind? Look at this.
The noodles turned completely soggy.
How dare you make me eat this trash?
Damn it.
You eat this.
Thank you.
Excuse me. May I have a glass of water?
Coming right up.
Your number too.
But she's not your type.
I have to say
these first-class seats
are super comfortable.
I'm really proud of you, little brother.
And the quality of this wine is top-notch.
You should have a glass too.
You see, Tae-sul,
there's this article I read.
If the brain is stressed all the time
like yours is…
What was that?
Right, adrenaline.
The body produces it,
which weakens the immune system.
I read it in the newspaper.
Hey, Tae-sul.
I'm talking to you. Look at me.
Are you mad at me or something?
Why are you ignoring me?
Because…
you're dead.
Here's your water.
Stay seated.
-Fasten your seat belts.
-Don't worry. It must be some turbulence.
Stay seated.
What's going on?
Got it.
Please fasten your seat belt.
We're experiencing some turbulence…
-…at the moment.
-Your seat belt, please.
Please return to your seats
and keep your seat belts fastened.
-What's happening?
-What's going on?
Captain.
Captain!
Stewardess!
Are you okay?
Tae-sul.
Tae-sul!
Han Tae-sul!
Sir, wake up. Sir!
Hey! Wake up, sir!
Wake up!
What is going on?
Someone just…
Right over there.
Captain.
Captain!
Please stay in your seats!
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm trying to fix the plane.
With that?
During World War II,
they used this to fix aircraft.
I told you.
Let's see.
It's hovering around 150.
It's about to stall!
Hold on.
The power's out
only for the control panel.
Can you make a safe landing
if I get it running again?
What?
Can you?
Yes.
We're at 20,000 feet above sea level now.
That means we've got
3 minutes and 30 seconds.
Let me know every 30 seconds. Okay?
Hurry!
Thirty seconds down.
Okay.
I'm going to divert the current
using a magnet.
It's…
Okay, let's go.
What are you doing?
You can't break that thing!
There's a magnet in this panel.
Here it is. Do you need this now?
We're going to crash!
This is nerve-wracking.
All right, let's see.
Which one's broken? Hold on.
Another 30 seconds down.
Only 2.5 minutes left.
This is the one.
Do you have a lighter?
SEUNG-BOK
Hey. Hey, look!
What?
Jeez, this prick. I'm busy right now.
I need to take this call.
Hey, Seung-bok.
Where are you now? I couldn't reach you!
-The board members are angry.
-It's been hours.
Why isn't he coming?
This is Mr. Han. I got a hold of him.
You'll get fired if you keep missing
the board meeting and causing trouble.
Who can fire me? It's my company.
Anyway, where are you now?
Me? On an airplane.
Airplane…
Then how did this call get through?
The plane's falling now.
What?
I'm not in the mood for jokes right now.
I'm serious.
You can get a signal at lower altitudes.
You said you couldn't reach me earlier.
That's enough.
You need to call 911 or the airport now.
Air Koreana JH007, arriving from Saipan.
The plane's about to crash in Seoul.
We're flying below 10,000 feet
at the moment.
And the current speed is 100 knots.
Captain! The captain's dead.
And the copilot. He's not doing well.
He's confused.
There was a 10cm-wide hole
on the window here, but I've taped it up.
I'm fixing the electrical system now.
So? Where's Mr. Han right now?
How much longer must we wait?
He's on his way now.
You rascal.
If this is a joke, I'm going to kill you.
Give me that.
His nonsense is getting out of hand.
What? "The plane is falling"?
You rascal.
BREAKING NEWS: AIR KOREANA JH007
STALLING OVER SEOUL, OUT OF CONTACT
Hey, Tae-sul.
Are you lying to me
after seeing this on the news?
Seriously?
Look. Isn't this cool?
Hey.
You're out of your mind.
Contact Air Koreana now!
Right now!
Hey, Seung-bok.
Start recording what I say.
Record this call!
Why should I record it?
Just do it! Are you ready?
Yes, ready. Speak.
I, Han Tae-sul,
will liquidate all my savings, stocks,
certificates of deposit,
and real estate properties
except for the penthouse
and donate half of it
to a foundation which I'll set up.
Come up with a name for it.
The other half will be put toward
the company's R&D funds.
And my stock options
will be transferred
to every Quantum & Time employee,
excluding the executives.
What in the world are you talking about?
My last words, Seung-bok.
You can have the penthouse.
Are you crazy?
Do you want more?
Take my Lamborghini and Porsche too.
And give my Maybach,
Range Rover, and 63 AMG
to my bodyguard, Yeo Bong-seon.
Tell him I appreciate his hard work.
That's it.
The plane will crash in 50 seconds.
Stop recording.
Did you hit the stop button?
I did.
Hey, this is just between you and me.
I won't say it twice, so listen carefully.
The password for the safe in
my dressing room at the penthouse. 1-0-0…
It's 100811.
August 11? The day we got listed?
Destroy all the research documents inside.
And there's something I have to tell you.
Remember your girlfriend
back in university? What was her name?
The mean one? Yu-ri.
Right, Yu-ri!
I'm the one who went to Wolmido with her.
I was reminded of her
because this feels like the Apollo Disco.
I'm sorry, buddy.
I wish you all the best, idiot!
Han Tae-sul, you…
Breaking news.
Air Koreana JH007 was scheduled to arrive…
-Mr. Han is on his way here.
-…at Incheon Airport from Saipan…
-…at 2 p.m. today.
-Come on.
But the control tower lost communication
with the aircraft at 1:53 p.m.
-He's on that flight.
-Fire Services has been dispatched…
-…in case the plane crashes.
-On that plane?
-The aircraft's location…
-What?
-…is currently being monitored.
-Why is he running late?
-The CEO of Quantum & Time, Han Tae-sul…
-Nonsense!
-…is one of the confirmed passengers.
-What?
Time's up.
Let's get ready.
You'll die without any safety equipment.
Really?
Then I can see you again.
The plane will crash!
No.
I won't let that happen!
The CEO of Quantum & Time, Han Tae-sul,
who was in critical condition,
regained consciousness this morning.
On the 15th of last month,
CEO Han Tae-sul managed to fix
Air Koreana JH007
when it was about to crash
due to an electrical problem
inside the flight deck
while making its way
to Incheon Airport from Saipan.
-He saved the lives of 261 passengers.
-The authorities believe it was caused…
-…by a bird strike.
-We're seeing…
countless social media posts
wishing him a quick recovery.
His nicknames on the internet included
"Sexy Brainiac"
and "Engineering Heartthrob."
CEO Han Tae-sul plans to move back home
and keep receiving medical treatment,
but Quantum & Time is refusing
to give detailed comments
on his current condition,
which is only sparking more curiosity.
CEO Han Tae-sul,
who had been in critical condition
since the plane crash last month,
miraculously regained consciousness
and was discharged today at 12 o'clock.
He took the world by storm
with the launch of Q20.
-But the company's ambition…
-You can go in now.
…now faces a crisis.
Quantum & Time is going to hold
a conference this August.
It is unclear
whether CEO Han will attend or not.
-But sources say that he will…
-Hurry, this way.
-…work from home until he recovers.
-It's not that heavy.
The authorities believe
the JH007's electrical problem
was caused by a bird strike,
a collision between an airborne animal
and the aircraft.
They're examining
the black box recordings at the moment.
I told them not to use that photo.
Go to our PR team's office
and rip that photo to pieces.
Hey, Bong-seon.
You must be disappointed.
My Maybach and Range Rover
could've been yours.
No, sir.
No?
You fool.
"Dear CEO Han Tae-sul."
Goodness.
Lee Hae-na, a first grader
from Nakmin Elementary School,
wants to marry me when she grows up.
What do I say in my reply?
How about this?
"Dear Hae-na.
By the time you can get married,
my telomeres would be so short
that my cells probably
wouldn't be able to divide anymore.
So I suggest you find
someone with healthier cells."
-Come again?
-You don't get it?
Then how about this?
"Dear Hae-na. By then,
I'll start receiving my pension."
Good one, right?
Why did you turn it off?
What's wrong?
You punk, you're sulking again.
Is this because of the Wolmido incident?
I shouldn't have told you.
I didn't even hold her hand. Trust me.
"Board Resolution.
If CEO Han Tae-sul
continues to harm the company's…"
What is this?
It was approved when you were dead.
When I was dead?
I said you were declared brain-dead.
Hey, I was just getting some rest
because I was exhausted
after saving 261 precious lives,
and the board tried to oust
the founder of the company?
This is why I begged you
to attend the board meetings.
Why do you keep causing trouble?
What trouble did I cause?
Did the plane crash because of me?
Why did you go to Saipan?
-To get some air.
-Without a word?
Why do I have to tell you?
Risperidone, amisulpride,
diazepam, zolpidem.
I'm not an idiot.
You drug addict, listen to me.
Things are different now.
The company has grown.
Be more responsible!
The livelihoods of 100,000 people
depend on you,
so stop taking those pills
and get therapy.
What if I don't?
Tae-san's dead.
You bastard.
It's been hard for me too.
I know you and Tae-san were close.
That day--
Hey, shut up and get lost.
Stop taking pills and get therapy.
If not, I can't help you anymore.
Han Tae-sul,
can you please snap out of it?
You weren't like this.
I was always like this.
You can act all messed up,
but I know you're better than this.
You risked your life
to save all those people.
Not everyone can do that.
Are you kidding me?
I don't care if they died or not.
All I did was fix what was broken.
That's all. Who cares?
It's been a month
since the accident took place.
How have you been?
Pretty okay.
Do you have trouble sleeping
or get flashbacks of the accident?
No, I don't.
How much sleep did you get last night?
I didn't sleep last night.
-Why not?
-I couldn't fall asleep.
Seo-jin.
Stop interrogating me
and just prescribe me some pills.
I can't just give you
a prescription anymore.
The company wants your counseling reports.
"The company"?
I think you're forgetting something here.
I'm the CEO of that company.
Mr. CEO,
you have to stay for the full session
for me to write this report.
"Report"?
Hold on.
Does that mean you're spying on me?
Please sit down, Mr. CEO.
I want us to be clear
about this one thing.
You dumped me. Right?
You secretly went to the Maldives
with that sexy idol singer.
That's why I dumped you.
Precisely.
Do you still see things?
Nope.
Promise me you'll prescribe me
those pills if I cooperate.
Tell me about your brother.
Your relationship with him
and how you felt about him.
I don't remember.
I heard the two of you
didn't exactly get along
before he passed away.
You guys had a big fight.
What happened?
Nothing happened. Let's stop here.
Just give me those pills.
They're only a temporary fix.
What was the last encounter
with your brother like?
Do you…
regret what happened that day?
Tae-sul!
CONGRATULATIONS
QUANTUM & TIME LISTED ON NASDAQ
Your hard work has paid off.
You just need to get rich now.
Congratulations.
Tae-sul!
I'll make it quick. Tae-sul!
-Hold on.
-You can't go in.
Tae-sul!
I'm his brother.
Just a second. I'm his brother.
Don't we look alike?
-Hold on.
-You can't go in.
Let go of me.
I told you that I'm Tae-sul's brother.
It's okay. I'm sorry.
-Tae-sul.
-What is it?
Sorry. It's an emergency.
I saw them.
Remember what I told you?
-Tae-san.
-I'm serious.
They were holding a suitcase--
Did you drink again?
A little. But that's not why
I'm telling you this.
Tae-sul. The director needs you.
Tae-san. How are you?
I'll be right in.
Stop rambling and go home.
I'll call you later.
-This is an important--
-This is important too.
It concerns you as well.
We're not the only ones in this world.
People who aren't from this world
are living among us.
Even now!
They're hiding somewhere, watching us.
Tae-san, please.
Enough of this crazy talk!
Listen to me. They're looking for you.
-Why are you doing this?
-Believe me, please.
They're looking for you.
They'll keep coming.
Who's coming? And from where?
That's not important. Remember--
All right, let's hear a few words
from Mr. Han Tae-sul,
who we're all so proud of.
Mr. Han.
Mr. Han?
Did you hear that?
My company got listed today
and we secured some investments.
-Tae-sul--
-You're a shareholder too.
Take this. I'll call you tomorrow.
Let's talk then.
-Come on. Take it.
-This isn't about money, you know.
It won't take long.
Just spare me five minutes.
I know you went through a lot,
but must I put up with this forever?
-I'm just--
-I'll repay you for everything, so--
No. I'm just so worried about you.
What if something happens--
Tae-san! If you really care about me,
drop this and just go home.
-Hey, let's step out for a moment.
-Seriously, enough!
-I'll explain outside.
-I'll call you!
-No, our phones are tapped!
-For God's sake!
Jeez.
Tae-sul.
Wait, Tae-sul. Tae-sul!
-Mr. Han.
-Tae-sul.
Say a few words.
Thank you. I'm truly grateful.
I couldn't have made it this far
without the help I received
from so many people.
And I'd like to personally thank
one person in particular,
the chairman of the board,
who's right next to me.
Please give him a big hand.
Are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
Got the counseling report. Well done.
Make sure you attend
the remaining sessions.
I expect to see you
at the management meeting tomorrow.
Who in the world is that?
Are you insane?
What's wrong with you?
Come with me.
Come on, you punk!
Bong-seon! Wait a second.
Let go of him. I think I know him.
Are you all right?
The plane will crash!
It's you.
The copilot on that flight.
What happened? Who did this to you?
The Control Bureau.
Are you
on their side?
What?
That was not a bird.
I saw it.
What exactly did you see?
The suitcase.
What?
We're experiencing some turbulence
at the moment.
Please return to your seats
and keep your seat belts fastened.
What's that?
A suitcase?
What is that?
Is that a man?
Tae-san.
Tae-san!
You punk. There should be more.
You're not blind, right?
Then take a good look.
Can't you see? 30,000 won is missing.
-I didn't take it.
-You little rat.
Don't hit me, please.
Shut your mouth, you little thief.
I didn't steal it.
You collected all the cash yourself.
-I know nothing about it.
-Jeez, this punk.
I really know nothing about it.
You little…
Hey.
Tidy up everything before you leave, okay?
GOOD FORTUNE
It's not 30,000 won.
It's 50,000 won.
Come on. Money doesn't grow on trees.
I'm struggling to pay my rent here
and pay off my debt.
I told you that I'll send it.
Jeez. Okay, got it.
How's Go-eun?
Again?
Okay.
Yes! I said okay.
I'm doing fine here,
so just worry about yourself.
Yes, bye.
Damn, I'll never get out of this hellhole.
Those damn stray cats.
You scared me.
What are you doing?
Can't you speak Korean?
Are you Chinese?
Are you Japanese?
Please don't kill me.
Food.
-Police.
-Are you the police?
A suspicious-looking woman
just came to this restaurant I work at.
Please calm down and give us more details.
She speaks Korean,
so I don't think she's a foreigner.
But she's a bit weird.
Give us more details
of what she looks like.
I think she's wearing pajamas.
And no shoes. She showed up
with a suitcase and nothing else.
And she's…
No way.
-The 911th draw generated…
-Keep eating.
-…sales of 89.3 billion won.
-I'm just going to watch this.
The total prize was 21.1 billion won.
There were ten winners in total,
and each winner received 2.11 billion won.
In 2020, Lollo accumulated
809.4 billion won in total.
Congratulations, everyone.
I envy those lucky rascals.
The draw has begun.
The first lucky number is five!
Let's find out the second lucky number.
The second number is 21.
Let's check the third lucky number now.
Twenty-two.
It's the number right after 21.
Number 22.
-The machine is still running.
-Eight?
Now, I wonder
what the fourth number will be.
The next number is eight.
-Is this from last week?
-Now…
We'll unveil the fifth lucky number.
-What will it be?
-It's 18.
It is 18.
Now, let's find out the sixth number.
THE 912TH DRAW
Is it 38?
It's 38.
Now, we'll draw the bonus ball
for our second prize.
Ten?
It's ten.
The 912th draw…
-How did you know?
-CEO Han Tae-sul…
who had been in critical condition
since the plane crash last month,
miraculously regained consciousness
and was discharged today at 12 o'clock.
He took the world by storm
with the launch of Q20.
-But the company's ambition…
-How did you guess those numbers?
…now faces a crisis.
-Han Tae-sul.
-Quantum & Time is…
going to hold a conference this August.
It is unclear
whether CEO Han will attend or not.
But sources say that he will…
What was that?
What?
Where did she go?
What in the world is going on?
You're up.
My suitcase.
Look, it's right there.
You suddenly passed out.
Here. I believe
you enjoyed this yesterday.
Peel it before you eat it.
It tastes even better.
Here.
What were you doing?
Running away?
Is there anything else you need?
If not…
Can you have a look at this?
Han Tae-sul.
What?
Han Tae-sul of Quantum & Time. Call him.
-Sir.
-What?
Here it is.
Thanks. Did they hand it over right away?
Yes, they handed it over
as soon as I said you asked for it.
Tell them I said thanks.
But they did ask why you needed it.
I was just curious.
That's what I told them.
-Good job. Go home.
-I'll get going, then.
Bye.
12 MILES TOWARD GYEONGSANGNAM-DO
16,525 FEET ABOVE SEA LEVEL
Gimpo.
Sir!
Sir, where are you going?
Bird-watching.
But, sir,
the VP asked me to make sure
you attend the meeting.
Hey, have you ever been in a plane crash?
It's extremely traumatizing.
It's hard for me
to even be around people now.
Even my doctor said
I need some alone time.
You know?
-I do know, but--
-See you later.
Grab a bite or something.
All right. Have a safe trip.
SEUNG-BOK
THE MEETING'S STARTED. WHERE ARE YOU?
Do you regret what happened that day?
Enough. Just give me those pills.
How many times must I ask you?
You're just trying to avoid it,
but it won't help you in any way.
I'm saying this because
I'm worried about you as your friend.
You'll ruin yourself.
I'm sure your brother
wouldn't want to see you doing this.
Please.
Relax and open up
when you're here at least.
"Regret"?
Do I regret it?
I do.
Since that day,
there hasn't been a single day
that I didn't think about it.
When I'm eating, taking a shower,
when I'm driving
or even lying in bed at night,
it pops into my head.
He died on the spot.
The body was quite damaged,
so you might not recognize him.
-Tae-san.
-He had this backpack with him.
Is this your brother's?
KIMCHI RAMYEON
I shouldn't have been so harsh that day.
I shouldn't have kicked him out.
I should've at least
given him a warm send-off.
I should've called him right away.
I should have said,
"He's my brother,"
proudly in front of everyone.
That's what I should have done.
I laugh and chat with strangers
as if they're my best friends,
but as for my brother,
I never even had a chance to thank him.
Had I known that would be the last time…
If I knew…
I'd do anything
to go back to that day, even just once.
But I can't.
I know that it can't be undone.
I just…
I just wish he could come back.
That's all. I miss my brother.
I miss him like crazy.
What do you expect me to do?
Just get over it
and move on?
It's easier said than done.
How's that even possible?
So, please…
Just prescribe me those pills.
Help me, Seo-jin.
This pain is killing me inside.
We love our customers!
This is customer service agent Lee Eun-ji
at Quantum & Time.
You can talk now.
I need to speak to Han Tae-sul.
It's urgent.
Ma'am, do you mean you have
a complaint to bring to our attention?
No, I need to speak
to Han Tae-sul directly.
I understand, ma'am.
However, I cannot transfer this call
to our CEO at the moment.
I'll transfer you to the customer service
so you can leave your feedback.
Hello, this is Han Tae-sul
of Quantum & Time.
Han Tae-sul?
Quantum & Time is always waiting
for our customers' precious feedback.
Listen to me carefully.
There are people who are watching you.
Whether it's a suggestion or a complaint,
we're here to listen to everything
you have to say.
Please leave your message after the beep.
They're coming to get you.
Run. If you're caught, you'll die.
They're a lot scarier than you think.
Don't
trust anyone.
REPORTER KIM GYU-HYEON
Hello, Mr. Kim.
I'll tell you the details in person.
No.
I haven't told the company yet.
Right, by that intersection.
I know where it is.
Then I'll see you later.
DO NOT OPEN THE SUITCASE!.
(CALL HAN TAE-SUL!) TAKE IT AND RUN?
The suitcase.
Do not open the suitcase.
Don't open it.
If you do, we're all doomed.
Just wait for me.
We'll meet soon,
so do whatever it takes to--
All right. Thank you very much
for your feedback.
Your words of encouragement
and constructive feedback
are always immensely helpful
to all of us at Quantum & Time.
We hope you have an excellent day.
We love all our customers.
Han Tae-sul?
Han Tae-sul.
Hey, can you smile a little?
Are you that excited?
How did you prepare all this?
It must have cost a lot.
Thank me later.
Repay me for the rest of your life.
Okay, I will.
What's the password?
-Your birthday.
-Why, of all things?
All of my passwords are your birthday.
Tae-san. Was that really you?
-This is impossible.
-What's with all these photographs?
-Did you get married?
-I don't even know this woman.
You married someone you don't even know?
Who are you? Are you a ghost?
Please spare me. Just this once!
It's the Control Bureau.
What?
-We have to go.
-Go where?
They'll kill you since you were with me.
I'm not going.
Unbelievable.
Illegal immigrants running around
in broad daylight?
I'm not going to die today.
Did you bring it?
Then you should've called me.
-I'm from the Immigration Office.
-Who are you guys?
What's important
isn't "where."
-Who are those guys?
-The Control Bureau.
Those guys are ruthless.
Once they catch you,
you'll never get back home alive.
If you want to know what's going on,
just do as I tell you.
Come with us.
"Run."
Let me go. Let go of me, you punks!
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi