Watch on kisskh.me
[laid-back
hip hop music playing]
[rapping] ♪ Can I kick it? ♪
[pigeons]
♪ Yes, you can ♪
- ♪ Can I kick it? ♪
- ♪ Yes, you can ♪
♪ Well, I'm gone ♪
♪ Go on, then ♪
♪ Can I kick it? ♪
♪ To all the people who can
Quest like A Tribe does ♪
♪ Before this, did you really
know what live was? ♪
♪ Comprehend to the track,
for it's why, cuz ♪
♪ Getting measures
on the tip of the vibers ♪
♪ Rock and roll to the beat
of the funk fuzz ♪
♪ Wipe your feet really good
on the rhythm rug ♪
♪ If you feel the urge to freak
Do the jitterbug ♪
♪ Come and spread your arms
If you really need a hug ♪
♪ Afrocentric living
is a big shrug ♪
- ♪ A life filled with ♪
- ♪ Fun ♪
♪ That's what I love ♪
♪ A lower plateau
is what we're above ♪
♪ If you diss us,
we won't even think of ♪
♪ Will Nipper the doggy
give a big shove? ♪
♪ This rhythm really fits
like a snug glove ♪
♪ Like a box of positives
is a plus, love ♪
♪ As the Tribe flies high
like a dove ♪
[instrumental music plays]
[screeches]
[whimpering]
[rat] Oh, we've been at
this all day, buddy, I get it.
Those other spots
didn't float your boat,
but wait until you see
this next place.
It screams mouse house.
Wait, can I say that?
Is that copyrighted?
Heh. There we go.
Whoop. Sorry about this,
the elevator's, uh,
being repaired.
[rat] Boom!
I just had a vision!
You're chillin'
in your new crib,
but then
you get claustrophobic,
and then you get dizzy,
and to save you...
Ta-da!
Look at that view!
Resplendent, ain't it, huh?
It's got everything.
Built-in stereo,
but be careful, those seats
are very flammable.
[chuckles] I'm kidding.
I'm not kidding.
Jerry, baby,
I know it's no beauty,
but let's be honest here,
with your budget,
this is all you can...
Hey! You don't just Batman me.
You haven't even seen
the trunk yet.
- [male] ♪ Can I kick it? ♪
- ♪ Yes, you can ♪
- ♪ Can I kick it? ♪
♪ Well, I'm gone ♪
♪ Go on, then ♪
♪ Can I kick it? ♪
♪ To my Tribe that
flows in layers ♪
♪ Right now,
Phife is a poem sayer ♪
♪ At times,
I'm a studio conveyor ♪
♪ Mr. Dinkins, would you please
be my mayor? ♪
- ♪ You'll be doing us a really big favor ♪
- [screaming in distance]
- ♪ Boy this track really has a lot of flavor ♪
- Ahhh!
♪ When it comes to rhythms,
Quest is your savior ♪
♪ Follow us
for the funky behavior ♪
[instrumental music plays]
[chittering]
[crowd exclaiming]
[playing funky music]
Look, Dad. That blind cat's
playing piano.
There's a lot of weird stuff
in this city.
- You just gotta keep walking.
- [dog yipping]
[woman] I mean,
he's amazing on the piano,
and blind, too!
[man 1] That's one cool cat.
[man 2] Man,
that cat is out of sight!
This is so cool.
[crowd] Whoa!
Oh, wow! Isn't he cute?
[crowd cheering]
I thought I'd seen it all with
the blind, piano-playing cat.
[gasps]
[all gasp]
[crowd exclaims]
[man] Oh, man.
He can see!
[woman 2] He's a fraud!
He's a regular cat
playing the piano.
Man, I want my money back!
[crowd muttering]
[yelps]
[racy instrumental music]
[people exclaim]
[people screaming and grunting]
[horse snorts, whinnies]
[Tom grunts]
Ahhh.
[blows raspberry]
Hey. Are you okay?
You gotta be careful next time.
You could have really hurt me.
Oh, my gosh.
[rock instrumental music plays]
[woman] Suspended? Why?
[man on phone] For starters,
the 100 pounds of underwear
strewn up 5th Avenue.
Oh, come on,
you can't blame me for that.
That was
a cat-and-mouse situation,
and everyone knows
you just don't get involved.
You can reapply in four weeks.
No. Please, sir,
please, just...
You... You...
You can't do that to me.
Oh.
Last week, I helped a man
do a pull-up for an hour.
An hour! He achieved
his fitness goals with me.
[woman sighs] Okay.
What if I just...
I come and be your assistant?
Ms. Forester,
you started two months ago.
- It just doesn't work like that.
- [sighs in exasperation]
Maybe this job
never was for me.
- Maybe it's not.
- You know what? I quit.
[sighs]
[jazz instrumental music plays]
[horse whinnies]
HORSE: Mm-hmm. Uh-huh.
Whoa!
[car horn blares]
[snarls]
[grunting]
[disco instrumental
music plays]
[imperceptible chatter]
- Hello.
- Hey.
Back for another free meal?
[disco music continues]
[elevator whirring]
[music stops]
So, you new in town?
Somewhat.
You know what they say,
it's not a trip
to the Big Apple
without a walking tour
of the city.
Have you ever done one?
They're very well-reviewed,
actually, mine are.
It's a great deal, great offer.
I'm not a guest.
Then, pray tell,
why do you have a suitcase?
I'm here to interview for one
of the temporary positions.
Because of the wedding.
What wedding?
Preeta and Ben. [chuckles]
Ah. As in, like,
the Preeta and Ben?
New York society's
favorite couple.
It's going to be
quite the event.
- Huh.
- [exhales deeply]
The hotel is hiring?
Yes, but they're
very exclusive.
They certainly wouldn't
hire you. [chuckles]
Mm.
And what did you say
your name was again?
Linda Perrybottom.
Linda Perrybottom,
unfortunately,
you just failed the test.
What?
Your interview
started the minute
that you walked in the door.
I didn't realize, I just...
Employees
of the Royal Gate Hotel
must be accommodating,
masterly,
but above all, Linda,
discreet.
If they're telling
a perfect stranger
the intimate details
of the inner workings of
this hotel's private events,
well, that doesn't
quite cut it now, does it?
- I'd...
- May I see your resume?
- Please?
- Uh...
Yes, of course.
Thank you.
[chuckles, snorts]
Oh, wow.
Yeah, you've had
a lot of really cool jobs.
Yes, I have.
- [hesitantly] The Dorsey?
- Dorsey.
[hesitantly] The Armada.
These all are hotels?
Well, none are in New York.
I just moved here from London.
Listen, Linda.
I don't think you're right
for this weekend.
Oh.
[smacks lips, sighs]
We just need someone more...
local.
Well, I understand.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Hi. If I wanted to apply
for a temporary position
for this weekend...
Is this your resume?
- No, it's not.
- Wow, this is impressive.
[chuckles] My only... copy.
Well, you are definitely
gonna get hired.
In fact, I'm gonna
call them right now.
Right now?
- Yeah.
- [chuckles nervously]
[dialing]
- Lola...
- Mm-hmm?
if I wanted to shop for,
say, a jacket...
Uh, yeah, sure.
Just to the left over there.
Thank you so much.
- [clears throat]
- Hi, yeah, we have
a very lovely young lady
down at the front desk.
Uh, she's going to be...
[mid-tempo instrumental
music playing]
[grunting]
[groans]
[upbeat hip-hop music plays]
Well, well, well. [chuckles]
Look at what we got here.
You know,
if I wasn't a betting cat,
I'd say Tommy boy here
is trying to break
into the hotel.
That's sure what it looks like.
[Topsy] This here is our alley,
punk!
Which makes this our hotel!
[Butch] Wait, hold up.
Are you trying
to break into our hotel?
Yo, guys, don't worry about it.
It was a big misunderstanding.
- Right, Tom?
- [laughs]
Are you laughing at me?
Now, I'm sure you know what
I do to cats that laugh at me.
[Topsy] Come on, boss!
Preach! Preach to him!
Now, I was about to,
if you would shut that grill
and let me handle this.
[Topsy] My bad, boss.
- So, are you gonna answer me?
- [whistles]
[brakes screech, engine revs]
[Lightning] Oh, snap!
It's five-o! Drop and run!
- [Meathead] Oh, no, not again!
- Somebody pick me up,
- I can't run that fast!
- Hey, I'll see you again, Tom!
- [Lightning] Break yourself!
- [officer] Hey, get back here!
Phew!
[wood creaks]
Oh, yeah!
[sensual jazz music playing]
Welcome.
Thank you so much.
- You must be...
- Hi. Buongiorno.
Forester, Kayla.
I'm sorry in advance
about my resume,
but there was
a child downstairs
trying to spit their
Hubba Bubba under a table.
So I tore off a piece.
Good. I'm Terence Mendoza,
Events Manager.
And this is Mr. Henry Dubros.
- Hi.
- [Mr. Dubros] A pleasure.
[Terence]
He's our general manager.
[chuckles]
And I assume that that's
the aquatics manager?
That's Goldie.
She has no official position
at the hotel. That's a fish.
- [Kayla] That's the...
- [Mr. Dubros clears throat]
I must say, this is
a very impressive resume.
The Dorsey?
Oh. [softly] The Dorsey.
You know, I hate to name names,
but, uh, I will.
You must have known
Mrs. Josephine Pennybaker.
She was my mentor at Cornell.
It's an Ivy League school
founded in 1865
by Mr. Ezra Cornell.
That's where I got my master's.
I'm just sharing.
Of course I know
old Jojo Pennyfoot.
[chuckles] Yeah. What a hoot.
- [Mr. Dubros chuckles]
- Pennyfoot?
Well, Miss Forester,
we'll cut to the chase.
As I'm sure you know,
we have
a very high-profile event
happening here this weekend.
Of course, I'm very aware
of Ben and Preeta's wedding.
Well, we need to hire additional
staff through the week.
But they must maintain
the level of service
guests of
the Royal Gate expect.
- Nonetheless.
- And I'll be honest,
it's not often we come across
a resume this distinguished.
Excuse me,
but this, this is just
a piece of paper.
If I'm gonna be worthy
of this institution,
you need to see me in...
[exhales sharply]
action.
Are you gonna pick it up
or just leave it there?
Yes, sir.
Put it in the bin.
Terence.
[whispering] She thought the fish
was the head of the department.
Really?
A fish can't even walk.
It can't even...
Terence.
[grunts]
You're hired.
- [chuckles dryly] Really?
- Yes.
I mean, thank you.
Can you start today?
[exhales sharply]
That's gonna be a tall order.
Mm... Very in demand.
Okay. Yeah, you know what?
I'm gonna pull some strings.
It's difficult,
but, yeah, no problem.
One other thing.
Uh, we will be asking
all temporary staff
to stay at the hotel
through the week
leading up to the wedding.
Uh, just so that we can be
available to guests
at a moment's notice.
Is that something
you'd be comfortable with?
Anything for this hotel.
[upbeat instrumental
music plays]
No, it's better down.
10-4, good buddy.
Breaker, breaker, 1-9.
[sighs] Go get 'em.
Hair's better up.
It's more professional.
- [elevator bell dings]
- Good morning.
Good morning, sir.
- [elevator bell dings]
- [Kayla sighs]
[Terence] The Royal Gate
opened its doors in 1930
and was declared
a New York City landmark
- by 1962.
- Mm.
It's been through
two major renovations,
yet it remains the beacon
of service excellence.
[sniffing]
This place has been host
to four presidents,
three popes, two kings,
one queen,
oh, and Drake.
There are 260 rooms,
104 suites, and 21 floors
of impeccable luxury.
The water pressure
is never below 50 PSI,
and our thread count
is never below 800.
[Tom shrieks]
- Button, please.
- [man] Sorry, sir.
[Terence] The spa is
top-of-the-line,
and our spin instructor won
the Tour de France. Twice.
[Kayla] Right.
[Terence] This wedding
is the most prestigious event
the Royal Gate has hosted.
And it will be
a perfect success.
It has to be.
The positive press an event
of this magnitude can generate
is invaluable.
Would you stop that, please?
- The... Yeah, sir.
- Okay.
Yes. It's just,
it tends to ride up.
[Terence] Our wedding menu
is being designed
by our very own Chef Jackie.
He's a rising star,
and whispers are
that Michelin agrees.
[chef Jackie] Hector!
[chef Jackie yells] Hector!
Look alive, people.
Why do you hate me?
Who butchered these onions?
Who?
Oh, I don't know. Francois?
- We should leave.
- [chef Jackie] You're killing my career!
He's a bit tricky,
but he's an artist.
And we're lucky to have him.
And some people
may see anger, but me?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I see passion.
Do you hear that?
- [Kayla] Hear what?
- [Terence] Your footsteps.
- [Kayla] Oh. [chuckles]
- [Terence] Carrara marble.
[Tom yelps]
This is Gavin, our doorman.
Master of small talk.
This is Kayla,
who recently worked
at the Dorsey Hotel in London.
Did she now?
[Terence] Yes. And she'll be
helping us out this week.
Mm. I'm sure you'll
knock 'em dead, Kayla.
- Morning!
- [gasps]
That's Joy, the bell girl.
I'm convinced
she was raised by wolves.
- [Kayla whispers] What?
- [Terence] She's not important.
[Kayla] Okay.
But this glass atrium.
Oh, wow. Now that is something.
It's one of a kind.
I call it the "crowning jewel
of the Royal Gate."
[cork pops open]
- This is Cameron, the barman.
- [Kayla chuckles]
[imitates popping]
Popping bottles. [chuckles]
Excuse me?
Don't spill any
on your Jordan 5s.
These are actually
retro reissues.
[chuckles]
Obviously, it's the lace tips.
- NikeLab?
- Flight Club.
On Broadway.
I'm sorry to interrupt
your riveting TED Talk,
but why are you
pouring champagne
at 11 o'clock in the morning?
I was told to pour two glasses
for the VIPs that just arrived.
They're here?
- Yes, sir.
- [whispers] Who's here?
The bride and groom.
Come with me.
- [paparazzi clamoring]
- [hip-hop music plays]
- [cameras clicking]
- [sirens whooping]
[Ben] Wow!
- Isn't it perfect?
- I love it.
Just as much as I did
last week when we visited.
All I care about
in the whole world
is that you're happy.
Think your dad's gonna like it?
You keep asking
what my dad thinks,
I'm gonna send him
on the honeymoon with you.
[Spike] Clear the way,
coming through. [laughs]
I sure hope room service
is open all night.
Right, Toots?
[meows]
Ben, Preeta, welcome back
to the Royal Gate.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you.
It's a toast
to your upcoming nuptials.
It's so great to be back here.
Thank you very much.
- Appreciate it.
- [Gavin] Absolutely.
[Ben] And thank you guys
for everything.
It's great to see you again,
Terence.
- [Terence] Thank you very much.
- [Spike] Mouse!
- [barking]
- [gasps]
Oh, my God!
Spike, get back here!
- [Ben] Hey! Hey!
- Oh, my gosh!
Simmer down, boy! Hey!
Get back here!
- [Preeta] I'm so sorry.
- It's no problem.
- [growls]
- [Preeta] Sorry.
- [Kayla] A little jumpy, huh?
- Ooh.
I'm sorry,
he's a little animated.
- Yeah, um...
- [Toots meows]
Oh, she's so sweet.
Wow, you're really good
with animals.
Toots is usually really shy.
And by "shy," I mean,
she... She scratches
people's faces off.
- Oh.
- Oh. Well... [clicks tongue]
she can smell
a bona fide animal lover.
[Kayla chuckles, snorts]
[Terence] You know,
Kayla's new here
and I was just about
to explain to her that, uh...
[panting]
we traditionally
have a no-pets policy...
- Oh, wow.
- ...but, uh, you know...
- [snarls]
- [Terence gasps]
[growls]
I would be delighted
to make an exception.
- Is your hand okay?
- [Terence] It's fine.
Looks like
your hand's bleeding.
It's fine, it's perfect.
We've prepared a list
of some of the most
prestigious dog parks
in the area, and I think
the one on 11th Street
is particularly luxurious.
But are the people uptight?
Because... I mean,
do they yell at the dogs
- for being off-leash?
- [Spike grunts]
- Spike, he's... he's... Yeah.
- You can just say it.
- He's disgusting.
- [Preeta] Yeah.
- [Terence] He's disgusting?
- Huh?
There is one that I know about
that's behind
this falafel place on 17th.
It's not technically
a dog park,
but they let
their dogs off-leash
and they kinda
look out for each other.
It's pretty low-key.
That is amazing.
Thank you, Kayla.
- Thanks, Kayla.
- Yes. Thank you, Kayla.
- [both chuckle]
- Of course. Any time.
I just have to say, I follow
you guys on Instagram,
and you are
the cutest couple ever.
And that rock, whoa!
- [Ben] Yes, well...
- [Preeta] Yeah.
Could see that thing
from outer space. Good job.
You know, you could see
our love from outer space.
Oh.
That was fantastic.
- [Ben] Great. Thank you.
- Shall we?
- [Ben] We shall.
- [Preeta] Come on, Tootsie.
- [grunting]
- [Ben] Come on, Spike.
[Ben] But in all seriousness,
is there a safe in the hotel?
It's a giant diamond.
[Terence] Of course, of course.
[sniffing]
How was the ride?
[Ben] Very good,
thank you very much.
- [muffled screaming]
- [gasps]
[people screaming]
[metal clattering]
Not... Not to worry.
That's probably
a scream of delight.
You know, someone seeing
their beautiful room
for the first time.
It happens all the time.
Lola? Can you see them
to their room?
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
[chef Jackie]
Leo is shaken to the core.
The mouse
ran right over his foot.
Look, Terence,
I've worked too frigging hard
to be saddled
with a bunch of inept...
Wonderful group of gifted
colleagues to have my career
tossed into a fish bucket
over some infestation.
[softly] Jackie,
Jackie, Jackie, Jackie.
I know the gravity
of this situation.
- And I will handle it.
- I'll catch it, sir.
Him. Or her.
It could be a female...
- I'm not gender biased
- No, no.
- and I don't want to go by...
- No, no, it's fine. It's gender-fluid now.
The point is, I will catch
that little mouse,
and I will be
discreet about it.
[imperceptible radio chatter]
Okay. I need you to understand
the sensitivity of this matter.
- Yes.
- If a picture of this mouse is tweeted up
to insta-book-face
or the ticky-tock,
we will be ruined.
No, sir. We're not ruined,
because it's not gonna happen.
Okay? So, you guys
clear your heads about it.
That Rodentia is toast.
["Queso" playing]
♪ I got that moolah, moolah
Queso, queso ♪
♪ Camouflage money
They can't see my bankroll ♪
♪ I been whippin', whippin'
Django, Django ♪
♪ Smooth
Blame it on the Jame-O ♪
♪ I really don't know ♪
- ♪ Why I call ♪
- ♪ Why you call her? ♪
♪ I said I really don't know ♪
- ♪ Why I call ♪
- ♪ Why you call her? ♪
♪ 'Cause I got everything
that I want ♪
♪ I said I really don't know ♪
- ♪ Why I call ♪
- ♪ Why you call her? ♪
♪ 'Cause I got everything
that I want ♪
♪ I got, I got... ♪
- What are you doing?
- [gasps]
Oh, my gosh, you scared me.
I scared you?
You know, you're the one
creeping around like a thief.
I am on a mouse hunt.
Thank you.
- [Cameron] Need any help?
- [Kayla scoffs]
What? Because I'm...
I'm... I'm the new girl?
[sniffing]
[Kayla] Well, obviously,
you haven't seen my resume.
It clearly states that
I am completely capable
of doing anything
that is required
to do that is needed
to be done here.
[Cameron] Oh, right.
And how hard can it be
to catch a little mouse?
[Cameron] Honestly, I wasn't
expecting you to say yes.
You know, you got that whole
independent vibe thing
going on,
and I don't
normally get involved
with how the new kids
do their jobs. So...
My name, um... My name is
Kayla. Yeah.
My mom calls me Kayla.
[chuckles] Oh, okay, Kayla.
Well, I doubt that mouse
catching is on your resume,
but if you do catch him,
you should come by
for a celebratory beverage.
Well, start popping another
bottle of champagne now,
because any minute now,
he's mine.
He's... One second.
What the...
[gasps]
Did someone leave their...
What is that?
[sighs] The sign
of a worthy competitor.
[thunder crashing]
[siren wailing in distance]
[somber piano music plays]
[thunder rumbling]
[sighs wearily]
[off-key tone beeps]
[muffled rap music playing
in distance]
Guess who's at the party?
[laughs evilly]
Come on, man.
Have some self-respect.
You are in a dumpster
and Jerry's inside,
safe and warm.
Look at him.
Just scouting the room and
seeing what he can steal next.
Now, who's the cat
and who's the mouse?
Hey, let's get back in there
and smash that mouse up good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Tom, my brother,
there's room for both cats
and mice to be happy.
Look, I'm sure if you asked
to share his food...
Share? You're lucky
the kids are watching, okay?
We're cats. Cats take!
Come on, he's just
an innocent little mouse.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
Why're we always arguing?
We shouldn't be fighting,
we look alike.
Why are we doing this?
Look, how about we do
something different this time?
Why don't we let Tom
make up his own mind, okay?
Now, see, that is a good idea.
Tom, I believe in you.
[laughs evilly] What a sucker.
Now go make me proud, Tom.
[dramatic music plays]
[muffled party music playing]
Whoa!
[stick clatters]
[music continues]
[gasps]
[Tom screaming]
[intense music playing]
[gasps]
Ahhh!
[intense music continues]
[heroic music playing]
[whimpers]
[music instensifies]
[screams]
[shrieks]
- Life, do you hear me?
- [electricity buzzing]
Give my creation life!
[thunder rumbling]
[glass squeaking]
["Don't Sweat the Technique"
playing]
♪ Don't sweat the technique ♪
- [spits]
- ♪ Don't sweat... ♪
[Frankenstein on TV]
Launch the third swing!
- [burps]
- ♪ Don't sweat the technique ♪
[squeaks]
♪ Technical styles
that'll be full of technology ♪
♪ Complete sights and
new heights after I get deep ♪
[Frankenstein on TV]
...my creation life!
♪ And peep the technique ♪
[blows raspberry]
♪ Don't sweat the technique ♪
- [groans]
- [elevator bell dings]
Go for Lone Wolf.
- [Terence on radio] Who?
- [sighs]
It's Kayla, sir.
Just trying on one of
those new code names.
[Terence] Well, don't.
Have you located the room yet?
I'm continuing
to get noise complaints.
Yes, sir...
Well, no, sir, I haven't yet,
but I'm... I'm on it. Over.
Well, hurry up so you can get
back to finding that mouse.
And please, do not say "over."
This isn't Star Trek.
[sighs]
Takes all the fun
out of walkie-talkies.
I mean, what's the point, then?
[sing-song]
I can still hear you.
[static crackles]
[muffled thudding
and screaming]
[exhales sharply]
I have eyes on the target,
sir, and I am moving north...
I'm moving toward the door.
[door lock beeps]
[yells]
[Kayla] Oh, no.
What did you do?
[door shuts]
Who...
Wait a second, I know you.
I know you! You're the cat
from the park with the bike
and you tackled me.
[sighs] Is this personal?
Is this some form
of revenge sabotage?
What are you... You're trying
to tell me something?
Okay. Two syllables.
One word. Is it a movie?
Is it a cartoon?
What's this? A pig?
[gasps]
A mouse?
[imitates nibbling]
A little mouse?
What? He was here, too?
[grunts] Gosh, I gotta catch
that little disaster.
If I don't,
I'm gonna lose this job.
Wait a second.
You're a cat.
Can't you catch a mouse?
Isn't that in your DNA?
[video game
sound effects playing]
Huh.
You got a name?
[blowing]
That is really well done, Mot.
Tom?
You could be
in a lot of trouble for this.
I mean, just look at this mess.
So, what should we do
about this?
You wanna catch
a mouse together?
There could be
a big reward in it for you.
[glass shatters]
[Kayla groans]
[Terence] Sir, I instructed her
to get rid of an animal,
not find another.
[Kayla]
Here's how I see it, sir.
We have a mouse problem
at this hotel,
so we could hire
an exterminator
to have him tramp up and down
this whole hotel,
just filling it with his poison
and alerting Ben and Preeta
to the possibility of vermin
at their wedding,
or we could leverage
millions of years
of predatory-prey evolution
and choose a more
subtle and eco-friendly
solution.
That's why I brought on Tom.
[Kayla] You brought on...
She's a temp. She doesn't
even have hiring power.
It's what we did
at the Dorsey, sir.
Really?
That is not what they did
at the Dorsey.
Why don't I ask
Mrs. Pennybaker?
[scoffs] Who...
wouldn't want you to ask
Mrs. Pennybaker
from the Dorsey?
Why don't I call her
right now, huh?
Absolutely not.
No one's calling anyone.
Word gets out that we're
thinking of hiring a cat,
well, the mouse problem
could leak.
And if word gets out that
we're refusing to hire a cat,
PETA will be here
before you can say
"discriminatory practices."
[Kayla] Mm-hmm.
You need to think
outside the box, Terence.
Could he wear a hat?
Excuse me, sir?
Could he wear a jaunty hat?
And, uh, perhaps a name tag?
I think that'd be adorable.
One second. [chuckles]
Sir, you, you can't be serious?
A hat?
As you can see,
he would love to wear a hat.
And a name tag.
Well, then I think this is a
creative and elegant solve, Kayla.
Thank you, sir. As do I.
[Mr. Dubros] That'll be all.
Thank you.
["Jungle" playing]
♪ I'm a wildcat ♪
♪ Tell all the creatures
Where I'm at ♪
♪ When I come back ♪
♪ Rewind that Tell all
the kids That I'm back ♪
♪ I'm unstoppable ♪
♪ Deep in the jungle ♪
♪ I am a wildfire ♪
♪ These primal screams
I have let ♪
You gotta fix your name tag.
There you go.
Yeah. [chuckles]
You look good.
[Terence]
I figured out who you are.
Who am I?
You're one of
those millennials.
that thinks they can get
whatever they want
whenever they want
without working for it,
preferably with free shipping.
[Kayla clears throat]
[chuckles] Who doesn't
like free shipping?
This is a cutthroat
$200 billion industry.
And I've clawed my way
all the way to the middle.
And I don't intend
on stopping there.
Okay?
You better hope
this little cat plan works.
Because if it doesn't,
I'll make sure you'll never
work in New York City again.
And that goes for you, too,
Tom. Yes, you.
Enjoy it
while it lasts because...
This is just a test, Tom.
- [object thuds]
- Uh-uh.
He doesn't think
that we can do it.
Just like most people I know.
But you and I,
we're different, Tom.
We don't go down easy.
All right,
I'm gonna start in the lobby.
Tom?
[Tom grunting]
Okay. All right. You done?
Ahhh! [gasping]
[growls]
[Spike] Mm?
[grunting]
Listen here, kitty-cat,
I don't like being pounded.
Capiche?
I see you again,
I bash your head in.
- [Ben] Spike, get back here.
- [Spike barks]
[barks]
Saw you again!
[muffled chatter]
[meows]
[growls]
[screams]
[snarling]
[Toots yowls, snarls]
[squeaks]
[Preeta] Toots.
[Toots hisses]
[Preeta] There you are, girl.
- [meows softly]
- What were you doing?
I was looking all over for you.
Whew!
[Kayla] Tom, what are you doing
in the lobby?
Oh! [chuckles]
- I see you becoming the hunter...
- [Tom sniffing]
feeling the hunted.
[continues sniffing]
Yeah, there we go.
Tracking the trail.
Yeah, you smell
those little paws. Yep.
My gosh, Tom. [chuckles]
I mean, be the predator. Yeah.
Oh. [chuckles]
Okay, why are you...
You're drawing a...
Look, I...
Oh. Tom, that is
a "wanted dead or alive..."
That is a stick figure
of a mouse
and your Es are backwards.
That's never gonna work.
- You're looking for a mouse?
- [gasps] Gosh! Hi.
Yes, Joy. Yeah.
Well, have you checked the tiny
little door on the 10th floor?
[chuckles lightly]
[blows]
At first, I thought, "Whoa, Joy, you
became really big. When did that happen?"
But then I saw another door
that was normal sized
and thought, "Okay, so one of
your eyeballs got small."
- But then I blinked a ton
- Yeah.
and realized, "No, Joy,
just this door was really small."
So, I cut up a towel to make tiny
little towels and left them here.
But now they're gone.
[muffled R&B music playing]
Thank you, Joy. You are
a fascinating creature.
- [Joy] Hmm. [chuckles]
- [chuckles]
Me, fascinating? I like that.
[knocks]
[Kayla inhales deeply]
Listen here, punk.
You and I gotta chat...
[scoffs]
[doorknob clicks]
What?
You want me to grab it?
Thank you.
Oh, wow. This is so detailed.
What kind of
tiny printer or... [sniffs]
And it's scented?
What the...
Listen here, Mr. Mouse.
Oh. Jerry.
I need this job.
So, simply put, this is a hotel
and you're a mouse. So,
you gotta go.
Well, if that's how
you feel about it,
I'll have to introduce you
to my enforcer.
[dramatic music plays]
[laughs]
[train horn toots]
- [Jerry squeaking]
- [Kayla] Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
- Oh.
- [Tom yowls]
No! [gasps]
Oh.
- [gasps, sighs]
- [Tom meows]
You do not get to beat up
my enforcer!
Open up the door!
Open up!
Let me in!
- [Terence on radio] Kayla!
- Argh!
[panting] What do you need,
sir?
Meet me in the bridal suite
immediately.
Right away, sir.
You figure out a solution
to get that mouse out of here.
[upbeat hip-hop music plays]
♪ Here we go! ♪
- [knock on door]
- Uh, come on in.
Hey, guys.
[growls, groans]
Sorry, it's sort of
the wedding situation room
up here.
Wow.
Ah!
Terence, you were right.
This simulator's amazing.
- Ah!
- It really replicates how bad I am at golf.
Oh, I see that.
I haven't seen this many
shanks since I was in prison.
White-collar crime, but, uh...
[chuckles]
Baby, do you wanna
maybe take a little break?
Or if you wanna
do something together,
we can go
scuba diving in Tahiti.
We, uh, could go
hang gliding in the Alps.
Or, uh, we could go
to this alien planet
and just sort of,
uh, shoot some aliens.
Kayla, you could
just put those down. Sorry.
- [Kayla] Where? Here?
- Just right behind you.
- Oh, okay.
- [Preeta] Yeah.
Terence, actually, could I
grab that one from you?
Ah, good. It's heavy.
- [Ben] Think this might be it.
- [meows]
Just a little bit of a
surprise for me and the Mrs.
[chuckles] Let's see.
By the way, while I have you,
Terence, um,
- could I ask you a question?
- Absolutely.
What do you think
about elephants?
Um... Elephants.
I think they are majestic
and noble creatures.
No, I mean for the wedding.
Oh, at the wedding?
Real elephants?
Yeah, I sort of thought
it might be fun.
Babe, I never said
that they wouldn't be fun.
- [Ben] Oh...
- [scratching]
So, uh, maybe, you know...
Maybe we'll do elephants.
Maybe we do elephants.
[Terence] Have you, um,
considered maybe
a smaller animal like a...
- like a hamster?
- Hamster?
- [chuckles] Oh. That's cute.
- Yeah.
We were gonna
ride in on it, though.
Can, can you ride a hamster?
Oh, yes. I mean, as long
as you have enough of them,
- you can ride them silly.
- Yes.
- [chuckles wryly]
- [Ben] Great. Yeah.
Well, that's something
to consider, too.
Babe, if getting elephants
at the wedding
would make you happy...
You being happy
would make me happy.
[both] Aw!
Okay, get the elephants.
All right!
We're gonna get the elephants.
Great! We'll do the elephants!
- [Kayla snorts]
- [Chuckles wryly]
[grunts] Boom.
Oh! It's a motorized
skateboard. I love those.
It's got, uh, you know, Wi-Fi.
Why does a skateboard
need Wi-Fi?
Why the fi not?
[chuckles wryly]
"Why the fi not?"
See what I'm dealing with?
[chuckles]
- [cell phone rings]
- Oh.
- Hello? Hey.
- [Ben speaks indistinctly]
- Yeah, uh, he's right here.
- [Ben whispers] Who is it?
[Preeta] My dad.
What? Do I look okay?
For a phone call? Yes.
Right.
One second. Phew.
Hello, Mr. Mehta.
You sound like
you look amazing.
Uh-huh?
- If you need anything at all, please don't hesitate to call.
- Yeah.
We'll help you accordingly.
You know what, Terence,
Spike got into some burritos
- earlier and, well...
- Huh?
I was, you know. Do you mind?
[Terence] Um... Of course.
[Spike] I'm ready! I'm ready!
[barks excitedly]
Thank you.
[chuckles] Kayla, can you...
Uh, actually,
I would love to keep Kayla
and maybe run through
some bridesmaids-related stuff
with her.
- You know, coordinating colors.
- Sure.
I have a very good eye.
No, that's fine. I'll just
run through it all with Kayla.
Here we go. I got the lead.
I got the lead. Come on.
Very well.
[panting excitedly, barks]
- Of course.
- Thank you, Terence.
[Terence yelps, grunts]
[growls excitedly, panting]
- [Spike growls]
- [yelps]
- [Preeta] Kayla.
- [Kayla] Yes.
- Wow, what a view!
- [pigeons cooing]
So, what are
your bridesmaids colors?
I lost my ring.
The big one?
Yeah, my big one.
My... My only one.
How?
Well, I was,
I was on my way to the spa,
and Ben had told me
to put it in the safe
because he's always convinced
that I'm gonna lose it.
But you did lose it.
Yeah, I mean, I misplaced it.
I thought first someone
must've taken it, but...
And would you say
that it is still in the spa?
Or the pool.
Or the lounge. I was
all over the place today,
but I don't want Ben to know
that it was ever missing.
Really? I mean,
won't he just be all adorable
and understanding about it?
[whispers] Babe,
that was a really big ring.
- Ah. Understood.
- [Preeta] Hey.
Hi.
- Hi.
- What did my dad want?
Nothing. He was just, uh,
we were just kinda bonding.
Great.
Uh, where is your ring?
Which ring?
Your engagement ring?
The giant one
that I gave you for love.
Oh, um... I...
Uh, the thing is...
It's a funny story
actually, sir.
I actually took it.
Yes, I did.
- To go get cleaned.
- Oh.
I took it to go get
a scrub-a-dub
and be all shiny
for the wedding.
Bright as bright as a diamond.
Great. That's actually
very thoughtful.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Kayla.
By the way, we really wanna put
some kind of gratuity
for you on the bill.
Whatever you see fit, sir.
- Thanks.
- Love you, guys.
- [Preeta] Love you.
- In different ways.
[inhales sharply] Thank you.
Anytime.
[Terence grunting]
[Spike] Whoop. Excuse me.
[Terence panting and grunting]
Come on, come on, come on.
[chuckles]
Stop, stop! Stop!
- Ow!
- [Spike grunting]
- No, no, no, wait, wait!
- Uh-oh.
- What?
- [Spike] Here it comes.
- [stomach grumbling]
- [Terence] Are you okay?
- [Spike] Oh, yes.
- No, no, no!
- [car horns beeping]
- Oh, come on!
Stop the beeping! You're
making him self-conscious!
- [defecating]
- How many burritos
- did you eat?
- [Spike sighs]
Oh!
I see what you did.
- [drivers yelling indistinctly]
- Okay.
[groans]
- [yells]
- [car horn beeps]
I'm scooping the poop, huh?
You saw he did it on purpose...
- [Spike] Let's go!
- [grunts]
[soul instrumental
music playing]
[Kayla] Joy?
[Joy] Hey, Kayla,
oh, how's the mouse hunt going?
[Kayla] Oh, it's going.
By the way,
quick question for you.
Say a VIP person lost a ring
and someone wanted
to look for said ring
without raising any eyebrows,
where would you say
that person should look?
Oh, my God, I, I,
I love riddles. Um...
Well, if I were that someone,
ah, but I'm not.
But I could be. Who knows?
One day. One can only dream.
[chuckles]
VIP. [chuckles]
Sorry, back to the question.
Um...
It would depend
on the size of the object.
Is it a car? Is it alive?
Could it be a dog?
I lose things all the time.
I lost my baby brother
last week.
Don't tell anyone, please,
because I was like,
"Joey, where are you? Please?"
And then, thank the Lord, he...
[imperceptible chatter]
[softly] Yeah.
[angelic music plays]
[wind whooshing softly]
[sniffing]
[continues sniffing]
[grunts]
[dramatic music playing]
[electrical whirring]
[whooshing]
[steam hissing]
[thud]
[gulps]
Tom! What?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, chill out!
Besides, that is never gonna
keep out
that minuscule sociopath.
What do you mean, he's gone?
[chuckles softly]
Like, like gone-gone?
Are you sure?
Yes! Booyah, Tom! Oh!
[singing] ♪ More hot milk
for you tonight ♪
Boom!
[mic feedback whines]
- [imperceptible conversation]
- Mr. Dubros,
I am delighted to inform you
that the job
that we hired Tom for,
- it is completed.
- Oh, wonderful.
Now we just have to figure out
how to let him go
without triggering
an equal employment issue.
Oh.
I should probably look into
severance packages.
- Right.
- Maybe a month of tuna?
- [snorts] 'Cause he's a cat.
- Mm-hmm.
[Preeta] I think
it's one per family.
And if there's any way to make
sure the guests get these
as soon as they check in...
The bride's taken
quite a shine to you.
[chuckles softly]
I don't know, I mean,
whatever I can do to help
with the wedding craziness.
They seem really stressed out
with it all.
If anything, the ceremony
is the perfect test
for a relationship.
'Cause you can promise
all you want in the vows.
When it comes down to it,
it's how you handle
the pressure of the planning.
Some couples rise to
the challenge and others fall.
Hmm. I should write that down.
[soft piano music playing]
So, did Tom tell you
the good news?
The mouse problem
has officially been handled.
Hey! She came, she saw,
she exterminated.
- [Kayla] Yeah.
- [chuckles]
So, how about we celebrate?
Flat club soda coming right up.
Yeah, there we go. [chuckles]
The real wild stuff. [chuckles]
- [soft piano music playing]
- [sighs]
Wow, those little paws
move quick, huh?
You should be his manager.
[chuckles]
I mean, sure, why not?
Maybe they'll see
how much I'm killing it
and bring me on permanently
to run everything?
Okay, so somebody thinks
they can skip a few steps.
Mm-mm.
No, it's just...
[sighs] I mean,
where I came from,
there were
no real opportunities.
Where's that?
A small town in Penn State.
Picture seeing
your whole future
in front of you
and you can't stand it.
That was me, there.
I just wanted to find that
thing that made me feel...
Important?
Yeah.
And New York seemed like the
right place to look for it.
Well, I mean,
I've heard about your resume.
[sighs] About that...
Hey, come on, don't be shy.
Whatever shot you're
looking for, you deserve.
You know, you're proof
that it takes more than
a fancy resume
to make it big in New York.
Right?
Guilty as charged. [chuckles]
[soft piano music continues]
[Preeta] Toots needs
a little pawpicure.
Kayla mentioned
you might have a spot.
- [loud heart beats]
- We could actually see her right now.
- That would be so great.
- [fancy tune plays]
[singing] ♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Well ♪
♪ Don't you know, baby ♪
[imperceptible]
♪ Child, don't you know, baby ♪
- [meows]
- ♪ Oh, don't you know, baby ♪
♪ Little girl, little girl,
Don't you know, oh ♪
♪ Please listen to me, baby ♪
[playing hip-hop music]
- ♪ Girl, I'm in love With you so ♪
- Yeah [laughs]
- [retches]
- ♪ Turn your lamp down low ♪
♪ I said turn
Your lamp down low ♪
♪ Whoo ♪
♪ Turn it down ♪
♪ Please turn your lamp down ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
- [piano keys plinking]
- [Preeta] Okay, come on, baby.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
[purrs]
Oh, my gosh.
[sighs]
No, no, no. Stop it.
Both of you. [huffs]
Why is he alive?
Why is he here?
[sighs]
It's over, Jerry.
I'm calling in the poison guys.
[Kayla sighs]
Why do you have Preeta's ring?
Have you had it
this entire time?
Give it to me.
Now. Drop the ring.
[Kayla sighing]
What do you want for it, Jerry?
You wanna stay here?
You little con artist.
Fine. We can discuss this
- on my terms.
- [Spike growling]
[Terence] Okay, no problem!
I got it!
- [muffled grunting]
- Tom...
- [Terence] Excuse me!
- Where did he go?
- [Kayla] Tom, where did he go?
- Find him. Now.
- [Terence] Stop. I said, stop!
- [barking]
- Stop! Stop!
Calmate!
I'm the boss.
[barks]
[Spike growls]
[sighs]
Why do I see temporary
employees socializing
on hotel property
in the middle of their shift?
We were just...
Terence, we're celebrating,
you know?
The, uh, hotel's mouse problem
is taken care of.
Oh, yeah, congratulations.
Teamwork is dream work, right?
Yeah, it's taken care of,
right, Tom?
[nervously] It is
so taken care of, right, Tom?
What... What is he doing?
He's not doing nothing.
- Why are you acting nervous?
- Huh?
[Terence]
You're acting nervous.
[Kayla] I'm not acting nervous.
No? What's in your pocket?
Ah. [grunts]
- Oh.
- Terence.
- Wait! No, he's in the pocket.
- Terence, what are you doing?
[Terence] The mouse
is in the pocket.
- [Kayla gasps]
- [Spike growls]
[Spike] Come back here!
Come back here!
[grunting]
- Oh!
- [Terence straining]
[groaning]
- Oh, I'm so sorry!
- [woman yelps]
- [Terence yelling]
- Whoa!
[all exclaiming]
- [grunting]
- [gasps]
[Spike] Come here, pussycat.
[whimpering]
[Terence] Everyone, keep calm!
- [Terence yelping]
- [all gasp]
Oh, no!
[all screaming]
Ooh.
[screaming]
[Spike growling]
[gasps] The mouse!
[clangs]
- [grunts]
- [elevator bell dings]
Huh? Whoa!
[Tom yowls]
[muffled rumbling]
[ceiling cracking]
[muffled rumbling continues]
[shrieks]
[people whimpering]
[Kayla gasps] Oh...
[Spike] What the...
- [Thuds]
- [laughing] Oh.
[Joy gasping]
[gasps]
[grunts]
This is definitely your bad.
[imperceptible chatter]
[slow dramatic music playing]
[Terence faintly] Kayla,
and what would you call this, huh?
[Kayla] This was a mistake.
It was
a total misunderstanding.
[Terence]
This is a dereliction of duty!
And it's a reflection
of the absence of character!
[clatters]
It's an embarrassment
to the hotel.
And it's an insult to you.
That's how serious
this matter is, sir.
I agree.
Terence,
I'm placing you on leave.
What?
It's clear that the magnitude
of this wedding
has overwhelmed you and you're
in something of a state.
- I think a break would...
- Hold on a sec. Let me make sure
that we're
on the same page here
regarding
the basic facts of this.
The cat
that she forced us to hire
failed to catch the mouse.
Kayla said
she got rid of the mouse.
Isn't that right?
- That is what I said.
- Ah!
That is what you said.
But that is not what you did.
The mouse that caused all that
destruction to our lobby
is still in the hotel.
I saw him
in the animal tornado.
Terence, listen to yourself.
No one saw a mouse.
I saw the mouse.
But they did see you
acting erratically
towards Miss Forester
after bringing the groom's
bulldog into a bar.
She brought the kitty-cat
to the bar, too.
Tom is an employee.
He has a name tag.
This is insane.
I'm going insane right now.
Well, you're certainly
acting insane.
You caused tens of
thousands of dollars of damage
to the hotel,
you've terrified our guests,
and now you're attempting
to frame it as Kayla's fault?
[laughs hysterically]
You know what?
You can't do this.
You can't fire
the event manager
in the middle of an event.
Please leave
on your own merits, Terence.
I don't want
to have to call security.
Please don't do this.
- [grunts]
- Oh.
Okay. [exhales heavily]
Okay.
Argh!
[objects clatter]
Oh, my days.
And I'm not picking it up.
[door opens]
- [door slams]
- [Terence] Get your tail out of your ears.
- [Tom whistling]
- It's disgusting.
Well, this is a disaster.
[sighs] Yeah.
Firing our events manager
before the biggest
and most important event
this hotel has thrown in years.
The only reason
I felt comfortable
asking Terence to take leave
is because we have someone
with your wealth
of experience here.
With the what now?
I got a call from Miss Preeta.
She told me
that you quietly found
a very important missing item
she was looking for.
- [chuckles uneasily]
- You're multitalented, Kayla.
Do you think you can handle
the role
of interim event manager?
Are you kidding?
Yes, yes, of course.
It's a massive endeavor.
Sir, "massive endeavor"
is my middle name.
It's Judith,
but you get the point.
I know you're new,
but your employment history
convinces me
you're qualified
to take this on.
And who knows, [exhales]
if this weekend goes well,
we may be discussing a more
permanent position on Monday.
I can't imagine... anything
that could
possibly mess this up.
- [Kayla] Stop it.
- [whirring]
You guys gotta stop fighting.
It's like you've been
doing this for years.
Listen, first of all,
thank you for the ring.
Helpful to have it back
after you stole it.
Never mind.
Remember when I said
to the both of you
that letting you stay here
wasn't up to me?
Well,
if you look right there,
I'm in charge now, all right?
And this wedding
- it's a huge responsibility.
- [sniffing]
It's the shot
that I've been waiting for
and I can't screw it up.
So, you two, you gotta go.
[clears throat]
Stop looking at me like that.
[sniffles]
Ugh! Okay.
Maybe you can stay here.
But not like this.
Uh-uh. That little mess
you caused downstairs,
it's a disaster.
You know what,
you wanna stay, right?
Fine. One condition.
You two have to prove to me
that you can coexist together.
And stay as far away
from here as possible.
Got it?
So, tomorrow,
I'm gonna plan an entire day
for you two to spend together
out there, in the Big Apple.
And if you do this,
you guys can stay.
Do we have a deal?
Your car will be here
at 9:00 a.m.
Don't be late.
["Bouncy House" playing]
♪ Everybody in the
bouncing house ♪
♪ Jumping up and down
Going bouncy bouncy ♪
♪ Bouncy, bouncy
bouncy, bouncy ♪
bouncy, bouncy... ♪
♪ Off the walls,
Off the floor ♪
- [sighs sharply]
- ♪ 220 degrees ♪
♪ Take off the door ♪
♪ ... if you stand
From the back ♪
♪ Hanging in the backyard
tell me where you at ♪
♪ Slip and slide everybody
get aside 'cause you have to ♪
♪ You don't wanna
be the last to ♪
♪ That's true, thats true ♪
♪ Welcome to my bouncy house ♪
♪ You don't want to be
the last one out ♪
♪ Hurry up! ♪
♪ Bouncy, bouncy
bouncy, bouncy ♪
♪ Everybody
in the bouncy house ♪
♪ Put your hands up ♪
♪ Go bouncy, bouncy, bouncy ♪
♪ Everybody with
A larger mouth ♪
- [pained scream]
- ♪ Go bouncy, bouncy... ♪
[gasps]
[Kayla] Okay, guys,
please, everyone...
- [all clamoring]
- [Kayla] Uh...
Please...
Any, any true emergencies?
- [clamoring continues]
- True emergencies?
Let's just go around the room
one at a time.
[Leo] I just caught
my finger in the door and...
[chef Jackie] Okay, please,
seriously, just shut up, please. Uh...
Madam Kaydra,
are we sure the mouse is gone?
Rumors are
the guest list includes
a Michelin
restaurant inspector,
so one slip-up
and me and my son
are out on the streets.
Jackie, rest assured,
the mouse is currently
being taken care of.
Anyone else have
any other problems?
Uh, did you address
the, um, elephant that's here?
[scoffs] Cameron,
yes, I addressed
the elephant in the room.
You weren't here for it.
Yeah, no, I mean literally.
[elephants trumpeting]
Where do you want 'em?
Um...
Pardon. The elephants?
Can't leave 'em in the truck.
No. That would be inhumane.
[trumpeting]
- They can be parked at valet.
- Okay.
- [loud thud]
- [elephant rumbles]
Relax, Cecil.
♪ We take you upside down,
We take you upside down ♪
♪ Always start
Once a visionary ♪
♪ Why she never wanna
Listen to me? ♪
♪ Why I know if we don't
Give them for free ♪
♪ Coz' this place still feels
Like prison to me ♪
- [gasps]
- [brakes squeal]
♪ Just the pride
And I call my generation ♪
♪ Refugee will all
I get my vision ♪
♪ I just wish
How to change my situation... ♪
Okay. How about we go ahead and put
all the birds in the staff room?
Um, the animal wrangler
said this time of year
they need room
to socialize and mate.
[both gasp]
I think they've
socialized enough, Joy.
This is a wedding after all,
not spring break.
- Ca-caw!
- So let's just go ahead
and put 'em in the staff room.
[coos] What...
What sound do peacocks make?
- I mean...
- [Joy] Ca-caw!
I think that sounds right.
[song continues]
♪ Free ♪
♪ Two times ♪
♪ No more talking coz'
You're saying too much ♪
- ♪ Too much! ♪
- [giggles]
- ♪ The people leavin' As away at a Dutch ♪
- [roars]
♪ We gave them taxes
They don't pay us enough ♪
♪ I live a one to two
To be walking alone ♪
♪ By now you see my patience
Is very low ♪
- ♪ And try to save my heart Which stopping wanting to go ♪
- [rattling]
- ♪ I made mistakes I never say that I don't ♪
- [laughs maniacally]
♪ one, two, three, go ♪
♪ Let me go,
Come on apologies ♪
♪ I just wanna be ♪
♪ I just wanna be free! ♪
♪ Free! ♪
♪ We running
Coz' we feel good ♪
♪ Oh-wah-oh, we oh ♪
- ♪ We runnin' Coz' we feel good ♪
- [slurps]
♪ Oh-wah-oh, we oh ♪
♪ We runnin'
Coz' we feel good ♪
[gulps]
♪ I just wanna be free ♪
Kayla, come on already.
[Kayla] Oh, gosh, I so regret
saying yes to this.
[sing-song] Pa-pa-pam-pam!
Oh, my God.
You look incredible.
Thank you. [chuckles]
Well, we are
a full-service hotel here.
Be it dog walking,
or quite even possibly,
saving someone's lost ring.
Hmm.
Is there anything else
I can help you with, milady?
Oh, no, thank you.
This wedding
is bonkers enough already.
- Why don't you just say no?
- [sighs]
Oh, no, we've...
We've just decided
to, um, avoid behaviors
that might give the impression
that we're fighting.
But what about
when it's just you two?
I mean, we disagree, of course,
about how big
- the wedding should be.
- Wow.
But I guess there was so much
pressure to maintain an image
that somewhere
we forgot how to fight.
Ben really loves you, Preeta.
Yeah. He's a really good guy.
It's just that when he goes,
he goes big.
And I love that about him.
Yeah.
But I have
this feeling that this
small Indian wedding is gonna
be a great big disaster.
[male announcer] Beautiful day
at Yankee Stadium.
Top of the 9th inning, two out,
and the Yankees up by one.
Big Alex Gordon at the plate.
That ball is crushed.
This might be it.
The ball game may be over.
The Yankees
could move on and...
Oh! What's this?
- A hairy fan has reached over and caught the ball.
- [crowd booing]
[female reporter] Mayhem
unfolds at Yankee Stadium.
Two baseball fans
seated in right field
interrupted
what could have been
the final out for the Yankees.
The culprits were later
taken away by animal control.
In other news...
[buzzing]
- [both gasp]
- Oh, my gosh!
- [Kayla] What was...
- [thuds]
Ben, was that a drone?
Not just any drone.
That was a CH-4000,
military-grade.
- Yeah.
- But I'm sure it's harmless.
[woman screams in distance]
Joy?
- Should I go see what that...
- Yes. Yes, Joy.
- Oh, okay. Going.
- Yes, Joy, go. Yep.
That was a scream.
It's harmless.
Yeah.
Military things usually are.
[both chuckle]
I got this drone
because I thought,
uh, when Preeta and I come into
the wedding on the elephants,
that the drone
could be kind of, uh...
As I'm saying the words
"drone" and "elephant,"
out loud
to another human being,
I'm wondering, is this, um...
is this a lot?
Weddings, Ben, [sighs]
they're already
stressful enough,
- you know?
- Yeah.
The important part
is that Preeta,
she can't wait to marry you.
So, just take it easy,
you know?
Enjoy the ride.
- Yeah.
- You only got one shot at it.
Like, one chance to,
like, get it right.
Uh-huh. So just go ahead
and pull it back.
Yeah. Pull it back
and just sorta let it rip.
Like, really,
just pull it way back
and just explode out of it.
That is not what I was
- trying to say to you.
- Yeah.
- [woman screaming]
- [crashes]
They said they'd
disabled the weapons.
- There's weapons?
- Uh, I'll make sure.
[Joy panting] I found it.
I found the...
Oh, my God!
Help me, help me, help me!
She found it.
Don't look it in the eyes, Joy.
[gate creaks]
Welcome to your new home,
gentlemen.
[barking aggressively]
[dog whimpers]
[barking]
[snarling]
Hey, hey, hey, pipe down!
You already been fed.
Hello.
- [cage rattling]
- Quiet.
[yelps]
Get comfortable.
You're gonna be here a while.
[laughs]
Have a nice stay!
[Butch sings eerily]
♪ Alley cats ♪
♪ Come out and play ♪
[Topsy] That's that cat
from the alley!
[Butch] Well, well, well.
So, we meet again.
You know, you and me?
We got some
unfinished business to settle.
[Meathead] Dinner time.
Snack is what
I like to call it.
[Butch] Relax, you two.
This won't take long,
as long as you don't fight it.
- [gasps]
- [Lightning] Gotcha.
[cat 1] Oh, don't be scared,
come here!
Are you gonna eat him?
Why don't you be a good
little kitty and hand him over
before I stop being nice?
Yeah, what are you, like,
friends or something?
Go ahead. Eat him now.
If we can't eat him,
you gotta eat him.
[cat 2] Looks like
a nice snack.
[Ash] Chew. Chew.
- [Lightning] Eat him. Eat. Eat.
- [Ash] Chew. Chew. Chew.
- Eat it.
- Chew. Chew.
[Meathead] Ah, ah,
there you go. Bottoms up!
- [Topsy] Eat him!
- [Meathead] There you go!
[cat 3] Is it as good
as it looks?
What are you waiting for? Chew.
[cats chanting] Chew. Chew.
- Chew. Chew. Chew. Chew.
- [sniffing]
If you don't start chewing,
we will.
[Topsy] Oh, that's spicy.
Cajun.
[Ash] Chew. Chew. Chew.
Wait a minute. Something
ain't right. Open your mouth.
[Topsy] You heard him,
open your trap!
[officer] Hey, cat.
You got a visitor.
- [Topsy] What?
- [Meathead] Visitors?
[Topsy] He didn't even eat him!
Mouse, you got one, too.
[Terence] Hola, Tom.
How are they treating you?
This place is, uh, horrible.
Cheese stick?
[sniffing]
Oh, you don't want it?
Here's the deal.
I know you wanna
come back to the hotel,
and I can help you do it.
As you may already know,
Kayla's been put
in charge of the wedding.
And, yeah, it's a tough job.
That's why she sent me here
to bring you back.
So you can help.
But there's a catch.
I can only take one of you.
You know what your friend said?
That it's your fault.
Maybe I shouldn't say this,
you know?
He says you smell like...
Like tuna.
- And a cheesy foot.
- [sniffing]
He also said that you're, uh...
You're emotionally unavailable.
He also wants
you to stay here and rot.
Now, you put me
in such a tough position.
As you already know,
I can only take one of you
back to the hotel.
Will it be the cat?
Or the mouse?
Okay.
I've made my decision.
[tense music plays]
[upbeat hip-hop music playing]
Check this out.
In celebrity news,
major commotion at the Royal Gate Hotel
as New York's elite couple,
Preeta and Ben,
are tying the knot in
a private, intimate wedding.
[upbeat hip-hop
music continues]
[imperceptible chatter]
[chef Jackie] Ah... Ah...
Ta-da!
- [chef Jackie chuckles]
- [applause]
Ta-da!
Okay.
- [applause]
- No, no. No, no, no.
[exhales deeply]
Move.
[grunts meaningfully]
Mr. Mehta, what do you think?
You're not wearing a turban.
Is that, Is that a question
or a statement?
I didn't know
if you wanted an answer.
I've been getting
really into cricket!
You're doing great.
How are we doing
on the champagne?
[Cameron] We good, we good.
There's just a lot of it,
and not enough hands.
Okay.
All right, bro.
Take these upstairs.
I'll be up in a minute.
You good?
Yeah, yeah. I think so.
[man on radio] Momma bird,
we got a problem here. We need you.
Okay, on my way.
[suspenseful music playing]
- Hmm.
- What?
I think I might have
just pulled this off.
[Indian music playing]
[emcee] Ladies and gentlemen,
the ceremony is about to begin.
All right, Malcolm,
game face, look impressive.
FYI, I'm always ready.
LOL. [chuckles]
Ben, this feels
so embarrassing.
Well, if it's any consolation,
you look very beautiful.
And in a way,
you know, we're the elephants.
Because we're never
gonna forget this wedding.
- [upbeat Indian music playing]
- Here we go.
[elephant trumpets]
[guests exclaiming]
[guests] Wow!
[woman] Preeta!
Wow.
The, the elephant are normal
in these kind of events?
We are an elephant-friendly
establishment.
Friendly establishment.
[guests exclaiming in awe]
Wow. [chuckles]
That's really beautiful.
The elephants
were a great choice.
Welcome back.
- [elephant trumpets]
- [imperceptible chatter]
Consider this wedding
a welcome party.
Just for you.
[gasps]
Oh, no.
No.
What is Jerry doing here?
Well, that must be awkward.
With all the horrible things
he said about you.
That you're not fit
to work at the Royal Gate.
Tom, come on, now.
Let's not be insensitive.
Oh, would you just
leave him alone already?
Well, I got something to say.
Okay, go ahead and speak, then!
As I was saying...
- [angel yelps]
- [laughs]
Gotcha! [laughs]
Now let's go finish
what we started.
- [cracks knuckles]
- Have fun.
[up-tempo Indian music plays]
Why is Tom here?
What the...
I don't see Jerry.
Do you see Jerry?
Uh, no. I don't.
- [Preeta] Hi. Hey.
- [Ben] Hi.
Isn't this great?
And look, your dad loves it.
At least,
I think he's loving it.
It's kinda hard to tell.
- [Mrs. Jacobson exclaims]
- Not bad.
Ah. Smile for the drone-cam.
[Ben] Drone-cam?
Yeah. They can put
a cam on a drone.
Wait. Are those peacocks?
Yeah, I think they might
have just been
part of the, uh,
exotic bird package.
- [tiger roaring]
- [guests exclaiming]
- [peacock screams]
- [people gasp]
And, and even the tiger?
Well, the tiger is our first.
[imitates roaring]
I begged you
to stop doing this stuff.
I'm sorry.
That is the last surprise.
You just don't listen.
Listen to what?
- [both snarling]
- [dramatic music playing]
Hmm?
[screams]
[gasps]
No, Tom. Don't do it.
Do it, Tom. Do it.
[inhales sharply, growls]
You're dead, mouse.
[grunts]
[people gasp]
[continues grunting]
[yells]
[slurps]
[whimpering]
[screams]
- [grunting]
- Yes!
[yells]
[grunts]
[Malcolm gasping]
OMG. Is that a mouse?
- WT... [trumpets]
- [all gasp]
Preeta!
[Malcolm trumpeting]
[Malcolm] Mouse! Mouse!
Mouse, mouse, mouse,
mouse, mouse!
- [man] We got him.
- Oh, my baby!
No, no. Stay calm, everyone!
[Cecil] Mouse! Ahh!
Mouse! Mouse!
[guests clamoring]
Mouse! Ah, mouse!
[trumpets] Ugh. Get off.
[Spike growls]
You?
[growls] No. Me.
- [roars]
- [both yelp]
[barks frantically]
- [roars]
- [grunts]
[Malcolm] Mouse, mouse,
mouse, mouse, mouse!
[trumpets] Mouse!
- [roars]
- [Toots yowls]
- [peacock screams]
[guests exclaim]
[groans]
[trumpets]
Please remain calm.
[Spike barking]
[Spike] Out of my way!
Out of my way!
[Malcolm trumpeting]
[roaring]
[Cecil] Malcolm!
I'm coming to save you!
Oh, no!
Huh? Oh.
[sighs]
[yowling]
[Ben] Preeta!
[Toots yowls]
Out the back door.
[man] Let's get out of here!
- [trumpets]
- [man] Oh, no!
- [guests screaming]
- [gasps]
[trumpets]
Cecil! Malcolm!
Stop! Stop!
[electricity crackling]
[imperceptible murmuring]
What is he doing here?
Terence is here
because he tried to warn me
about Kayla, who clearly lied
about who she is.
No, sir. Uh, this was a misunderstanding.
It was, um...
No.
Actually, it wasn't
a misunderstanding.
Sir, when I came
into your office that day,
I had stolen
someone else's resume...
[Tom gasps softly]
and pretended that it was mine.
I don't have
any qualifications for this.
Or for anything, really.
[Terence] You not only
destroyed this wedding,
but may have destroyed
the future of this hotel.
I'm sorry.
Perhaps I could salvage this.
Don't bother.
I just came here
to inform Mr. Dubros
that the wedding's off.
[sighs softly]
[Ben] Preeta.
Oh...
I guess we were both
in over our heads.
[hesitates] I...
Kayla, I don't get
why you just...
I was gonna tell you, Cameron.
I was gonna tell
all of you the truth.
I just wanted to prove to
you all that I deserved this.
That I could do this.
I'm sorry.
["Something Beautiful" plays]
♪ Here I stand ♪
♪ Taking off my pride ♪
♪ And I run
With nowhere to hide ♪
[grunts]
And don't even
think about coming back.
You think I was gonna
let some street animals
live at the Royal Gate Hotel?
[scoffs] Oh, no.
[song continues]
♪ Like the sun ♪
♪ Shining through the rain ♪
♪ Here with you,
Sharing better days ♪
♪ I'd be lost
Lost without you ♪
♪ Thank God you're still here ♪
♪ And that's something
Beautiful ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ That's something beautiful ♪
♪ That you are here ♪
♪ Here with me ♪
♪ That's something beautiful ♪
[snaps fingers]
[Kayla] Hey.
Thanks for meeting me.
I know I wasn't
very convincing yesterday.
But what I was trying to say
was, I really am sorry.
I still can't believe
that I saw everything
that woman accomplished
on her resume,
and I thought that my pure
ambition was an even swap.
Come on, Kayla,
- everybody screws up.
- [sighs]
It's just hard.
I mean, every morning I wake up
and I look at my phone,
and my newsfeed
is filled with people
who are our age,
you know, they're succeeding
at what they're doing.
Well, maybe we just need
to stop comparing ourselves
to everybody
and just work for it.
Listen, Kayla,
you're gonna get the skills.
You already got the smarts,
you got the funny,
and you got the love
of helping people.
Even if I wanted to make
this right, I couldn't.
Well, maybe they
can help
convince you otherwise.
[Kayla] No.
You two are the last people
that I wanna see right now.
[Jerry squeaks]
What is all this?
I think that's Preeta and Ben.
All right, you know what? Just cut the
chalkboard act and tell me what's going on.
Okay, you and Jerry
have an idea for what?
How did you...
[mimics trumpeting]
Elephants?
[mimics squealing] Ca-caw!
And peacocks? A big cake?
Guys, are you
just making fun of me?
Oh, so, this is like charades?
[Kayla] No.
[Cameron]
'Cause he did like a...
No? All right, never mind.
I think what they're
trying to tell us
is that if we go back
to the hotel,
quickly salvage what we can,
and we find a last-minute venue
and some sort
of befitting celebrant,
we can fix this by putting on
a makeshift wedding.
And you got
all of that from that?
Yeah.
We kinda understand
each other now.
Let's do it.
What do we have to lose?
[soul instrumental
music playing]
Hey.
Where's Preeta going?
A doorman never tells.
JFK.
[sighs]
Okay, guys. I know that
you both don't get along,
but now it's time
to change that.
So, help me save this wedding
and go catch that bride, okay?
And bring her back here.
[imperceptible chatter]
What do you want?
I just need to talk to Ben
for a minute.
No, don't you think
you've done enough?
Ben. This wedding
can still happen, today.
How? I mean,
everything's destroyed.
[Kayla] It doesn't matter.
Preeta never actually
wanted any of this.
She just wanted
you to listen to her.
I, I don't think so.
Wait. Someone once told me
that a wedding
is a couple's very first test.
And some couples,
well, they rise to that.
[mockingly] Stupid.
What kind of idiot said that?
- I mean, seriously...
- Me.
Oh.
I apologize. I'm sorry.
I was being, uh, sarcastic.
You can rise, Ben.
We can still pull this off.
Needless to say,
everything at this hotel
will be at your disposal.
Except, of course, the hotel.
What about the garden
- across the street?
- [all gasp]
Uh, I'm sorry, garden?
Mm-hmm.
Wait, do you mean Central Park?
Sure. Whatever nickname
you have for it.
That's actually
an amazing idea.
Joy, thank you.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, how about, Terence,
you and Ben
get a guest list together,
and then let everyone know
where to meet us?
You expect me to assist you
after what you've done
to this hotel?
I think we both did some things
that we regret
to keep our jobs.
[softly] Tom and Jerry
told me what you did.
I'm not gonna tell anybody.
[whispers] Okay, thank you.
If Tom and Jerry can be
out there working together,
then so can we.
♪ Ladies and gentlemen ♪
[phone vibrating]
[Toots sighs]
♪ Ladies and gentlemen ♪
[Tom yelping]
[Kayla on radio]
Roger, roger, over.
Come in, Tom and Jerry.
I know you can't talk,
but I'm sure you can hear me.
Preeta's on Lexington,
and it looks like she's headed
for the Midtown Tunnel.
- [engine accelerating]
- [Tom yelping]
- [yelps]
- [car horn blares]
♪ Green light go ♪
[car horn beeps]
♪ People wanna know where Mase,
Pos, and Dave went ♪
♪ Still here,
Still in your ear ♪
♪ With a style so hot,
You'll see where all The sun rays went ♪
♪ Legs, arms, and head ♪
[yelps]
♪ The blends be all
The right cred ♪
[car horn honks]
[screams]
♪ When we rocking over pearls
In the instrumental ♪
[whimpering, yelps]
♪ Jump to the rhythm
As hard as you can go ♪
[grunting]
No, wait, they're actually
making a left turn on 57th.
They're going for
the Queensboro Bridge.
♪ But can you rock it
Like rocket fuel? ♪
♪ What you talking 'bout?
Space or out your mind? ♪
♪ But can you rock it
Like rocket, fool? ♪
♪ That's a close encounter of
What kind? ♪
[man] Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Guys, you have to get them
before they make it
to the bridge.
Hello?
Ugh, this no-talking thing
is really getting old.
♪ When it was time To get it
lit We got it hot like fever ♪
♪ Sick with the talk,
Pass to your receiver ♪
[men] Whoa!
♪ Simultaneously over joints
We rock ♪
♪ We earned thirty years,
So you can say that we got ♪
♪ Three turns
live off the board ♪
♪ Unlike you
and your chessmen ♪
♪ We install doubt in you
and your yes-men ♪
♪ And if the game have veins,
We'll insert the needle ♪
♪ upheaval the ground ♪
♪ 'Cause the adrenaline ♪
♪ we blend with the sound
Is our thing ♪
♪ relieving the kings
Of all crowns ♪
- [gasps]
- [Toots yowls]
- [snarls]
- [blows raspberry]
- [yowls]
- [Preeta] Toots!
[yowling in slow motion]
♪ Like rocket fuel? ♪
♪ What you talking 'bout?
Space or out your mind? ♪
- Stop the car!
- [brakes screech]
♪ But can you rock it
Like rocket, fool? ♪
♪ That's a close encounter of
What kind? ♪
[Toots yowls]
- ♪ Are you ready? ♪
- ♪ Ready ♪
Follow them. Let's go.
♪ Jump to the rhythm
as hard as you can go ♪
- ♪ Keep it steady ♪
- ♪ Steady ♪
- ♪ To the letter, right? ♪
- ♪ Bet ♪
♪ Turn it up,
We giving a show ♪
Could you keep up?
[Kayla] Great job, guys.
I'm sending you
a new location.
♪ But can you rock it
Like rocket, fool? ♪
♪ That's a close encounter of
What kind? ♪
♪ Ready, set ♪
- ♪ Steady, bet ♪
- [Preeta] Toots.
Come back!
♪ But can you rock it
Like rocket fuel? ♪
[soft instrumental music plays]
[imperceptible chatter]
What...
Kayla, what is going on?
[Kayla] Hear me out.
I know
yesterday was a disaster.
But I promise you
that most of the chaos
was because of me.
And them. [chuckles]
But just like me,
they've changed their ways.
But, Preeta,
I really think we have
the chance to make this right.
- Good luck.
- [Spike panting]
- [snarls]
- [gasps]
Listen, Preeta, I'm sorry.
Okay? I wanted to give you
the wedding of your dreams,
but at some point,
it drifted into my dreams
and your father's dreams,
and then your father
was in my dreams,
and in one of them,
he was riding a tiger.
It was really weird.
And then...
I'm sorry that
I didn't just shut up
and listen to what you wanted.
What I want is you.
It's only ever been that.
Going forward,
I promise fewer surprises,
and I promise more truth.
'Cause honestly,
I love you.
Will you please take this back?
[Spike moans]
[sighs and farts]
[retches]
And will you marry me again,
but better this time?
[celebratory music plays]
[people cheering]
- [Indian music plays]
- [Malcom trumpeting]
[all laughing and cheering]
- [low growl]
- [peacocks screaming]
[grunts softly]
♪ I ain't holding back
Let's bring it to life ♪
- [slurps]
- [gulps]
♪ ...out of sight ♪
♪ Color my world
With purple and green ♪
♪ You know what I mean,
Baby we got... ♪
You know, it wasn't
all Thomas and Jerome.
I know you had
a hand in it, too.
You were right
from the beginning.
A resume
is just a piece of paper.
You have to give
someone a chance
to find out what they can do.
I agree.
Yes, you, um,
did a very good job.
Thank you, Terence.
On that note,
I would love to introduce you
to Miss Linda Perrybottom.
Mr. Dubros.
The real owner of the resume.
Hello.
You must be Terence.
Uh, I am.
Josephine Pennybaker
at the Dorsey
says the most wonderful things
about you.
Oh, she does?
It's quite
an impressive resume.
Um...
I guess I'll see you
in my office tomorrow, or,
um, in Mr. Dubros' office
tomorrow.
[chuckles awkwardly]
Thank you, Kayla.
And we'll see you tomorrow.
Thank you, sir.
And I won't let you down.
Good luck, Terence.
[grunts softly]
[Toot purrs]
[purrs]
[gulps]
All right, I think we actually
might've pulled this off,
maybe.
[Cameron] Oh, definitely.
- [Kayla] Champagne.
- [Cameron] Mm-hmm.
Cheers.
[instrumental music continues]
[discordant notes playing]
[bench clicks]
[upbeat music plays]
[Jerry blows raspberry]
[Spike] Huh? [growls]
[Spike grunts]
[snarling]
[Spike] Come here, pussycat.
You're ruining the whole day.
[grunts] I'm gonna
turn you into a biscuit.
- [Spike] Huh?
- [Ben clears throat]
[Spike chuckles awkwardly]
Sorry. Nothing to see here.
What the...
["cut em in" playing]
- [Tom screams]
- ♪ Sometimes you need a friend ♪
♪ Not the ones
that just show up ♪
♪ And don't put nothin' in ♪
♪ You know the ones
that lend a hand ♪
♪ And wanna see you win ♪
♪ When you come up on a lick ♪
♪ Make sure you cut 'em in ♪
♪ And then, huh ♪
- ♪ Sometimes you need a foe ♪
- ♪ You need a foe ♪
♪ One that keep
Your eyes open ♪
♪ Keep you on your toes ♪
♪ You know the ones
that wanna keep you ♪
♪ Where you been before ♪
- ♪ But I can't go ♪
- ♪ No, I can't go ♪
♪ And woah, huh ♪
♪ Sometimes I need a check ♪
♪ Not the sneakers but the ones
That make you watch your step ♪
♪ Your chain, your name ♪
♪ How 'bout your respect? ♪
♪ Givin' more than what I get,
Expectin' nothing back ♪
- ♪ In fact ♪
- ♪ Nothing back ♪
♪ You know I sat down
With my accountant ♪
♪ He said, I got good news
And I got bad news ♪
- ♪ Okay. ♪
- ♪ I said, What's the good news? ♪
♪ He said, The good news is
You made a lot ♪
- ♪ Okay. ♪
- ♪ I said, What's the bad news? ♪
♪ The bad news is
You spent more ♪
♪ Okay ♪
[female] Maybach music...
♪ Grew up havin' nothing ♪
♪ You're labeled impatient ♪
♪ But once the boss made it,
you labeled amazin' ♪
♪ Meticulous with words,
That's your force of nature ♪
- ♪ Boss ♪
- ♪ I don't wanna seem absurd ♪
♪ But that boy's a gangster ♪
♪ Foc-focusin' on me,
Way from Tel-Aviv ♪
♪ Barbados with the hustle,
Pockets Elandis ♪
♪ Distinctive destinations
All I wanna see ♪
♪ Oceanfront residences,
Three different ones a week ♪
♪ 'Cause I deserve that,
It's time to learn that ♪
♪ Mess around
And put that thing up ♪
♪ Where your perm at ♪
♪ Six figures every year,
Yeah, I earned that ♪
♪ At the front of this line
Is where my turn at, huh ♪
♪ Sometimes you need a friend ♪
♪ Not the ones that
just show up ♪
♪ And don't put nothin' in ♪
♪ You know the ones
that lend a hand ♪
♪ And wanna see you win ♪
♪ When you come up on a lick,
Make sure you cut 'em in ♪
- ♪ And then... ♪
- ♪ Huh. ♪
♪ Sometimes you need a foe ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Men gon' lie,
Women gon' lie ♪
♪ You lookin' for the truth,
Then the numbers don't hide ♪
♪ Lookin' for the root Of all
evil, Then you need to go ♪
♪ Open up the briefcase,
See it with your eyes ♪
♪ Everybody claim
To be greatest of all times ♪
♪ But they never spend a day
In the rain in the front line ♪
♪ No lie, no lie ♪
♪ Uh, stop playin'
On my phoneline ♪
♪ Shoot, lock and load,
Pull up in the space coupe ♪
♪ With the roof optional,
Wonder why they follow suit ♪
♪ I've been groomed
From the womb ♪
- ♪ came out of my mama ♪
- ♪ Woo! ♪
♪ With some brand new
Tennis shoes ♪
♪ Faster than
The speedin' bullet ♪
♪ Nah, nah, nah,
It's cool, it's cool ♪
♪ Don't play with it, baby ♪
♪ Say what you gon'
Do with that ♪
♪ Stop playin' with it, baby ♪
♪ Turn around,
If you don't do it now ♪
♪ Don't play with it, baby ♪
♪ Exactly, yeah, 'cause you're
Not built like that ♪
♪ It's not a game ♪
[upbeat instrumental
music plays]
Uh, Mr. Dubros, I just
got a bill for both weddings.
That's a joke, right?
Well, you know, I, uh,
had Terence run some numbers
earlier and...
it doesn't look good for you.
Thank you for choosing
the Royal Gate.
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull