♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow
that fills up the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed
with the legend of the four-leaf clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse
carriage and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away all loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 35=
Although the company and the lab
have already been shut down,
but we still have to go through
the necessary procedures.
Please sign the consent form.
Mr. Gu, have you finished reading it?
Do you need to
reconsider your decision?
What do you mean?
You were
once our client
so we have to
satisfy all your requests,
but restoring
Normal Mode right now
is equivalent to committing suicide.
This is unprecedented
because no one
wants to shorten their own lives.
So, in my opinion,
you should reconsider it.
There's no need to.
I've already made up my mind.
Please restore it.
Let's get started then.
(Lifting Safe Mode)
Are you done with the exam?
Excuse me, Miss.
Sir,
are you talking to me?
Yes.
Are you waiting for someone?
Then, I'd like to ask,
are you waiting for your girlfriend?
Of course.
I'm waiting for my girlfriend.
I can't keep chatting with you.
Otherwise, when my girlfriend comes out
and sees us,
she'll get jealous.
Nonsense.
I'm not that petty.
Here. Your favorite.
Thank you.
So refreshing.
How did the exam go?
Hardly encountered any difficulties.
It's hard not to get a high score
after being tutored by a nice teacher.
And did you know?
There was a question
which we had encountered
in our art gallery project.
I had the answer right away.
Really?
Say...
This...
How come you smile all of a sudden?
I haven't seen
you smile in such a long time.
I didn't like smiling before
but I'm trying to
go along with your good mood
so you can relax.
I thought...
What?
What are you thinking?
I'm finally done with the exam.
Should we celebrate?
To celebrate...
Shall we go to...
The old family house.
-The old family house.
Then I'll bring my grandma
and my aunt too.
Sure.
Let's go.
Mom.
She's asleep.
Mom. Are you asleep?
Where are we?
Guess.
I think I recognize this road.
Are we going home?
Yes, we're going home.
We're going home.
Going home.
Look how happy my mom is.
This looks exactly like
our old family house.
Mom. Come and take a look.
Is it?
Can you still recognize it?
This is our home.
How can I not recognize it?
Really.
This is great.
The walls and the foundation are done.
Its exterior appearance won't change too much.
Grandma will recognize
this is our house with just one glimpse.
Xiao Ning.
You've really made something of yourself.
I'm so happy.
You're finishing
what your dad
couldn't.
I get emotional when talking about this.
Aunty, this is something to be happy about.
Let's stop being sad.
Right. I'll stop.
Mr. Gu.
I know that
you are the one
who has done most of what we see here.
But since
we're going to be
family in the future,
I won't
say thank you.
You're welcome, Aunty.
Aunty, what are you talking about?
Gu Chuan, why aren't
the workers here today?
It's their day off.
When you come here tomorrow,
remind them that
the waterproof layer isn't thick enough.
Okay.
The yard looks so pretty
after it has been cleaned up.
I came back after such a long time.
I have to go visit our old neighbors.
Mom, don't scare me.
How come you're not forgetful now?
You keep saying I'm a forgetful old lady.
I don't like it.
OK, you don't like it.
Which neighbor do I not know?
Alright, alright.
How about
you take me to visit
each and every one?
I haven't seen them in so long.
I don't know them anymore.
Grandma.
Mom.
-Mom, don't scare me like this.
-Grandma.
-Mom. Mom.
(Operating room)
Don't be so anxious.
Grandma will be okay.
I kept thinking
that it can't be good
since she's been getting sleepy all the time.
But I didn't know
it would get this bad all of a sudden.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have brought her to the old family house.
How is this your fault?
It's okay.
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
Xiao Ning.
Uncle Tang. I'm sorry.
I'm at the hospital.
I wasn't looking at my phone.
Wait.
Why are you at the hospital?
Something went wrong with Grandma.
Where's the patient's family?
Doctor.
How is my mom doing?
Relax. She's stable right now.
But her blood pressure is unstable,
causing severe damage to
the blood vessels in her brain.
The patient is already awake.
Let her rest more.
Doctor.
So everything is okay?
For now.
One of you
get the procedures done for her admission.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'll handle it.
You and Aunty go take care of Grandma.
Everything's okay, Aunty.
That really scared me.
There there. It's okay.
Granda is already awake.
(In-patient department)
Grandma.
Aunty, Grandma is awake.
Mom.
Mom, you're finally awake.
You almost scared me to death.
I'm not dead yet.
Why are you crying?
Grandma, Aunty is crying happy tears.
Happy tears.
It's great as long as you've woken up.
I feel like
I was in a dream.
When I wake up, here I am.
Mom.
It's great as long as you've woken up.
Uncle Tang.
Here, just a little something.
Thank you, Uncle Tang.
Grandma, Uncle Tang came to see you.
Xiao Mai.
Mrs. Jiang.
It's Guang Da.
Guang Da.
Don't get too emotional.
-Guang Da.
-Don't get too emotional.
Mom.
Guang Da.
He's not Guang Da.
He's the reason why Guang Da died.
Aunty.
Uncle Tang.
Grandma has been having trouble
recognizing people these few years.
Why did it take you so long
to come back?
Were you busy with work?
Or did anyone judge you?
Just go along with what she says.
I've been...
really busy with work.
It's good to be busy.
At least, it's better than not having a job.
A lot of people
have been saying that you embezzled public funds.
Not only public funds
but also much of
the retired employees' pension.
Someone died because of it.
But I don't believe them.
I brought you up.
I know
what kind of person you are.
You've been upright and kind
ever since you were a child.
You never made me worry.
I brought you and
Xiao Mai up by myself.
Many people asked me
why I sent my kids away
from home to go to school.
I don't think they understand
that going to school is the only way out.
You are the only one of our family
that have achieved something.
Don't be scared.
Mom believes in you.
When you walk out that door,
you need to keep your head up.
We won't confess to anything
we have never done before.
Guang Da.
I am not babying you
or being
partial to you because you're my son.
I know you're innocent.
You're innocent.
You're not guilty.
So, child,
don't be scared to come home.
Guang Da.
All these years,
-life has been tough on you.
-Don't get too emotional.
Don't get too emotional.
My son.
You've gone through so much.
Mom.
Lie down.
My son.
Guang Da.
Mom, you need to rest.
Mom.
Don't get too emotional.
Xiao Mai.
Your big brother hasn't eaten yet.
Hurry,
get him something good to eat.
I got it, Mom.
I'll ask Xiao Ning
to take him to get some good food.
Xiao Ning.
Uncle Tang.
My son is back.
Guang Da is back.
Rest well.
Mom, be at ease.
Sorry, Uncle Tang.
Grandma can't really think straight sometimes.
It's alright.
What do the doctors think?
The doctor said everything's fine.
Why were you in such a rush
to talk to me?
It's nothing.
I was worried about Grandma,
so I came by.
Take good care of her.
I'll come find you another day.
Okay.
I want to finish
the old family house as soon as possible
so Grandma can move in early.
I'm worried that she...
I'll contact them and ask them
to increase the manpower
and speed up the construction progress.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Let's go.
♪Walking across an empty space
and taking a chance♪
♪Is this the place of your dreams?♪
♪Ah♪
♪We can start again from here♪
♪Cuz I got the feeling♪
♪I got the feeling♪
♪No one's in the building♪
♪Should I go or should I let you know♪
♪For you, I let myself go♪
(Chuan&Ning 2020.10)
Please write down
what we discussed today.
Sure.
Okay.
Bye.
Later.
Goodbye.
See you.
Bye.
Alright, we're leaving.
Okay.
You've been working so hard lately.
Want to take a day off?
No.
I don't want to miss anything.
I want to watch
the house being built little by little.
What are you going to do
with the burnt future
you've collected?
I want to transform them
and put them back into the house.
The furniture
carry the past.
They can jog Grandma's
and Aunty's memories.
It might make them feel better than
just giving them a house.
Designs filled with love
are perfect.
Let's go.
Hi, Uncle Tang.
Xiao Ning, do you have time?
I have something very important
to tell you.
(Ward one, Beds 56-58)
Here, have some water.
Thank you.
Uncle Tang.
Do you have something
to tell me?
During the ten years I spent in prison,
to be honest,
I thought about your dad every day.
I'm really sorry. I've failed your parents,
your grandma, and you.
Uncle Tang, you...
Your dad was framed.
That car crash ten years ago
wasn't an accident.
It was planned.
The person who actually embezzled public funds
was...
No.
What are you doing?
What's so secretive
that we have to come here to talk?
What's going on?
The numbers don't add up.
You and I are in charge
of this project.
If something goes wrong,
we'd be held responsible.
Don't worry.
No one knows about this money.
Even if someone finds out,
our superiors will have to be confronted with it first.
You mean... Xu Guo Xiang?
Right.
Lao Tang.
Can he shoulder the responsibility?
It's more than 10 million yuan.
Besides,
he's the department head,
but we are the ones in charge
of this project.
If something goes wrong,
we'd be the ones to take the blame.
Lao Tang. Tell me the truth.
Where did the money go?
Tell me.
I can't tell you right now.
Lao Tang.
Being the kind of person you are,
you'd never do anything like this.
Xu Guo Xiang must be
the one behind you.
You two are in this together.
Right?
Lao Tang, what were you thinking?
You're sending yourself to jail,
you know?
Plus, these funds
include the pension for
the retired employees.
If you embezzle that money,
what will they live off of?
How dare you do something that
tramples over your conscience?
As time passes by,
there will be serious consequences!
Whatever,
suit yourself.
How much information does Jiang Guang Da have?
He started looking
for evidence a few days ago.
He's also the project manager.
He probably has all the
relevant evidence by now.
He...
He's going to report us.
What do we do?
Looks like we really...
have to think things through.
After your dad passed away,
we changed all the numbers.
Because the dead cannot give witness,
we shifted the majority
of the blame onto him
and I was only convicted as an accessory offender.
But being the department head,
Xu Guo Xiang only had to resign.
I'm sorry, Xiao Ning.
These are the accounting records...
I've kept from back then.
All the evidence
is in this thumb drive.
There's nothing I can do to make up for it.
I just want to give
these to you
and prove your dad's innocence.
So,
that car crash from ten years ago...
It was planned by Xu Guo Xiang
to make sure that the witness
will never talk again.
That car crash
not only killed my parents
but also badly injured Gu Chuan,
who tried to save us.
His life
has been a living hell for ten years.
No one knows
how much longer he has left.
I'm sorry, Xiao Ning.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
I caused your dad's death,
and you lost your mom because of me.
What's wrong?
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night. Ah~♪
I'm sorry.
This isn't your fault
or your parents' fault.
You're all victims.
It's my fault.
It's all my fault.
If I hadn't been so unlucky,
my dad wouldn't have run into
such terrible things;
there wouldn't have been a car crash;
my parents wouldn't have passed away;
you wouldn't have been injured,
and you wouldn't have been tortured
by the mechanical heart.
Now...
If it hadn't been for everything that had happened,
how could I have met you,
right?
But how come I'm the only one
who's alive and well?
My parents left me behind
and now even you are...
Don't leave me behind, okay?
What should I do?
I don't know what I should do.
It's okay.
Stop thinking about that.
I've looked through the information
and the accounting records in the thumb drive.
It's all solid evidence.
You can totally prove
your dad's innocence.
It can also prove
that Xu Guo Xiang was the major offender.
It's Xu Cheng Ran.
I asked him to come.
I wanted to give him a heads-up
so he can be mentally prepared
before we call the police.
(Accounting records of Dongjiang Group)
I never would've thought that
it was my dad who ruined your lives.
He killed Xiao Ning's parents
and almost killed
my best friend.
I...
I don't know what to say.
I don't deserve to be your friend.
What are you doing?
Chuan.
Xiao Ning.
I'm sorry.
Don't blame yourself.
None of these is your fault.
But he's my dad.
That's a fact that cannot be changed.
No one will blame you.
This matter has nothing
to do with you.
Chuan.
I'd rather you scold me,
hit me, or whatever, right now.
At least,
I'd feel slightly better that way.
Don't say anything to comfort me.
Ran Ran.
We cannot change anything
that has already happened.
Right now, we should be thinking about
how to solve the problem.
Calm down.
Mr. Xu.
You are Gu Chuan's friend,
Sister Yan Yan's husband,
and my friend.
But,
I'm sorry.
I cannot forgive your father
just because of this.
He still has to be
punished by law.
The reason we chose to
tell you as soon as we could
was for you
to be mentally prepared.
I understand.
I won't stop you,
but
I have a presumptuous request.
Ran Ran,
be reasonable.
I just want to say...
that he is my dad after all.
Could you give me a bit of time
to convince him
to turn himself in?
I promise
if he has
no intention to repent,
I'll turn him over
to the police myself.
What brings you back?
Dad.
You killed
Jiang Xiao Ning's parents.
What did you say?
I know everything.
I've already seen
all the evidence
about your embezzlement back then.
Who told you?
Jiang Xiao Ning?
Gu Chuan?
Does it matter?
Or are you going to kill the witnesses again?
Just like how you dealt with
Jiang Xiao Ning's family
and Gu Chuan by hitting them off the mountain
all those years ago.
When I found out about it,
I felt
that I didn't know you anymore.
I don't understand.
How could you have done
something so heinous?
How could you be so cruel?
You not only committed embezzlement
but also murder, really?
Gu Chuan
and Jiang Xiao Ning,
are my best friends.
You have ruined their lives.
I can't face them
anymore.
Why did you do that?
I don't understand.
I don't understand
how my dad could be a murderer?
Why?
There is no "why".
Look at this house!
Think about the company!
After I die,
everything will be yours.
That's why!
Because you're my son!
Do you think that leaving the money,
this house,
and Reindeer Group to me
is for the best of my interest?
Have you thought about
what I want?
I just want an unbroken family,
with both of you and mom in it.
Go turn yourself in.
This is the only thing
I can do for you right now.
Xu Cheng Ran.
You're going to send
your own father to prison
for an outsider?
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night~~♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪