♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and let's count down
to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 36=
Dad,
I've always hated you since I was a kid
and I always went against you.
But I have never
told you this.
Actually, you have always been my hero.
I have always
wanted your approval.
That's why I partnered with Gu Chuan
to start a company.
That's why I returned to Reindeer Group.
I don't want my hero
to be an irresponsible man.
For all the things you did back then,
I could pretend
you did it for our family
and it was a momentary lapse in judgment.
But wrong is wrong.
You have to own up to it.
I don't want my father
to end up being one who has no conscience.
Do you think I've
had a good time all these years?
You know what?
Actually, I have always
been beating myself up
and living with guilt.
Now that it has come to this.
It has come to this.
Thankfully.
You're all grown up now.
You can handle everything on your own.
I have nothing
to worry about now.
All right.
I'll listen to you.
I'll turn myself in.
Tomorrow morning.
Okay.
But...
you wouldn't try to run away,
would you?
I'm old now
and this kind of thing has happened.
Do you think running away will do me any good?
Son.
I have lived in this house
for far too long.
I just
want to stay quietly in this house
for another night
and I'll have no regrets.
Son.
I have wronged you
and let you down.
Hello, Director Xu.
Tang Xu was just here.
I have warned him.
Yes?
Jiang Xiao Ning and Gu Chuan?
Okay, I got it.
All right. I'll go now.
What's wrong?
Pack up your things.
Let's leave this place.
Didn't I tell you that I'm not leaving?
You have to go.
What's going on, Dad?
Are you hiding something from me?
Look.
Xu Guo Xiang is going to jail and he'll
definitely drag you into this.
Wait a second.
How do you know that he is going to jail?
Hold on.
See for yourself.
And this.
(Account name: Dongjiang Group)
Have you got home?
Almost there.
I'll go and meet you
after I'm done charging.
I'm going home to get some things for Grandma.
Then, I'll go to the hospital to swap shifts.
Why don't we meet in the hospital?
It's all right.
You've been running around with me all day.
Just go home and rest.
Get some sleep.
Don't worry about me.
I must be keeping you company
so that I can rest assured.
I know you must be in a bad mood.
But give Xu Cheng Ran
some time.
I believe
he'll be able to talk his dad round.
I know. I believe Mr. Xu, too.
That's all for now. I'm hanging up.
- Open the door! What are you...
- Don't move!
(Gu Chuan)
Xiao Ning?
Who are you?
Where's the evidence?
I have given it to the police.
If that's true,
things will be different now.
Don't lie to me.
None of you can get away with it.
Do you have a death wish?
Give me the evidence.
It's not with me.
Xiao Ning, where are you?
The evidence is with you, right?
Who are you?
That's not important.
What matters
is if the evidence is with you.
Yes.
It's with me.
If you dare to
lay a finger on Jiang Xiao Ning,
you won't get the evidence.
She's not what I want.
Give me the evidence
and I'll send her back to you.
Remember.
Come alone.
Don't try to play tricks.
Otherwise, I can't promise
that you'll see Jiang Xiao Ning
in one piece.
Where do I meet you?
I'll call you later.
Director Xu.
Where are you going?
How dare you
show up in front of me?
You've got a lot of nerve.
I'm not in the same league as you.
You could actually order the kill on people.
Let me ask you.
Mr. Jiang and his wife's deaths
are on you, right?
Did your dad
cook up nonsense again?
It looks like serving
ten years in jail isn't enough for Tang.
He didn't turn over a new leaf.
I suggest that
he should continue
serving time in jail.
I'm warning you.
Don't lay a finger on my dad.
He took the fall for you
and served ten years in jail.
I merely took some money of yours
and that isn't enough
to make up for his loss!
Xiao Xu.
I've told you before.
Don't line your pockets with my money.
I'm afraid if you do,
you can't come back from that.
Got it?
You have to pay a great price
for stealing my money.
You killed Xiao Ning's parents
and got my dad thrown behind bars for ten years.
I can't let things slide.
Well,
what are you going to do?
Call the police?
Sure.
But before you do that,
look at yourself first.
If I get jailed,
do you think you can get away with it?
I wouldn't be here
if I wanted to call the police.
Suits yourself then.
Where are you going?
It's none of your business.
Dad, going somewhere?
Why are you back here?
All I can say is that
nobody understands one's father
better than his son.
Did you forget
what you promised me?
I told you
that I would turn myself in tomorrow morning.
From what I see,
it doesn't seem like it.
Do you really
want your father
to be thrown behind bars?
You did let me down.
Ran Ran.
Actually, things aren't...
Say no more.
You have lied all your life.
Aren't you tired?
All I know is that
to achieve great things,
one needn't stand on trifles.
The so-called great things
are doing things by hook or by crook
and even by killing people for money.
If so, I'll never understand.
Perhaps,
Tang Xu will resonate with you.
Don't drag me into
your family affairs.
I'm leaving.
(Police)
No one will get away with it.
Whatever you have to say,
you can say it to the police.
Who called the police?
Me.
(Dad, I'm sorry.)
(I have been avoiding it.)
(If I had straightened you out sooner,)
(maybe you wouldn't end up like this.)
(Dad, I'm sorry.)
(Please forgive your unfilial son.)
Get on the boat.
Where's the stuff?
What's the hurry?
It's right here.
Let her go first.
Are you all right?
Why are you here?
You can't give them the evidence.
Don't bother about that.
How would I know
if you had a backup copy?
Or
if you had called the cops?
The reason I didn't call the police
is that I wanted to keep it on the down low.
After all,
it was ten years ago.
As long as I can take her away from here,
we'll pretend like
none of this has ever happened.
Why should I believe you?
I have no reason to lie.
I can abduct her today
and I can do it anytime again.
You'll have to pay a great price if you lie to me.
Why would I want to lie to you?
Let's go.
What's the meaning of this?
I'm sorry, you two.
No one is leaving today.
Do it.
Are you all right?
Watch out!
You shouldn't have messed with me.
Gu Chuan!
Gu Chuan, wake up!
Gu Chuan, don't scare me!
Gu Chuan!
His vital signs
are stable now.
As to when
he'll wake up,
we don't know
for sure.
Hasn't the safe mode
been activated?
Why would there still be electricity discharge?
Actually,
I've helped him
restore the initial mode.
His mechanical heart
has exited the safe mode.
What?
Mr. Gu said,
despite knowing his time left would be cut short,
at least, he would feel alive.
Also, he gets to feel
real emotions,
instead of living
like a machine.
(Mr. Gu said,)
(despite knowing his time left would be cut short,)
(at least, he would feel alive.)
(Also, he gets to feel)
(real emotions,)
(instead of living)
(like a machine.)
(Outpatient Department)
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The destined one♪
♪Guide me forward♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
♪We are total strangers
meeting for the first time♪
Don't be afraid.
I'm right here
♪Why does my heart beat so fiercely♪
with you.
♪Ah~ah~♪
Gu Chuan.
Ten years ago, you didn't give up on me
and encouraged me to live on.
Now,
it's my turn.
♪A dream with you in it♪
I won't give up on your either.
So don't give up.
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪The destined one♪
♪Guide me forward♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪
Ran Ran?
(Divorce Agreement)
(Yan Yan.)
(I can only say goodbye to you)
(in this way)
(because I don't have the courage)
(to look you in the eye)
(and say goodbye.)
(Indeed, I'm not an ambitious person.)
(But I have always wanted)
(to bring joy)
(to everyone around me,)
(make a good friend,)
(and fall in love with a girl.)
(All my dreams)
(have come true.)
(Department of Civil Affairs of Jiangdong)
(But)
(my dad)
(shattered my dreams.)
(All of a sudden,)
(I've lost the direction in my life.)
(Reindeer Group has gone bankrupt)
(and my dad is in jail.)
(I have to deal with a lot)
(of compensation issues.)
(Everything was ruined)
(in an instant.)
(Yan Yan.)
(I love you.)
(But)
(I don't have the ability)
(to protect our love.)
(I don't want to be a drag on you)
(and make you suffer with me.)
(Just leave the agreement here)
(after you have signed it.)
(I'll send someone to get it.)
(I hope)
(you'll live)
(a happy life.)
(Take care. Xu Cheng Ran.)
Why don't you hide away if you want to leave?
You picked such an easy place to find.
What do you want to do?
Kill yourself?
Is Gu Chuan awake?
Will he
stay like this forever?
How long do you plan to hide from me?
Xu Cheng Ran, do you still love me?
Indeed, your dad has hurt them.
But not you.
Besides,
what do all these have to do with us?
My dad has been arrested
and all his property has been confiscated.
My family
is broke and ruined now.
And from now on,
no matter where I go,
people will point fingers at me.
There's nothing that I can give to you.
Why bother coming to see me?
I don't need anything.
All I want is you.
I don't think
you'll need anything from me.
All these years,
I've never believed in love
because I was afraid of getting hurt.
That's why I didn't believe anyone
nor did I believe in eternal love
until I met Xu Cheng Ran.
After being with Xu Cheng Ran,
I don't have to twist open a bottle cap,
change a light bulb,
nor do I have to eat alone
or walk late at night.
Xu Cheng Ran is
willing to accept me for who I am
and go along with all my ridiculous requests.
Most importantly,
he loves my bad temper the most.
So I was thinking.
If I don't come and find him,
other girls
might steal him from me.
It will all be too late then.
I'm not that good...
Shut up. Let me finish.
So I came here today
to make it up to him
for all the pain
that I put him through back then.
I...
Zhao Yan...
kneel before Xu Cheng Ran
to ask his hand in marriage.
I hope
he'll come back to me
and let me be his queen again.
He'll always be prepared to let me
take advantage of him
and be at my beck
and call.
Let me use my lifetime
to love him with all my heart
for all eternity.
Xu Cheng Ran.
Will you marry me?
I do. Of course, I do.
But I've lost my job
and my company now.
How am I to support you?
♪You're the haze in my sky♪
I'll support you.
♪But you're my most gentle cover♪
♪Blocking out the blinding sunlight♪
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who asked me to love♪
♪I love this bad guy♪
♪I want to rely on you♪
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who asked me to love♪
♪I have no idea♪
♪I won't let go♪
Good morning.
Take a look.
We need to make some amendments.
Guys!
There's a meeting at 2 PM.
It's a last-minute meeting. Don't be late.
I'll be waiting for you.
Okay.
Here. Take a look.
This.
(Emergency)
(Inpatient Department)
Good morning, Boss.
Today is Monday.
It's a working day.
So I still have to call you "Boss".
The weather is good today.
You don't have any plans anyway.
The only thing you need to do
is to lie in bed
and have a chat with me.
I'll tell you stories
and news.
Mr. Xu said,
Chen Ao,
the young man
who caused the car accident ten years ago, died.
The police found out
that Xu Guo Xiang
ordered Assistant Liu to do it.
That adds to their list of crimes
and they'll be given heavy punishments.
I have no idea
how to comfort Mr. Xu.
But don't worry.
Sister Yan Yan will surely
be with him and help him get through it.
The biggest news of today is that
I have got my degree certificate.
From now on,
I'm officially a designer.
You feel happy for me, right?
Yesterday, Grandma and Aunty
have moved into our family house.
I stayed there last night.
When I see all those things
that you prepared for me,
lying in the starry room that you made for me,
I would recall
the old memories.
The doctor said
that Alzheimer's is hereditary.
I'm afraid that I'll forget you someday.
If you don't want me
to forget you,
then wake up, alright?
All right now.
It's time for you to listen to the news.
A well-known Cambridge neuroscientist
recently pointed out
in a large public event in the United Kingdom
that although the human brain
is extremely complex,
the understanding
of various parts of brain cells
is gradually deepening.
If the computer has the function
of recreating a 100M connection,
it will
no longer be a dream to transform the brain
into a program code
to survive in the machine.
Did you hear that?
This new technology
seems like a good chance
for us.
What if
we convert our consciousness
into a digital file
and upload it to a computer,
does it mean
we can meet again
in the cloud?
Gu Chuan.
You can hear me, right?
All right.
I'll go downstairs and get some fruits.
(Three years later)
I'm back.
Do you feel tired today?
It's all right.
I went to the construction site today.
Everything goes according to plan.
It's going smoothly.
By the way,
Sister Yan Yan asked me
to accompany her for the prenatal
testing next week.
Shouldn't Xu Cheng Ran
go with him instead?
Sister Yan Yan doesn't
want him to go with her.
Xu Cheng Ran gets all nervous
each time he hears
the baby's heartbeat from the device.
All right then.
What delicious food did you buy today?
Take a guess.
Steak?
Why did you get it right again?
That's because
I've got the red wine ready in advance.
No one can beat
the chemistry between us.
Are you done charging?
Yes.
Do you want to test it?
Test what?
What can it be?
Here.
There isn't much fluctuation.
Your heart rate
remains over 80bpm now.
Back then, it would jump up
to over 100bpm when I kissed you.
Does it mean
we can take it to the next level?
What's the rush?
What if
something goes wrong again?
Fine.
The rules of us getting along
remain unchanged for now.
Keep things the way they are now.
Actually, this is good enough for me.
Once in a while,
you can drink some wine
and let me kiss and hug you.
I think
we should take one step at a time.
When I'm fully recovered,
we can go directly
from the first to the third base.
It's cooking time.
♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
(In the past three years of waiting,)
(each day was a torment.)
(The memories between Gu Chuan and I)
(were the only thing that kept me going.)
(Our encounter, our love,)
(and all the ups and downs we had)
(are like a long movie)
(that constantly plays in my head.)
(In this long wait,)
(I look forward to a miracle.)
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away all loneliness♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
(Finally,)
(Qing Zi found a new scientific research team)
(to fix the loopholes based on the results)
(of Dr. Peer's research.)
(Finally, Gu Chuan has a heart)
(Dear Qing Zi, we're getting married!)
(that allows him to live a normal life.)
(Although)
(this heart doesn't have a heartbeat,)
(Gu Chuan's love)
(for me)
(is long proven even without it.)
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away all loneliness♪
(Chuan & Ning, October 2020)
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪