(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
Wow, you look so relaxed,
sitting out here drawing.
Did you enjoy getting me expelled?
Why did you do it? Why?
Why did you even get involved?
- Because I'm a witness. - What?
I only described what I saw.
You're a real psycho.
You're out of your mind, aren't you?
Han Dong Rim.
You seem to think you're something.
Don't, because you're not.
I'll kill you.
Sure.
Kill me if you can.
Kill me.
Let's go.
Kid!
Kid?
If you hear this, come to Muji High School.
We have a shelter.
(Dark Hole)
If you hear this, come to Muji High School.
We have a shelter.
Anyone can come.
If you hear this, come to Muji High School.
We have a shelter.
If you're a survivor, come to Muji High School.
If you hear this, come to Muji High School.
We have a shelter.
Anyone can come.
- Come on! Hurry! - Come to Muji High School.
We have a shelter.
- Are you okay? - Are you okay?
Dad, I think I sprained my ankle.
I'll take her.
- Get going without us. Go on. - Dad.
Hurry up and go!
Keep going! Go!
Run!
Go!
Is he trying to get everyone in here killed?
- Sir. - Let go of me.
We need to save people who are outside.
There are monsters out there. We can't open the door.
Sir, listen.
There are people out there including our students.
Director Choi doesn't want anyone to open the door.
What?
- Mr. Choi. - Hyun Mi.
Hyun Mi! Hyun Mi!
Hyun Mi... Hyun Mi!
Hyun Mi!
Hyun Mi! Hyun Mi! Hyun...
Did you see that?
Are you going to keep listening to the director?
Would you have done the same if that kid was your daughter?
Kid.
Where are you?
Do they not harm animals?
Come inside. Hurry.
Are you okay?
Thank you.
By any chance, did a kid happen to come in here?
It's a girl.
Are you looking for Do Yoon?
Do you know her?
Detective.
Detective, are you okay?
If you're hurt, let me take a look.
It's okay.
I just bumped into an injured person.
But why did you take the kid?
There seems to be a misunderstanding.
I only brought her here because she was all alone.
Do you know her?
Yes, I work as a nurse at the same hospital as her mother.
Did you say you're a detective?
I'm a detective from the regional investigation unit in Seoul.
What brings you all the way here from Seoul?
I came looking for someone.
Are you here to catch a criminal?
But where's Do Yoon's mother?
She's dead.
Do Yoon.
It's okay.
You can stay here with me from now on.
Sister, why don't you give Do Yoon something to drink?
Okay, sure.
We have hot chocolate. Would you like some?
You don't need to ask me for permission.
Okay.
Is it because you're a detective?
How could you say her mother died right in front of the kid?
She needs to be strong from now on.
What is this place?
Don't be afraid.
We are here with the New Savior.
Are you all right?
Yes.
What is it?
This belongs to one of our believers.
I thought you might want to change...
since your clothes are stained with blood.
Thank you.
Are you really okay?
What?
You don't seem so well.
Would you like to drink the water of life?
This will help you calm your anxiety.
No, it's okay.
Let me tell you this.
You and Do Yoon are here...
because that's what the New Savior wanted.
Right now, the New Savior...
is punishing those who have no faith.
What do you mean?
The New Savior led you here.
So you should believe in the New Savior.
Do you really mean that?
I can see you're very suspicious.
You must let go of your suspicions if you want to go to paradise...
Listen.
You're free to believe in whatever you want to believe.
But you'd better stay alert.
That's the only way you can stay alive.
What about Do Yoon?
You're free to choose your own path.
But you don't have the right to choose what's good for her.
Do Yoon...
is safer here with me.
You think about that.
Help. Please help.
Help. Let me in.
Please.
Please take me to the hospital.
Please hurry up and take me to the hospital.
(Taehan Towing)
My gosh. Good work.
Doctor, this will be enough to keep out the black smoke, right?
Yes. Those are three-panel doors. No smoke will get through them.
But I'm not sure about the mutants.
Officer Cho and I will keep you safe.
Don't worry.
Everyone, you can relax.
The rescue time will be here any moment.
- Yes! - Yes!
- Hooray for Officer Park! - You're the best!
Hooray for Officer Park!
- Hooray for Officer Park! - Officer Park, you did a great job.
Have some coffee.
I appreciate it.
Officer, you really are incredible.
You're risking your life and taking the initiative...
for the citizens.
Everyone.
We all...
should trust Park Soon Il and relax.
- Of course. - We trust him.
Thank you so much.
I feel so safe now.
Goodness, he really did a good job.
The person you have reached is not available...
Still not working?
No.
It's going to be restored soon. Don't worry too much.
(Taehan Towing)
What happened?
(Police)
Hello? Open the door!
Hello? Please open the door!
Hello?
Soon Il, it's me. It's Tae Han.
Open the door!
There's an emergency patient.
Open up!
It's urgent! What are you doing?
This is getting interesting.
Hey, Doctor!
There's an emergency patient. Please open the door.
Officer Park, we should open the door right now.
- Okay. - Hold on.
Our priority is to keep the people in here safe.
If that man is infected, he'll put everyone in danger.
Open the door right now!
Open up! Now!
(Muji Hospital)
Are you out of your mind?
- I'll break the door! - Officer Park!
We can't let the smoke in. Open the door right now.
So? Should I break it?
Okay.
- Take him to the emergency room. - Okay.
You almost killed me.
You crazy idiot. You almost killed all of us.
Calm down.
It wasn't easy for us to open the door in this situation.
I'm sorry.
Follow me. You seem to need treatment.
Doctor, what do you think you're doing?
If he's been bitten by a mutant,
he must be infected too.
Not everyone who gets bitten gets infected.
I'll take full responsibility.
Come with me.
Do you remember me?
Yesterday, you told me...
to keep the smoke out of the hospital.
That's right.
We could protect our patients and their families...
thanks to you.
Thank you.
Rest up now.
Your arm...
I'm sorry.
Sure.
You're free to choose your own path.
But you don't have the right to choose what's good for her.
Do Yoon...
is safer here with me.
You think about that.
Detective?
Detective, do you hear me?
Yes, I hear you.
Good. You're safe.
Yes. You too.
So... The kid. Did you save her?
I saved the kid,
but not the nurse.
I too...
couldn't save my friend.
Don't blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
Where are you?
I briefly took shelter somewhere safe.
I'm at Muji Hospital.
Are there any survivors there?
Yes, fortunately.
I see.
I think I should head to the school.
They have a shelter.
I'll contact you again.
Be careful.
I'll give you an antibiotic and tetanus shot.
Thanks.
(Yoon Saet Byeol, Nurse)
- Yoon Saet Byeol. - Is she from here?
- She's from Seoul. - How old is she?
She's 22.
What does she do?
Are you interrogating me?
- I bet she's weird. - She's not.
She's an angel. A total angel.
Do you...
happen to know a Nam Young Sik?
Wait. Do you know Young Sik too?
Yes. We're friends.
He didn't tell you something weird, did he?
Not really.
He said you're nice.
He'll be safe too, won't he?
Well,
he does have lots of talents.
He does.
I bet he's hiding somewhere safe.
He's quick-witted, very unlike his looks.
Were you...
on the radio with a detective?
Yes.
Then will we all be rescued?
I don't know.
I see.
I hope things go back to normal.
Just eat.
(Emergency Center)
Come on. Will you just get up?
- Come over here. - Oh, dear.
Salute.
Rookie. Repeat after me. Sparrows go...
Sparrows go...
- Sparrows... - Yoo Tae Han.
All I have to say to you is,
do not become like him.
- Do you understand? - Yes, sir.
You're so out of it. Stand up straight.
Why is this place so...
- out of order? - What are you doing?
How's this?
Go on your way. We're wrestling.
How dare you? Stand down.
I saw you.
Pardon?
Where's the woman?
The woman?
That woman inhaled black smoke too.
Don't be too anxious.
You'll find out soon.
Mr. Kim, we can't use the broadcasting booth now, can we?
No. Director Choi smashed it up.
Isn't that where the emergency communication equipment is?
It is.
It's for the best.
If people hear the broadcast and keep coming here,
we'll run out of food.
The few who are here need to survive, right?
- I'll get more tape. - Okay.
Stack it up so there are no spaces for mutants to squeeze through!
Get to it!
What are you doing? Move faster.
My gosh.
Are you stupid? You can't even do this?
Is your finger tasty? Give me that.
Can't you even hammer a nail?
- You moron. - It really hurt.
You moron.
- Watch it. - What?
Darn you.
Are you here to fool around?
No, sir.
They're still young.
They're not good with nails.
Look.
Do you think the mutants differentiate men, women, and kids?
Hello, Director Choi.
Do your job right.
One person's mistake can get us all killed.
Do you understand?
Mr. Seo. It's your responsibility.
Report to me when everything's done.
I understand, sir.
How are we to overcome a crisis with this slack mindset?
Kids these days don't think.
All they know to do is waste taxes.
Did you check the gas masks?
Yes. We'd bought some last year for the crisis management course.
Is the emergency generator fueled?
If we use it sparingly, it'll last us a month.
And rations?
I checked the food we have in the cafeteria.
We have enough for a week.
One week?
Yes. For the students, staff, and local residents.
- Starting today, we eat once a day. - Once a day?
Are you here on a picnic?
This is an emergency.
We don't know how long this will go on for.
Should we feed everyone three meals a day?
Do you want us all to die?
I apologize. I didn't think that far, sir.
Do you remember what we must do...
in case of an emergency?
Yes, sir.
Bye, then.
(The New Savior is waiting for you.)
Detective, you must be hungry.
Let's eat.
Do Yoon, you can come eat with me.
(Evangelize for the New Paradise)
Let's all say grace.
We sincerely thank the New Savior for providing us food...
during these times of hardships.
We believe you will save us and take us to the new paradise.
- We believe. - We believe.
Let our faith enable you to achieve all your plans.
- We believe! - We believe!
- Our savior will achieve his plans! - We believe.
Let us eat now.
What's wrong?
Do you not like instant food?
No, it's not that.
I think it's time for me to leave.
Let's go, Do Yoon.
She should eat first.
Don't you agree?
Eat up. Here.
- My goodness. - Oh, gosh.
Do Yoon.
- My goodness. - What's wrong?
My goodness, Do Yoon. What's wrong?
- Do Yoon. - Is she okay?
Do Yoon, what's wrong?
Oh, dear.
Do Yoon. Do Yoon, hang in there.
- Help me lay her down. - Okay.
Just a second. Do Yoon, open your eyes.
Do you see me?
Wait.
Is this where it hurts?
We need to increase her body temperature, so bring me a blanket.
- Okay. - Do Yoon.
Do Yoon, look at me. Do Yoon, can you hear me?
She'll be okay soon.
What happened to her?
Do Yoon has anaphylaxis.
How do you treat that?
She needs an epinephrine injection.
What?
She needs an adrenaline shot.
Don't worry.
The New Savior will protect Do Yoon.
You will recover soon.
- We believe. - We believe.
Do Yoon, why don't you drink the water of life...
so that you will recover soon?
Let's go.
I know what you're thinking.
But that will only put Do Yoon in danger.
She's a lot safer here with us.
Do you really think...
you can protect her until this is all over?
Are you going somewhere?
How's the kid?
She's okay now.
Ms. Kim...
is taking good care of her, so don't worry.
I haven't seen you eat anything.
You should at least drink some water.
You might think we're bizarre. I understand that.
But we're not bad people...
like criminals.
Please don't get the wrong idea about us.
I heard an announcement before coming here.
Are you talking about the school?
Once the kid gets better,
we'll be going there.
Detective, do you seriously believe the announcement?
Schools turn into shelters in disasters like this happen.
How foolish of you.
Going there...
won't help you get rid of your fears.
No.
You're the ones who are trembling in fear.
You just blindly depend on that savior of yours.
Okay, fine. You lack faith.
So you're free to leave.
But you can't take Do Yoon.
She'll be staying with us...
so she can get on the boat to the new paradise.
That is what's best for Do Yoon.
Don't worry.
Ms. Kim just mixed...
a small dose of tranquilizer into your water.
Hello.
I'm sorry about this afternoon.
No, it's okay. You were right.
I know the girl who died wasn't my daughter or anything.
But I just didn't want to get scolded by the director...
and ended up making the wrong choice.
Does that mean you forgive me for what happened earlier?
Gosh, there's nothing to forgive.
You're the one who's going through the most.
No, that's not true. You have a lot more to do.
No, that's nonsense.
- Anyway, thank you. - Don't mention it.
It's even scary to pee in the bathroom now.
But we're lucky because we won't have to take the CSATs.
What does the CSATs have anything to do with you? My gosh.
- Are you nuts? - What?
If I put my mind to it and study hard,
I can easily go to a four-year university.
Hey.
I still can't access the Internet.
Are you sure Korea is an IT powerhouse?
What if it's not just us? What if the entire country's destroyed?
Why would you even say something so absurd?
- Just go to sleep. - My gosh.
What are you doing?
Hey, why don't you guys just be quiet?
Say a word about...
what happened to the kids in the mountains, and you're dead meat.
Do you understand?
What are you so afraid of?
What?
Oh, because you let a friend die to save yourself?
Is that it?
What do you know?
Stop pretending to be tough.
I can see how terrified you are.
It won't be long until you turn into...
a monster yourself.
Shut it.
I won't.
Never.
Everyone. For us to be able to ascend,
we must leave all our sins here on earth.
That way, we won't be bogged down by our sins anymore.
Absolutely.
So what must we do now?
- We must cleanse our souls. - We must cleanse our souls.
That's right.
We must empty ourselves of our sins completely.
- We believe. - We believe.
If we do that, we can reach the new paradise...
on the vessel of redemption with the New Savior!
- We believe! - We believe!
It will come true!
We believe!
- It will come true! - It will come true!
We believe. Save us.
We believe.
It will come true.
Now,
think of your sins that you must cleanse yourself from.
(Evangelize for the New Paradise)
We are now ready to ascend to the new paradise...
and the moment of redemption is here!
It's okay.
Stop!
Send the kid...
to me.
You still don't understand?
There is nothing you can do for this kid.
Let Do Yoon's soul be redeemed.
Stop this nonsense.
This is not redemption. This is murder!
Shut it, you demon!
Do Yoon, hurry up and drink.
This is your last warning.
Detective.
Do you still not see it?
The world is coming to an end.
Before it's too late,
aboard the vessel of redemption with us.
Enough!
Then how about we let the kid choose?
Does she really want to stay here with you,
in the world that is coming to an end?
Do Yoon. Don't you...
want to see your mom again?
I...
want to see her.
Do you want to come with us...
or stay here with that woman?
Kid.
Come to me.
Your mom asked me to protect you.
Let me keep that promise.
Do Yoon. Come on.
Do Yoon.
Come to me.
How dare you ruin the plans of our New Savior?
Run away, now!
4 times 4 is 16. 4 times 5 is 20.
4 times 6 is 24. 4 times 7 is 28.
- Kid. - 4 times 8 is...
Where are you?
My mom...
would always find me whenever I would hide.
There you are.
Did you think I wouldn't find you if you hid here?
How did you know I was here, Mom?
It was your smell.
Not a bad smell. A really nice smell.
Do Yoon. Do Yoon! Jung Do Yoon!
Mom!
Do Yoon. Are you okay? Are you hurt?
I'm okay.
My baby.
She said she could find me because I have a nice smell.
It's okay now.
My mom trusted you.
So I trust you too.
We must get out of here.
Let's go.
(Emergency Equipment)
Please forgive us for our sins.
As we forgive those who caused...
Go away. Get away from me.
Satan. You devil!
Go away! Step away!
I command you in the name of our New Savior!
Leave!
(Muji Hospital)
Hey.
What now?
That bite. It's from a mutant, isn't it?
A mutant?
That's what we call people whose eyes turned black.
Don't change the topic. Roll up your sleeve.
Why should I?
I'm right.
Officer Cho, handcuff him.
- Will you let it go? - Come on now.
Don't you know you're abusing your authority?
I'm not abusing my authority.
I'm doing my job to protect the public.
Undo it.
Doctor, there's something you must see.
- What is it? - There's a survivor.
What? Where?
In the lab on the fifth floor.
Someone survived.
Look at that.
The surgical ward was shut down.
(Help! There are survivors here.)
Wait.
Look. Isn't that your wife?
Daddy's off to work. See you.
Take care!
That's my wife.
My Ji Hye's up there!
Hwa Sun!
(All child actors underwent psychological therapy.)
(Special thanks to Jung Hae Kyun.)
(Dark Hole)
Don't lie.
You know no one's coming to rescue us.
What are you doing?
What if everyone here got infected?
The expectant mother isn't doing well.
To save everyone else, sacrifices must be made!
Would you have said that if they were your family?
Hwa Sun!
I think someone's controlling them.
Open the door quick.
The black smoke wasn't the end of it.