(Episode 2)
Are your legs made of jelly?
Why are you all over the place?
Who says so?
It's your engagement party
tomorrow. Are you ready?
Do you need any help?
No, but thanks for the offer.
Right. Unit 4502 has been sold.
Really?
Does that mean
I'll finally have a neighbor?
That's great!
What kind of a person are they?
It's a bit of an unlucky suite
with Oh Yoon Hee and all.
Did the person buy the suite
without knowing that?
Chairman Joo recommended it
to him.
He's the CEO of an American
biopharmaceutical company.
Is he Korean?
Or Korean-American?
He's Korean.
The company's name is JohnBIO.
Oh my. JohnBIO?
Looks like Hera Palace's prices
will rise again!
How do you know about JohnBIO?
Their sexual enhancer is a huge hit.
My husband uses it all the time.
It works so well.
You know I'm alone.
Are you teasing me or what?
Let's finish it up here.
Should we?
My mind is all over the place
with the engagement tomorrow.
Great work, reporters.
You must be extra nervous since it's
your 20th-anniversary concert.
I didn't expect to
hear you go off-pitch.
I guess my throat is dry.
You won't publish it, will you?
Of course not.
Did you prepare anything special
for this performance?
The industry is expecting you
to do something new.
I won't disappoint.
Bye now.
- Secretary Do!
- Yes, ma'am.
He better not write
a ridiculous article again.
Let's go from there again.
Hitting a high F won't be possible
in this condition.
You should head home.
It's your engagement tomorrow.
Performing is more important
than my engagement.
You know that this is the most
important performance of my life!
I can do it.
Play from the last part.
Well, how have you all been?
Are you in the middle of something?
Why do you look so surprised?
Am I not allowed here?
Oh, I'd like to introduce my wife,
Oh Yoon Hee.
What?
It's been a while.
Congratulations
on your engagement, Seo Jin.
Your wife?
Did I hear it wrong?
Are you saying you two got married?
So, Dr. Ha, you're saying
that your wife is Oh Yoon Hee?
You two?
What's this surprise?
How could you get involved
with her, of all people?
Exactly. Of all women,
why a possible murderer?
- Ms. Kang.
- Yes?
I see you talk as much as always.
But that's enough.
It's impolite to question something
that the law has already...
concluded.
But... What about Ro Na?
Did she come too?
Nice dress.
It looks good on you.
I don't remember inviting you
to my engagement party.
Don't get the wrong idea.
We had some business at the hotel,
that's all.
Still.
It's nice to see you again.
Dr. Ha.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Didn't you say you were conducting
some research in the US?
Well... Being a doctor
wasn't the right fit for me.
So I started a small business.
A business?
That's even a worse fit.
You two didn't start...
seeing each other when you lived
in Hera Palace, did you?
Definitely not.
I don't do things like that.
We met in the US. By chance.
Dr. Ha.
This is quite rude.
This is a happy day.
You came on purpose
to ruin it for us.
We really stopped by
on our way somewhere.
Well... I apologize
if we caused an interference.
See you around.
Congrats, Eun Byeol.
You have a stepmom too.
A super famous one
from the news, at that.
Don't look at me like that.
I like you all of a sudden.
Don't we feel closer now?
The feeling is mutual.
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol! Where are you going?
Murderer.
How dare you show your face here?
Seok Kyung!
I don't believe
that you're innocent.
Ms. Yang would've never
killed my mom.
You killed her.
My mom was so good to you.
Why did you kill her? Why?
I was sad because everyone seemed
to have forgotten...
all about Su Ryeon.
I feel good knowing
you remember your mom.
Let's go.
I won't fall for it.
Murderer. Demon!
That brat.
How did she change so much?
I already thought...
seven million dollars was too much
in alimony for you.
What more are you trying to get,
that you show up in a chopper...
and designer clothes,
trying to look like you matter?
If Oh Yoon Hee was...
all you could think of
to get under Seo Jin's skin,
I'm very disappointed.
It's quite a novel approach,
but this is where it ends.
If you show your face again...
Let go!
Stop.
Hey. Shall we go?
Sure.
Are you okay?
Of course.
What happened?
He should've been fish food.
Why is he still alive?
They said they took care of him.
You loser.
Find out if Ha Yoon Chul
and Oh Yoon Hee really are married.
Find out everything she did
over the past three months.
Do you like it?
We couldn't go far this time
because of your concert,
but once it's over,
let's go to Italy for a few days.
Sound good?
Our engagement is
public information now.
There's no reason to delay
the merger.
I'll hire an M and A expert
next week...
- and form a special...
- What's the rush?
I'm busy this year with concerts.
That's why we got engaged
instead of getting married.
- Does it bother you?
- What?
You've been thinking only about
that jerk Ha Yoon Chul.
I did not.
I know you.
I'm trying my best
to make you happy,
but your mind is elsewhere.
He ruined our engagement party.
In front of everyone from
Hera Palace and our VIP guests.
I don't know what they're up to.
Do you think...
Yoon Hee reconnected with Logan
in the US?
They could've brought Yoon Chul in
to get revenge on us.
It's not him.
Logan is pretty much
on house arrest right now.
I'm in touch with his father
constantly.
If they are not involved...
Are you saying
they really got married?
That's ridiculous.
They were each other's first love.
The losers must have formed a pact.
He wouldn't get married easily
at least because of Eun Byeol.
And what? Business?
I wired him 10 million dollars
when the land in Myeongdong sold.
10 million dollars? When was that?
A year ago.
He'd never stop being a doctor.
He doesn't have the guts
to do business...
nor the greed.
We got engaged today!
How long will you talk
about Ha Yoon Chul?
Can't you leave it to me?
Do you have that little faith in me?
Sorry...
for yelling.
I must've been upset
because of Eun Byeol.
Ha Yoon Chul. Oh Yoon Hee.
They have nothing to do
with my life anymore.
I'll never see them again.
Are you okay?
Ms. Kang. What is it?
Ms. Cheon. This is huge.
The new resident of Unit 4502...
is Oh Yoon Hee.
It's Dr. Ha and Oh Yoon Hee.
What do you mean?
That's...
Let's talk later.
Yoon Hee is back.
What?
In Hera Palace.
What do you mean?
Yoon Chul is the one
who bought unit 4502!
Ha Yoon Chul?
How could he...
Wait. JohnBIO?
That's ridiculous.
Why didn't you check and confirm?
How could you approve the sale?
How could I have known? It was
bought in the corporation's name.
You should've been thorough.
Weren't you having Yoon Hee watched?
Didn't you consider the fact
that the two of them could meet?
Must I keep tabs on
your ex-husband too, now?
This is my fault too?
You're incompetent!
You need to admit it.
Then you should've kicked him out...
to some hinterland where
he could never return.
Don't you know what I did to kick
Yoon Hee out of Hera Palace?
Don't you know what I did
to get her out of my sight?
And she's back.
Because of you.
If you had taken care
of Ms. Yang properly,
Oh Yoon Hee wouldn't have
been acquitted.
That's all in the past now.
Even if she's back, what can she do?
All her properties have been seized.
She may have been acquitted,
but her label as a murderer
will never go away.
Ha Yoon Chul is the CEO of JohnBIO!
And Oh Yoon Hee is his wife!
I must have underestimated
Oh Yoon Hee.
I have to go back.
What can you do?
We freed up our time to be here.
We can't let those scum
ruin our precious time.
It's already ruined.
I can't trust you anymore.
I'll handle everything myself.
Darn it!
What is it?
I found out why Dr. Ha
came back to Korea.
He's the actual owner
of the American startup, JohnBIO.
Why are you
telling me that now, you jerk?
Gosh!
No way. It can't be.
Power Up was developed
by Ha Yoon Chul?
The CEO of JohnBIO, one of
the three people I respect the most,
turns out to be the loser,
Ha Yoon Chul?
This is humiliating.
His time in the US seems to have
done him a lot of good.
He has this successful
businessman's vibe to him now.
When his company goes public,
the stock prices will soar.
Will he make it to the penthouse
on the 100th floor before us?
You're right.
Even the Gangnam assemblyman is
still around the 50th floor.
How did Oh Yoon Hee get so lucky?
Do you think I'm not going up there
because I can't afford it?
It's because the voters are
not happy about it.
- Didn't Dr. Ha look so stylish?
- I know.
That Italian suit
looked perfect on him.
Was he always that good-looking?
That's why a man needs to
meet the right woman.
- He's become so sweet and gentle.
- Exactly.
I heard that they're
each other's first love.
If Ms. Cheon hadn't stolen him,
they would have gotten married
and lived happily.
This is such a huge blow
to Ms. Cheon, isn't it?
Serves her right.
Imagine how jealous she must be.
Why would she be?
She's getting married to
Chairman Joo soon anyway.
Women are not like that.
How can you still be
so clueless about women?
I can see why he's
so unpopular with them.
You have no idea.
- I won 52 percent of the votes.
- Oh Yoon Hee probably...
- saved a country in her past life.
- People on the internet adore me.
- I even won a beauty pageant...
- I thought Dr. Ha had a photoshoot.
- As a kid.
- Exactly.
What are you doing, Ms. Jin?
Ms. Cheon.
I thought you were on a trip.
I said, what are you doing?
Why are you cooking at this hour?
It's Eun Byeol's turn
to bring snacks tomorrow,
so I thought I should start
preparing them.
Pizza, tteokbokki, fritters...
What time did Eun Byeol go to bed?
Well, I don't know exactly.
How is that possible?
Didn't I tell you...
to keep a close eye on her
throughout her senior year?
You go to bed with her
and wake up with her.
You make sure she's feeling well,
going to the bathroom regularly,
and having regular periods.
Didn't I tell you to watch
her every move?
From her diet to her class schedule,
health, weight, and sleep cycle,
you're in charge
of everything about her.
I am well aware of that.
I also know that I should
handle her with utmost care.
I do want you to pay more attention.
- Mom.
- You're still up?
It's past 3 a.m.
Well, I had some studying to do.
When did you get back?
What about your trip?
I came back early
because I was worried about you.
Why would you be worried about me?
I'm doing fine.
I was hoping that you and Mr. Joo
would enjoy some time together.
Well, my throat is a little sore.
I wrapped up
so I wouldn't catch a cold.
Don't forget to take
your propolis and vitamins.
Okay.
Have you been...
talking to your dad lately?
You're the one who blocked
his calls and e-mails.
Did you know that...
he got married to Ro Na's mom?
No, I had no idea.
It's humiliating.
It's driving me crazy.
Why Bae Ro Na, of all people?
He knows how much I loathe her.
Do you see it now?
Your dad is never any help.
I've already erased him
from my life.
I'm not going to see him
even if he contacts me.
That's a good idea.
Until you reach the top,
I'll support you fully.
You're all I have.
I'll study some more.
Go to bed, Mom.
- Don't strain yourself.
- Okay.
Hurry up and leave
through the back door.
What are you doing over there?
Are you here to see Ro Na?
No.
(Fragile, picture frame)
What are you doing
to someone else's photo?
Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol.
My girl, you must have
been surprised.
Are you going to live here?
At Hera Palace? With Bae Ro Na?
I'm sorry, Eun Byeol.
I was about to tell you beforehand,
but I couldn't reach you.
You wouldn't answer
my calls, texts, or e-mails...
You don't have to explain.
Or apologize.
We're strangers now anyway.
Strangers?
What are you talking about?
You left me when I was
at the lowest point in my life.
I don't want you to say hi
even if you see me again.
Eun Byeol!
Oh, my. Ms. Cheon,
you didn't go on a trip?
Or did you get back early?
Sang A, my heart is racing.
Why am I suddenly so excited?
Hera Palace has been quiet lately,
but I predict a storm coming.
Oh Yoon Hee!
Where are you?
Come out, Oh Yoon Hee!
What's the matter?
Explain what happened.
Why are you here?
Why did you have to move back here?
Do you have nowhere else to go?
Are you a stalker?
You talk like I'm not allowed here.
I used to live here.
And I was so happy
when I first moved in here.
That's why I came back.
Did you forget
who died in the penthouse?
You should be having nightmares
every night.
And you want to live here?
Many neighbors still remember how
you were cuffed and arrested here.
- To them, you're still...
- You too...
still live here.
That gave me the courage.
What?
You're making a scene at my place.
Go somewhere else
if you need to talk.
No.
Here is good.
I don't care whether you two
got married for real or not.
But you can't live here.
Why is that?
Your daughter, Eun Byeol,
lives here.
Don't you care if she gets hurt?
Do you call yourself her dad?
I moved here
because I care about her.
You cut off all communication
between me and her.
So what else could I do?
I'm going to live close to her
so I can at least run into her.
We may be divorced,
but I want to stay close
to Eun Byeol.
Oh, my. He is so manly.
He's so charismatic.
What right do you have
to meet Eun Byeol?
Eun Byeol doesn't want a dad either!
Why are you so scared?
You have everything you want.
The Director position
that you've wanted,
the man you want,
and Eun Byeol too.
You can live your life
as you've been doing.
A happy life with Joo Dan Tae.
I'm going to live a happy life too,
with Yoon Hee.
I'm thankful for you, actually.
My life has changed so much
since our divorce.
Don't you try to act cool.
The home that you just happen
to move into...
just in time for my engagement...
is right in my building?
If you're doing this because you
still have feelings, don't.
There's no way I'll go back to you.
Don't insult my husband.
He's not your man anymore.
You're the one
who's insulting yourself!
Everyone in Hera Palace...
knows that your husband and I
were married.
And everyone knows that Chairman Joo
and you had an affair.
But you don't care about that.
You still live here just fine.
Why do you look so anxious?
I feel bad for you.
Let's both be happy
with our respective families.
You care for yours, I care for mine.
Can you leave now?
We have to rush if we want
all of our things here by lunch.
Is this yours?
Be careful. You might lose it.
Oh Yoon Hee totally won this round.
Oh Yoon Hee!
Why is she back?
What has she been doing?
(Cheong A Medical Center)
Please sing a long note.
Good. Please sing
five short notes this time.
Good.
I feel out of breath
when I sing high notes these days.
I feel something in my throat too.
It's nothing, right?
You need to cancel
your concerts immediately.
Sorry?
You have serious vocal cord nodules.
I see a lump
that doesn't look good either.
If it gets worse from here,
you might need to get surgery.
A surgery? Why me?
No way.
If you leave it be,
you might not have your voice back.
You must cancel this performance...
and get some rest.
There's no way I can cancel it.
I've already paid
the rental fees to the venue,
and signed with the orchestra
for the concert.
I can't cancel it.
I have to get on stage.
You may never sing again.
Are you okay with that?
We got double the snacks today.
Can you eat this all?
Absolutely. I was starving.
Yoo Jenny!
Make it feel like I'm eating.
You have to be more real.
Is it a talent of yours to make food
look so unappetizing?
Don't you hear me? Open wide!
Look at all those greasy food.
Think of how much trans fat
she's consuming.
That's disgusting!
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
Don't be so ruthless.
Seems like she's not feeling well.
As promised, I'll take it that you
won't come to my mom's concert.
Why? I did everything
you told me to!
I ate everything I was told to!
I promised that I'll go with my mom.
Please let me go, Eun Byeol.
When were you ever our friends?
You have another friend.
Do you still keep in touch with her?
No, I haven't been
in touch with her since then.
Trust me on this.
Come up with a good excuse
to tell your mom why you can't go.
Let's go.
Sir, there's a guest.
What did you just say?
I'd like to be back in Hera Club.
You've become quite shameless
since the last time I saw you.
Your move-in hasn't even been
confirmed yet,
and you're asking to join Hera Club?
Don't you think it's setting
a bad example for the kids...
for a divorced couple to live...
in the same building?
That's what Seo Jin said too.
Did you two meet?
I worked to my bones
to succeed in the US,
and as long as I'm in Korea,
doesn't it make sense for me
to want to move...
into Korea's best condo?
The board is planning on
rejecting your move.
Moving out may be easy,
but moving in isn't.
That's how Hera Palace works.
You don't like me being
around Seo Jin?
Why?
You feel scared because you're
only engaged?
Or is there another reason?
You're not the same
Ha Yoon Chul of old.
You can't think straight now that
you've experienced being rich.
People change after all.
(JohnBio's promise to you)
That's right. I forgot to give you
my business card.
You can just call me "Mr. Ha"
next time we meet.
Don't speak casually to me...
as if we're close or something.
Mr. Ha.
If that's what you want,
I'll call you "Mr. Ha."
If you want to move into Hera Palace
that badly,
make a donation.
How much?
Two million dollars?
10 million?
If you are willing to donate
that much,
I'll consider it.
(Director Cheon Seo Jin)
("It's Time Soprano Cheon Seo Jin
Forfeits the Crown")
(Vocal cord nodules form
straining or overusing the voice.)
Those rats.
They wrote about it already?
No. It's too risky.
Do as I say.
It isn't impossible.
It's just that
the public never found out.
Still.
No one who made a debut.
Find an amateur.
She can't be too young or too old.
She must be as close to my age
as possible.
We don't have time.
We have one week.
This concert must be perfect...
no matter what.
(Dan Tae)
What? I'm about to leave.
Now?
I know.
Sorry, I'm late.
We just got here ourselves.
The traffic is terrible, isn't it?
Sometimes, there's traffic
even with the elevator.
Can we decide among ourselves
as the board...
to refuse to permit
Unit 4502 from moving in?
Oh dear. You must not have heard.
It has been decided already.
What do you mean?
JohnBIO...
Your previous husband. Your ex.
He donated five million dollars
to Hera Palace.
So there's no need for us to vote.
Chairman Joo, why did you create
that silly provision?
According to the rules of donations,
they've automatically been approved.
What happened?
You didn't tell me anything.
Hello!
Welcome.
You're all here.
It's an honor to be invited
to join Hera Club.
- Come and sit.
- Please sit.
Sit. Sit.
There's no need
for formal introductions, right?
I'm happy to move into Hera Palace.
Hey.
Thanks for welcoming us.
Yoon Hee.
You look so good.
And guess what?
Kyu Jin's an assemblyman now.
I heard. You've gone so high
since I saw you last.
And you look great.
Sang A. I hope I'll be seeing
a lot of you as well.
Welcome back.
Come over for dinner
this weekend, okay?
I'll bring fruits and dessert.
What did Yoon Hee like again?
You know, let's not do this.
Mr. Ha, you and your wife
should rejoin Hera Club.
Residents of the same district
should be close to each other.
I agree. We've been too distant
ever since we lost Su Ryeon.
Why don't we vote on it
while we're all here?
I'm for it.
Definitely.
What are you trying to do?
Hera Club?
Have you lost your mind?
Since when were we friendly
with Oh Yoon Hee?
Don't you know who she is?
What?
You'll give us JohnBIO's
unlisted stock?
- Yes.
- To us?
Do you mean it?
I was dividing them up
with my hardworking employees,
and I remembered your two families.
We used to be like family,
weren't we?
Sexual enhancers will always
be steady sellers...
as long as human beings exist.
Of course, we're interested.
Then may I ask for a favor?
Of course. I'm in.
Anything you want. Anything.
I don't know
what they're giving you,
but I'm against it.
Hera Club has a reputation.
How could a woman like Yoon Hee...
Watch how you talk about my woman.
The whole world knows
that Yoon Hee is a murderer.
Did you see her kill her?
Actually,
don't you all owe her an apology?
You accused an innocent woman
of murder and didn't help her.
But she didn't resent you.
She was understanding
and patient.
Do you know how much
my heart broke seeing that?
I'm almost moved to tears.
We're all making a new start.
Let's not bring up the past
to hurt each other.
You can say whatever you want to me,
but I won't let you hurt my woman.
That's enough. I'm fine.
You're making me uncomfortable.
Why are you uncomfortable, honey?
You can be confident.
I thought Chairman Joo
also acknowledged...
that Ms. Yang killed Su Ryeon.
Fine.
Then I'll leave Hera Club.
Problem solved.
You're not leaving. Why should you?
Let go of me!
Ms. Cheon. Ms. Cheon?
Chairman Joo.
Anyway, Mr. Ha.
You're a really good speaker.
You sound like a lawyer.
I was so moved.
Dr. Ha. Were you always
this manly?
You seem completely different.
Why are you so upset?
You know this won't solve anything.
How could I not be upset?
Didn't you hear Yoon Chul?
Since when was he
so thoughtful of his wife?
"My wife"?
What's this?
Are you angry...
that your loser ex-husband
became successful?
Or are you uncomfortable...
that Oh Yoon Hee, whom you despise,
made a grand comeback?
Or both?
You just disgraced me
with your actions.
"Cheon Seo Jin still has feelings
for Ha Yoon Chul."
"She regrets getting engaged
to Joo Dan Tae."
"She's still jealous of Oh Yoon Hee"
Those big mouths will talk about it
every single day.
Are you happy
now that you humiliated me?
What do you mean?
Why would I regret it?
I've lost all interest in
Yoon Chul long ago.
You realize we keep fighting
ever since we got engaged.
Who would this please the most?
Oh Yoon Hee is more dangerous
than Ha Yoon Chul.
We need to know why she's back here.
It's probably because of us.
There's one principle I always
stick to in business.
The more dangerous they are,
the closer I keep them.
That way, I know what they're after.
All that Ha Yoon Chul has is wealth.
I don't know how he became
such a success,
but he can't stay up there for long.
He offered a donation,
so I accepted it.
I'll just use him as I see fit.
If you get upset and attack,
you'll only show them
that you're anxious.
Sorry.
I've been irritable
because of the concert.
Look at yourself.
You are an amazing woman.
Oh Yoon Hee can't even compare.
She has already hit bottom.
So you should remain dignified
as you deal with her. Okay?
I don't know what I'm so afraid of.
Since Oh Yoon Hee came back,
everything's been a mess.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Why did you drink so much?
Don't do that again next time.
I'll break my back while carrying
another woman's husband.
Gosh. I'm exhausted.
Why is he so heavy?
Is he made of stone? Gosh, my back.
Wait a second. I'll get you
something cold to drink.
What do you want to drink?
Anything is fine. Gosh, my back.
Honey.
Dr. Ha gave me something great.
It's his latest product.
It's supposed to be amazing.
Be prepared.
Thank you so much.
What are you talking about?
Your honey is over there...
Is orange juice fine?
What? Orange juice sounds perfect.
If possible, with naked...
I mean, with crushed ice.
Give me just a second here.
Orange slushie coming up.
It's done.
Oh, my. He's taking off his clothes.
- My goodness.
- He'll catch a cold.
I can't believe him.
What are you doing?
This is embarrassing.
Jenny must be waiting. I have to go.
Why don't you drink this first?
Keep it for later.
What's with her?
You must be tired.
Moving is exhausting.
Do you like the place?
Yes, I love it. Thank you so much.
We managed to get into Hera Club
as we had planned.
With our wedding photos
on the wall and everything,
it feels like
we're married for real.
I wouldn't have made it here alone.
I could come back here
thanks to you.
Cheon Seo Jin and Joo Dan Tae...
will do everything it takes
to kick us out of here.
If I was afraid of that,
I wouldn't have come back here
in the first place.
Don't worry.
They won't mess with you again.
I'll protect you.
Remember?
I'm your business partner
and husband.
You're cheeky.
Don't ever betray me again.
If you do, you're dead meat.
Never.
Oh, what about Ro Na? Not yet?
No.
I'm sure I can see her
again someday.
When I deserve to see her.
(Cheong A Arts High School)
Next.
Not this either. Next.
No. Not this. Next.
Next.
She's singing flat. Next.
No, not this! Turn it off right now.
The audience has listened
to me singing all their lives.
They would notice the slightest
change in the way I breathe.
None of these singers are
good enough to fool them.
The broker introduced
about 10 singers,
and you've listened to all of them.
How about we cancel the concert
before it's too late?
No way.
There are people
waiting for me to crumble.
Are you telling me
to make myself their prey?
They'll be excited and thrilled,
gossiping and laughing.
"Cheon Seo Jin steps down
as a prima donna after 20 years,"
"finally giving up her crown."
Actually, there was one singer
who sounded just like you,
but she suddenly announced that
she couldn't take the job anymore.
She refused a teaching position
at Cheong A Arts High School?
Let me hear it.
(Resume, Park Young Ran)
This is it.
She sings every note in tune.
And she never runs out of breath.
- Who is she?
- She's in her late 30s.
She teaches kids in Ulsan
at the moment.
She hasn't debuted...
and went to a college
in a smaller city?
Hire her.
Bring her in front of me
whatever it takes.
Get in touch with her right now.
Welcome. Nice to meet you.
Don't look back.
What's your name?
It's Park Young Ran.
I've always been your huge fan.
It's such an honor
to meet you in person.
I really enjoyed
listening to your demo.
You do have an amazing voice.
I have a long way to go.
Hearing that compliment
from my idol,
I don't know what to say.
Why did you turn down
a teaching position...
at Cheong A Arts High School?
Well...
My father recently
had surgery...
and is not feeling so well.
So I thought it'd be impossible
for me to work in Seoul.
He needs me by his side now.
If that's what it's about,
I could help you.
I can see to it that...
your father is treated...
at Cheong A Medical Center
by our best staff.
Of course,
he will have caregivers
around the clock.
You won't have much to do.
Pardon?
On the condition that...
you do me a little favor.
I'm going to talk
about something very important.
No one can know about it, ever.
Can you promise?
This will be...
the most important
opportunity in your life.
I promise.
I won't tell anyone.
First, sign
a non-disclosure agreement.
The opening song will be
"Una Voce Poco Fa".
Master the song completely...
and send me over a demo.
The most important thing is that...
we're in perfect sync.
("Una Voce Poco Fa" demo,
Park Young Ran)
No mistakes are allowed.
You must sing
exactly like you practiced.
Keep that in mind.
Seo Jin.
It's your 20th-anniversary concert
tomorrow, right?
Congratulations.
Yes. Thank you.
Whether you mean it or not.
- Honey, you must be hungry.
- I am.
I'll make you something nice.
- Put that down. It's heavy.
- Okay.
Oh, I made your favorite,
cheonggukjang.
- Really?
- Yes.
You're the best.
I'm happy that you like my cooking.
Goodness, what did I do
to deserve you?
Well? Wasn't that quite natural?
Are you serious?
Who said you could do
things like that?
I couldn't help it. That's all.
I must've rehearsed too much
because it's an important concert.
Should we call it a day?
What happened? Your rehearsals
were always like the real thing.
Can you perform at the concert?
It's not my first time.
I'll rest a little
in the dressing room.
I'll check the stage and go.
Please do your best today.
While you're singing on stage,
Park Young Ran will be singing
in this secret area.
(Concert stage)
(Park Young Ran)
I just need this concert to go well.
Once my vocal cord nodules go away,
I can sing again
as I used to. Then...
nothing will go wrong.
(Soprano Cheon Seo Jin's
20th Anniversary Concert)
We should've
gotten her a bigger one.
- This is enough.
- Really?
Suction.
Again.
Make some noise.
Again. Try a loud noise.
Is there some kind of problem?
I think it's too hard.
At this point,
the vocal cords aren't moving.
She wants to try one more time.
We're going to try again.
Make some noise.
Again.
Brava!
How could it be?
It was a perfect high F.
You were the best ever.
I got chills.
Why didn't you tell me
you were raising the finale?
You've exceeded your prime.
What happened?
You didn't say
you'd raise it to a high F.
It's hard enough to hit it
after a break.
It's nearly impossible to hit it
in one breath.
Did you intentionally hold back
what you could do?
There must be a reason why
you tried to deceive my ears.
Hey, you.
Who are you?
How...
How are you...
Finally, I get to say hi.
I hope we get along
from now on, Seo Jin.
(The Penthouse 2)
Yoon Hee!
This is just the beginning.
Just you wait.
Track them down if
they try to get in my way!
The best voice and Yoon Chul
were both mine...
initially.
Now it feels real
that I'm back in Hera Club.
How dare you come to our school?
Your daughter
is included in my plan.
Put someone on Seo Jin too.
I'm getting nervous.
Yoon Hee...
I'm going to kill you.