[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 2]
[Sun Bin Yu]
Lu Jing, come, come. Come over here.
I wanted to ask you something.
What is it?
Can you do your buddy a favour?
Fire away.
Actually it's not a big deal.
I just need you to guide my friend
with Beautiful Soul,
it's only for a month.
I'm going for Sadhana tomorrow.
Who is that?
My friend.
A girl.
She's very gentle, well-behaved
-and really cute.
-She's a noob?
[Lu Jing, you have second sight now.]
Newbies have to go through a stage
where they die in the game easily.
But my friend can pick up really fast.
I mean it.
Reward?
Iron Man limited edition
garage kit figure.
Deal.
Great. I'll ask her to add you on WeChat.
Don't you change your mind.
I didn't know you'd call so soon.
[Orange, I've set it up for you.
[I'll recommend a friend to you
on WeChat.]
[My friend is amazing at the game.]
[Rest assured and stick with him.]
Alright, I got it.
[Happy Bootlicker, Lu Jing]
Happy Bootlicker, Lu Jing.
I can totally tell he's not a decent guy.
[Sun Bin Yu]
[Orange,]
have you added my friend?
No.
God knows what kind of person
you've introduced me to.
[What kind of person?]
Your friend.
Happy Bootlicker?
[Is he some sort of desperate guy?]
What nonsense are you talking about?
Hold on.
[Happy Bootlicker, Lu Jing]
Since when did he change it?
This brat only causes me trouble.
[Orange]
Orange,
he's just an ordinary university student.
[He's a good student and well-behaved,]
[just add him already.]
Fine. Bye.
[Happy Bootlicker, Lu Jing]
Happy Bootlicker,
let's see what you're capable of.
[Friend Verification]
[Hi, I'm a friend of Taro.]
[Friend Verification Send]
[Happy Bootlicker, Lu Jing]
My trick worked like magic, didn't it?
No girls added you on WeChat, right?
This girl must be a warrior.
She had the guts to add
a 'Happy Bootlicker'?
Don't worry.
We can change it.
Let's change it to Royal Mad Man,
how about that?
The Dream of 1.3 Billion Girls.
Not good enough.
[Hi, I'm a friend of Taro.]
[Please teach me when you have time.]
[Thank you.]
[Don't worry about it.]
[What's your ID?]
[I'll add you tonight.]
Scroll it back.
Play the first video clip.
Why?
So adorable.
She's indeed the girl I like.
You could tell from her laughter?
I can recognise Liang Chen's voice
no matter what it turns into.
[Beautiful Soul]
[You Have Me sent you a friend request]
You Have Me?
That should be a coincidence.
[YY room number is]
[1352687505.]
[Come on in.]
What is YY?
Do I have to download it?
[YY Voice Desktop Version]
Jing,
the food delivery is here.
Thanks.
Don't touch my Liang Chen
with your nasty hands.
[You Have Me]
Yours?
Does she even know you?
Does she even know your name?
Your Liang Chen?
Good evening,
my babies.
You didn't even leave one for me.
You're so mean!
Please throw it away.
I'm setting off fireworks.
Lu Jing, care to join?
No.
What are you doing?
Guiding a girl.
You're guiding a girl?
[Are you not done yet?]
[Soon.]
[I am registering an account.]
[Hi, nice to meet you.]
[She doesn't even have a YY account.]
[Could I have met a deep-rooted noob?]
Lu Jing, I didn't know
that you'd also end up like this.
I guess he won't be able
to maintain his record.
What the heck were they talking about?
But they do make sense.
But I have my ego too.
[Lu Jing,]
as a person who went through this,
I'm telling you
[Herman's Room]
this girl will definitely
be your nightmare.
What do you mean?
You have no idea.
Last time, I guided a junior,
then my data dropped like flies.
That's because you're bad at guiding.
Exactly. You were terrible at guiding.
How could you blame that girl?
You're humiliating me.
If you were to guide a female rookie,
your data might fall
just like a meteor.
Even if I'm guiding a real noob,
I still won't be affected.
Fine. Let's bet.
If you lose today,
you have to promise us something.
I won't do anything illegal.
Don't worry.
We will abide by the code of conduct
for undergraduates.
So what will it be?
Will you take the bet?
Fine.
I won't lose anyway.
[Baidu]
What to do
if I'm terrible at Beautiful Soul?
[Beautiful Soul Test Forum]
[Uninstall it right away
for a better world.]
No way, no way.
I'm not someone who gives up easily.
[Tell yourself that you're a robot,
you're just too good.]
That's nonsense.
[People can't recognise you anyway.]
[Check out YY voice changer.]
Sounds like a good idea.
Voice changer?
If I'm terrible at it,
they won't know who I am.
Cute female voice,
gentle female voice,
domineering female voice,
prince charming voice?
There are so many to choose from.
[Herman's Room]
She's entered the room.
Lu Jing hardly guides any girl.
I wonder if she has a cute voice.
[Hello, I've entered the room.]
Jing, will you date me?
I have a Lolita's voice.
So do I.
Bad guy.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
[Yes, I can.]
This person has a pretty good voice.
I can see you. I'll get you in there.
[Click confirm.]
Is this how you got here?
Bullets have no eyes.
I was afraid of getting hurt.
Put on the bulletproof vest.
It's safer that way.
This is hideous.
I won't wear it.
I want to look pretty even if I die.
Come on in, come on in.
Hurry up.
What is wrong with you?
There's a robot. I'm afraid.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
No, no! When there are many robots,
I'd die easily.
How quickly?
I restarted the game six times
within half an hour.
So you're quite persistent, huh?
What should we do now?
Our mission this time
is to find the robot's plan
for invading the earth.
I will storm out later.
Just follow me.
Okay.
Don't let me die.
Please.
Let's go.
[First mission accomplished.]
[Data has been received.]
[Next, please go to the attic]
[to continue searching
for confidential documents.]
There's a robot behind the cabinet.
Sorry.
Another one by the door.
What... What is going on?
Many robots will appear downstairs.
Watch closely.
Did you get a good look?
Did you get it?
Do you want to know my true feelings?
Fill me in.
I think
I'm blind.
Do you also think that you're deaf?
Blind and deaf.
How did you determine it?
Just listen to the sound.
You're amazing.
This is so ugly. Nope.
This gun is huge.
It might come in handy.
What is this?
Lu Jing, help!
[Lu Jing, help!]
How did you die?
Somehow I bumped into a robot.
[Overall Evaluation]
That was such a wrongful death.
I lost all the props that I found!
[They're all gone!]
Downwind.
Play it.
We'll present a song
for God Jing's lousy teammate.
[Downwind]
[When I composed this song,]
[I really didn't know
that it'd be presented to me.]
[Downwind]
It's okay.
Just get up
from where you fall.
Let's try it again.
This time, just stick with me.
I think
this round will end within three minutes.
Two minutes.
Thirty seconds.
You've gone overboard.
[Second mission accomplished.]
[Data has been sent.]
[Next, please escape from the pursuit.]
Let's jump.
Are we Superman?
Will you do it or I'll do it?
Will I die? If I land with my face,
won't I look horrible?
Don't hit me! I don't want to die!
This is amazing. We're still alive.
We wouldn't die.
I checked before jumping.
The suitcase is here too.
Let's go!
When can we get rid of these robots?
Soon. We'll storm out soon.
Take out the smoke bomb in your bag
-and throw it out.
-Okay.
Disrupt their vision.
Is this the one?
Don't throw it!
[Overall Evaluation]
Jing,
you're so cool.
Your own teammate blew you up!
We feel terribly sorry for you.
[Overall Evaluation]
[Failed]
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
[It's just a mission.]
Are you giving up on me?
Hello?
Where did he go?
Did it break down?
[Happy Bootlicker, Lu Jing]
[My internet was disconnected.]
Luckily he didn't run away
because of my terrible performance.
[Happy Bootlicker, Lu Jing]
[Since I've promised Taro,]
[I won't leave you before he gets back.]
Lu Jing,
who was the girl that you guided today?
She's a friend of my friend.
I don't know her.
Is she pretty?
It's not that I've met her.
There should be photos on her Moments,
I've never seen it.
Speaking of that,
why would she use the voice changer?
I know it now.
What else do you know?
Could she be a man?
A man weighing over a hundred kilograms.
Lu Jing,
you might've flirted with a man today.
Shut up.
[Lu Jing,]
who was the girl that you guided today?
She's a friend of my friend.
I don't know her.
Could she be a man?
A man weighing over a hundred kilograms.
[Only Moments from the past three days
will be displayed]
She doesn't even have any Moments.
Could she really
be a man with Lolita voice?
[Who is your friend?]
[Lu Jing]
[She's such a rookie.]
[She's a sister who's not related to me.]
[Guide her properly.]
[This game means a lot to her.]
What kind of place is this?
It doesn't even have any signal.
[I think I'll get hosting fees from you.]
[Lu Jing]
No signal is better.
We're here.
Come. Change it.
Change it. Hurry up.
Light.
Set up the light here.
Thank you.
Hurry up.
Actors and assistant director!
Rush the actors to put on makeup.
Hurry up.
[Guys,]
[I'm practising Sadhana in a mountain.]
[In the coming month,]
[just assume that I'm dead.]
Lu Jing.
You are...
My name is Qi Qi.
I am a third year student
from Foreign Languages Department.
Last year, we joined
the exchange students reception.
Does a Foreign Language major
take this course too?
Lu Jing.
What's the matter?
We're here to study.
Do you know that
if you keep imitating Lu Jing,
everyone will think
that you have a crush on him, not me?
Nonsense.
I'm obviously in love with you.
Why does this class
always have a good attendance?
Okay. Let's start our class.
Let's recap
what we learned last time.
[Ocean Deep Chaos National
Undergraduate Challenge in Big Data]
How was it?
Among these four demos,
two of them were composed
by famous producers,
another two were composed by newcomers.
They're all special on their own.
What's the matter?
Still not happy with it?
They're special on their own indeed,
but I can't decide yet now.
This time,
we really spared no effort
to find good songs for you.
But now, it's extremely difficult
to find a good song.
I know.
Mr Zhou, thanks for your hard work.
Then, I'll listen to them again.
If you have something to do, go ahead.
Sure.
Listen to them first.
I really think
that these songs are really good.
Think it over.
How did it go?
Anything suitable for the album?
They're not bad,
but I just don't feel anything.
What happened?
Will it get better
if you give it another try?
I'm not sure either.
What is going on?
If you keep staying in your comfort zone,
of course it's boring.
If you want a breakthrough,
you have to take the challenge.
Amazing.
As expected from our top student.
This is not something that an ordinary
people like me can understand.
This contest only accepts teams.
You know, don't you?
So?
I've signed you up too.
What?
You signed me up for Big Data Contest?
Why do you have confidence in me?
I have confidence in myself.
If you stick with me,
you're bound to make progress.
Where's Lu Jing?
Follow me.
[What time are we meeting tonight?]
[Teachers,]
[propagate the doctrine, impart knowledge
and resolve doubts.]
[Today, we've invited]
[Professor Chen Bei from the artificial
intelligence at Nanze University]
[to explain the current
cutting-edge results.]
Liu,
take me to Nanze University.
Okay.
Chen, why do you want to go
to Nanze University?
To find inspiration.
What are you doing?
Do you remember losing your bet last time?
Now it is time for you to pay the price.
Go!
There is never an end of taking revenge.
If you're a man, learn to let go.
No way.
Dream on it.
You wish.
Follow me.
-Let's go.
Come on.
Where on earth are you taking me to?
It's definitely
the Faculty of Music.
Let's go, let's go.
Chen, where exactly are you going?
It's right ahead of us,
the Faculty of Music.
Chen, there are so many people here.
Don't worry. Just be careful.
No one will notice us.
I remember
that when I was still a student,
I often felt the magic of music
brought by nature here.
Back then,
all my worries would disappear.
Chen,
you don't have
to make skipping class
sound so novel and sophisticated.
Nature and music are just so magical.
I feel like all the troubles
have gone away now.
Hello.
Hello, hello.
Hello, everyone.
We're the Fantastic Four
from Computing Science.
The guy standing beside us
is a top student
from Computing Science, Lu Jing.
All of you must be tired
from practising.
Next,
let us enjoy
his wonderful solo performance!
A round of applause!
Zhou Zhou,
didn't you say he's tone-deaf?
This melody is so familiar.
Symphony No. 35 in D major.
When I was composing 'You Have Me',
it was my inspiration.
It sounds really nice.
Chen, it's this way.
[Concert Hall]