[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 7]
[Supreme Master]
What do you mean?
[What do you mean?]
[I've analysed the cloud patterns]
[over the past few hours,]
[and ran a storm simulation.]
[Shanghai has an 83 percent chance]
[of storm next week.]
Can't we just see the weather forecast?
[So what?]
[Be careful when you come back.]
[I won't be here till next week.]
[I'll be back tomorrow.]
Ke Ke, we'll go back tomorrow.
But our PR event tomorrow
won't end till noon.
We'll go back when it's over.
That's right.
Okay.
Did Liang Chen say anything
today, Zhu Guang?
She didn't say anything to me.
She asked about your birthday.
When was it?
When I returned to collect
your mobile phone.
Act Three, Scene Four, Take 31.
[Can't Hide From Love]
Okay, ready.
Action!
Who do you think you are?
Cut!
For god's sake.
He flew away from the scene
before Ms Ma even lifted her leg.
Director He.
Is this the passionate scene
you were talking about?
Was it passionate enough?
Was it exciting?
Let's end this quickly.
Remove the wire.
We'll do it the easy way.
-Are you sure?
-Yes.
Stop wasting my time and do it now.
Okay then. Remove the wire!
Give me another chance, sir.
Nope, remove the wire.
-You did well.
-Well done.
Hurry and remove it.
Be careful.
I'll be fine.
You did well, Ms Ma.
Thank you, Ms Ma.
Let's put our hearts into this
and do it in one take.
[Can't Hide From Love]
Act Three, Scene Four, Take 32.
Who do you think you are?
Nice!
Change the scene!
Ask them to get ready
once they reach the set.
-Yes.
-Dinner at home.
Okay, Director.
Why is Mr Sun still lying here?
He got too deep into character.
He!
High-five!
Save, save...
Director!
What's the point of living
if life isn't filled
with the bliss of joy
and the ecstasy of pain?
Lu Jing?
Lu Jing!
Got it?
I'm hungry.
Can we get some crayfish?
How aloof.
Zhou Zhou.
Crayfish.
-Sure!
Bring the food over!
The crayfish is here!
It's here!
Come!
Time to have crayfish with cola!
Come on.
How great it would be
if there's a crayfish peeling service.
Where's the fun
in letting others peel for you?
[Lucky Spicy Crayfish]
Why is there such a long queue?
That's right.
We've been waiting
for one and a half hour.
Lu Jing?
What a small world.
I'm so hungry.
Don't wait for me.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Coming through.
Excuse me.
I'm looking for someone!
What a coincidence, Lu Jing!
You're here to eat as well?
What are you looking at?
Eat.
Please ignore me.
You're too slow.
What do you mean, I'm slow?
You are slow.
Let's see who's slower.
Sure.
[Let the fireworks begin!]
[Where are you?]
[Where are you, man?]
[There's a crayfish here
in need of your help.]
[I'm having crayfish with my friends.]
[Are you home?]
[Yes.]
[Give me ten minutes.]
What's wrong, Lu Jing?
Stop playing with your phone
and be serious.
I concede.
What did you say?
I said I concede.
You're better at peeling crayfish.
Takeaway, Mr Proprietor!
Right away!
I'll have these two plates to go.
And two more bowls for them.
Sure!
What do you mean?
Thanks for your peeled crayfish.
Feel free to eat.
This meal's on me.
Take it as a warm up.
Mr Proprietor!
Three more bowls.
-Here's your takeaway.
-Thanks.
Three bowls, coming up.
I'm leaving now.
-Goodbye.
[Lucky Spicy Crayfish]
[Friends List]
[Herman's Room]
I'm here.
What shall we play today?
Wait.
What is this?
Do you like it?
Yes!
Are you giving it to me?
No.
I'm selling it.
For one yuan.
[WeChat Pay]
[Thousand Years Box Spirit]
[Red Packet from
Thousand Years Box Spirit]
[Redeemed Successfully]
Do you know the place?
Should I repeat the rules?
You take the enemy, I take the items.
Smart girl.
Lu Jing!
What are you squatting there for?
Digging for treasure?
I'm being careful.
You can pick them up
with your head held high.
Why be scared when I'm here?
I like this vibe.
You're so handsome.
Can you inform me before you throw it?
Okay.
Not bad! You did well.
-It's all yours.
-Hug me tight.
Let's go!
Once we get out,
the world will be ours.
Charge!
There's a bazooka there.
[Fail]
Didn't you say the world
would be ours?
I was balancing the straits.
Liar!
I saw your live streams.
This isn't the first time
you threw a game.
Even a pro like me would throw
a game for your sake.
What are you complaining about?
Are you saying I'm too weak?
I might've eaten too much
crayfish tonight.
Was it delicious?
Not bad.
Where did you eat?
Nanyang University, East Gate.
I can treat you to a meal
when you're free.
We'll talk about it later.
Crayfish is a hassle to eat.
It's getting late now. Do get some rest.
Goodnight.
[Herman's Room]
Leave me alone.
Action!
Let's go.
What do you want?
Who is she?
Is she from our school?
Which year is she in?
How did you meet her?
Is there a picture?
Is she beautiful?
What are you talking about?
You left without finishing the crayfish.
What could be more enticing than that?
It couldn't be programming.
It could only be girls.
We promised to stay single together,
but you secretly hooked up with a girl?
Come on.
Teach us how to get a girlfriend.
You think too much.
The author Mark Twain once said,
"Candor is the product of
honesty and bravery."
Why so poetic?
I think we need to force the
truth out of him.
That's right.
If I lied,
may the head of department himself
set the exam paper.
Don't be so cruel.
We're innocent.
[I can treat you to a meal]
[when you're free.]
[We'll talk about it later.]
[Multiple Exposure, Liang Chen]
Found it.
Nanze University.
Dormitory A,
8A-417.
Lu Jing.
[Ding Jia Yun]
Hello, Jia Yun?
Boss.
Ms Lan Yao invites you to dinner.
Tell her I'm occupied.
You wouldn't say that if it were
Ms Liang who invited you.
What's with her?
It's so obvious to me.
Why didn't she know?
Perhaps she refused to know.
Here.
Fresh off the grill.
Cola with barbeque.
What a nice day!
We should have barbeque parties every day!
Dream on!
Don't you know we're tight on expenses?
I'm buying you this meal
to mend your broken back.
Really?
Thanks, Director.
The pork knuckles are ready.
Do help yourselves.
Okay!
Coming.
Here's a pork knuckle for you.
Nice work today, kid.
This is your reward.
Thanks, Director!
It's the least I can do as an actor.
I never thought
I would be so compatible with Ms Ma.
By the way,
where's Ms Ma?
Why isn't she here?
Ms Ma sprained her foot today.
She must be in her room now.
Let her have some rest.
Ms Ma?
Ms Ma, are you in there?
It's me, Sun Bin Yu.
Ms Ma?
There you are, Ms Ma.
What is it?
Here.
You may be missing out on the party
due to your foot,
but we didn't forget about you.
So I came here to send our regards.
I'm fine, thank you.
No, Ms Ma! Don't close the door!
Eat it while it's hot.
It's good for your foot.
No, thank you.
Ke Ke.
Why did you pack so many dresses for me?
I'm not going on a vacation.
What if you meet a hot guy in Guangzhou?
Are hot guys more important
than writing songs?
Are relationships
more fulfilling than work?
Stop pretending.
You think I don't know you?
If you were in a relationship,
you'd have so much inspiration
that songs would practically pour
out of you.
Who could I possibly date?
A pair of pants.
A piece of hoodie.
Five pairs of socks.
A pair of underwear.
I'm done.
Your books?
Your documents?
Entry form, charger and data cables.
Did you bring them?
What? I can't hear you.
Why don't you do it for me?
Look how clumsy you are.
[Undergraduate Challenge in Big Data,
Entry Form]
Lu Jing!
Can't you get a girlfriend
and stop focusing on me?
I wish I could.
This way please.
Please wait for a moment.
Thank you.
Liang Chen.
Choose a piece for me.
I'm giving it away.
[Heritage Series]
I'm not really good at this.
Who are you giving it to?
My mother.
Her birthday is on November 7.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
-Here.
-Okay.
The pieces are here.
What does Mrs Lu usually like?
There's a gold one inlaid with jade,
one that's pure gold,
and a small ornament.
They're all beautiful.
I really don't know.
Please choose one for me.
I think jade complements Mrs Lu's look,
and it's beneficial to health.
Okay.
I'll take this one.
Sure.
Thank you so much.
My mother will be pleased
with the present.
You're welcome.
You two will walk
briskly, like this.
And angrily.
-We'll shoot the scene here, okay?
-Okay.
That's it. Hurry!
I told you, Xiao Qi!
There's nothing between us.
Why are you so petty?
Yes, I'm petty when it comes to love.
But at least I know what I want.
Mr Sun.
I don't remember you having
any PR events today.
What are you doing?
I'm thinking.
I'm thinking when I would
have the chance to collaborate
with Shan Shan
on a comedy.
Love themed, of course.
Do you want to remake
"One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest"
with Shan Shan?
What do you mean?
I'm a versatile actor.
My only restriction
is my handsome face.
Then why do you want to collaborate
with Shan Shan?
You two don't seem compatible.
Because
she's my "hard disk goddess."
Ten terabytes.
You're awake, Ms Ma.
No, I...
I can explain, Ms Ma!
[Taro's Drive]
I'm right.
I have another nine terabytes back home.
Wait for me!
We're only going for two days.
Why carry such a big suitcase
for five pairs of socks?
You don't know what it's like
to a man of refinement.
Hello?
[Hello.]
[Are you the passenger]
[of flight DA1718 to Guangzhou?]
Yes, I am.
[I'm sorry.]
[There's only one seat left]
[in the economy cabin.]
[We can upgrade]
[one of your seats to first class.]
[Which one of you will take the upgrade?]
Lu Jing, have you been in
a first class cabin?
What time is the flight, Ke Ke?
7:50.
In the past, at this time of year,
my new album would've begun selling.
But this year,
there's nothing.
Don't pressure yourself.
I'm going over, Chen.
[I'll be busy in the morning.]
[Hit me up tonight if you want]
[to play Beautiful Soul.]
Was that Liang Chen?
Yes.
But don't tell anyone.
[Guess who I saw
in the first class cabin?]
Are my earphones with you?
Thank you.
Why are you standing there?
I...
Are my earphones here?
[I'll be busy in the morning.]
[I'll be busy during the morning.]
[Hit me up tonight if you want]
[to play Beautiful Soul.]
[to pay Beautiful Soul.]
I'll look for it.
[I'm on a business trip.]
[I'm not free.]
[Where?]
[Guangzhou.]
[Okay.]
Who are you texting?
My mother.
I'm selecting some dresses for her.
This looks nice.
[Flight mode on]
Your earphones.
[1]
Hello, sir.
Please return to your seat, thank you.
-Little Box?
-[Ladies and gentlemen.]
[Our plane will be taking off soon.]
[The cabin crew]
[will begin their security check.]
[Please fasten your seat belts]
[and put up the trays.]
[Keep the window shades open.]
[Thank you for your cooperation.]
How could it be?
What are you looking at?
Nothing.