[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 8]
-Little Box?
-[Ladies and gentlemen.]
[Our plane will take off soon.]
It can't be.
-Sir, your cake.
-Thank you very much.
You're welcome.
Sun.
He.
Whose birthday is it?
Ms Ma has finished her shooting.
Our group is not financially well off.
There's not even a
cake for her wrapping up.
[Congrats on Wrapping Up]
I thought I could celebrate it with her.
Trying to impress her?
I'll join you after washing my face.
Wait!
It would be better if you don't show up.
There's not enough cake.
Is that how you talk to the director?
Ms Ma, congratulations for wrapping up.
Ms Ma?
Hello, ma'am.
Where is the guest living here?
Checked out.
She's checked out?
-Failed to meet her?
-Where's Ms Ma?
-She has left.
-Where did she go?
She has a tight schedule.
She has a variety show in Guangzhou.
She went to the airport as
soon as the shooting wrapped.
Be polite with the director from now on.
[Pearl River City]
We just landed.
Everything is fine.
Thank you.
[1]
[Never mind.]
Is it that person again?
Which one?
The one you reported your Shanghai
itinerary to.
No.
Keep your mouth shut.
It's almost time.
Go and confirm the venue
for tomorrow's birthday party.
[Liang Chen's Birthday Party
in Guangzhou]
This ticketing website is really annoying.
It is still reminding me
to attend Liang Chen's birthday party.
Doesn't it know that
I have a competition tomorrow?
If you are lucky,
and the order of draw
lots is towards the front,
you should be able to
make it for the event.
Jing, I rely on you then.
Can you show me your participant pass?
Our birthday party is
going to be held here?
Yes.
What is this event?
It seems quite interesting.
This one...
It looks like some kind
of computer contest.
I'm not so sure either.
[Talk Show Life Through The Mirror]
Let's go.
Hello, try for free and get prizes,
Come in and have a look.
[Wooden House BBQ]
What is it?
Hello, our shop is organizing an event.
By finishing the given
barbecue within specified time,
there will be gifts.
You can take a look.
Really?
-Yes.
-Eat for free?
Yes.
[Little Box might like it.]
Can you do it?
Don't underestimate me.
If I rank second as a freeloader,
no one dares to be the first.
You are right.
Come, let's eat!
[Cheers Guangzhou]
Roasted durians?
Can't you change to some other food?
I'm sorry, the rest of our
food has been given away.
Only roasted durians are left.
We have Coca-Cola here.
You can help yourself if it is not enough.
I refuse to take it.
I'm off.
If we can't finish all, just go Dutch.
Then eat.
Jing, you start first.
You first.
You're welcome.
Lu Jing.
The taste of Coke combined with durian,
it's peerless.
Lu Jing, are you a human?
I will vomit if I take one more bite.
Look at me.
As soon as I see durian I'll...
Excuse...
Chen, you entered the wrong place.
You go first.
Long time no see, Shan Shan.
It's been a long time.
How are you doing?
Not bad.
Filming for a show?
Do you have time tonight?
Shall we have a meal together?
Shan Shan.
The studio is almost ready.
You have to change your outfit soon.
I need to go.
I can't make it today.
Perhaps another day.
Shan Shan,
since you know Liang Chen,
can you help me
get her signature?
I barely know her.
[Dear audience,]
[let's give a big round of applause]
[and welcome our goddess of comedy,]
[Lady Ma!]
Your baby is here!
Baby, I'm here too!
[Rendezvous with Shan Shan]
Keep jumping if
you're not clapping your hands.
Good.
No, I'm fine.
I can get up.
Okay, for the next three hours,
let us enjoy the next show.
[Rendezvous with Shan Shan]
-Is there water?
-Mistake!
A mistake.
Come on.
Thank you!
See you next time.
Do you really like it so much?
If you do,
go and beg them to give it to you.
You go.
No.
I don't need it after all.
The one who wants it should go.
Can you give me this?
I'm sorry.
You two failed
to complete the assigned task.
According to our regulations,
we can't give it away.
Pretty Miss.
I really like this doll.
Please give it to me.
Please, won't you?
Does it look like the Box Spirit?
Just because of that Box Spirit,
you forced me to eat so many
disgusting roasted durians?
Are you okay?
For the sake of The Box Spirit,
you used the honey trap?
Lu Jing,
there's something wrong with you.
What are you implying?
Lu Jing, you are in love.
You didn't even deny it.
Are you here to meet your online lover?
Thanks!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you!
Thank you.
Okay, thank you.
Thanks for being with us for three hours.
Coming up
is our last
lucky segment.
So what is the lucky segment?
The lucky segment tonight is
to invite an audience to the stage,
to give our princess Shan Shan
a princess-style carry
plus ten deep squats!
Ten!
Oh my gosh!
It's so cruel!
From now on,
all entrances are sealed.
It's too late to ask for a refund.
Our lighting technician,
please sway the lights!
Let's take a look at
everyone's gaze full of desire.
Who will be the unluckiest
yet fortunate one tonight?
Let's take a look.
Three, two, one!
Great! it's you!
No, no!
Go, go on!
Come on, it is hard to be the lucky one.
Go, go, go!
I wouldn't exactly call that lucky.
Look at me, I'm so thin.
I can't take it.
Gosh.
It's so awkward.
Is no one willing to carry me?
That guy gave up on
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Am I not popular enough?
Are you all with your girlfriends?
Maybe they came with others' girlfriends.
Let me try!
Me!
The real warrior is over there.
Let's welcome him onto the stage!
Come, come.
Please stand in the middle, young man.
Hello, Ms Ma.
Young man, I think
you are a little thin too.
Thin? I'm masculine.
I have muscles too.
Ms Ma, feel it.
I just noticed too.
Young man, as her old partner,
Let me remind you gently.
Be careful not to sprain your back.
Don't worry, my back is strong.
Just try and you will find out.
Good!
It sounds like a duel!
A round of applause
and welcome his attempt to try it out.
Don't clap, you. Give a try, quick.
Okay. I'm about to carry you.
Let's begin.
Exert force.
Come on, keep going!
Come on!
Try again.
Come on, keep going!
Okay.
He needs to warm up.
Please applaud.
Are you ready?
Come.
Get ready.
Three, two, one.
How do you feel?
My back doesn't hurt at all.
Awesome, I like this fighting spirit.
Start squatting!
Squat now, young man.
This audience seems to love me very much.
Is the applause not loud enough?
One.
Two.
Three.
-Ke Ke.
-Four.
Is that Sun Bin Yu?
-Five.
-Isn't he on location shooting?
It can't be him.
-Six.
-Just a look-alike.
Impossible.
-Seven.
-His expression is eligible for a patent.
Seven.
Eight.
Nine.
The last one.
Come on!
That was tough. Good job, young man!
Alright. You may go down and take a rest.
Thanks.
Come.
Alright.
Looking at him walking away
with contentment.
It's getting late and
there are a lot of people.
The room is ready too.
It's time to say goodbye again.
Happy times are always short lived.
[Sun Bin Yu]
It's time to say goodbye.
The same time next Friday,
till we meet again in
Rendezvous with Shan Shan.
Good night!
[Orange]
Now he doesn't even
bother to answer my call.
Mr Sun.
Why are you here?
My friend gave me a ticket.
I came over since I'm free.
Ms Ma.
We meet again, what a coincidence !
Mr Sun, it's a hard day indeed.
Hard day? Not at all.
Besides, I was the lucky audience.
But...
The back of your pants has ripped.
When did that happen?
Such a big hole.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
-Why didn't I notice?
-Let's make a move.
-We're off.
-Don't go, you...
[Orange]
Hello, what's up?
[Where are you?]
I'm at a shoot.
[Why didn't you answer my call?]
What did you say?
The signal is not so good.
I can't hear properly.
Hello?
Speak louder!
Is the signal better now?
It's much better now.
Aren't you filming?
Why are you here alone?
Yes.
Our group is on location shooting here.
Location shooting?
You are the only one here.
They...
Forget it.
It's my fault, madam.
Our team hasn't finished shooting yet.
I sneaked out secretly.
I have to fly back in a while.
It's so hard to rush like this.
It's not hard at all.
This is for my artistic pursuit.
Is there anything else you pursue?
My current pursuit is...
to be at the airport
without taking a step.
Okay.
Orange, open the door.
Orange!
Open the door, Orange!
Women can be so heartless.
[Data Mining and Early Phase
Behavioural Analysis]
The room I choose
always has to be special.
Do you like it, Brother Jing?
[It looks more and more like you]
[It looks more and more like you.]
It's not similar at all.
[Use as wallpaper]
Show me the photo of Box Spirit.
Don't have it.
You haven't even seen her picture?
How old is she then?
I have no idea.
You can't be serious.
Are you crazy?
At least you should know her name, right?
I don't know.
What if she is a man?
That's why she uses a voice changer.
That's impossible,
you think too much.
Then tell me. Why is she
using a voice changer?
Whenever I see you smile happily,
you must be looking at your phone.
Is that so?
I smile happily when I watch TV too.
By the way,
does that person know your identity?
Are you going to tell him?
I haven't thought it through.
I'm not ready yet.
Has Box Spirit just sent you
a message?
I will help you find out.
It's He Ye.
I asked him to unpack a package for me.
Boring.
[Liang Chen's not-for-sale
complimentary album.]
[There's a signature too.]
[That's awesome.]
[Who gave you this?]
It's the gift from Box Spirit?
What's going on between you two?
[Data Intensive...]
[Application System Design...]
His major is E-sports.
He likes robots.
His hands-on ability should be good.
He is a hygienic guy.
I'm sure he's good in studies.
[Thank you.]
[You're welcome. Do you like it?]
[Not bad.]
Not bad?
[Not bad?]
[I already have this
complimentary album.]
[I already have this complimentary album.]
[Oh]
[Thanks anyway.]
[Thank you anyway.]
[You're welcome.]
How lame.
He already has it.
He had it?
He already had this
complimentary album earlier.
He must be my die-hard fan.
He must like me very, very much.
Shun.
Do you know
who can obtain a singer’s
internal complimentary album?
[Only three kinds of person
can have it.]
[The staff working with the singer,]
[people around them,]
[and the singer themselves.]
Thank you.
Liang Chen?
Little Box?
[Guangzhou Garden Hotel]
The Garden Hotel, Guangzhou?
He is in Guangzhou too?
[Liang Chen's Schedule]
A week ago,
Liang Chen appeared
in a TV program in Shanghai.
[Liang Chen's Schedule]
Liang Chen to attend
events in Guangzhou today.
[Are you in Guangzhou too?]
[Too?]
Too?
[I'm also in Guangzhou.]
[I'm in Guangzhou as well.]
[Are you here to attend
Liang Chen’s birthday party?]
[Are you here]
[for Liang Chen's birthday party?]
[Liang Chen's Schedule]
[Liang Chen just arrived
in Guangzhou today.]
[You happen to be in Guangzhou too.]
[You happen to be in Guangzhou.]
[When Liang Chen was
in Shanghai last time,]
[Last time when Liang Chen
was in Shanghai,]
[you were there too.]
[You also have her internal
complimentary album.]
[You have her internal
complimentary album too.]
[Who are you exactly?]
[Liang Chen just arrived
in Guangzhou today.]
[You happen to be in Guangzhou.]
[Last time when Liang
Chen was in Shanghai,]
[you were there too.]
[You also have her internal
complimentary album.]
[Who are you exactly?]
Why is your hand shaking
eating a cookie?
Shaking? Says who?
Buddy.
It is said that learning should
integrate both work and leisure.
You're losing your senses.
Let me revive them with moisturiser.
That's enough.
Back off.
Liu Liu Da Shun is so cute.
I really like him.
[Today I saw]
[Liu Liu Da Shun's live stream.]
[It's quite interesting.]
She is fast in changing subject.
[He's really amazing.]
[He is so cute.]
[I like him so much.]
Is he really cute?
[He is funny when he talks,]
[strong in coordination,]
[strong in coordination.]
[He looks cool
when he jumps out from a window.]
[What's so cool about
jumping out from a window?]
[I'll show you how I jump
off the building then.]
This young boy is simply too naive.
[Okay.]
[Say,]
[if you do a stream today,]
[who would care about Liu Liu Da Shun?]
Compared to me,
you are still lacking skills and tricks.
[See you tonight.]
[1]
Where are you going?
A cyber cafe.
It's dissertation defence tomorrow.
Why are you so stubborn?
Ke Ke, bring the computer here.
You didn't bring the computer.
Give me your ID.
Don't ask anything.
Double bonus this month.
Please accept.
[Zero Gravity Internet Cafe]
Is there a private room?
No.
Help me find a seat in a corner, please.
Thank you.
Do you want to apply for a
card? There's top up with a discount.
No thanks.
Where's the money?
There you go.
There are empty seats in
the middle row of the hall.
Thank you.
You haven't returned my balance.
Have you been to a cyber cafe?
You will get your refund once you log off.
Fine. Keep the change.
-Is there a private room?
-No.
Help me find a corner seat.
-Do you want to...
-No.
[Oh no.]
[Did I get busted so soon?]
It's automatic.
[Where are you?]
[I'm switching on the computer.]
I'm here.
I'll invite you.
[Mission begins.]
[Please help]
[the scientist kidnapped by
the evil robots.]
Three bandages,
two first aid kits.
What are they for?
To arm yourself well.
What about you?
I will not die.
Have you heard of this?
The person I adore is a great  hero.
Someday he will we put on a
first-class bulletproof vest,
wear a second level helmet,
take a heavy duty Magnum
military sniper rifle,
and ride an auto-rickshaw to pick me up.
Ready to shoot.
Take it.
You do it.
I control the car, you control the gun.
Aim at the bulls-eye.
Three.
Two.
One!
I hit the target.
Yes, you shot it.
Get ready.
Shoot!
Here.
Shot!
shoot!
Nice job.
♫ The wind directs me to your side ♫
♫ You shot me with the arrow of love ♫
♫ Breaking my defences ♫
♫ So let's go just with the wind ♫
Awesome!
You sing very well.
That's...
[I'm the original singer,
of course it's good.]
I practised for a long time.
I was hoping for a chance
to sing out loud.
Your water.
Complimentary?
[Webmaster: The water you
ordered has been delivered! ]
Forget it.
The service here is pretty good.
Free water for me.
The service of my cyber cafe
is not good at all.
You are also at a cyber cafe?
Who ordered fish-flavoured
shredded pork rice?
Who ordered the fish-flavoured
Did you order this, mister?
I'm sorry.
Your fish-flavoured
shredded pork rice?
You ordered it?
Why didn't you answer my call?
What a bother.
Fish-flavoured shredded pork rice?