[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 3]
Hey,
what are you doing here?
Professor Qin.
[Auditorium]
Liang Chen.
-It's been a while.
-Indeed.
Why didn't you tell me you're coming back?
Come on.
Let's talk in my office.
Okay.
Here.
Have a glass of water.
Thank you, Professor Qin.
How have you been?
I'm doing great.
It's just that I've got stuck
on my composition recently.
So I'm coming back here
to look for some inspiration.
Please tell me more.
I think I...
Liang.
Hi.
I'm Mr Luo,
league secretary of the academy.
[All rivers run into sea]
You've won
two Golden Cicada Awards this year.
You're the pride of our university.
-Yes, that's right.
-Right?
Hurry, take a photo of us.
-Let's take a photo.
-Okay.
-Come on.
Liang's eyes
are filled with devotion
to her alma mater.
We look close.
Right, right.
We must make good use of this.
-We must make good use of this.
-Yes, yes.
[What time should we play tonight?]
[Sorry, I have something to do today.]
[Sorry, I have something to do today.
Let's do it next time.]
[Next time.]
Why are you walking so fast?
Let's turn back.
Liang Chen is here in the music academy.
-Hurry up.
-Liang Chen is here!
Where?
Forget it.
I'd rather go to the library.
The library is that way.
You're going to the wrong direction.
I have long legs.
I like to take the long way, can't I?
Just admit you want to see Liang Chen.
Wait up! Wait up!
[Liang Chen]
Boiling water coming through!
[Cute little fairy, Liang Chen]
Hold on! Hold on!
Watch it, it's burning hot!
This is neat.
I heard that she looks better
in person than in photos.
Really?
I'm so excited!
[111111111111111]
Ms Liang, what were you looking at?
Nothing.
Was that Liang Chen?
She just locked eyes with me.
That was me.
Pretty much the same.
I guess
that was almost the same
as she had talked to me.
If you want to guess,
it was me Liang Chen had talked to.
Ke Ke,
if someone sends you a lot of ones,
what does he mean?
How come you don't know this?
I don't know how to explain this to you.
The more ones he sends,
the more he agrees with you.
It means,
"Sure, sure, I can't agree more."
[He just didn't need to lead me
in the game for today.]
[Does he really need to be so excited?]
Mr Sun.
Yes?
Hurry up.
Director He is waiting to take bath too.
I'm coming out.
We've been taking cold showers
during winter,
how many more days do we need to do this?
Probably a few days more.
Careful.
What kind of place is this?
It's a great honour
to have you here.
Despite the poor condition here
and our crew's limited budget,
however,
I have prepared a pot of meat for you.
Sun.
Sun, Sun.
You just took a bath?
Allow me to introduce.
This is your partner in the movie.
Ma Shan Shan, Ms Ma.
Hello.
And this is...
I don't know what's wrong with him today.
But don't worry. I...
I can assure you he's a great actor.
Let's go to eat.
Lu Jing, let's go.
My brain works less efficiently
after eating.
I'll go after I finish adjusting
the movement parameters.
What kind of big data research
are you working on again?
It looks so complicated.
I'm writing Lu Lu Xiu.
What is Lu Lu Xiu?
We'll leave you then.
Lu Jing, keep it up.
Let's go.
[SOMERSET]
I have to calm down.
Otherwise, I can't compose anything.
Yes.
Happy Bootlicker isn't online?
It's still early.
I'll give it a try.
[DANGER LEVEL 99%]
What is this?
[Failed]
Again.
Sir,
please don't do this to me.
Let me sing Downwind for you.
Go where the wind blows.
[DANGER LEVEL 95%]
[Failed]
What?
You can't see me, you can't see me.
[DANGER LEVEL 95%]
[Incomplete]
What a stupid mission!
I can't complete it every time.
I'm so mad! So mad!
I don't want to play anymore.
Quick guide for Beautiful Soul.
[Quick guide for Beautiful Soul]
How to become
an expert player in ten minutes.
[How to become an
expert player in ten minutes.]
[Beautiful Soul Quick Guide]
It is quite easy, isn't it?
Here we go.
[Dear Box Spirits,]
[you thought you could
get rid of the fate]
[of letting others take away your supplies
after reading this?]
[Naive.]
Darn it.
[Even chicken that is pecking rice
on keyboard can play better than me.]
[Dedicate a Downwind for you.]
You're making me want to blacklist you.
[I found a high level backpack
and suit today,]
and suit today, and a legendary AKB48.]
[and a legendary AKB48.]
[It's called AK47.]
[Never mind the details.]
[I thought I could complete the mission,]
[but the truth is
I didn't make it for five minutes.]
[but the truth is I didn't
make it for five minutes.]
[Am I really that bad?]
[Don't you know it yourself?]
[I'll go online ten minutes later.]
[I'll take you to experience
the fun of setting off fireworks.]
[I'll take you to experience the fun
of setting off fireworks.]
[You're in a good mood today.]
[A little bit.]
1264.
1265.
1266.
1267.
1228.
1269.
Hold on, I need a break.
Just a short break.
[Who are those two next to you?]
My finger slipped.
I clicked on the wrong mode.
They are passerby players.
[It's fine.]
[Four players won't be an issue.]
I'll assign tasks later,
I'll team up with you.
Okay.
[Mission One. Please search
for the entrance to the tomb.]
Guys, are you there?
I'll assign the tasks.
Oh my god.
Herman!
Are you Herman?
I can't believe I got to
be matched with Herman.
Am I going to win this round
without having to lift a finger?
Please take a photo with us.
Yes, yes.
Herman?
You didn't know I was Herman until now,
did you?
Of course not.
What is Herman?
What? You don't even know about Herman?
Gaming streamer, Herman.
You're kidding, right?
You don't know Herman?
The sniper god.
Herman?
Did you play the song Downwind?
And then, that song became famous?
It was me.
You are a fan of Liang Chen?
Any problem with that?
No problem.
No problem at all.
We'll split into two teams to find clues.
Guys, you're going to
the direction of the camp.
There are fewer robots over there.
We're going to the opposite direction.
Whoever finds the entrance
to the tomb first
will inform everyone.
Any questions?
No.
No!
Just shut up.
Why do you like Liang Chen?
Is it because she is
exceptionally outstanding?
Exceptionally beautiful?
Exceptionally talented?
Have you seen it?
There are seven robots out there.
So?
So do you prefer to die by a robot's gun
or mine?
Let me ask one more question.
One last question.
What exactly is this mission of ours?
We need to retrieve the rare energy stone
left by the Mayans from the robots.
What is the use of energy stone?
It's no use for us,
but it can stop the evil robots
from making powerful weapons
to threaten earth.
Saving the planet.
I like this mission.
Get in the car.
Coming.
Here's your chance.
Give me a hand.
Don't miss this
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
Or you will regret it.
Wait.
I'm your idol!
Sir, wait for me!
Drive slower!
Sir!
Why did you pick up so many things?
Based on your capability,
the best you can do is running after me.
I picked them up for you.
They're not for me.
For me?
I read a guide before.
It said that this is particularly useful.
You're being favoured by god indeed.
You actually found an airdrop gun.
Is this gun that powerful?
It gives longest period of continuous fire
with highest accuracy rate.
It's usually available
in airdrop box only.
Use it then.
I have a lot of other things for you
in my bag.
You see.
Bullets.
And cartridges.
I'm your human backpack now.
Just tell me if you need anything.
You
trust me that much?
Of course.
You are much stronger than
those players in video tutorials.
Since you trust me so much,
-I'll take you for a ride then.
-Okay.
I'll show you
my drift skill in the jungle.
Okay.
Lu Jing, drive slower. I'm scared.
Lu Jing, slower.
There is a slope ahead!
Don't be afraid.
I'm taking you flying.
Keep showing off.
You've crashed, haven't you?
You called this a crash?
I call this a skilful brake.
Who are you talking to?
My son.
You insolent son,
is this how you talk to your father?
Seriously?
What makes you think
you can pick on me?
Don't fight.
Let go of me, let go.
I'm going to fight him in real life today.
We'll see about that.
Come on.
He challenged me!
He... he challenged me!
You promised to take me flying,
but we crashed before we even flew higher.
Wait up.
We found the tomb.
Come here now.
We found the tomb?
You see.
I told you,
you would find the exit if you follow me.
The luck of a rookie like you who
always dies in the beginning of the game
is usually good.
Can't you just compliment me?
No.
I...
You're welcome...
Not even a thank you.
[Mission One completed.]
[Data has been saved.]
[Next, please get the Mayan Energy Stone.]
-Herman.
Let's hurry up.
Once the door is open,
the robots should be here soon.
You guys go in first
to find the energy stone.
I'll stay here and block them.
You too, go in first.
Are you sure you can do this alone?
Let me stay and help.
Go in.
Stay safe.
[He's stopping the robots all by himself.]
[It's so dangerous.]
Lu Jing.
What are you doing back?
I'm giving you the bullets,
in case you run out of them.
Here.
Smoke bomb.
Are you trying to blind the enemy
with flash grenade?
Sorry, a mistake.
Here.
Let's go.
It's so foggy.
How are you going to shoot?
See how I did it?
Whenever I shoot,
watch and learn.
I'll try next time.
How do you tell their positions
in this situation?
Before I threw the grenades,
I had already confirmed their positions.
Also,
when you are unable to tell,
just listen.
Expert,
may I have your autograph?
That was such a brilliant performance,
but why aren't your two fans reacting?
For the sake of your return
to give me bullets,
it was a private tutoring.
I didn't press the talk button.
They couldn't hear me.
[Why are you laughing?]
You heard it?
Because I have good hearing.
I just got a feeling like I'm
a person who got only
20 points in mathematics,
and I suddenly received
a tutor by Hua Luo Geng.
So
you got only 20 points in maths exam?
No.
I don't need to take maths for my major.
Let's go.
Coming.
What are they looking for?
The mechanism to the treasure.
Let's go look for it too.
Just now,
why did you call your roommate, your son?
We might look like roommates,
but actually,
we all want to be each other's father.
Is this how college students
interact with each other nowadays?
You're not a student?
I graduated many years ago.
Did you think
I'm a student?
I can't believe
someone would still think I'm a student.
Based on your gaming capability,
you're probably
just an elementary student.
Can't be older than that.
What's the matter?
It seems that every tone is different.
It's a pentatonic scale.
Do, Re, Mi, Sol and La.
I found a stone tablet.
How do we use this?
Looks like it's a music formation.
The five large bells
represent the pentatonic scale.
We should use the musical score
on the stone tablet
to ring the corresponding bells.
Let me try it.
Go and hit the bell. I'll cover you.
Wait!
Hold on.
Music.
Charge!
What are you doing?
How many bells are left?
One.
Hit the bell!
[Mission Two completed.]
[Data has been saved.]
[Next, please return
the Mayan Energy Stone.]
What is this place?
It's so beautiful.
The energy stone belongs to the universe.
After we returned it,
the system will rain down
meteors automatically.
What happened?
Is the system having a bug?
Did I set off fireworks?
What else could it be?
Oh my god! I actually set off fireworks!
I actually saw the fireworks!
[This is awesome!]
No way.
I have to take a photo
and share it on my social media.
I have to record this historic moment.
[The future sniper goddess.]
Impressive, impressive.
[Future sniper goddess]
The future sniper goddess
who has zero achievement.
Even Orange has set off fireworks.
It made me feel like playing too.
Let me watch a live stream.
[Request channel timed out.
Please re-enter channel.]
What...
What's with the poor network connection?
I can't even watch a live stream.
Will such day ever end?
Director.
Shan Shan has got her make-up done.
Ms Ma.
-It's good, it's good.
-It's not bad.
Finally something to look forward to
for the rest of the days.
Rest assured. It's safe, absolutely safe.
I say, you really are a pro.
That was impressive.
I'm fine.
[You]
are indeed Liang Chen's fans.
Rest early,
Little Box.
Who are you calling a little box?
Definitely not myself.
Goodbye.
I wonder what he was thinking.
He is obviously an expert player,
why would he use such creepy nickname?
[Edit Tag and Label]
[Supreme Master]
[Thousand Years Box Spirit]