Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 13
Who is so bold
to dismantle my store?
Brother!
Your brother?
Xiao!
Your brother looks strange.
Is he drunk?
My… My brother never drinks.
Your brother looks very strange.
Where did you get the materials
of the sword?
-Xiao!
-Watch out!
Sir!
Are you okay?
Yin Xiao,
are you crazy?
How could you
treat an elderly that way?
Just vent your anger on me…
I…
I feel very disappointed in you.
Got it?
You are not good at drinking.
Don’t drink secretly in the future.
It is inappropriate to drink so much.
Huotu Xin, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Go, let’s go.
Go.
Xiao!
What’s wrong with my brother?
He must have been enchanted.
Enchanted?
Do you have a cure?
Yes.
My cure is upstairs.
Upstairs?
I am afraid my umbrella can’t stand it.
What shall we do now?
Put on the bracelets.
Hurry up.
Both of you.
And then?
Touch them.
Touch.
Don’t hurt my brother.
How to use it?
Use water.
Water?
How… How to use it?
Water… How…
Xiao.
Yin…
Yin… Yin Zhuang.
Xiao.
My masterpiece!
An invaluable treasure indeed!
I…
Your Majesty, Minister Fei,
Zhu Xi’s people have entered Zhaodu.
Zhu Xi has only one hundred people,
but we have to dispatch
all our guards against them.
Is it too big a response on our part?
Even a lion has to do its best
to catch a rabbit.
Zhu Xi has arrived too quickly this time
and I am afraid he is ready for it.
Just take it easy.
You have made preparations for long.
Just do your best.
I will guard the imperial city for you.
After long-term preparations,
finally
they are all here.
Yuan Yi…
I think I have to leave first.
It’s okay.
What can I do for you?
It is said Zhu Xi has arrived.
The person who keeps chasing
you has shown up.
Are you scared?
I am not scared.
I must see
who he really is.
Blacksmith
It hurts so much.
What’s wrong?
I have no idea.
Let’s
have another try.
It hurts so much.
What shall we do now?
It is my dowry.
I suggest
having a rest first.
Take the medicine.
It can cure
your mesmerism.
Feel better?
I am sorry.
I almost wounded you
and smashed your store
in order to save Yin Zhuang.
It doesn’t matter.
Consider it a test for the bracelets.
Pingting is full of
different types of people.
Sir,
have you offended anyone?
I have no idea.
Thank you
for helping make the jewelry.
You are welcome.
Actually I should
say thank you to you instead.
I saw
the two valuable crystal stones
of your sister,
and I was afraid they were spoiled
by the mediocre craftsmen.
So I felt…
obliged to do it.
Forget it.
How do you think
about the pair of bracelets?
Your techniques
are really marvelous.
It is hard to find
another jewelry master like you
in Suchuan.
But why do you
live in reclusion here?
It is a long story.
It really hurts too much.
Why is that?
Don’t worry.
It can certainly be removed.
Is it destiny?
It must be
destiny.
God doesn’t wish you
to marry Weisheng Yan.
Your brother is coming.
We have to leave now.
Xiao,
are you okay?
But… My…
My bracelet…
Just leave it on his wrist first.
What?
After we arrive in Zhaodu,
I will cut off his hand
and get it for you.
Don’t worry.
Your daughter can cure you.
You said
you would take me to Zhaodu?
It is said Zhu Xi
set out for Zhaodu yesterday.
Zhu Xi has never shown up in Zhaodu
since the emperor was crowned.
He must be looking for Linglong
in this trip.
Other than Zhu Xi,
I am afraid Weisheng Yan
is also on the way.
Do you mean
Weisheng Yan and Zhu Xi conspired?
Weisheng Yan
isn’t a simple person.
I am afraid what we encountered
in Pingting previously
has something to do with him,
including
your wedding.
Now,
I must keep myself separate
in order to see it clearly.
Yin Xiao,
do you mean
Zhu Xi has gone to Zhaodu?
If
your daughter is really the Goddess,
there isn’t any safe place
for your daughter
in Suchuan.
Do you have any latest news
about Linglong?
The Ritual of Eternity
will be held in Zhaodu soon.
Ritual of Eternity?
What is Ritual of Eternity?
The ritual to apotheosize Linglong.
If she succeeds,
she will be the real Goddess.
If she fails,
she…
She will be killed as a monster
or a liar.
Kill the Goddess on the altar.
Nothing is more thrilling
than this.
Zhu Xi wants to
kill Linglong at the Ritual of Eternity.
Why?
A menace
or a token of authority?
I have no idea.
But it is his plan.
The Yuan family has been irreplaceable
in the past centuries
just for its role as god-picked king.
If Zhu Xi can kill the Goddess,
the base of the Yuan family
will be endangered.
In that case,
the Yuan family won’t be irreplaceable.
To kill the Goddess
at the Ritual of Eternity?
It is in Zhaodu!
Moreover,
if Linglong is really the goddess,
Zhu Xi won’t hurt her.
Goddess or monster,
it is just their decision.
I will take you to see somebody.
Who is that?
Yin Zhuang,
let’s break
your engagement.
As you requested,
I told that lad about Jia’s daughter
being the monster
left by the plague seventeen years ago.
Sorry, Grandfather.
I made you worry again.
Tell me
if you have fallen in love with him.
Grandfather,
stop your nonsense.
You have refused
numerous wooers
these years.
I counted them in the beginning,
but it was beyond me in the end.
But
he is the only one
who gets close to us.
No kidding.
Girl,
I don’t know
why you got in touch with him.
It must
be something dangerous.
Keep an eye on him anyway.
Otherwise,
you may feel sorry in the future.
Grandfather.
Look, it is the punishment
for your nonsense.
His Majesty and Goddess have arrived.
Greetings, Your Majesty!
Spare it.
Thanks, Your Majesty!
What have you learned in Tianqi Sect
these days?
Your Majesty,
the followers of Tianqi Sect
guided us to read through Gods’ stories
and examine their historic collections.
It is a fruitful trip.
Not bad.
You can share with Marquis Pingjiang
what you have learned these days
after he arrives.
I don’t expect him to miss it
due to late arrival.
Report!
Your Majesty!
Marquis Pingjiang asks for a meeting.
Summon!
Sorry for my late arrival
to protect Your Majesty!
Please pardon me, Your Majesty.
Zhu Xi,
there is no assassinator here.
You don’t have to protect me.
Frankly,
the so-called Goddess beside you
is actually a liar.
The magic displayed during the burial of
Fozhuan is just her trick to cheat you.
I have guarded you secretly all the way
from Fire Tribe to Zhaodu.
I attempted to kill the liar for times,
but she managed to escape.
Marquis Pingjiang,
do you know what you are saying?
Your Majesty,
please check the article she used
to disguise herself as the Goddess.
It is nothing more than a kid’s toy
in Pingting.
Are you justified to claim me
a fake goddess with this small article?
Isn’t it too naive?
Take her here.
Xia Ling?
Linglong.
I have personally visited Fire Tribe
to inquire about her history
and brought here
a villager who witnessed her killings.
Your Majesty,
she is not only a liar,
but also a cruel monster.
Fire Tribe is blocked.
The people there haven’t
heard about stories of the Goddess.
It is normal for the tribesmen
to take the Goddess
as a monster when she woke up.
Even if the Fire Tribe didn’t know
about the Goddess,
they must be able to
differentiate a Goddess and a monster.
Only a monster
kills innocent people.
I didn’t kill any innocent people.
All tribesmen
know she is a monster.
They didn’t drive her
out of the village
as they felt sorry for her father.
Enough.
Shut up.
I have never hurt you.
Why did you say that?
Your Majesty,
I have numerous evidence to prove
she is
an inexcusable monster.
What evidence do you have
to prove yourself?
I am not a monster.
Don’t kill me. Don’t kill me.
I don’t need any evidence.
I am the Goddess.
If you don’t believe it,
let’s have a try.
Poke your sword into my chest.
If I am hurt by an earthly weapon
and shed a single drop of blood,
I will be the fake one,
and you can
kill me before His Majesty.
If you can’t hurt me,
you will be the sinner
who despises the Goddess,
and I will penetrate your throat
with the sword
and hang your head
high on the city walls
as a warning to all.
Your fiefs will be returned
to His Majesty,
and your people
will take you as a shame.
How is it?
Marquis Pingjiang,
let’s have a try.
Nonsense!
You are just a liar.
You aren’t qualified to bet with me.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Zhu Xi,
your reluctance to bet with the Goddess
proves that
you aren’t sure
if the Goddess is true or fake.
Why did you
defame the Goddess just now?
Calm down, Your Majesty.
It is not my reluctance.
It is unnecessary indeed.
Look, Your Majesty.
Anybody?
Crap.
It is too late.
It seems she has been taken away.
Where is she now?
The girl is the only clue and evidence
of the plague in Pingting.
Jia hid her for seventeen years
and she has been taken as a monster,
suffering
unlimited humiliations and tortures.
It must be Zhu Xi
who has taken her away.
If the plague in Pingting
seventeen years ago was manmade
just to cover up
a more horrible truth,
Jia’s daughter must be
a monster created by the plague.
If…
If she has been taken to Zhaodu...
Linglong
will be in danger.
Let go of me.
Do you feel surprised, too?
You should feel pleasant.
What do you mean?
What on earth is this?
Your Majesty,
the plague in Pingting
seventeen years ago was caused
by the monsters.
They turned Pingting
into a dead city
and caused numerous people
homeless.
This person
and her mother
are one of those monsters
who survived my hunting.
Your Majesty,
if you continue to
cover up for these monsters,
they will bring the plague again
and revive the disaster 17 years ago.
The imperial city
and even the whole Suchuan
will suffer great famines
with starving people
and corpses all around.
Today,
I must absolutely kill her
for the good of our people.
It is already in the past.
We should make a thorough
investigation before any conclusion.
Don’t kill me.
You know my mother.
I am not a monster.
Don’t kill me.
Father, save me.
Father.
Your Majesty!
Please be sure to kill this monster
in order to save Suchuan’s people.
My mother isn’t a monster.
Monster is dangerous.
Protect His Majesty!
Guards of Immortal Blood,
protect His Majesty!
Stop!
Catch her.
Aye.
Please.
My goodness!
Look at the face of that person.
She is too ugly.
What is that?
I am not a monster.
Don’t kill me.
Too scary.
-I am not a monster.
-Let’s go.
I am not a monster.
Don’t kill me! Don’t kill me!
Fei Tian.
Release her.
It is easy for me to release her.
Will Zhu Xi release her?
I will let Zhu Xi know
it is impossible for him
to harm Linglong in Zhaodu.
Zhu Xi didn’t dare to take actions
due to lack of justification before.
But you’re protecting
a well-known monster now.
Once Zhu Xi takes it as an excuse
to attack Zhaodu,
how will you respond,
Your Majesty?
Linglong isn’t a monster.
I will find the truth.
If Zhu Xi dares to attack Zhaodu,
we will be justified for a crusade.
Do you want to fight back?
Do you want to
protect the Goddess with the fleshes
of your people and soldiers?
Your Majesty!
Have you forgotten your
original purpose to find the Goddess?
I will protect the people of Zhaodu.
I won’t abandon Linglong, either.
I will stop whoever
wants to kill her.
Zhaodu is besieged by Shixu.
We need to take a detour.
It is expected
to take us more time.
What on earth is Shixu?
An enormous abyss
that is a shield to guard
and isolate Zhaodu.
But it takes only one day
by Weisheng Yan’s fish boat.
Then let’s use
Weisheng Yan’s fish boat.
Yin Zhuang,
where did you go last night?
Weisheng Yan,
we won’t go back.
Your engagement with Yin Zhuang
is hereby canceled.
You have no relation with each other
from now on.
Our wedding is already known
by most people of Suchuan
and all the big clans are expecting it.
Your cancellation of the engagement
will undermine the Yin’s reputation.
Moreover,
your stay at my mansion
is also widely known.
If you leave now,
how will you be viewed by others?
Weisheng Yan,
she just doesn’t want to marry you.
Do you think
it is meaningful
to talk about nonsense?
Just be a man
and let her go.
Yin Zhuang is my fiancée,
and it has nothing to do with you.
It has
something to do with me.
Look here.
This is a pair of Yin Yang Bracelets
made of the Yin’s heirloom.
Yin Zhuang
is my girl now.
Do you know
what fate really means?
Regardless of your wealth,
Yin Zhuang
is mine.
Yin Zhuang!
A trade
will be completed one day.
What if I use force to keep you here?
You can’t.
It is alleged to protect true love.
I will show you
the real meaning of an inborn couple.
Incredible!
This is
really invaluable.
This is the power
that guards love.
If you don’t explain,
it will look more marvelous.
Weisheng Yan,
that is the end of it.
You can leave.
I will remember you.
Weisheng Yan,
wait a minute.
I… I want to borrow something from you.
Don’t go too far.
Bullshit!
You almost killed me twice.
It is not too much
for me to ask something from you.
Do you want to borrow my boat
for Zhaodu?
It is too late.
What? What do you mean?
Marquis Pingjiang
has borrowed all my boats
and left not even a single one for me.
What?
Zhu Xi borrowed fish boats?
He wants
to launch a sneak attack on Zhaodu.
Linglong…
Chief Priest, aren’t you afraid of
being mistaken as my partner
by asking me to your divine palace
in public?
Zhu Xi,
listen.
Never harm the Goddess.
Are you too old
or have you gone blind and deaf?
It is Fei Tian instead of me
who wants to harm the Goddess.
Your enemy is Fei Tian.
Fei Tian has established
an execution ground for your Goddess.
If you want to save her,
just go to Fei Tian.
It is senseless
to come to me for it.
It is all
because of you.
Listen.
I don’t mean
today.
It is
all about seventeen years ago.
It seems you
know much about it.
Why don’t you tell the truth?
Is it because you can’t say
or you don’t want to say?
Maybe
they are all waiting for you to speak.
Whether she is the Goddess or a monster
will be proven
on the execution ground.
If she can prove herself as the Goddess,
I promise
I will certainly be her subject.
Will Fei Tian
do the same?
Zhu Xi,
what on earth are you going to do?
How come you don’t realize it?
I am a loyal official, right?
How can I tolerate His Majesty
being fooled by a monster?
I want
to clear
the evil people
beside His Majesty.
Take care.
Okay.
Weisheng Yan didn’t cheat us this time.
Why are you laughing?
It is really a good play
just now.
I did it
just to convince him.
I take back what I said yesterday.
What?
You did
know something.
Okay,
we have no time to waste.
We must get the boats right away.
Well…
Is what Weisheng Yan said
about the boats
credible?
Whether it is credible or not,
we must break
Zhu Xi’s troops firstly.
I have an idea.
I will use this to guide the fires here
and keep it on fire
to drive all of them away.
Come on.
What’s up?
Why doesn’t it work?
Mr. Wu Yan said
the two bracelets needed
to accumulate powers
for some time after use.
It seems
they haven’t recovered.
Well… I didn’t expect such a time limit.
Don’t think you can guard true love
just by using physical materials.
Let’s go.
Just follow me.
My brother’s power
has no time limit.
Let’s go.
No, no. There are so many people here.
Who is that?
Get away.
No admission here.
I am rushing against time
and won’t show mercy.
I hope you know it.
You won’t escape!
Hurry up.
Close your eyes.
Xiao.
Leave someone to row the boat.
Go.
Go and row the boat.
Wu Yuan?
You are too late.
I have been waiting for long.
Escaping with other's wife?
What’s up?
Your Highness!
You are not needed here.
Be dismissed.
Wait.
I almost forgot it.
Please give it to Weisheng Yan.
Thanks.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Linglong.
Xia Ling.
I have brought you
the pork cake I made myself.
Only after leaving Fire Tribe
did you find
pork cake was unique to our tribe.
Thanks.
Despite our frequent quarrels before,
we have grown up together.
If there were afterlife,
don’t be a monster.
Afterlife?
Why did you help Zhu Xi?
I can’t allow you to harm our tribesmen
and more innocent people.
Yes.
To you,
I am just a monster
whose coughing
will spread plagues now.
Not even the prison guard
dares to deliver foods to me,
let alone you.
Just help yourself.
I…
I am leaving now.
Zhu Xi
really has
spent much on me.
Weisheng Yan never fails to revenge.
He won’t let you go away easily
as you have taken away his wife.
I haven’t lived a better life anyway.
Why are you here?
According to Marquis Pingjiang’s order,
I need to go to Zhaodu
and kill your daughter.
Linglong
is just a tool of Zhu Xi
to replace Yuan Yi,
right?
Why?
Linglong and her mother
are just different from others.
I don’t believe in Goddess
and they aren’t monsters.
They are just different from others.
Why are they treated in this way?
Zhaodu
honors Linglong as its Goddess
just to re-establish
the ruling authority of the Yuan family.
Zhu Xi wants to kill Linglong
just to replace Yuan Yi.
Goddess
is already a legend
dating back to five hundred years ago.
Your daughter
must be eliminated
before he can replace the Yuan family.
So
the plague in Pingting 17 years ago
is just a fraud
created by Zhu Xi
to slaughter all aliens like her,
isn’t it?
Your Jin’er is possibly
the only person who survived.
Jia’s daughter
has been taken by Zhu Xi to Zhaodu.
She is different from
Linglong and Jin’er.
But she is also taken as a monster.
Jia has hidden her for 17 years.
Why was she
discovered by Zhu Xi this time?
Is it because of me?
Who
has been tracking me?
Is that you?
Don’t disembark at Zhaodu.
Otherwise,
I will kill you.
Okay.
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪