Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
The Blessed Girl
Episode 14
Is that woman
Zhu Xi’s people?
Yes.
Reliable?
Isn’t this boat
prepared by Weisheng Yan?
Yin Zhuang’s bracelets
were made by her grandfather.
They both
taught me the same thing.
In Pingting,
nobody is reliable.
It is really ridiculous.
Although you helped her get away,
her reputation was tainted by you.
You should
take responsibility for it.
Yin Zhuang is an innocent girl.
You must explain clearly
what happened last night.
I… I…
Otherwise,
I will punish you.
Yin Zhuang!
Xiao, look here.
These are peppers grown
on Bright Moon Island
and these
are all specialties from there.
What are you doing in the kitchen?
Cooking.
Cooking?
We will certainly have a hard battle
on the trip to Zhaodu.
How can we win if we are hungry?
I really feel so happy
to see you like this.
I know.
If I did marry Weisheng Yan,
do you want to kill him?
Doesn’t he deserve it?
Who knows?
It has nothing to do with me.
But I have never believed
you would marry Weisheng Yan.
Am I not a good actor?
No.
Yin Zhuang,
promise me.
Never do anything
not good for yourself in the future.
Just be yourself.
Okay, Xiao,
I am not such a good girl
as you imagine.
I just wanted to marry a rich person
and help you out.
It is not a big trouble for me indeed.
Promise me.
I have never felt sorry
for marrying Weisheng Yan.
Without a try,
I may feel sorry in the future.
I may wonder why I hadn’t
tried my best
to help my brother realize his dreams?
We would live on
Bright Moon Island for our life.
The coming back of the Goddess
is just another new message
brought by a traveler.
We can’t even
distinguish if Zhu Xi’s killing of God
is true or false.
We won’t go to Zhaodu and
guard the Goddess and His Majesty
as what we are doing now.
So
I have just followed my heart
to marry Weisheng Yan.
I’m also following my heart
to leave him.
I will never feel sorry
for my choices.
So I won’t feel sad.
Aren’t you the same kind of person?
To others,
it looks so ridiculous that
you have given up
your empery of Pingting
and gone to Zhaodu to guard
a declining king.
But I know
it is a supreme honor
for you.
My sister
has grown up.
You know it
even better than I do.
Without such an excellent brother,
I can’t feel so free
to do whatever I like.
Yin Zhuang,
what happened
last night?
Nothing special.
What do you think happened then?
I will support you
whatever you do in the future.
Maybe…
I think…
What do you think?
Nothing.
Let’s talk about it in the future.
Linglong,
are you a monster
or the Goddess?
It is really a pity
that I haven’t shown
this beautiful dress to my father.
Where are you going?
Zhaodu.
We are visiting His Majesty.
Do you have any imperial edict?
No.
Without an imperial edict,
you won’t be admitted.
Please go back.
I am the Goddess’s father.
Zhu Xi wants to kill my daughter
and attack Zhaodu.
What else do you have to say?
Today,
another person disguised as the Goddess
will be decapitated.
I have kept in mind
the looks
and also the names
of half the people here.
Two days ago,
you took me as your Goddess
and paid tribute to me wherever I was.
Why are you lowering your heads?
Don’t feel ashamed.
You should feel proud instead.
You will decapitate a monster
who has brought disasters
to the state and the people.
You are all witnesses,
and the heroes of Suchuan.
Moreover,
the person there,
Marquis Pingjiang!
People say you have
the greatest military power
and the richest fief in Suchuan.
But to me,
you are just rubbish.
You want to kill me
because you are afraid of me.
How much do you fear me?
Am I still a big threat to you
even if I am at the edge of death now?
How dare you say that!
Finally,
I want to blame the Goddess.
You aren’t a monster.
You are just a joke.
If you all claim
to kill the monster,
I will satisfy your wish.
Kill me
and terminate this farce.
Come on.
Report!
What’s up?
Have you got it?
Chief Priest,
thank you for helping me
and trusting me.
I just can’t help you complete
the Ritual of Eternity.
I am really sorry.
Stop it!
What do you have to say?
Fei Tian!
Do you know
what you are doing now?
I am decapitating a liar.
Do you oppose it?
I will prove
if she is real or fake
at the Ritual of Eternity.
If she
is a fake one,
she will be at your disposal then.
I won’t oppose it anymore.
Since the very beginning, I have felt
she is a liar.
Moreover, Marquis Pingjiang
has shown the best evidence,
but she can’t prove herself.
Chief Priest,
tell me your justification
to hold
the Ritual of Eternity.
Fei Tian,
you are utterly wrong!
For Suchuan and His Majesty,
I’m willing
to bear all responsibilities.
Stop!
Zhu Xi,
she isn’t a monster.
I will make a thorough investigation
into the causes of the plague
seventeen years ago
and provide an explanation to you all.
But never do anything
before that.
Your Majesty.
If you still need further evidence,
just come back to Pingting with me
and see the troubles of people
left by the monster then.
Okay?
Zhu Xi,
do you remember this?
You are really a young talent.
Not even I have discovered
your good trick.
I didn’t expect
the closest mentor of my son
was your people.
Me too.
I didn’t expect
you could find the survived monsters
seventeen years ago.
Let’s get straight to the point.
Is my son okay?
You will know it
when you return to Pingting
after the Ritual of Eternity.
You and Fei Tian
have planned it for the monster
in the past eight years.
Do you think it is worthwhile?
You know
she isn’t a monster.
But Suchuan doesn’t know it.
If Your Majesty
already has an arrangement,
I will
leave first.
Your Majesty,
I think
if her identity
is still in doubt,
why not allow her to prove herself
and clear the doubts of all?
Linglong,
whatever may come out,
you will always have my thanks.
Linglong!
Wu Yuan,
set sail.
There are Moon Guards here.
Rush over.
Pillar of Eternity.
The Pillar of Eternity is illuminated!
Please forgive me, Goddess!
Do you see it?
Kneel down!
Your Majesty!
I
am guilty!
This…
Is the punishment of the Goddess!
Zhu Xi has committed
a severe crime
by calumniating the Goddess.
Your kind lenience is anticipated!
Your Majesty!
Shall we
forgive him?
No.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Lenience!
Thanks, Your Majesty!
Thanks, Goddess!
Goddess has arrived!
Universal celebration!
Welcome, Goddess!
Congratulations on Your Majesty!
Linglong,
you’ve succeeded!
I have seen it.
-I…
-Don’t show off hastily.
Drink it up first
to replenish yourself.
Did I look very cool just now?
Were they
impressed by my power?
I’m starving.
Answer my question.
Did I look very cool?
You still remember it?
Yes.
When I transformed
last time,
I felt as if I had lost my memory.
But I remembered it clearly
this time.
It shows that
you are already the Goddess.
But
I must still blame you.
Fei Tian already
told me your plan.
I don’t think it is appropriate
to make such a big fuss
just to force the Chief Priest
to tell the truth.
Previously
we already discovered that
the Tianqi followers dispatched
to Fire Tribe had died successively.
Zhu Xi further
revealed the Pingting monster
seventeen years ago.
All the doubts are oriented
to what happened seventeen years ago.
The Chief Priest
must know something
that he hesitates to say.
But you even kept it a secret to me.
Tell you?
You almost spoiled it up
even if I hadn’t told you.
The Chief Priest was about
to tell the truth,
but you persuaded Zhu Xi to retreat.
Tell me.
How did you force Zhu Xi to retreat?
It isn’t important.
Answer me.
Is it within your plan
that Fei Tian let the guillotine fall?
Fei Tian...
She
really wanted to kill me.
Crazy!
How dare
you risk your life that way?
Are you...
angry?
Don’t be angry.
Whether you live or die,
it is always the best result
for Fei Tian.
But
didn’t you ever consider
to retreat?
♪Together with you I want♪
Because you said
you would always protect me
whatever happened.
Really?
♪Know each other heart to heart♪
I dared to do it
because I believed
you would certainly protect me
That is too…
♪But I am so ordinary♪
Too impetuous.
Never have such a dangerous
and stupid idea in the future.
♪Meet you at this moment♪
It isn’t a stupid idea.
At least it is much better
than your idea of marriage for peace.
♪How long♪
Who says
the marriage is only for your peace?
♪The time is♪
Then
what else is it for?
First,
it helps to consolidate the empery.
Second,
the marriage
of theocracy and regality can…
No more daydreaming!
Nothing else!
♪I’m so lonely♪
♪Without his love♪
Even if you don’t like it,
♪Listen♪
from now on,
I won’t have any more concubine.
♪I am so brave♪
♪But how to get him♪
♪Oh Forget it♪
♪What can I do♪
Those girls
are all from an aristocratic family,
knowledgeable, reasonable,
kind and amicable,
but...
♪So be it then♪
But...?
♪Be opposite♪
But I don’t like self-disciplined girls.
♪Be opposite against the world♪
I will discover
what the Chief Priest hasn’t said.
I will fulfill
your plan for you.
Just take a rest first.
Chief Priest,
why are you kneeling here?
Your Majesty!
I am guilty.
The Goddess has recovered.
You don’t have to blame yourself.
I have something
to tell you
about the Goddess.
I told you not to break it.
If you could have made it faster,
it would be…
You can’t blame me.
It is the Moon Guards of Fei Tian.
You can’t escape
even if you have wings.
Don’t worry.
Just wait for an edict from Zhaodu.
I am not worried!
The Pillar of Eternity
has been illuminated.
Maybe Linglong
is enjoying
the hurrahs of all.
That is what Zhu Xi is waiting for.
Why not
fight our way out of here?
Fei Tian.
Sorry,
it is my fault.
From the day
when you agreed to work with me,
you already had an idea to kill me,
right?
Do you know why
Zhu Xi released you
at the sight of the gold tortoise?
Why?
Some days ago,
he gave it
to his favorite son
as a gift.
Do you have your people
beside Zhu Xi?
Stand up!
Eight years ago when
the youngest son of Zhu Xi was born,
His Majesty made this plan.
Even I was astonished then.
But I didn’t expect
His Majesty made
the eight-year plan
specifically for you.
So I must drop the guillotine
as I wouldn’t allow you to become
an excuse of all to attack Zhaodu.
If you were fake,
everybody would have believed
I had just killed another liar.
But I am the real one.
Your Majesty,
Linglong
is really the Goddess.
But the Goddess
isn’t Linglong.
Linglong is just a carrier
of the Goddess’s soul.
When the Goddess is fully awake,
she
will thoroughly disappear.
Why didn’t you tell me earlier?
It is my fault.
What is the use
of punishing you?
Your Majesty!
I did it all for your good.
I recognized
your increasing love for Linglong,
and I was afraid
you couldn’t stay awake.
Linglong already said you had secrets,
but I kept denying it.
For the Goddess,
I wish
to die.
What is the use of your death?
Is there any way
to save Linglong?
I
prefer not to have this Goddess.
Your Majesty!
This is
the will of the Goddess.
No mortal
can violate her will.
So long as I stop her from transforming,
she will always be Linglong.
Your Majesty,
the Goddess
has woken up.
Please forgive me.
The Goddess
belongs to Suchuan
instead of
Your Majesty alone.
But Linglong
belongs to me.
His Majesty has preferred
the stories of the God since childhood,
but I have never recommended
him having it
as the way of state ruling.
Maybe you can
really be the one
to help him.
My dream
is more than
helping Yuan Yi take back the state.
Compared with the people of Fire Tribe
who guard the Flame Chilling Wall,
the battle for empery
is too pettish.
Do you want to know about
the stories of the Moon Tribe?
Will you tell me?
Numerous people
are recalling ancient Suchuan
every day.
But I never,
because at that time,
the people of Moon Tribe
were forced to hide and rest
at the most perilous cliff
to avoid hunting.
They couldn’t escape disasters
from time to time.
Civilization is progressing
and conquest replaces massacre.
The wings that can fly over ravines
and convey messages are better
than the ornaments on the wall.
Later on,
the Moon Tribe was gradually used
as the messenger
and left the cliff.
Therefore,
the Moon Tribe got out of miseries.
No.
Although we became the messenger,
we didn’t gain an equal footing
with the human beings.
The human beings mounted
a special iron ring on our wings.
We could still fly.
But we would feel
extreme pains
at each flip of wings.
Only when we were back
beside our master
would the master remove the ring
to give us a momentary break.
At that time,
the Moon Tribe just changed
from being the prey
into slaves.
Generations of the Moon Tribe
were born into this world.
But they were shackled
from the time of birth.
His Majesty was crowned at nine
and he is the last blood
of the Yuan family.
But His Majesty
released the first edict
to award the Moon Tribe
with the same status as all others
in Suchuan
despite all objections.
People of the Moon Tribe
were no longer slaves.
Only with His Majesty’s support
can the Moon Tribe
live in Suchuan with real freedom.
After the war,
His Majesty appointed me
as the prime minister
and Suchuan
had someone of the Moon Tribe as
the prime minister for the first time.
Goddess,
the Moon Tribe has never
believed in god.
The Moon Tribe only owes
to the royal family
or the Yuan family.
I didn’t expect
Yuan Yi to be so smart
at the age of eleven.
Sorry,
I have
misunderstood you.
No,
I have misunderstood you instead.
Report.
Goddess.
Minister Fei.
The Moon Guards intercepted
a fish boat breaking into Zhaodu
and caught two men and two women.
One of them
claimed to be the Goddess’s father.
My father has come!
Where is he?
I didn’t dare to take him here
without approval
and he is currently
kept by the Moon Guards.
Take me there now.
Beware of fraud.
I will go and check first.
Your Highness!
It is ready now.
Have Pingting’s fish boats set sail?
Yes.
The girl is mature now.
We can’t wait any longer.
But…
She is the real Goddess.
Are you sure to kill her?
Weisheng Yan said this sword was made
by the Fire Tribe with Earth Fire
five hundred years ago.
Do you know
how many monster heads I have
cut off with it seventeen years ago?
Great power, Your Highness!
Tonight,
I will allow it to suck
the blood of the Goddess again.
What a big pair of wings!
You must be the manager here.
Where is Linglong?
Where is she?
Are you the father of Linglong?
I am her father.
My name is Huotu Xin.
The Yins?
Yin Xiao, Yin Zhuang?
You must be Minister Fei.
Minister Fei?
His Majesty talked about you.
Who are you?
I am a nobody.
I am just a boatwoman.
Madam,
just forget her.
It doesn’t matter who she is.
Madam,
are you the manager here?
I have something very important
to tell you.
Listen,
Linglong is in great danger.
Don’t lock me up here.
Allow me to meet her now.
I was just notified
somebody claimed
to be the father of the goddess.
I was worried it was a fraud.
But you look like the real one.
No fraud, no fraud.
Just take it easy.
Your daughter is very safe.
She is
the Goddess of the whole Suchuan now.
She is in danger
only because she is the Goddess.
Goddess!
Has Minister Fei returned?
Not yet.
This is comfort tea delivered here
at the order of His Majesty.
You performed magic just now
and it can help you replenish energies.
Where is His Majesty?
He seems to be with the Chief Priest.
Don’t worry, Goddess.
Drink the tea first
and replenish your energies.
Zhu Xi wants
to kill Linglong
after she is apotheosized.
Did you hear about it in jail?
He told me personally.
How did you escape
from the jail of Zhu Xi?
I…
Somebody rescued me.
It is incredible that
somebody can take away a prisoner
from the jail of Zhu Xi.
Who saved you?
How?
You don’t know him even if I tell you.
I must know him if he is able
to save someone from Zhu Xi’s jail.
There is no time.
His army
will arrive soon.
Can you take me
to see Linglong first?
Don’t worry.
She is very safe in Zhaodu.
Zhu Xi was shocked
by her mightiness just now.
I don’t think
he will take actions so quickly.
Moreover, he has only
slightly more than 100 people with him.
They are being supervised
by the Moon Guards
and won’t threaten us in any way.
Don’t be cheated by him.
Linglong’s Ritual of Eternity is
the best chance for him to take actions.
If he can kill the Goddess on the altar,
he will be able to replace Yuan Yi
in the most stunning way.
You can ask them.
Zhu Xi has borrowed
all the fish boats of Weisheng Yan
and what we have is just one of them.
Other boats will possibly
arrive soon.
Zhu Xi does want to attack Zhaodu.
Somebody.
Keep a close eye
on the defenses around Zhaodu and
report to me upon anything abnormal.
Ask all people of the Moon Tribe
to gather with the Moon Guards.
All the guards in all four directions
must watch out and
shoot down any fish boat of Zhu Xi
upon discovery.
No fish boat is permitted
to pass the Moon Guards.
Yes.
If Zhaodu isn’t safe
as you said,
the Moon Guards must be
the safest place
for its unique location.
Just wait here
and I will dispatch someone
to take Linglong here.
Let’s figure out Zhu Xi’s plan
before any further arrangement.
Thanks, Minister Fei.
Linglong.
Linglong!
Where is the Goddess?
Just now a Moon Guard reported
the Goddess’s father
had come to Zhaodu
and the Goddess had gone to meet him.
What?
Your Majesty!
The Goddess isn’t found.
Not found.
This is Zhaodu.
It is my territory.
Go and search again!
Aye.
Your Majesty!
Marquis Pingjiang is gone, too.
What?
Your Majesty!
Both Linglong and Zhu Xi are gone.
According to Linglong’s father,
Zhu Xi may attack Zhaodu at any time.
I shouldn’t have
spared his life.
Zhu Xi is well prepared for it.
All Guards of Immortal Blood.
Please listen.
Distribute my order
to guard the city gate strictly
and never admit anybody to go in and out.
Aye.
Sub by WeTV & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪