THE CHARACTERS, LOCATIONS,
INCIDENTS, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND BACKGROUND OF THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL.
EPISODE 5
Why are you here?
You said I was your daughter too.
Can't a daughter visit her mom to hang out?
I'm busy.
Say what it is and leave.
I have many documents to review.
Cheong A Art Festival is in a few days.
I've waited really long for it.
What dress should I wear?
I'm so excited.
The notice should be up by now.
The teachers decided today to
disqualify you from entering.
What you did was too heinous.
It was out of my hands.
Don't make jokes.
My dad asked you, remember?
Just let me compete.
You're the director. You have the power.
Oh dear. Did I surprise you?
I was imitating Eun Byeol.
I don't need to respond anymore, right?
Since you're being nice anyway,
how about you give me the grand prize?
- What?
- If you truly love my dad,
you can do that much for me.
Are you kidding me?
You have no skills. How could
you ask for the grand prize?
You know...
I can't beat Eun Byeol with my skills.
That's why I'm being shameless
and asking you for this favor.
Must I call your dad for
you to shut your mouth?
Get out. Now.
You'll regret it if you act like that.
I know a pretty big secret, lady.
What?
When Director Cheon Myung Soo passed away,
you were on the staircase with him.
Why did you just run away?
Instead of saving your dad?
What did you just say?
You must've been shocked.
Okay, then. Shall we restart our discussion?
Seok Kyung,
what nonsense are you speaking?
Do you want to participate
in the festival that badly?
You can try whatever you want,
but you've already been disqualified.
You think the parents of the
victims will just let you be?
You think I'm only doing this for me?
I'm protecting your secret too.
It's a win-win situation.
Stop speaking like a lunatic.
You think I'd give in to a threat like that?
I see.
You need proof?
All right.
I'll give you proof if that's what you want.
But when you see it for yourself,
it'll only be more difficult for you.
You need some water.
Your face is so pale.
You have to be healthy, after all.
That brat!
What does she have that
she's being like that?
Was she the one who sent me
those threatening text messages?
No, that can't be.
If she had a video, she would've
shown it to me right already.
Calm down.
MS. KO
Hello?
Ms. Cheon! It's a mess here!
How could you do this to me?
What harm did my Jenny ever cause you?
Not only you bullied her,
you fed her until she threw up,
filmed that, and laughed at her!
How can you call yourselves humans?
How are you going to make
up for Jenny's broken heart?
Stop it!
What are you doing? This isn't your house.
You did me wrong too!
I don't know if you're just trying
to cover it up for Seok Kyung,
but don't underestimate me.
I won't forgive the kids...
involved in this.
I'll make sure they're all punished.
Eun Byeol! Min Hyuk!
I won't forgive them!
The only thing the other kids
did wrong was being there.
We've confirmed it already.
I see. You want to dump it all on Seok Kyung.
Why? Because your child
is among the assailants?
Calling her an "assailant" is offensive.
Those children are my precious students too.
Do you want all the top
students in the school...
to be punished?
You need to think about
the school's position too!
That's right.
Our innocent Min Hyuk had to do it
because Seok Kyung forced him to.
We're victims too.
Don't give me that garbage.
Jenny told me everything.
That no one helped her
when she was being bullied.
Being a bystander is assault too!
That's why we let Jenny
compete in the festival.
That's a given!
What I want is for every
assailant to be punished.
I will not settle or make exceptions!
Why are you being so cold?
We've been friends for so long.
Exactly.
There's just so much we can take.
We'll keep seeing each other
in the same apartment building.
You should give it a rest
and give in a little.
That's only right.
For the sake of our future relationship.
That's why I'm saying this.
Ma Ri.
Don't do this.
Our relationship.
Don't give me that garbage.
This means war.
I won't even talk to jerks
who hurt my daughter.
I'm seeing red right now.
You! If you don't go and
apologize to Jenny right now,
I'll break your legs.
You too!
You too. Get your act together.
Stop her. Stop her.
She left.
Where?
She's a total thug!
Fine. This is war.
My gosh. My gosh.
Min Hyuk is all grown up.
Son. Prepare hard for the festival.
Your dad will take care of...
Shut it.
Look at your face.
I'm so humiliated.
I thought an assemblyman was powerful, but...
Ma Ri.
How dare you take me...
for a chump?
It's me. Kyu Jin.
Hello, Kyu... I mean, sir.
A woman named Kang Ma Ri lives
in Unit 4503 in our building.
Find out everything you can.
Yes, sir. You can count on me.
All I need is Eun Byeol's phone.
Do you even have a brain?
You were put on probation?
School violence will go on your record.
Then you can kiss college
goodbye before you even apply!
I poured so much money into the school.
I could've built a building
in Cheongdam-dong with that!
Why is everyone only yelling at me?
Your fiancee's daughter bullied
Jenny when no one looked...
and did much worse things to her.
Then you shouldn't have gotten caught either!
Why are you inferior to Eun
Byeol in every single way?
You came from a good family
and had the best teachers.
I spent all that money to help you succeed,
but you can't beat that one girl?
It's not my fault I was born stupid!
My birth mom must've been dumb.
Why you...
I refuse to be punished alone.
That witch hid behind her mom.
I won't go down alone.
Just go study abroad.
I never expected you to
win the grand prize anyway.
Why should I leave?
I can go to Seoul National University.
Rather than apply to a college
way out of your league...
and be humiliated,
go to any random country and get a diploma.
It'll be much cheaper to get
you the SAT answer sheet.
I don't need your help anymore.
I'll win the grand prize at
Cheong A Art Festival somehow.
Just keep your promise to let me move out.
Joo Seok Kyung! Get back here!
Joo Seok Kyung!
I'll talk to her.
Why are you making things worse?
What do you gain by angering Father?
I said to be patient, that I would...
Don't act like you care about me.
Ro Na is back at school.
Doesn't it make you sick
just seeing her face?
Stop being unreasonable.
Ro Na's mom didn't kill Mom.
You believe that?
Do you think Ms. Yang killed Mom?
That's...
I didn't do it for money.
Take this. You are an
important person to me now.
100,000 DOLLARS
I know for sure that Ro
Na's mom didn't kill her.
So don't dump your guilty
conscience onto someone else.
How could you say that?
You're the same as Ro Na.
I don't owe you anything anymore.
Do you want me to reveal
what you did to my husband,
which you tried to cover up...
by giving me an apartment?
I don't think it's a good idea
to bring that up, Ms. Kang.
It was for Jenny's sake that
my husband took the fall...
and went to prison instead of you.
And your daughter ripped her heart to pieces.
Be prepared. I might even kill your daughter,
Seok Kyung.
Yoo Dong Pil is behaving and
living quietly in prison.
He doesn't seem to know
yet about his daughter.
When is he being released?
Two months.
We can't let him out already.
Your wife...
dared to mess with me.
Why did you call us here?
Our kids have to go to school.
If you're here to kill our mood
first thing in the morning...
I'm sorry.
Jenny. Ro Na.
I sincerely apologize.
Drop the act. It won't work on us.
I know I was wrong.
It was too hard for me...
after my mom died.
I wasn't prepared to accept it yet,
and my dad got engaged.
I had to become a family with Eun Byeol.
I couldn't handle it.
Do you think that's an excuse?
Just because you were hurting,
you took it out on innocent kids?
I still hate Ro Na and Ms. Oh,
but I got angry that
Jenny was close to Ro Na.
That's why...
I'm sorry.
It'll never happen again.
Please...
Please forgive me.
I'll accept the probation.
It has been my dream to perform
at Cheong A Art Festival.
Please... Please let me do that at least.
Please.
That witch Seok Kyung
can't be sincere, can she?
It's obviously an act.
There's still fire in her eyes.
She was not sorry.
Still, she swallowed her
pride and got on her knees.
She's still a kid.
Shouldn't we give her another chance?
No. I won't forgive her.
"It has been my dream to perform
at Cheong A Art Festival."
Then even more so.
She has to lose that which
is the most precious...
for it to be true punishment.
Shouldn't you...
at least apologize?
The Office of Education is taking
what Seok Kyung did to Ro Na...
very seriously and is investigating.
Do as you wish.
Have her expelled or report her to the police
I will never bow down to you.
If Su Ryeon were to see Seok Kyung now,
what would she say?
How can you bring up
that name so shamelessly?
Aren't you the one who
begged me to get rid of her?
Is that why...
you killed her?
For my sake?
What?
Forget it.
It's all in the past now.
And it's true that...
I wanted Su Ryeon gone.
Why are you back anyway?
To get back at me or abandoning you?
Do you think that's possible?
You seem to underestimate me.
Stop wasting your time and
get lost with Ha Yoon Chul...
unless your child has two lives.
Thank you for your concern,
but shouldn't you be worried
about your company instead?
Rumor has it that it's
experiencing financial difficulty,
and its stocks have been plummeting for days.
I read an article in the financial paper...
advising against investing in your stocks.
The merger plan with Cheong A
Foundation seems to be called off,
and it's said that things are
not good between you and Seo Jin.
With all your financial sources drying up,
your company may face
severe financial strain.
Are you sure it'll be all right?
You're being nosy. I don't need your advice.
J KING HOLDINGS
It's already down by five percent today.
Where did the rumor about
financial difficulty leak?
It's definitely not the banks.
I think it's because of Ms. Cheon's scandal.
My company is going to falter
unless the merger is announced soon.
CEO JOO DAN TAE
NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT
I, PARK YOUNG RAN, AGREE NOT
TO DISCLOSE ANY INFORMATION...
SIGNED BY CHEON SEO JIN AND PARK YOUNG RAN
Is it time to play this card in the end?
Are you preparing the Grand Prize for me?
Don't forget to engrave the
trophy with my name beforehand.
My patience has a limit.
Come on. Don't worry.
You'll see the evidence that
you're dying to see soon enough.
You won't be disappointed.
What is she hiding from me?
- You're here.
- Yes.
Seo Young, it's been a while.
I know. Sorry we showed up unannounced.
You seem very busy.
I was at the auditorium preparing
for Cheong A Art Festival.
What brings you here?
I was very moved by your
20th anniversary concert.
Sorry it took me so long to
congratulate you in person.
That's not necessary. We're family.
Especially the first song.
I've never heard you sing so perfectly.
Your father would've been so proud.
It's such a shame.
What are you trying to say?
This is just ridiculous.
Open it.
NON-DISCLOSURE AGREEMENT
How reckless of you.
How dare you use a ghost singer
at such an important concert?
I was really shocked.
The country's most renowned singer...
fooled the whole country?
It creeps me out.
Where...
did you get this?
An anonymous report was made to
the foundation's ethics committee.
You've brought disgrace
upon the whole family.
Do you know how much trouble I went
through to keep the committee quiet?
But you didn't do that for me, did you?
As my mom, shouldn't you
ask how my voice is...
and how serious my condition is...
before anything else?
If you were my real mom, I mean.
Am I wrong?
What did you say?
Step down as the director...
before you humiliate yourself further.
Let Seo Young take over.
What?
Have you ever thought about...
the damage that the foundation
will suffer once this gets out?
The foundation that your
father devoted his life to...
might crumble overnight.
Is that what this is all about?
Taking your stepdaughter's position away...
and giving it to your real daughter?
Will that make you happy?
Now that Father is gone,
you don't have to pretend to
be my mom anymore, do you?
You rude brat. How dare
you speak to me that way?
I've looked after you for the past 35 years.
Have you ever acknowledged that once?
How can I possibly love you
when you never open up to me?
Aren't you responsible for that?
All these years,
you've tried so hard to make Father hate me.
Step down,
or I'll disclose it myself.
One more thing.
Sell off Cheong A Art Center...
as soon as it's completed.
Why would you waste the foundation's money...
on a stupid opera house?
It was Father's life-long dream.
I'm going to run it myself no matter what.
I can't let you do that.
I have a 30-percent share
of the foundation, remember?
Let go of the idea that you're
irreplaceable, will you?
Oh Yoon Hee.
You revealed it in the end?
Why did you have to rush me?
I'm stressed out as it is.
I don't even have any
reservations today, do I?
Apparently, someone
recommended you to this lady.
She even brought these flowers,
specifically asking for you.
- What?
- She's waiting. Hurry up.
What's more, she paid the
membership fee in cash.
Is she in the scrub room?
- Yes.
- Okay.
MA RI SAUNA
Hello.
I wonder who recommended me to you.
Usually,
you have to make a reservation
at least the day before.
I'm only making an exception here
because someone recommended me...
to you...
Now I understand why you smell like soap...
every time you've been out, Ms. Kang.
I thought you were having an affair,
but this is even more shocking.
I've never heard about anyone
like you at Hera Palace.
How did you find this place?
Put on some clothes already.
Assemblyman Lee hates waiting.
Yuck.
Sorry.
SAUNA
Honey.
What?
The outfit looks even better
on you than I expected.
When my aide told me that...
you work at a sauna, I didn't believe it.
But look at you.
This is why everyone should dress
in something that suits them.
You look fantastic. Right, honey?
Exactly.
I knew something didn't feel right...
when she bragged to everyone at Hera Palace.
So what?
I have nothing to be ashamed of.
I swear that I've lived
more honestly than you two.
I've earned money through hard work.
You have no right to mock me.
Then why did you hide it
from everyone so completely?
- Well...
- It's for your child, right?
But the thing is,
this sauna looks so run down.
Since her mom works her bottom
off at a place like this,
Jenny really should study hard.
So I had my aide...
send a few pictures to Jenny.
She should grow up.
What?
Shouldn't you run?
Ms. Kang!
That was hilarious.
Gosh, my stomach hurts.
Ro Na,
are you just coming in?
Things are going fine at school, right?
Ms. Oh, is it okay if I prepare
for the festival with Ro Na?
I feel scared to do it on my own.
Of course, you can.
Let's go. I'll cook you tteokbokki.
- Sorry.
- Excuse me.
Sorry. Goodness!
Why is her head so thick?
I'm sorry.
I'm fine.
Excuse me,
who are you?
It's a secret.
A bathhouse?
Who's that?
These must've been delivered
to the wrong suite.
This is ours.
Jenny!
Are you okay?
Did anyone come by?
Mom, why do you look like this?
Where are you coming from?
I was at the sauna.
I forgot I had dinner
arrangements with someone.
Why don't you and Jenny go
out and have dinner instead?
I'll cook you tteokbokki another time.
Mom, is that okay?
Yes.
All right. I'll be back.
- Let's go, Ro Na.
- See you.
Are you looking for these?
Goodness.
Lee Kyu Jin that jerk! This is
what you became an assemblyman for?
Who's that?
DUBAI
Yes, officer.
Is something wrong with my husband?
What?
What do you mean?
My husband is hurt?
There was a fight between the prisoners,
and he got beaten up badly and
is at a hospital right now.
He got into a fight?
What happened?
He's been watching out for himself so much.
This has never happened before.
We're looking into it right now.
Just know that it happened.
One must be careful of the
smallest things before a release.
If anything goes wrong, his
release might get delayed.
Hello? Officer!
What's happening?
Who did he possibly fight with?
Could it be Joo Dan Tae?
That jerk!
This was your plan all along?
You sing for me once, and you
use that against me like this?
What are you saying? Talk
to me like a normal person!
Why my mother?
Why my sister?
You probably thought that that
was the best way to bring me down,
but whatever you do,
I won't let anyone take Cheong
A Arts High School from me.
Nobody can take my director position!
I don't know what's going on with you,
but are you going to rage at me
every time something goes wrong?
I'm sorry, but I haven't done anything yet.
I guess...
you have a lot more enemies than just me.
- Shut up.
- What are you doing?
Get out of my house.
I warned you.
I won't stay still if you hurt my wife.
You must know...
what that wench has been up to!
Since you live with her,
you must know too.
How fun has that been?
Are you having a blast?
How dare you just laugh with her, you jerk!
What do you mean?
Even if you hate me,
how could you team up with
Yoon Hee to get back at me?
You know...
what Cheong A Foundation means to me.
Are you okay? Did something
go on between you two?
No, it's nothing.
There must've been a misunderstanding.
I can't just let her be.
She's being like that because we let her.
Don't do anything.
It'll just get tiring
for us if we make a mess.
Stop letting people walk all over you!
If someone comes at you, you go at them too!
I'm here to protect you.
You're not on your own.
It's nothing. Don't overreact.
Dinner's ready.
I'm heading out for a moment.
I won't take long.
Be careful.
Why can't I reach you?
I've been worried sick.
Why?
Your mother called.
I heard that you're resigning
from being the director.
Is that true?
Is that what my mom told you?
What's going on?
Is there an issue that I don't know of?
Tell me so that I can help.
The Cheong A Arts Center project...
is going well, right?
Of course. As you've dreamed of,
it'll become the world's best opera house.
Rush...
the merge.
Is it because of what happened today?
Don't rush anything.
Think over it carefully. It's a big decision.
No. I've been thinking
about it for a long time.
There's no reason to stall time.
Announce the merge.
I can give the department store
and the hotel to Mom and my sister.
All I want is Cheong A Arts Center.
I'll give you the right to decide
on anything regarding the merge.
If that's what you want,
I'll get started on it.
It's going to be huge.
You might become richer than you can imagine.
I'm already satisfied...
with the wealth that I already have.
I don't know.
Can one's desire for
wealth ever be fulfilled?
Even when you live on a
100th-floor penthouse,
humans are built to want more, to go higher.
Isn't that why you chose me, after all?
Let's not push our wedding back any further.
Move in as soon as the Arts Festival is over.
Your daughter, Seok Kyung.
Will I be able to handle her?
Us two moving in together is...
What about Seok Kyung?
Did she do something wrong again?
No. Let's talk later.
I'm sorry. Can you please leave?
I need some rest.
All right.
Cheon Seo Jin will complete my dream.
CHEONG A ARTS CENTER
CHEONSOO DISTRICT 27
All I need now is to find Joo Hye In.
Then, her land can be mine too.
Had it not been for Shim
Su Ryeon, that wench,
everything would've already been mine by now.
Stop drinking.
Are you going to be drunk in front of Jenny?
Don't stop me.
I'm going to drink until I die tonight.
No, everyone is going to die.
Because you're embarrassed...
that you work at a bathhouse?
You saw? You saw, didn't you?
Why did you do that?
What's wrong with working at a bathhouse?
It's not like you're
committing a crime or anything.
Are you teasing me now?
Those who are threatening you
with that should be embarrassed.
Why are you the one who's embarrassed?
It's Min Hyuk's family that
sent you the photos, isn't it?
That brat.
He doesn't even care that
his son did so wrong.
Instead, he's busy threatening
me using my weakness.
Why hasn't lightning struck him yet?
There's no point in grumbling.
When you're weak, people
are bound to get you.
That's how I let people get me too.
The Hera Palace people, I mean.
I know it must look terrible
of me to apologize to you...
at a time like this,
but I was crazy.
You know, people are just like this.
I had no idea...
until I've been in your shoes too.
Sue me if you're pissed.
Even your apology sounds much like you.
You don't have clear evidence...
for the bullying incident,
so if you keep going forward,
you're the one who'll get hurt.
Why don't you settle it now?
I know that I'm being stubborn too.
But...
I can't forgive myself...
for having had no idea of all of this...
when my own child was going through so much.
I feel so bad.
Give one,
but we'll make sure that you get one too.
Get what?
I want to go to school with Eun Byeol.
Where is she?
She's taking a shower right now.
I can wait.
It's going to take some
time. Have a seat and wait.
What? Why isn't it here?
Did she take it?
Eun Byeol, are you done getting ready?
What are you doing here?
That hurts!
I get it. Let go.
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you in her room
when she's not even here?
I came to go to school with Eun Byeol.
Why don't you trust me?
Since when were you so close to Eun Byeol?
Mom, what's wrong?
Get out!
You know that you're going overboard, right?
I thought you said that you're innocent.
Seems like you'll get caught soon.
Joo Seok Kyung!
I guess I'm too early. See you at school!
Mom, what's going on?
Distance yourself from Seok Kyung.
If she talks nonsense, just ignore her.
You understand?
Yes.
PRACTICE ROOM
Stop.
Did you know...
that Seok Hoon and Ro Na are dating again?
What? Who said that?
I saw the two together last night.
Things were looking quite serious.
It looked like Seok Hoon
is still not over Ro Na.
Do you know anything?
No, not at all.
Let go! What are you doing?
Let me go!
Stop playing with Seok Hoon!
Don't you and your mom have the
slightest bit of conscience?
Are both of you into
taking other women's men?
Watch your mouth. What are you talking about?
Seok Hoon is my boyfriend. We're dating.
Don't talk to him.
Don't even look at him. Don't be around him.
It's annoying.
Your mother and Seok Hoon's dad are engaged.
How can you two be together?
You're not worth explaining anything to.
I've warned you.
If I find you with Seok Hoon again,
you and I are both dead.
All right?
They're dating?
Lies. This can't be.
What did you just say?
I'll drop the bullying incident.
Let's just end it at Seok Kyung on probation.
That's what you should've
done from the start.
Did you finally get some sense in yourself?
And let Seok Kyung...
compete at the Cheong A Art Festival.
What made you change your mind so suddenly?
Right.
Isn't it better for Jenny if
Seok Kyung doesn't compete?
The more participants there are,
the lower your daughter's
rank is going to be.
I want to show everyone that
my Jenny can beat Seok Kyung...
any day.
I got some kind of an apology too, after all.
Anyway,
thank you for making this decision.
Ms. Oh, you agree with this too, right?
I do,
but under one condition.
What is it?
I'll join the PTA committee.
As a PTA committee member,
I'll have the right to observe school life...
and check the security videos as I please.
There's no guarantee that the
kids won't harass Ro Na anymore,
so it makes me nervous.
As in, you'll observe them?
I have to protect my child, don't I?
While we're on the topic,
let the PTA choose...
the judges for the upcoming
Cheong A Art Festival.
That's...
the right of the school.
That's why there has been
corruption for all these years.
There were questionable
grand prize winners too.
That's a bit extreme.
It's true that the fairness of
the judging has been questioned.
If you want to avoid such suspicions,
you can just proceed as Ms. Oh proposes.
I'm for it.
Ms. Ko Sang A?
I have no reason to oppose.
Also, I'll notify the Office of Education...
that we will settle and drop the case...
only after my request is granted.
What do you say?
7 DAYS BEFORE CHEONG A
ART FESTIVAL PRELIMINARIES
Nothing salty.
You have to eat very balanced meals.
You have to eat well to
have the strength to sing.
That's a good boy.
- No, no.
- Mom, my throat.
No. There. Wrap it.
Wrap it.
Again! Is that all you can do?
You need to breathe lower
the higher you sing.
Raise the pitch and make
your upper lip vibrate.
Okay. I'll try it again.
MI YUN YI
What's wrong?
Is something wrong?
It's nothing.
Focus on your singing.
Why can't you hold your breath longer?
How can you win the grand prize like that?
If you let Ro Na win the grand prize,
my life will be over.
You must beat Ro Na at all costs.
Even if you have to kill her.
I can do it.
I'll win the grand prize.
I won't lose to Ro Na.
You must make the perfect sound...
and squash the jerks whining about fairness.
You must practice and
practice until you get it.
Until you can hold your breath longer.
Flex your abs.
More!
I was worried for nothing.
She has no evidence.
How could I let a kid scare me?
That wasn't like me.
More!
It'll be hard not to win the grand prize.
- Was I really okay?
- Yes.
Take care of your throat
until the preliminaries.
Congrats in advance.
Thank you.
CEO JOO DAN TAE
MERGER AGREEMENT SIGNING CEREMONY
J KING HOLDINGS
CHEONG A FOUNDATION
MERGER AGREEMENT SIGNING CEREMONY
I wanted to celebrate quietly just us.
We're engaged and we merged companies.
I feel like we're really one now.
I feel like a weight has been lifted.
It took me a while to decide,
but now that we did it, I trust you.
Cheong A Group will lead
construction and investment.
They're your specialties.
I already have the business model.
Here.
This is what I'm developing.
It's 20 minutes from Gangnam.
Your Cheong A Art Center
will be at the center here.
Construction will be completed soon, right?
I'm excited.
Once the development is announced,
it'll be impossible for
anyone to buy the land.
It'll be worth much more than Hera Palace.
It'll become a wealthy
area surpassing Dogok-dong.
If it's worth that much,
large corporations must
have coveted it as well.
It was possible because I'm Joo Dan Tae.
I'm hungry. I have to eat light and go.
Cheong A Art Festival is tomorrow.
Okay. You must be fired from preparing it.
And thanks for letting Seok Kyung enter.
It's only natural.
Whether it's Eun Byeol or Seok
Kyung that wins the grand prize,
I can congratulate her sincerely.
Let's drink.
I can't wait for tomorrow.
ALARM IN 6 HOURS
AWAKE SMART DEVICES
TURN ON TV, TURN ON AIR FILTER
I HOPE YOU WIN THE GRAND
PRIZE. GOOD LUCK. DAD.
I hope you win the grand prize. Good luck.
Dad.
We will have a sunny day today.
The fine dust level is average.
If you're going to the East
Sea, be careful of strong waves.
There will be a wide range of temperatures.
In Seoul...
Good luck, Ro Na. See you later.
See you later.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
Ro Na.
Here. Drink it. It'll give you energy.
Just do as you have been in practice.
You were good.
Keep this in your mouth
until you have to go up.
It'll keep your mouth from getting dry.
Thanks. I'll do my best.
At least have a banana.
Where's that drug?
You said you wouldn't take it this time.
I can't do it.
I just need to get my shaking under control.
Take just one.
It's for heart disease, so one's
enough to calm your nerves.
ALPRANAX
Okay.
We don't have time, so please hurry!
Yes, sir.
Make it clean so there are no fingerprints.
CELEBRATING A BRIGHT FUTURE J KING HOLDINGS
HA YOON CHUL
LEE KYU JIN
All right. The competition starts soon.
Everyone, go to the concert hall now.
Try to relax.
Cheong A Art Festival, the
classical singing section.
Please welcome contestant
number one, Bae Ro Na, on stage.
You can do this!
- You look gorgeous!
- Let's do this!
Ma'am.
What's wrong?
It's not the right key.
THE 28TH CHEONG A ART FESTIVAL
JUDGES
It's perfect. She pulled it off flawlessly.
That was insane.
- Well done.
- Next up is...
- Thanks.
- Ha Eun Byeol.
- Oh, my.
- What happened?
I'm sorry. I didn't expect
Ro Na to pull it off.
Our deal is over now. Keep your mouth shut.
Don't worry about that.
I hope Eun Byeol doesn't get too nervous.
DON'T FORGET THAT THERE ARE ALWAYS
PEOPLE WHO ARE ON YOUR SIDE.
Don't forget that there are always
people who are on your side.
I root for you. From Yoon Chul.
- Nice!
- Jenny!
- Good job!
- Well done!
Great job, everyone.
Since everyone sang way better than usual,
this year's grand prize winner
will win by only one point.
Everyone, enjoy the festival while
the judges make their decision.
That's all.
After all my hard work...
It's all Ro Na's fault.
You did an amazing job today.
I was mind-blown.
- Here.
- Thanks.
What? Why doesn't it work?
She changed the pattern?
THE 28TH CHEONG A ART FESTIVAL
JUDGES
SCORE SHEET
JUDGES' ROOM
Have you decided...
on the grand prize winner?
Yes, we just did.
The decision was made
based on the potential...
and the tone of the voice.
Here's the final result.
Thank you very much.
- Let's hand out the prizes now.
- Yes, ma'am.
Eun Byeol, it's Mom. Are you okay?
Why did you get so nervous?
Your voice cracked a little,
but it wasn't a crucial mistake.
Don't worry too much.
I'm not so sure about that, Ms. Cheon.
I'd say it was a crucial mistake.
Why do you...
Why do you have Eun Byeol's phone?
Seok Kyung!
That was fast.
I'm winning the grand
prize as we agreed, right?
Don't be ridiculous.
I don't know who will win the grand prize.
The judges made a fair decision
based on who sang best.
A fair decision?
Ask people on the street...
if anything at Cheong A Arts
High School is ever fair.
After promising that you'd bring
me evidence so confidently,
is this all you could cook up?
The result will be announced soon.
I didn't mean to be all dramatic,
but I'll show you the evidence
that you so desperately want.
Here it is.
The evidence.
What are you talking about?
Eun Byeol had it all along.
The evidence that...
you killed her grandfather.
Why did she hold on to this?
What was she going to do with it?
I'm not interested.
What I want is the grand prize trophy.
Whether she wins the grand prize or not,
Eun Byeol is good enough to get
into Seoul University of Music.
So regardless of whose name
you find in the envelope,
just call my name.
I feel like we've finally
become family for real.
See you later, Mom.
Seo Jin.
Hey...
Where are you?
We have to announce the winner.
What did you and Seok Hoon talk about?
He congratulated me for doing well.
They'll announce the
winner soon. I have to go.
Why?
Do you think you can win the grand prize?
That will never happen.
My mom will never give the
grand prize to the likes of you.
Just like with my mom?
- What?
- Even then,
she stole that trophy from her.
Your mom stole it from my mom.
Thanks to your grandfather.
My mom won it because she deserved to.
Don't insult my mom.
And then she stabbed my mom in the neck.
Because of your mom, my mom
had her chance at college,
her trophy, and her dream stolen from her.
That's not true. My mom would never do that!
You can deny it, but everyone knows...
that my mom was much better
than Ms. Cheon even back then.
And she still is.
You lost to me, Eun Byeol.
Your dad bribed my pianist, didn't he?
You probably asked him...
to ruin my performance.
Did you want the grand prize that badly?
But I can't let you have it.
Because I have to win the
grand prize this year.
You know, right? No matter what anyone says,
you're my only daughter.
You'll win the grand prize
today too no matter what.
Trust me.
Do you mean it?
Of course, I do.
Why? You don't believe me?
Then prove it.
Prove I'm your only daughter.
Fine. What is it?
I'll do anything you want.
What must I do?
Ruin Ro Na's performance today.
Break the piano.
Bribe the pianist.
Make sure Ro Na doesn't win the grand prize.
Eun Byeol. That's...
You promised to do anything I ask.
You'll do it for me, right?
If you don't,
I'll never talk to you again.
Eun Byeol.
What's wrong?
If you let Ro Na win the grand prize,
my life will be over.
You must beat Ro Na at all costs.
Even if you have to kill her.
Stop it.
Stop it!
You lost to me, Eun Byeol.
Your dad, Seok Hoon,
and the grand prize...
are all mine.
No!
Shut it!
Eun Byeol. What are you doing?
We'll bring our director, Ms. Cheon Seo Jin,
to the stage to announce the winner.
A round of applause, please.
Classical singing. Bronze award.
Seniors from Cheong A Arts High School,
Noh Ji Ah and Cho Bo Mi.
Congratulations.
Classical singing. Silver award.
Yoo Jenny.
What? Jenny? Jenny! Jenny!
Jenny! Jenny!
Congratulations.
Jenny!
We will now announce the grand prize winner.
The grand prize winner will
be announced by the director.
The highlight of the 28th
Cheong A Art Festival.
The recipient of the grand prize,
given to the singer who has...
the most-divine voice, is...
Our director must be very nervous as well.
The winner receives a free pass
to Seoul University of Music.
The winner of the grand prize
for classical singing is?
Ms. Cheon. Please read out the name.
28TH CHEONG A ART FESTIVAL
CHEONG A ARTS HIGH SCHOOL SENIOR
BAE RO NA
Ro Na!
You're wrong, Ro Na.
I will not lose anything to you.
Not my dad, not Seok Hoon,
not the grand prize trophy.
Cheong A Arts High School senior...
BAE RO NA
What I want is the trophy.
So,
regardless of whose name is in that envelope,
you just have to say my name.
Bae Ro Na.
THE PENTHOUSE 2
Wasn't that murder?
The killer was in the school.
Seok Kyung tried to kill Ro Na!
What happened?
Tell the truth!
Seok Kyung isn't the culprit.
- Did you do this? - No!
I'm so sorry!
I'm going to protect her with my life.
Even if that means you
have to kill Bae Ro Na?
Yoon Chul, you can't do that to Ro Na.
The culprit for Ro Na's case!
Who are you?