No.
Ms. Hong.
Please stop.
Let go.
You really…
shouldn't have been born.
Never.
You scum.
Han-seo…
Damn it!
The address is
49-8, Yeonseo-dong, Sangun-gu.
Two people got shot. Please hurry.
-Ms. Hong.
-Mr. Cassano.
Vincenzo.
Are you okay?
I…
did well, didn't I?
You did.
You deserve to be my brother.
For the first time…
in my life…
I've helped someone.
Hey.
You know what to do.
Thank you…
for everything.
EPISODE 20
I paid for this private room.
I paid for your room for ten days.
Does it hurt a lot?
Now I know what it feels like…
to get shot.
Your muscles are damaged,
so you can't move your shoulder
for the time being.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
You blamed yourself all night, didn't you?
For what happened.
We were fighting in a war together,
and I happened to get shot.
It's not your fault.
Now that I've woken up,
don't worry about me,
and go finish the job.
Okay.
I'll be done within 24 hours.
After that…
You'll be leaving.
Then…
I guess this is our last night together.
I'll keep my promise.
Once you're done,
leave immediately without calling me.
Do you understand?
BABEL'S CHAIRMAN JANG MURDERS BROTHER
AND ATTEMPTS TO MURDER A LAWYER
Vincenzo.
I'm relieved that Ms. Hong is recovering.
What is this, the Wild West?
Why shoot a gun?
Mr. Park, should I get a gun, too?
I was an excellent marksman
in the military.
I bet you were the biggest clown
in your barracks at best.
Hey. Fighting is
all about mental strength.
At least he's now
officially a wanted criminal.
He has nowhere to run now.
That dirty little bastard.
We all fought against him
without giving up,
and it finally paid off.
We're not who we used to be.
Whoever messes with us
will have their hair pulled out.
Sorry.
Let them come.
I'll make sure no one leaves here
in one piece.
We should stay strong
and help the lawyers until the end.
I'll put my practice on hold for now
and fight alongside you.
I'll fight with all my might
for Mr. Cassano.
Bring it on.
How long will it take to unlock it?
It depends on the model,
but three to four hours at most.
I'll have an expert
work on it immediately.
Thank you.
And take this.
It's the Guillotine file.
Consigliere.
Discuss how best to use it
with Director Tae.
I have a copy too.
Thank you so much.
I will use it
for the justice of this country.
Rather than that,
use it to trample on your enemy.
Pardon?
Here's how a villain thinks.
Enemies I'm the least afraid of are…
politicians and government officials
who only talk about justice.
Talking about justice
doesn't bring about justice.
These are the people
that I'm most afraid of.
Pizzeria owners standing outside my house
with baseball bats
because I raised the protection money.
Keep that in mind.
I will make sure…
to follow your teaching, Consigliere.
NAME: HAN SEUNG-HYUK
CRIME: BRIBERY AND EMBEZZLEMENT
Once you sign it,
you'll be arrested, charged,
and taken into detention.
It seems like everything's finally ready.
Should I sign here?
Embarrassment is only momentary.
Staying alive is more important.
I'm going to the detention center.
Let me see.
VINCENZO
Gosh, that startled me. Goodness.
Darn it. It's so noisy.
What is it?
Let me tell you how you can survive.
Hold on.
-Excuse me for one second.
-Sure.
Go on.
Get Choi Myung-hee out
within three hours, and you'll live.
HAN SEUNG-HYUK
What are you talking about?
I won't tell you again.
Get Choi Myung-hee out
within three hours at all costs,
and you'll live.
Hey! How can I trust you?
You're going to kill me, too, aren't you?
You'd already be dead
if I wanted to kill you.
When you left the restaurant two days ago
or when you were at the driving range
yesterday.
How did you…
Hurry if you want to live.
Hold on.
Do you promise you'll spare my life?
-Yes.
-Thank you.
I'll…
Just do what I told you to do.
Don't make a mistake.
PROSECUTION SERVICE
LAW FIRM WUSANG
-What's going to happen now?
-I have no idea.
What's going on?
Can I help you?
We're from the Namdongbu Office
with a search and seizure warrant.
Open all the cabinets, please.
-Namdongbu Office?
-Really?
-Wait!
-Hold on!
You're being released.
I'm being released?
Why?
It's an order.
SEOUL NAMDONGBU DETENTION CENTER
What happened?
The Namdongbu Office
cleared you of all charges.
They concluded that you took the fall
under the threat of death
from Chairman Jang.
How did they find the evidence?
They conducted a search and seizure
this morning.
My goodness, Seung-hyuk.
What are you thinking?
This way.
VINCENZO
Get Choi Myung-hee out
within three hours, and you'll live.
What are you talking about?
I won't tell you again.
Get Choi Myung-hee out
within three hours at all costs,
and you'll live.
Hurry if you want to live.
Hold on.
Do you promise you'll spare my life?
Yes.
Congratulations on your release.
Today is your last day.
CHOI MYUNG-HEE
Han Seung-hyuk, that scumbag.
It seems like she's heading to Wusang.
Watch her from a distance.
Call me if she heads somewhere remote.
She might be meeting up
with Jang Han-seok.
Yes, sir.
1 UNREAD MESSAGE
Call this number when you're released.
How did you get out so soon?
Han Seung-hyuk sold me out to Vincenzo
to save his own ass.
I'm not surprised.
You and I shouldn't meet.
There might be a trap.
You're right.
First, go to my place
and sort out my property.
I'll text you where my laptop is
and bank passwords.
And wire five billion to your account.
Thank you.
What's your plan?
I'm going to stow away after midnight.
I'm going to Mexico.
You should also
hide somewhere far away.
Okay. Be careful.
We've unlocked it. Check the phone.
It seems like he's heading to Seocho-dong.
-You can see this too, right?
-Yes.
I can see it on my laptop as well.
Then keep me posted.
Okay.
Time to get going.
My, look at all the reporters.
-Hello.
-Hello. Nice to see you all.
Can we talk?
What do you want to know this time?
Hold on. Step aside for a moment.
There are rumors going around
about you and Jang Han-seok‚
who is on the run.
Turn off your recorders and cameras
so I can talk comfortably.
All right.
Listen up.
He was my client,
and I was his attorney. That's all.
A long time ago, at that.
But isn't it true that Wusang helped
Babel with their illegal activities?
Not Wusang.
It was Ms. Choi's personal decision.
To think how much trouble
that caused for Wusang.
Excuse me a second.
Han Seung-hyuk speaking.
Looks like you're having fun.
-What's going on?
-Who is it?
Mr. Han, this is not acceptable.
What do you mean?
You should've remained respectful to me.
I don't think you're in the position
to say that.
Go keep my brother company.
What?
Get him. Get that bastard!
Let's go.
Step back!
The Chief Prosecutor is dead.
-What?
-Two guys suddenly stabbed him.
-Were they holding a grudge?
-I'm not sure what just happened.
-Step back!
-Move!
-Take him inside.
-Step back.
Around 3:30 p.m. today,
Chief Prosecutor Han Seung-hyuk
was attacked by two men and died
in front of the Namdongbu
Prosecutor's Office.
The police are tracking down the van
that the two men disappeared in.
Based on the CCTV camera footage
and the witness statements,
the police are…
Jang Han-seok must've hired some men
as his mercenaries.
I hope Mr. Cassano
stays safe.
Mr. Nam.
No one can kill Vincenzo Cassano.
You know that.
Hello, Mr. Cho.
Are you after Chairman Jang?
Yes.
But he's disappeared from the GPS.
He must've gone underground
where there's no reception.
I think I know
where Choi Myung-hee is heading.
Where?
You finished off Han Seung-hyuk
like a scene from a movie.
I wanted to give him
the dramatic end he deserved.
I've switched the main bank account.
I've also wired some money
to the borrowed-name account for you.
Thank you. You should leave immediately.
Security!
Don't be a fool.
Are you looking for this?
How could they be so useless
when I paid a fortune?
When you're facing a predator,
it's better to hide than run.
Why are you so reckless?
I didn't know that.
I've always been a predator myself.
The money you wired to Jang Han-seok
will be used for a good cause.
It's been intercepted and sent
to a place that needs it.
You've made a fool of me
on so many levels.
That's my number-one specialty,
next to killing.
Let me just finish this.
Then you can kill me.
Aren't you…
more of a Zumba person than a beer person?
Right?
I will…
let you dance all you want.
So Ms. Choi, the CEO of Wusang,
was abducted in that car?
Yes. Her guards who were on standby
in the parking lot reported it.
Who are the abductors?
One of them hasn't been identified,
but the other is Vincenzo Cassano,
a member of the Italian Mafia.
-Why would a Mafia member…
-I'm not sure.
Anyway, Ms. Choi is the attorney
for Jang Han-seok
who is currently on the run.
And the late Han Seung-hyuk
was the former CEO of Wusang.
There's something fishy about it.
They must be related in some way.
Put out an APB on the Mafia member
and track him down along with Jang.
Also, secure footage from Namdongbu
and Ms. Choi's apartment.
Yes, sir.
Don't even try to stand up.
It'll only add to the pain.
Kill me already.
Stop messing around.
What are you going to do with me next?
I told you.
I won't let you die comfortably.
What difference does it make
if you kill me?
Think about it.
Will it bring peace to the world?
Or will it leave a meaningful message?
No way.
It makes no difference whatsoever.
Like you said, I'm just a scumbag
who was killed by another scumbag.
No matter how cleverly you kill me,
you're a scumbag like me all the same.
Not at all.
How so?
I'd love to hear how.
I am Vaisravana
who leads yakshas and rakshasas.
What are you talking about?
Are you joking?
It seems like our conversation is
making you less afraid of death.
Don't tell me this is…
You'll feel an intense pain
from beginning to end.
No.
You're going way too far.
Don't you think so, Vincenzo?
This isn't right. Didn't you say
you never harm women and children?
To me, you're not a woman.
You're just a monster…
driven by desires.
No.
This isn't right. There are other ways.
Use a gun.
Shoot me. Just shoot me!
Shoot me!
No, no. I'm sorry.
Get back here!
Vincenzo!
Mr. An, do we have a signal on Jang?
Yes, we have him again.
He's heading towards the Seobu Expressway.
It's far from where you are,
so I've sent a team to follow him.
I'll catch up soon.
Tell them to be careful
because Jang Han-seok has a gun.
And the police have put out an APB on you.
So you should move quickly.
I understand.
He's getting farther and farther away.
Step on it!
I'm going as fast as I can.
There's too many people. That's why.
That's ridiculous.
This isn't a cultivator.
We were in second gear. Sorry.
-Gosh!
-Seriously!
Damn it.
Let me switch to third gear.
We're going to lose him!
-Third. Good now?
-Good.
Good. Here we go. Third gear.
Switching to fourth gear.
Look at you guys. Why are you so down?
This isn't right for a chairman
of a conglomerate.
-How embarrassing.
-All right.
Let's get it on by the sea!
Don't resist.
You'll only be choked even harder.
Stop it, you bastard! That's enough!
Put down the knife!
-Mr. Lee!
Mr. Lee! What should we do?
-Call 911 right now.
-Okay.
Hang in there.
Help will arrive soon.
Hello? Is this 911?
I'm calling from Geumjo Port.
Someone has been stabbed. Please hurry.
That son of a bitch.
Mr. Lee.
We caught him…
right?
Yes, we did.
Don't hand him over to the police.
Make sure to punish him yourself.
Okay. Don't talk anymore.
Once Dal-rae…
is born,
I wanted…
to ask you to be her godfather.
Okay.
I'll do that. I'll be her godfather.
You…
You promised. Keep your promise.
Okay?
Of course.
I will.
Thank…
Thank you.
Mr. Lee.
Hurry!
Let me help him.
Mr. Lee, raise your right leg.
-I'll raise it, okay?
-Mr. Lee, don't close your eyes.
Hang in there.
What should we do?
No!
Don't touch it.
-Never.
-Do you even know what you're doing?
I used to be a surgical nurse.
The White Angel of Geumga-dong!
Hang in there. Don't talk to me.
Almost done. Hang in there.
That's not 911. It's the police.
See you again, Consigliere.
Thank you for everything.
Be safe.
Go on, now.
Go.
Stop the SUV. We'll fire if you don't.
-What are you doing?
-We have a patient.
-Move your car!
-What are you doing?
-Move it.
-We have a patient here!
Move your car!
-Move it!
-Someone's hurt.
Okay.
He escaped safely.
And he has Chairman Jang with him.
Things will finally come to an end.
Ms. Hong.
Mr. Lee is…
What about him?
How did you find me?
Your brother told me.
What?
Hey, do you want to hear
something interesting?
On the morning of the inauguration,
Han-seok suddenly gave me a watch
as a gift.
Okay.
And matching watches at that.
He's not the type to do that.
So I found it suspicious
and disassembled it.
Guess what I found.
An expert said that it was a tracker.
A tracker? So what did you do?
I put it in his watch without his knowing.
And I didn't wear mine.
Also, I downloaded an app
that can track him whenever I want.
It was quite expensive. Was I ripped off?
But why are you tracking him?
I'm certain that
he'll do something horrible again soon.
Then he'll run away like always.
Even when he killed his friends
in middle school,
my father sent him away
so no one could find him.
Had he been punished then,
he may not have turned out this way.
But doesn't he change watches every day?
What's the use?
That's why I put trackers in all of them.
-What?
-I tend to be foolish like that.
In the end, he was right.
He's damn useless until the very end.
By the way,
what is this toy?
I learned it from the Russian Mafia
when I visited Russia.
It's called kop'yo iskuplen'ya.
"The spear of atonement."
Do you really think
I'll atone for my sins?
I couldn't care less.
As long as you're in pain, I'm happy.
You should've just killed me
back at the port.
I always keep my word.
Do you remember everything
I've told you until now?
Wait.
I'm glad you seem to remember.
What is this?
The spear of atonement
will pierce by 5mm every 5 minutes.
You'll feel lightheaded
from all the blood loss,
and feel excruciating pain.
Around tomorrow noon,
it'll pierce your lung,
and you'll die instantly.
Vincenzo.
Aren't we both businessmen?
I have many great offers to make.
You don't need to resort
to such barbaric acts!
-Please.
-Barbaric acts?
Yes.
This world has always been barbaric.
I'll give you all the money I have.
So, please…
If that's not enough,
you can cut off one of my limbs.
Sparing me isn't that difficult, right?
It's not.
But I don't want to.
It hasn't been five minutes yet!
I've controlled it manually for now.
I'll switch it back to auto.
Vincenzo. Please.
Vincenzo, this isn't you.
Just shoot me in the head, okay?
Just shoot me! Shoot!
Please… Vincenzo.
Go apologize to your brother.
Please…
I'll keep this as a trophy.
Vincenzo…
Vincenzo.
Hey!
Just shoot me! Kill me now!
LAWYER HONG CHA-YOUNG
POWER OFF
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've lured the investigation team
to Busan.
Here. It's a Korean passport.
You must board within the next 30 minutes.
Until then, your background check
and face recognition
will be linked to that photo.
After 30 minutes,
the data will be linked to you, so hurry.
Thank you.
You should thank Director Tae, not us.
I see. Please tell him I said thank you.
If you can't come back…
do give us a call someday.
Thank you,
Let's go.
Mr. Cassano.
You shouldn't move around.
I'm okay.
I'm glad I got to see you.
You should go now.
There will be a lot of headaches for you
after I leave.
I can handle that.
Goodbye.
Be safe.
I'll get going.
Hurry.
Thank you for everything.
Goodbye, Mr. Nam.
Sir, we have no time.
It's been a month since Lawyer C,
a former Italian Mafia member
charged with kidnapping Lawyer Choi
and Babel's Chairman Jang,
has been at large.
The police inspected all domestic ports
in case he'd try to stow away,
but they have failed to find
any trace of him.
Believing the suspect to be
hiding in the country,
the police have decided to reinforce…
In our vineyard,
you can buy or lease a single row
and tend to it on the weekends.
The rows with name tags on them
are already taken.
To top it all off,
you'll be able to make wine
with grapes you grow yourself.
Our vineyard has a winery
that you can use as well.
Would you like to take a look?
-Okay.
Let's go over there, sweetie.
It's the fertilizing season.
We've weeded out the soil,
so it's quite mushy.
-Be careful.
-Okay.
LEE JIN-A
I'll try my best to make wine
out of these cheap grapes.
1 YEAR LATER
-Wasn't his kick amazing?
-I agree.
-It was a 360-degree spin.
-He's totally into it these days.
That's exactly why
you don't get good grades.
You should study more like I do.
-I'm smarter than you.
-That's not true.
-You're wrong.
-I'm smarter than you.
I got a higher score last time.
-That was once.
-Still…
But I do usually get better grades.
That's true.
But not that much.
BABEL AND ALL ITS SUBSIDIARIES
TO GO INTO RECEIVERSHIP
Gosh, they're all so boring.
-Let's go watch a movie.
-Which one?
Let's think on our way there.
Let's check out the posters there.
LAWYER HONG YU-CHAN
Currently, Sangcheon-gu
is the poorest borough in the city.
Stopping the redevelopment
around Geumga Plaza
is a flagrant decision made
by the government
that blocks your ownership rights.
I, candidate three Kim Seok-u,
will restart the redevelopment plans
and make Sangcheon-gu a wealthy borough!
Everyone!
SANGCHEON-GU'S FUTURE
KIM SEOK-U
Kim Seok-u!
-Kim Seok-u!
Are you sure it's the borough
that'll become rich?
Or…
is it you who'll become rich?
Who are you?
We're the Cassano Geumga Family.
Come on, now.
Interrupting a campaign is illegal.
Shut up.
What's illegal is
resuming the redevelopment.
We won't allow you to raze this area
to the ground.
We won't stand
for scumbags like you either.
Get rid of them, will you?
Let's go.
I don't think that's a wise decision.
No one can touch us.
Hey!
If you keep this up, I'll call the police.
Be my guest.
We're not scared of the police at all.
I'm dying to bite him.
My teeth are itching.
Ms. Hong.
We'll take care of this.
You have a trial to attend.
Don't worry. We got this.
Thank you.
-Good luck.
See you later.
Look at you.
Do you not know the strongman,
Baek Yong-gu?
Check this out.
You little…
The results of the retrial
for the murder of Hwang Deok-bae
from six years ago has come out.
He was found guilty
of attempted sexual assault,
and Oh, the accused, was found guilty
of manslaughter, not murder.
Chairwoman Seo Yeong-sun,
the former wife of Chairman Hwang,
was found guilty of negligence
despite witnessing the incident.
She has been arrested on the spot
following the trial.
This fact came to light
after Hwang Min-seong, her son,
submitted a written confession
from prison.
Look at you,
a nameless lawyer acting mighty.
Look at you, a rich, old fogey acting out.
You sly snake.
What the hell have you done to my son?
Nothing.
I just sent him some photos
of Lawyer Vincenzo Cassano.
You won't get away with this!
-You little witch.
-Move aside.
She always spews the same nonsense.
I won't see you out.
Excuse me.
Please share a few words.
-Please move aside.
-Hold on.
We have a few questions.
Please say a few words.
Be quiet!
-How do you feel?
-Are you sorry?
Please say something!
Wait!
-Please say a few words.
-Please say something!
-Are you happy with the result?
-How do you feel?
I truly am.
It's not a surprise that we won.
Is it?
-Pass.
-Go.
Good job.
Tae-ho…
DIRECTOR AN GI-SEOK
Where in the world are you, Consigliere?
I've been searching for a whole year.
What are you doing,
looking all sentimental?
Sir.
Have you yet to find Vincenzo?
No, sir. He vanished into thin air.
I'm sure he'll come back
when the time's right.
About the Guillotine file…
The prosecution wanted to do
a joint investigation,
but I turned it down.
I told them we'd do it alone.
That was a wise decision.
We must find every single one of them
and root them out.
We must.
Come in.
Right.
-Say hello.
-We already know each other.
Hi, old-looking man.
Hello, young-looking,sir.
Gosh.
What do you say
we bring him back to
the International Organized Crime Bureau?
I'd be more than happy.
Let's look for the consigliere first.
Let's do that.
Hey, can you please work?
You and your corn salad.
-Goodbye.
-Look into it immediately.
-Yes, sir.
-Right now?
-Yes.
Hello,
I'd like to pawn this tablet computer.
Goodness.
The specifications are below average.
I see many cracks as well.
I'm in need of urgent money.
Is that so?
-Dal-rae, what should I do?
-God, it's busted.
But it works just fine.
-Are you a student?
-Yes.
He's a student.
Let's take it.
Give him 180,000 won.
I'm sorry, Dal-rae.
Are you hungry?
I'll give you 200,000 won instead.
Have you gone insane?
-Here.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm sorry. Goodness.
-Here. Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-Goodbye.
-Study hard.
-I will.
-Come back to get it.
-Okay. Thank you.
Dal-rae.
Seok-do, can you wipe the shelves?
I already did it.
Do it again. Once isn't enough.
You're so pretty.
Think of Dal-rae.
Right, Dal-rae?
You're adorable.
You are indeed.
Did you miss daddy?
-Honey, she needs to eat.
-Okay.
Did you miss me?
Let's lie down.
-Goodness.
-You're so cute.
-How nice.
-What a good girl.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
It's spotless.
Why did you tell me to wipe this?
Just be nice and wipe it.
I am. Gosh.
You're doing great.
By the way, had I fully recovered,
I would've flipped that truck over.
You should be grateful
that you're even alive.
Thanks to his first aid,
the surgery was a success.
It was dangerous.
Nutria of Geumga-dong.
Ma'am, this piano isn't working.
Oh, don't use that one. It's broken.
Don't play on this one.
Use the one behind you.
-Okay.
-Good.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
MARRIAGE PROPOSAL TEMPLE
NANYAK TEMPLE
-From black hair to white hair
Congratulations.
From black hair to white hair
We are all bound to meet again by fate.
I will look forward to that day.
I have a question to ask you
before I leave.
Sure.
I don't think I can give up
doing what I do.
I can't do what's right either.
Eventually, I'll end up returning
to my place.
I will feel regret and anguish
for the rest of my life.
Among the Four Heavenly Kings,
there's a king named Vaisravana.
It's the scary face you see
when you enter a temple.
Vaisravana keeps yakshas
and rakshasas in check
and protects Buddha's ways and all humans.
Since you have committed many sins,
you won't be able to become like Buddha
no matter how hard you try.
However, you can fight for the people
alongside the yakshas and the rakshasas.
You may not become like Buddha,
but you will get compliments from him
from time to time.
What if
you can never return to Korea?
I can visit you instead.
-The bridge of birds.
-What?
You know, on July 7.
Magpies and crows form a bridge
so that Gyeon-u and Ung-nyeo can meet.
It's Jik-nyeo, not Ung-nyeo.
I see.
But Mr. Nam said…
Then…
in our case, Inzaghi and its friends
could form a bridge for us.
You're right. Inzaghi.
Those pigeons are quite strong.
Then it'll be a bridge of pigeons.
I'm not joking.
I'll return like Gyeon-u did.
Okay.
I'm serious.
-Ms. Hong.
-What?
Who was Ung-nyeo then?
Great job.
I feel great.
It's Ms. Oh's death anniversary tomorrow.
I'm glad I could give her a gift.
I'm sure she's elated.
By the way,
there's something on your desk.
FRIENDS ARE LIKE ONE SOUL IN TWO BODIES
Right. This too.
What is this?
CELEBRATION OF KOREA AND ITALY'S
DIPLOMATIC RELATIONS
Do you want to go with me tomorrow?
But I'll be attending
a paper airplane competition tomorrow.
See?
You can do it, Edward.
Good.
I see.
CELEBRATION OF KOREA AND ITALY'S
DIPLOMATIC RELATIONS
It's been a while, Ambassador Sponza.
War and art are best observed
from a distance.
Good evening, miss.
Have you been well?
How did you get here?
I sneaked in with the Italian delegation.
I'll be leaving tomorrow.
Are you only able to come
during an event like this?
Yes. Just for a day.
But…
I'll invite you to my island.
Your island?
You mean the island in the postcard?
I bought a deserted island near Malta.
I named it myself as well. Pagliuzza.
In Korean, it means "straws."
You must've spent all your money on that.
I have a bit left.
Thanks for letting me hide the gold.
I was truly relieved
that you had that spot in your house.
Is that where you're living?
Yes.
The Cassano family settled there.
In secret, of course.
Are you their boss now?
You're a boss now, not a consigliere?
The island has many purposes.
It's a refuge for exhausted fighters,
a hideout for your loved ones,
and a place of healing.
Can I go there as well?
Yes.
I've set aside a room for you.
No way.
I can't wait to go there.
I've missed you a lot.
Me too.
You've always been on my mind
ever since I left.
That's hard to believe.
Do you believe me now?
Villains never break up
because they're tenacious…
even when they love.
Two days ago, I used three Luciano
family members as manure for the vineyard
and took over the olive plantations
in Malta.
I'm still a villain
and couldn't care less about justice.
Justice is weak and empty.
One cannot win against any villains
with justice alone.
If merciless justice exists,
I am willing to yield to it.
Even villains long to live
in a peaceful world.
However, since that's impossible,
I've taken up a new hobby.
Getting rid of garbage.
If I don't do that, people will die
buried underneath the garbage.
There's one last thing I'd like to say
from a villain's perspective.
Evil is…
prevalen and vehement.
SPECIAL THANKS TO CHA SOON-BAE,
KIM SUNG-CHEOL, AND JEON GUK-HYANG
THE END
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim