♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 28=
What about you?
I'm just going to die.
I thought you would give it a try.
Well.
You saved my granddaughter,
and I'm indebted to you.
You don't have to risk your life.
That means
I've done whatever I should?
Yes, you have.
All right. Fulfill your promise.
Two thousand Gold Soul Coins.
I don't have the money.
As I live here,
whatever I eat and use,
it's sent by the royal family.
I don't have money.
Then why did you promise me?
I wanted to save Yan Yan at that time,
so I just made a promise.
Then...
All right.
The second condition.
Help me find the Grand Soul Land Master
behind Cang Hui School.
You mean...
You suspected that Shi Nian
who is in the Mind Branch
has controlled Hao Tian Soul Master?
That's right.
No way.
What do you mean?
A Grand Soul Land Master
is someone
who sees through
the nature of Martial Soul.
Unless
they meet someone who is in the Mind Branch
with Nine Soul Rings.
Otherwise,
they couldn't be controlled.
So, if Hao Tian Soul Master
really stands behind Cang Hui School,
he won't be affected by the Mind Branch.
You're right.
Then why didn't you mention it
when you promised me?
I was eager to save someone.
I just made a promise.
So...
You didn't keep either of your promises.
No matter what,
it's still a good ending.
You...
As a Grand Soul Land Master
with Nine Soul Rings,
you can't even keep your promises.
What promise?
I've been staying in this cave
and have rarely talked to people,
how could I know about
keeping promises?
I only know how to make poison here.
You...
What's wrong?
Let's go, Wu.
Let's go back to the school.
Wait.
Now what?
I can't give you 2,000 Gold Soul Coins.
But I have another way
to repay you.
It depends
on how capable you are.
A valley within a mountain?
Initially, this was
also a mountain.
Then how did this valley
take shape?
Many years ago,
a Grand Soul Land Master
with Nine Soul Rings
fought a battle
with Martial Soul Hall here.
Someone crushed the peak
and made this valley.
Such a big valley
was left by the battle?
How powerful were the Soul Masters fighting?
The Grand Soul Land Master
with Nine Soul Rings.
There was more than one.
Who were they?
I have no idea.
At that time,
I only had Seven Soul Rings.
I only dared to come closer
long after the battle had ended.
When I came here,
I realised
that many herbs were growing here.
Either for making poison or for curing it,
the herbs were quite precious.
So, I decided to stay here
to pursue my studies.
Finally, I've got Nine Soul Rings.
Then...
What does it have to do with the payment?
Brother, look.
There are so many herbs.
So, these herbs are the payment?
Then how many should we pluck
to make up 2,000 Gold Soul Coins?
I don't sell herbs.
How can I know?
You...
Brother, forget it.
Since we're already here,
let's just pluck some.
Actually, there is a barrier.
Behind it,
there is
a space that I cannot enter.
The space behind it
might have something more precious
than the herbs you see here.
There might be some unknown danger,
or nothing at all.
It feels cool.
There might really be something inside.
But why don't you enter?
I've tried many times,
but still fail to enter it.
Can't enter it?
(Tang San.)
(Use your Blue Silver Plant.)
Even I with Nine Soul Rings can't enter it.
I think you two...
They just entered it?
This...
How did we reach here suddenly?
This is...
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum?
Is this a herb?
This isn't just a normal herb.
It's a premium herb.
Premium?
A magical herb that contains Soul Power.
Wait, this is...
Eight Petal Fairy Orchid?
Why are these all premium herbs?
What kind of place is this?
I have no idea, either.
I only remember that I was feeling dizzy
and then I got here.
It's so beautiful.
I have been here
in my dream.
Dream?
In your dream,
does this shining circle exist too?
Yes.
Ever since childhood, I've been
having the same dream.
I dreamt of this place.
And then?
There was a woman's voice
calling my name in the dream.
Woman's voice?
I didn't hear it.
I can't believe
this place actually exists.
But why did I dream of this place?
It sounds so magical.
Did the Blue Silver Plant in your dream
shine too?
It didn't.
But the surroundings looked just the same.
Maybe, this light is the key.
Wu, we're up in the air now.
Wu, are you all right?
Finally you're here, Tang San.
(This is the voice in my dream.)
Who are you?
I'm your mother.
I know you have questions,
but I can't hear them.
I don't believe it.
My dad has never told me anything
about my mother.
I don't believe you.
Wu, let's go.
Before I passed away,
I hid the power of Blue Silver Plant
in your heart.
That's why you dreamt of this place.
Don't lie to me.
Don't lie to me with this matter!
On the day of your birth,
when I was hugging you,
you were so tiny and soft.
I brought you to this world,
but I didn't fulfill my responsibility
as a mother.
I didn't get the chance
to hug you more
or watch you growing up.
That's my greatest regret.
I'll never
forgive myself.
Son,
I'm sorry.
I owe you a lot.
How old are you now?
Have you grown up?
I told your father
to hide everything about me.
If you don't become a Soul Master,
if you don't practice the Xuan Tian Records,
then you won't be here
and hear what I've just said.
You'll live your life
in peace.
Isn't that good too?
Since you're here,
it proves
that you have potential.
You're my hope.
I don't get it.
I left the Xuan Tian Records to you.
My death
was related to it.
The day when you were born,
Chief Qian Xun Ji
led the other Soul Masters
from Martial Soul Hall
to kill me.
There were two reasons.
One, my real identity.
You don't need to know for now.
When you're ready,
your dad will tell you.
The second reason
was the Xuan Tian Records.
For a thousand years in Douluo Continent,
the Soul Master system has been so strong
that Soul Masters and Souls Beasts
are irreconcilable.
They will go to war one day.
Xuan Tian Records
could be another way of training.
It's another type of power
that no longer requires Martial Soul.
Replacing the Soul Masters?
If it really succeeds,
then Soul Masters will be in the past,
and Martial Soul Hall
will vanish too.
So Chief Qian Xun Ji of Martial Soul Hall
wouldn't spare me.
Unfortunately,
Your dad and I
failed to learn
the Xuan Tian Records.
So we suspected
that someone has to master the Xuan Tian Records
and use it as the base,
and then train their Soul Skills
and become a Soul Master.
Only then can he fully utilise
the power of the Xuan Tian Records.
So,
since you're here,
it proves
that this is the right way.
Telling you the truth
doesn't mean I want you to take revenge.
It's just the opposite.
I hope you won't have hatred
in your heart.
You have your own mission and future.
Don't let hatred
blind you
and ruin your life.
My only wish
is that you can live well,
and advance your Soul Skills
and your practice of the Xuan Tian Records
to the greatest extent.
And then find a way
that Soul Masters won't
depend on Martial Souls anymore.
The future of Douluo Continent
lies in your hand.
Unfortunately,
I won't be able to witness it.
Tang San.
I gave you your name.
Three give birth to everything.
It's simple yet hopeful.
At the same time, I was a bit selfish.
Your dad, you, and I,
the three of us would make a family.
When you were born,
it was the happiest moment in my life.
Your dad and I
would have a meaning in our lives from then on.
I have almost a thousand,
or even ten thousand things to tell you.
I wish to give you everything.
But my path
has come to an end.
I'm sorry, my son.
I'm sorry.
In this interspace that I've created,
I've left some herbs for you.
I guess you must have seen them
on your way here.
Maybe these herbs
can help you in the future.
Also,
this divine herb above the premium
and Ice Fire Mouth Spring
are my real gifts for you.
This is Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
This flower feeds on love,
and is extremely useful.
Before I died,
I had hidden all my Soul Power
in this flower.
I hope it can help you become powerful.
Live well.
This is Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
It can help you to absorb
the Soul Beast that is
beyond your capacity.
Actually, I want to give you
my company
and the warmth of a family.
But I can't do it.
These gifts, this power,
I hope they can protect you.
Mom, I don't want anything.
I just want you to come back!
I don't want anything else.
I used up my last power
to create this interspace.
Apart from you,
no one can enter here.
Not even your father.
I couldn't imagine
how strong his hatred
towards Martial Soul Hall would be
after my death.
I hope you can accompany him.
Don't let him fall into the abyss of revenge
or lose his humanity.
Cang Hui School.
Revenge on Martial Soul Hall.
Son,
there's something I must tell you.
You're my most beloved one
in this world.
You must be healthy and happy.
Learn to be kind.
Don't be afraid of hardship.
My heart
will always be with you.
Tang San.
I really wish to see you.
Goodbye.
No! Mom!
I'm here.
Mom!
He saved my life?
Then how should I repay his kindness?
I brought the two of them
to the Dream Valley.
I didn't expect
they would really enter it
to look for treasures within.
Impossible.
We've tried so many times
and we still failed to enter.
Yes, I'm curious too.
Clearly, you've locked them up.
They are my saviours!
How is that possible?
Why should I lock them up?
I wasn't lying.
Find them back.
I can't do anything
if they don't come out.
Since your poison is cured now,
it doesn't matter
if they are coming back or not.
Besides, I'm not close to them.
But they are my friends!
Just find new ones.
Actually,
we're not merely friends.
We treat each other like old friends
and are considering getting married.
What?
Maybe...
Maybe he'll become your grandson-in-law.
If you don't find him,
I can't live anymore!
This...
That brat.
Don't cry.
Don't cry. I'll look for him.
I think I fell asleep.
This spring looks magical.
When did it appear?
Brother.
What happened?
Are you all right?
This is my mom.
You mean the voice in your dream?
She left this place
for me.
The voice in my dream,
it was her calling me.
Now I know.
She has been guiding me to this place.
Guiding you here?
Did you see her?
She's gone.
Wu,
do you know?
Ever since young,
other kids have been accompanied
by their mothers.
Except me.
That's why I really wish...
No.
I was very much eager
to know things about my mom.
But all this time,
my dad hasn't told me anything.
In order to know
my mom's Martial Soul,
I purposely went
to the Martial Soul Awakening Rite.
When I knew that I have Twin Martial Souls,
that I'm so lucky to have inherited
both my parents' Martial Souls,
I knew I have to work harder.
Having undergone extreme hardships,
no matter how difficult it is,
I'll never give up.
Because I remember
what my dad told me.
Remember, in the future,
to use the Hammer on your left hand
to protect the Plant on your right hand.
Always.
I have to be like my dad
and always protect my mom.
Brother.
Actually, our looks
are the combination of our parents.
So, you somehow look
like your mom.
I'll show you if you don't believe it.
Look.
Over here.
You look like Uncle Tang.
So,
here!
It should look like your mom.
Let's go out in a while.
Your Martial Soul is gone too.
We should hurry and think of a way.
It's strange.
After I woke up,
I can feel the Soul Power
running within my body.
Not only my Martial Soul has been recovered,
but my Soul Power is also full.
I feel like
I can advance to Quadruple Soul Rings.
My Soul Power is full too.
I'm ready to advance.
How did that happen?
Probably Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet
transferred the Soul Power to you.
This is...
It's a premium herb.
My mom left her Soul Power
in it.
Then why did she give it to me?
That's great.
As long as you can recover, it's great.
It's strange. I feel
that I'm connected to this flower.
As though
it's protecting me.
This spring
is called Ice Fire Mouth Spring.
It's my mom's gift as well.
Ice Fire Mouth Spring?
The magical spring in the legend?
I heard that it can help
Soul Masters to absorb
Soul Rings beyond their limits.
But I also heard
that after the spring is absorbed,
it'll disappear.
So I only have one chance?
Yes.
This was formed by my mom's energy.
I can't bear to absorb it.
Oh, right.
This flower,
you should keep it.
You're the first person who touched it.
This flower will be just like me,
accompanying you forever.
Let's stay for a while before we leave.
Before we go,
remember to grab some premium herbs.
Brother,
how do we get out now?
Hold my hand.
We're back.
You're poisoned?
Both of you finally came out?
What's inside?
Nothing much.
Fine.
Follow me back
and discuss your marriage.
Go!
Marriage?
I was just joking around.
How could you joke about that?
Because he saved my life!
What does it have to do with this?
I know you well.
If I hadn't said so,
would you have gone out and looked for him?
You little girl.
But, he's quite cute.
Sounds good if we really get married.
Are you being serious this time?
I'm serious! How about
I prove it to you?
How?
I'll kiss him.
No way!
Why not?
I was just joking.
Don't be holding the herbs.
Here, put them in the box.
There is someone I like.
I won't take Tang San away from you.
Who do you like?
What will you do after I tell you about it?
Catch him back to marry you.
Then I surely won't tell you.
Why would I have
such a disobedient granddaughter like you?
I learnt that from you!
What are you looking at?
Hurry and go back.
Go.
Senior.
I want to make a deal with you again.
I'll cure your poison,
and you help our school
to get into the final.
Cure my poison?
How?
I only need this Octa Dark Frost.
Where did you get it?
The interspace.
You just came
and easily found
the interspace.
You even
got so many premium herbs.
What's the use of this herb?
Don't touch!
What's wrong?
It's the most poisonous herb.
What are you going to do with it?
Cure your grandfather's poison.
Isn't this the most poisonous herb?
Octa Dark Frost
can gather all the poisons
in the body,
and unleash
its own poison.
Then how will it cure him?
I was concerned
that the poison in my body
is changing all the time.
With this, the poison will be fixed.
With my ability as Venom Soul Master,
it's easy to cure the poison.
Kid,
this is great.
You're smart
to think
of counteracting one poison with another.
I'll take this gift.
Senior, let me be frank.
This isn't a gift.
It's a deal.
Help your school to enter the final?
That's right.
But I can't fight for you
in the School Contest.
We can handle
the contest.
But whatever that is beyond the contest,
we need your help.
But...
I don't have 2,000 Gold Soul Coins.
We can solve
the money problem ourselves.
Great.
All right, you can go back first.
After I've cured the poison,
I'll look for you.
Wu, let's go.
I swear, I won't kiss him.
Both of you have come back?
You're back?
Come. Let's talk along the way.
We were going to look for you.
I've also brought gifts for you all.
Gifts?
Weren't you captured?
Sounds like you were on a vacation.
Brother Dai, this is yours.
I'm glad that you're back.
You don't need to bring a gift for me.
Open and see.
Have a look.
It feels like he's proposing to you.
Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum!
Premium herb.
It's super effective
for your Strength Type Martial Soul.
It suits you very much!
After eating it,
you should be able
to advance to Quadruple Soul Rings.
But...
How should I eat this?
First the stamen, then the petals.
Don't eat the rhizome.
Thank you.
Don't mention it.
Brother San, what about me?
There you go.
My goodness.
Eight Petal Fairy Orchid.
Eight Petal Fairy Orchid is mild.
It suits
Food Branch Soul Masters like you.
This suits you
more than Rare Powerful Chrysanthemum does.
These two are premium herbs.
Did you unearth
Venom Soul Master's treasure?
Daffodil Jade Beauty
suits your Speed Type Martial Soul.
Thank you.
Hong Jun.
Let me see.
Rong Rong.
Mine? Thank you.
Yours is good.
Mine is cooked?
Cockscomb Phoenix Flower
can refine your flame,
empower your flame power,
and avoid loss of control.
Thank you, Brother San.
Mine is shining.
Silk Woven Tulip
purifies the essence. It's suitable
for Support Branch Martial Souls to advance.
This is so great!
If Wu weren't here,
I would just give you a kiss.
Brother San must have stolen
Venom Soul Master's treasure.
We should hurry and eat them,
so that he can't have any evidence.
We can't let him have any chance
to grab them away.
Let's go.
She's right.
She's got a point.
Ma Hong Jun, follow me.
Come.
Have a seat.
What's the matter?
It's your first time eating
this kind of premium herb, right?
Yes.
Don't you also think
this moment is very important?
I think
we should eat them together,
so there is a sense of ritual.
I'm also a person
who pays attention to the sense of ritual.
Let me see
how we can make it even better.
Wait.
There's no need.
We eat half of our herbs,
and we take the remaining part
to cook with our food.
I really like you,
little brother!
You have a point. I'll go to get the pot.
Wait.
If we add some big sausages
and Weeping Forsythia,
would it enhance
the sense of ritual?
That's right.
That's even better.
I'll make them now.
Wait!
What now?
Lend me
your pen and paper.
Pen and paper.
Here. What are these for?
We should sketch it out before we eat.
We don't know if we'll have
such a chance again
to eat this precious item.
We should draw it out as a memento.
Drawing before eating?
I heard that it's quite famous
in Tian Dou City.
Right.
Draw it.
What are you doing here?
Hurry and get the pot!
All right!
Master. Headmaster.
Tang San, you're back?
It's good that you're back. How are you?
Did Venom Soul Master do anything to you?
No.
Master,
you brought me
into the world of Soul Masters.
I've never given you any gifts.
This is for you.
Grade Nine Purple Mushroom?
Isn't your Soul Power inherently weak,
and you can't advance to Triple Soul Rings?
Grade Nine Purple Mushroom
is good for expanding limits.
Maybe this might help.
This suits you.
This premium herb was extinct long ago.
Headmaster, I'm not sure
which premium herb
suits you and Teacher Liu.
How about you pick it yourself?
Are there all premium herbs?
We can sell the rest to earn some money.
Let's see
if we can gather 2,000 Gold Soul Coins.
Venom Soul Master gave these to you?
He thanked me for curing his poison.
Now we have a chance to take part in the contest.
I'll talk to Liu Er Long now.
She knows a lot of people.
These are great things.
Here.
What's going on?
Venom Soul Master won't have
so many premium herbs.
Insofar as his character is concerned,
it's impossible
that he gave them all to you.
He brought me and Wu
to the Dream Valley.
I heard
the voice in my dream again there.
She asked me to use Blue Silver Plant.
It was strange
that I was the only one
who could hear the voice.
So I used my Blue Silver Plant.
Wu and I
entered the interspace.
These herbs
were collected there.
The interspace?
The interspace can only be created
by a few Grand Soul Land Masters.
Without a special method,
no one can enter or leave.
Your Blue Silver Plant was the key
to open up the entrance
of the interspace.
In that case, the interspace
is especially meant for you.
Yes.
My mom left it to me.
I was holding Wu's hand at that time,
so
we got in together.
But my mom said
that except me, no one else can enter.
Not even my dad.
Have you seen your mother?
No.
The day when I was born,
my mom was
killed by Chief Qian Xun Ji
and his men from Martial Soul Hall.
Before she died,
she left a message to me.
So I knew the reason why she had been killed.
Master.
You said only a few Grand Soul Land Masters
can create the interspace.
Was my mom
a Grand Soul Land Master?
I'm not sure about that.
There are not many Grand Soul Land Masters.
Young female Grand Soul Land Masters
are even rarer.
Maybe you can get some information
from the library in Martial Soul Hall.
Those from Martial Soul Hall
who tried to kill my mom,
I won't let any of them go.
But Qian Xun Ji
was the former chief of Martial Soul Hall.
He's dead.
Dead?
How?
Severe injuries.
Does he still have other family members?
Bi Bi Dong, her wife,
is the present chief.
They have a daughter, Qian Ren Xue.
But they
have nothing to do with your mother's death.
Qian Xun Ji was the mastermind.
When he tried to kill my mom,
did he think about her child?
Her husband!
If one day,
I meet those people
from Martial Soul Hall,
I...
I'm not sure
if I'll act rationally.
Kid,
hatred shouldn't be spread.
You shouldn't hate
everyone from Martial Soul Hall.
Your mother wouldn't hope
that you live with hatred forever.
Telling you the truth
doesn't mean I want you to take revenge.
It's just the opposite.
I hope you won't have hatred in your heart.
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪