♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 29=
(The reason why I tell you the truth)
(is not for you to take revenge.)
(Instead,)
(I hope that you won't keep
the grudge in your heart.)
(You have your own goal and mission.)
(Never let hatred blind your eyes)
(and ruin your life.)
However, for those from Martial Soul Hall
who have threatened to kill my mom back then,
I'll never let even a single one off.
Master.
Regarding my parents,
is there anything else I don't know?
If you know,
please tell me.
It'd be better
for you not to know that.
At least you wouldn't suffer.
Master, you've told me before
that misery loves to attach to strong people.
The moment when we embrace misery,
we'll reflect on ourselves.
Regardless of the consequence,
I'll surely keep moving forward,
and never be defeated.
Master, I'm ready.
Tell me, please.
Well.
Your father was
the right-hand man of Qian Xun Ji.
He was a robust invincible
and was once my idol.
After the Golden Iron Triangle
was disbanded,
I followed after your father
and serviced under Martial Soul Mall.
I dedicated myself to studying
Mutated Martial Soul.
That's why when we were
in Shi Lan Ke School
after Wu was poisoned by Bu Le,
you said you'd go to Martial Soul Hall
for the antidote.
What should we do
if he doesn't appear tomorrow?
Wu can't wait for so long.
If he doesn't appear after three days,
I'll go to Martial Soul Hall.
Martial Soul Hall?
Why?
Don't ask.
I know what to do.
Yes.
When I was in Martial Soul Hall,
I was doing the core research
on Mutant Soul.
After your father left
Martial Soul Hall,
he was chased by Qian Xun Ji.
Your father was defeated,
and since then no news was heard
about him.
I left Martial Soul Hall, too.
The research on Mutant Soul
was terminated.
Matters regarding the details behind
and your mother
were highly confidential
to Martial Soul Hall.
What happened next?
After Qian Xun Ji died,
his wife, Bi Bi Dong
succeeded to the throne.
I haven't bothered about
Martial Soul Hall since then.
Until the appearance
of Mutant Soul's drug
at Nightfire Village,
I doubted that
the mastermind behind Ye Zhi Qiu
is related to Martial Soul Hall.
However, when I found out
that Hu Lie Na was also investigating
the drug of Mutant Soul,
I dispelled my doubts.
Master,
for now, I can confirm that
the mastermind behind
the case of Mutant Soul
is my father.
Firstly,
he has once worked under
Martial Soul Hall
and he's able to access
the drug research of Mutant Soul.
Secondly,
he would act against Martial Soul Hall
to revenge for my mother.
Besides, Ye Zhi Qiu mentioned that
The Hao Tian Soul Master
used the drug of Mutant Soul
to manipulate many Soul Masters
to work for him.
If the Mutant Soul Masters of
the entire Douluo Continent
collaborated to revolt Martial Soul Hall,
it'd be a disaster.
What's your next plan?
Enter the final and stop him.
And then?
I want to tell him that
we'll never forget the grudge,
however, we couldn't get the innocent involved.
I want to wake him up.
The entire Martial Soul Hall is not our enemy.
I'll surely help you to fight till the final
and let the entire Douluo Continent
witness your excellence.
No.
Let the Douluo Continent
witness the excellence of our Shi Lan Ke School.
Wu,
do you want to eat with us?
No need.
Didn't
Tang San prepare for you?
I have this.
What kind of premium herb is this?
Tang San said
it's Lovesick Heartbroken Scarlet.
Don't you eat it?
Wu.
You've been absent-minded
since you came back.
What's wrong?
Is there anything bothering you?
Du Gu Yan said she liked Tang San.
Then?
She was just kidding.
Luckily.
But
I find myself strange.
What do you mean?
I'm very nervous.
I'm upset that Du Gu Yan likes Tang San.
I'm confused now.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
Look at her,
what a silly girl.
Because you like Tang San.
Like?
But I just take him as my brother.
Give it a try
to verify your thoughts.
How to try?
Kiss him
and you'll know
what's your feeling towards him.
Are her words true?
I think
this method is kind of aggressive,
but
it may work.
How did Brother Dai and you kiss?
Both of you had kissed?
Dai Mu Bai and you?
-When did it happen?
-We didn't.
We rarely met with each other before.
It was just because of the marriage contract...
Marriage contract?
Stay aside.
Don't go.
Tell me what happened.
Go away.
Sister Qing.
Please tell me.
Don't be so petty.
I'll give you my premium herb.
I don't want it.
Kiss him
and I'll know?
Sister Qing.
Stop annoying me. Go away.
Tell me, please.
How's it, Master?
Grade Nine Purple Mushroom
has heightened my limit.
Tang San, I think
I'm able to obtain
Triple Soul Rings at last.
Congratulations.
Since you've broken through
this bottleneck,
you must be able to reach a higher level.
That's not important to me.
But all of you, you're my hope.
Thank you, Master.
It seems both of you have a great relationship.
Elder.
When did you come?
I just arrived.
Have a seat.
Elder,
why are you not wearing
the jade pendant?
I took it off
since I don't need it anymore.
Is the poison resolved?
This time,
I owe you a favour.
In your coming contest,
I'll help you to settle your opponents
secretly.
I guarantee you to go straight to the final
without battling.
This...
Of course.
I won't touch
Tian Dou royals.
Elder,
aren't you using dirty tricks?
Can you bite your tongue?
Please don't, Elder.
Please don't do that.
If there's someone
who tries to harm us secretly,
it'll be great
if you can protect us secretly.
Please don't do
any other things.
Don't blame me
if you lose.
Of course.
We want a fair contest.
We'll accept it regardless of its consequences.
Don't you want to enter the final?
I prefer to battle till the end
by myself.
Isn't he silly?
Refuse to take shortcuts.
Luckily, you're not
my grandson-in-law.
Well.
I'm going to Cang Hui School now.
Do you want to follow?
Why are you going there?
To revenge.
Those bastards
poisoned my granddaughter and me.
Elder, please listen to me.
I'm going to tell you about this.
Could you please refrain from revenge?
And also, could you please
wear the jade pendant again?
Why?
Let's not reveal
that the poison has been rectified.
I'm afraid that Cang Hui will
think of new tricks
after knowing this.
Could we wait and see
how Cang Hui is going
to deal with you?
Don't you know
the Grand Soul Land Master behind them?
Just ask him directly.
I can't meet him now.
But I really want to know
what his plan is.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
By the way,
do you still need
premium herbs?
They are useless for me
since I've obtained Six Soul Rings.
Soul Masters would have
to depend on themselves
as they reach higher levels.
That's right.
Keep this in mind.
Of course,
depending on Tian Dou royals,
you'll get the resources faster.
Don't need to remember this.
I heard that
tomorrow is the last day for registration.
You have to enroll
as soon as possible.
Don't worry.
After selling these premium herbs,
we'll earn more than
2,000 Gold Soul Coins.
Well.
I'm leaving then.
Little Venom,
find me at the cave if anything happens.
Little Venom?
Impregnable to poisons and
the matter of mezzanine,
doesn't this name suit you just well?
I'm off.
Take care.
Thank you.
Master told me that
he has obtained Triple Soul Rings.
Sister Qing and Rong Rong said
their Soul Power has brimmed.
They can ascend one level.
That's great.
The strength of our school
has been upgraded by leaps and bounds.
What's wrong?
Is there anything on my face?
Have you washed your face?
I did wash it this morning.
Now it's nighttime.
Do you
want to clean your lips?
Clean my mouth?
Done.
Clean it properly.
Do it again.
Why? Is it dirty?
Brother San.
Hong Jun?
Both my Soul Power and Ou Si Ke 's have brimmed.
Brother Dai is able to obtain
the fourth Soul Rings too.
All of us have upgraded.
That's great.
Sister Wu.
What are you doing here?
She asked me to clean my mouth.
Clean your mouth?
Why?
I don't know.
I'm going to tell Headmaster about this.
You go first.
Tang San.
Headmaster?
Your Soul Power has brimmed,
why are you pacing about it?
Forget about that.
Sister Qing.
How's Wu going?
She might succeed.
Let's go and check them out.
Check?
No way.
Sister Qing.
It's not good.
It's nothing.
Well,
I'll use Qibao Amber Pagoda
to amplify our speed.
Then, we might be able to escape
once they found us.
Sister Qing.
Don't you think
the pagoda looks different?
Can Qibao Amber Pagoda
transform?
I have no idea.
I've never seen this before.
Is it broken?
Try to initiate it.
Power Boost! Speed Boost!
Luckily,
it's still in good condition.
Come on.
Let's go and check them out.
No way.
Don't go.
Let's go.
I'll go by myself then.
I'm going now.
I'm going to guard Rong Rong.
I don't mean to see them.
Even premium herbs can't be sold?
It's the not case.
All of them said
they would buy it two days later.
But tomorrow is the last day for registration.
I've asked people around me.
It's the order of Prince Xue Xing.
They purposely do it on these two days.
Does that mean we can't register?
No rush.
Let's find other ways.
If we can't think of any,
let's go and meet the Crown Prince, Xue Qing He.
But Yu Tian Heng mentioned that
the Crown Prince refuses
to meet people recently.
We have to try anyhow.
Everything will be okay.
Boss Lander, let's go now.
Gang.
You just took
the Grade Nine Purple Mushroom.
You'd better not move around.
I'll go with Boss Lander.
Don't worry.
If the Crown Prince refuses to meet us,
I'll burn his place into ashes.
You're making me
more worried.
Are you worrying about me?
The Crown Prince, I mean.
Look at him. He's lying again.
No worries.
I'll guard her well.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Do you want me to send you back first?
So that you could take a good rest.
I'm fine.
I can walk slowly.
Golden Iron Triangle should help each other.
Let's go.
The moonlight is nice.
I'm going to take a moonlight bath.
How come there's moonlight on this cloudy day?
-Hurry up.
-I'll wait for you outside.
Okay.
Watch out.
Can we...
Can we move faster?
Of course.
This way. Let's take a shortcut.
Isn't this route longer?
No.
Brother San.
I know this place well. I won't be wrong.
Are you thirsty?
Look at you.
Why are you drinking so fast?
Are you really thirsty?
Oh gosh.
Could Headmaster settle it?
Rong Rong!
Rong Rong?
What happened?
Just now, when Rong Rong and I
came to see you,
she was captured.
Headmaster is chasing them now.
She was captured? Who did this?
The person was too fast.
I can't see his face.
In which direction did he go?
That way.
What's the sound just now?
Rong Rong was captured.
Who was captured?
It's Rong Rong.
I heard someone shouting just now.
What happened?
Rong Rong was captured!
Rong Rong was cap...
Rong Rong!
Stop there.
Headmaster, are you all right?
Is the sword which pointed at you
a Soul Skill?
It's Tool Soul which uses a sword
as the main body
and the strength is extremely powerful.
This person is much beyond our level.
Could he be a Grand Soul Land Master?
I don't think so.
The Grand Soul Land Master
whose Martial Soul is a sword
is a member of Qibao Amber Clan.
It's impossible for him
to take Rong Rong away.
Qibao Amber Clan?
A member of Qibao Amber Clan...
Let me off!
Do you know who I am?
How dare you!
You scoundrel!
Stop it.
I thrash you.
Enough.
I want to thrash you.
Grandpa Sword?
Your fists are really powerful.
It's painful.
Why did you capture me?
Come here.
Headmaster, what's wrong?
Here.
Sit down.
Headmaster,
why did you bring us back?
Everyone is searching for Rong Rong.
That's right.
I've told Master and Er Long
to inform the branch of Qibao Amber Clan
in Tian Dou City.
Qibao Amber Clan is
one of the three elders
and has many mentees.
I hope that they will collaborate
to find her whereabouts.
We should search together, shouldn't we?
He's right.
No rush.
You have another task.
Task?
What's it?
This
is the entry permit of the auction
in Tian Dou City.
Auction?
I was just informed that
the auction will be held on
tomorrow morning.
I have commissioned the auction
of those premium herbs.
Both of you, get ready to set off
and take this permit to collect money.
We may get to register in time.
Let's proceed separately.
But Headmaster...
Tang San,
you're discreet.
As for Wu,
you know well about
the effects of those herbs.
I'd only rest assured to hand the task
to both of you.
How about Rong Rong?
Don't worry.
We'll surely find Rong Rong back
and participate in the contest together.
Therefore,
this is crucial.
Do you get me?
I don't.
Why did you bring me here?
Rong Rong.
Send me back to school now.
Listen to me.
Please.
Rong Rong!
Are they your schoolmates?
They're coming for me.
I have to go now.
No, Rong Rong.
Let's go back and meet the chief.
He'll tell you
everything.
The teachers of Shi Lan Ke came just now,
saying that our young mistress
has gone missing.
They asked for our help.
Just send some people
to pretend that we help them.
Don't leak the secret.
Yes.
Why don't you let me return to school?
Why did you
bring me back here?
It's the chief's order.
Impossible.
It was him who asked me
to go to Shi Lan Ke School.
How could it be?
Grandpa Sword,
are you involved
in the rebellion of the clan,
for which
you took me back as the hostage?
What are you saying?
Oh my.
If not,
explain it to me.
This...
It's my order.
Dad?
From now onwards,
you don't have to go to
Shi Lan Ke School anymore.
Why?
Initially, I sent you to Shi Lan Ke School
to avoid you from participating
Soul Master School Contest.
However,
I've never expected that this school
without qualification
would come to Tian Dou City.
Isn't it merely a school contest?
What's wrong with that?
Someone is paying a hefty price
to hire Grandpa Sword
to sabotage the finalist.
Isn't it
a contest between schools?
It's impossible to get
The Grand Soul Land Master involved.
This means that
it's not merely a contest.
So, just don't join it.
Tell me then.
Who is the target?
I don't know.
They will only tell us
during the final.
How about the paymaster?
I have no idea.
Since you know nothing,
why did you get yourself involved?
Because they're paying a hefty price.
Dad, are you kidding me?
How could Qibao Amber Clan
be short of money?
They are giving
a prodigious resource.
What's it
that is worth of Grandpa Sword's service?
Rong Rong.
Perhaps you have no idea
of the secret of Ning's family.
Qibao Amber Pagoda
is not the limit of our Martial Souls.
In the history of our clan,
there was once a genius
who obtained the Mutant Soul,
and upgraded Qibao Amber Pagoda
to Jiubao Amber Pagoda.
That's the ultimate level
of our Martial Souls.
Dad.
Why didn't you tell me before?
The condition they offered
is to help you mutate your Martial Soul.
Help me?
My Martial Soul has already been fixed.
But you still have hope.
As long as you could obtain
Jiubao Amber Pagoda,
our clan
will do everything for it.
Dad,
have you seen
Jiubao Amber Pagoda before?
It's hard to describe.
All in all,
Martial Soul has various forms.
Anyway,
this is related to our clan's fate,
we have to go all out.
You must get ready now.
When the time comes...
Chief...
Dad.
Does Jiubao Amber Pagoda
look like this?
Well, distinguished guests.
The following lot Seven
is a coral with fire attributes.
It helps to improve the Soul Power of
Soul Masters with fire attributes.
This is your place.
After the auction,
if your bid is sold,
you'll get the money directly.
OK.
Thirty-five Gold Soul Coins.
Forty Gold Soul Coins.
Thank you.
Forty-five Gold Soul Coins.
Fifty Gold Soul Coins.
The price is so high.
Any higher bid?
Now, the bid has reached
55 Gold Soul Coins.
The price has jumped manifold.
Any higher bid?
Calling once.
I think it'll be no problem.
Calling twice.
Last calling.
Deal.
Good.
The next lot
is incredible
and rare.
They are premium herbs.
These premium herbs
are sold as a whole.
The varieties
are recorded in the manual freely provided.
The starting price is 3,000 Gold Soul Coins.
Anyone?
Three thousand Gold Soul Coins.
They are extremely rare treasures.
They're extraordinary.
Amongst them,
there're herbs that are rarely seen by people.
Everyone, look at this.
This Snow Silkworm
is bigger than any common caterpillar fungus
and has better efficacy.
It helps those
who have Ice Branch Martial Soul greatly.
Is anyone interested?
Three thousand Gold Soul Coins.
Well.
The seller consented
to lower the starting price
of the premium herbs
to 2,500 Gold Soul Coins.
That is
way too cheap.
Look at this.
This Fiery Soft Apricot
is a precious poisonous herb
that possesses extreme fire poison.
This herb...
It's screwed.
We have lowered the price several times.
These premium herbs
have dropped to knockdown price,
yet no one would bid for them.
Once you touch it,
the fire poison starts invading you.
Prince Xue Xing said
if you leave Shi Lan Ke
and offer your service to him,
His Highness will consider
letting you join the Tian Dou Royal School.
You'll be able to join the contest by then.
This is the lowest price ever.
It's rare to be seen.
I will never compromise.
If there's no more bid,
these premium herbs would be passed.
Calling once.
Calling twice.
Last calling.
I'll go for 2,500 Gold Soul Coins.
Over there, 2,500 Gold Soul Coins.
Any higher bid?
Brother San.
Calling twice.
What happened?
Last calling.
Deal.
We have hope now.
Are you Tang San?
Do you know me?
I'm Ning Feng Zhi,
Ning Rong Rong's father.
Are you the chief of Qibao Amber Clan?
Since Jiubao Amber Pagoda is so important,
I should thank Tang San personally.
The chief has paid them the money.
Isn't his purpose to participate in the contest?
This is the best repayment.
How about me?
Why are you locking me here?
The chief did say
he doesn't want you to get involved
in the contest.
It's impossible.
I'll never
leave the school matter aside.
I have to go back
and explain to them.
Elder Sword,
there came a young man, Ou Si Ke.
Ou Si Ke?
I can't believe he would come here.
I'll chase him out.
I'll go with you.
Wait.
Rong Rong,
what's that?
What?
Grandpa Sword.
Grandpa Sword, how can you lie to me?
Chief is doing this for your good.
Let me go out.
Grandpa Sword!
Are you the person in charge?
I'm a student of Shi Lan Ke School.
My name is Ou Si Ke.
I'm Rong Rong's schoolmate.
What's the matter?
Last night,
Rong Rong was captured by someone.
We still couldn't find her now.
Regarding this,
your school has reported to us.
I was thinking that,
you could list out
those rivals and enemies
of Qibao Amber Clan.
Perhaps this may help
you search for Rong Rong.
Well, you may go now.
Rong Rong is the daughter of your chief.
Why aren't you worried?
See him out.
Wait, please listen to me.
I reckon...
I reckon the person
who took Rong Rong away
is someone with a strong influence.
And he might have a grudge
with Qibao Amber Clan.
Listen to me.
Please.
Please let me finish.
Think about it carefully, I...
What's the matter?
Look carefully.
A gift for you.
Rong Rong is at the back.
If that's the case,
it means you have found her.
Something's wrong.
If you had brought her back,
you should tell me just now.
But only Rong Rong and I
know about these fireworks.
She must be using it
to indicate her location.
Since she
wanted to inform me of her location
yet she can't meet me,
this indicates that she wants me
to come over.
If it's so,
and you all keep hindering me,
this means she was seeking my help.
And this means that
she is in grave danger right now.
Have you done talking?
I got it now.
It was you who captured Rong Rong.
Am I right?
But she is the daughter of your chief.
Why did you capture her?
-She...
-I know it!
You want to use Rong Rong
to threaten her father, right?
To threaten her father?
Why?
What's the reason?
Well...
I got it now.
You're taking this chance
to steal the throne.
You must be concealed for a long time
in Qibao Amber Clan,
and you finally got the chance now.
Am I right?
Listen,
no matter how big the grudge is
between you and her father,
Rong Rong has nothing to do with this.
Your imagination
is extremely wild.
Chase him out.
What's this?
Release Rong Rong.
Didn't you say I'm a betrayer?
How would I release her then?
Just let me go in.
I want to bring her out.
Leave now and I won't kill you.
Let him go.
This brat is kind of interesting.
Rong Rong!
Where are you, Rong Rong?
Ou Si Ke!
Ou Si Ke, I'm here.
I'm here.
Rong Rong.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
This lock is so big.
Grandpa Sword did this.
Why are you still calling him Grandpa Sword?
He's involved in the rebellion.
What? Rebellion?
What are you doing?
I want to...
I want to break off this lock.
You...
You just broke off like this?
Get ready to run.
Later, I'll stop him.
And you prepare to run.
Why should I run?
You can never win over Grandpa Sword.
I still have to fight even if I can't.
Otherwise, you'll be in danger.
Run!
Rong Rong, run!
Elder Sword,
I quit.
Rong Rong, I can't fight over him.
I know.
Elder, I surrender.
I'm willing to join you.
Do you think it's okay?
You're not saving her?
No, I'm not saving her.
I'm too weak to fight.
Besides, she used to treat me rudely
and she always scolds me.
Why should I
accept your surrender?
♪The trees are shining against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to break ordinary rules in life♪