♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 18=
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Drink the Lethe Tea
and go across the Luofeng Bridge.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
I’ll be by your side.
I gave you fireflies
because the girl I like is named after
the insect.
But Yuchi,
aren’t you with the girl you like,
Liuying?
You’re Liuying.
You’re the same person.
The same person?
A long time ago, your name was Liuying.
And later, you were Ayu.
You mean
I’m the girl you like?
Yes.
My name is Yuchi Longyan.
A long time ago,
you called me the Dragon King.
The Dragon King?
Miss Ayu,
drink the Lethe Tea
and you’ll forget the past.
Yuchi, after I drink the Lethe Tea,
will I forget you
like Liuying did?
I’ll remember you.
Wherever you are,
I will find you.
But I don’t want to forget you.
Miss Ayu,
it’s about time. Please drink it.
Drink the Lethe Tea,
bury the past in dust
and leave it behind you.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Drink it.
Don’t miss the time.
Will you please stop staring at me?
I’m nervous.
I’ve finished it.
Ayu,
wait for me.
Yuchi,
I won’t forget you.
The imperial palace is huge.
I’m scared.
The palace is secure.
You won’t need my protection any longer.
But I don’t want to go.
I have no friends in the palace.
Am I too greedy to just hope
to see you?
Yuchi,
I won’t forget you.
From now on,
I’m the master of my fate.
(General’s Mansion)
Brother.
Congratulations, General.
You have a daughter.
Great!
Zhao, look at my baby.
Wow,
she’s pretty.
Her big eyes
are just like yours in the earlier days.
Congratulations, brother.
You have an heir. Like father, like son.
Mind your words.
This is my daughter.
Yes, my tongue slipped.
A daughter is also good.
She looks heroic.
Maybe a female general in the future.
Dad will make sure you grow up
to a gorgeous lady
who enchants everyone.
By then,
-This time Liuying is Feng Chenyue,
-we’ll organize a tournament
-the general’s daughter.
-to find you an invincible husband.
Congratulations, General.
I thought she’d
be like the ladies in operas,
a tender, perfumed
and gentle lady of rank.
Unexpectedly,
that gentle girl is me,
while she...
Bravo! Bravo!
Well done!
Be serious with it. The general said
the winner of the tournament
will be promoted the chiliarch.
It seems Gao Yang is better.
General!
Rise, my men.
Well, she likes swords and spears
more than men do.
Like her late father,
she was given the General’s seal
and now defends the border
from Dongluo’s attacks.
Gao Yang’s kung fu is impressive.
How fortunate it is to have a henchman
like him in our army.
Gao Yang,
you’re the chiliarch now.
Anyone has dissents?
No! No! No!
Thank you, General.
The competition isn’t a real war.
We’re brothers bonded by blood.
Yet you lost control in order to win.
Twenty club-beatings
to make sure you remember.
Yes, General.
But the unyielding spirit
to fight till the last second
is exemplary.
You’re the chiliarch’s deputy now.
Be a role model for the men.
Thank you, General.
From this competition,
I saw all your progress.
We’ll have a feast tonight.
Thank you, General.
(Loving Father Feng Se)
Father,
I will realize your dream
to defeat the Dongluo invaders
and bring peace to the border.
Alright.
If that’s your dream,
I’ll stay with you on this path
and help you realize it.
I’ll remember you.
Wherever you are,
I will find you.
Yuchi, I won’t forget you.
From now on,
I’m the master of my fate.
My name is Yuchi Longyan.
A long time ago,
you called me the Dragon King,
or Brother Yuchi.
Yuchi.
Cheers!
Come on, bottoms up!
My men, drink up.
Cheers!
General, General,
may I have a word? Come with me.
-What is it, Uncle Zhao?
-Over here.
I mean, General,
how could you sit so close
to them?
It’s improper.
We’re brothers bonded by blood.
What’s the matter with dining with them?
It’s not what I mean.
They’re men while you’re a woman.
All in all,
you’re Lady Feng.
How could you sit so close to them?
Uncle Zhao, Dongluo troops
are still there.
In Feng Army, we’re all fighting men,
and I’m not Lady Feng.
I don’t care.
I promised to your father.
Forgive me about the nagging,
but I have to say it.
You need to keep some distance.
Look, you gave them a leave
and they're lost in fun.
I’ll hush them off.
Uncle Zhao, I’ll scare them off.
Hey, General, oh...
Look, the girls on the book
are in perfect shapes.
They’re so...
How to put it?
Plump and hot.
Yes. Right.
-This is absurd!
-General.
General, General.
What’s up? Go on.
They’re pretty.
Look, General,
it’s a wrongdoing.
In the army, this kind of book
is contraband.
Why?
Your father said
this kind of book weakens the morale.
Right.
This kind of book weakens the morale.
Give it here. It’s confiscated.
-Give it to the General.
-Hurry.
Do you have nothing else to do?
You know the rules.
Practice the boxing you learned today
for 10 times.
Uncle Zhao, it’s break time.
They’ve finished all the practices.
Let them go.
-Yes.
-No, we can’t.
They knew it’s a violation.
So they should be punished.
Yes, it’s a violation.
But...
A fault confessed is half redressed.
Confess.
General Zhao, we’ve learned it.
It’s not right. We’re sorry.
Since the General pleaded for you,
you can go now.
-Thank you, General.
Come on. Let’s go.
General.
(An Evilly Charming Emperor’s Requite)
An Evilly Charming Emperor’s Requite.
(Chapter Four)
(Chapter Five)
General.
Not again.
You swing the sword all day long. Look.
Come on.
Look at the calluses on your hand.
Have some hand cream.
The thing you’re applying
is greasy for the hand.
When we were in the palace...
I heard that’s what the women
in the palace do.
They’re in the palace.
We’re in the army.
Who said women need skincare?
A woman grooms for her lover.
Dress yourself up
for the man you love.
No, no, no.
I can’t agree with this.
Women dress up to please ourselves.
I’m happy when I’m not dressed up.
So why bother? Take it away.
No.
You won’t be able
to find a good husband like this.
You need it.
My father’s will isn’t completed.
I have no mood for romance.
Besides,
if a man likes me
when I’m not dressed up,
he likes the real me.
The kind of man
who doesn’t only care the appearance
is the kind I like.
You have a point.
Right?
Come on.
Off you go with these.
Men come to the General’s tent often.
It’s inconvenient. Go.
-Be a good girl. Off you go.
-What about the skincare?
Go, go, go.
(Chapter Eight)
The Dragon King is strong,
muscular and slim.
Not bad.
The mortal girl is a maid.
Good shaped,
but kind of silly when she talks.
General.
General, the new Military Supervisor
is here.
Who is here?
The new Military Supervisor
appointed by the Emperor.
Let’s welcome him.
I watched it so many times
and must have learned it.
Why can’t I do it?
I’m so stupid.
What’s up?
Nothing.
Then why covering your forehead?
Headache?
Your forehead...
Let me see what’s wrong.
Who?
Who is it?
Is it...?
Is it
a ghost or something?
Help!
I’m invisible. I’m invisible.
You’re such a timid elf.
Having been too long in mortal world,
I forgot I’m an elf.
Didn’t I tell you
when you want the peach makeup,
you can just summon me?
Why did you poke your forehead?
I...
How did you know it?
Because
I linked your forehead
with mine
using the Body-Sharing Spell.
When you poked your forehead,
I felt the pain too.
Funny.
Not again.
Why did you cast such a spell on me?
Because you’re the dearest to me,
aren’t you?
I am your suitor.
Impossible.
I’m truly a suitor.
He said he’s my suitor.
Was he serious?
Or perhaps, it was just a joke.
Did I scare her?
I mean
you were my personal maid.
Of course we’re close.
See?
Suitor?
He was kidding.
Hey, you,
aren’t you busy in Luofeng Pavilion?
You come every a few days.
That’s absurd.
My lord, don’t joke with me.
Help me with the peach makeup
and then go back to work.
I told you
to stop addressing me my lord.
You can call me by my name,
Xue Qianxun.
You want to keep it going?
Alright.
My dear Lord Xue Qianxun,
help me with the peach makeup, please.
Come on.
Is our love
mutual now?
Uncle Zhao said
the new Military Supervisor
is a new noble.
How can I win him over?
Should I go soft or tough on him?
Mr. Lu, have some tea.
What’s with his gaze?
It’s so impolite.
I can finally have a closer look at you.
I guess you think that as a woman.
I’m not equal
to the post of the general.
If I guess wrong,
stop looking at me
with your filthy eyes.
General.
No.
Chenyue,
I must apologize.
I just want to see
how long it’ll take
until you recognize me.
You are...
I’m your brother, Zheng.
My brother Zheng?
Zheng!
It’s you, Zheng.
Get up.
You’ve changed so much.
I didn’t recognize you.
Good for you, Lu Zheng,
the Military Supervisor.
Call me Zheng.
Alright, Zheng.
You’re still so good-looking.
That hasn’t changed.
Like when we were young,
you still have no manners.
Here. Have some tea.
Alright.
Zheng is still the same.
However,
Yuchi in my dream is more of a man.
(Deceptions in War)
(An Evilly Charming Emperor’s Requite)
What are the chances?
I’m also reading this book.
(An Evilly Charming Emperor’s Requite)
This is...
Chenyue,
as the General,
how could you read a book
that will undermine the morale?
This is... not mine.
I confiscated it from a few
soldiers.
I would never read this kind of books
that will undermine the morale.
That’s good.
I’ll burn it now.
I should do it.
You’re my supervisor.
How could I leave it to you?
Zheng,
you had a rough journey to come here.
Go and have some rest.
There’s a welcoming dinner.
Right.
Thank you, Chenyue.
See you tonight.
Please.
(An Evilly Charming Emperor’s Requite)
(Chapter Two)
It’s just a book.
How can it possibly
undermine the morale?
I should find out.
Help!
Stop!
Darling!
Mother!
Stop crying.
It’s Dongluo troops.
Save the villagers.
-Yes.
(Lu’s Art of War)
Who are you?
My name is Chenyue. What’s up?
How can a girl climb up the tree?
Where are your manners?
It’s a lot of fun.
Look, there are tasty fruits on it.
Here. Catch it.
Young master, are you alright?
Young master.
Really?
If you don’t like the fruit,
I’ll give you this flower.
You’re like a girl as pretty
as the flower.
Mind your tongue.
I’m a boy and I’m older than you.
You should call me Brother Zheng.
Brother Zheng.
It’s been ten years.
The flower is still here.
You haven’t changed at all,
which is great.
(Lu’s Art of War)
General, according to our scouts
in Dongluo,
their troops have nothing abnormal.
And they let their guard down.
The Dongluo Crown Prince
used to eat deer meat every day.
But recently,
he didn’t ask the kitchen to roast it.
I heard their crown prince loves luxury
and is a hedonistic man.
Yes.
He’s quite not himself lately.
I think something is wrong.
A man who is used to deer meat
gives up his favorite suddenly.
Is he
not in the troops?
But I didn’t hear any reports
from the scouts.
Maybe he covered it up.
Uncle Zhao,
order the camp on full alert.
Send out all our scouts
to search for Dongluo Crown Prince.
Yes.
What’s it in your hands?
What is it?
It’s a labyrinth casket.
(Jade)
A friend gave it to me.
It helps me get my head straight
when I cannot think.
Is it difficult?
It depends on the player.
Have a try.
Yuchi.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪