♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 17=
Go see her
before she goes to the palace.
Are you encouraging me to see Ayu?
Is it proper?
Let’s say you can bear with it.
But what about her?
Thank you.
Never mind.
(Shen’s Mansion)
My Lady Divine,
you must learn the imperial courtesy,
or you’d be in trouble.
Madam Zhao,
teach her women’s manners
and the imperial courtesy quickly.
Yes.
I’ll teach you formal kneeling.
Practice 30 times at least tonight.
Do as I teach you.
Right hand on top.
Both hands on the right side.
Withdraw the right foot, and curtsy.
Smile.
Repeat the courtesy I taught you tonight
until your moves are natural.
It’d be impolite to do otherwise
in the palace.
I’ll check on you tomorrow.
It says the one who survives is blessed.
But the life as a concubine
to be locked away in the palace
is never the one I want.
Perhaps,
I should count my blessings.
Yuchi,
I know I have to forget you.
But now,
let me spare a thought on you.
Yuchi.
Yuchi,
is it true that I won’t
see you again?
You will not come to see me
when I release the firefly?
No.
Just try it.
Little firefly,
please tell Yuchi for me
that I have so much to talk to him.
You don’t even care to try, do you?
I’m here.
Yuchi!
Don’t come close.
Alright, I won’t.
I know everything.
Congratulations.
But
I don’t want to be
the emperor’s concubine.
Yuchi, can you take me away with you?
Ayu,
approaching you now
means nothing but harm.
I can’t.
Right.
If the emperor’s
new concubine disappears,
what a huge uproar it will be.
Yuchi, can we please
watch the fireworks one more time
on the city wall?
Please, I beg you.
One last time.
Close your eyes then.
♪Moonlight casts on the river
and the lady’s face♪
♪Like a dream Her hair turns grey♪
♪The thin figure is missing someone
at the frosty night♪
♪Better departure than a long farewell♪
♪Soft tone amid harp playing♪
♪Missing from dawn to dusk♪
♪The harp sings all the sorrow in life♪
Yuchi,
I like you.
What?
♪Enjoy the peaceful life alone♪
I said,
I like you!
♪In the fleeting time How to forget♪
♪The man Love and memories♪
♪Waving goodbye But one day♪
Yuchi,
why are you so good to me?
Why would you watch fireworks,
shooting stars and Star Halo with me?
And last time,
I was surrounded by butterflies.
You made it happen, right?
Yuchi,
I like you.
Do you also...?
No, I don’t.
You know men and demons
go separate ways.
And you’re a girl.
Mind your tongue.
I’m afraid I’d never be able to say it.
Yuchi,
you gave me a jar of fireflies
so that I can summon you anytime.
But each time I summon you,
it’s out of my deepest affection.
I don’t care that you’re a demon.
I’m...
just afraid you don’t feel the same.
You misunderstand.
I gave fireflies
because the girl I like is named after
the insect.
Fireworks and Star Halo
are also her favorites.
But you’re Ayu,
not my girl, Liuying.
Liuying?
Who is she?
She’s the one I love.
I’m good to you
because you resemble her a lot.
That’s it? I look like her?
The fireworks show is over.
Yuchi,
can you give me more fireflies?
The imperial palace is huge.
I’m scared.
You don’t need them.
You’re the Lady Divine.
The Emperor will give you everything.
The palace is secure.
You won’t need my protection any longer.
But I don’t want to go.
I have no friends in the palace.
Don’t worry.
Qingqing will go with you.
Well, can you
come by occasionally?
I cannot.
You don’t have to come often.
I just hope to see you
on my birthdays.
Still not convenient?
If I’m...
not occupied.
Great, I’ll be waiting for you.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪The fate of time♪
♪I repay with four lives♪
♪I gave you my youth♪
♪The wish in hand♪
♪It’s meant to be♪
The peach makeup Xue Qianxun put on me
is indeed charming.
It’s sad mine isn’t as good as his.
Let me teach you.
Xue Qianxun…
I mean,
my lord.
Alright, I paint it on purpose.
However,
the one you painted is fiercer.
But the meteor mark on your forehead
is unique.
It’s ugly.
Are you mocking me?
No, I’m not.
In my eyes,
you’re always good.
The meteor mark is also good.
Are you well lately?
Yes.
Right.
How could you come here?
The Dragon King said
non-mortals have to defeat
the heavenly guards
to get in the palace.
I’m immortal lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
Right.
You’re not a demon.
Well, did you come to see me?
Everything alright?
I want to know
if you’re happy living in the palace.
Fine clothes and food,
as many as I want.
You know, there are various of foods
for the imperials,
like rose cake,
osmanthus and chestnut biscuit,
octagon jujube cake.
So delicious that I bit my tongue,
but...
But
we’re like caged canaries.
Not until now
did I realize how beautiful my life was.
I could go anywhere as my wish.
I...
also want to know
your opinion on your lord,
I mean, on me,
Xue Qianxun.
It’s fine.
Say your mind.
My...
However, you must be honest.
Are you sure you want to hear?
Please.
I’ll say it then.
Your face is as cold as ice.
You’re rigid
with rules and intolerant.
And you’re easily
offended.
You asked me to say it.
You never spare anyone
the shame of punishment.
And you’re not easy-going.
Take the sachet for an example...
Where are you?
I just started.
It’s not finished yet.
Do you know what the sachet is for?
To keep demons and elves away.
And you gave it to me, a bird elf?
But for the sake
of its exquisite embroidery
and your good will,
I’ll take it with delight.
And there’s your ice-cold face.
Cold and serious though,
it’s good-looking.
I can never get tired of it.
You’re rigid with rules.
But you can’t do anything about it.
You’re the lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
To run the place, you must be strict.
As for the punishments,
you punish me
for many of my behaviors.
But they’re not harsh at all.
So, you’re actually very nice to me,
giving me gifts,
buying me osmanthus cakes
and putting on peach makeup for me.
Others
may mistake that you’re my suitor.
I am your suitor.
Impossible.
I’m truly a suitor.
When...
When did you come back?
I never left.
I thought you hate me.
You often scold me
and
mock at the meteor mark on my forehead.
I did scold you.
♪Dare not to run too fast
Steps are soft♪
But you were never afraid of me.
Why?
I... I don’t know, either.
Is it possibly because…
♪If I don’t come along♪
♪Will you only hesitate♪
you like me back?
My...
My lord.
Stop addressing me my lord.
You can call me by my name.
♪The heart beats fast and deafening♪
Qingqing.
♪Wait until the red sunset♪
Ayu calls. I have to go.
♪Embrace the warm wind♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
♪Like a thick wine flows into the sea♪
♪And into your heart♪
Qingqing.
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
Qingqing, are you alright?
♪Like a thick wine flows into the sea♪
Yeah, I’m fine.
♪And into your heart♪
Qingqing, how do I look?
Like a fairy.
Come, take a seat.
It’s your birthday.
Yuchi is coming any minute now.
I will just stand.
It’s getting dark.
Why hasn’t Yuchi come?
He...
is held up perhaps.
Or maybe,
he forgot our promise.
After all, I’m not Liuying.
I’m just Ayu
who looks a lot like her.
It’s not true.
Stop guessing.
What’s wrong with the Dragon King?
The heavenly guards are too tough?
Heavenly guards?
Well... um...
I...
It’s Yuchi!
Where’s he?
Yuchi!
Yuchi, is it you?
Little butterfly,
is Yuchi
occupied?
Did he send you over?
Tell him for me
that I’ll wait for him
on every birthday.
Am I too greedy to just hope
to see you?
Ayu,
don’t wait for me any longer.
However,
the emperor’s love didn’t last long.
Over decades in the palace,
Ayu saw the emperor favoring new girls
and leaving her in her chamber alone.
She waits quietly
for the butterfly
to appear in the garden
and the long-lasting love in her heart.
Forgive me
for all your sufferings in these years.
It’s my fault.
I thought
if you married the emperor,
you’d be free from poverty and bullies.
But I didn’t know
the mortal emperor
would be so inhumane.
Yuchi is still occupied, isn’t he?
Never mind.
He didn’t come
in two years.
But one day,
he will come.
If I could,
I really wish to take you away.
However,
I can do nothing but wait,
in pain,
loneliness,
and with patience.
You broke into the palace
to see her again?
I sent her to the palace,
hoping she could live a better life,
free from unfair treatment.
But now,
I regret it.
Well,
you worry too much.
Stealing Fire Protection Shield,
making rain without authorization,
and defying the heavenly guards
to see her?
If God finds out
and holds you accountable,
there will be more punishments.
I don’t care about that.
You know what?
Waiting is driving me crazy.
It’s a much crueler punishment for me.
I just hope
time goes by faster.
Be a little more patient.
Trust me.
Your dream will come true soon.
Consort Dowager Yu, look,
fireworks! How beautiful!
I remember
the most beautiful fireworks I’ve seen.
Back then
I was a lowly fisherman’s daughter.
I like you!
For just a moment though,
it’s been the sweetest for 60 years.
You’ve always
been in my heart.
If we meet again,
I’ll not let you go.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪