(All characters, locations, organizations, religions,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictional.)
The reason behind everything that disappears.
"I am the first and the last,"
"the beginning and the end."
- It's risky? - I'm that.
Will I die?
The last. The end.
The deity that makes everything vanish.
I want everything destroyed!
Just bring doom to this world!
- Hello. - Who are you?
- Myul Mang. - What do you want?
We don't have time. You're going to die soon.
Exactly 100 days later.
You're not scared of things you can't see.
But once they become visible,
your fear suddenly becomes real.
Stop!
Stop it!
And just like that,
I held Myul Mang's hand.
Why me?
Why? Why must it be me?
Fate.
This won't do. Let's live together.
Sure.
The terms are...
I have to ask you...
to destroy the world before I die.
What are you doing?
Instilling fear.
Get out.
During the period of our contract, my last 100 days,
I will not feel any pain.
I've seen you before.
You were crying that day.
You have to grant me a real wish.
Beings like you usually pity humans.
Especially humans like me.
If I violate the terms of the contract...
I've been too nice for no reason.
The person I love the most...
I need your hand. Give me your hand!
Is that your wish?
In the world will die...
Then, this is my plan.
At that very moment.
My plan is to love you.
Then, I'll be able to live...
(Doom, person I love the most)
Without losing anything.
You can't love me.
No human has ever loved me before.
Die!
Everyone either resents me or just wants me.
But no one can love me.
Can someone call this in?
Your hand...
Let go. Let go!
Don't move.
- What just happened? - Don't look.
It's not even worth it.
Don't move. Stop!
Get away from me!
I'll give back...
what I took from you.
I told you.
It's impossible to love me.
Everyone either resents me or wants me.
Or...
some fear me.
(Episode 5)
Are you crazy? Why would you grab that with your bare hand?
That healed quickly.
What's with you?
What's wrong with you?
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
Come this way.
Out of the way.
- Let's go. - Didn't others get injured?
- "Others"? - The people he attacked.
A man and woman.
"A man and woman"?
Whom are you talking about?
What do you mean?
What?
Did I say something just now?
I thought you wanted me to die.
But you said you can't die.
If you knew that, why did you jump in front of me?
Maybe I should've just left you to get stabbed.
That would've taught you a lesson.
It would've taught you that you could die by getting involved.
So what if you can't die?
You're still bleeding like crazy.
What am I supposed to say when you ask me why I did that...
with that heartbroken face of yours?
I was worried it might hurt you even more.
- I'm not the one who's sick. - Yes, I know. It's me.
I'm glad you know that.
So stop yelling at me.
When someone's sick, you don't get angry at them,
which is why I'm trying not to get angry at you.
Are you seriously telling me you're not angry right now?
Forget it. Let's drop it.
I don't even know why I'm talking to you right now.
I did it because I wanted to.
That's all.
I want to know why.
You asked me...
why I need to live.
I thought about it, and I couldn't think of a reason.
I just want to live.
It's similar to that. There was no specific reason.
I just instantly found myself standing in front of you.
You're right. I should've known better.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you know that.
But I don't regret it.
So...
just thank me for what I did.
The guy from earlier is going to die.
You saw how I killed him.
So don't sacrifice yourself for me...
for no specific reason.
I'm just not worth it.
I'm sure...
you did it for a reason.
You're that kind of being.
Dong Kyung!
Hey. Sun Kyung.
Hey, what...
What's the matter?
He knows you're going to die.
Hey, calm down.
Blood?
What's that blood?
Is it that bad already?
- No... - Dong Kyung!
I'm sorry!
I should've been a better brother!
How did you find out?
Why is that important? That's not important right now.
What's important is...
that I saw you covered in blood.
It wasn't mine. It just happened to get on my clothes.
Will you stop crying?
How can I stop crying?
You're... You're not well.
So how can I stop crying?
Because I'm terminally ill?
Please don't say that.
What happened to your leg?
- Take a right. - I know.
My leg isn't important.
If I could help you get better,
I'd willingly sacrifice my leg.
I know I'm dying soon, but your leg still matters.
Because it's covered in blood.
Yes, because it's covered in blood.
What do you mean you know you're dying soon?
How could you say that?
You should get hospitalized. Turn the car around.
Turn the car around.
I can't focus on driving because you're so loud.
If you keep this up, we'll all die.
Will you stop talking about death?
- Can't you do something about him? - Do what?
Like erasing his memory or...
Is that your wish?
Forget it. Why do I bother?
I'm a jerk. I deserve to die.
No. Don't talk about dying, you idiot.
Did you know my sister was sick?
Yes.
- Since when? - Since the beginning.
I thought you were using her.
My brother.
You're the real deal.
Thanks, Brother-in-law.
Will you keep calling him that?
Yes, I will.
Live together. You have my blessing.
I will...
allow it.
Who are you to allow it?
I, Tak Sun Kyung,
root for true love...
wholeheartedly.
I know that no matter how tough you act...
No. There's no time for this. I'll go now.
I'll leave her to you now.
Where are you going?
Just get some sleep.
Don't worry about me.
He's the one who's worrying.
Hi, Sang Geun.
I can't go to the lessons with you.
It's nothing serious.
I need to make some money.
No.
I'll explain... Everything... Later.
My poor sister.
The poor thing.
I'm the head of the family.
I'm her guardian now.
(Help wanted)
- Hello... - Are you still...
hiring?
You're hired.
I'm on the scene.
The Gusin-dong Murder suspect,
Kim, killed himself...
in a hospital in Seoul today.
Kim, who was being transported to the hospital,
caused a scene in front of the ER...
and tried to commit suicide.
He was brought into the OR,
but he ended up dying from losing too much blood.
On the 23rd of the month...
They're not mentioning us at all.
Kim attacked people with a weapon...
killing Choi and two other people...
and critically injuring four.
You haven't turned a single page this entire time.
Lee and Park are still in a coma...
and are being treated in the ICU.
I was right. That you had a reason.
Was it a punishment?
Punishment?
("The Black Leaf in My Mouth")
Don't get any ideas. I'm not into that.
If you're not into it, is it your life's calling?
How grand.
I couldn't stand the stuff he was doing.
You keep saying that.
You said that to me too.
But he and I can't be the same.
How are you different?
I don't know. How are we different?
Hey, this isn't...
(Ms. Soo Ja, My babies)
(Emergency Dispatch)
(Building 3, Lower, 5)
(Late night medical care)
- Hey. - Move.
Die!
Why did you do that?
Why are you here?
I asked why you did that.
- What? - Why did you protect her?
Because she did it first.
Since when did you care about that?
Because...
if she dies, I can't end the world.
What a great excuse.
- Your hand. - I want to know as well.
Whether that's really it...
or if it's something else.
Then ask...
which is which.
I want to know too.
Is that really how you feel?
Hey.
When did you get here?
What did you mean by that?
- What? - So you just wanted to save me.
I just wanted to do that. That's it. It doesn't mean anything.
You saved me because if I disappear, you'd die, right?
Is that it?
I knew it.
What do you think?
How would I know that?
I can't hear your thoughts because of our deal.
Then, make an effort.
- Make an effort? - Yes.
You can observe me and think about why I did it.
"Why did she do that?"
Why should I do that?
Because I do that often.
"Why on earth is he like this?"
"I see. That's why."
It's some kind of skill people need to have in this world.
Right. Can you not do that because you're not human?
How do you do that?
Over there. Why do you think she's standing over there?
She must really want to drink.
She got an arm lift, so she couldn't drink for two weeks.
I see. She can't drink, then.
It might cause an infection.
Until she recovers, she can't... No!
Hey, don't just tell me their thoughts.
Observe someone and think about that person.
What?
I observed you and thought about you.
I got it.
You're annoyed at me.
You're mad at me.
Good. Nicely done.
Hey, Tak Dong Kyung. What were you implying?
You weren't being nice, right?
That was sarcasm, right?
By the way, what's your name?
- Why do you ask? - When I get angry,
I want to call you by your name.
Only you get to do that.
I don't have a name.
Only people need names.
Then, be Human.
I can't be human. How many times must I remind you...
until you accept that I'm not human?
Your name. Your name can be Human.
What about your last name?
You can be a Kim. That's the most common last name.
Kim Human. That's good. Kim Human.
What are you talking about?
Hey, Kim Human!
You almost crashed into the cart.
Look around before you go.
And let go of me now.
I really can't figure you out.
Okay.
- What? - You want me to watch and think.
I'll watch you and think.
Remember. You were the one who told me to do this.
So...
he's...
Jung Min?
Of course, he is. He's not Joo Ik.
Oh, right. He's Jung Min.
Yes, it's Jung Min. I'm sure it's him.
There's Jung Min.
Jung Min, these are the printouts for our meeting.
Sort them and get them in the meeting room.
Have you gone mad? Why are you here?
What about Jung Min? Where's Jung Min now?
Don't worry. I kept him alive.
How could you say that? Come on!
Yes. I'm coming.
You know how to do this, right?
No.
That was a joke.
If Young Prince causes trouble again, we can't handle it then.
We had to cut a deal with the platform for this huge event.
- So make sure to stay on top of it. - Okay.
And did you meet with Lee Hyun?
- Pardon? - Did you see her after that?
After when? I'm not sure what you're referring to.
After you and I talked about that kiss.
What? No. I didn't see her after that.
I'm not the type to gossip about other people's private stuff.
Why not?
What?
I want a proposal and overall review of all of her novels...
from the first one to the recent one by the end of today.
Why do you need that all of a sudden?
That's it.
Are you dating Jung Min?
Me? Why would I?
No, right?
Did you cross him or something?
What?
He's been staring at you the whole time.
Come on.
I'm bleeding.
I was working.
Gosh. What a dangerous job you have.
Is your finger a document?
All good, right?
Why did you put that on?
Because it's bleeding.
It probably stopped before you put it on.
You don't think I don't know that?
It's like a comforting ritual.
It's recognizing your pain. It doesn't mean anything.
You said that again.
Tak Dong...
Ms. Tak.
What is it this time?
How do I do this?
- What's "this"? - Printing.
If you don't even know how to do that, why are you here?
You think I can't do this?
What?
I just wanted to do it. It didn't mean anything.
No.
It's not what you think.
No. It's not what you think at all.
That's not it.
No!
I said, no.
Hello.
Please sit there, Mr. Cha.
I like sitting here.
Why don't you sit here?
Just sit there.
Okay.
Jjamppong or jjajangmyeon. That is the question.
I need to cure a hangover. I'll get jjamppong.
It sounds like you drink so you could have jjamppong.
- I want fried rice. - Me too.
- I'll get japchae over rice. - Me too.
[VIU Ver] tvN E05 'Doom at Your Service'
"Why Would She Do That?"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
I'm too scared to say anything in front of you now.
You took it literally...
when I told you to observe and think.
Even elementary school kids won't do that.
Are you coming to work again tomorrow?
No.
I won't be there tomorrow.
What is it?
She's getting off at this station.
Really?
The train is approaching the station.
The doors are on your left.
The doors are opening.
This is my first time sitting down in the subway...
on my way home after I got a job here.
I observed you and thought about how you might feel.
You seemed tired,
and I figured you might want to sit.
I'm so touched. You're...
pretty much human now.
Are there no available seats?
There are.
Then go and sit down.
- I don't need to. - Why not?
Because I need to stand here and observe you.
Go ahead and observe me all you want.
I also need to read something.
Yes, I'm already observing you all I want.
(Favorites, "Second First Love" by Lee Hyun)
("Second First Love", Episode 38, Written by Lee Hyun)
This is so fun. Keep up the great work.
(This story is so repetitive. It keeps going back.)
("Waking up as a Singer", Written by Young Prince)
- Why are you smiling? - What?
No, it's nothing.
Is it funny that the storyline doesn't connect?
What do you mean?
Apparently, the storyline doesn't connect.
("Waking up as a Singer", Episode 93)
("Waking up as a Singer", Episode 96)
I didn't see this. I didn't hear anything.
I got off work.
I'm no longer at the office. Whatever.
My gosh.
I guess something bad happened.
This is so fun. Keep up the great work.
(This is so fun. Keep up the great work.)
("Second First Love", Episode 38, Written by Lee Hyun)
(Search)
(Lee Hyun)
("Second First Love", "101 Ways to Fall in Love")
("He Always Smells of Soap")
(Lee Hyun)
This is so fun. I can't wait for the next episode.
(Comments)
I really love all your stuff.
Keep up the great work.
("Second First Love")
(Comments)
Your stories were interesting at first.
But all your male characters...
are always the same in all your stories.
You show no effort. I've had enough of it.
I'm done.
That's why they're all like that.
Because they're based on him.
Lee Hyun Kyu. I'll make you pay.
(Episode 38, Gone, Written by Lee Hyun)
(- Then what are you going to do? - I'll try not to do it anymore.)
(I was in love with her.)
(I'll make you pay.)
You came home awfully early today.
There are only two ways to avoid running into the employees.
Either go home first or go home last.
Why don't you just tell them your parents own the building?
- No. - Why not?
I slack off because I don't want to work.
I don't want them to think it's because I'm rich.
I see.
Did you see our new part-timer? Isn't he good-looking?
- Wash your hands. - They're clean.
I wash the dishes dozens of times with these hands.
Okay, fine.
Did you see the part-timer or not?
No, I didn't.
Are you not interested in me?
When was I ever interested in you?
You've changed.
What are you looking at?
What is this?
"He ran away from love and embarrassment."
"That's how he chose to end their love."
(Fine. Let's break up.)
This guy is a piece of trash.
Why is she still having a hard time getting over this jerk?
I know, right? I wonder what she liked so much about him.
(I hate it when you're like this.)
("Second First Love" Episode 38, Gone)
(Rate)
(Writer's comment: Thank you for reading.)
(Favorites)
Who did this?
You'd better make sure Young Prince doesn't stop writing.
How are we going to make money if he stops writing?
We don't even have that many famous writers.
Why couldn't you keep things in check?
How could you make a mess just because I'm not there?
Who did this? Who uploaded it wrong?
Who was it? Who did it?
Why aren't you guys talking?
Do you all want to get fired?
Do you think I won't do it?
Jung Min, I just saw you glancing somewhere else.
Da In, was it you?
No, it was me.
Tak...
- I'm sorry. - An apology won't cut it!
I had to talk to his mom past midnight!
International phone calls are expensive!
Do you know how scary his mom is?
You'd better convince him to keep writing.
- If you fail, you'll have to quit. - Okay.
Hey.
Where are you going?
To quit.
Are you kidding me?
Go convince Young Prince right now!
Gosh, what a pity. This was my chance to quit.
I'm sorry.
- I'll take responsibility... - And do what?
It's all my fault.
Gosh, I shouldn't have ignored it.
- What? - Forget it.
You make mistakes so you can learn from them.
I went through the same thing. I learned from my mistakes.
No, I'm done.
I know you're here to ask me to keep writing.
I've been meaning to quit anyway.
I should go now.
The school's serving us tonkatsu for lunch today.
Hey, wait.
You came all the way here amid your busy schedule.
I feel really bad that you have to leave so early.
Exactly.
I wrote that novel amid my busy schedule.
And I'm really upset that you uploaded it that way.
I really don't know what to say.
How about we eat together...
and talk about it for a little while?
I swear I won't take up too much of your time.
I even brought this to treat you to a nice meal.
Ta-da. This is a company card.
- I'll explain what it is. - I know what it is.
Right.
I shouldn't have said that.
Can I eat something expensive?
Of course. Just tell me what you want.
Then I'll have...
Yeopgi Tteokbokki.
Oh, okay. Sure.
Hello.
Hey, what...
What? Were you talking to me?
Hey, what a lovely smell! Don't you agree?
Hey, I'm going to go home after I eat.
I'm not going back to school today.
We'll have one tteokbokki and...
We'll add one udon, two extra servings of cheese,
and a combination of fritters, but change the vegetable fritter...
with the seaweed glass noodle roll.
We'll have the spiciest one.
Got it.
"Got it"?
Did he just say "Got it"?
No.
I think he said, "Yes, sir."
What if I give it a terrible ending?
Like the earth exploding.
Wow. Talk about a grand finale. That's nice.
The protagonist dies...
A sad ending stays in the hearts of the readers.
It turns out it was all a dream.
The "Inception" of web novels.
- But... - Yes?
It's odd.
What is?
There are hardly any sausages.
Sausages?
Here's a sausage.
Anyway, It's not that simple.
You may not know since you're not a writer.
Yes, of course.
To be completely honest, I don't care about editing.
I just really enjoy your story.
It's really fun, so I want to read more of it.
It's out of personal selfishness.
Oh no. You can't tell my boss...
that I said that, okay?
May I get an extra order of sausages?
Of course. You can order anything you want.
Excuse me.
More sausages and cheese please.
I'm out.
What? Then more dumplings.
Then quail eggs...
- I'm out. - What do you have?
Don't you think he's very rude?
Sausages? Quail eggs?
If they're out, I'll go buy them myself.
I saw a convenience store next door.
Give me a minute.
Is that all right, sir?
Hey, you.
Why are you so rude, kid?
All you care about is sausages.
Okay.
It must be nice being old.
Don't you like sausages?
Stop talking back to me, runt.
Stop starting fights, old man.
Do you want to die?
No. I don't want to die.
That girl will pick up the tab.
Sir...
Hey. Where did he go?
You... Darn it.
Sir. Did you get back safely?
I hope I didn't take too much of your time.
I'm terribly sorry about what happened.
I'd really appreciate it if you'd consider what I said today.
I look forward to hearing back from you.
I get it, so stop texting.
I have a mask on right now.
Seriously. You young twerp.
You should've talked like that before.
You don't understand. It's my job.
It looked more like you were in prison, not working.
- Is he your prison guard? - Pretty much.
It is suffocating.
Hey. How long have you been following me?
Since the tteokbokki place? Or...
Since the moment you were born.
I follow people from the moment they're born.
It's just that you noticed now.
I've completed monitoring you professionally.
I came to monitor you personally,
but it ended up being professional again.
What was the conclusion of your professional monitoring?
You should reflect on what you saw.
Why don't you just make a wish and ask for money?
I don't want to hear it if that's your conclusion.
I'm going to use it for a very good cause.
I know it's unfair and annoying,
but I'm not the only one living like this.
Does everyone live like that?
Yes, everyone.
Everyone has a sob story.
As sad as yours?
I don't know about that,
but everyone has their share of sorrow.
Everyone has their share of burdens.
What are you doing?
Your share looked too heavy.
I thought you may want this.
What is this?
Isn't this a dream?
It's real. Be careful not to drown.
It's real?
I feel like I can breathe now.
I've never told anyone before,
but I always sat here like this whenever I wanted to cry...
ever since I was a child.
I came when I missed my mom.
I came when I missed my dad.
I came when Sun Kyung stressed me out.
I came when I felt guilty toward my aunt.
I came just because.
Why?
You could've just cried.
Why did you sit here and fight the tears?
I know, right?
I just didn't want anyone to know that I was crying.
You could've cried alone when no one was looking.
Then no one would know.
I'd know.
I know.
And I hated that.
Why are you suddenly being nice to me?
To seduce you.
Just kidding.
Do you want to kiss?
I'll pretend I didn't hear that then.
Let's go. It's cold.
Okay.
It's cold.
Dong Kyung.
Yes?
Aren't you going to take them down? They're dry.
Whatever! I won't.
I heard Hyun Kyu is coming to the reunion.
Yes. Make me look ten times hotter.
No. Make it 30 times.
What a loser.
He said he was studying after going abroad,
so he didn't answer your calls.
But he's coming to the reunion?
I bet he wasn't even studying. He was busy partying.
He posts a lot of photos on social media.
Whenever I think about how he broke up with you...
over a text, it still infuriates me.
What a scumbag.
Nice eyes.
That's the right attitude.
I'll make your hair look so great. You just wait.
(Mr. Cha Joo Ik)
- Yes. - Where are you?
Pardon?
Let's meet. I need to talk to you.
- Did you call the wrong person? - No.
So let's meet now.
(I wanted to share a kiss like we shared glances.)
(Kiss)
Do you think that's enough to break the desk?
- Where are you going? - I have a meeting.
Please review it. I already reviewed it.
What's this?
A proposal?
From character selection and development...
to data research, episode outline,
plot development, and some hand-holding too.
I'll make you get into the top 10.
And when you do,
I will get five percent of your earnings as my remuneration.
I already have a contract with the company.
This is between you and me. A personal contract.
I saw potential in you.
Getting into the top 10 isn't easy.
Do you think you can agree to and comply with all of my demands?
That will be easier, then.
- How can I trust... - Did you do your hair?
What?
Yes.
I have a school reunion.
Is Lee Hyun Kyu coming too?
I guess he is. That's why you did your hair.
- You know... - Don't go to the school reunion.
Don't see him.
But you will still go...
and see him no matter what I said, right?
This doesn't concern you.
I read all of your novels.
And you need one thing.
A new male character.
And I'll help you with that.
So don't hold on to him.
You know, this isn't...
revenge. You just haven't let him go.
- Where are you going? - To work.
Hey.
What?
Let me come with you.
- Buy your wedding box! - Buy your wedding box!
- My gosh. I'm so tired. - Buy your wedding box.
I'm so exhausted. I can't walk anymore.
My goodness. He's too hungry to walk!
- Oh, no. What should we do? - Gosh.
Getting married at the age of 50 isn't something to brag about.
Let's make this easy on ourselves.
Take this. Hey, bring the food now!
- Get up. - Gosh.
- All right. Hurry. - Let's go.
- Buy your wedding box! - Buy your wedding box!
I've never seen this ceremony before.
I didn't know people still did this. I only saw this on TV.
It's reaching its end.
Inanimate things end too.
Traditions will die too.
All right. Let's go!
You won't be able to see things you used to see every day.
And watching such things is my job too.
How beautiful...
and sad.
Most of the things that disappear are beautiful.
Do you know what a supernova is?
Right before stars vanish from the world,
they shine brightly.
And that explosion creates...
the energy for the new stars in the future.
It will become a star again.
Maybe, that's what this is.
The reason why things disappear and why you are here.
Don't comfort me. It won't work.
I thought I picked the wrong person.
I thought I shouldn't have picked you.
That's why I thought I was in this mess.
Do you still think so?
No.
I picked the right person.
So I came to this conclusion.
Love me.
Love me if you can.
That wouldn't be such a bad idea either.
So...
be the first human to love me.
(Doom at Your Service)
Be crazy...
in life.
I brought you flowers this time.
Sleep with me. Please?
Sweetie, open it.
Everyone even the kids look down on me!
You should say that you want to fall madly in love.
That's how romance begins.
It seems like you've met...
the right person.
I have a wish.
I want you to love me.