♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 39=
You're here.
Dad.
It's really you.
You are the mastermind behind everything?
Why are you shocked?
You want to assassinate Bi Bi Dong
for revenge?
Yes.
You have
controlled Cang Hui School,
poisoned Du Gu Bo,
and threatened Qibao Amber Clan?
I can't kill Bi Bi Dong
alone.
You also
enhanced the mutation of Martial Souls?
I need more forces.
But the process of creating Mutant Souls
harmed a lot of people.
Ma Hong Jun's dad died because of that too.
I'll compensate Ma Hong Jun
after I kill Bi Bi Dong.
Dad,
this is not a problem
that can be settled by compensation.
Someone has to sacrifice
for a big enterprise.
I didn't expect
you would become a person like this.
How am I now?
Why did you look for me?
Cang Hui must enter the final.
Why?
The last step can only be taken
when Cang Hui becomes the champion.
For the champion,
Bi Bi Dong will present the award in person.
I found
a special Mutant Soul.
His only Soul Skill
is Blank Space.
He can only use
his Soul Skill once in a lifetime.
He'll die after using it.
This is a Soul Skill
performed by one's life.
The only strength of this Soul Skill
is to make the people
in proximity
lose control of their power.
What is the use of the arrow then?
It works like a sign.
So that his strength
can be released with a target.
His target
will only be Bi Bi Dong.
But, Bi Bi Dong may not come close to him.
Therefore, I have prepared
a few more people for her.
First, it's Spear of Void.
A Soul Sect with Quadruple Soul Rings
cannot harm the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
He just needs
to block the vision.
Mutant Soul, Returning Mirror.
It can exchange spaces.
It's effective on humans too.
Bi Bi Dong will lose
her spirit control over Soul Power
in a very short period.
My final preparation
is Mutant Soul, Space Isolation.
His Soul Skill
has no offensive ability.
It can only block all the assistance
in a short period.
Then,
it's those Grand Soul Land Masters
that I've prepared.
If we block all the assistance,
how can those Grand Soul Land Masters
get in the arena?
What do you think?
Returning Mirror.
This is the best time
for all the Grand Soul Land Masters
to take action.
Bi Bi Dong is really strong.
But,
under the successive attacks,
she'll lose control over her Martial Soul.
She'll definitely die.
Why do we have to wait until after the final
to implement this plan?
Her position is high.
Normally, no one can get close to her.
Only when she presents the award
will she come close
to the students of Cang Hui alone.
After all, they only have Quadruple Soul Rings.
She won't be too alert.
The student who is going to use the arrow
will die.
Actually,
all the students of Cang Hui
will die.
Is it worth it to let many people die
only to kill the chief of Martial Soul Hall?
Bi Bi Dong is the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
She's the Greatest Soul Master
in Douluo Continent.
It's impossible to kill her
without any sacrifice.
I can't accept it.
You don't have to do anything.
You just have to allow
Cang Hui School to enter the final.
How is it possible for them
to defeat Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team?
I'll arrange it.
You just have to convince your teammates.
It's wrong to do those things.
I'm your dad.
I'll not hurt you.
I refuse to obey.
Actually,
I have other ways
to solve the problem.
Tang San!
We didn't see you come back after a while,
so we came here.
Is he the mastermind?
Wait a minute.
Protect Tang San.
Kill them now.
Cang Hui can also enter the final!
Stop it!
Brother Dai!
Dad!
Ou Si Ke.
Stop it!
Wu, step aside!
Zhu Zhu Qing!
Dad!
Dad, stop it, please.
Let's go back to the Saint of Soul Village.
You'll be the ironsmith.
I'm your son.
We'll stay together.
Give up the struggle.
Let me decide for you.
If you quit the contest,
I'll spare her.
No need.
You can kill her.
What?
She's not Wu.
You're not my dad.
When did I fall into your trap?
Teacher Shi Nian.
If I had given up everything
and followed your arrangement,
I would have been
controlled by you, right?
What are you talking about?
The wind chime.
What?
The wind chime is the symbol of home
to my dad and me.
It represents the love of my dad to me.
He won't destroy this love.
So, you can only create
their figures,
but you can't know about my memory.
Let me think.
You didn't speak to me voluntarily.
I spoke first.
Therefore, you knew
that Hao Tian Soul Master is my dad.
Since you saw me
in Shi Lan Ke's lodging,
I've trapped you in a dream.
You're right.
When you're in despair
and admit your failure,
you'll be controlled by me.
Therefore, your plan failed.
Not yet.
There's a more troublesome plan.
It's to kill you repeatedly
in your dream.
To torture you
until you lose all your hope.
Then,
I'll still be able to control you.
It's useless.
You are no match for me
even in the dream.
Although I need to waste more time,
the result will still be the same.
I didn't expect
that you're the son of Hao Tian Soul Master.
So, my dad is not the one
behind Cang Hui.
The mastermind is
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
You asked too much.
Are you ready
to die in pain repeatedly?
What is this?
Who hid such great power
in your heart?
(Tang San.)
This is the power of the Grand Soul Land Master.
(Son.)
(I left my final strength)
(in your heart.)
(Although I can't see you again,)
(I'll always be with you)
(and protect you until the end.)
Mom.
Hold on.
Tang San,
hold on!
I'll tell you who the mastermind is.
You let me go.
Tang San...
I broke his Mind Branch Martial Soul.
Where are we?
All of you are awake now?
He became like this
after his Mind Branch Martial Soul was broken.
This should be the backlash effect
of his Mind Branch Martial Soul.
How did you break it?
Everyone has a secret.
I understand. I'll not ask anymore.
Where are the rest?
They're awake now.
Their last memory
remains the first time when they came to Cang Hui.
It has been a long time.
They can't get used to it.
How about you?
I plan to leave Martial Soul City
with them.
How about the contest?
It's nothing.
Thank you.
We got rid of this demon finally.
Do you plan to leave him here?
I want to bring him with me.
Revenge?
No.
I'm going to keep an eye on him
and prevent him from waking up again.
How about you?
Although we have solved
almost everything about Cang Hui School,
the Grand Soul Land Master
behind Cang Hui
is still out there.
Moreover,
the contest hasn't ended yet.
Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team is too strong.
I think it's hard for your team to win.
We have to try.
I wish that your team can win.
Oh yes.
When will you leave Martial Soul City?
As soon as possible.
We'll not send you off then.
Tang San.
Thank you. I am indebted to you.
If you are in trouble in the future,
come to me.
What if Shi Nian wakes up again?
If you face something like this in the future,
you must bring me along.
Sure.
Are we going
to look for Venom Soul Master and the others now?
Battle of three Grand Soul Land Masters.
I wonder what the result will be.
I hope everything will go smoothly.
This is the compulsory route
to return to Martial Soul Hall
from the arena.
Let's block
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master here.
Chief.
Just be frank to me.
We don't have to hide
anything from Senior Du Gu.
If the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
is really going to assassinate
the chief of Martial Soul Hall,
I think we should observe
the situation first.
You can leave if you
don't want to get involved.
We are
the only Support Branch Clan.
Now,
Martial Soul Hall is at its strongest.
Instead of becoming their enemy,
how about we try to be their friend?
Then, Chief,
your objective this time
is to get close to Martial Soul Hall?
Stopping the assassination
is helping her too.
It's also a safe passage for us in the future.
Chief, you're so optimistic
about the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
Some people
are destined to do something big.
Judging from the contest this time,
the chief of Martial Soul Hall
is ambitious and has a long-term vision.
We shouldn't go
against this kind of people.
You've talked so much.
Are you going to take action?
We'll take action.
Good.
You're the mastermind
behind everything?
Is there anyone else?
Qibao Amber Pagoda, Chief Ning.
I'm just being cautious.
Before we take action,
I still want to ask,
are you the one
who planned to assassinate
the chief of Martial Soul Hall?
You knew too much.
It's really you.
How do you know we are here?
Someone saw you guys going in this direction.
I guessed you guys came to Cang Hui.
Give it to me.
What?
My token.
Oh yes.
We were discussing serious matters yesterday
and forgot to give it back to you.
Here.
You lied to me.
What did I lie about?
Didn't you say
you wanted to go to the library
to investigate
the past of Yu Xiao Gang and the chief?
But, someone from the library came to ask me
why I checked
the view records of "The Secret of Star".
I checked it.
Why did they ask you?
Nonsense.
This is my token.
Of course, my name would be recorded.
Forget it.
Let's take a look at the result.
I also want to know
why the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
wants to kill the chief.
Why are you still standing here?
You mean
that I used your token,
so your name would be
on the view records?
Nonsense.
Wait a moment.
Over the years,
there was only one Grand Soul Land Master
who viewed "The Secret of Star".
The Grand Chrysanthemum Master?
It turns out
that he's the spy in Martial Soul Hall.
You said
someone from the library had asked you
about the view records?
Yes.
So, if I were the spy,
I wouldn't use my token
to investigate.
Am I right?
Yes.
It'll be too obvious then.
So, you think
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
may not be the spy?
But, he indeed researched about Soul Beasts
without the permission of Martial Soul Hall.
But, researching about Soul Beasts
doesn't mean
he wants to kill
the chief of Martial Soul Hall, right?
You said he was the spy yesterday.
Today, you said it might not be the case.
I'm thinking
could it be that someone
stole the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's token
and went to the library?
How is that possible?
What if someone borrowed it?
Someone will only lend the token
to someone very close.
Who is the closest to him?
The Grand Ghost Master
is the closest
to the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
It's bad.
What's wrong?
Let's go to the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
Who are you?
How dare you all walk around in Martial Soul Hall?
It's none of your business.
Stop it.
Wait a moment.
How come you're here?
Didn't we agree to meet later?
You are involved in it too?
Did you betray Martial Soul Hall?
I betrayed Martial Soul Hall?
This is a serious offense.
Grand Chrysanthemum Master,
did you visit the library
in these few years?
Did you lend your token
to the Grand Ghost Master?
Why
did you ask about this suddenly?
My inference may be wrong.
He may not be
the real mastermind.
He admitted it just now.
He wants to kill the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
What?
He admitted it?
Yes.
Even the kids know about it.
You really betrayed Martial Soul Hall.
What happened?
Chief,
these people
knew about the assassination already.
Chief Ning.
Chief.
You're quite good.
Senior Du Gu and the Grand Sword Master
just wanted to know the truth.
I'll let them go,
as long as they don't cause trouble
during the final.
The actual scenario is
that Cang Hui and others colluded secretly
to kill you.
You're one of the students of Shi Lan Ke too?
Yes, I'm Wu.
Interesting.
Cang Hui has withdrawn from the contest?
Yes.
Their teacher, Shi Nian,
used his Mind Branch Martial Soul on me.
He lost control of all his students
after he had failed.
Did you know
about everything?
Of course, I know who wants to kill me.
It's the Grand Ghost Master, right?
He caught
the people from the schools that had been out.
Don't worry. They are still alive.
He just wanted everyone to think
that I was the one
who harmed the excellent students
of Douluo Continent.
He might take the chance to find more helpers.
How about those who disappeared?
After the final,
I'll set all of them free.
Why didn't you stop him in advance?
After Cang Hui withdrew from the contest,
your school will enter the final.
To be honest,
I'm quite surprised.
You knew that the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
had been killing Soul Beasts cruelly?
Martial Soul Hall wants to advance.
Of course, we need to research
the Nature of Soul Beasts.
That's why you need to kill so many Soul Beasts?
For the experiment,
the interspace created
by the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
only allows me, himself, and Soul Beasts to enter.
I wondered
how you found out the truth.
Now, I understand it.
I don't want to influence the final.
Let's discuss everything
after the final.
All of you can leave now.
You are quite good
that you can investigate
the matter to this point.
Therefore, you also knew
that the Grand Ghost Master is the mastermind?
If you had chosen to be my disciple,
I would have told you earlier.
The teacher of Shi Lan Ke
will never lie to their students.
Looks like
I'm the nosy one now.
She knows everything,
but she pretends that she doesn't know
and doesn't care.
Maybe in her heart,
I'm just a pawn.
Nobody knows
the thinking of your chief.
Do you really want to participate in the final?
Why?
You're already famous as you get to the final.
Why don't you give up?
Do you think we will do that?
Xie Yue
is already very dissatisfied with you.
Although his brain has some problems,
he's really strong.
No one can defeat him.
Isn't a Soul Master
meant to challenge his fate?
If we give up when we face someone stronger,
what's the point of being a Soul Master?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean?
The champion
can only be Shi Lan Ke School.
In the future,
you may face a lot of battles,
but youth only comes once.
It doesn't matter whether you win or lose.
It doesn't matter
whether you become the champion, either.
I just hope
you can give your best during the battle.
Don't leave any regrets.
Lastly,
protect yourself.
Master is right.
Kids,
youth only comes once.
I'm very lucky.
Shi Lan Ke School is very lucky too
to accompany you on this journey
and have good memories
of your youth.
Today,
this is the last battle
where you are representing Shi Lan Ke School.
All feasts will come to an end.
When there is meeting, there is parting too.
Shi Lan Ke School
has been wanting to help
and nurture all of you
to be great Soul Masters.
And let you have
a determined and kind heart.
We also taught you
how to be a good person
and how to face
the complicated yet wonderful world.
Hi.
We are here for the registration
to attend Shi Lan Ke School.
Pay your registration fees first.
Fifty Gold Soul Coins.
Five...
Twenty-five per person?
It's 50 for each person.
My surname is Ou,
and my given name is Si Ke.
Where is Dai Mu Bai?
I want to fight with you.
Ma Hong Jun,
listen to me.
You still have us.
We can be brothers.
Headmaster and Master can be our fathers.
You can't
give up your hope!
Do you understand?
I didn't have the opportunity this afternoon
to introduce myself.
Hello, everyone. I'm Ning Rong Rong.
All of you did it now.
I'm proud to announce
Shi Lan Ke School's students
have graduated.
I don't want to graduate.
How come it's so fast?
I just joined the school.
But, Rong Rong,
you're different now.
You've learnt
about team spirit.
You also know how to respect others now.
Dai Mu Bai,
you're a genius.
I have never worried about your ability.
I was just worried
that you don't know
how to communicate with others.
But now,
you know
how to take care of your teammates.
Very good.
You're a qualified captain.
Headmaster,
I'm your student forever.
♪Walking upright in the world♪
♪The breeze in spring is tender♪
Zhu Zhu Qing.
You came to Shi Lan Ke
to challenge Dai Mu Bai.
I saw dissatisfaction and hatred
in your heart.
Now, I'm happy
that only friendship and memories
are left in your heart.
♪Join hands and look at the world♪
Both of you are teammates now,
not enemies.
♪The light is so brilliant♪
♪The dream is burning in my chest♪
♪The wind whizzes past my face♪
Hong Jun,
I was very worried about you.
I was afraid that pain would distort your soul.
I was afraid that there was only hatred
in your heart.
But now I can see
that you're smiling and become part of the team.
I'm very happy.
Headmaster,
without the school,
Brother San, and everyone,
I'll forever be
an inferior and timid guy.
The school gives me this feeling
and soothes my pain.
Come, hug me.
♪Get through the sea of clouds♪
Remember
not to release fire easily in the future.
You know what I meant.
♪To seek the memory of the former life♪
The school is my home.
I grew up here.
I don't want to go anywhere.
You can stay here.
Really?
I let you stay here,
so that you have more time to think
and understand
what you want to do
and where you want to go in the future.
After you have a plan for your future,
I'll be very happy to send you away.
Thank you, Dad.
♪The wind whizzes past my face♪
Do you still remember
how much you paid for your school fees?
Beside one Gold Soul Coin
and some loose change,
we still need
3975 Copper Soul Coins.
♪The youth still goes on his adventure♪
One Gold Soul Coin.
Do you think it is worth it?
♪Look at the world♪
♪Overlook the sky♪
I think
this is the most precious Gold Soul Coin.
It changed my life.
Since the establishment of Shi Lan Ke,
you two have been the most special.
Because you paid the least tuition fees.
I think I won't forget both of you
in this lifetime.
♪I have a fire in my heart♪
Headmaster,
just like what Brother Dai said,
we're your students forever.
The final is about to begin.
Don't make them feel depressed.
You're right.
Let's not talk about parting.
Let's take about the future.
Everyone,
after the final,
what do you want to do? Where do you want to go?
I'll return to Xing Luo.
I've been hiding for a long time.
I should return
to face my elder brother and father.
To face my fate.
I'll go with you.
My home is in Xing Luo too.
Can't I go back?
It's okay. You don't have to explain.
We understand.
I think
I should be returning
to Qibao Amber Clan.
I said it.
I'll stay in the school for now
and help the next batch of students.
Moreover,
I have to be there
during the admission test.
My excellent acting skills are necessary.
Then,
I'll look for you.
Why do you want to look for me?
I...
We're all from the same school.
It's reasonable
for me to look for you, right?
How about Ma Hong Jun?
I want to travel around in Douluo Continent.
Although Shi Nian has failed,
there are still many Mutant Souls
in Douluo Continent.
I want to help them.
Hong Jun,
you have good thinking.
I support you.
Anyway, I just want to try my best.
How about Tang San?
I think I'll continue to look for my dad.
Wherever Tang San goes,
-I'll go too.
-You'll go too.
We can guess
what you want to say.
So, I think everyone has his own future.
You still have
a long way to go.
From now on,
take your first step.
Complete this final battle
and overcome yourself!
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪