♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 38=
Could it be done
by the Grand Chrysanthemum Master?
He wants to kill Bi Bi Dong.
Why did he capture people
from the schools that had been out?
Maybe he wanted to frame Bi Bi Dong?
That's possible.
Too bad it's only a speculation.
We can't prove that.
If we capture him,
then we'll know the truth.
You want to capture
a Grand Soul Land Master?
Do you think it's possible?
Of course we can't.
Not even with Headmaster and the others.
Who's the strongest
in Martial Soul City?
Bi Bi Dong?
You mean
you want to use Martial Soul Hall to capture him?
That's the only way.
Have you thought clearly about it?
Chi Huo School,
Yu Tian Heng, Du Gu Yan,
and your brother
have all gone missing.
Whether Bi Bi Dong
or the Grand Chrysanthemum Master is the bad guy,
I don't care.
I just want to save people.
Cang Hui is working
with the Grand Chrysanthemum Master?
Do you think I will believe it?
Didn't Martial Soul Hall
lose an officer?
So what?
He was the one
who brought me into the hall.
Also,
he hid an arrow
in the Soul Bone that would serve as the prize.
Arrow?
For what?
I'm not sure.
Fine.
Even if Cang Hui is plotting something,
that doesn't prove
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master a traitor.
Let me ask you,
how many Grand Soul Land Masters
are left in Martial Soul City?
Due to the Soul Beasts in the Star Forest,
they're all on the way there now.
That means,
in Martial Soul City,
there's only
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master left.
So?
All the schools that had been out disappeared.
Beside the Grand Soul Land Master,
who else is capable to do that?
But why did he do that?
Just ask your chief to capture him.
Then you'll know the reason.
Just with what you said,
do you really think the chief
will capture her own Grand Soul Land Master?
What if it's false?
What will happen?
What if it's true?
You can tell what we said
to your chief,
and let her decide.
I need to verify it first.
Are you going to ask him directly?
Stay here.
Where are you going?
I'll be back soon.
I feel like
she believes you.
That's all you've got?
Seriously,
I don't think you deserve
to be part of Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team.
From the beginning,
Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team
only needs me alone.
People like you
are just provisional.
You disappointed me! Again!
If he finds the chance,
he'll surely kill you.
Can he?
Alright, calm down.
I'm training my member.
I need him.
Only the strongest Soul Masters
can stay in Martial Soul Hall.
I'm helping him.
I want to ask you a favor,
but I can't tell you the reason.
Just say it.
I think she might not believe us.
Don't you worry?
For what?
What if she leads her people here
and captures us?
Why?
Perhaps
she's also working
for the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
I don't think so.
Why not?
Because I feel
she really likes the chief
of Martial Soul Hall.
How do you know?
Every time when she
mentioned Bi Bi Dong,
it felt to be different.
You just believe her
because of your instinct?
A liar can speak
a thousand words,
but they can't hide the feelings.
Tang San.
Do you believe Hu Lie Na?
I believe Wu.
If your instinct is so good,
why don't you use it
to detect
if the Grand Chrysanthemum Master is a spy?
It takes time to tell.
Where have you been just now?
I told Yan
to distract the Grand Chrysanthemum Master,
so that we can
check his room out.
Yan?
The person using flame on your team?
He's not in a good mental state,
so his flame might get out of control.
The Grand Chrysanthemum Master helps him
to solve it every time.
What if this fire guy
is an accomplice
of the Grand Chrysanthemum Master?
It's meaningless to think of those things.
She's right.
The Grand Chrysanthemum Master
should be on his way now.
Let's hurry up.
What are you trying to get in his room?
Evidence of him betraying the chief.
You think it's so easy to find?
We'll see.
Let's go.
This is where he lives?
The Grand Chrysanthemum Master once said
that when one reached maximum power,
one would want simpler things.
This is considered good.
The Grand Ghost Master
doesn't even have a room.
He stays in the basement.
With no guard?
The Grand Soul Land Master doesn't need guards.
Actually,
I've never entered the room.
There are still chrysanthemums in this season?
Even if the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
has secrets,
it's impossible that he just hides them
in his room.
What's wrong?
This is the group division plan for the final.
Anything weird?
It has been altered.
These flowers are quite beautiful.
Yes, they are.
There's something wrong with it.
I can see that too.
Tang San, come over here.
Where is this?
Weren't we
in the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's room
just now?
I remember I touched the petals,
and then we are here.
We can't leave anymore.
Just now they were still here.
It's strange.
Are there any traps
in Martial Soul Hall?
This is the room of a Grand Soul Land Master.
Who would dare to set a trap here?
Then...
Don't look at me this way.
This is obviously
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's trick.
What does it have to do with me?
Let's ask him then.
Are you crazy?
Then what about Tang San and Wu?
I'll look for the chief.
Will she believe us?
Let me try.
I'll come with you.
Why it isn't working?
Didn't we touch it and get here just now?
Are the entrance and exit of the interspace
separated?
Are these gates the exit?
It looks more like a prison.
It's locked?
What?
Tang San
disappeared
in the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's room?
Not only that,
Tang San also suspected
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
is working with Cang Hui School
to assassinate you.
Hilarious.
We found the group division plan for the contest
in the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's room.
The plan shows
that Cang Hui's position
has been changed.
Previously,
Cang Hui was in Group B with Martial Soul Hall.
That means,
they should encounter
Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team
in the divisional battle.
But the Grand Chrysanthemum Master changed
them to Group A,
and put Tian Dou Imperial in Group B.
Then we would encounter
Tian Dou Imperial earlier.
So what?
That means,
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
is misusing his authority
to help Cang Hui.
His objective
is to let Cang Hui enter the final.
Just by changing a battle team,
he'll be able to kill me?
No matter what,
Chief, you should
ask the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
Enough.
The royal family of Xing Luo
even wants
to interfere with matters of Martial Soul Hall?
That's not it.
I just wish to find Tang San.
Do you know how vast is Douluo Continent?
As the greatest Sect in Douluo Continent,
Martial Soul Hall
needs to handle countless matters every day.
I don't have time
to listen to your childish speculations!
Go.
I have something to tell the chief.
Please leave.
What do you want to tell me?
I've stayed in Shi Lan Ke School
for some time.
I know Tang San very well.
He's not someone who talks nonsense.
He said only the Grand Soul Land Master
could make
the schools that had been out disappear.
You believe everything he said?
I only feel
that you should
talk to the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
Focus on the contest.
You shouldn't be involved
in these matters.
You've never believed
in my capability.
Do you think you're very strong?
Back then,
I suggested using your spider pendant
to go to Xing Luo and replace Dai Mu Bai.
My plan was so thorough,
but what have you done?
You've just ignored it.
So, you
made your own decision
to leave Martial Soul Hall
and go to Tian Dou Empire.
In order to ensure your safety,
I had to send Su Yun Tao
to go with you.
Ensure my safety?
Or it was just to spy on me?
After Su Yun Tao died,
didn't you also send out Yan?
No matter what happened in the process,
the result proved
that I was successful.
It was a big success.
I controlled Xue Qing He.
Even the whole Tian Dou
is under our control now.
I have done these things
just to tell you
I can help Martial Soul Hall,
and I can help you!
Do you really think
you were able to fake Xue Qing He?
I've done it.
I've already imprisoned Xue Qing He
and Prince Xue Xing.
The whole Tian Dou City
has changed because of me.
And then?
After the contest?
You will go back to Tian Dou
as Xue Qing He?
Why not?
Do you really think
you can deceive everyone?
Your mission now
is to help Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team
to be the champion in the final.
As for the rest,
you shouldn't bother with them.
In your eyes,
I'm always just a pawn.
A puppet that can't have
its own thoughts.
Tell me.
Tell me, what should I do
to gain trust from you?
Mother!
I've said
that you have to hide your identity!
Call me master.
Why?
Why can't I say
I'm your daughter, Qian Ren Xue?
Why do I have to pretend to be Hu Lie Na
and be a disciple of the chief?
It's Martial Soul Hall
and you're the chief.
What danger can I get into?
You may leave!
I still think
you should talk
to the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
I'll leave now.
How was it?
She didn't believe me.
What?
But she's your master.
Then what about Tang San?
I'll prove my capability.
How?
Go back
to the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's place first.
And then?
And we will
capture the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
ourselves.
Why do these bodies
look like humans?
They are Soul Beasts.
I don't understand.
Wouldn't all Soul Beasts vanish in light dots
after their Soul Rings were absorbed?
Why these bodies can still remain?
Do you know?
A Century Millennium Soul Beast
will turn into a human shape.
You mean all these?
These were close to that.
So,
they started to change.
Soul Beasts that had lived so long
were killed and abandoned here.
Were they used in experiments?
It means that the one who killed them
didn't absorb their Soul Rings,
but tried to seal the power
back into their bodies again.
That's too cruel.
I thought
when Soul Beasts turned into humans,
they could live peacefully with the humans.
But the result is like this.
I've been considering a question.
Why was Azure Bull Python
from the Star Forest
willing to cooperate with humans
against Martial Soul Hall?
Maybe this is the answer.
Maybe.
If Da Ming...
I mean, if Azure Bull Python
knows that Martial Soul Hall
has been slaughtering Soul Beasts,
it'll be very angry.
So the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
maltreated Soul Beasts
and framed the chief of Martial Soul Hall.
That made Azure Bull Python angry.
Wu,
we'd better leave now.
I'm afraid the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
may come back and see us.
Brother San.
You think,
if a Century Millennium Soul Beast
turns into a human shape,
is it really a human?
My dad has told me
that when the day comes,
they are no different from humans anymore.
Actually, I think
Soul Beasts that have become humans
had a tougher life than we think.
Because before transforming,
they had to avoid being killed by Soul Masters.
After transforming into humans,
they had no choice
but to leave their native environment
and train all over again
in the society of Soul Masters.
Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
What's wrong?
He's back.
What do we do now?
He might find Tang San.
This is bad.
We need to stop him.
Let me try.
Can you do it?
I don't talk to him often,
and I don't have a good reason
to stop him.
How about this?
I'll distract him,
and you go in to look for Tang San and Wu.
What will you do?
Just let me try.
Why are you here in Martial Soul Hall?
I'm purposely here to look for you.
Look for me?
Actually, I've been thinking
about what you told me.
Didn't you want to take me
as your pupil?
You changed your mind?
Can we talk at another place?
This is where I live.
Follow me.
We'd better not talk in Martial Soul Hall.
I still think that the exit
is related to this flower.
This interspace doesn't look like a trap,
but more like
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's secret chamber.
I don't understand.
Why did we
get in so easily?
How should we leave now?
What did we do
in his room just now?
We didn't do anything.
I just touched the petals.
Why there's no response now?
Wu?
Where have you been?
Where's Tang San?
I came back?
Why didn't Tang San come out?
From where?
Wait.
This flower should be
the entrance and exit of the interspace.
Flower.
What's going on?
You were right.
The flower is the entrance and exit
of the interspace.
I tried, but it didn't work.
But didn't we enter just now?
Just now?
These flowers are quite beautiful.
Yes, they are.
You brought me in.
Tang San?
What's going on?
Interspace.
Wu can enter it.
What's inside?
Bodies of Soul Beasts.
It's impossible that a Soul Beast
can leave a dead body behind.
Bring me in.
We've walked for quite some time.
What do you want to say?
I don't want to be your pupil.
One, because of Shi Lan Ke Battle Team.
Two, because of Martial Soul Hall.
Martial Soul Hall?
Yes.
Martial Soul Hall is trying
to manipulate the others
with their strong influence. It's annoying.
So?
So,
have you thought
about leaving Martial Soul Hall?
Where should I go?
You're a Grand Soul Land Master.
You are welcome everywhere.
Is this a message
from the royal family of Xing Luo?
No.
It's my personal view.
Everyone knows
the chief of Martial Soul Hall
is the strongest in the world.
Even though you're a Grand Soul Land Master,
you'll never be like the chief.
Why not try to change?
Even though we're in Shi Lan Ke's house now,
don't forget
we're still in Martial Soul City.
You're quite bold
to say something like this.
You haven't had this kind of idea before?
Don't say these things to anyone else.
I know.
Focus on the contest.
I hope you can enter the final.
I'll go now.
How about I walk you back?
No need.
It's been a long talk.
Do you want
some new tea from the royal family of Xing Luo?
To soothe your throat.
Teleport?
Now we can basically confirm
there's something wrong
with the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
Can you tell
your chief about it now?
No.
I need to think of a way to capture him.
Why?
The chief trusts
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master a lot.
I'm going to use my way
to prove that I am right.
I have some friends in Martial Soul Hall too.
Maybe we can try to ambush
and capture the Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
So,
they are also Grand Soul Land Masters?
The Grand Soul Land Masters
all went to the Star Forest.
It seems
he caused the Soul Beasts to come out.
But Master also said
only a Grand Soul Land Master
can contend with another Grand Soul Land Master.
But there's none.
Then tell me
about the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's
schedule tomorrow.
What are you trying to do?
Tell me first.
The contest covers these two days.
The Grand Chrysanthemum Master is the referee.
It is even Cang Hui's turn tomorrow.
After the contest ends?
He'll go back to Martial Soul Hall.
Anyone guarding him?
He's a Grand Soul Land Master.
He doesn't need protection.
Tell me which way he will take
to get back to Martial Soul Hall.
You wish to block him on the way?
Yes.
You just said
only a Grand Soul Land Master
can contend with him.
Are you still hiding
something from me?
You don't need to know.
Just tell me which way he will take tomorrow
to go back.
Don't you want to stop him
from assassinating your chief?
You won't succeed.
Let me try.
I'll tell you the route.
Brother Dai.
Where have you been?
I'll tell you on the way.
Where are we going?
To see Senior Du Gu.
We'll capture
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master tomorrow.
A battle
between Grand Soul Land Masters?
Where should we look for them?
I've talked to them.
We will leave a sign in the city tomorrow night.
Senior Du Gu will come and look for us.
Brother Dai.
Please don't tell
Ou Si Ke,
Headmaster, and the others.
Got it.
Even if something goes wrong,
it has nothing to do with the school.
I'll go first.
Little Venom Freak.
What do you want from me?
Senior.
Here, have a seat.
Have you heard
of the Grand Chrysanthemum Master?
Grand Soul Land Master of Martial Soul Hall.
What's wrong?
If Chief Ning, you,
and the Grand Sword Master join hands,
can you guys capture him alive?
You are planning something big?
Listen to me first.
This person is likely to be
the spy working for Cang Hui
in Martial Soul Hall.
If we capture him,
we'll know where Hao Tian Soul Master is.
If the three of us join hands
and take him by surprise,
I think we should be able to capture him.
Then let's go through the details.
Hold on.
Tell me first.
How do you know he is the spy?
I was brought into Martial Soul Hall,
and I saw the prize for the contest.
And the arrow
merged into the Soul Bone.
Good.
Also,
the person who brought me
into the hall
committed suicide.
Of course he should die,
or it'll cause trouble.
You are different.
When it's done,
I'll ensure your safety.
Thank you, Teacher.
After winning tomorrow's battle,
we have one opponent left in Group A.
Shi Lan Ke School?
Defeat Shi Lan Ke School,
and you will enter the final.
I've watched
Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team's matches.
Even if we enter the final,
I'm afraid we can't win.
You don't have to worry about that.
There shouldn't be any problem
with tomorrow's battle.
The only trouble
is Shi Lan Ke School.
I've helped Shi Lan Ke so much.
It's time to end it.
What should I do?
Just focus on the contest.
I'll handle the rest.
Alright.
After hearing what you've said,
you might be right.
We need to capture
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
in order to get the answer.
So, what's your relationship
with Martial Soul Hall?
None.
Then why do you want to stop him
from assassinating the chief?
One, for what Cang Hui did.
I've borrowed some special medicine
that might cause the mutation of Martial Soul.
It seems like he was poisoned.
Hold it.
Shi Nian made them like this.
Shi Nian's Martial Soul is Broken Dream.
It can cause hallucinations
that are inescapable.
They created Mutant Souls
and poisoned you and Du Gu Yan.
They even used spirit control
on their own students.
I don't care
if he's going to kill the chief
of Martial Soul Hall.
I just think
if an evil person like him
gains power one day,
it might be a scarier catastrophe
for Douluo Continent.
What else?
There's another reason.
Promise me
that you'll stay calm when you hear it.
Why should I be worried?
All the students who have been out are missing.
I suspect
that the Grand Chrysanthemum Master did it.
Yan Yan is missing?
Senior, calm down.
Listen to me.
We must capture
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master
in order to find them.
I'll capture him tomorrow!
Actually,
there's another personal reason.
Probably,
only he knows
where Hao Tian Soul Master is.
Don't worry.
We will capture him.
I've checked
the Grand Chrysanthemum Master's schedule.
After Cang Hui's match tomorrow,
he'll leave the arena.
His route back to Martial Soul Hall
is here.
You may take a look
and choose a place to ambush him.
How do you get this?
Hu Lie Na from Martial Soul Hall
gave it to me.
Martial Soul Hall can be hard to deal with.
You'd better not have
any relationship with them.
Understood.
We were just cooperating this time.
With me, Ning Feng Zhi,
and the Grand Sword Master,
we'll succeed.
There won't be a mistake.
Master.
Tang San!
Help me tie it.
Let me have a look.
Can you be gentler?
It's tight now.
You shouldn't be so weak.
When is Rong Rong coming?
I'll call her.
Your opponent in the semi-final
is likely to be Cang Hui.
Look carefully
at their Martial Soul Types.
Then we'll discuss together
what tactic to be used.
Are you both exchanging love glances?
What are you talking about?
Oh right.
Where did you go yesterday?
Master and Teacher Liu
made so many great dishes,
but you weren't there.
We were discussing
Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team.
Really?
Even though there are only a few of them,
they are indeed very strong.
Then what tactic should we use
against the three people from Martial Soul Hall?
I suspect
Xie Yue
has more than Quadruple Soul Rings.
No way.
Not many Soul Masters at this age
have Quadruple Soul Rings.
If he has Five Soul Rings,
how can we fight him?
Life is not a competition.
It won't pick a suitable opponent
for you every time.
Back then, when Lander, Er Long, and I
were wandering Douluo Continent,
we met strong opponents many times.
Fate puts the enemy you can't defeat
in front of you.
There is no time to grieve.
You can only face it.
Don't think about the match much later.
Look carefully at Cang Hui,
and win each time.
Alright!
We can do it.
Tang San.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I've promised you
that after you enter the final,
I'll bring you
to meet Hao Tian Soul Master.
Now,
I'm here to fulfill my promise.
You are bringing me to him?
He's waiting for you.
If nothing goes wrong,
the semi-final will be
Cang Hui versus Shi Lan Ke.
I'm here to tell you in advance
that Cang Hui School must win.
So,
please cooperate.
You want us to surrender?
Surrender seems bad.
I only want the result.
As for the process,
you can do whatever you want.
Fake fight?
The prize for the champion
is only two Soul Bones.
If you cooperate,
I can give one to each of your teammates.
All the hard training we had at school
is not for fake fights.
Like I said,
I only want the result.
You're humiliating the contest
and also
the participants who have trained hard.
Don't reject me so soon.
The person you wish to see
is waiting for you inside.
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪