The Long Ballad
Episode 46
I didn’t expect you to do it for me
By hitting the Crown Prince
Thanks a lot
Why are you here
You asked Emperor Tang to lock us together
I’m here to take you out
You can leave soon
I
What about you
You
What’s the price for you to go back
She’er
Before going back
I still decide to tell you something
I didn’t kill your wolf
All these years
This is the only thing
I can’t forgive Father Khan
He didn’t want to
See us two brothers care for one another
Only by restricting each other
Is best for his throne
He killed your little wolf
Made wolf skin into a quiver
Gave it to me
Why did you tell me now?
Just say what you want
What?
Afraid you won’t have a chance after I go out
Afraid I can’t accept it
The truth
Can you accept it
Even if you can accept it
Do you dare to resist
She’er
For the grassland
There must be someone between us
Stand up and do it
That person is me
Sun
What are you going to do
This is Mu Jin of the Eagle Division
You all know each other
Hiding in Dingxiang for many days
Plot a rebellion
Now Ashile Tribe
Relocated to Dingxiang
Hope you know the current affairs
Focus on Dingxiang
Anyone who has two minds
All ends like this
Rest assured
Your master didn’t come
I won’t kill you
Kill or not
Listen well
Mother
I thought you wouldn’t come to greet your mother
I will always be your son
Even if it doesn’t connect with me
Our mother and son
It’s just a perfect match
Mother
I have been in prison these few days
I often think of my childhood
Every day at that time
Fell asleep in Mother’s arms
With Mother
No need to fight, no need to grab
No worries nor fear
Is the most pleasant time
But in your heart
So-called cozy time
All fragile
Just a word from your Uncle Khan
Can easily break
Everything Mother does now
Just for the future
No one will tear us apart again
Only our mother and son
Really strong
In order to be stable
Understand?
Let’s go
Go home with Mother
Tang Emperor
A princess of Great Tang
Pretending to be the envoy of Mobei
I don’t know if it’s your arrangement
I hope it’s my arrangement
It’s a pity that the princess
Would rather be the Mobei Princess
And not willing to go back to Chang’an
Envoys
The grievances between me and Great Tang
It’s my personal business
Many reasons for this
I don’t need to say more
But since I can
On behalf as the Envoy of Mobei
That was instructed by the King of Mobei
I don’t need to say much
I can prove
King of Mobei and my father
Reach a consensus
Unanimously to form an alliance with Great Tang
In addition
How do I deal with the princess
I don’t need to explain to you guys
Is the identity of this princess
Between the ministries and Great Tang
Is the key to peace?
This is not
This indeed
It’s Great Tang’s own family affair
Has nothing to do with me
I just want to ask Tang Emperor
Your Majesty wants to release Young Khan
Dealing with Ashile Tribe
Why
Lied to be allies with the desert
Is this the tribes
That Ashley Tribe
The list of the abducted hundred names
There is still a list
The beginning of the alliance
Great Tang wanted to serve the various ministries of the Great Desert
Return the captives
Everyone, this is Ashile Tribe
Honorary roster of prisoners
Nothing missing
Therefore, Tang Emperor
Did you release Young Khan?
Young Khan intends to assassinate the East Palace
Sent someone to assassinate
As a personal servant of the prince
Except for this reason
Why do I still release
A criminal who committed such a felony
This covenant is always valid
If you don’t want to
Sign with Great Tang
I will never force
Tribes that don’t want to be allies
Don’t worry
I will still treat your people
Sent you home safe and sound
If you don’t sign
We can still leave
Yeah
You can go as you like
Not only will Great Tang not stop
Will send troops to escort
A long way
It will take time for you to return to your hometown
Presumably when you arrive home
Great Tang has put your people
They were all sent back safely
Have been sent back
Great Tang today promises
No matter whether it is an alliance or not
No worries about each tribes
And Great Tang’s ally
If you have something to ask for help in the future
Great Tang will support to the end
Good now
You can rest assured now
Yeah this is great
I just got my life back in Zhixi
Speaking of
I really owe Great Tang a kindness
What else can’t be trusted
My Tiele Tribe
Willing to form an alliance with Great Tang
We Monan will also signed
If the princess is afraid of pain
The red mud on the side can be used to stamped
Everyone, we came to Great Tang
Just to form an alliance
Are you going back empty-handed?
Just form an alliance
Yes yes yes
This this
Great Tang and various ministries
Today’s blood is an alliance
Regardless of disasters and wars in the future
Great Tang and other ministries advance and retreat together
No regrets
Mimi
If you wanna leave
I will find a way
Transfer you away from Mother
No need
Why
I want to stay with Khatun
I still have someone I want to meet
Arrived in Dingxiang
I will protect you
Changge
I know you hate me
But I’m still your second uncle
If you are willing
I will keep you in the name of the queen
Share the honor of Princess with Leyan
You can live happily in Chang’an
No one will force you to marry
Or do any
Things you don’t want to do
So you let A’Sun
Go to Dingxiang alone
Facing the unknown
Just for
Me have a stable life
That’s Tegin Sun’s own choice
You should understand his intentions
What I don’t want
Chang’an’s wealth and prosperity
I don’t want
The name of the princess
Where is A’Sun
I will be there
Dingxiang storm is approaching
Perilous
I can’t let you take risks anymore
Changge, you have to come home
Second Uncle won’t let you go again
Come home
For today’s court
My existence
It’s just a hidden danger
Why do you force me to stay
Let’s just say
You want to compensate
Come to calm your heart
Compensation
Because of your mother’s
Final hope
She hope you will be safe
This is your mother’s
Only wish
Mother
I know this day
Will come sooner or later
I will send you mother and daughter away
After that
What kind of life do you want to live
I will arrange for you
Until now
You treat me and Changge
As thoughtful as before
But
I’m not blessed anymore to enjoy
Madam, don’t be too persistent
No one can control the affairs of the temple
Even if there is no Madam
Maybe it will be today
Such a result
Not
I can’t pass this level of myself
That day
It’s the letter I wrote to you
I know
I can never go back
Although the Crown Prince never touched me
Never treated me harshly
But I betrayed him
I didn’t want to kill him
If Your Highness doesn’t kill
You will be killed
Country’s royal power
I am a woman
What can I say
That year
You saved my life
And treat Changge as your own
Teach her how to behave
Changge also regards you as a father
I can see all of these
Now I use this way
I’m still paying back what I owe you
Crown Prince
Crown Prince, what can I use to repay him?
But
I still have to thank you
Don’t be impulsive
Don’t come over
Promise me
You have to protect Changge
Her safety forever
Make her happy
Happy
Do whatever she wants
Don’t let her marry
Someone she doesn’t want to marry
Don’t let her suffer any wrongdoing
You promise me
I promise I promise
Don’t be impulsive
This time
I owe no one
A’Jin!
One is my father
One is you
No matter which one of you die
Mother can’t live, right?
Where’s Mother’s letter
Where
I want to see
Naturally burned
How can I leave evidence
Your Mother repaid me
Between dilemmas
She finally chose to kill herself
Come to seek relief
Second Uncle deserves no shame in this life
Only when I think of her
My heart always hurts badly
Changge, whether you believe it or not
Second Uncle never
Want your life
I want to protect you
But I don’t know where you are
Eventful autumn here
To be up to one’s ears in work
I don’t know many things
Later learned
Your exile
I learned that because of Great Tang
The sacrifice made
Second Uncle feels distressed
Changge stay
Let me take good care of you
If you give me another chance
I will still make
Same choice
I am willing to serve the people of Great Tang
Sacrifice oneself
But I definitely can’t
Let those who love me sacrifice for me
Dingxiang
I must go
I should have been pleased with your remarks
But now
The war with Ashile Tribe
On the verge of
This Dingxiang
If you have to go
Then your mother’s request
I’m afraid I will fail
You go
Maybe you and me from now on
Forget it
You and I are not
Ordinary people of a household
Can’t just seek
The simplest ordinary joy
Changge has grown up now
Have your own path to choose
I say no more
Child take care
Second Uncle waits for you to come back
This will always be your home
It’s true you killed my father
It’s true that you are my second uncle
If one day
You are not good to the people
I will come back to you to settle the account
Okay
A’Jin
Your daughter looks like you
Your Majesty
This is from Princess Yongning
She asked someone to submit it when I was leaving the palace
Mother
It turns out all this
It’s your choice
Regretting that Mother
Bear all this alone
Only blame Changge for understanding too late
I came today
I want to say goodbye to Mother
I am going to save
The one I love
Mother will support me, right
Madam Jin
I am Ashile Sun
I want to be with your daughter in this life
Marry Li Changge
Spend a lifetime together
I pledge my life
Protect Changge in this life
Love her forever
Give her freedom
Give her happiness
Never leave
Sincerely, Ashile Sun
So he has already visited you
Mother
This cup
Is from your daughter who is going to get married
Second cup
On behalf of A’Sun, toast you
Third cup
Mother
In the future, Ashile Sun
Will be my husband
Hope Mother knows about it
And keep A’Sun safe
Young Khan
What do you mean
Commander Lei ordered
Great Khan is severely ill
No one can enter to disturb
Who is Lei’s master?
It is me
Young Khan, please
Hurry up and report to Commander Lei
Yes
Uncle Khan
It’s me She’er
What’s wrong with you
Uncle Khan
It’s me, She’er
You don’t recognize me
Alright, I will leave
You may leave
Yes
What you look like now
It’s better than before
Looks much pleasing to the eye
Mimi, thank you Master
As long as you are obedient
I will let
Your sister and brother met
Thank you Master
But you have to remember
Back to Dingxiang
You won’t have a chance to make mistakes again
If you don’t obey
Don’t think about
Seeing your brother again
I won’t
I will be obedient
Princess, when Young Khan came back
He went to the Great Khan’s bedroom
No one can stop him
Let him go
Just do things later
Be more careful
Don’t give
Unnecessary misunderstanding
Yes
Your Majesty
How free it flies
What are you doing?
Your Majesty
You just stay there
Buzhen
Your Majesty follow me
Let me go
You
Buzhen
Sister
Buzhen, let me look at you
Yes
Hands
I don’t know why
They want to chop my finger
His Highness Sui saved me
I’m fine
It’s fine
Commander Lei, new from the west
It’s okay Sister
I don’t hurt anymore
Sister doesn’t cry
Take a step back
Yes
Buzhen
Sister
- Buzhen
- Sister
Let’s go
You let me go
- Buzhen
- Sister
You come back with me
Young Khan, why are you here?
Open the door I want to go in
This
This this
This can be explained
What
My words won’t work in Dingxiang
Young Khan, don’t be angry
I’ll explain it later
What I’ve been to today
No need to report to Khatun
I understand
I won’t let the anyone say
Any nonsense
Take me to Ashile Sun
Yes
Open the door
Young Khan please
Went to the dungeon
I’m going to see Ashile Sun
I can go by myself
Yes
When did you like
To come to the dungeon to drink
I like to see you
The unlucky in prison
This Dingxiang is better
Better appetizers?
Too lazy to talk nonsense with you
Hurry and leave after drinking
Don’t want to be found by your mother
If she comes, she comes
Is there anything I can’t let her know
The expression on your face
That’s not what I said
Shut up
I saw the Great Khan
How is he
Sick
Same as Mother said
So sick that people can’t recognize him
He also drove me away
You really believe
Overnight, Great Khan would be
Seriously ill?
Why can’t I believe it
You don’t have to provoke anymore
I’m so eager to see Uncle Khan like this
See Mother not have to live tremblingly
Can see me anytime
What’s wrong with this
Stop lie to yourself She’er
If you really believe
Why would you come to me for a drink
Young Khan
Khatun is here
You should go
Yes, Young Khan
I let you in secretly
If this is known by Khatun
Even if I have ten heads...
What are you panicking
Just walk from the back door
I will take you out
Keep your mouth shut
You won’t lose your head
I got it
Please
Young Khan, let’s hurry up
Hurry
Young Khan
I know the way, so go back first
Lest you be suspicious
Thank you, Young Khan
Greetings, Khatun.
Why are you here
I...
I called him
I want to drink
Bring some more wine
You think
Is this still your Eagle Division?
Leave
Yes
On the grassland
The majestic God of War
Now locked up here
A place where the sun doesn’t see the sun
Tell the truth
I am also a little bit reluctant
But just say what you want to say
No need to obscure
Ashile Sun is smart
No wonder your Father Khan likes you
Father Khan also likes She’er
Even without his mother
Calculate everywhere
She’er can do it sooner or later
Rely on his own strength
Recognized by the grassland
How do I pave the way for my son
No need for you to comment
Your beloved son is eager
After all, I went the wrong way
I won’t argue with you today
Only negotiate terms with you
Condition
Tang Dynasty has alliance with various ministries
Soon the army will be overwhelmed
Yicheng
What qualifications do you have
To talk to me about terms
Since you guessed it
Then I won’t lie to you
You are a smart person
A wise man submits to circumstances.
If you can make your Eagle Division
Fight for the grasslands
I can forgive you
If I gather Eagle Division
I’m afraid it’s not fighting for the grassland
But for Khatun
Fight for the so-called former Sui Dynasty
If I guessed right
Since the Khan’s Tent refused
Give the Eagle Division gromwell to begin with
No
Maybe earlier
The owner of Khan’ Tent
Is not Father Khan anymore
It’s just you
The Eagle Division’s plague
Bear Division wanted to attack and kill Eagle Division in Mobei
And my father’s illness
It’s all your arrangement
It’s all because of you
Is it?
Without you
She’er on the grassland
Will not be threatened
Ashile Sun
Aren’t you very loyal?
It’s you now
Time to help your brother
I won’t help him
Won’t help you
Good
Bring Mu Jin
Mu Jin
Yicheng!
Mu Jin concealed the battle
Privately sneaked into Dingxiang with intent to be unruly
This is a capital crime
The reason why I spared his life
It’s also for your face
Take him down
Yes
Mu Jin
I promise you
But I have two conditions
Speak
One, cure Mu Jin
Two, cure my father’s illness
Your appetite is not small
I can promise you the first one
Of curing Mu Jin
As for your Father Khan
Then wait for the Eagle Division
To win the battle for me
I will naturally let
You father and son are reunited
You finally admitted
Father Khan’s illness is caused by you