The Long Ballad
Episode 45
If I hadn’t seen it with my own eyes
Heard
I don’t believe in all of this either
The reason why I keep hiding
Did not show up
Just want to see
What other unseen things will Ashile Tribe do?
Did not expect
They even faked it
News of the dispatch of troops
I can’t bear it
Only then came forward to prove
Zhixi died
Chihe jumped out
Preventing the peace alliance
Everyone may wish to recall memories
Who was the first in Sifang Pavilion?
Spread Ashile Tribe
News about the attack on the desert
Who would it be
Tiele Tribe
That’s right
It was Tiele Tribe
Hurry and eat
Even if you go on a hunger strike
Father Khan won’t let you
Come back to your mother
If your mother find out
She will be sad
I won’t see Mother from now on
Only you will be by my side
No one can separate us
You are surprisingly quiet today
I thought you would be like
The same as when I was young
Keep grumbling with me
Don’t be too self-righteous
Did you argue with Yicheng?
That’s my mother
Don’t call her by her first name
Finally get together with your mother
But mother and son are at odds
This is...
You pretend like you understand
You use Mimi to get information
Here again now
Fake appearance
I really look down on you
I’m willing to do anything for Changge
This Li Changge
What kind of woman is she
You and Mimi for her
Don’t even want your life
You don’t need to understand
I’m just curious about her
Even a bit
Jealous
Ashile Sun
For Li Changge
Even the Ashile Tribe
Don’t you want it?
You voluntarily go to jail today
Didn’t you also put the Ashile Tribe aside
I don’t know if Mother will hate me
Enduring for so long
Finally waited for this day
At the moment
I will never give up
She’er
Someday
You will come back to me
So enjoyable
Zhixi’s fake death
Simply superb
Changge
How did you think of it
I thought about it
Use this to grab the hand behind someone’s back
But even so
I can’t hold Yixheng’s weak spot
It might hurt
Chihe family
What does this mean
Threatened by family
This is Yicheng
The tactics used in other tribes
Yicheng
Is an evil person
So we can’t
Take her lightly
Maybe she has other
Backup plan
It’s possible in this Chang’an city
There are still more Chijing Tribe
Hao Du, I need your help
Don’t move
Thanks to you guys today
Guarding Great Tang
It’s my responsbility
Not right
There’s one less person
You mean the person next to Yicheng
Yes
That person’s name is Yang Cheng
Just today
It’s a private transfer of troops
Can’t ask Yicheng directly
What to do then
Although Chihe was part of the Chijing Tribe
But the main evil has not been eliminated
It’s not a success
Take these people back first
We have to let Leyan
Enter the palace before the court
State of affairs
Okay
Go
Be honest
Leyan
Outside teahouse
Go
Leyan
Don’t act rashly
Hand over the fish token to me
Hao Du
He just wants to take away Chijing Tribe
Won’t do anything to Leyan
Princess
You are really smart
We can exchange with you
Hao Du
Don’t exchange
I will count three times
What to do
You decide for yourself
Li Changge
Give me the fish token
We exchange with him
Hao Du
Li Changge
Ok I will release them
Changge
I will personally take you there
Then they will obey orders
And let people out
But what you have
Is Tang Emperor’s beloved daughter
If you dare to hurt her
You will never leave alive
Stop talking nonsense with me
Throw me the fish token
The Sui Dynasty
It’s just self-defeating
Less nonsense
Since I has fallen into your hands
Want to kill
Not important
Listen well
Ready soon
How about it
Have the people been accounted for it?
All confessed
Tomorrow morning
I will report the truth to the ministers
Then you will follow the plan
I will be
In front of the envoys
Uncover the true face of Yicheng
Facilitate the alliance
Let me
Does it hurt?
You can cry if it hurts
Don’t bear it
I’m still here
Can you restrain a bit
Also
Hao Du made a great contribution this time
That one will definitely give you a marriage
Then I
Right
She wasn’t hurt deeply
Won’t delay your major event
I’m leaving now
A’Sun
Are you okay in jail
Young Master, you are back
Master waited for you all night
Father
You are the one who transferred the troops without authorization
It was an emergency
I didn’t explain to you
To make a decision when it’s time to decide
Really worthy of being
my son
The remnants of the former Sui Dynasty
Had no choice but to remove them
Yes
Come with me
Kneel down
Kneel here
Kowtow
Pour the wine
Father
This is not the custom
From today
You are from our Du family
Your name will be on the family tree
You are my son
Father
I know you are always confidant
I want to you to rely on your own ability
Climb to a high place
But
Since you want to be the Prince Consort
I as a father
I have to pave the road for you
Father
You said it wrong
You are already my son
Understand?
Father
Good
Child
Accompany me into the palace
Report to His Majesty
Good
Your Majesty
Yang Cheng was the right-hand support of Emperor Yang of the Sui Dynasty
After the Sui Dynasty
He assembled all
The surviving soldiers of the former Sui Dynasty
Advisor Du is having trouble
Let Hao Du speak
Your Majesty
All this group of people have their household registrations cancelled
Now like a ghost
Survive in the world
They call themselves Chijing Tribe
Loyal to Princess Yicheng
Although this time they admitted
The crime of spreading rumors
But it’s a pity
Yang Cheng alone
Contact Yicheng
Yang Cheng would not talk
And also tried to commit suicide
So this time
I’m afraid I can’t execute Yi Cheng
No hurry
The man with all wings
How far can we struggle
Yes
Everybody
Yang Cheng is with Yicheng
Envoy Chihe
Are from the former Sui
Chihe thinks
Yang Cheng wants to restore the Sui Dynasty
The Sui Dynasty and the Great Deserts peace alliance
Tiele Tribe will naturally rise
When the time comes
Join Ashile Tribe
Don’t be surprised
Yi Cheng has been married to the grassland for many years
Secretly
Chijing Tribe remains
All under Yang Cheng
Naturally no one has seen her
Yang Cheng is one of the few who obey her
And someone who can identify her
It was all arranged by Yicheng
Mobei Princess is really good at talking
Just a few words
Will bring disaster to the east
Intended to point to me
I’m married and weak woman
How could he be the master behind the scenes?
You said this by yourself
None of us said that
Don’t worry
Yang Cheng went to court without uttering a word
Just begging to die
I wait to save his life
I haven’t gotten a hand to ask him
Not to mention that Yang Cheng is so loyal
How can he betray Khatun
Khatun, look
Everyone dare not speak
How dare I pour dirty water
Since you know it’s slander
Everyone should leave, right?
What are you doing here?
Special Envoy is here!
Everybody
This is my Great Tang
Edict written to you by hand
In short
If the various ministries are at war
Great Tang must advance and retreat together
Great Tang and its various ministries depend on blessings and disasters
Civilized
Food and drink
Reclaiming wasteland and planting
Business relations
If needed
Great Tang never excuses
If Great Tang has slavery
Self-defeating covenant
Good
I’ll take my father’s place
My Monan
Will sign first
Then we
Will also sign
Then should we sign or not
Let’s form an alliance with Great Tang
Let’s sign too
Still ok
It’s still fair
Good for everyone
Wait a minute
Hao Du
You clean up the rest of the Chijing Tribe
Make great contributions
But you transferred your troops privately
But committed an offense
I am guilty
Father, this matter was my idea
It has nothing to do with Hao Du
So
I want to punish your Prince Consort
Leyan didn’t mean to purposely hide it from Father
I just don’t want to startled the enemy
This matter
Princess
Prince Consort
Father
My Yan’er has really grown up
Hao Du
No, Young Master Du
I hand Yan’er to you
You have to treat her well
If you dislike my daughter in the future,
Delayed your future
Or fading and relaxing over time
I don’t blame you
But you must keep her intact
Sent back to me
Thank you, Your Majesty
Your Majesty, please rest assured
I must take good care of the princess
Not because she is a princess
Because
She is Leyan
Good
Let’s wait for Young Master Wei
To return from the peace alliance
We’ll just pick a day to get married
Thank you, Your Majesty
You can’t sign this alliance agreement
I can’t just stand by
Watching everyone
By this fake princess
Push into the fire pit
Mimi
Fake
She is nothing at all
Mobei Princess
Her true identity is
The one who was wiped out
Daughter of the former Prince of the Tang Dynasty
Li Changge
Turned out to be her
She is a fake princess
What’s going on
Really unexpected
Daughter of the former prince
How could there be such a thing
Mimi Guli
I will never allow you
Destroy the princess’s plan
This this
This is simply
Acted on the order of Li Changge
It’s just that she wants to put each tribe
Involved in the war
Just an excuse
What she wants
Just one
A battle draped personally by the Emperor Tang
This can make the Tang Army
Exhausted in the battle
Like this
She can kill the emperor for revenge
If Li Changge
Take any more action
You are in front of everyone
Expose her identity
Otherwise
Your brother Buzhen and also Mu Jin
Mu Jin
You think I don’t know
Mu Jin has
Sneak into Dingxiang?
Maybe at this moment
In the hands of Lei Meng
Receiving Qianao
But I will do whatever you say
Khatun
I beg you
I beg you to forgive Bu Zhen
Don’t die with Mu Jin, okay?
I do everything
I listen to you everything
Then it depends on you
Your performance
For hatred
She is a member of Great Tang
But can be with the remnants of the former Sui Dynasty
Cooperate with Chijing
What Three Armies
People dejected
She doesn’t care at all
So this time the peace alliance
Simply
It’s just a conspiracy of Li Changge
Turned out to be her conspiracy
Hidden deep enough
Yeah yeah
Don’t be too sloppy
We still have to consider the long-term plan
Yes yes yes
Take Li Changge away temporarily
I will present to His Majesty
To be decided by His Majesty
Changge
Did not expect
Something like this will happen
Father
Changge
When did Yicheng know
The identity of Changge
I don’t know
Now the envoys of various ministries in the desert
I’m afraid can’t wait
To see how I punish Changge
To show sincerity
Your Majesty
Various ministries of the desert
I’m the one who is afraid
Not Li Changge
So Young Master Wei said
They can’t believe me
I dare not
I think
Even if Li Changge is executed
It doesn’t help
Then what do you say should be done
The minister dare not say anything
Father
You have said
To forgive Li Jiancheng
With Li Yuanji relatives
Now built the identity of the widow
Made public
Proper placement
If the emperor
The minister will die to the end
Father
Young Master Wei
Go see Yicheng tomorrow
She made this move
It’s nothing more than to ask me
To release the Young Khan
No matter what she wants tomorrow
You tell her
I only need all the ministries in the desert
Captives in the hands of the Ashile
I understand
Father
No one will hurt Changge
Yan’er
Get up
Yan’er, remember
Stop the war by killing
Never the right way
Strong country and strong soldiers
Conspiracy
Come as you like
Great Tang
Will never give in
Time to eat
You don’t have anything
Looks like your mother doesn’t spend less money
I am not hungry
Eat it, I’ll take it to you
No need
You eat
To avoid seeing Sirius
As a starving ghost
I don’t believe we can’t get out
You have faith in Emperor Tang
Still have faith in your mother
I am right, your Li Changge
Is confident
If she is a loyal person
Will never let you
Just die here
I hope she doesn’t
Jump into this muddy water again
She’er
If we this time
Can get out alive
I will continue
To be enemies with your mother
To the death
Ashile Tribe
Great Tang
Former Sui Dynasty
Are these really that important?
Why must it be mixed together?
You can’t talk to your Li Changge
Find a peaceful place
Do you live a happy life?
Is that better?
Natural good
Only the world is really peaceful
The people can be at ease
Khatun
His Majesty of Great Tang
Only want Ambassador Wei to come
Eagle Division intended to murder the East Palace
Refers to the recognition of Khatun and Young Khan
Is the master behind it
Such an important case is unfinished
Your Majesty will try
Can’t get away
Ambassador Wei is so straightforward
I will get to the point
Let my son go
I promise
Within five years
Ashile Tribe and Great Tang will not
Meet on the battlefield
The covenant is meant to be signed
Just because of the leader of peace alliance
Is the daughter of Li Jiancheng
So the ministries gave up the peace alliance
To join is still so
So-called promise
I’m afraid it’s just a sentence
It’s just light and flirty
What does Tang Emperor want
I heard that in Ashile Tribe’s hands
Are many prisoners from various parts of the desert
Great Tang’s appetite
Isn’t it too big?
Khatun
People are uneasy now
Want to stabilize
Envoys of the various ministries of the desert
Severely punishing Young Khan
Is best to show
The Great Tang’s way
Khatun would like to see me
I’m afraid I don’t know
This makes sense
Sorry
I really can’t help you this time
Peace alliance is lost
90% of those who don’t want to sign up
That means
Working hard for the remaining 10%
The remaining 10%
Is tidying up
Prepare to return to the desert tomorrow
Where is A’Sun
Ashile Sun and Ashile She’er
Have special status
Separately in prison
No visits
But they have one room
Not to fight
Changge
Ashile Sun does not hesitate to reveal his identity
To drag himself into the water
Dead fish
He did
Probably with you this time
Almost killed
He saved me more than once or twice
If not for him
Maybe from the cliff
I died the day I fell
You guys have known each other a long time ago
So he was the one who saved you
If this time Ashile Sun
Be able to survive
As your brother
I can trust you to him
Before meeting him
I never thought
I can live and die with someone
After meeting him
I never thought about being with someone else
Spend the rest of your life together
Your Majesty
Yicheng agreed
Yes
Ashile Tribe will return to Dingxiang tomorrow
She asked for Young  Khan
In front of all the people in the desert
Leave with her
But she can think of it
Follow her
Your Majesty
She also wants Ashile Sun
Four days
As Young Master, it’s still the first time
Been detained for so long
It seems that the situation is not very optimistic
What
Afraid of death
When does the warriors of the grassland be afraid of death
If you were wronged here this time
I can’t help you
I heard it right
Ashile Sun would actually apologize
This is the death of man
Is the word good?
Some things are not clear at the moment
There will be no chance again
She’er
Blame it on you
Young Khan from Ashile Tribe
No chance
I don’t think so
I, Ashile She’er, insisted
This prison of the Tang Dynasty
I must be sleepy
Bastard child
If we really can get out
Apologize to me
Have a drink with me
Maybe I can forgive you
Forgive
As long as you are Yicheng’s son
I’m still Khan’s adopted son
The word is between you and me
It’s impossible
She’er
Forgiveness
Next life
You really think you are dead
You never said before
Such frustrating words
I ask you
If you live again
What do you want to do
I don’t know
But I will never leave the grassland
How nice the grassland is
Vast and beautiful
Don’t need too many soldiers
No need for subordinates
Just with the person you like
Together
Horseback hunting
Cattle and sheep
At this point you are with me
Thought of it together
Who rarely talk to you
Think of it together
What’re you guys up to?
Ashile Sun
You must not go with them
Don’t forget the key
Thanks for your help
You’re welcome
Take him away
If you want to kill him
I’m not opposed to it actually
As long as you don’t move me
But
Great Tang’s Crown Prince?
How dare you
actually hit me alone
I don’t believe you’ll be able to do it
You’ve actually don’t want to go overboard right?
I...
I thought I wouldn’t do it in jail
I was afraid of leaving trails
But since Young Khan doesn’t want
to lose face
That simply
Do nothing but never stop
I can finally be a good friend
And get revenge
You...
You dare to stop me
Greetings Crown Prince
Why do you want to kill Ashile Sun?
It simply because he killed Shengxin
Everyone in the world despises him
All despise Sheng Xin
Because of his life, it’s not worth pursuing
If I...
I’m not going to be a good friend
and yet he already died
But Sheng Xin is a ghost
the villain next to Your Highness
You’re speaking nonsense
Hao Du already swept clean of the rest of remaining enemies
They have confessed that they had
planted Shen Xinan as their spy earlier in Luoyang
Was placed by Your Highness’s side
To confuse Your Highness’s mind
He took the advantage of the convenience provided by Your highness
and waited for the right opportunity
If you don’t believe the bigger picture in front of you
then Your Highness must ask in person
If you don’t believe
His Majesty would like to seek an audience with Tegin
You are the famous Tegin of Eagle Division
who’s unwillingly to salute to the Emperor of the Tang Dynasty
Simply
let’s just say
Li Changge’s followers
are naturally reluctant to bow down to her second uncle
Take a look around
For my niece
What kind of things can you even offer?
In here I will offer you two choices
You have probably seen this box before
It’s Changge’s household registration
I added a copy of yours
From here
You can change your surname into Wan
Stay with Changge in Chang’an
In here there can’t be an Ashile Sun
but I promise you no worries forever
This choice
Changge has already refused
So I put this thing
So that’s why I prepared to give this to you
You’re also unwillingly to leave her side
until the day when the knife will lick the blood (until the end of the bloodshed)
I only want her to do what she wants to do
Furthermore
I also won’t
Abandon my surname as Ashile
Then this second choice
Like I said earlier
I’m guessing Sun has a clear understanding
Understood
For Changge
You’re willingly to fight with your fate
With no hesitation
Before leaving Changan
You’ll need to see someone
I thought
He was my friend
Why did he lie to me
Is it because I’m so stupid?
Of course not
Your Highness is just kind
Too credulous
You don’t need to comfort me
I know in my heart
Actually Father can’t look down on me
This is my first time
Want to work hard for one person
Want to avenge him
Avenge him
But in the end
It’s all a joke
Your Highness was alone and courageous
For friends
Now you find that the sentiment is fake
Your Highness is regretting
Regret
After that
Will Your Highness still
Believe in a person without reservation
Will
But not
So blind
Isn’t that great
Your Highness has also grown
How about you
What did you try to save?
Do you regret something?
Your Highness
The past cannot be traced
People want to look forward