(Police)
(Episode 12)
Make sure not to miss a spot.
- Yes, sir.
(Police)
- There are photos here.
- Take it.
There are more here.
Why would anyone hide photos
under the couch?
There's one here.
Isn't that Cheon Seo Jin? Take it.
Yes, sir.
Hey. Move this.
Where are the bars?
I'm sorry! Please don't kill me.
- Please don't kill me.
- It's okay. We're the police.
- I'm sorry!
What's your name?
I'm Shim Su Ryeon.
Were you locked in here?
Joo Dan Tae...
locked us in here.
How long have you been here?
What's today's date?
Please take this child
to the hospital first.
Please. Quick!
Call an ambulance right now.
We found people underground.
Two.
Are you okay?
Please light the way.
It sounds crazy,
but can you trust me for once?
I have a great plan...
to finish off Dan Tae.
What did you just say?
You want to get back at him.
Then do it.
I'll take his money.
But you can't tell anyone...
about me.
What do you say? Deal?
Forget it. I don't trust you.
What if I leave this to you?
Protect your daughter yourself.
You must protect your child
at all costs.
Since you're her mom.
Mothers need to get evil to protect
their children sometimes, no?
You said a mother should do
anything for her child.
I canceled the contract?
Didn't you know?
Na Ae Gyo suddenly
notified me last night...
that she was canceling the contract.
I know you wanted it for a while.
So I came to ask
why you changed your mind.
What are you talking about?
She said she needed the cash
urgently.
She seemed desperate,
so I didn't even charge her
the penalty.
No one can cancel the contract
without my permission.
Then did Na Ae Gyo deceive you?
(Property Sale Contract
Cancellation)
You must've trusted her
a great deal.
Enough to bet your all.
The person you have reached is
unavailable. Please leave...
My money...
How dare you take off with my money?
I'll kill you, Na Ae Gyo.
You can really get rid
of Joo Dan Tae?
As long as you do as I say.
We'll make...
Joo Dan Tae guilty of things,
one by one.
I'll help you, Cheon Seo Jin.
So that your daughter and Yoon Chul
can be proven innocent.
If you play along well,
we'll be able to get Eun Byeol's
necklace from him.
Really?
What do I have to do?
Tonight,
someone will die.
Who?
Na Ae Gyo.
Na Ae Gyo...
Seok Kyung's birth mom?
So you knew.
I never met her.
I only know...
that Dan Tae has been meeting her
secretly about Cheonsoo District.
Did she take off with his money?
Pretty much.
Why do you want...
to kill her?
Are you telling me
to help you murder someone?
It's not your first time.
You helped Joo Dan Tae
to kill Su Ryeon,
didn't you?
Did you forget already?
It's time to pay him back...
for everything I've received.
You don't have to do it
if you don't want to.
If you want to live in misery
in the palm of his hand forever.
I'll do it. I'll do anything.
But you have to keep your promise.
Give me Eun Byeol's necklace.
Don't worry. I'll keep my promise.
Na Ae Gyo will
die tonight at 10 p.m.
We must finish everything
before then.
(1 hour before Na Ae Gyo's death)
(Sleep inducer)
What took you so long?
I asked you to bring me drinks
ages ago.
Who are you
so desperately looking for?
Who is this Na Ae Gyo?
Why? Are you
going to find her for me?
Slow down. You'll get drunk.
Stop getting on my nerves
and get lost.
Darn it. Seriously.
Bring the money to the storage
by 10 p.m. and I'll spare your life.
(Na Ae Gyo)
It's time.
I put his clothes
and shoes in there.
Update me on his every move.
He may wake up.
He's passed out.
He won't wake up
even if you beat him with a stick.
This has to work.
Eun Byeol's and my lives
depend on it.
I can trust you, right?
Please check the memory card.
(30 minutes
before Na Ae Gyo's death)
- Where's Na Ae Gyo?
- She's heading to the warehouse.
Be careful.
You too.
(1 minute before Na Ae Gyo's death)
Hello?
Joo Dan Tae is trying to kill me.
Save me.
Where am I?
Are you okay? Were you hurt?
I'm okay.
Thank goodness.
Escort her safely.
Here.
Dan Tae gave this ring to Ae Gyo.
Use it as evidence.
(Rest in Peace)
(Shim Su Ryeon)
(4 hours after Na Ae Gyo's death)
Please take care of the rest.
Stay safe, Logan.
Where's Dan Tae's phone?
Come to the storage
with the other guys right now.
(Power off)
Joo Dan Tae, you're doomed.
Stay here and keep an eye on him.
Everyone to the cottage.
(Emergency Medical Center)
It's been a while, Seok Hoon.
We'll chat later.
Leave Ro Na to me now.
You stay out of it.
No. Let me come with you.
I can't trust anything grown-ups say
without seeing it with my own eyes.
Mom, will Ro Na be okay?
You trust me, right?
I'll protect her.
Don't worry.
Where's Seok Kyung?
I told her to stay
in the study room.
That's good.
The police will storm any minute.
Don't go home tonight.
Leave now
and take Seok Hoon with you.
I'll take over from here.
Whatever you do,
I'm on your side.
Okay. Thanks for trusting me.
Ms. Shim?
Where am I?
I'm about to ask you...
to do something difficult.
I'm planning to punish
the people who harmed you.
If we do that,
can we go back to the way we were?
I'll do anything.
I'd like to pay you and Seol A back.
Go to the cottage in Pangyo,
place the pictures,
and lock the basement door.
(5 hours and 20 minutes
after Na Ae Gyo's death)
(6 hours after Na Ae Gyo's death)
Explain what's going on.
Did Na Ae Gyo really die?
You couldn't have done it
on your own.
Who's behind you? Logan?
You'll see tomorrow.
Just finish things up well.
I did everything you told me to do.
Keep your word.
Where's Eun Byeol's necklace?
It's in Dan Tae's cottage in Pangyo.
This is the key to the drawer.
I don't know exactly where it is.
Get back before Dan Tae wakes up.
6 a.m. at the latest.
The police will start searching
the cottage in the morning.
What are you waiting for?
Gosh!
Darn it. Which drawer is it?
Where's the necklace?
(Alarm, 6 a.m.)
(8 hours after Na Ae Gyo's death)
How are you feeling?
What happened yesterday?
You blacked out
because you drank too fast.
Should I make some soup?
No, you don't have to.
My head is splitting.
Why can't I remember anything?
I didn't drink that much.
Where's my phone?
I couldn't find it in the room.
I haven't seen it. Should I call it?
This is a search and
seizure warrant.
Dan Tae!
- Don't step on this.
- Dan Tae!
Dan Tae! Dan Tae!
Don't step on this either.
- Search the place.
- These people...
- Joo Dan Tae, correct?
- I am.
You are under arrest...
for murder and desecration
of a human corpse.
Cuff him.
What are you talking about?
- Whom did I kill?
- Stop it.
Are you people out of your minds?
Na Ae Gyo died last night.
Ae Gyo died?
- Oh my gosh.
- Let's talk at the station.
- Wait.
- Dan Tae.
Dan Tae. What's going on?
You killed a person?
You didn't right? Talk to me!
He has a soft heart.
He can't even kill a bug.
There must be a mistake.
- Let go!
- Then...
can you confirm where he was
last night?
You know...
I came home early and went to sleep.
Tell them.
We use separate rooms,
so I'm not positive.
I know he was drunk...
and very upset.
That's all I know...
Wait. He kept calling someone.
Who?
He said, "Na Ae Gyo."
Why you... Have you gone mad?
Let go of me!
I did not kill her.
Show me proof!
I won't go anywhere until you do.
Call my secretary. Get my lawyer!
Darn it.
We found this in the chimney.
Oh my gosh.
A partially burned glove,
raincoat, and shoes.
- Take it as evidence.
- Yes, sir.
It wasn't me.
I've never even seen that before.
I saw muddy footprints...
by the door this morning,
so I thought it was strange.
Did you really kill that woman?
The kids' biological mom?
How do you know...
who Ae Gyo is?
Take him away.
Let go!
What do you mean, I killed someone?
Who are you?
Why is he there? What are you doing?
Let go!
What are you doing here?
You punk!
It's payback.
Payback? Ridiculous!
Hey! Logan!
Why is he over there?
(Search History)
He's searched up a warehouse
and a crematorium.
- What about the dashcam?
- It doesn't have a memory card.
He must've taken it out
before he started driving.
There's a ring here.
Collect it.
Retrieve all fingerprints too.
Cheong A Group's Chairman,
Joo Dan Tae,
has been arrested
without a warrant just now.
The victim, Ms. Na, is...
the birth mother
of his two children,
Chairman Joo's business partner,
as well as his mistress
for a long time.
This is a shock to everyone.
Give me updates.
The DNA is a match
with Joo Dan Tae's.
We found these
at the animal crematorium.
These look like ashes of a bag.
Is this the man who came last night?
Yes, it is.
Last night, I think it was because
of money,
but Chairman Joo seemed furious.
It was about selling properties
without his permission.
He was beating the woman
like he was going to kill her.
I've already put
the surveillance camera footage...
into this flash drive.
There's something here.
It's an urn.
An urn?
Oh my gosh! It can't be!
Send it to NFS right away.
Find out if there's any DNA left.
- Rush it.
- Yes, sir.
Oh Yoon Hee, why aren't you
picking up?
Okay.
They found human ashes...
in your study.
Ashes?
What ridiculous gibberish is that?
Why would there be ashes in my home?
I heard you said
you'd kill Na Ae Gyo.
We have a witness.
What witness?
I slept all day. Who saw me? Where?
I'm the witness.
What is this gibberish?
I met with him yesterday morning
in his penthouse.
He was extremely angry at Na Ae Gyo.
The look in his eyes was terrifying.
So I recorded it just in case.
My money...
How dare you take off with my money?
I'll kill you, Na Ae Gyo.
You have a clear motive,
and all the circumstances
point to you.
Will you still deny it?
Is there any record of her
making direct threats?
She said this to me.
I recorded it just in case.
I waited because I have
a favor to ask you.
(Recording)
Get rid...
of Shim Su Ryeon.
Oh Yoon Hee. You...
You've got a lot of enemies
around you,
which made it much easier for me,
of course.
What?
You taught me.
If there's no proof,
I must make the proof.
How do you feel
now that you're the murderer?
Oh Yoon Hee! Cheon Seo Jin!
You witches did it, didn't you?
I'm going to kill all of you.
I'm going to kill you!
I'll kill you!
Let go!
I'm going to kill her! Let go of me!
Don't worry.
You won't rot in jail alone.
Good luck.
Oh Yoon Hee! Stop there.
Where's Na Ae Gyo?
What have you done to her?
Let go of me! I didn't kill her.
This is all a setup!
Get that crazy witch, Oh Yoon Hee!
I didn't kill her!
I didn't do such a thing. Let me go!
(National Forensic Service)
- Block the reporters.
- Yes, sir.
Don't take photos.
Get out of the way.
What happened at the cottage?
(Detective)
When I asked for a divorce,
Joo Dan Tae...
forged my death...
and locked me up at the cottage.
And every night,
he threatened me to give him
all of my wealth.
When I refused,
he...
did terrible things to me
in the basement.
Do you remember who hurt you?
Yes.
Who is it?
It's okay. You can tell them.
It's Mr. Joo Dan Tae
from the penthouse.
(VIP Patient Room)
Everything is fine, right?
It's all good?
Everything is done.
I told my testimony.
It's all thanks to you, Logan.
I was so scared...
that you'd disappear again.
I'm so glad.
I'm very glad.
Don't leave me again.
I'm sorry.
Please investigate thoroughly.
- Have a safe trip back.
- Goodbye.
Secretary Do,
get the divorce papers ready.
Check if it's possible for me
to get all my properties,
50 million dollars, and shares
to Cheong A Group back from him.
Look into it right now.
My goodness.
When did you come back?
Didn't you say that you were
going to study in the study room?
Everything you've said.
Are they all true?
Are you saying I'm lying?
You're talking as if you were
waiting for this to happen.
As if you knew all the things
my dad has done.
Did my dad really kill
my birth mother?
You must be shocked because your dad
has been arrested.
But this is your dad's true self.
Although, you probably already knew.
Are you completely innocent?
Is my dad the only bad one?
What?
I don't care about who you are.
You don't want to be my mom, anyway.
I guess I'm really an orphan now.
Where are you, Seok Hoon?
Come to Cheong A Medical Center
right now.
Why?
We have to see Mom.
Mom?
(Police)
Chairman! What happened?
What took you so long to get here,
you useless rat?
You texted me to come
to the storage,
so I got everyone there.
What storage? I didn't text you
such a thing!
Hire a lawyer right now.
Get every lawyer you can,
whether it be 10 or 100!
I'll kill you if you don't get me
out of here!
Get your work done, you rat!
What's happening?
A murder? Is Chairman Joo crazy?
I can't believe...
that I was his neighbor!
I'm too scared to live
at this condo now.
It's a relief that he didn't
kill her in the building.
Why is that a relief?
From Chairman Joo to Dr. Ha,
how many murderers have we had
at Hera Palace lately?
How could that be?
How could Chairman Joo kill
the twins' birth mother?
I saw the detectives leaving
just now.
Did they get all evidence?
It's exactly what you saw
on the news.
I'm exhausted. Let's talk
another time.
The woman we saw at the auction...
is the twins' birth mother.
You know, the one
with huge sunglasses...
and colorful clothes.
The one who called
50 million dollars.
No wonder she called
such a high price.
It was her?
I guess she's been planning
to scam Chairman Joo for a while.
She sold all the Cheonsoo District
properties and fled.
Poor Chairman Joo.
He lost his money, got betrayed,
and is now a murderer.
Why would you feel bad for him?
Why would you feel bad for a man...
who hid his children's
birth mother...
as his mistress for 20 years?
He should be executed right away.
Seo Jin, how much did you know?
You couldn't have known anything.
I didn't know anything.
I've never even seen
the birth mother.
You didn't know that Shim Su Ryeon
is alive, either?
What?
What do you mean?
Who's alive?
You haven't heard?
It's on the news everywhere.
Shim Su Ryeon. She's back.
And she's alive.
She's been locked
in the Ex-wife 1 Cottage...
for two whole years.
A...
A cottage?
Apparently, Chairman Joo locked
Su Ryeon up at the cottage...
and tortured her
while only giving her water.
I almost peed myself
because I was so scared.
What's happening now, then?
Who's his wife? Su Ryeon or you?
Why is that important?
As if being his wife is good.
Not getting involved
with that psychopath is luck.
Shim Su Ryeon is alive?
No way! That can't be.
Why do you want to kill her?
Are you telling me
to help you murder someone?
It's not your first time.
You helped Joo Dan Tae
to kill Su Ryeon,
didn't you?
Did you forget already?
It's time to pay him back...
for everything I've received.
It was Shim Su Ryeon
behind Oh Yoon Hee!
Does that mean that I've been
helping Shim Su Ryeon myself?
- Oh, my.
- Goodness.
No!
- What?
- No!
No!
Ms. Cheon? Where is she going?
We haven't even gotten to the part
where Ro Na is alive.
What if there's a war
at Hera Palace?
I bet Su Ryeon hates everyone here.
I'm getting goosebumps.
I don't feel good about this.
What if Su Ryeon tries to harm us?
What did we do wrong?
Chairman Joo is the one
who kidnapped and locked her up!
Don't get scared!
And that was so long ago.
What?
Don't get scared!
(Unit 4502
The bell is ringing.)
Open the door, Oh Yoon Hee!
I know you're there. Come out!
Come out and talk to me!
You knew that Shim Su Ryeon was
alive all along, didn't you?
Get out!
What are you up to?
Tell me!
(Unit 4502)
(Cheon Seo Jin)
(Power off)
My pretty daughter.
I...
miss you so much.
Eun Byeol! Eun Byeol!
Ms. Jin.
Ms. Jin!
Eun Byeol. Eun Byeol!
Eun Byeol.
What happened to her room?
The person you have reached...
Eun Byeol.
- Where are they?
- The phone is turned off. Please...
Where's Eun Byeol?
I sent her to the pool...
since I'm cleaning out her room.
There were too many books
and clothes that she doesn't need.
I'm replacing her furniture
as well...
to cheer her up.
Why are you doing that?
If I don't do it, who will?
I'll take full care of her
from now on.
She needs me
more than she needs her mom.
Didn't you know that?
What?
You crazy...
You're fired.
Get out of my home now.
Didn't you hear me?
Get out before I drag you out.
You're the one who needs to leave.
Come in.
(Warrant for Arrest)
Cheon Seo Jin.
What is it?
I have nothing more to say...
about Dan Tae.
Do you admit
to working with Joo Dan Tae...
in the abduction
and false imprisonment...
of Shim Su Ryeon and Bae Ro Na?
Abduction?
I know nothing about it.
The victims already gave
their statements.
Did you do it to steal
Shim Su Ryeon's fortune...
and husband?
Who said such nonsense?
I didn't even know
that Su Ryeon was alive.
Last night...
you used the secret passage...
and went to the cottage
where Shim Su Ryeon was being held.
Yoon Hee.
Was this what you were trying to do?
You are under arrest
for kidnapping, false imprisonment,
and assault.
Cuff her.
Ms. Jin, where's Eun Byeol?
I have to see her.
This isn't true.
Bring her to me. Hurry.
Hurry!
Don't worry too much
about Eun Byeol.
I'll take care of her like her mom.
I told you,
she's like a daughter to me.
Where is Eun Byeol?
Where is she? No. Let go of me!
Let go!
That's right.
Ro Na's mom from unit 4502
said to give this to you.
She said you'd know.
Take it.
No. No. Give it back! No!
Who are you?
Are you with Yoon Hee?
No, right?
Tell me you're not.
What did you do with Eun Byeol?
Let go! I'm innocent.
I didn't do it!
Something went seriously wrong.
Let go!
Let go. Ms. Jin. Where's Eun Byeol?
I didn't do it!
Chairman Joo Dan Tae,
you'll have to brace yourself.
The murder of Na Ae Gyo,
the kidnapping and false
imprisonment of Shim Su Ryeon,
and the attempted murder
of Bae Ro Na.
Su Ryeon was alive?
She was with Ro Na?
In my cottage?
Insane.
This is insane.
Who came up with this insane...
I have a question for you.
When did you quit smoking?
Did I not tell you?
I quit because I couldn't stop
coughing.
Maybe it's because I haven't
seen you in a while.
You feel...
a little different.
The way you hold your glass.
You always held your glass
with your left hand,
but you're holding it
with your right.
You got angry at me when I asked you
to change yourself...
to be right-handed just so that you
can be like Shim Su Ryeon.
Having had to pretend
I'm Shim Su Ryeon my whole life,
I guess I got used to using
my right hand.
Shim Su Ryeon?
She was Su Ryeon, not Ae Gyo.
Then who died back then?
How could you...
No. That can't be.
No way. That's ridiculous.
No.
No! It can't be.
- It can't be.
- Grab him!
No! It isn't true. Bring me Ae Gyo.
I didn't do it! No!
- Stay still!
- No!
Hold him tight.
Ae Gyo...
The detention warrant
will be issued soon.
You can't get out of it this time...
even if the man upstairs
has your back.
So give up, Chairman Joo.
Wait. Please.
Let me make a phone call.
Just one call.
You already called all your lawyers.
Give me your cell phone
before I rip your mouth!
Now!
The district originally selected
for redevelopment...
was Opyeong, not Cheonsoo.
Did you really...
change the district
just for Joo Dan Tae?
Mr. Jung.
(Innovation and Development
of Korea)
I know what your relationship was
with his wife.
Did you give him the information...
for her?
But sadly,
the woman you were seeing...
was not Shim Su Ryeon.
I know.
She was...
Na Ae Gyo.
(Happy Future Party)
You knew?
Ever since I was young,
I looked up to Chairman Shim
of Simoon Construction,
and received a lot of help from him.
At first,
I saw her
because she was his daughter.
But I knew right away...
that she was a completely
different person.
Then why did you continue
to see her?
I...
loved the woman...
Na Ae Gyo.
People can judge me all they want,
but my feelings for her were real.
She was a sad woman.
I don't get it.
Why did you give her
the information...
if you knew who she was?
That was the only way
she could live.
Joo Dan Tae would've
killed Ae Gyo as well...
once she stopped
being useful to him.
He never forgave anyone...
who betrayed him,
regardless of who that may be.
Then she tried to leave the country
two years ago...
To escape...
from Joo Dan Tae.
I got her...
a house to live in abroad, but...
she never came.
I found out
after I lost contact with her...
That it wasn't Su Ryeon...
but Ae Gyo who died.
Mr. Jung, this is Joo Dan Tae.
I'm at the police station right now.
Hello?
(Power off)
(Happy Future Party)
I guess...
it's time to put everything right.
Ae Gyo was killed...
by Joo Dan Tae.
And I finally get to destroy him.
I'm relieved.
But you might get hurt.
I'm prepared.
What a crazy idiot.
How dare he hang up on me?
After fooling around with my woman?
I won't go down alone.
That little...
Everyone must have realized
what's going on.
Why don't you give up?
One more call.
Let me just make one more call.
It's an international call
this time.
Logan Lee. Your dad
won't be able to ignore me...
if he wants to keep
his 35 billion dollars.
She's not fully recovered yet.
Make sure she stays in bed.
Okay.
(Prescription medication)
Don't just wait. Call her.
I sent her a message earlier.
I'm sure she'll be here soon.
I don't know
what I should say to her first.
And she's probably too shocked
to even rush over.
Thanks, Logan.
The meeting with Mr. Jung went well.
Dan Tae must be losing his mind
right now.
All his connections
have been cut off.
It seems like Mr. Jung
sincerely loved Ae Gyo.
Did you know that?
I could sense it...
when I first saw Ae Gyo
at a hotel...
two years ago.
See you.
- Su Ryeon.
- Does this make you happy?
Making money...
by impersonating another person
and deceiving people?
This is why I despise rich women.
It's not like I killed someone.
You'll never understand...
because you've never been poor
in your life.
But everyone lives like me.
They lie when they can
and feel humiliated at times.
If you're so tired of money,
why do you live so luxuriously
in a penthouse?
When did you start impersonating me?
Pretending to be Shim Su Ryeon,
you pry...
real estate information out of
politicians and build new buildings.
Did you think
no one would ever find out?
Come to your senses.
If you care about
Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung,
you shouldn't cooperate
with someone like Joo Dan Tae.
Fine, I stole your name. So what?
People treated me like a human being
for once because I look like you.
Thinking I'm the Simoon Construction
chairman's daughter,
people buy me meals and clothes.
They even voluntarily tell me
all kinds of information.
What's so wrong
with making use of it?
Don't I deserve to live like that?
I'll tell Mr. Jung everything.
That you're fake.
Stay away from him. Leave him alone.
If you mess with him,
you're dead meat.
So you do feel bad?
Then why are you
helping Joo Dan Tae?
I'm helping who?
Are you crazy?
All I do is receive political funds
from Joo Dan Tae...
and help Mr. Jung.
It's the only thing
I can do for him.
It's the same
with Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung.
For my children to live comfortably
in a fancy home,
I must give Dan Tae what he wants.
Seok Hoon and Seok Kyung
aren't doing well.
They're being abused by Dan Tae.
"Abused"?
That son of a...
Na Ae Gyo was also...
in love with Mr. Jung.
Then it's not Mr. Jung but Dan Tae
who was fooled by her.
He believed Ae Gyo was on his side
until the end.
Joo Dan Tae is
never going to give up.
To get himself out of trouble,
he'll find someone to blackmail.
We have to find a way
to corner him even more.
Mom?
Is that really you?
Seok Kyung.
Are you really my mom?
Answer me. Are you my mom?
Where have you been?
Why did you lie that you died?
Do you know...
how much I missed you?
I wanted to die every day.
Why did you do that? Why?
Mom.
- I hate you.
- I'm sorry it took me so long.
Sweetheart.
- I hate you.
- How have you been?
I'm sorry.
Your parents are being investigated
by the police in the US.
They were accused of illegal
bone marrow acquisition.
Don't tell me you were involved.
I'm going back to the US
as soon as things settle down here.
- I should be investigated.
- Logan.
It's only right for me
to pay for what I've done.
Don't say anything to Su Ryeon.
What about Ms. Oh?
Have you heard anything from her?
No. Her phone is turned off.
Ro Na hasn't heard anything
from her yet either.
Oh Yoon Hee.
What could she be thinking?
(Jin Bun Hong)
Ms. Jin, have you seen Ms. Oh today?
No, I haven't.
I guess she went to see Ro Na.
I haven't said anything
to Eun Byeol yet.
She'll be too shocked
to find out Ro Na is still alive.
Cheon Seo Jin was just arrested
by the police.
I guess she'll serve at least
a few years in prison.
This is the end of her.
Thank you for everything.
Are you going back to the US?
I'm not sure.
I'll take my time
and think about it.
Sweetheart,
you're sleeping like a baby.
Those people don't deserve
to be your parents.
From now on, I'll protect you.
Mommy will protect you.
Ms. Jin.
Is it night already?
How long was I asleep?
You were sound asleep,
so I didn't wake you.
My mom called.
I wonder why.
Your mom was...
arrested by the police.
What? She was? Why?
I don't know either,
but she must've been involved in...
the murder case of
Seok Hoon's mother two years ago.
She was?
My mom helped kill her? Why?
Where's my mom?
- Mom.
- Calm down.
Your mom said
not to tell you anything.
She said not to call...
or go see her.
She doesn't want to see you.
How could she go without telling me?
She's supposed to be my mom.
You have me.
I will never leave you.
Really?
You won't leave me?
Don't worry. I will...
be your mom...
and your dad.
I'll charge you a flat fee...
of 30 million dollars.
Then my law firm...
will create a team
of the best lawyers...
and get you out.
What gibberish is that?
I'm bitter enough
that I was framed for murder,
and you want to overcharge me?
I don't care whether or not
you were framed.
But I've recently made
a large investment,
so I need cash.
If you pay it all upfront,
you'll get a 10-percent discount.
You'll get out on bail
within a month.
If you pay less,
your time in detention
will get longer.
How dare you try to scam me
with that?
I'm Joo Dan Tae.
I did nothing wrong. Why should I
pay you 30 million dollars?
You don't get it.
You are royally done for, punk.
"Punk"?
Murder,
desecration of a human corpse,
kidnapping, false imprisonment,
embezzlement.
No other law firm
will represent you.
What? Will you wait
for a public defender?
You little twerp.
You knew, didn't you?
You schemed with Su Ryeon
and bought up my land.
Let go! Let go!
Lock the door.
Stay still.
I've been too nice to you,
haven't I?
You don't know your place.
How dare
a former construction worker...
touch an assemblyman?
You rat.
Why you... Hold him properly.
Bite down hard.
Hadouken!
Sit him down.
Deposit the money by tomorrow.
Are you insane?
Don't be scared.
Have you heard
anything I've said?
I went to Na Ae Gyo's cottage
for the first time today.
How many times must I tell you?
Then why did you have
this key to the basement?
I got that from Yoon Hee.
It isn't mine.
We found your clothes, shoes,
and bags in the cottage...
as well as your wedding photos.
Do you still deny it?
Your fingerprints and hair were
found all over the place too.
How will you explain that?
Yoon Hee did this.
She schemed with Su Ryeon
to entrap me.
Bring her here.
Let me confront her.
She's behind this con.
You're all being fooled!
Sorry.
I promised to fix it,
but I didn't keep my promise.
It's okay.
It still feels like a dream
that I can sing again.
I got my voice back,
I got my first love back,
and Ro Na's back.
I'm so happy lately.
Although it's just an act
that will come to an end eventually.
I'm happy if you're happy.
It feels like we're newlyweds.
I get excited every time...
I come home.
Yoon Chul.
If after we finish our revenge...
What if I won't let you go?
Will you stay with me?
Just kidding.
Relax.
Are you that scared?
I won't let you go...
even if you try to run away.
2091.
2395.
2358. You have mail.
(Ha Yoon Chul)
I have the feeling...
you're spending every day consumed
by regret and self-loathe.
That's why I'm writing you.
I know...
you didn't kill Ro Na.
They'll find the real killer soon,
so you'll be cleared of your charge.
I'm the one
who couldn't protect her.
So don't feel guilty anymore.
I'll take all the blame with me.
Yoon Hee.
Yoon Hee. What are you thinking?
Yoon Hee is missing?
What do you mean?
I can't reach her.
And her phone is off.
Doesn't she know yet
that Ro Na is alive?
I didn't tell her yet.
What if...
she does something drastic?
She wouldn't. Definitely not.
Su Ryeon. Su Ryeon.
(VIP Patient Room)
Yoon Hee.
Where are you?
You can finally see her again.
Why are you doing this?
You're scaring me.
Yoon Hee.
(To Su Ryeon)
To Su Ryeon.
I've committed a sin against you
that cannot be cleansed.
No words or actions
can bring me forgiveness.
Why did I...
decide to do that back then?
If I hadn't done
such a horrible thing,
Dan Tae never would've
thought of killing you...
and Ro Na wouldn't have died.
(Bae Ro Na)
Not here either.
I've missed you so much.
I loved you,
and that's why I resented you
and felt bad for you all the more.
I'll take my punishment.
Here's my last act...
of forgiveness for you.
Goodbye.
Yoon Hee...
(The Penthouse 2)
Abandoning a corpse?
You killed Seol A's dad,
pushed Seol A to the edge,
and killed Na Ae Gyo.
Assemblyman Lee Kyu Jin is here!
- Ma Ri!
- I heard you have a real name.
So we meet.
- I can do it alone.
- Seok Kyung is offering to help.
- Are you proposing?
- Are you really back in Korea?
Her dad is a very scary man.
- Get me out of here right now.
- That's too bad.
Until your misfortune reaches
its height...
I hope you die a painful death.