(Daebak Realty)
When a dead person...
remains in this world as a soul
without a body,
it's like standing outside
in your underwear...
in the midst of a snowstorm
in midwinter.
Please help me.
No matter what you hear,
do not come downstairs.
Understood?
Hwa Jeong, listen carefully.
A child possessed
by an egg ghost is here.
But I cannot perform
an exorcism ritual on an egg ghost.
Killing the person
that's been possessed...
is the only way
to dissipate the spirit.
In Bum, let's go.
I heard what you said on your phone.
Move.
If I don't perform the exorcism,
more people will die.
To stop that disaster,
we must sacrifice the boy.
What are you talking about?
I don't care about that disaster.
You cannot kill In Bum!
You will never understand.
No.
Spare my life.
I'm sorry.
Die. Die!
I just need you to die!
Uncle Sung Sik.
Please spare me.
Mom!
Mom?
The needle.
Stab the heart accurately.
Stab...
the heart accurately.
Mom.
Mi Jin.
Mom...
(Record of Exorcism)
My mom...
was killed.
Ms. Hong. Ms. Hong!
No.
Ms. Hong! Wake up.
Hong Ji A!
Visitation hours are over.
We need to go.
No.
I need to keep her warm.
You've done enough.
What do you think...
she was doing?
I think she was possessed by her mom
several times.
Isn't it dangerous for the exorcist
to be possessed?
Not once,
but many times at that.
An exorcist hallucinates...
when they're possessed
by an unrested spirit.
In Ji A's case, she hallucinates...
about the day her mom died.
But...
when she was possessed
by that water ghost last time,
she told me that she remembered
a forgotten piece of memory.
Are you saying...
that she was trying to retrieve
her lost memory from 20 years ago?
I think...
she wanted to find out the truth.
Even if her life was at stake.
Have you still not located
Kim Tae Jin?
I'm sorry, sir.
We're currently searching for him.
How could you still not find him...
when he had promised to hand over
the memorandum?
He was recently spotted
at an employment agency,
so I've sent some men over.
That sly fox.
They could've ordered...
some sweet and sour pork for me as well.
Your ID.
What?
(Ant Employment Agency)
"Yang Chang Hwa?"
Hey, are you Chang Hwa?
- The son of Changhwa Restaurant?
- Yes.
It's nice to finally meet you.
What a coincidence.
Who are you?
That's none of your business.
You little scumbag.
Your mom is desperately waiting
for your return, so hurry over.
If I could have it my way,
I'd drag you there.
But I can't do that.
Never mind. Give me your phone.
Let's call her.
Do you not have one?
Do you even remember her number?
Hey, give me a piece of paper and a pen.
Here.
Doing this won't wash away
all my sins.
Take it.
You little scumbag.
You'll be severely punished
if you break your parents' hearts.
I'm speaking from experience.
You better call her, okay?
What's your deal?
- Hey.
- Yes?
Kim Tae Jin is here, isn't he?
No, sir.
We haven't been in touch recently.
Hey! Kim Tae Jin! Stop right there!
- Do you think I'd listen to you?
- Stop!
Hey, the jjajangmyeon is going
to get soggy. Eat up.
Hey.
- Hey!
- You scumbag!
- You sly, little fox!
- Stop right there!
- Hey!
- Stop!
Run as far away as you can!
(Haesin General Hospital)
(Patient: Hong)
Are you awake?
Your face is pale.
Are you still cold?
In Bum.
Get out.
Did you get possessed by her on purpose?
Why would you do
such a dangerous thing?
You could've been
in some serious danger.
I saw everything.
I don't know what you saw,
but that was also a hallucination.
It's not accurate.
I remember everything.
I remember everything...
that happened that day.
Mi Jin.
Mom...
You saw it too.
How...
How I stabbed my own mother to death.
You were...
only performing the exorcism.
Shut your mouth!
How could you be so arrogant?
Do you think you're some deity?
For 20 years,
I have followed the path
you put out for me.
Did you have fun watching me?
- I...
- Don't give me...
a ridiculous excuse
that you did it for my sake.
I don't even want to hear your voice...
or see that face of yours.
It's horrifying.
Get out.
Get out!
What happened?
Ms. Ju. You didn't eat yet, right?
Let's...
Something feels off here.
Did something happen?
Try some.
The restaurant lady made this for you.
Something is definitely off.
What do you mean?
It's odd that she fought with Ms. Ju
as soon as she woke up.
They had a fight?
I thought they would never fight.
What happened between them?
The way Ms. Hong looked at me
was weird too.
When people get sick,
they get sensitive and easily irritated.
Give her some time.
(Patient: Hong)
Ms. Hong. I'm coming in.
(This is where
security and safety begins.)
(Ju Hwa Jeong)
Since you remembered everything,
there's no point in hiding it.
(Team Leader So Jae Hwan)
(2001 Realty Murder Case
in Bangso-dong)
Opening that cabinet drawer was
everything I had to do.
So everyone was in it together
to make a fool out of me.
I'm sorry.
(2001 Realty Murder Case in Bangso-dong)
(Case Report)
(The deceased, Hong Mi Jin,
was stabbed by a sharp hairpin...)
By the time I arrived at the scene
after getting a phone call,
your mother had already passed away.
And you, Oh In Bum,
and Oh Sung Sik...
were unconscious.
The cause of death was...
excessive bleeding after getting
stabbed by a sharp hairpin.
And the fingerprints found
on the hairpin...
belong to you and your mother.
And after analyzing the angle
and depth of the wound,
the person who stabbed the victim...
was you, Ji A.
That was the conclusion I reached.
(Crime Scene Photos)
That's why she stayed with me.
A mother was stabbed to death
by her own daughter.
Of course, she'd hold a grudge.
Then, what should I do, Mom?
For this to end,
I have to disappear, right?
Right?
I think she wanted to find out the truth.
Even if her life was at stake.
My mom...
was killed.
- Ms. Hong.
- Sorry. It's me.
You haven't found
Ms. Hong yet, right?
I searched around the neighborhood,
but I didn't see her.
You should stay here and call me
if Ms. Hong comes back.
Okay.
Where are you going?
You know, don't you?
I'm talking about the truth...
behind the day Ms. Hong remembered.
By any chance,
did I kill Ms. Hong's mother
20 years ago when I was possessed?
Did I?
It's the opposite.
Ji A's mother tried to kill you.
Then, this necklace...
isn't probably from Ms. Hong's mother.
She wouldn't give a necklace
to the kid she tried to kill.
In Bum. In Bum...
It's... It's all my fault.
You can't die, In Bum.
Mr. Oh.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
He said he would give me
an apartment unit.
I must have gone mad. I'm sorry.
It's you who created the egg ghost.
The spirits of the seven people
who died in a fire you set...
became an egg ghost.
And Mi Jin died when
she tried to get rid of the ghost.
Eight people died
all because of your greed.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault. I'm so sorry.
If you really think it's your fault,
turn yourself in.
Turn yourself in and pay for your crime.
Yes. I'll do that.
I was going to turn myself in.
I'm telling the truth.
And this.
Put this necklace on your nephew.
With that necklace,
something like this will never happen.
Whatever happens,
make sure he never takes it off.
Okay. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I hated your uncle for what he'd done.
But you were innocent in this.
And I did my best
in the situation I was given.
For you...
and for Ji A.
Your best...
Are you telling me that trying
to hide the truth forever...
and deceiving Ms. Hong
was doing your best?
Don't patronize me.
Ji A had to distort and forget...
her memories of that day
on her own to survive.
When she was trying to survive,
should I have told her this mighty truth?
I once asked Ms. Hong...
about you, Ms. Ju.
Ms. Ju is...
the only person I trust
in this world.
You betrayed...
her only trust.
Thank you very much...
for this necklace.
Thanks to this necklace,
I could live without much trouble.
(Blue Salt)
No touching.
Why not?
I just have to put this in, right?
No, that's not right.
I heard your new psychic
has amazing psychic powers.
He quit.
What a shame.
Secretary Ju said
he was good-looking too.
No? Was she exaggerating?
No, she wasn't.
I see.
So? Are you allowed to be away
from your office for so long?
I'm quitting my job as an exorcist.
Is that so?
I sold the realty office too.
This time, you actually mean it.
How will you make a living
if you quit working as an exorcist?
I'm going to travel.
You're a homebody.
Where will you go?
You hate traveling.
I can't stay home forever.
I don't think you'll be able to quit.
I can too.
Do you really think
you've taken up this job...
and worked to this day
just because of your mother?
You say you're sick of them
and never want to see them again,
but I doubt you can turn a blind eye
to unrested spirits...
shivering in the cold
and living in pain.
That was my mom.
You took after her.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
She was bound to find out someday.
If possible,
I never wanted her to find out.
Ji A is an adult too.
She can deal with this on her own.
Detective Kang had been
helping me out...
in re-investigating Do Hak Sung.
When you brokered
the sale of Green Villas,
the one who uploaded the phone call
between Mr. Hwang and Do Hak Sung...
was you, wasn't it?
Could I listen to the original file?
How could I trust this man?
Someone once said,
"There's more than meets the eye."
That there's another side...
to everything.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
Ms. Hong should be here.
(Blue Salt)
Are you the psychic for Daebak Realty?
How did you know?
I made that.
Where is Ms. Hong?
I think she just went
into the bamboo forest.
You can come in and wait.
She'll return before the sun sets.
I'll go catch her.
He's as good-looking as she said.
- I need to talk to you.
- I have nothing to say.
But I do. So please listen.
I heard everything from Ms. Ju.
It wasn't your fault.
It was just as you said.
If my uncle and I hadn't come,
your mother wouldn't have passed away.
So let's not be sorry.
I'm not going to feel sorry
for what happened with my uncle,
so please don't feel sorry for me
for what happened with your mother.
After all, I'm still alive.
But my mother is dead.
I...
killed my mom with my hands.
That's how you're still alive.
Whenever I see you,
I'm vividly reminded of the fact
that I killed my mother.
That's why it's impossible
for me to see you.
I'm going home.
I know you're not sleeping.
I don't expect you to show your face,
but you should at least say bye.
Darn it.
Do you want to know how to avoid
becoming an unrested spirit?
Sorry?
When you're thankful,
express your gratitude.
When you've done wrong, apologize.
And show affection to those you love.
We could die at any given moment.
We shouldn't hesitate or be afraid.
What if you die
of a car accident today?
Won't you feel bitter?
Say what you want or must
if you don't want to turn...
into an unrested spirit.
Hold on. Or will that prevent
the other person from becoming one?
I don't know.
(Blue Salt)
It's me.
I came...
to tell you something
for the last time.
You're the one...
who saved me 20 years ago.
Thank you.
Also, you were the first person...
to tell me that I was special...
and that I was a good person.
Thank you for that as well.
Eat your favorite dishes,
watch your favorite shows,
and buy whatever you like.
Try to take your mind off of it.
Going for a walk?
Let me join you.
Oh, right.
Did you make up
with that handsome psychic...
last night?
Gosh, you refused to see him,
didn't you?
I told you I'm retiring.
What's there to talk about
with a psychic?
Don't push away someone
who likes you.
It's not like that.
What do you mean?
I didn't mean anything romantic.
This is just a piece of life advice.
If you keep pushing people away
due to trivial reasons,
you'll eventually be all alone.
I don't care.
So? Will you cut ties
with Secretary Ju as well?
If you're going to live all alone
your entire life,
how's that any different
from becoming an unrested spirit?
I see. So Tae Jin said
this is the ledger...
from that employment agency?
He said he'd tell me
if he ever saw Chang Hwa.
One minute.
(Ant Employment Agency)
I found you.
I'm looking for this man.
His name is Kim Tae Jin.
I don't know him.
Oh, is that so?
All right.
"I don't know him."
I already know everything.
(Ant Employment Agency)
What? That's his little gofer.
Okay. I got you.
Someone came here just a while ago,
looking for Tae Jin.
- Who was it?
- Beats me.
But I don't think he was
one of Do Hak Sung's men.
(Ant Employment Agency)
Why are you being annoying
and tailing me?
I want to meet with Tae Jin.
And why is that?
I want to buy the memorandum.
- What?
- Tell him, and he'll know.
Tell him I want to buy it...
for 135,720 dollars.
- That much?
- Yes.
Your number.
- Sorry?
- I'll tell him and let you know,
- so give me your number.
- Yes, sir.
(Bankbook)
It may not have been a townhouse,
but I wanted to get her
an apartment.
Fine.
I can always make more money.
This is all for In Bum.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
In Bum.
What about Ms. Hong?
Did she not come with you?
I understand.
Every time she sees me,
she'll be reminded
of the painful past...
that she had desperately wanted
to forget.
The only thing I can do for her...
is to disappear.
What should we do?
I resent my uncle.
He shouldn't have started the fire.
He shouldn't have taken those lives.
Don't despise him.
Do Hak Sung is to blame here.
Let's be frank.
If it wasn't for him,
do you think your uncle
would've done such a thing?
In Bum,
let's find that memorandum...
and punish that son of a gun.
It's an arm's reach away.
Were you able to find Kim Tae Jin?
No.
I'll tell you once I know for sure.
You trust me, right?
(Daebak Realty)
Hurry up.
- Hey, go over there.
- Yes, sir.
- You, over there.
- Make sure they stamp it.
- Yes, sir.
(We're against the redevelopment
that will rob us!)
Hello.
(Real Estate Purchase Contract)
Done.
Honey.
Let's...
just sell this place and move out.
Just give up.
He would've come already
if he wanted to.
It's not that he can't.
He refuses to return.
If you want to leave,
do so.
I'll be right here
waiting for our son.
Even if I turn into a ghost,
I'll stay right here until he returns!
(Daebak Realty)
(Changhwa Restaurant)
Gosh. Those jerks.
They cut off the electricity too?
Who... Who is it?
Is that you,
Chang Hwa?
You're Chang Hwa, right?
You brat.
Where have you been all this time?
What took you so long?
I have never been able...
to sleep soundly
because of you, brat.
What...
happened to your leg?
I heard you work
at construction sites.
Did you hurt your leg there?
And why do you look so messy?
Did you eat?
Why not?
You couldn't even feed yourself?
Wait here.
I have kimchi stew, your favorite.
It won't take long.
Yes, this is Changhwa Restaurant.
Are you Yang Chang Hwa's family?
Yes.
What do you mean Chang Hwa is dead?
Are you sure it's Chang Hwa?
Yes. I found this
in your son's pocket.
So we were able to call you.
Is this...
Chang Hwa.
Chang Hwa. Oh, no. My boy...
Oh, no.
Chang Hwa... My boy...
My boy, Chang Hwa.
(Blue Salt)
All right.
Are you going home?
I told you. I'm going to travel now.
Sure. Enjoy your trip.
Come back
and tell me about your trip.
Thank you for everything.
(Secretary Ju)
Yes, Ms. Ju. It's been a while.
Who died?
Yang Chang Hwa?
(Funeral Hall)
I know your grandma just passed.
You must be in mourning too.
Thank you for coming.
Gosh. Whenever
you were at my restaurant,
you always reminded me of my son.
Goodness.
Gosh. Hang in there.
Ms. Hong.
When did you get...
Where are you going?
Stay here a bit longer.
Ms. Hong will be uncomfortable
to see me here.
Gosh.
I'm sorry.
I truly thought...
what I did was best for you.
But I was arrogant.
You don't need to make me
feel better.
I'm not asking for your forgiveness.
Just in case,
if you're blaming yourself for this,
I don't want you to do that.
That's what I wanted to tell you.
I'll leave now.
(Daebak Realty)
(Redevelopment Plan Notice
for District B of Bangso-dong)
(Voluntary Relocation Period,
April 17 to May 18)
(Changhwa Restaurant)
It's always money!
Fine. I'll go out and make money.
Gosh. As if.
For what?
Why was I so mean to him?
Chang... Chang Hwa.
Chang Hwa.
Ms. Hong.
Are you in?
Thanks a lot for coming to the funeral.
I haven't been in my right mind,
so I forgot to thank you.
Of course, I should've been there.
You know,
I think...
I might be crazy or something.
But I...
keep seeing my dead son.
I must be seeing things, right?
He didn't become a ghost, did he?
That darned rascal.
Why didn't he come sooner?
He can't even die in peace.
That unlucky fool.
My poor son.
Ms. Hong.
Could you let my son pass in peace?
Please, I ask of you.
Please do that
for my poor Chang Hwa.
(Yang Chang Hwa)
She'll suffer longer
if I waste my time...
looking for another psychic,
so I called you to do this quickly.
Thanks for calling.
Let's go.
(Changhwa Restaurant)
Did you know him well?
Yes.
We're about to begin.
Until we're done with everything,
keep your eyes closed.
Once we do this,
we can let Chang Hwa
leave this world, right?
Yes.
Take your necklace off.
In Bum. In Bum!
In Bum!
Are you okay?
What happened?
Mom. Mom?
This is the same as that time.
I...
killed my son.
I killed him.
The unrested spirit
didn't choose to leave behind.
She's keeping him from leaving.
(Sell Your Haunted House)
My obsession is the reason
why my mom can't leave.
No!
You look too unstable.
How can I leave you alone?
Have I ever told you
about my daughter?
Before we see another one
become an unrested spirit...
because of him,
someone has to stop Do Hak Sung.
The chairman will die of shock
once he sees this.
I'm on my way to see the chairman.
Where's the memorandum?
Do you know what it means to me?
The In Bum I know
wouldn't give up this easily.
Everything is ready, so take your time.
Chairman Do Hak Sung has been...
There's a possibility of murder.
In Bum.