Did Paolo send you?
Perhaps.
Paolo told me
to give you a painless death
if you show respect to Paolo.
Relay this message to Paolo.
I will not respect him
even after I die.
Inzaghi?
Inzaghi.
Did you get the rooftop ready?
-Well, yes.
-Good.
Wait. Why don't we drink in the office?
There's so much pigeon poop
on the rooftop.
Let me carry that.
I bet it was Inzaghi
and the other pigeons.
Inzaghi is not that kind of pigeon.
I bet it was other pigeons.
Don't badmouth Inzaghi.
It would hurt Inzaghi.
What happened here?
A nail must have torn it
when I was moving the table.
Why did you move that by yourself?
Let's drink standing up.
-Ms. Hong.
-What?
My knees are aching.
Can we drink sitting down?
Sure.
Did you send the file from the gallery
to Prosecutor Jung?
Yes. He should be
on his way to make the arrest.
That's great.
Why would you hold such a stupid event
and cause so much trouble?
The gallery is not your playground!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, sir.
This won't end with you.
I…
Be quiet.
I'm thinking.
This is ridiculous.
It's like she doesn't think at all.
You should leave the country
before they bar you from going abroad.
Why? Go where?
I'll take the fall for him. Why bother?
All the evidence they have points to you.
They will be able to track the IP address
from the gallery to your home.
Han-seo.
Get me the earliest flight
leaving for New York now.
Yes, sir.
Before I leave,
I want to see Vincenzo's dead body.
Yes, sir. We took care of it.
But I found Choi Myung-hee's phone number
in the call history
on one of the cell phones.
Okay. Well done. Wrap it up.
-Yes. Mr. Consigliere.
-Hey, Luca.
RESTRICTED NUMBER
They failed again.
He's so hard to kill.
And they call themselves
the Mafia's hitmen?
They look like the thieves
from Home Alone. Look at the feather.
Ms. Choi Myung-hee!
What will you do about it?
I'm sorry, sir. Let's go
to the airport now. I'll escort you.
Stop them now.
Forget it.
ARREST WARRANT
I came personally
to mark this historical day.
You seem very happy.
Why wouldn't I be?
Take him.
I'll come to you as soon as I'm ready.
Inzaghi.
Were you returning the favor?
Were you?
Is that it?
No way. It can't be.
How can a pigeon save a man?
There's a news embargo.
Jang Han-seok's been arrested.
Prosecutor Jung will announce it
at a press conference tomorrow morning.
Good job.
This is beautiful.
Goodness. Thank you, Ms. Oh.
You wrote a letter, too?
Hold on. Not now.
Please read it at home.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-You're here.
Ms. Hong, isn't it safe to say
that it was all thanks to us
that Babel's chairman was arrested?
Yes. Thanks to your help,
we were able to catch Chairman Jang!
Prosecutor Jung In-kuk will
now begin the press conference
-All right. It's starting.
-about the investigation against Babel.
-Hello.
-He's on.
I'm Prosecutor Jung In-kuk of
Seoul Namdongbu Prosecutors' Office.
There he is.
I have been investigating Babel Group on
six different charges for the past year.
They're all depraved
corporate corruption charges.
The charges violated the national economic
system and legal system.
That's it! There you go!
That hits the spot.
But I must tell the truth now.
When Jang Guk-hwan was the chairman,
I was eager to make a name for myself
and took my investigation too far.
As a result, I was demoted.
My personal feelings got the better of me.
I tried to indict Chairman Jang Han-seok
of Babel with unproven claims.
What's he saying? Has he gone mad?
And I crossed the line again
and caused damage
to the Babel Group
with yesterday's incident.
Is that really Mr. Jung?
It looks like he switched sides.
So he betrayed us?
I am holding this press conference
to come clean about my wrongdoings
and to recover the trust
the Namdongbu office has lost.
From now on, I will serve the people
of our country without
-letting my emotions get the better of me.
-I didn't see this coming.
If this happened in a drama,
people would say it's too unrealistic.
Moreover,
-They'd be up in arms about it.
-my ambition
has deeply mistreated
Chairman Jang Han-seok of Babel.
I would like to apologize for my actions.
That's okay.
I knew he was going to cave in
like that in the end.
That arrogant jerk.
NAMDONGBU OFFICE PRESS CONFERENCE
ON THE BABEL INVESTIGATION
You should apologize to me, too!
That greedy bastard…
Look at him bowing down like that.
As of today, all the charges
against Babel will be dropped,
and the investigation will be closed.
I would like to apologize
for the confusion I've caused.
Ms. Hong.
Gosh.
Let's visit him later.
I should go and slap him.
He won't see us anyway.
We'll go later.
This is unbelievably cruel.
He despised Babel.
How could he switch sides overnight?
Why didn't we see this coming?
You can dodge a flying dagger,
but you can't dodge a hidden dagger.
Aren't you angry?
Angry?
I'm furious.
I'm just used to it.
I'll make him pay for this.
He'll pay no matter what.
If we react emotionally to betrayals,
it'll end up hurting us.
The bigger the betrayal is,
the more careful we must be.
If you were going to do this anyway,
you should've gone easy on them.
I'm sorry for my reckless behavior, sir.
I'll suspend you for two weeks
as a formality.
Take a breather.
When you return, you'll be promoted.
For your office…
Take Mr. Seo's office.
Make yourself at home.
Okay. Thank you.
Anything else you need?
Could you put some guards
around me and my family?
The Mafia might be gunning for me.
Let's go.
You know that I obtained
some hard evidence today, don't you?
There's no way out for you this time.
But what if I make this all go away?
How high can I go?
I'm serious right now.
Gosh. Is this some kind of prank?
Why all of a sudden?
Since it's finally time.
Then why have you been
harassing me all this time?
Because I needed Vincenzo to bring me
the best evidence, like today.
Let me ask you again.
How high can I go?
I can make you the Chief Prosecutor.
Make me the Prosecutor General…
or higher.
You're very greedy.
What if I have something
that allows me to be greedy?
The Guillotine file.
Do you know where the file is
and who has it?
How come there aren't any guards?
Honey.
Seung-min!
Honey. Seung-min.
Honey.
Seung-min. Honey!
-Dad!
-Yes.
Hello, my friend.
-Dad.
-Yes?
Your colleague from Italy is so handsome.
He's my type.
You should have told us
that he was coming today.
-He ended up cooking everything.
-Yes.
His spaghetti was so tasty.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
Seung-min.
Did you have dinner?
Seung-min,
I guess he hasn't had dinner yet.
Please sit.
We have a lot of catching up to do.
-Sit down, honey.
-Okay.
Seung-min.
Shall we make yummy spaghetti
for your dad, too?
Yes.
Can you help me cook?
I don't care if you kill me,
but leave my family out of this.
Don't worry. I'm not like you.
Is there any way I can save myself?
I'll do anything.
Do you know how you can tell
when someone's become evil?
It's when they stop feeling ashamed.
And you crossed that line.
Please…
Please don't kill me.
I don't plan on killing you yet.
Since killing a traitor early
is an act of great generosity.
Do whatever you want to.
When you have everything you wanted,
I will kill you, then.
And cook some pasta for Seung-min.
She said you always choose
your favorite meals when you eat out.
Han-seo.
Set up a meeting
with Mr. Oh Jeong-bae of Daechang Daily.
We're not that close.
May I ask what this is about?
I want to talk about an article
for our EVs and the production
of batteries by Babel Chemicals.
Can't Director Chun take care of that?
He won't be enough. I'm trying to get
Babel Chemicals' stocks to go up.
I have to talk to the CEO.
But…
we're still planning to develop them.
Our technology isn't ready yet.
I'm not saying
that we'll make cars for real.
We'll get the stocks up and pull out.
You are so smart. I'll never be able to
be on the same level as you.
Cut the crap. Who was it?
Just handle the gallery director.
I can't have her yap
about what happened. Okay?
Do a good job. Come on, do better.
My hair was perfect today.
I can't sleep
since that prosecutor betrayed us.
Why is that?
-Right?
-Yes.
We're not the ones who were betrayed,
but strangely, it upsets me so much.
-Do you know why?
-Why is that?
We've become interested
in what's happening around us.
We used to not care
because we were busy making a living.
Now it feels like it's our business.
You have a point.
We didn't care about rich people
or the law back then.
I'm not even well-educated,
but I can see what's wrong now.
Mr. Cassano told me this
when he was straightening me out.
"We become what we think.
If you think you're strong, you will be."
Isn't that awesome?
Anyway, I will follow Mr. Cassano
and continue to fight them.
-Yes.
-Good.
But don't get into any trouble.
Now we might have a baby…
What?
Did you guys have a change of heart?
We're going to try for a baby now.
-My gosh.
-Goodness.
-Great news. Have some meat.
-Oh, my.
That way, you'll fight less and get along.
-Goodness.
-Thank you.
-Come on. Eat up.
-Gosh.
That's great.
-I bet the baby will be handsome.
-Of course.
How was it?
This is beautiful.
Mr. Cassano.
What do you think?
It's nice.
But didn't you already buy enough
the other day?
It's not for me.
I'm picking out a gift for Ms. Oh.
Before her illness gets worse,
I want to take her out for some fresh air.
I see.
Won't that be too much for her?
Her doctor said she can go out
for an hour or two.
She hasn't gone out in ages.
She should dress up.
You should pick one, too.
I know you have good taste.
You bought it for her, so you should
give it to your mother yourself.
It's fine. You should…
Pardon?
Why are you so surprised?
You give it to your mother.
Did your father tell you?
No.
He never told me privileged information
about his clients.
Then how did you find out?
You paid for her medical bills.
You got back at Shinkwang Bank for her
even if you hated acting.
You said the same thing about
bungeoppang and ingeoppang.
Isn't it obvious that you are her son?
I really hate getting involved
in other people's family matters.
But let me be nosy just this once.
Why don't you tell her now?
That you know you're her son.
She doesn't have much time left.
So every single day she has left counts.
Remember what you told me?
"Regret is the most
painful thing in life."
Turns out it is true.
I hope you won't have to go through
such a painful thing.
This looks so refined.
I don't know if I deserve this.
Thank you, Mr. Cassano.
It's nothing.
It took him an hour
to pick this bag for you.
What?
Gosh. You didn't have to do that.
By the way,
I don't think I should go out.
I'm not well.
I'll only inconvenience you two.
Well, I'm not coming that day.
He will take you out.
Right?
Yes.
I know you're busy. I feel awful.
No. Think about all the places
you would like to visit.
Okay.
We should let her rest. Let's go.
Ms. Hong.
I have something to tell you.
I would like to…
file for a retrial.
Really?
Yes.
Why the sudden change of heart?
Actually…
there wasn't a day
I didn't want to file for a retrial.
I thought of doing it every day.
But…
I was hesitant.
I didn't have enough courage.
But…
now that I'm nearing my death,
I finally have the courage to do it.
Can you help me with this?
Do you think you can do it for me?
What do you think, Mr. Cassano?
I'll follow your decision.
Okay.
Let's do it.
I'll get started right away.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Since your father passed away,
you've never come to see me, you brat.
I'm sorry. It's been hectic.
Why are things so crazy over at Babel?
Daechang has been working our butt off
to cover for you.
I'll return the favor.
-Han-seo already told you, right?
-Yes.
You want an editorial about
Babel Chemicals' battery production.
But Han-seok,
even elementary school kids
invest in stocks nowadays.
This is a sensitive and risky move.
But you did it for my dad.
Just do what you did for him.
Why does a beautiful woman like you
need to flee the country this urgently?
I have made…
a terrible mistake.
I can't make up for it even with my life.
That's awful.
Don't worry too much.
Actually, we have a spot,
so you can leave later today.
You're certain that
it's a direct flight to Taiwan, right?
Of course. The wind is strong today.
You could go to Cebu if you wanted.
Is it possible to end up
flying past the destination?
It is quite random, to tell you the truth.
If you don't want to…
-Hey--
-I'll take it!
Yes, that's the contract.
Read it carefully.
BYEBYE BALLOON
TRAVEL CONTRACT
We have a client here.
What is it this time?
I just got a stock investment tip.
Daechang is preparing
to publish an article
to promote Babel Chemicals.
It's about EVs and batteries.
-Excuse me. Read the contract.
-Okay.
I should buy Babel Chemicals' stocks.
These Babel assholes won't die.
They are getting richer instead.
How? Why is that?
Everyone, do you want some coffee?
I'm not in the mood to drink coffee now.
I'm not in the mood to make coffee now.
Okay.
Gosh. That traitor, Jung.
Babel will get more powerful
because of that bastard.
You met him last night. Why didn't you
make him pay for what he did?
He will do that in installments.
Do you think it's possible
he's just pretending to have switch sides?
Maybe he wants to expose
-all the secrets from within--
-Mr. Nam.
That's never happened
in the history of this country.
We don't need Prosecutor Jung.
What's that?
This?
The Guillotine file.
You said you accidentally threw it
in the secret room and closed the door.
Who said that? Me?
-Yes.
-Did I say that?
My goodness. Vincenzo Cassano.
Let's reveal what's in the file.
Once it goes online,
it'll go international in an hour.
-That's not a good idea.
-Why not?
It'll last a few days. But…
no one that's in this file
will pay for what they did.
This file wasn't created
to expose the truth to the world
but for evil men to exploit the weakness
of other evil men.
Only an evil man can use it properly.
And we can use it just like they would.
We'll keep them on a leash
and order them around.
I see.
How frightening.
Did you read the file?
No. Not yet.
I wanted us to read it together.
Mr. Nam.
-The laptop!
-Right, the laptop!
Gosh. Something doesn't feel right.
I'm sure Prosecutor Jung and Mr. Jang
made a deal over something.
You know, the file.
The file they got from the gallery.
Do you think that's all?
That should be more than enough.
He has my brother
on tax evasion, illegally acquired stocks,
and everything on that file.
No. I get the feeling
that there's more.
What else? What else could there…
Is there really more?
-I don't know that.
-Me neither.
Anyway, Jung is
on your brother's side now.
And the deal with Daechang Daily
went smoothly.
Now your brother is going
to become powerful beyond control.
PROSECUTION
Gosh. The tabloids are nothing
compared to this.
It is unbelievable.
To get this kind of information,
they must've surveilled them illegally.
This time, we'll be targeting Babel
-and Daechang Daily.
-Daechang Daily.
I've been waiting
to crush this trashy agency.
Back in the day, newspapers could be
used as toilet paper.
But now, there's no use for them.
I mean, this so-called newspaper
makes ridiculous claims all year round.
They're absurd and make no sense.
If they keep doing it,
it is their attitude. It'll never change.
If Daechang Daily is gone,
it will cleanse our eyes and ears.
First, I'm planning to make them
fight and destroy each other.
Each other? How will you
make them go after each other?
Don't forget.
We have this Guillotine file.
Right, we'll pit one evil against another.
All right. Look over here.
Well, your office is…
It looks lame and awkward. It's nice.
Why are you here?
What? I can come if I want to.
It's nothing much. It's just
the most expensive coffee, Kopi Luwak.
I'm sure you know what it is.
It's a rare product
made from civets' poop.
What a load of crap.
Who is that guy?
I'm not sure if Vincenzo is just lucky
or he's really competent.
But he's impressive.
The Guillotine file and 15 tons of gold.
No one will even think that it's there.
If we can get the file,
all the powerful people in Korea
will kneel
before you.
It sounds like the One Ring
from The Lord of the Rings.
You watched it, so you must know.
If it falls into the wrong hands,
it'll cause problems.
Only people like us
will do justice to the Ring.
Let's demolish Geumga Plaza
as fast as we can.
That way, we can get the file out.
I'll give you some of the gold
in the secret room.
Sure.
I'll gladly accept it.
Thank you.
Hey, wait.
Why didn't you make the coffee
that I brought?
We don't have a coffee maker.
Gosh. Your working conditions here
are awful.
Damn it. It's so bitter. Hey, dude.
Why is this so bitter?
I heard that you asked Mr. Cassano
to get rid of your own brother.
It would have all worked out
if he did what I asked.
Things have gotten worse
because you declined.
Didn't I tell you?
I never exploit betrayals within a family.
I forgot to tell you this
because I was flustered.
I'm not trying to betray my own brother.
What I want…
How should I put it?
I don't want people to die anymore.
-Right.
-I'm trying to run Babel legally.
I guess you've been studying a lot.
Your vocabulary has gotten better.
Let me get this straight. You want to run
the company properly
after getting rid of your brother?
-That's it.
-Okay.
I really love Babel.
I want to run the company the right way.
I really don't want people to get killed.
I mean that.
Why don't you fix it then?
Why are you asking us for help?
That's because…
no matter how much I think about it,
you are the only people who can beat him.
I like your intention.
But do you deserve the seat?
I've been studying how to run a company.
I'm reading a lot of books.
Humanities and economy. I read everything.
I want to read all the time.
Then here's a quiz.
A quiz all of a sudden?
Fine. Go ahead. Give me a question.
In the Wealth of Nations, Adam Smith says
this hand brings order
to a market economy? What is it?
-Polite hand.
-Wrong.
"The invisible hand."
As the economy grows,
government expenditures
in gross national product also increase.
Name this law.
-Law of the Jungle.
-Wrong.
"Wagner's law."
This is the easiest one.
To improve the company's competitiveness,
you learn something from another company.
What is this term
that originated from an iron rod?
Here's a hint. Bench…
Wrong.
-Get out.
-Wait.
Hold on.
Didn't I get one right?
How could you get everything wrong?
The polite hand was correct. No?
If you want our help, go study more.
If you want to join us, you must be smart.
Is this a symposium or what? Why?
Feel free to say no.
Get out.
This is ridiculous.
What…
Wait. Hold on.
If I pass your quiz
the next time I come here,
you'll really have to help me.
Get out.
Seriously. You're so petty.
Fine. I'll leave.
What will you quiz me on?
Out. Mr. Nam.
Did you know about the polite hand?
Here are my polite hands.
Will you really help Jang Han-seo?
You know,
I was trying to take Vincenzo's life.
But it turns out Vincenzo has been taking
what I cherish.
And that thing in the gallery.
What should I take from him
to make him suffer?
I must steal what's important to him.
Once he's dead, it's over.
So it's not his life.
If I were to go down that route…
Should I look into his family?
"Family"?
Is that important?
To regular people,
family is important.
I see.
Okay. I guess only I didn't know.
Then I'll go with that.
YEONGHO SNACK BAR
Why do you look so exhausted?
It's so fun.
I haven't eaten or taken a dump
to read the file nonstop.
I'll go read some more after our briefing.
You should still go to the bathroom.
If you don't, toxins will build up.
I looked into some major problems
of Daechang Daily's owner, Oh Jeong-bae.
He's such a bastard.
What's the worst he did?
He murdered his older brother.
Daechang is just as awful.
How come they all hate their siblings?
Why did he kill his brother?
They fought over the company.
But he was acquitted of the charge.
He went hiking with his older brother
and killed him by pushing him off a cliff.
I bet there were no witnesses.
Is there any evidence that it was murder?
The environmental monitoring camera
caught him in the act.
But the International Security
Intelligence Service
obtained the footage, not the cops.
The agency must have
used the footage
to cut a deal with Mr. Oh.
That's correct.
He's a total asshole.
How could he kill his own brother?
You heard everything.
I can hear better when people whisper.
Don't worry. My lips are sealed.
Mr. Nam, did you find anything else?
There's a shaman
he trusts and follows blindly.
There's a child who has matured over
ten months and is about to make his mark.
When he makes decisions, big or small,
he does as the shaman says.
-Let me see.
-For both his family and company.
But the shaman's a former cult leader
who has been convicted
four times
for fraud and sexual harassment.
And of course, Mr. Oh has no idea.
Gosh. This is crazy.
He takes advice from a fraud like that?
You know how people are.
The less you know about something,
the easier you believe it.
I should check if he's really
a fraud or gifted.
I'll go and finish reading it.
Gosh.
Don't move.
I'm telling you, Daechang Daily
burns the best.
When newspapers are full of lies,
you should use them to start a fire.
-Hey, who are you guys?
-Who do you think?
We brought you in,
so you could read our fortune.
What?
Hey, who are you?
I wonder
if you know that you'll burn
to death five minutes later.
He must know. He's a gifted shaman.
Does he also know he'll take a fall
after burning to death?
Of course. He's gifted.
Spare me.
But his fate can be changed, right?
As long as he does what I tell him.
Why are you doing this to me, sirs?
By the way, do his customers know?
That he's a former cult leader
who was arrested four times
for fraud and sexual harassment?
I'm not sure.
They don't know that yet, sir.
Then…
shall we start talking now?
-Should I pour it?
-Yes?
-Gosh.
-Let's pay a silent tribute.
-Shall we?
-Okay.
This is for the deceased.
No, don't do that.
-Why…
-It's over. Let's do it.
-Can you lift your legs?
-No.
-The head first.
-The head?
-This is lamp oil.
-Wait.
I'll talk.
-No.
-Light it.
-Let's talk.
-Daechang Daily.
Let's use that newspaper.
Here we go.
-It's burning. No!
-Gosh.
All right.
To screw over Babel and Daechang Daily,
we will hold a vote to pick a person
who will act as a shaman.
Please vote for the person
that suits the role of a shaman the best.
Put it in there.
All right.
We all have voted for the person
who will act as the shaman.
Now, I will count the votes.
VINCENZO
"Vincenzo."
Me?
This isn't a joke.
-Mr. Nam.
-You saw it?
"Mr. Cassano."
"Vincenzo Casanova,
Corn Salad. I love you."
What…
Is this funny?
"Vincenzo."
-"Vitamin-cenzo."
-Why did you…
-"Mr. Vin."
-What are you guys doing?
"Mr. Vin, Vincenzo."
-"Vincenzo."
-Everyone.
"Mr. Cassano."
"Vincenzo. Vincenzo Quassano."
"Quassano"?
This is probably Vincenzo.
Yes, "Mr. Cassano."
All right.
This is the last vote.
Do we need to check the last vote?
Vincen… "Hong Cha-young."
Why me?
-It was you, wasn't it?
-All right.
Mr. Cassano has been voted
for the role of the shaman.
-Vincenzo!
HOW BABEL CHEMICALS BECAME
THE LEADER IN THE EV MARKET
CEO OH JEONG-BAE
Hello, sir.
I need to speak to you
about an urgent matter.
Pardon? What are you talking about?
Sir.
I can no longer communicate
with any spirits.
The mountains deity has left me.
No.
I need you.
You must pull through.
Sir, please.
Mr. Oh, listen carefully.
Okay.
I'm useless now.
But I know a really powerful shaman.
No, he's much better than me
at communicating with the spirits.
No. You must go see him instead.
That's the only way we'll survive.
-I'm number five.
-I'm number six.
-I'm number seven.
-Why?
Gosh.
-It'll take five minutes per person.
-Right.
-I heard he's really good.
-Really?
-Yes.
-I should've gotten more time.
-I can't wait to find out.
-Right. I've been waiting for an hour.
-What's your number?
-Number four.
-I'm number six.
-Okay.
PARK HYO SHRINE
I heard he's really good.
-Hey.
-You can't cut in line.
You just got here.
-We're in line here.
-Right.
-Go grab a ticket.
-Yes.
We've been waiting here
before you got here.
-See?
-Right.
-Look.
But I made a reservation.
-Is that so?
-I see.
I didn't know about that. Then, go inside.
-I'm jealous.
-Gosh.
-Good for you.
-Awesome.
-I'm so jealous.
Good luck.
How may I help you?
Well…
shaman Biryu recommended me
to see the shaman here.
-I'm Daechang's--
-"Daechang."
Welcome.
Young Master Yeorim is waiting for you.
I see.
OH, INZAGHI
You have an interesting name
for your shrine.
We named it after Park Hyo,
the Chief State Councilor of Joseon.
He was enlightened
after going into the mountains
and became a mountain deity.
That is why the deity we worship is
known as "Park Hyo Shin."
"Shin" meaning god.
I see. Okay.
Following the long shadow
Well…
I'm here because I want some answers
to my questions.
But I'm not sure if I should ask them.
Should I ask them?
Or not?
Get out.
I have nothing to say to a dead man.
Look.
I won't have to send condolence money
since we just met.
Who do you think I am?
You con artists.
Jeong-bae.
What?
"Jeong-bae"?
How dare you call me by my first name?
-I'm your brother, Jeong-bae.
-What?
I'm so cold.
I'm cold.
My hands are freezing.
I'm so cold.
How could you push me off
the cliff and leave me?
I'm still here.
How…
-How could my brother…
-I'm cold.
Jeong-bae, help me up already.
It's freezing down here. Okay?
-I'm so cold, Jeong-bae.
-Go away.
-Get away from me.
-Jeong-bae.
-Get off me.
Jeong-bae.
-Let go.
-Jeong-bae.
-No!
-Go away.
-I'm cold, Jeong-bae.
Jeong-bae, I'm so cold.
Get away from me!
Why are there
so many burdens in my life?
It's not that you have many burdens.
You are just weak.
The weaker you are,
the heavier your burdens become.
I see.
Do you want to see
what will kill you eventually?
Yes. I do.
BABEL
Unless you cut ties with Babel,
you will die a miserable death.
Is that all I need to do?
It's more than cutting ties with them.
You must cut ties with them
as you completely trample on them.
What?
To get rid of bad luck altogether.
That's…
It's not that easy.
I see.
That's the number of days you have left.
Five days.
Poor thing.
You know what?
I went too hard earlier.
My arms are hurting. They hurt so much.
Isn't it ironic?
A newspaper company is supposed to
publish facts, but he's so superstitious.
He's superstitious
because he has no interest in facts.
You startled me.
Oh, right.
I forgot to tell you
because we were so busy today.
I found something shocking about
Jang Han-seok in the Guillotine file.
-What is it?
-Chairman Jang
killed four of his classmates
in middle and high school.
He brought classmates he didn't like
to a rooftop and made them jump.
Or he hunted and killed them
in the mountains like they were prey.
He killed the last one because he stole
a ball from him during a gym class.
Jang used the goal net to strangle him.
Here's what's scarier.
JANG HAN-SEOK
He took the deceased's watches
as some kind of a trophy.
And he even bragged about it
like he was proud of it.
He's a psychopath.
He was diagnosed as a psychopath
at the age of 16.
That's why his father sent him
to the States
fearing that he might become
a serial killer.
Jang Han-seo was beaten
and tortured by him,
so he's been seeing a therapist
ever since he was little.
And that's how he ended up doing drugs.
Even so, he shouldn't be doing drugs.
That jerk.
Anyway, their father, Jang Guk-hwan,
covered everything up with money
and kept it a secret.
That explains why he was so hard to beat.
Turns out he's
the biggest monster of them all.
BABEL SUSPECTED TO HAVE MADE
FALSE STATEMENTS TO RAISE STOCK VALUE
DAECHANG DAILY
Hello?
What are you doing?
-What the hell is this?
-Mr. Jang.
There has been a change
in the guidelines at my company.
Did I do something to offend you?
No, you didn't.
Now Daechang Daily is an honest newspaper
that only speaks the truth.
The truth?
You're the most corrupt newspaper company
in Korea. But what? The truth?
Watch what you say.
So, why didn't you
run your company properly?
I'm hanging up.
Mr. Oh? Mr. Oh!
Hey!
How come my days are still numbered?
I just cut all ties with Babel.
That won't be enough to save your life.
Pardon?
Then what more do I need to do?
The owner of Babel.
The king of Babel.
Are you talking about
Chairman Jang Han-seok?
He's the one
who's holding onto your misfortune.
If you expose his past evils,
and relieve the spirits that wander
the realm of the living because of him,
those spirits will help you.
The wandering spirits?
Are you saying Han-seok killed someone?
Han-seok.
I'm sorry.
Don't hit me.
Han-seok. I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
-I'm not Han-seok.
-I'm sorry.
-I'm not him.
-Don't strangle me.
-I can't breathe.
-Jang Han-seok.
Don't strangle me.
-Jang Han-seok. Spare me.
-No.
-It's my fault.
-Don't do it.
No. I'm not Han-seok!
That's my watch.
That's my watch. It's mine.
-It's my watch.
-No.
The chairman of Babel,
one of the biggest companies in Korea,
was a bully?
No. It was more of a massacre.
This has come
as shocking news to the public.
On top of that,
he was never punished for his crimes,
and was able to climb the ladder
to become the chairman.
I mean, seriously?
Where were the police and prosecutors
in all of this?
Right now, a lot of people
are urging this killer chairman
to be punished
on many of the online forums
and petitioning for it as well.
Gosh.
How did they know?
Even Mr. Oh wouldn't
know about my childhood.
…update you with a follow-up coverage.
Right now, Babel Group
-has dismissed the claims
-Hey.
-It wasn't you, right?
-as being false.
-They will soon release
-What? Of course, it wasn't me.
The article even said I was crazy
and did drugs. You think I did that?
Well, you're right.
It was reported that there hadn't been
an investigation on this in the past.
Who else knows about this?
My dad, the detective who worked the case,
and the prosecutor in charge.
Then there's a source we're not aware of.
The problem is the intention.
Why is Mr. Oh attacking you now?
It looks like
he's trying to bring me down.
LIFE
It's all done.
You have been spared.
Fate has a weakness for brave souls,
but it can be a powerful foe
to those who are weak.
You have been brave
and averted this crisis.
Thank you.
It's been a while, Mr. Cho.
Can we meet now?
I'll meet you at the parking lot
of the plaza.
Okay. Sure.
Okay.
Run!
Who are they?
I think Prosecutor Jung sent them.
Prosecutor Jung?
It's as expected.
It was Vincenzo.
He exploited Mr. Oh's tendency
to have blind faith in shamans.
He's so detailed.
I really can't beat a Mafia member.
Anyway…
how did he find out
what happened when I was young?
That's still a mystery to me.
But it's most likely that he got it
from the intelligence agency.
How on earth did he find out?
Given the current circumstances,
he's pitted Babel and Daechang
against each other.
Even so. Mr. Oh of all people
can't do that to me.
What should we do?
Make Vincenzo end it himself.
Oh, right. I must show you something.
What is it?
Vincenzo's Korean name is Park Ju-hyeong.
He was adopted after being abandoned
by his mother when he was little.
OH GYEONG-JA, PERSONAL DETAILS
Is his mom alive?
She is. But she recently got out of prison
-because of pancreatic cancer.
-What was she in for?
She was the housekeeper
who was involved in the death
of Shinkwang Finance's Chairman Hwang.
NAMDONGBU DISTRICT COURT
RULING
Wait.
He ruined the signing ceremony
a while ago.
Is this why he did that?
Yes.
Hong Yu-chan was the public defender
who took her case.
And today, she filed for a retrial
regarding the death of Hwang Deok-bae.
A retrial?
-Who filed it?
-Cha-young did.
Of course, Vincenzo must be behind it.
That means Vincenzo
has been spending time with his mother.
I'm trying to find out which hospital
his mother is being treated in.
I met Jung at the International Security
Intelligence Service five years ago.
He was dispatched for a case,
and I had a desk job there.
We found out the true nature
of the Guillotine file,
and Jung thought he could
root out all corruption in Korea
with the file.
So he desperately tried
to get his hands on it,
and I joined hands with him.
That was before he went dirty.
Yes.
But soon,
the file was hacked and vanished,
and I volunteered to look for the file.
That's how I got here.
But Jung has betrayed you, right?
Yes. In fact, I suspected him
these past few months.
I felt he had an ulterior motive
for looking for the file.
Now that he is on Jang Han-seok's side,
he must know by now
that the file and the gold are here.
And he must know he has to demolish
the plaza to retrieve them.
GEUMGA PLAZA
PETITION FOR A RETRIAL
Damn it.
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Oh Jeong-bae.
SPECIAL THANKS TO LEE HYE-JUNG
AND IM SUNG-JAE
It was a setup, wasn't it?
Then we'll have to use
the most effective method.
I'll make sure no one ever gets it.
I have to find the person who lured me.
I'll make sure everyone who tried to
build it will be punished.
He could stir up the entire nation.
To cherish Geumga Plaza
as a historical building.
Make him pay.
It's time for you to die.
You will die a slow death,
experiencing it every step of the way.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son