Hey, wait! Let's talk it out. We can talk this out!
That's enough. You might kill him.
- Can I just kill him? - That hurts.
I think you're the one who'll die.
Please let me live. Please!
I'll... I'll give you money.
- Stay still! - Please spare my life.
- I can't aim right. - Please let me go.
Who are you?
You promised you'll give us an apartment unit.
- What? - I set the place on fire...
and killed people.
Give me the apartment.
The apartment.
- Give me my apartment. - What the heck is this nonsense?
Give me my apartment!
What are you doing? Go tend to the chairman now!
Get up.
(Episode 7)
What's going on?
Stop overreacting.
You didn't break anything. You only pulled a ligament.
Hey.
- What happened? - The spirit on Do Hak Sung...
suddenly possessed your body, then you began to attack him.
Thanks to you, the whole thing ended.
I see. So some evil spirits end up possessing people.
Figures. I'd be surprised if he had no unrested spirits on him...
after all that he has done.
You promised you'll give us an apartment unit.
- What? - I set the place on fire...
and killed people.
- Give me the apartment. - The apartment.
Anyway, how did you end up getting caught by them?
Man, only if they didn't attack me from behind, I could've...
(King-sized Mandu)
If you're about to take out your knife, don't.
You're the one who'll be hurt by the knife.
My story is similar to yours.
I thought you were invincible, but you're rather sloppy.
Wait, come to think about it,
I already saved your life twice.
Man, I don't think saying thank you is going to cover this.
Don't you think you owe me a nice suit?
You need to quit working as a psychic.
You're firing me to save on that suit?
It doesn't cost that much.
You need to quit before you get hurt from lurking around me.
Our contract will expire soon anyway.
I'm not going to sell my place until I help my mom leave.
And something like this is bound to happen again.
Then...
why are you unable to send your mother away?
I remember you saying it's difficult because her spirit is special.
It's always difficult to send away an exorcist's spirit.
Until now, I just thought I needed to find a powerful psychic.
But I really have no idea now.
What was she like?
I mean your mother, Ms. Hong.
She was pleasant,
cool, and nice.
That's why she died. She was too nice.
She passed away because she was too nice?
What do you mean?
- Her last client was... - Help me.
an arsonist who murdered seven people.
She passed away helping someone who doesn't deserve to be helped.
I'll never forgive them.
Maybe what Kim Tae Jin said is true.
That he always saw ghosts near Daebak Realty.
What has gotten into you?
I'm sorry, but...
Silence! Go and get me...
all the information you can find on everyone at Daebak Realty!
- Don't leave anyone out! - Yes, sir.
I could've come home alone.
Get some rest. I'm leaving.
Ms. Joo.
I'd like to meet Mr. Jung.
Why do you suddenly want to see him?
I need to know what exactly happened to my mother...
and if I'm missing anything.
I thought Mr. Jung would know.
Okay, I'll give him a call. We can go see him.
No, I'll meet him alone.
Goodbye.
(Criminal Record, Hong Ji A)
So she's the CEO.
She may not have gone to jail,
but she has seven previous convictions.
Attempted fraud...
and blackmail.
Birds of a feather flock together.
They're a scamming duo.
Who is this lovely woman?
You startled me.
It's nothing.
Don't lie.
You're obviously abusing your power...
and doing a background check on someone you're interested in.
Cut that nonsense.
That's ridiculous.
I'll get back to work.
Why did you kill them?
I didn't want them to become burdens.
Isn't it obvious?
Ji A will visit you.
Please don't let her look into the case...
from 20 years ago.
Okay.
That woman didn't hesitate...
to kill her own kids...
out of selfishness.
(Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency)
It's been a long time.
I barely recognized you.
I know.
I'd like to read the case file from 20 years ago...
as well as the photos.
You're still just as direct.
But since your mother wasn't a victim...
and rather died of a cardiac arrest,
her file has been discarded.
But why are you looking for something...
that happened 20 years ago?
I recently remembered something new from that night.
You arrived at the scene first, didn't you?
I did.
Could you tell me everything you remember?
Let's see. It's been quite a long time.
Nothing really stood out.
I just saw 2 adults and 2 kids lying unconsciously.
It looked like any other realty.
I'm sorry I couldn't be of much help.
A realty that specializes in haunted houses?
That's correct.
Also, Oh In Bum and Heo Ji Chul are frauds...
who fabricate hauntings.
They fabricate hauntings?
I knew it.
How dare those brazen scumbags mess with me?
Sir, it turns out that Oh In Bum is...
Oh Sung Sik's nephew.
The arsonist of Yongnam Village from 20 years ago.
"Oh Sung Sik"?
And the last place he went...
before his death was...
Daebak Realty.
What?
I truly thought no one was there.
I'm telling you the truth! It's the truth!
That spirit possessed my nephew!
I'm serious!
In Bum!
I should've died instead.
Please call the police.
I said, please call the police!
I don't need any money...
or the apartment.
Are you finally awake?
Sir.
You're hell-bent on letting everyone know,
aren't you?
You even asked for the police.
Why? To report me?
No, sir.
I will never tell them that you had ordered it.
I'm going to tell them that I did it...
and receive my punishment.
Did someone persuade you to do this?
Did they say I'd give you more money...
if you threatened me like this?
Threatening you?
Not at all.
- No? - I didn't tell a soul.
Please believe me!
I just can't burden the guilt.
I've taken many lives.
My goodness. I'm so softhearted.
Write that down.
(The fire at Yongnam Village on November 15 was my doing.)
That's a written statement claiming that you did it.
I should have a reason to believe you.
If you write that, I'll still give you the apartment.
Really?
Okay. I'll do it right now.
(The fire at Yongnam Village on November 15 was my doing.)
Thank you, sir.
Don't worry about a thing and rest up.
Dream about your new apartment.
I will. Thank you, sir.
Don't be.
Sleep tight.
You promised you'll give us an apartment unit.
- What? - I set the place on fire...
and killed people.
How did Oh In Bum know...
about that?
Perhaps, he found the memorandum...
that we had failed to find.
Read that after you discharge.
The doctor said you needed to rest up.
("Mysterious Fire at Yongnam Village Kills 7 Residents")
Goodness, sir. Let me help you.
- Thank you. - Take it slowly.
In Bum, I'll be right back.
Her last client was...
an arsonist who murdered seven people.
My uncle wasn't...
a criminal.
Something's wrong.
("Arson Suspected as the Cause of the Fire")
("Case Ends After the Arsonist Commits Suicide")
I can't believe the Yongnam Village fire happened...
20 years ago.
Time flies.
Please tell me everything that you remember.
To be honest, I refuse to believe that my uncle...
was an arsonist...
and that he had committed suicide.
That's completely understandable.
At first, we suspected it was Golden Construction's doing...
since they were determined to redevelop the area.
It was also odd how Chairman Do Hak Sung...
had visited Mr. Oh before his death.
Did you just say "Do Hak Sung"?
(Dohak Construction)
(Ceremony for the Redevelopment of Sungso-dong, Daejeon)
(Ceremony for the Redevelopment of Golden Apartment)
Why would Secretary Joo meet...
with Do Hak Sung's secretary?
You're actually back.
What kind of hello is that?
I expected you to have quit after what had happened.
Ms. Hong...
would be in a pickle without her special psychic.
Such a trivial incident won't make me quit.
A responsible fraud?
Were you at Dohak Construction this afternoon?
I think I saw you there.
Judging by your face, I'm right.
Does Ms. Hong know?
No.
She doesn't.
Just like how she doesn't know that you're Oh Sung Sik's nephew.
I don't know why you came here,
but keep your mouth shut and leave once your contract ends.
Seeing how you didn't tell Ms. Hong about me even when you knew,
must mean you must also have an ulterior motive.
It's chilly in here. Is it just me?
Hello.
Is this the real estate agency that sells haunted houses?
Well, the house belongs to my mother.
We want to sell the house because people say it's haunted.
- Did you see the spirit yourself? - No. We don't live there.
Our tenants told us that their son was possessed by a spirit.
Gosh. There's no such thing.
He was sick, to begin with.
All right. Let's go inside and look at our new house.
Is that you, Jun Seo?
Jun Seo.
What are you doing in the dark?
Anyway, because of the rumor that our house is haunted,
no one even came to see the house when we tried to sell it.
And other real estate agents told us to lower the price by half.
You guys will help us sell the house at market price, right?
Ms. Yoo Young Soon?
Yes?
Will you sell the house?
Yes. She will.
Why are you asking my mom?
The house belongs to her.
I must ask the homeowner if she wants to sell or not.
Why did you say it like that?
Then, are you insinuating that we're trying to take her house?
Mom, why won't you tell her?
Just say that you will sell it.
I...
Because you won't speak up,
she thinks we're taking advantage of you.
I'll sell it. I will.
Gosh.
Okay.
(Daebak Realty)
Watch your head.
Hey. One second.
What?
Can she stay with you next month again?
What are you talking about?
We were supposed to alternate every month.
Exams are around the corner for Do Hyun. He's on edge now.
No. If I tell my wife that we're taking care of her again this month,
she'll kick me out.
Unbelievable. Isn't she being so selfish?
She hasn't done anything for Mom as her daughter-in-law.
Then what did you do for her as her daughter?
You just want to take a cut of the inheritance.
Hey!
Then, is the boy who was possessed by the spirit...
a psychic like me?
We'll know once we get there, but it's highly likely.
The spirit could have been there before they moved in,
but it had been quiet because its energy was weak.
But after the boy moved in, it must have made its move.
Hey. The house is haunted, right?
- There was a spirit, right? - Yes.
My secretary will call you to schedule an exorcism.
My boy is sick.
I thought living in a place with good air might help his health.
That's why we moved here. Gosh.
I should have checked more thoroughly before moving here.
Does he have a place to stay for the time being?
Until the house gets rented out, we'll stay with his aunt.
That's good. Let's go.
This is for you. You can keep it.
When I was young, I went through a lot of weird stuff like you.
But after wearing this necklace, things like that stopped happening.
Consider it a shield that protects your character in games.
So don't take off this necklace no matter what. Okay?
Can you do that for me?
Gosh. What was that?
You must have nothing to fear for. How could you take off the necklace?
Out of all things, how could you do something like that?
You know that there's an unrested spirit in the house.
What if you get possessed?
You said that the spirit had weak energy.
Besides, you're right here with me. I'm sure you would help me.
What?
But think about that boy.
He'd have kept getting possessed without knowing why.
How could I turn a blind eye on him?
Not everyone born with the ability becomes a psychic.
Usually, when boys like him have girlfriends or date girls,
they'd be fine because his energy gets mixed with yin energy.
"Usually"?
What do you mean by that?
What... What do you mean?
Can you elaborate? What do you mean?
- Tell me. - Shut your mouth and get in.
Come on.
This is a very old house.
At first, Yoo Young Soon's family lived in the house.
But starting 50 years ago, they left the house vacant...
or rented it out, so they kept getting new tenants.
I have put together...
a list of old tenants who died from the 1960s to now.
In 1979, an old man who rented Ms. Yoo's house died...
when he lost his footing at the reservoir.
And in 1993,
after Yoo Young Soon left...
It's none of these people.
What?
Right, you saw their face.
How's everything going with you, Ms. Joo?
I asked the detectives in the area for help with the search,
but it might take a while since we don't know the time of death.
I'll meet some elderly people in the town starting tomorrow.
Then I'll go meet Ms. Yoo Young Soon.
Where does she live?
She said she'll be at her daughter's place this week.
You haven't lived in that house for 50 years now.
Is there a particular reason?
I found it odd that you didn't live there for 50 years,
yet you didn't choose to sell it either.
You were hesitant about selling it the last time you came.
Many people keep their property as an investment too.
You know,
I don't even know how my father passed away.
The year when I turned 20,
my father collapsed after a stroke.
Then he was diagnosed with dementia after two years.
You never showed up since our father collapsed,
then the first thing you say is you want to sell this house?
I really think my next business will thrive.
Do you know how much you lost trying to run a business?
Stop obsessing over this.
Get a grip, will you?
Half of the share will be mine once Dad passes, right?
What's so bad about taking that share beforehand?
- It's not your money. - He's still alive.
He can't even recognize me!
How is that any different from being dead?
Instead of keeping him at home,
you should rather get him in a nursing home.
Get out.
I can't consider someone like you as my brother or family.
Get out of here!
That night, my father suddenly disappeared.
It probably wasn't easy for him to walk after his stroke.
He disappeared.
I'm sure Young Sik killed him...
for his father's money.
Goodness, no matter how much he coveted after money,
how could a son kill his father?
His son could do that and worse.
Even before Young Sik graduated high school,
he sold off his late mother's jewelry...
to start a business or something.
Then were the police suspicious of him?
They were.
But his father's body wasn't found, and there was no evidence.
What could they do?
I see. So there was no evidence.
He must've felt guilty.
He ran off as soon as he got released,
then never stepped a foot inside his hometown after that.
That should be considered as hard evidence. Don't you think?
I think that might be the case.
Where did you bury him? Just tell me where his body is.
- Tell me! - Stop it. How would I know?
Young Sik, please. We need to give him a funeral.
Let me go.
Young Sik!
Since that day,
I was unable to live in that house...
or sell that place to someone else.
This is a photo I took when I graduated my school.
I always keep this with me.
My other albums are at my son's place.
What did your father like?
He had a sweet tooth.
He loved chocolate, candies, and sweet snacks.
He'd buy those treats without telling my mom.
That's an expensive apartment.
But why does it look more like a jail than a home?
(Yoo Chul Gu)
Why are you taking so much sugar?
Because I need it.
My gosh.
And only because she doesn't have to carry this.
(Brown Sugar)
I think you have the wrong bait.
Shut it.
It's here. The ants are here.
- You called ants here. - And cockroaches.
Where? My gosh!
You have an awful taste in pranks.
Take your necklace off.
- What's he doing? - I think he came back to himself.
You can just leave it.
Dad, let me draw you a bath.
You look great, Dad.
Thanks. Thank you.
He can't even recognize me!
You should rather get him in a nursing home.
Get out.
I can't consider someone like you as my brother or family.
Get out of here!
Dad.
I'm sorry.
I just pity...
my sister. That's all.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You look great, Dad.
In Bum.
In Bum, where are you going?
(Do not enter.)
This is it.
- What do you mean? - He threw himself down the well.
He struggled to walk...
all the way here from his house...
and killed himself.
So?
Are you going to whine and tell me...
that she needs to know the truth?
Do you think you're a deity?
Reading an unrested spirit's memory...
doesn't give you the right to meddle in others' lives.
- I'm not trying to be a deity. - Then?
Remember what she told us?
She said she didn't know how her father passed away.
I also don't know how my uncle passed away.
What a cold-hearted scumbag.
I know very well how painful it feels...
not to know the reason behind your beloved's death...
and having to force yourself to accept it and move on.
I do.
If I were her, I'd want to know the truth...
no matter how gruesome it may be.
(Daebak Realty)
You once asked me...
what kind of person I was.
When I first started this job,
I was just like you.
I thought it was right to tell them the truth I had witnessed.
I thought that would relieve the unrested spirits' grudges.
However...
What did you just say?
My son killed my wife?
He's only in middle school.
How dare you utter such a thing just to make more money?
I will report you for fraud.
- Goodness. - Excuse me.
(Emergency)
Goodness. He killed his son then committed suicide.
Why would he kill his son as well?
- What did that boy do so wrong? - Tell me about it.
That's when I promised myself not to interfere in their lives...
no matter what I learned during the exorcisms.
Goodwill doesn't always reap good fruit.
In fact,
it often brings bad results.
Then...
I'd like to at least tell her where he is.
We can do...
that much.
They must've found the body by now.
Does it bother you?
I can't help but see myself in Ms. Yoo Young Soon.
I've wasted the past 20 years of my life...
since I didn't know the truth.
Is it right for me to let her continue believing...
in a lie?
At times, the truth is more painful.
(Forensic)
I had no idea you were so close.
You must've been so cold.
It's so beautiful.
How could you take such good care of the house?
It's rare to find such an old but beautiful house.
This is a perfect place to raise one's children...
since it's surrounded by nature.
What? Oh In Bum?
What brings you here?
We make sure our houses...
are always in tip-top condition.
I'm so grateful.
In Bum.
Hey, snap out of it.
Ms. Hong, I'll give them a house tour.
Sure.
- Shall we? - No, thank you.
I'll wait here.
- Feel free to look around. - Okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
This way.
The trees have grown so much.
I heard my father planted them the year I was born.
Nothing has changed.
Only I have aged.
I'd make snowmen out here...
and have watermelon during the summer.
This house holds...
so many memories.
Don't you want to look...
for your brother?
If you want, we can help you find him.
My brother died 50 years ago.
Don't you just love how it was renovated?
Yes. You can move in right away.
What do you think? Did you look around the house?
Yes. I will talk to my husband one more time and call you.
Yes. Take all the time you need and make your decision.
Okay.
Shall we get going?
No. I'm going to stay here for a bit more.
Today might be my last day here.
Okay. I will call you soon.
Okay.
You're still here.
Your brother didn't kill your father.
Pardon? What are you talking about all of a sudden?
We are only telling you the truth which we came across...
while performing an exorcism in this house.
Your father...
took his own life.
Why are you telling me such a lie?
I'm not lying.
That's the last memory...
your father held onto down to his last moment.
With that memory, we were able to find his body.
Your brother...
wasn't after the inheritance.
He just wasn't good at expressing himself.
He was heartbroken for you and the trouble you went through.
And your father knew how truly your brother had felt.
The fact that he was a burden...
on his children caused him more pain...
than his illness.
That's why when he was lucid,
he decided to end his own life.
Even until the last moment,
all he ever wanted was for you two to be happy.
If he knew that you guys would be strangers 50 years,
he would not have made...
that decision.
- Ma'am. - I see.
Thank you for telling me.
Ma'am.
I am sorry.
You are sorry? That's it?
What if our mother dies? How will you fix that?
Darn it.
Mom. Wake up.
Mom. Oh, Mom...
Are you okay?
Why did you do that? That wasn't like you.
I'm the troublemaker between us.
- Hey. - He's here.
Sir.
This is Ms. Hong Ji A, the CEO of Daebak Realty.
I see.
Hello. I'm Yoo Young Sik.
The visiting hours are over, sir.
Young Sik.
Young Soon. Can you recognize me?
Now that you are older,
you look just like Dad.
I came too late, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
No. Thank you for coming.
I should apologize.
I was young and didn't know any better then.
I only made things worse for you.
Thank you. Thank you for coming to see me.
(Daebak Realty)
I must have scared you dearly.
No.
Thank you so much for making a great recovery.
Right.
That day,
I never got to thank you before I fainted.
I am sorry about that.
After hearing what you told me,
it would be a lie if I told you that I wasn't shocked.
But now that I am a mother...
and older,
I can understand why my father...
made that decision.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you for helping me...
not resent my brother at the end of my life.
I'm sorry to do this to you,
but I cannot sell the house.
I want to spend my remaining time in that house...
where I have so many childhood memories...
before my time is up.
I'm sure your father will be very happy.
Okay.
Lighten up. Everything ended well.
By the way, why did you really do it?
You told me that our job was sending away the unrested spirit...
and not to get involved in their lives.
Why did you tell Ms. Yoo the truth all of a sudden?
Your nosy quality must have rubbed off on me.
So you're giving me all the credit.
Yes. You deserve all the credit.
What's all this?
Are you trying to make my heart flutter?
No. Right after you thanked me the other day,
you told me to go into the water.
What's the catch?
What will you make me do now?
There's no catch.
I've thought about this case.
Helping her find out the truth about her late father was nice.
But helping Ms. Yoo reconcile with her brother...
made me happier.
She'll be able to live without resentment now.
- Performing an exorcism isn't... - Performing an exorcism isn't...
- just for the unrested spirit. - just for the unrested spirit.
It's also for the people who are left behind.
They must go on their lives.
Yes. I was just about to say that.
That's a nice lesson.
She was a good exorcist.
My mother used to say that all the time when I was young.
Back then, I didn't understand what she meant by that.
Are you sure you can live here all by yourself?
Goodness. I still got a few good years left in me!
Living alone would be great. It'll be very relaxing.
You should come by often.
Okay.
- You got it, Young Soon. - Okay.
(Daebak Realty)
(Withdrawn)
Forget about hitting the jackpot. That was a bust.
We lost two cases in a row.
There are some bad days too.
(Record of Exorcism: 2021)
(Record of Exorcism: 1980)
(Record of Exorcism: 1978)
Only the record from 1979 is missing.
What?
What... What's going on?
Darn it.
(Record of Exorcism: 1979)
At times,
the truth is more painful.
Did you give it a thought?
I told you to quit working as a psychic.
Aren't you the one who'd miss having me around?
Do you know that your theme today is very odd?
- You seemed cute, that's all. - Shut up.
- Hold me. - Do not move.
It's right behind you.
Will you be okay? I don't think Ji A will give up easily.
If she finds out anything...
I won't let that happen.
I'm the only one who looks into the Record of Exorcism.
One of my grandmother's Record of Exorcism is gone.
Did you take it?