EPISODE 8
- Wake up.
- That's my sister!
- What are we going to do?
- Move aside!
- Where are we going?
- Please let her live.
Goodness, stop doing this and leave.
Get over there.
What did you see?
Come back to yourself.
That...
In March
of the Year of the Black Horse,
laborers who were...
building up the capital city
died of an epidemic.
Those who survived claimed...
they witnessed a man without a face.
In February
of the Year of the Black Chicken,
three days went by...
after rumors of the faceless man
broke out in Hanyang.
A fire broke out
from the southern part of Hanyang...
and engulfed the entire city,
burning down over 2,000 houses.
Leap February, near spring
of the Year of the White Dragon,
hailstones the size of an egg
fell upon Gyeongsang Province,
freezing and withering the crops.
Farmers claimed
to have seen a faceless woman.
Oh my gosh.
These are records that say
big disasters broke out...
after faceless people were
witnessed.
There are similar records
from other time periods too.
Faceless people?
Egg ghosts.
You'll see an explanation
in the evil spirits section...
of the Encyclopedia
of Unrested Spirits.
"Egg ghosts are created..."
"through an entanglement of spirits
who die on the same day..."
"and the same hour..."
"due to events such as wars,
epidemics, and big fires."
"It can be characterized by
the lack of eyes, nose, and mouth."
"Once this ghost is observed,"
"many people will
either become ill or die."
The kid Oh Sung Sik brought
also didn't have a face.
The spirits who died from his arson
must've become an egg ghost,
then went onto possess that kid.
But it says right here...
that it's impossible
to drive it out with the needle.
That's what makes me concerned.
My mother already knew
that her needle was useless.
But she clearly made use of it
on that day.
I need to know
what she wanted to do.
But that doesn't change the fact
you need a strong psychic...
to send away the unrested spirit
of an exorcist.
Oh In Bum was strong enough,
but we couldn't do it.
It may not be
the problem of the psychic.
Just as I was sure
of my incorrect memory for 20 years,
I may be missing something again.
Anyway, the egg ghost is
the only lead I have at this point.
Anyway,
what have you been looking for?
You're being very distractive.
I've been looking through
Records of Exorcism to check...
if any of my ancestors
have driven out an egg ghost.
Only the record
from 1979 is missing.
Really?
I'm the only one who
looks into the Record of Exorcism.
I guess there was one more.
(From sunset to sunrise)
So from your boarding house
and your car,
you are missing 4 laptops
and 2 tablet PCs, correct?
I think that's about it for now.
I'll give you a call
when we find something.
But there are no CCTVs around here,
so it won't be easy.
Were you worried about us?
- It's nothing...
- Did you go through my bookcase?
What?
One of my grandmother's
Record of Exorcism is gone.
Did you take it?
She's treating me like a thief
on the day I got something stolen.
Did a thief
break into your place too?
What's a Record of Exorcism?
Is that expensive?
If you didn't, forget it.
Hey, you can't leave like this.
Hey, what's a Record of Exorcism?
Tell me!
Shouldn't you apologize
for suspecting me without proof?
I do have proof.
Did you forget that I caught you
snooping around my bookshelf?
Why would you bring that up?
You're so grudging.
- Ms. Hong, I'm off now.
- Okay.
- See you in the evening.
- Goodbye.
What in the world
is this Record of Exorcism?
They're exorcism records
written by an exorcist.
I see. Like a workbook.
You even have ones
from the Joseon Era.
This is a family business.
Correct.
But it'll end with me.
Why?
Why would I hand down something
so evil?
You absorb strangers' memories
and feel sadness,
hatred, and regret.
With time,
you start hating humans in general.
You don't know which emotions
are truly yours.
In the end,
you lose your entire life.
Don't worry.
You're someone...
that can't be forgotten so easily.
- Is it empty?
- Should we break in?
Who are you?
Hello, ma'am.
Doesn't Oh In Bum live here?
We're his friends.
Hello.
- Look over there.
- What are you looking for?
Get out! Get out this instant!
Stop bothering me!
We looked
into Oh In Bum's surroundings...
and his grandmother's house,
but found no memorandum.
(Chairman Do Hak Sung)
Are you sure?
Seeing how he's been visiting those
who knew his uncle,
I don't think he knows anything
for sure.
You promised
you'll give us an apartment unit.
- What?
- I set the place on fire...
and killed people.
No.
He wouldn't have said such a thing
had he not known anything.
I'm sure there's something.
(Ceremony for the Redevelopment
of Golden Apartment)
What was that?
Should I eat something
before I go to bed?
What was that?
Hold on.
Was I seeing things?
Gosh, that startled me.
I was scared to death.
What?
What's wrong with this? What?
Rumors about a child spirit
have been going around...
since last month.
It's not uncommon for spirits
to appear in accident spots.
Did you two also witness
this child spirit?
No, we didn't.
Then why are you suddenly
putting your house on the market?
It's Byeol.
- Sorry?
- That child spirit...
is our daughter, Byeol.
She refuses...
to leave this earth
because it's too unfair for her.
It's all because
her murderer hasn't been punished.
He's so shameless.
He keeps denying
that he had anything to do with it.
Honey.
To be frank,
I've never believed in spirits.
But...
after hearing that our poor kid
was still wandering this earth,
how could I ignore it?
That's why we came all the way here
to ask for your help.
Please help our daughter...
find peace.
I beg you.
Nothing's for certain just yet.
Perhaps,
there really is an unrested spirit.
Or people could've concocted
that story...
just for fun
or could've just seen things.
If it turns out
that there is no unrested spirit,
we will decline your request.
I will start the briefing.
(Rendezvous Park Apartment)
("Young Girl Dies in a Car Accident
in Front of an Apartment Complex")
Rumors about an unrested spirit
appearing around the complex...
started a month ago...
after a car accident took place.
The victim was Eun Byeol,
a ten-year-old.
She lived in Block 108.
She got hit
by another resident's car...
on her way home from her friend's
in Block 109.
Goodness. Poor girl.
The driver claims
that he's innocent.
You murderer. Bring her back!
Stop it already!
How many times must I tell you?
I didn't kill her!
She was already on the ground!
It was too dark to see anything!
- Come on, now.
- Bring her back!
What about the CCTV?
They were putting up fences
inside the complex,
so both the street lamps
and the CCTV were turned off.
"Putting up fences?"
Is it normal to put up fences
inside apartment complexes?
This is a social-mix complex...
where local residents
and public rental residents...
live together.
"Social-mix"?
Some of the apartments
were given to low-income families...
when they were originally built.
Families from different statuses
were mixed together,
thus the term "social mix".
Just putting them together
won't help them become closer.
That's why the two groups
had a conflict.
The local residents put up fences
to keep themselves divided.
The public rental residents
were against this.
Then which group was Byeol in?
The local residents.
How could you block a pathway?
What about our kids?
They'll have to take a longer route
to school.
Please stop screaming.
This is right for our kids' safety.
Strangers come and go here.
It's not safe for them.
Are you calling us strangers?
Why won't you answer me?
We're residents
from the same complex,
so let's not fight.
We may live in the same complex,
but we're not the same.
What did you just say?
Don't push me! How uncivil of you!
I looked into the rumors.
I searched online community sites
for mothers and ghost story sites.
The most popular stories...
were about drivers who died
of a cardiac arrest...
at the sudden appearance
of a child spirit...
or the child spirit covered
the driver's eyes...
Child spirits aren't evil.
No victims from that area
were hospitalized or passed away.
Ghost stories and facts
don't go hand in hand.
Continue.
Anyway,
due to consecutive accidents,
they've blocked all vehicles
from entering the complex.
To be precise,
only delivery vans are forbidden.
The accident wasn't even caused
by a delivery van.
They're just abusing their power.
That has nothing to do with us.
- We'll end the briefing here.
- Okay.
Will you visit the site today?
Yes. I should.
I ought to.
What?
Can you even drive in that?
- Be quiet.
- You look cute, that's all.
Shut up.
Gosh.
Look at that. You can't do it.
Do it yourself.
Gosh.
You can't do it?
The representative meeting
concluded...
that unauthorized vehicles
were forbidden to enter.
Don't get mad at me.
How am I to carry all these parcels
in there?
In any case,
your vehicle's not allowed to enter.
It's forbidden.
I knew it.
This is exactly why I hate kids.
They have no pattern.
You can do it, Ji A.
Do you know that
your theme today is very odd?
Child spirits
just don't stand still.
They go everywhere.
That's why it's difficult
to identify them.
My body temperature plummets
as well.
What's there to worry about?
Your special psychic is here.
Stop rambling.
You're distracting me.
What? Have you forgotten
that I saved your life twice...
It's here.
Darn it.
Oh, my.
What was that?
She's such a good runner.
Oh, no.
Hold my hand.
That's what I'm here for.
Don't move.
The child spirit is behind you.
Why aren't you doing anything?
- Did she leave?
- Wait.
I didn't get to check her face yet.
What are you two doing here?
They are my guests, sir.
I see. They are here for you?
I got a complaint about
a stranger going around the complex.
- I'm sorry about that.
- Have a good night.
Mom.
Did you confirm everything?
Is it my daughter, Byeol?
Yes.
It's Byeol.
Ma'am.
Are you feeling better now?
It's all my fault.
Ma'am.
I should've tried hard
to move to a better apartment.
Only if we didn't move in here...
Since I checked the face
of the unrested spirit,
my secretary will be in touch
to schedule the exorcism.
Ms. Hong.
When you perform the exorcism,
can't I be there with you?
No. It's dangerous to have
an outsider present.
I don't want her to be alone
when she leaves this world.
Please.
Please let me be there for her.
Let's go.
Not a word.
You don't know
what I'm going to say.
Just keep your mouth shut.
Don't even sigh.
What?
It's a green light now.
(Land, Private Properties,
Commercial Buildings, Rent)
(Changhwa Restaurant)
What? You...
My gosh.
Don't worry. He'll leave soon.
Did the universe finally punish you?
What a mess you are.
Thanks.
What happened?
Do Hak Sung tossed me out...
because I couldn't...
get rid of Daebak Realty.
He kicked me out of my nightclub.
- No. I can't leave!
- My gosh. Goodness.
Hey!
Oh In Bum.
What? Don't sound so serious.
Let me ask you one thing.
Remember that day...
when you scammed me
saying my nightclub was haunted?
It's the same thing, right?
What you saw that day?
(Taejin Service)
What I saw that day...
wasn't a real spirit, right?
It was a real spirit.
I'm sure you heard...
that Ms. Hong's late mother's spirit
still lives here.
Is that so?
I see.
Use this opportunity
to stop bullying people.
Live an honest life.
- Oh In Bum.
- Don't hold my hand. It's creepy.
Do you think Daebak Realty has...
an opening for me?
Gosh. You're a lunatic.
To be in that line of business,
I'm sure they'd need
some kind of bodyguard.
Ms. Hong is the bodyguard.
Besides, if you were in her shoes,
do you think you'd hire yourself?
Darn it. Ms. Hong is
stronger than me.
And she can fight better than me.
Hey, don't you owe me money?
350,000 dollars.
You won't have to pay me back.
Unbelievable.
I don't owe you any money
to begin with.
I earned the 50,000 dollars...
fair and square
for the exorcism I performed.
I really don't have a place to go.
Hey, look at this.
I'm trying to not get caught
by Do Hak Sung. Seriously.
He's a scary guy.
He really might kill me.
I'm really sorry
this happened to you.
You're on your own.
You're here anyway. Eat up.
Don't ever come back.
Slow down.
Hey, In Bum.
My baby sent me a present...
- My gosh.
- Are you sure her photo is real?
You've never met her in person.
Why would she send you
a birthday present?
She's real. My girlfriend is real.
We're meeting next week.
- Really?
- Yes.
That will be your first date.
It's underwear.
Read it.
"Thank you as always, Ji Chul.
Happy birthday."
My gosh. Let me see.
Wow, look how classy these are.
Don't you think
my baby has great taste?
Yes. They sure do look special.
Here. That's for you.
But aren't these your birthday gift
from your girlfriend?
- She told me to share with you.
- With me?
- Why?
- Because my baby is that kind.
Anyway,
don't you think it's very special
that she gave me underwear?
Yes, sure.
Giving underwear to a man.
I have to think hard now.
What kind of a special present
am I going to get her?
Congrats.
(Daebak Realty)
Hello.
This is it. This is the address.
- Is this it?
- Yes.
It doesn't look too great.
"From sunset to sunrise?"
- Are they open or not?
- What's going on?
- Hello?
- Excuse us.
Hello.
- My gosh.
- She was in.
- Come later.
- Let's go inside.
- Later, my foot.
- Let's go.
- Hey, I said...
- You tell her.
- No, you talk to her.
Hye Jung's mother?
Byeol's family
put their house on sale, right?
I hear they're selling it urgently.
Is that correct?
The residents of Rendezvous Park
promised to not drop the price...
below 10,000 dollars
per square meter,
so please keep that promise.
I never made any promises.
Our residents made this promise
for everyone who lives there.
If one family
sells it at a cheaper price,
the price for our entire complex
will drop down.
It's a measure we took
to protect our property rights.
Rigging the price is illegal.
Rig...
We aren't rigging the price.
It's how our community
stands together.
Byeol's mother
knows that very well too.
She got a little emotional
and made this mistake.
You already know why she's leaving.
Yet you're here only to discuss
the selling price,
and you call that standing together?
We're more heartbroken
than anybody...
about what happened to that family.
However, that doesn't mean
we should all suffer a loss.
A loss.
Please leave.
I need to get some rest.
Well, it looks like
we've made our point very clear.
Let's go.
Unbelievable.
The problem
with tonight's operation is...
that it'll be held outdoors,
just like the time at the hospital.
Incense burns much faster outdoors,
so it'll become very problematic
if we get even a little stalled.
So don't you dare get distracted
or do anything else.
I never do anything else.
Whatever.
I already talked
to a security guard...
who works the night shift to keep
as many people away as possible.
- "Talked?"
- She bribed him.
I see.
(Eun Byeol)
You really won't tell her mother?
I told you not to get distracted
or do anything else.
I mean, she's a little kid.
You should do it with the mother...
Do you think we're holding
an open class for exorcism?
Are we letting parents in now?
I just thought I'd mention it.
I knew you'd say no.
All of her memories will flow
into me afterward,
so I thought it'd be better
to send her away in peace.
Oh In Bum. You did that again.
It wasn't me.
Ms. Hong, I beg you.
Please let me see her one last time.
I can't do that.
It's impossible for you to see
her unrested spirit anyway.
I don't mind.
Just let me be there with her
as she leaves this world.
Please do this
and help me save myself.
Please, I beg you.
Please.
Ma'am, please stand up.
You cannot see her.
But it might be possible...
for you to hear her voice.
I can't be sure of that either.
Are you all right with that?
That's more than enough. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
But you must promise me one thing.
You have to cover your eyes
with this...
and stay in this circle.
No matter what you hear,
you cannot take a step outside
or take off your blindfold.
Okay.
Let's get started.
We won't need that soccer ball.
Her mother is here.
Mom!
It's time. Take it off.
Mom.
Byeol?
Mom!
Byeol.
Byeol, is that you?
Byeol!
Byeol.
Mom, I'm sorry.
No.
I should be sorry.
I'll make sure I catch that man...
who did that to you.
I lied to you and said
I went to the English academy...
when I actually went to play
with Yoo Ri.
- Mom!
- Byeol.
- Hello.
- Hi, are you Byeol's friend?
Yes, Yoo Ri lives
in this apartment too.
- Really? Which block?
- Block 109.
I see, Block 109.
Okay. Goodbye.
Why are your clothes dirty?
Where did you play?
- What?
- Let's go.
You'll be
in fourth grade next year, right?
The other students will get
better grades than you...
if you only play soccer.
Yoo Ri's mom told her...
that she could play soccer
as much as she pleased.
That's why she's the best player
in our class.
That's why they live
in the rental block.
What's so bad about that?
Only the poor live there.
If you don't study,
you'll end up living there too.
Is that what you want?
If you don't know what I mean,
just do as I say.
I'm only doing this for your sake.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Goodness. My princess.
- Hello.
- I'm glad we ran into you.
Where are you headed?
Residents from the rental block...
are causing a scene
at the fence construction site.
- Let's go together.
- Really?
I should go as well.
Goodbye.
Make sure to come home
right after the academy.
Dad's buying macarons,
your favorite.
- Yes!
- How cute.
I'm so late. Mom's going to kill me.
I need to get home.
I'm late. I should hurry.
You weren't hit by a car?
You fell off the fence?
Do you mean that fence...
that I allowed them to build?
I'm sorry, Mom.
I know you told me not to do
anything dangerous.
I really thought I could climb
over it.
No. No, Byeol. It's not your fault.
It's my fault.
I built that fence. I...
I killed my own daughter.
Byeol! I'm so sorry!
I'm... I'm so sorry!
It's okay. Don't cry.
Byeol.
Byeol, I'm so sorry!
Byeol...
Byeol.
I'm sorry.
Byeol, I'm so sorry.
Did Byeol leave safely?
She did.
I'm glad.
I was worried
because I didn't absorb her memory.
That's because
I didn't use the stick.
An unrested spirit's memory channels
through the stick.
Is it possible to send them away
without using it?
This is my first time
actually experiencing it.
Hello.
You're the one
who called Byeol's mom,
didn't you?
I'm a wench...
who killed her own kids.
I knew something had to be done.
I'm sorry.
Byeol found peace.
She told her everything she wanted.
She was even mature enough
to comfort her mom.
That's great.
Thank you.
(Daebak Realty)
All right. So you had already
planned everything out...
when you entered the inn.
I bet you weren't confident about it
and were terrified.
But had you asked for help,
many people could've done so.
You could've sent them
to an orphanage as well.
Why did you kill them?
That was unnecessary,
don't you think?
I didn't want them
to become burdens.
Isn't it obvious?
Gosh, look at you.
I told you to wait for me.
Ji A called me this afternoon.
She wanted to see the case file
on Woo Sung Sik's suicide.
I told her no, of course.
Will you be all right?
I doubt she'll give up that easily.
What if she snoops around
and finds out?
I'm going to make sure...
she doesn't...
find out.
Hello, ma'am.
My daughter...
didn't die of a car accident.
She fell off the fence.
The fence that I allowed
to be built.
Did a witness come forward?
No.
She told me herself.
Your daughter told you?
Yes.
I wasn't the only one there.
Ms. Hong from the realty
also heard it.
"Ms. Hong from the realty?"
Do you mean Daebak Realty?
Ms. Hong Ji A?
(2021 Rendezvous Park Apartment)
(Closed)
Are you here to eat?
Why did she close the restaurant?
She received a call about someone
having spotted her son this morning,
so she went to check.
She went to a rural area,
so she'll be back late.
Where are you going?
I haven't eaten yet either.
(Ttang Ttang Chicken)
They have both fried
and oven-baked chicken.
Set three, this, this, and this.
I just ordered mine. What about you?
What?
I'd like this one, please.
You eat so well.
I can't eat as much nowadays
due to stress.
It's delicious.
(Kind, Present, and Swift Police)
(Daebak Realty, Ju Hwa Jeong)
Sir.
We received the autopsy result.
Like what the driver claimed,
she had already passed away
before getting hit by his car.
They believe she fell.
I guess what the mother told us
was true.
Do you think this is a coincidence?
- What do you mean?
- The real estate agency.
They got it right twice in a row.
It could be a coincidence
the first time around.
But seeing how they did it again,
it can't be.
Then, what?
Should we ask her who the culprit is
for the robbery case in Suam-dong?
We don't have evidence,
so we can't crack it.
Right. You should go to her
and ask her this too.
Ask her when you'll get slapped.
Are you kidding me?
Get back to work.
- What a useless thing to say.
- What?
After everything you said to me,
you're looking into Daebak Realty
behind my back.
- It's not what you think.
- Of course, it is.
Come here. Grab a chair.
Listen up.
Twenty years ago,
someone died at Daebak Realty.
And the person who died was
Hong Mi Jin, Hong Ji A's mother.
And Young Hong Ji A,
Young Oh In Bum,
and his uncle, Oh Sung Sik were
at the scene.
But the first person to call in
this incident was...
(Case Report)
- Ju Hwa Jeong.
- Really?
And two days later,
Oh Sung Sik wrote in his suicide
note that he was the one...
who set Yongnam Village on fire
and killed himself.
Yongnam Village?
The fire in the shantytown?
Right.
Golden Properties was the biggest
benefactor of the fire.
So obviously,
they were our prime suspect.
But with Oh Sung Sik dead,
they were no longer the suspect.
You know this company,
Golden Properties...
- Do you know what it is now?
- What is it?
It's Dohak Construction now.
Gosh. Keep going.
Here's what I think.
Golden Properties made
Oh Sung Sik...
set the shantytown on fire.
And they got Hong Mi Jin
to kill Oh Sung Sik.
But things went south,
so she was the one who died.
So they got rid of Oh Sung Sik
by making it look like a suicide.
Gosh. That makes no sense.
It makes perfect sense.
Then, how could the daughter
of Hong Mi Jin...
and the nephew of Oh Sung Sik
work together now?
It's hard to get over
that kind of past.
That's what puzzles me.
Did you think about it?
About what?
I told you to quit
working as a psychic.
I already gave you my answer.
That I won't quit.
Let's be honest. If I quit,
wouldn't that affect you the most?
I remember their memories
and absorb their habits.
I even help you bring back
your temperature.
You won't be able to find
a valuable partner like me again.
I'm not kidding.
I'm not kidding either.
To be honest, this job was tough.
But it was fun.
This was the first time
I felt rewarded...
for what I did.
I didn't know.
But I think I can be
a good person too.
You are a good person.
So you should quit.
You weren't going to keep working...
as my psychic anyway
once your contract ended.
Who knows?
Hello.
What? Why are you here?
Until when will you waste your time?
- Go and deliver the food first.
- Okay. I'll go deliver it.
- I'll be back.
- What?
Enjoy your meal. Enjoy.
He's working here now?
- It just happened.
- How?
Why do you keep asking me questions?
Am I on trial?
Come here.
What happened?
I thought she got news about her son
and went to a rural area.
That was a bust.
So she came back all disappointed.
And I guess he was in front of
the restaurant, looking all shabby.
So that must have reminded her
of her son.
Really?
- I don't feel good about this.
- Same here.
So the chairman let out the guys?
Yes. They raided
Oh In Bum's van, lodging,
and his house in the rural area.
We don't know what it is,
but he is looking for
something important. I'm sure of it.
Something important
for the chairman?
- Make sure to find out what it is.
- Okay.
Sir.
Are you making deliveries too?
To jump,
I must crouch down
no matter how embarrassing it is.
I am disgraced right now.
But I will find out the weakness...
of Oh In Bum and Hong Ji A
who are responsible for my disgrace.
And I will earn
the chairman's approval...
and go back to my position
with my head held high.
- Sun Nyu.
- Yes.
Pay for my food.
- Have a good night!
Help me.
Nothing really stood out.
I just saw 2 adults and 2 kids
lying unconsciously.
(Oh Sung Sik)
(Had a 53-year-old mother
and a 7-year-old nephew)
His residence is unknown
ever since he moved out...
after he graduated high school.
It's not easy to track him down.
(Born in Geonjeong-myeon, Haju,
South Gyeongsang Province)
Where are you going?
I bought us some treats.
I'm going to a rural area.
Don't come to work today.
Where? Let me come with you.
- We can eat this on our way there.
- It's a personal matter.
What?
Eat it as you drive there.
I thought of you, so I even
stood in line to get them for you.
Be careful when you drive.
It's good.
Is anyone home?
My goodness. I don't feel good.
Gosh.
Is anyone inside?
- Goodness.
- Ms. Jung Geum Ja?
Gosh.
Oh, my.
Goodness. I don't feel good.
Let's talk.
What took you so long?
- I couldn't reach you either.
- Pardon?
- Aren't you her guardian?
- No.
I just happened to be...
Wait. Ma'am. Where...
Where are you going?
Ma'am.
Gosh. You can't leave right now.
The cancer cells started to spread.
You're in critical condition.
Go to a big hospital now.
- I know that. Forget it.
- You must get...
My gosh. Ma'am.
(Dr. Kim's Clinic)
Ms. Jung.
I'll drive you home.
Please get in the car.
Buses are still running.
Do you even have a wallet?
Don't you have to call
your children?
They are all dead.
You're not in touch with
your grandson at all?
Why are you asking?
Did he take something of yours too?
Not exactly.
After he left home,
he's never called me.
Goodbye.
Where do you think you're going?
Eat before you go.
I'm fine.
Do I have enough rice?
I'm not hungry.
- Do you want more rice?
- Yes.
Here.
It's late. You should stay over.
No, I'm leaving right away.
Anyway, why are you
looking for In Bum?
- What?
- You're here to look for him too.
Aren't you?
Is your grandson named...
Oh In Bum?
(February 2014, Haju High School)
(Oh In Bum)
What are you hiding in a hurry?
Weren't you told
not to come to work today?
It became a habit now,
so I can't seem to sleep.
What are you doing?
I'm just going to look.
Am I not allowed to do that?
I told you to finish your contract,
then leave quietly.
Why are you dying to make me leave?
- Because I can't trust you.
- What about you?
Are you trustworthy?
You're back.
You're here.
Didn't you enjoy the macaroons?
In Bum.
That kid from 20 years ago is...
you?
Was it you?
Yes.
Tell me.
What happened on that day?
Tell me what caused...
my mother's death on that day.
- Tell me!
- How would I know?
I'm here to find that out too.
What?
What did your mother do to my uncle
on that day...
to cause his death?
I wanted to know.
Do you want me to tell you why
Oh Sung Sik died?
Because you're a psychic.
If it hadn't been for you,
your uncle and my mother...
would be alive.
No one would've died.
The one who killed my mother is...
you.
SELL YOUR HAUNTED HOUSE
There are too many mysteries
surrounding my uncle's death.
But I do know that I can
no longer stay at Daebak Realty.
Maybe he tried to con us
by using his history.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I didn't know he caused your death.
That jerk.
No, something is
definitely going on between them.
Someone was murdered
at the officetel I live in.
Please spare me.
I'll find you another psychic.
It's over, right?
I cannot begin investigating
on pure speculation!
You don't have to believe
what I said about spirits.
But shouldn't you trust
what someone alive is saying?
- Ms. Hong!
- She's possessed.
Drop your knife and get up.