#ROMANTIC
#FREE-SPIRITED
#GIRLCRUSH
#VOLUNTARILY SINGLE
#IN A LONG-TERM RELATIONSHIP
HOW IS YOUR LOVE?
LOVESTRUCK IN THE CITY
What is this place?
You didn't have to rent a nice place
like this just for an interview.
LET'S TALK ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
TEN MINUTES AGO
You know me.
-I like kissing.
-I must have been out of my mind.
What do you mean, "out of my mind"?
-Why did I do that?
-What do you mean?
-I regret it.
-Hey! What?
Did you just say you regret it?
Did she say she regrets… This is insane.
Seriously? Did you just say you regret it?
Do you mean it?
Wait!
You know what?
Think carefully before you answer.
If you say that you regret it now,
I'm going to go insane. I'm serious.
-I regret it.
-Damn it.
Hey, you kissed me first.
You always kissed me first.
You even kissed me first in Yangyang.
-Right. I must have been crazy.
-What do you mean, "crazy"?
You're not crazy. You're in love with me.
You… Hold on.
Look. Look at this.
I threw this ring away in Cheonggyecheon.
The fact that she has it here means
she went into the water on a cold day
and picked it up.
You know what?
I could never do something like that.
You loved me.
I did back then.
It broke my heart
when you threw it away in Cheonggyecheon,
so I picked it up in the water
on that cold day.
Yes. You did that. But what?
-What about now?
-But I regret it now.
I regret fishing it out and kissing you.
Look at her, everyone.
Look at her!
Look at her, everyone!
And guys, remember that face!
She kissed me first,
but she says she regrets it.
She's tearing my heart out.
Should I just report her
for sexual assault?
Report me? You kissed me back.
Fine. I kissed you back. So what?
I like you, so I don't regret it.
I like you, too. So I kissed you.
But I still regret it.
I like you.
It's true that I like you,
but you're not my top priority right now.
Okay. You do like me.
Fine. Let's hear it, then.
What's so important to you right now?
I'm sure Kyeong-jun already told you
how stupid and frustrating I used to be.
That you were engaged to another guy?
So what? What about that?
I don't care about it at all.
What's the big deal about it?
What does it have to do
with you liking me back?
It might not matter to you,
but it does to me.
It was a secret I wanted to take
to the grave without anyone finding out.
You found out about it,
and I feel humiliated.
"Humiliated"? What about me?
Look at me.
I'm begging you to take me back
like a crazy idiot.
Right now, I just look insane.
-Stop it. People are watching.
-I don't care!
They can watch us. Go ahead and watch!
I'm crazy!
I don't mind. They can watch.
I'm fine with it.
They already think I'm crazy.
Let them watch.
You know what?
You're really selfish.
Fine. I am selfish.
I pity, value,
and cherish myself the most.
I decided to live only for myself.
I'd rather be a horrible woman
than a stupid slowpoke.
You said Lee Eun-o was frustrating, too.
We're not that couple
who fell for each other in Yangyang.
We've seen each other's worst moments.
Do you think we can be happy together now?
My head hurts.
I'm going crazy.
What should I do? Can anyone tell me?
What do I do? I'll do as you say.
No. You know what, Seon-a…
No.
Lee Eun-o. I will get
revenge.
I mean it. I'll get revenge.
Is there a way
to make her cry?
Is there a way to make her
shed tears of blood?
Please tell me.
What? Meet someone else?
That doesn't solve anything.
I still like Eun-o.
It'd make that woman feel bad,
don't you think?
I can't date someone else
in this condition.
Right now, I'm the crazy one!
Never mind.
Never mind. No.
You know what? I cannot let this slide.
Here. Look. I'll show you.
You're dead meat.
Fine.
CRAZY IDIOT
-Hello?
-How can you sleep right now?
What?
Did she hang up?
Truly unbelievable.
-What?
-How can you sleep right now?
I'm sleepy. So what?
"Sleepy"? Gosh, you are
truly awful, indeed!
-Damn it.
-I know.
You…
You are terrible.
I am.
Hello?
She must be out of her mind.
She hung up again.
Don't hang up on me.
Don't hang up. Please don't hang up on me.
Also,
don't go to sleep.
If you do,
it will drive me crazy
and torture me to death.
Okay. I won't.
Yes. Good.
Just
stay like that.
Fine. I will.
By the way, if I'm the bad one here,
what are you?
I'm…
I'm the crazy guy.
-Do you know you're crazy?
-Yes.
It's all because of you.
But you know what?
Do you really regret meeting me?
I don't regret it.
Me neither.
I've done all sorts of crazy things
after I met you.
But I never regretted meeting you.
When I was with you,
I loved every moment.
I tried out things
I'd wanted to do but never tried.
And…
the fact that you liked me
made me very grateful.
That's what I needed back then.
I wanted to become someone else.
And I wanted to be loved.
Do you
honestly believe
that you weren't yourself in Yangyang?
I still don't know.
I don't know if I've changed
or if I'm just Lee Eun-o
pretending to be Yoon Seon-a.
I've tried and reminded myself
not to go back
to the stupid old me.
But there are times
when even that effort feels fake.
That's it.
Your top priority.
You're right.
I
want to find my true self.
I want to know what I'm made of.
I still don't know who I really am.
But I don't want to go back to the old me.
I'm sorry that this is the real me.
But…
finding myself is more important to me.
Taking care of myself is,
for now,
more important than loving you.
Your keys.
Hello. How can I help you?
Hi. The side-view mirror here fell off.
Take them.
It's for my conscience.
Okay.
I don't want you to feel guilty.
Here.
You left it at my place
when you slept over.
You said you're finding yourself.
So good luck.
Okay.
Aren't you going to tell me to take care?
We'll see each other at work.
Yes. You're right. See you.
Did you glue the fork?
I knew it.
Do you want a new bike?
No, thanks. I want something else.
One hundred kisses.
One hundred "I love you's."
And one hundred hugs.
Then, how about tonight?
Tonight?
No.
I'm washing my bedding now.
I'm sleeping over at Eun-o's tonight.
Just buy an extra set of bedding! Please!
I beg you!
SEON-YEONG
I finally found your place. Come out.
I'm in front of your house.
Where is she?
Whose house is she waiting at?
It's cold outside. Come on.
-What do you want?
-Sorry.
Attention. At ease.
Attention.
Look at these punks. I said, "attention."
Are you leaning on one foot?
Stand properly.
You just kicked me.
Yes. I did kick you.
So what are you going to do?
Should we go to the police
or the Office of Education? You choose.
Smoking itself is bad enough,
but throwing away cigarette butts
on the streets is even worse.
Now, start picking up the cigarette butts
you threw away yourself.
Right now.
Now!
Pick them up. Hurry up.
Why is that tissue here?
Did you blow your nose?
Gosh. Move faster.
Hey, right here. Pick it up.
-Here. Pick that up.
-You blew your nose?
Mister, just mind your business.
You're quite tall.
What a rude punk.
-Do you know how old I am?
-Why should I care?
You're irritating me.
"Irritating"?
How dare you pick a fight
when you're being disciplined?
Get a grip.
By the way, he's my boyfriend.
Don't bother him.
He'll hurt his handsome face.
Right.
I'm her boyfriend.
Do you hear me?
I told you just to turn a blind eye
to such students.
Do you know how scary kids are?
It's okay. I'm scarier.
Yes, that's true.
Why did you say you're at my house?
I couldn't find your house,
so I did a little experiment.
I wanted to see if you could find me
if I texted you.
Do you still miss your mom?
Yes. I miss her when I drink,
when I'm rolling on the floor
with a hangover,
when I'm walking on the streets
late at night,
and when my principal lectures me
for being late.
How could you miss your mom
only in situations
where your mom would be furious?
I feel like she'll come to my rescue.
I'm hot-tempered
because I take after my mom.
"Hey! You shouldn't live like that!
Get a grip!"
I feel like
she'll show up in my dreams to scold me.
What do you want to say if you meet her?
I would tell her there's this guy
I keep thinking about.
He's really slow and really ugly.
He's a total idiot.
Why did you dump him then?
Why didn't you stop me?
You're not the kind of woman I could stop.
I waited for you.
I thought you would stop me
and tell me to reconsider.
I wanted you to beg me to stay.
So I waited, but you didn't come back.
If it was someone else,
I would have just moved on
and wouldn't even have cared.
But because it was you,
I was so angry, annoyed…
and sad.
Do you know how special you are to me?
Whenever I told guys I missed my mom,
they all said,
"Cheer up.
I understand how you feel.
I would feel the same way."
But you were different.
"Whenever you miss your mom, come to me."
You were the only guy who said that.
Look at you.
You're not trying to comfort me.
Instead, you're letting me
talk about my mom all I want.
I guess…
I wanted to be like that to you.
You like Eun-o, right?
No.
That's the first time you said no.
Lee Eun-o. Suh Rin-i.
I don't see them as women.
Even if I see them as women,
I think you're the prettiest
and the sexiest.
What?
Sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I thought you were looking
for an excuse to break up with me.
I thought you fell out of love,
so you wanted to break up.
Why can't I
be in a long-term relationship
with one guy?
Your romance may be short,
but it's passionate.
Every moment counts.
From now on, I won't visit you
even when I miss my mom.
I'll pull through on my own.
I will end our relationship for good.
I came to say that.
Whenever we meet, it snows.
It won't snow for long.
Let's part our ways here.
Hey.
You know…
If you see those punks again
in that alley,
tell them you're my boyfriend.
I get the feeling
they'll punch you someday.
What do you take me for?
When will you get a real job
instead of a part-time job?
Just take your wallet out, Mr. Unemployed.
I'm not unemployed. I'm a novelist.
It's been three years
since you published anything.
A few days ago,
I had a meeting with the editor.
You've been having meetings
for three years
and haven't published anything.
You always rub salt in my wound.
Here's my card.
Hey, are we drinking beer tonight?
No. I'm lighting the candle today.
Why? What's the matter?
I'll tell you later.
-What time does your shift end?
-At ten.
But I'm crashing at your place.
I washed my bedding today.
You seem excited.
Isn't it annoying to come over?
Just get an extra set.
It's a waste. One set is enough.
Go now.
Pack them yourself.
I'm lighting the candle today.
I have something to tell you.
My place, at ten.
No way.
It's my turn to light the candle.
The candle day?
The three of them have been friends
since kindergarten.
When one of them lights a candle,
the other two just listen.
That's what I heard.
Me? I transferred to another school
when I was in second grade,
so I'm not their childhood friend.
I met them again through Rin-i.
Do you remember?
A year ago,
I went off the radar
and came back to Seoul.
My house must be cold inside.
What? Why are all the lights on?
Why is it so warm in here?
You startled me.
Why are you here?
Why are you at my house?
I thought
it would be cold when you came.
I washed your bedding.
And I took out the bedding for winter.
I thought the electricity and water
would have been cut off.
I took care of the bills.
Isn't it cold outside?
Yes.
It's freezing.
Did you know Rin-i came back?
-When?
-When she heard you disappeared.
She even went to Busan to find you.
Unpack your things. Let's eat.
Call Rin-i first.
I think Rin-i came here often to check.
They were on the door.
I put them there for you to see.
Eun-o, it's Rin-i.
I found rice weevils while cleaning,
so I bought a new bag of rice.
It's not for free.
Pay me back when you come back.
I put curry inside the fridge.
I hope you'll come and eat it soon.
Where on earth are you?
Prepare for a huge fight
when you come back.
Come back soon, Eun-o. I miss you.
EUN-O, ARE YOU EATING WELL?
EUN-O, I CLEANED THE HOUSE!
I EVEN WASHED THE BLANKETS!
Back then,
you kept my house warm.
And both of you waited for me.
Thank you.
It's all in the past.
Why bring that up now?
I'm sure you had so many questions
and wanted some answers
from me.
I know you didn't ask
out of consideration.
I knew it all along
but pretended I didn't.
Instead, I hid behind your kindness.
I'm sorry.
Sorry
and thank you.
So…
You can tell us next time if it's hard.
Right, Eun-o.
You don't have to tell us today.
We see each other all the time.
No.
I can't run away again.
I kept secrets from you.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to do that again.
I…
I am…
Yoon Seon-a.
I stole Jae-won's cameras.
Telling the truth is so hard.
Honestly,
I haven't changed at all.
I'm still the same stupid Lee Eun-o.
Why do you think you're stupid?
Back then, I thought it happened
because I was stupid.
Why is that your fault?
It was Kang Min-su's fault.
Your job offer, too.
It was the company's fault, not yours.
I just
didn't want Jae-won
to find out how stupid I was.
I really didn't.
I hated that the girl Jae-won met
in Yangyang was all fake.
And I didn't want Jae-won to find out
why I ended up going
all the way to Yangyang.
I didn't want you to find out
because it's embarrassing and humiliating.
I'm so mad at you.
Same here.
How could you keep that a secret?
What are friends for?
I'm sorry.
But it wasn't because
I didn't think you weren't my friends.
I wanted to keep it to myself.
I just didn't want anyone
to find out about this.
Eun-o.
I have something to tell you.
The old Eun-o
wasn't stupid.
She's right.
You were kind and warmhearted.
I liked the old you so much.
Me too.
And I like the new you, too.
Now you cry when you want to, smile a lot,
get angry easily,
move on quickly, and goof around.
That's why I like you.
The old you. The new you.
Both of them are Eun-o.
They're all Eun-o.
So I don't want you to say that again.
Why are you crying?
Because you're crying.
Don't cry, Rin-i.
You too.
Sorry.
What are you sorry about?
My dear Eun-o.
I'm lonely.
Why am I so lonely?
You left it at my place
when you slept over.
You said you're finding yourself.
So good luck.
What is this?
Right. You wanted to light a candle too.
Oh, me?
Why? What's the matter?
I
broke up with Seon-yeong
before I went to the supermarket.
But you broke up three years ago.
We broke up again.
When she was telling me something,
my heart just…
That's all for the candle day.
I'm going to wash up.
Even so,
it must have been hard on you.
You have to go and work, right?
Yes. I have some work left.
Fine, go. Leave.
Subtitle translation by: Won-hyang Son
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs