Who is that?
Help me.
Killing my mother
wasn't just evil. It was utterly foolish.
I knew that you killed countless people
and even tried to kill me.
But do you know why I didn't kill you?
Because it was a hassle.
I had a job to do.
So if I'd killed you,
it would've inconvenienced me a lot.
Killing these small flies wouldn't,
though.
Anyway…
You have to die now.
-No. Please.
-Why? No.
Don't be scared.
It won't be today.
You see, I've got a principle.
"A painless death is a blessing."
I will give you two things.
A humiliation worse than death,
and…
a slow death, where you'll experience it
every step of the way.
You can take care of that garbage.
And don't even think about
pinning it on me.
If you do, people will find out…
who put him up to it.
I should give you a preview.
Mr. Jang!
-Mr. Jang!
-Sir!
Oh, no. Call 911.
-Call 911.
-Call an ambulance.
We will take her now.
Wait.
Mom.
Mom!
DECEASED, OH GYEONG-JA
EPISODE 17
Her son came back after 30 years,
but what came out of it was her death.
If I hadn't shown up,
she would have lived longer.
In the end, I'm living in hell.
The hell that is regret.
No.
It was brief,
but you gave your mother
eternal happiness.
And your mother did
the same for you as well.
Once you're done hurting, you'll know.
But what pains me the most…
is that I already miss her.
I miss my mother.
Ms. Hong.
Once I'm gone,
please give this scarf
to my son, Ju-hyeong, for me.
The only thing
this foolish mother could give my poor son
is this simple scarf,
which is quite embarrassing.
And…
please tell him this for me.
"Ju-hyeong,
you were a blessing
and happiness to me.
You were the reason
why I carried on living.
Ever since the moment
I could feel your movement in my stomach,
there hasn't been
a single second that I did not love you.
I'm sorry
that I couldn't show you
how much I love you
by your side.
My baby…
My Ju-hyeong…
I love you.
I love you to pieces.
I'm grateful that you're my son,
and I'm sorry for everything."
Please take good care of Ju-hyeong.
Thank you.
Go and get my doctor right now.
Right now!
Get me discharged now.
That will take a while to heal.
You should stay here for now.
Ms. Choi.
Go and kill Vincenzo right now.
I don't care if you have to hire
100 or 200 men.
Kill him by any means necessary.
I don't care how much it costs.
Okay?
Please calm down.
Treating your wound takes priority.
I told you I don't need treatments!
You don't have to tell me.
I will make sure to kill Vincenzo.
But right now, you must think
about Babel first.
Okay…
but don't just kill him.
We'll make him suffer
like he plans to do with us.
Of course.
Ju-hyeong.
Why don't we just kill Jang Han-seok
and Choi Myung-hee and call it a day?
This isn't for revenge.
I'm playing a game of chess.
I'm going to move my pawn today.
All right, then.
Everything is almost ready.
YEONGHO SNACK BAR
CLOSED TEMPORARILY
DUE TO PERSONAL REASONS
FATE PIANO ACADEMY WILL BE
CLOSED TEMPORARILY
PAWN SHOP
NOTICE
ARNO WILL BE CLOSED TEMPORARILY
LAUNDROMAT
CLOSED TEMPORARILY
Mr. Cassano.
We're closing our businesses
for the time being.
We want to help you bring down Babel
in earnest.
We want us to work together
as a team from now on.
To tell you the truth,
I can be quite scary when I'm angry.
I'll help, too.
The whole plaza decided to help you,
so please let us.
We'll be on standby.
Let us know if you need anything.
I'm still in my first trimester,
so I can move around without a problem.
I can help too.
You know that I used to work in the field.
Use me whenever you want.
All this time,
we thought we were weak.
But we weren't weak.
We just didn't try to be strong.
We're going to give it our all now.
Let us fight with you.
Mr. Cassano.
We are all
a part of the Cassano Family.
Vincenzo Cassano!
Why don't you rest at home today?
We'll take care of things.
I should be there.
It's the last day of feeding.
It's just a few locals from Sangcheon-gu.
You don't have to go.
Right. We will take care of
the agreements ourselves.
Why are you so chatty today?
I said I'm going.
Right. I told you he was coming.
Did your mom's funeral go well?
It's Vincenzo.
Yes, thanks to you.
Is your hearing okay?
Yes, thanks to your excellent aim.
By the way,
am I going to die today?
There's one more step before that.
I don't remember.
I shot your ear,
but your brain must have been damaged.
A humiliation worse than death.
To give you that, I'm playing a game
of chess with you starting today.
And I'll get rid of your pieces
one by one.
Imagine being left all alone
on the chessboard.
Isn't that embarrassing and scary?
No.
I don't plan on losing in this chess game.
Unfortunately, you already started losing.
Defeat begins
with one's fear.
Sir, what did Vincenzo say?
Go and ship the miniature.
Okay.
I doubt he just called to say hello.
Right. What if there's another trap?
Gosh. No.
No way. He can't be setting traps
all the time.
-Come on.
-Right.
What did I do to this valuable thing?
Ms. Choi, help us move…
Gosh.
-How can we move it?
-We should push it.
-Unplug it first.
-Unplug it?
We wouldn't be
that much help to him anyway.
That doesn't matter.
It's fine as long as he knows
how serious we are.
Let's think about
how else we can help him.
What's wrong?
What's with the credit card?
Mr. Cassano gave us his credit card
for the well-being of the family.
"Family"?
Let's go to a department store.
What for?
To buy a team uniform
for the Cassano Family.
CONSTRUCTION PERMIT REPORT
BABEL TOWER PROJECT PROGRESS
The approval process for Babel Tower
is ridiculous no matter how I look at it.
It's not just ridiculous.
It's nothing more than a doodle on a wall.
Once Mr. Nam is done
looking over the Guillotine file,
we'll find more ridiculous stuff.
Since we'll be bringing the tower down,
it'll be much better
to bury more trash under it.
Hello, everyone.
-Hello. See you soon.
-Hello.
Sir. Yes.
Let's see.
Secretaries can stay
in the waiting area downstairs.
What's this?
Only the VIPs can enter.
We weren't informed.
-Let's call them.
-Come on.
-This is ridiculous.
-Let's go downstairs for now.
-Please step aside.
-Step aside.
CONGRATULATIONS ON MOVING IN,
MAKE A LOT OF MONEY
Everyone, stay calm and man your posts.
Don't let anyone in.
Yes, Mr. Consigliere.
You cannot go here.
-Please go down.
-We're sorry.
All right.
Hello, my dear guests from Sangcheon-gu.
We appreciate your patience.
I will be the host of today's event.
I am Babel's helper,
Vice Chairman Jang Han-seo.
Finally, today…
we'll be giving out the present
we've promised you.
It's…
your chance to win units at our tower!
That's right.
All right. Sir.
I'm Jang Han-seok.
For Babel Tower to be built,
the help
from the head of our district office,
-the police chief,
-Yes.
Assemblyman Kim…
I'm Kim Uk-hyeon.
…and other VIP guests from Sangcheon-gu
were absolutely necessary.
And of course,
Babel ought to return the favor.
-Enjoy yourselves tonight.
-I forgot to ask.
-I hope you win a unit.
-Will we get a lot?
-Shut up.
-Congratulations.
All right. Let the party begin now!
This is for the 92nd floor of Building A.
And the floor goes to…
Congratulations, Mr. Kim Uk-hyeon.
-I did it!
-Gosh.
I won!
-He's loving it.
These men are unbelievable.
-Don't be so disappointed.
-They're shameless.
-It's the penthouse at Building B.
-How could they be so shameless?
People can't control their greed.
-Only thing bigger than greed…
-It overlooks Han River,
-a park, and the city.
-is just bigger greed.
It has the perfect view.
Yes, Ms. District Chief.
Tax exemption on construction!
Tax exemption on construction? My gosh!
-Police Chief.
-I'll dispatch more men
-when you demolish the plaza.
-More cops for demolition!
That's pretty big. Anyone else?
Ms. District Chief.
All the private businesses
related to Sangcheon-gu
will have to do business with Babel Group.
-Sold! Yes!
-I won?
The penthouse goes to the District Chief!
-This way. My gosh.
-Goodness.
Good for you. I'm so jealous.
Hold on. How may I help you?
All right. He's the last winner
of today's event.
It's the 52nd floor.
Congratulations, Mr. Ham Seung-un.
Congratulations.
You seem so happy.
We have given out all the units now.
We will now cut the cake
to celebrate our event today.
District Chief, Mr. Kim,
and the police chief,
please come forward now.
Who's that?
What is it?
You can't come in here.
Hey!
-Hey, you…
-Who is that?
What's going on?
This is a bomb!
A bomb?
I'm being threatened now.
Ms. Choi, you must help me.
-Do you know him?
-No.
I don't know him.
How dare you!
If you scream
or try to run away,
this bomb will go off.
-Everyone, don't move.
-Wait!
Who the heck put you up to this?
I don't know, either.
I was abducted and have been getting
instructions via text.
And…
What's that?
-What?
-What is that?
There's a bomb here.
-That must be the bomb.
-My gosh.
I'm just doing as instructed.
You must do as I tell you to from now on
if you want to stop this bomb.
That's a nice start.
He's ready.
Make them believe that it's a real bomb.
Yes, sir. Don't worry.
After this,
you guys will be free.
Yes, sir.
Make Choi Myung-hee pay
for humiliating you guys
when you worked for her.
Oh, right. After the party,
I'll pay you right away.
Leave Korea by the end of today.
Everyone here
must annul the agreement you signed
with the Babel Group
and cut all ties
with Chairman Jang Han-seok.
Swear it on your knees.
What? We have to kneel?
Vincenzo?
Hey, you! You are trying
to fool us, aren't you?
There's no bomb! This is Korea!
Now! The bomb can go off any minute.
Something looks off.
Right. Yes. That's right. That looks fake.
I think they're just portable chargers.
If this is one of your fake stunts,
you'd better stop it now!
For those of you who refuse to believe me,
I will show you this.
In five seconds,
the miniature model
of Babel Tower will explode.
-What?
-What's he talking about?
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
-Help!
-Open up!
-Open the door.
-Open it.
-Help!
-Open it now!
-Open the door.
-Open it now.
Is he really dead?
Remember what I told you?
That when it was time,
I would let you throw the hunting dogs
that killed your dad
to the lion's den.
I was going to let you push the button,
but I figured I should do it.
I see.
Did you change your mind?
No, I didn't.
They should pay for what they did.
RESTRICTED NUMBER
The bomb in the cake
can wipe out the entire room.
-What?
-What's going on?
-Oh, no.
-What should we do?
-Look.
-What?
-Open the door now.
What? I didn't get one.
-What's this about?
-The bomb…
It can wipe out the room!
Wait.
Sir.
I think that's a real bomb.
For your information,
I've been recording you from the start.
SEND TEXT MESSAGE
DO AS THE DEAD MAN SAID RIGHT NOW
MESSAGE SENT
RESTRICTED NUMBER
Do as the dead man said right now.
Find your agreement,
chew it, and swallow it.
And after identifying yourself,
swear on your knees.
-The agreement!
-Where is the agreement?
The agreement…
Spit it out. Gosh, come on!
I, the Chief of Sangcheon Police Station
-will cut ties with Babel Group.
-Hey. I need my agreement.
I swear it to God!
I, Assemblyman Kim Uk-hyeon,
will cut ties with Babel Group. I swear.
Be quiet!
You be quiet!
Do you want us all to die?
I, the head of Sangcheon-gu
district office,
swear to cut all ties with Babel Group!
It'll be easy to nullify
the approval of Babel Tower now.
I swear!
The timer stopped! It stopped!
-Oh, my.
-Gosh.
Hey.
Good job.
Use your influence
to make it seem as
the party today never happened.
You may all leave.
Let's get out.
We must get out of here now!
-Let's go.
-I'm leaving now.
-Hurry up!
-Move!
-Hurry.
-Let's get out of here now.
-We should get out now.
-Hurry up.
Sir, this cake… The bomb…
I think something bad is going to happen.
Shut up.
The timer!
The timer is back on.
-The timer.
-Mr. Jang!
The timer!
Thanks.
We won even without moving our bishop.
Getting what we wanted
was easier than I thought.
The second party
will be much grander
and crazier than this.
I'll handle the second party.
-He's out.
-That's him, right? Okay.
Sir!
Hello. Salute.
Mr. Han.
What brings you here this early?
I wanted to see you, sir.
I hope he's doing well.
His approval ratings went up,
so he's in a good mood.
Well, you are the kingmaker.
He must feel
as if he has an entire army by his side.
You came to see me after a long time
just to flatter me?
Seriously. What's this about?
Well…
would it be possible to meet with him?
Why?
There's something
I would like to talk to him about.
Why don't we meet after the election?
We can't be too careful
before the election.
It's regarding the Guillotine file.
-Ms. Choi!
-Jeez!
Stay here.
You scared me.
You punk.
Where have you been all this time?
I'm sorry.
I should have come to see you sooner.
Have you and Hwang-gyu
been working for Vincenzo
after betraying me?
We were in a bit of a situation.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me.
I can't believe this jerk.
How dare you come here
after what you've done?
I was out of my mind, ma'am.
Please help me.
You have to help me.
Get up.
People are watching. Get up.
You and I need to have a very long talk.
If you want to live,
you better tell me everything.
Yes, ma'am.
Get in. Let's go get a drink.
-Ms. Hong?
-Where?
Come on.
Darn it.
You come here.
You're not good at hockey.
The tip I gave you was useful, right?
You were able to ruin the party
thanks to me.
It wasn't bad.
Gosh. Can't you just give me credit
when I deserve it?
What should I do next?
There might be a shift
in the power dynamic at Babel.
What change?
Power is bound to shift after a big loss.
When that happens, tell me.
We'll meet here.
Sure. I can do that.
Let me ask you one thing.
You won't kill me, right?
I know. I know you won't,
but I just feel anxious for some reason.
As long as you don't
drop honorifics.
I'm not even wearing my helmet.
How could you do that?
How could you do that, sir?
You scared me, sir.
Have you been studying?
My eyes are killing me these days
because I read so many books, sir.
Your best source of protection
isn't a gun or a sword.
It's your brain. Don't forget that.
Bye.
Wait.
What is it?
What?
What did you say?
Thank you, sir.
You made me realize
what an idiot I had been.
Gosh.
Vincenzo.
Thank you.
My gosh. You are hurt badly.
Spare me.
What did you say?
Do you still think I'm a pushover?
Bury him.
GEUMGA PLAZA
Now, you should all go out and fight.
Can you teach us how?
We're not that knowledgeable in that area.
First of all, you must use
your enemy's weaknesses as weapons.
You must be brazen.
Forget about manners.
Treat them as if they killed your parents
and as if you'd never see them again.
Never back down from your demands.
Don't let their social status
intimidate you.
Be strong
and act like you're their equal.
BLUE SKY, SANGCHEON
Are you a goat or what,
munching on a piece of paper?
Why are you doing this to me?
You know the on-site inspection
for the construction of Babel Tower
had issues, right?
CONSTRUCTION PERMIT REEXAMINATION
You should reevaluate.
And based on that,
you must reexamine
the approval process as well.
I, the Chief of Sangcheon Police Station
-will cut ties with Babel Group.
-It wasn't some speech contest.
Didn't your throat bleed afterwards?
What is it that you want?
Firstly…
dispatch cops around Geumga Plaza
around the clock
and reinforce security.
Secondly…
give the tenants of Geumga Plaza
Courageous Citizen Awards.
I won!
He's loving it!
What do you want me to do?
Nullify all the redevelopment plans
around Geumga Plaza.
Get all the bribes you took
from Babel Group
and donate it to Geumga Orphanage
unless you want to be humiliated.
GO, GO, BABEL TOWER HELPERS
"Babel Tower Helpers"?
What kind of name is that
for a group of lowlife thugs?
It sounds like a name for a yogurt.
You'll end up in a freezer next time,
you assholes.
Remember my face.
I'm Geumga-dong's nutria.
What?
They say they are reexamining
the approval process.
What is Wusang doing now?
Darn it.
I just gave them hell,
so they'll come up with a plan.
-Sit down.
-Okay.
When I was shot in the ear,
the moment you shot me
flashed through my head.
Why are you bringing that up?
I'm just saying I'm glad to be alive.
Remember what I told you?
It's just us two now.
We're brothers.
A long time ago,
your mother asked me for a favor.
She asked me to be nice to you
and look after you
even if I don't give you anything.
She did?
Yes.
But you're pretty smart now.
I want to give you something.
No.
No, sir.
I'm happy as it is.
Babel Bio.
Take over and launch it.
You wanted to run a subsidiary.
Sir, I'm not cut out to do
such an important job.
And Babel Bio… Gosh, no.
-This makes no sense.
-Try it, you punk.
If you do a good job,
I'll leave Babel Pharmaceuticals
or Chemicals to you.
If you insist…
I will do my best.
Come here.
Be an innovative entrepreneur
like Elizabeth Holmes.
I'll back you up.
Yes, sir. I will do my best. Thank you.
Do a good job.
CANDIDATE 3, PARK SEUNG-JUN
LEADER OF THE NEW ERA, PARK SEUNG-JUN!
I said there's no problem.
Yes. Just proceed with that.
God, this jerk.
-It's been a while, Mr. Han.
-Hello, sir!
Gosh, "sir"? Don't be so formal.
So Wusang is doing well, right?
Gosh, I'm a nobody, but you
even remember my firm. Thank you.
-Sit down.
-Okay.
You danced tango by yourself
at the company dinner party.
You sang "Dead Drunk," right?
How can I forget such a quirky junior?
My gosh. I must have been
out of my mind. I did that again?
Oh, no. I'm so embarrassed.
Anyway, tell me about the Guillotine file.
-What's that about?
-Okay.
It's been a crazy couple of weeks, sir.
Mr. Cassano. Ms. Hong.
I analyzed
everything related to Babel
from the Guillotine file.
Do you know the keyword
that comes up the most?
Bribery or sex scandals?
-Wrong.
-It's got to be real estate.
-How did you know?
-We're in Korea.
That's right. To be precise, it's IUDC.
"IUDC"?
What's IUDC?
"Innovative Urban
Development Corporation."
They develop and provide real estate
for building new cities.
You get it, right?
NAME: PARK SEUNG-JUN
SPECIALTY: REAL-ESTATE
As expected, the main industry
of the Korean cartels is real estate.
IUDC is involved in every process.
Babel and IUDC were already
in on it together.
The insiders and the people
who colluded with them
must've made a fortune
by buying land around Babel Tower.
You know, the forerunner of
the presidential election, Park Seung-jun?
He acquired some land around the plaza
using certain loopholes five years ago.
His brother-in-law is the head of IUDC.
-His brother-in-law?
-Yes.
Maybe we shouldn't have opened
the Guillotine file.
It's the root of our frustration.
We keep finding more corruption…
when Babel is our only target.
Where are you going?
It's about time
that we deal with our greed.
I'll be back.
Mr. Cassano. What now?
Let me get this straight.
The Guillotine File and 1.5 trillion won's
worth of gold bars are buried
underneath the Babel Tower?
Yes, sir.
And an Italian Mafia lawyer
has control over it?
Yes. That's right.
-Mr. Kim.
-Yes.
Is this a plot for a cartoon?
Well…
it's been confirmed that
his information is somewhat credible.
I see.
Be it politics or life,
there's no such thing as too much drama.
All of these matters
are very serious, sir.
The Babel Tower…
The Guillotine file…
Everything…
Every one of them
is like a sword that's aimed at my neck.
Sir.
I will be your unbreakable shield.
What should I do
to have to use that shield?
Sir…
I'm sorry to ask you this again,
but you have to move.
I'll find you another place.
What is this about now?
You were lucky the other day.
If there's another explosion,
it'll be dangerous to stay here.
So I urge you to move as soon as possible.
Jeokha and I will follow
the words of Buddha
and stay here as we have been.
-Mr. Cassano.
-Yes?
I've wanted to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
NANYAK TEMPLE
Are you sure you'll be able to
build Babel Tower?
I heard that they are reexamining it now.
From my experience, it will be difficult
to build a tower there
with hiccups like this.
The media are already starting
to suspect something is going on.
Everyone.
It's a minor error with the document.
It's nothing.
Wusang will take care of it in a few days.
Why don't we all have a drink now?
And it's nothing big,
but check the present I prepared for you.
Gosh.
Come on, everyone.
I'm sure you know how this works. Come on.
Those annoying bastards.
Can't we just get rid of them?
We cannot lose the people
who were at the meeting today.
Keep reassuring them.
They might not be my bishops,
but they'll make good pawns.
Gosh, you're amazing.
You're making a chess analogy.
That's so cool.
Where are you?
Everyone left, right?
I'm bringing a guest with me.
A guest?
It's nice to finally meet you,
Mr. Vincenzo Cassano.
Hello, sir.
I'm Hong Cha-young.
Oh, my. I've also heard a lot about you.
Hello, sir. Nice to meet you.
I'm the paralegal here.
I see. Hi.
Mr. An, we need to talk.
So…
Excuse me.
You have the Guillotine file?
Ms. Hong, Mr. Nam, you, and I
are the only people who know about it.
Don't tell a soul.
Then, we should head over to my agency--
No. Not yet.
We have a job to do with this file.
Right.
We can destroy everyone with the file.
That's right.
-You trust me, right?
-Totally.
Then, let me use the Guillotine file
the way I see fit.
After I'm done, I'll hand it over to you.
I think I know how you'll use it.
I trust you, Mr. Consigliere.
Thank you.
But I have a favor to ask.
Go ahead.
Hey!
So let me get this straight.
The Guillotine file is
locked in the basement of Geumga Plaza?
And Vincenzo Cassano is the only person
who can take it out?
-Yes.
-You punk.
You have been working
with Vincenzo Cassano for a reason!
I will give you the Guillotine file soon.
-Okay.
-Then, use the file
to beat Directors Kim Hui-won
and Park Jae-beom and become
the president of our agency.
-The president?
-Yes.
Hui-won. Jae-beom.
So tell me. What should I do to help?
All right.
The best floors at Babel Tower.
I'll start with
the 120th and 121st floors.
What is it?
First, infiltrate Babel Group
and find their dirty laundry.
To take out the Guillotine file safely,
we must bring down Babel.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I had an urgent meeting.
I'm Director Tae Jong-gu of
the International Organized Crime Bureau
at the International Security
Intelligence Service.
And secondly,
make sure no one comes after Mr. Cassano.
Well, about Vincenzo Cassano…
You should never go after him.
-Pardon?
-He fled to Korea
with evidence of corruption
pertaining to not only Italian,
but also British and French politicians.
I didn't know he was that important.
He is.
He set up a system
that makes the evidence spread
all over the dark web when he dies.
And if an international scandal breaks
because of us,
our government will have to
take responsibility.
They are having a blast.
Their cheeks must hurt smiling like that.
Look at that gold toad.
I bet it doesn't even cost much.
I wore a spy cam
to the first meeting as well,
but it didn't record anything.
Gi-seok did a bad job
explaining how to use it.
Mr. Tae confused "on" with "off."
Anyway, thanks to you, I think
I might be taking up a bigger position.
Actually, I didn't do much.
He deserves more credit.
Hello, sir.
What? Yeong-un?
What are you doing here?
Well, to answer that,
it'd be a long story.
Right? I knew it.
Mr. Cho here is one of our agents, right?
I knew it. He looked familiar.
You should catch up with your colleagues.
Which year did you join?
No. Gi-seok started working
before you did.
-You look so young.
-Attention.
-At ease.
-Gosh.
"Gosh"? Focus.
That's enough.
How…
That makes no sense, Mr. Kim.
So…
Mr. Han will be the chief prosecutor
of Namdongbu Prosecution Service?
And Ms. Choi will just be
the CEO of Wusang?
You might not know this about me,
but I was in the Investigative Division
at the Supreme Prosecutors' Office.
You got kicked out
because you always lost!
I did?
And about the Italian Mafia lawyer.
Don't go after him.
He's much bigger than you think.
He's on an international scale.
We just met, but you're quite bossy.
Don't butt in our business.
Mr. Park is being generous,
giving you a second chance.
I don't need his generosity.
For a boy who poisoned
his own father to death,
you sure talk back a lot.
What?
You didn't think I'd know?
And one more thing.
I think it'll be better if Han-seok
takes a break for the time being
and Han-seo runs the company again.
What?
You mean me?
Sir.
I know that this is coming from Mr. Park,
but you cannot tell a private company--
Choi Myung-hee. Jang Han-seok.
Don't you want a smooth transition
with the new administration?
And you, Myung-hee.
If you talk back to me again,
I'll take it that you're challenging
a presidential candidate
with an approval rating of 38.7 percent.
Congratulations, Chairman Jang.
-One more time.
-Chairman Jang.
Am I really the chairman again?
Do you know how hard I worked
to make this happen?
Mr. Han…
No.
Seung-hyuk.
Gosh. I'm the Chief Prosecutor now.
Chief Prosecutor Han.
I feel like I'm dreaming right now.
I cannot believe this is happening.
What was his name?
Jang Joon-woo?
-Vincenzo.
The Interpol will come to arrest him
within 24 hours.
The Interpol?
-The International police.
-I know that.
Right.
You know…
I called the boss of the Cassano Family
and set a trap.
I asked him to find a crime
that we could frame Vincenzo with.
And I reported it to the Interpol.
Gosh.
Stop it.
Why didn't I think of that?
Let's get rid of the person who is
most likely to obtain the Guillotine file.
And you, my dear chairman,
will demolish Geumga Plaza
and obtain the Guillotine file.
But what if Vincenzo comes back
after some time?
No. Gosh. That's impossible.
Now, you can just focus on leading Babel.
I, the chief prosecutor,
will back you up on other things.
Jang Han-seok…
Let's see
Who comes out on top
INAUGURATION OF CHIEF PROSECUTOR
HAN SEUNG-HYUK
Please say a few words
as the new chief prosecutor.
I am infinitely honored to have the chance
to serve the people of our country.
As the guardian of the Constitution
and democracy,
I will dedicate my life
so that the principle of justice
can be the driving force
of our legal system.
How do you plan to clear up
suspicion about
-colluding with Babel?
-Just like that?
How did he become
the chief prosecutor overnight?
Jang Han-seok doesn't have
enough influence to make that happen.
They must've used someone much higher up
to ward off our attacks.
-Yes. I am
-Then, could it be…
well-aware of the public's mistrust
and concerns.
Then why didn't Jang Han-seo
report this to us? This is huge.
Right. He's slacking off already.
He's not slacking off just yet.
Go ahead.
We need to talk. It's urgent.
They're being led to area A.
POLICE
What do you need to discuss?
This is driving me crazy.
You see…
Something's been bothering me.
What is it? Tell me.
I wish I didn't have to make
so many choices in life.
It's been fun.
But this is…
where our fun ends.
You're just like your brother.
I didn't expect much from you anyway.
A gun?
Don't shoot. I have a gun, too.
Your betrayal means
that you've accomplished your goal.
If either of us starts shooting,
we might both die.
So let's both lower our guns. Okay?
I don't plan on doing that.
Actually, my gun isn't loaded. It's empty.
I see.
Shoot your head first then.
No. I said it's empty.
I'm pointing it at you to scare you.
Shoot first.
Vincenzo Cassano.
We're from the Interpol.
We came here to arrest you
and repatriate you.
Drop your gun, Vincenzo Cassano.
SPECIAL THANKS TO LEE GEUNG-YOUNG