♪Remembering the old days in a trance♪
♪We are destined to fight together♪
♪The past has gone but the memory lasts♪
♪Our happiness and sorrow
in the good old days♪
♪The journey is difficult,
through the crowds, to the end of time♪
♪I'm brave and undefeatable♪
♪The sky has become dark
and the birds have returned home♪
♪Breaking all obstacles
and reaching the peak above the clouds♪
♪Watching the thin plumes of smoke
and the beautiful scenery♪
♪Working together,
overcoming all difficulties♪
♪I will be known as the fearless one♪
=Douluo Continent=
=Episode 40=
Complete this final battle
and overcome yourself!
Fight for Shi Lan Ke School!
Fight for our future!
For...
Fight!
The Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke will prevail!
Victory!
Chief.
Before the match starts,
would you like to give a speech?
They have the arena now.
The others should not interfere.
The match begins!
Are you ready?
Come on!
Is this how you treat your teammates?
Teammates?
There are only three people
on Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team.
The rule is seven versus seven.
That's why we took these useless people in.
Now,
the final really begins.
Don't worry.
I will defeat you guys first
and get rid of your Support Branch.
Stick to the plan.
Jiubao Boosts!
First, Strength! Second, Speed!
Go!
Attack the two of them separately.
And you are here to stall me.
Should I praise your bravery,
or should I mock your stupidity?
Do you really think
you alone can stop me?
We'll see.
Purple Demon Eye!
You can follow my speed.
Formidable defense.
My Martial Soul is Flame Lord.
It's more than Flame Branch!
He is both Flame and Earth Branch!
Take him down as soon as you can.
Then go to help Tang San.
Yes!
Second Soul Skill, Charm!
What happened to your eyes?
That didn't look like your Soul Skill.
You are complaining as you can't hit me?
You are harder to deal with than I imagined.
However,
that's it.
Do you know
why I haven't shown
my Soul Rings so far?
You really have Five Soul Rings.
I've been hiding them,
so my opponent wouldn't lose his will to fight
after seeing my Five Soul Rings.
That would make my victory so boring.
You are overthinking it.
I have full confidence.
Great.
My Martial Soul is Moon Blade.
I have Five Soul Rings,
but I have no Soul Skill.
When each of my Soul Rings lights up,
there's only one function.
It makes my Moon Blade
quicker and sharper.
More powerful!
You managed to catch up.
Your Blue Silver Plant is strong.
But that's it.
With Double Soul Rings,
I can defeat you.
You can change the Moon Blade's trajectory?
Ma Hong Jun!
His reaction was so quick!
You're an interesting Support Branch.
His Martial Soul is flawless.
He's an all-rounder.
We'll blind his sight!
Martial Soul Fusion Skill.
Watch out!
If you fall off the stage,
stay there!
So Ma Hong Jun was a decoy too.
You guys sought to focus your power
to take down Yan.
I'm surprised
that you could hold on until now.
Teleport!
It would be deadly if we get hit by the blade.
You won't lose with me around.
Without his help,
I would have lost.
But it wasn't successful.
I don't want his help.
Consider I lost.
Martial Soul Hall's Battle Team
only had me at first.
They are only complimentary.
He is the last man standing.
We'll give our full support to Tang San.
It's been a long time
since someone of my age
made me light up my Third Soul Ring!
Watch out!
Ou Si Ke, Ning Rong Rong,
get off the stage!
We can still fight!
You will die if you stay!
Leave now.
Let's go.
I'll cut off your arms first.
Soul Bone?
You have some tricks.
This is the end.
Who can stop my Moon Blade?
I'm afraid Tang San will never
live in peace again.
Twin Martial Souls, Hao Tian Hammer?
You are quite a genius.
It's a pity
that in this generation of Soul Masters,
I'm the strongest in Douluo Continent!
You've been preparing this right from the start.
Facing a strong opponent,
I can only beat him by surprise!
Go to die!
I'm here for you.
Shi Lan Ke School wins.
Hong Jun?
Come.
Get up.
Zhu Qing, how are you?
We won.
Brother Dai, are you all right?
Are you okay?
We won.
The Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke!
A surprising miracle.
The champion
of Douluo Soul Master School Tournament
turns out to be
a little obscure school.
This is intriguing.
The Seven Devils of Shi Lan Ke!
Shi Lan Ke School wins.
The award ceremony begins now.
Let's welcome the Chief.
Hold on.
How did you find me?
You concealed
your Martial Soul's space-folding ability,
but I knew it all along.
Kill her now!
They are all Grand Soul Land Masters.
Impossible.
All the Grand Soul Land Masters
are subdued at once.
When your ability about space reaches its limit,
you will get to have the ability about time.
Your Reversal Skill is not bad.
How is this possible?
You are also a Grand Soul Land Master.
When did you become so powerful?
My old friend.
The Chief's power
is beyond your imagination.
Do you know why I want to kill her?
The former Chief Qian Xun Ji
was murdered by her!
Do you admit your crime?
Yes!
I killed Qian Xun Ji.
Do you have a problem with that?
If it weren't for Chief Qian Xun Ji,
I wouldn't have had the right
to become a Soul Master.
I've endured for many years,
so as to avenge him.
It's a pity.
All these Grand Soul Land Masters
are no match for you.
We can join hands.
There is no way
that Bi Bi Dong can't be defeated.
Why should I work with you?
Didn't you listen to me just now?
She killed the former chief!
The former chief is dead.
What matters is the person
in charge of Martial Soul Hall.
And the future we have!
You don't seem surprised at all.
You knew the truth a long time ago?
I knew about Qian Xun Ji's death.
I also knew you had planned
to assassinate the chief.
She knew everything.
You knew it?
I know you contacted the King of Star Forest.
I know you assassinated my direct disciple.
I also know
that you founded Cang Hui School
and contacted other Grand Soul Land Masters.
I know all your plan
very well!
I didn't expose you
because I wanted you to gather
all the people
who had wanted to kill me!
In that case,
I can finish them off once and for all.
To be honest,
there are fewer than I expected.
So what if you know everything?
My Martial Soul has no physical form.
You can never catch me.
If I have a chance,
I can take you down anytime.
I believe
I will succeed one day.
My Martial Soul.
Why can't I use it?
The side story is over.
Let's move on.
Shi Lan Ke is still the champion.
Grand Chrysanthemum Master.
Reward the Soul Masters with Soul Bones,
except for Wu.
Wu!
Tang San!
What do you want?
This contest
is meant for all Soul Masters.
That means
only Soul Masters are qualified to join.
She is a Soul Master.
You really have no idea.
What?
She is not a Soul Master.
She is not even a human.
She is a Soul Beast.
A Century Millennium Soul Beast
can turn into a human form.
Look at the Flexible Bunny at her back.
That is her true form.
Wu...
I'm sorry.
I didn't tell you.
Soul Masters and Soul Beasts cannot co-exist.
After I gained my human form,
I left the Star Forest,
so I could learn about Martial Soul
and find the way to advance.
My goal was to bring harmony
to humans and Soul Beasts.
The rivalry between
Soul Masters and Soul Beasts
can never be resolved.
However,
my collection
doesn't have a Century Millennium Soul Beast
in human form.
This is none of your business.
Shi Lan Ke School is still the champion.
Release her!
Did you not hear me?
She is not a human.
She is a Soul Beast!
So what if she is a human
or a Soul Beast?
All I know is
that she is my sister!
She is also my lover!
No matter what will happen in the future,
I will always be with her!
I will always protect her.
I won't abandon her!
I don't care who she is,
or whether she is your lover!
She is merely a Soul Beast!
Do you want
to go against Martial Soul Hall
only for a Soul Beast?
If you want to kill her,
step over my dead body!
Fine.
No.
Let him go!
I'll go with you.
You can have my life.
I beg you.
Let him go.
No one can touch my son!
Father!
Tang Hao.
You are finally here.
I didn't expect
that you killed Qian Xun Ji.
If you hadn't wounded him back then,
I wouldn't have had the chance.
I could wound Qian Xun Ji back then.
I can do the same to you.
Compared with what he used to be,
I am much more powerful.
Tang San.
Look closely.
This is the true form of Hao Tian Hammer.
Wu, you are safe.
Brother.
Brother!
He will be fine.
When he wakes up,
he can get treated.
Thank you.
Bi Bi Dong was right.
She is much stronger than Qian Xun Ji.
She is indeed the Greatest Soul Master
in Douluo Continent.
But you fended off Bi Bi Dong.
Do you know?
From the standpoint of a Soul Master,
I should catch you.
A Century Millennium Soul Beast
will bring great benefits
to a Soul Master.
Perhaps one day,
Tang San might need you.
If I can help him,
I am willing to accept my fate.
You resemble her a lot.
Who?
Tang San's mother.
Do you know why I saved you?
It's because of Tang San.
It's because of Tang San's mother.
Because...
she was just like you.
She was a Century Millennium Soul Beast.
Tang San
is the child of a Soul Master
and a Soul Beast.
After the Century Millennium Soul Beast
turns into the human form,
it will no longer be a Soul Beast.
It is a human.
Tang San
is the child of a normal couple.
Martial Soul Hall chased after you
for this reason.
It's one of the reasons.
Soul Masters and Soul Beasts
are irreconcilable.
It's extremely hard
for them to get together.
Have you considered these things?
Are you ready?
I will be prepared.
But you are still too weak.
If you stay with Tang San,
you two
will get into greater danger.
I don't want you two to suffer the same fate as ours.
You should leave him.
Stay away from him until you've become stronger,
strong enough to be fearless.
I understand.
I'll leave.
My Martial Soul is a bunny.
And you?
Blue Silver Plant.
What a coincidence!
What is it?
Doesn't a bunny nibble on grass?
Tang San!
Don't be afraid.
I'm going to save you.
Let go!
Without bloodshed and pain,
how can I walk my own path?
Tang San!
If one day
I am being chased by countless Soul Masters,
I hope you can forget me.
Let them
step over my dead body.
Otherwise,
no one can hurt you.
You can't die.
I will die.
No, I won't allow it.
No way!
It can't be interrupted.
You must wake up, Tang San.
You will wake up.
(Tang San, you really wake up.)
(What is truth? What is the self? Wake up, Tang San.)
♪The trees are shining
against the light♪
♪Like a stubborn young man♪
♪The far destination is
where I'm heading♪
♪My bags are packed but I'm in a daze♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪
♪Because♪
♪Because I want to
become the unique one♪
♪Stumble my way into the next sunset♪
♪So I will hope for brighter fireworks♪
♪The dream of faith♪
♪Will always prevail♪
♪And become a beautiful galaxy♪
♪There's no need to comfort me♪
♪Going separate ways
and we'll all endure suffering♪
♪Don't hide,
take it as another challenge for us♪
♪A stubborn choice and a burning heart♪
♪Take the bumpy road under the storm♪
♪Not afraid to
break ordinary rules in life♪