(BOTH GRUNTING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Bo-Katan
sent me to talk to you.
I hope it's about him.
Grogu and I
can feel each other's thoughts.
THE MANDALORIAN: Grogu?
AHSOKA TANO: Yes. That's his name.
THE MANDALORIAN: I've been quested
to bring him to his kind.
I must deliver him to a Jedi.
Go to the planet Tython.
There, you will find
the ancient ruins of a Temple
that has a strong connection to the Force.
Place Grogu on the seeing stone
at the top of the mountain.
If he reaches out through the Force,
there's a chance a Jedi may sense
his presence and come searching for him.
OFFICER: Moff Gideon.
The tracking beacon
has been installed on the Razor Crest.
Does he still have the asset?
Our source confirmed it.
(BABBLING)
-Grogu.
-(COOS)
(CHUCKLES)
(COOS)
Grogu?
(CHUCKLES)
Give me the ball.
(GRUNTS)
Grogu, give me the ball.
Come on.
(GRUNTS)
(GROGU SQUEALS)
Okay, here we go.
(COOS)
You can have it, just like before.
Grogu, come on. You can have it.
Come on.
-(COOING)
-Dank farrik!
Hey, no. I'm not mad at you.
You did good.
I just...
When the nice lady said
you had training, I just...
(SIGHS)
-You're very special, kid.
-(COOS)
We're gonna find that place you belong
and they're gonna take
real good care of you.
(BABBLES)
(BEEPING)
This is Tython.
That's where we're gonna
try and find you a Jedi.
(GROGU GRUNTS)
But you have to agree to go with them
if they want you to. Understand?
Plus, I can't train you.
You're too powerful.
Don't you wanna learn
more of that Jedi stuff?
(GRUNTS)
I agreed to take you back
to your own kind,
so that's what I need to do.
You understand, right?
Looks like that's the magic rock
I'm supposed to take you to down there.
(GRUNTS)
(COOS)
Sorry, buddy. I can't land on the top.
Too small.
We're gonna have to travel
the last stretch with the windows down.
(GROGU WHOOPING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Well, I guess this is it.
Does this look Jedi to you?
I guess you sit right here.
Okay. Here we go.
(COOS)
This is the seeing stone,
are you seeing anything?
(COOS)
Or are they supposed to see you?
Maybe there's
some kind of control or something.
(COOS)
(SIGHS)
Oh, come on, kid.
Ahsoka told me all I had to do
was get you here and you'd do the rest.
(COOS)
(SHIP APPROACHING)
Time's up, kid. We gotta get out of here.
We don't have time for this.
We got to get... (GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hey! Snap out of it, kid!
We got to get out of here!
I'll see if I can buy you some time.
Can you please hurry up?
MAN: I've been tracking you, Mandalorian.
THE MANDALORIAN: Are you Jedi?
Or are you after the Child?
I'm here for the armor.
If you want my armor,
you'll have to peel it off my dead body.
I don't want your armor.
I want my armor that you got
from Cobb Vanth back on Tatooine.
It belongs to me.
Are you Mandalorian?
I'm a simple man
making his way through the galaxy.
Like my father before me.
Did you take the Creed?
I give my allegiance to no one.
The beskar belongs to the Mandalorians.
It was looted from us during the Purge.
The armor was my father's.
Now it's mine.
What's to stop me
from dropping you right where you stand?
Because I have
a sharpshooter up on that ridge
with a locked scope that will unload
by the time my body hits the ground.
I'm the one wearing beskar.
As soon as I see that muzzle flash,
you're both dead.
I didn't mean she was going to shoot you.
My friend's locked onto that
little companion of yours up on the henge.
SNIPER: And if you remember,
I don't miss.
THE MANDALORIAN: Fennec?
FENNEC SHAND: You have a keen ear, Mando.
THE MANDALORIAN: You point
that gun away from the kid
or I'll drop you both where you stand.
Let's all put down
our weapons, have a chat.
There's no need for bloodshed.
Tell her to drop the gun.
After you put down the jetpack.
Same time.
Stand down.
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
You look like you've just seen a ghost.
You were dead.
MAN: She was left for dead
on the sands of Tatooine, as was I.
But fate sometimes steps in
to rescue the wretched.
In my case, Boba Fett was that fate.
And I am now in his service.
I want my armor back.
THE MANDALORIAN: It goes against
the Mandalorian Creed.
The armor was given
to my father, Jango, by your forebears.
In exchange, I guarantee the safety
of the Child, as well as your own.
The bounty on your little friend
has risen significantly.
You can buy ten suits of armor
for the price on its head.
I'd say we're offering a fair deal
under the circumstances.
(SHIP APPROACHING)
THE MANDALORIAN: (GRUNTS) Time to go, kid!
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
STORMTROOPER 1: Go, go!
Advance and take... (GROANS)
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
(GROANS)
Up top. Move out!
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
STORMTROOPER 2: Flank left and from above.
Sir, there's too much fire!
-Flank them, you idiot!
-(GROANS)
Up top! Get up there!
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(STORMTROOPER GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
(BOBA FETT GRUNTS)
(STORMTROOPER GROANING)
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING) One, two...
(YELLING)
-STORMTROOPER: Get back! Get...
-(ALL SCREAM)
(SCREAMS)
Go, go!
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-STORMTROOPER: No.
-(GRUNTS)
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(STORMTROOPER GROANS)
(GROANING)
STORMTROOPER: Flank left. Move out!
THE MANDALORIAN: That's it, kid.
We got to get out of here!
(GRUNTING)
(YELPS)
Okay, I'm gonna protect you.
Just stay there. I'll be back soon.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
STORMTROOPER: Give yourselves up!
We don't want you, we want the Child.
(ALL GROANING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Okay, let's move in.
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
This isn't looking good.
THE MANDALORIAN: I've seen worse.
You can get out of here.
I owe you from last time.
We have a deal.
(BEEPING)
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
(GROANING)
(STORMTROOPERS CONTINUE GROANING)
STORMTROOPER: Back to the ship!
Back to the ship!
Go! Go!
THE MANDALORIAN: Nice shot.
BOBA FETT: I was aiming for the other one.
Better get to your ship.
THE MANDALORIAN: The kid!
OFFICER: Direct hit.
Have the dark troopers been engaged?
Momentarily.
(WHIMPERS)
FENNEC SHAND: They've got the baby.
Don't let them get away!
BOBA FETT: Affirmative.
I have a lock.
THE MANDALORIAN: Stop him.
I don't want the Child hurt.
FENNEC SHAND: Abort pursuit. Disengage.
Do not harm the Child.
BOBA FETT: Copy. I'll do a loose follow,
see where they're headed.
-They're back.
-FENNEC SHAND: Who?
BOBA FETT: The Empire.
They're back.
FENNEC SHAND: That can't be.
The Outer Rim is under
the jurisdiction of the New Republic.
BOBA FETT: This isn't a spice dream.
I can see the Imperial cruiser
with my own eyes.
Heading down.
(FENNEC SHAND SIGHS)
THE MANDALORIAN:
This is all that survived.
Beskar.
I want you to take a look at something.
My chain code has been encoded
in this armor for 25 years.
You see, this is me. Boba Fett.
This is my father, Jango Fett.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Your father was a foundling.
Yes.
He even fought
in the Mandalorian Civil Wars.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Then that armor belongs to you.
I appreciate its return.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Then our deal is complete.
Not quite.
THE MANDALORIAN: How so?
We agreed in exchange
for the return of my armor,
we will ensure the safety of the Child.
THE MANDALORIAN: The Child's gone.
Until he is returned to you safely,
we are in your debt.
THE MANDALORIAN: Cara Dune,
Marshal of the New Republic.
I heard rumors you might have gone legit.
I wouldn't go that far.
I need your help.
Name it.
I need you to locate someone
in the prison registry.
Let's see what I can do.
THE MANDALORIAN: Ex-Imperial sharpshooter,
last name Mayfeld.
Apprehended near the Dilestri system
on a derelict prison ship.
CARA: Migs Mayfeld.
Serving 50 years
in the Karthon Chop Fields
for springing a prisoner himself.
Accessory to the death
of a New Republic officer.
Huh. Sounds like a real piece of work.
What do you want with him?
I need to spring him to help me
locate Moff Gideon's light cruiser.
You know how I feel about the Empire.
But these stripes...
mean there are rules I need to follow.
They have the kid.
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
(BOTH GROANING)
(CHOKING)
-STORMTROOPER: Set to stun.
-Wait.
(BOTH GROANING)
(BOTH YELPING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(STORMTROOPER GROANING)
You've gotten very good with that.
But it makes you oh-so sleepy.
Have you ever seen one of these?
From years past?
(CHUCKLING) Oh, uh-uh-uh.
You're not ready to play with such things.
Liable to put an eye out
with one of these.
Looks like you could use
a nice, long sleep.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Put it in shackles.
When we come out of hyperspace,
send an encrypted message to Dr. Pershing.
Let him know we have got our donor.
Yes, sir.