THE MANDALORIAN:
You have something I want.
BO-KATAN:
I can lead you to one of their kind.
But first,
we need your help on our mission.
The Darksaber. Does he have it?
-(GRUNTS)
-(CRACKLING)
DR. PERSHING: We have exhausted
our initial supply of blood.
I highly doubt we'll find a donor
with a higher M-count, though.
AHSOKA TANO: Go to the planet Tython.
You will find
the ancient ruins of a temple
that has a strong connection to the Force.
Place Grogu on the seeing stone
at the top of the mountain.
If he reaches out through the Force,
there's a chance a Jedi may sense
his presence and come searching for him.
Then again, there aren't many Jedi left.
(WHIMPERS)
THE MANDALORIAN:
You may think you have some idea
of what you are in possession of,
but you do not.
It means more to me
than you will ever know.
What's going on? Who are they?
I suggest you shut your mouth,
this isn't your laboratory.
(BEEPS)
They hit us with an ion cannon.
Avionics are down.
Comms are down!
BOBA FETT: Lower your shields,
disengage all transponders,
prepare for boarding.
They're pirates. Shouldn't we fight?
I don't have a death wish, do you?
(SHIP APPROACHING)
(LOUD THUD)
Before you make a mistake,
this is Dr. Pershing.
We've met. Is the kid alive?
Yes. He's on the cruiser. (GASPS)
Stay back, Dropper.
Easy, pal. Okay?
I'm not with him.
We can work something out.
(GROANS)
Drop your weapon.
No. No, you listen to me.
This is a top-tier target
of the New Republic.
This is a clone engineer.
And if they find out that
he's dead because of you,
you're gonna wish you never left Alderaan.
I saw the tear.
You wanna know what else I saw?
I saw your planet destroyed.
I was on the Death Star.
Which one?
(PILOT LAUGHS MOCKINGLY)
You think you're funny?
Do you know how many millions
were killed on those bases?
Drop your blaster.
As the galaxy cheered?
Last chance.
Destroying your planet was a small price
to pay to rid the galaxy of terrorism.
-(DR. PERSHING SCREAMING)
-(THUDS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
THE MANDALORIAN: I need your help.
Not all Mandalorians are bounty hunters.
Some of us serve a higher purpose.
They took the Child.
Who?
Moff Gideon.
You'll never find him.
BOBA FETT: We don't need these two.
Let's get outta here.
You are not a Mandalorian.
BOBA FETT: Never said I was.
I didn't know sidekicks
were allowed to talk.
(BOBA FETT CHUCKLES)
Well, if that isn't the Quacta
calling the Stifling slimy.
Easy there, little one.
You'll be talking through
the window of a bacta tank.
All right, easy. Save it for the Imps.
We have his coordinates.
You can bring me to Moff Gideon?
The Moff has a light cruiser.
It could be helpful in your effort
to regain Mandalore.
BOBA FETT:
You gotta be kidding me. Mandalore?
The Empire turned that planet to glass.
You are a disgrace to your armor.
BOBA FETT:
This armor belonged to my father.
Don't you mean your donor?
Careful, princess.
You are a clone.
I've heard your voice thousands of times.
Mine might be the last one you hear.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(STRAINING)
Enough! Both of you!
If we had shown
half that spine to the Empire
we would've never lost our planet.
We will help you.
In exchange, we will keep that ship
to retake Mandalore.
If you should manage to finish your quest,
I would have you reconsider
joining our efforts.
Mandalorians have been in exile
from our home world for far too long.
-Fair enough.
-One more thing.
Gideon has a weapon
that once belonged to me.
It is an ancient weapon
that can cut through anything.
Almost anything.
It cannot cut through pure beskar.
I will kill the Moff
and retake what is rightfully mine.
With the Darksaber restored to me,
Mandalore will finally be within reach.
Help me rescue the Child
and you can have whatever you want.
He is my only priority.
This is Moff Gideon's
Imperial light cruiser.
In the old days,
it would carry a crew of several hundred.
Now it operates with
a tiny fraction of that.
-Your assessment is misleading.
-CARA: Oh, great.
An objective opinion.
This isn't subterfuge. I assure you.
Let him speak.
There's a garrison
of dark troopers on board.
They abducted the Child.
How many troopers do they have
armed in those suits?
These are third-generation design.
They are no longer suits.
The human inside was the final weakness
to be solved.
They're droids.
Where are they bivouacked?
DR. PERSHING:
They're held in cold storage
in this cargo bay.
They draw too much power
to be kept at ready.
FENNEC SHAND: How long to power up?
A few minutes, perhaps.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Where is the Child being held?
This is the brig.
He's being held here under armed guard.
Very well. We split into two parties.
THE MANDALORIAN:
I go alone.
Fine.
Phase one,
Lambda shuttle issues a distress call.
Two, we emergency land
at the mouth of the fighter launch tube,
cutting off any potential interceptors.
Koska, Fennec, Dune and myself disembark
with maximum initiative.
Once we've neutralized the launch bay,
we make our way through these tandem decks
in a penetration maneuver.
-THE MANDALORIAN: And me?
-We'll be misdirection.
Once we draw a crowd,
you slip through the shadows, get the kid.
Those dark troopers
are gonna be a real skank in the scud pie.
Their bay is on the way to the brig.
Can he make it there before they deploy?
It's possible.
Here. Take his code cylinder
and seal off their holding bay.
Anyone else, we can handle.
We'll meet at the bridge.
BO-KATAN:
Moff Gideon is mine.
Got it?
He's ex-ISB.
He's got a lot of information.
I need him alive.
I don't care what happens to him
as long as he surrenders to me.
Prepare to exit jump space.
BO-KATAN: Copy that.
Get the hell out of there
as soon as they clear us to dock.
And your shots
have to look convincing.
Power up those shields, princess.
I'll put on a good show.
Watch out for those deck cannons.
Don't worry about me.
Just be careful in there.
Exiting hyperspace in three, two, one...
(ALARM BEEPING)
BO-KATAN: This is Lambda shuttle,
Two-Seven-Four-Three.
Requesting emergency docking.
Repeat,
requesting emergency docking.
We are under attack.
Copy, Lambda shuttle. Request received.
Launch TIE fighters.
Stay clear of launch tube.
Deploying fighter squadron.
Request denied! Please clear launch tube
until fighters deploy!
BO-KATAN: Negative! Negative!
We are under attack!
Clear launch tube immediately.
OPERATOR: (ON PA)
We have incoming at two-eight-four-six.
Hangar control, stand down!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
(ALARM BEEPING)
Hang on!
STORMTROOPER 1: Look out.
STORMTROOPER 2: Clear the launch tube!
STORMTROOPER 3: What are you doing?
-Get that thing out of here!
-(BOTH GROAN)
STORMTROOPER 4: Move in! Blast 'em!
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
Fire!
STORMTROOPER 5: Wait, stop!
Activate the dark troopers.
KOSKA REEVES: All clear.
BO-KATAN: A little too clear.
Keep your eyes open.
(BOTH GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
STORMTROOPER 1: Freeze! Drop your weapons!
Sector four, hold your position.
STORMTROOPER 2:
We're heading to the bridge now.
(GAS HISSING)
(DARK TROOPERS POWERING UP)
Cover me.
BO-KATAN: We got your back.
-(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
-(FENNEC SHAND GRUNTS)
STORMTROOPER: There they are!
(DROID SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(GUN BUZZES)
My gun's jammed!
I got you.
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
Thanks.
(ALARM BLARING)
No. No!
(GROANS)
(SCREAMING)
(CHOKING)
(GROANING)
-(GAS HISSING)
-(YELPS)
(GROANS)
(DARK TROOPERS POUNDING ON DOOR)
(THE MANDALORIAN YELPS)
(GRUNTING)
(DARK TROOPER SCREAMS)
(STRUGGLING) Dank farrik!
Son of a mudscuffer!
BO-KATAN: Are you sure
you don't need any help?
-(CARA GRUNTS)
-(GUN POWERS UP)
(SIGHS) I think that did it. Excuse me.
STORMTROOPER: Hostiles! Stop!
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
KOSKA REEVES: Weapons system disarmed.
Where's Gideon?
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
(NECK SNAPS)
(COOING)
Drop the blaster.
Slowly.
Now kick it over to me.
Very nice.
Give me the kid.
The kid is just fine where he is.
Mesmerizing, isn't it?
Used to belong to Bo-Katan.
Yes. I know you've been traveling
with Bo-Katan.
A friendly piece of advice,
assume that I know everything.
Like the fact that your wrist launcher
has fired its one and only salvo.
Where is this going?
This is where it's going.
I'm guessing that Bo-Katan
and her boarding party
have arrived at the bridge,
seeking me or, more accurately, this.
But I'm not there.
And I imagine that they've killed
everyone on the bridge,
being the murderous savages that they are.
And now, they're beginning to panic.
You see, she wants this.
Do you know why?
Because it brings power.
Whoever wields this sword...
has the right to lay claim
to the Mandalorian throne.
You keep it. I just want the kid.
Very well.
I've already got what I want from him.
His blood.
All I wanted was to study his blood.
This Child is extremely gifted...
and has been blessed with rare properties
that have the potential
to bring order back to the galaxy.
I see your bond with him.
Take him,
but you will leave my ship immediately
and we will go our separate ways.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
You're sparing my life?
Well, this should be interesting.
(DOOR CLOSES)
What happened?
CARA: He brought him in alive,
that's what happened.
And now the New Republic's
gonna have to double the payment.
That's not what she's talking about.
Why don't you kill him now and take it?
It's yours now.
THE MANDALORIAN: What is?
The Darksaber. It belongs to you.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Now... it belongs to her.
She can't take it.
It must be won in battle.
In order for her
to wield the Darksaber again,
she would need to defeat you in combat.
I yield. It's yours.
Oh, no.
(CHUCKLING)
It doesn't work that way.
The Darksaber doesn't have power.
The story does.
Without that blade,
she's a pretender to the throne.
He's right.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Come on, just take it.
(ALARM BEEPING)
Well, perhaps she'll get
another crack at it.
FENNEC SHAND:
The ray shields have been breached.
We're being boarded.
How many life forms?
None.
You're about to face off
with the dark troopers.
You had your hands full with one.
Let's see how you do
against a platoon.
BO-KATAN: They're headed this way.
Don't worry, kid.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Seal the blast doors!
They're here.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
You have an impressive
fire team protecting you.
But I think we all know,
after a valiant stand,
everyone in this room will be dead...
but me...
and the Child.
(ALARM BEEPING)
An X-wing.
One X-wing? Great. We're saved.
Incoming craft, identify yourself.
(COOING)
Why did they stop?
(LASERS FIRING)
BO-KATAN: A Jedi?
-(LASERS FIRING)
-(LIGHTSABER HUMMING)
(BO-KATAN GROANING)
(THUDS)
Drop it!
(LIGHTSABER WHOOSHING)
(ELEVATOR BEEPING)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(WHINES)
THE MANDALORIAN: Open the doors.
I said, open the doors.
Are you crazy?
THE MANDALORIAN:
Are you a Jedi?
I am.
Come, little one.
(COOING)
He doesn't want to go with you.
He wants your permission.
He is strong with the Force,
but talent without training is nothing.
I will give my life
to protect the Child...
but he will not be safe
until he masters his abilities.
THE MANDALORIAN: Hey, go on.
That's who you belong with.
He's one of your kind.
I'll see you again.
I promise.
(COOING)
All right, pal.
It's time to go.
(WHINES)
Don't be afraid.
(GROGU COOING)
(R2-D2 BEEPING)
(GROGU CONTINUES COOING)
(COOS)
(BEEPING)
May the Force be with you.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(SPEAKING HUTTESE)
-(GUNFIRE)
-(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(SCREAMS)
(SPEAKING HUTTESE)
(PANICKED CHATTERING)
(GUARDS GROAN)
(WHIMPERING)
(BIB FORTUNA LAUGHING
AND SPEAKING HUTTESE)
(BIB FORTUNA LAUGHING)
(GROANS)
(BODY THUDS)