ARMORER:
Have you ever removed your helmet?
THE MANDALORIAN: No.
ARMORER:
Has it ever been removed by others?
THE MANDALORIAN: Never.
ARMORER: This is the Way.
MANDALORIAN GROUP: This is the Way.
A Mandalorian covert is close.
The contact will lead you to them.
However, no hyperdrive.
Moving fast is the only thing
keeping me safe.
CARSON: Razor Crest, stand down.
We will fire.
-THE MANDALORIAN: Hold on.
-(FROG LADY SCREAMS)
(GRUNTS)
THE MANDALORIAN: We're lucky if we
get off this frozen tomb with our lives.
Go, go, go! Back to the ship!
(GROWLS)
(GROANS)
Am I under arrest?
CARSON: Technically, you should be.
But these are trying times.
I'm gonna repair the cockpit enough
for us to limp to Trask.
There's nothing I can do
about the main hull's integrity,
so we're gonna have to get cozy
in the cockpit.
It's gonna be a long ride.
(ALL SNORING)
(ALARM BEEPING)
(THE MANDALORIAN GASPS)
(COOS)
(FROG LADY GRUNTS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Looks like we made it.
Get ready for landing.
Dank farrik!
The landing array isn't responding.
Without the guidance system,
it'll be a manual re-entry.
It might get choppy.
Once we're through the atmosphere,
there should be enough fuel to slow down.
If we don't burn to a crisp.
(ALARM BLARING)
(GRUNTING)
Come up here. I need your hands!
(FROG LADY GRUNTS)
This lever needs to stay back.
Can you do that?
(GRUNTS IN AGREEMENT)
Keep it steady. Here we go.
FLIGHT CONTROL:
Razor Crest, this is Trask flight control.
Please reduce your speed to port protocol.
I'm trying my best here.
Engage reverse thrusters. Brace!
Hold on.
FLIGHT CONTROL: Razor Crest, do you copy?
You have to reduce speed.
Almost there, almost there.
FLIGHT CONTROL: Razor Crest, do you copy?
Razor Crest, you're coming in too fast.
You have to re...
Here we go. Nice and easy.
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
(FROG LADY YELPING)
DOCK WORKER:
So, how can I help you?
THE MANDALORIAN:
Can you fix it?
Fix it? Nah.
But I can make it fly.
Do what you can.
I'll fuel it up.
If it still holds fuel.
(SHOUTING IN FROG)
(FROG MAN SHOUTING IN FROG)
(SQUEALING)
(BOTH SPEAKING FROG)
(WHINING)
I know you're hungry.
-We'll get you something to eat.
-(WHIMPERS)
-(SPEAKING FROG)
-You're welcome.
I was told you could lead me
to others of my kind.
(CONTINUES SPEAKING FROG)
The inn? Over there?
(SPEAKING FROG)
(FROG MAN SPEAKING FROG)
(BOTH SPEAKING FROG)
THE MANDALORIAN: Thank you.
Have a seat over there.
What can I get you?
Nothing for me.
A bowl of chowder for my friend.
These seats are scarce, buddy.
Everyone seated needs to eat.
I can buy something else.
Information.
Have you seen others that look like me?
(COOS)
Others with beskar have been through here.
THE MANDALORIAN: Who can take me to them?
SERVER:
I know someone who might help.
There's a Mandalorian.
Looking for others of his kind.
He was askin' about passage...
He's wearing beskar.
(SQUEALING)
Don't play with your food.
Hmm.
You seek others of your kind?
-Have you seen them?
-Aye.
I can bring you to them.
(CHUCKLING)
-Where?
-Only a few hours' sail.
It'll cost you, though.
QUARREN'S BROTHER 1: Coming around.
QUARREN'S BROTHER 2: Try the other side.
QUARREN'S BROTHER 3:
Oh, give me! Yeah, thank you.
QUARREN'S BROTHER 2:
Over the side!
You ever see a mamacore eat?
Quite a sight.
Child might take an interest.
(COOS)
You should take a look.
Come on over here.
Get a good view. Let the kid see.
-All right, close enough.
-(QUARREN GRUNTING)
QUARREN: There we go.
She must be hungry.
Oftentimes we'll feed her
in the early morning,
but we missed that
'cause we were goin' out of port!
No!
(THE CHILD WHIMPERS)
Lock it up! Go, go! Now! Go!
The beskar is ours!
(QUARREN LAUGHING)
(THE MANDALORIAN COUGHING)
-Drown him!
-(ALL LAUGHING)
-Get him! Get him! There we go!
-Drown him.
(THE MANDALORIAN COUGHS)
-We're rich, brothers!
-(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
-(GASPING)
-He didn't sink! Finish him!
Keep him down!
(THE MANDALORIAN COUGHING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
-(THE MANDALORIAN GASPING)
-(ALL GRUNTING)
(COUGHING)
(THE MANDALORIAN
CONTINUES COUGHING)
Take my hand.
There's a creature.
-It has the Child.
-On it!
(THE MANDALORIAN
CONTINUES COUGHING)
THE MANDALORIAN:
The Child. Help the Child.
BO-KATAN:
Don't worry, brother. We've got this.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(MAMACORE SCREECHING)
-(SCREECHING STOPS)
-(PANTING)
(KOSKA REEVES GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
KOSKA REEVES:
Here you go, little one.
(THE MANDALORIAN BREATHING HEAVILY)
Thank you.
I've been searching for more of our kind.
BO-KATAN:
Well, lucky we found you first.
I've been quested to deliver this Child.
I was hoping that...
Where did you get that armor?
This armor has been in my family
for three generations.
You do not cover your face.
You are not Mandalorian.
-He's one of them.
-Dank farrik.
One of what?
I am Bo-Katan of Clan Kryze.
I was born on Mandalore
and fought in the Purge.
I am the last of my line.
And you are a Child of the Watch.
The Watch?
Children of the Watch
are a cult of religious zealots
that broke away from Mandalorian society.
Their goal was to re-establish
the ancient way.
THE MANDALORIAN:
There is only one way.
The Way of the Mandalore.
(BO-KATAN SIGHS)
QUARREN: Hey!
You...
You killed my brother.
Let me pass.
(QUARREN CHUCKLES)
I don't you think you understand.
You killed my brother
and now I'm gonna kill your pet.
(WHIMPERS)
BO-KATAN:
He didn't kill your brother.
I did.
Can we at least buy you a drink?
Trask is a black market port.
They're staging weapons
that have been bought and sold
with the plunders of our planet.
We're seizing those weapons
and using them to retake our home world.
Once we've done that,
we'll seat a new Mandalore on the throne.
That planet is cursed.
Anyone who goes there dies.
Once the Empire knew
they couldn't control it,
they made sure no one else could either.
BO-KATAN:
Don't believe everything you hear.
Our enemies wanna separate us.
But Mandalorians are stronger together.
That's not part of my plan.
I've been quested
with returning this Child to the Jedi.
-What do you know of the Jedi?
-THE MANDALORIAN: Nothing.
I was hoping you would help me by Creed.
(COOS)
I can lead you to one of their kind.
But first,
we need your help on our mission.
Mission?
BO-KATAN:
You see that Imperial Gozanti freighter?
It's being loaded with weapons
as we speak.
According to the port's manifest,
it's scheduled to depart at first light.
So we stow away?
We've been hitting 'em pretty hard.
They scan for life forms as a precaution
before pushing back.
THE MANDALORIAN:
If you wanna do this with four,
you're gonna need the element of surprise.
Exactly.
The freighter will maintain trawling speed
while inside the shipping lanes
and then ascend in orbit.
We'll jet up when they're cruising
in atmosphere.
The tower won't allow them to climb
until they've left the port's airspace.
Troopers?
A squad at most.
And they couldn't hit
the side of a bantha.
Something's come up.
-Can I leave him with you for a bit?
-(SPEAKING FROG)
You are gonna stay here,
so I want you to be respectful.
And mind your manners.
You know what I'm talking about.
(BOTH SPEAKING FROG)
Thanks.
(THE CHILD COOING)
I'll be back for him.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(STORMTROOPERS SCREAMING)
Pirates.
(ALARM BLARING)
Pirates again.
(GROANS AND SCREAMS)
Guard that hall.
-Seal the hatch.
-Yes, sir.
STORMTROOPER: A breach in security.
Check the exterior door.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(STORMTROOPER SCREAMING)
What's going on?
How many of them are there?
STORMTROOPER: At least ten, maybe more.
Sir, there are only four life forms.
Wait. They're Mandalorian!
We've... (GROANS)
They're headed to the cargo bay.
How long until we clear the atmosphere
and can make the jump to hyperspace?
We can't climb until we leave
the harbor zone, sir.
Climb now.
Climb now!
(ENGINES ACCELERATING)
STORMTROOPER:
Look. Over there. Stop them!
(STORMTROOPERS SCREAMING)
STORMTROOPER: Go, go, go!
What's happening?
SECURITY OFFICER:
The intruders are heading your way.
Just hold them off
until we can make the jump to hyperspace
and rendezvous with the fleet.
Copy.
We need to hold them off until
we can make the jump to hyperspace.
(STORMTROOPERS GROANING)
-Close the doors.
-STORMTROOPER: Sir?
Close the doors!
-Which one?
-All of them! All of them!
Close all of them! Close all the doors!
(SCREAMING)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
We have them trapped, sir.
Trapped them where?
In the cargo control area.
-Where?
-In the cargo control area!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALARM BLARING)
Come in.
Do you copy?
I copy.
Thanks for packing up all this gear
so nicely.
Imagine what a division of us can do
when we get our hands on
what's inside these shiny little boxes.
CAPTAIN: If you think
you're going to escape
with those weapons,
you are sadly mistaken.
Even if you've managed to jettison
a few of those crates,
we will comb the entire area
until you are hunted down and killed.
Oh, we're not jettisoning anything.
We're taking the entire ship.
What?
Put some tea on. We'll be up in a minute.
THE MANDALORIAN:
This is more than I signed up for.
There is something I need,
if I am to rule Mandalore.
Something that was once mine.
They know where it is and soon, so will I.
Regardless, we are taking the ship
for the battles ahead.
I got you your weapons.
I have to return to my ship
with the foundling.
If you want my help finding the Jedi,
you will help me take this ship.
You're changing the terms of the deal.
This is the Way.
MOFF GIDEON: What is it, Captain?
-Another pirate hijacking.
-Were you able to eliminate them?
No. We need backup immediately.
Are these the same "pirates"
that have attacked our other vessels?
They appear to be, sir.
How far have they gotten?
They've breached the cargo hold
and taken everything but the bridge.
We require immediate backup.
If they've taken that much of the ship,
I'm afraid that's no longer an option.
You know what to do.
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
Long live the Empire.
(SECURITY OFFICERS GROAN)
(BO-KATAN GRUNTS)
BO-KATAN: They're taking the ship down.
Let's move!
-There's the bridge. Come on!
-STORMTROOPER: Blast 'em!
BO-KATAN: How many troopers?
AXE WOVES: Six to ten.
Two with heavy repeating blasters.
KOSKA REEVES: We're losing altitude fast.
-We need to move now.
-AXE WOVES: They have too much firepower!
KOSKA REEVES:
Still dropping. Ten thousand.
AXE WOVES:
We won't make it to the bridge!
KOSKA REEVES: Nine thousand.
Eight thousand.
Seven thousand.
THE MANDALORIAN: Cover me.
(GRUNTING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Come on!
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(BOTH STRAINING)
BO-KATAN: Where is it?
CAPTAIN: Where's what?
BO-KATAN: The Dark saber. Does he have it?
If you're asking, you already know.
THE MANDALORIAN: Easy. Easy.
(BOTH PANTING)
I'll let you live.
But you will take me to him.
You might let me live,
but he won't.
-(GRUNTS)
-(CRACKLING)
-BO-KATAN: No!
-(THUDS)
KOSKA REEVES: We have to go.
He sent a distress signal.
BO-KATAN:
Clear the atmosphere and prepare to jump.
Are you sure you won't join us?
THE MANDALORIAN:
There's something I need to do.
BO-KATAN: The offer stands
if you change your mind.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Where can I find the Jedi?
Take the foundling to the city of Calodan
on the forest planet of Corvus.
There you will find Ahsoka Tano.
Tell her you were sent by Bo-Katan.
And thank you.
Your bravery will not be forgotten.
This is the Way.
-(BABY FROG CHIRPING)
-(COOING)
(PARENTS SPEAKING FROG)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
THE MANDALORIAN:
Thank you for watching him.
Okay, kid.
Come on. It's time to go.
-(WHINING)
-Let go. Come on, kid.
Congratulations.
-(FROG MAN SPEAKING FROG)
-(THE CHILD WHINING)
THE MANDALORIAN: No, I have enough pets.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
THE MANDALORIAN:
I gave you a thousand credits,
this was the best you could do?
Mon Calamari.
(COOING)
Unbelievable.
(SHIP POWERING UP)
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTS)
(COOING)
(SQUEALS)
(HISSING)
(GIGGLING)
I finally know where I'm taking you.
But it's gonna be a bumpy ride.