ARMORER: When one chooses to walk
the Way of the Mandalore,
you are both hunter and prey.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
GREEF KARGA: There is one job.
THE MANDALORIAN: Underworld?
How uncharacteristic
of one of your reputation.
Is it not the Code of the Guild
that these events are now forgotten?
FENNEC SHAND: A Mandalorian
shot up the Guild on Nevarro,
took some high value target
and went rogue.
THE MANDALORIAN: Traveling with me,
that's no life for a kid.
-CARA: They'll keep coming.
-(COOS)
KUIIL: None will be free
until the old ways are gone forever.
MOFF GIDEON: You have something I want.
ARMORER: This is the one
you hunted, then saved?
THE MANDALORIAN: Its species
can move objects with its mind.
ARMORER: The songs of eons past tell
of battles between Mandalore The Great,
and an order of sorcerers called Jedi.
By Creed, it is in your care.
-You must reunite it with its own kind.
-THE MANDALORIAN: I was a foundling.
The Mandalorians raised me
in the Fighting Corps.
I was treated as one of their own.
-Did you do this?
-No!
THE MANDALORIAN: Did any survive?
ARMORER: We knew what could happen
if we left the covert.
Our secrecy is our survival.
Take care of this little one.
This is the Way.
(JAWAS GASP)
(CREATURES GROWLING)
(WHIMPERS)
I'm here to see Gor Koresh.
(COOS)
Enjoy the fights.
(DOOR OPENS)
(SPECTATORS SHOUTING)
(SPECTATORS CHEERING)
(SHOUTING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
SPECTATORS: Oh!
(SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
You know this is no place for a child.
THE MANDALORIAN: Wherever I go, he goes.
(CHUCKLES) So I've heard.
I've been quested
to bring him to his kind.
If I can locate other Mandalorians,
they can help guide me.
I'm told you know where to find them.
It's uncouth to talk business immediately.
Just enjoy the entertainment.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(COOS)
Bah! My Gamorrean's not doing well.
Kill him! Finish him!
SPECTATORS: Oh!
Do you gamble, Mando?
Not when it can be avoided.
(CHUCKLES) Well, I'll bet you
the information you seek
that this Gamorrean's going to die
within the next minute and a half.
And all you have to put up in exchange
is your shiny beskar armor.
I'm prepared
to pay you for the information.
I'm not leaving my fate up to chance.
Nor am I.
(GROANS)
(PANICKED CHATTERING)
(CHUCKLES) Thank you for coming to me.
Normally, I have to seek out remnants
of you Mandalorians in your hidden hives
to harvest your
precious shiny shells. (CHUCKLES)
Beskar's value continues to rise.
I've grown quite fond of it.
Give it to me now
or I will peel it off your corpse.
THE MANDALORIAN: Tell me
where the Mandalorians are
and I'll walk outta here
without killing you.
I thought you said
you weren't a gambler...
I'm not.
(THUGS GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(YELPS)
(GROANS) All right, stop, stop!
I'll tell you where he is.
(GOR KORESH GRUNTS)
But you must promise
that you won't kill me.
I promise you will not die by my hand.
Now, where is the Mandalorian you know of?
(GROANS) Tatooine.
THE MANDALORIAN: What?
The Mando I know of is on Tatooine.
THE MANDALORIAN: I've spent much time on
Tatooine. I never saw a Mandalorian there.
My information is good, I tell you.
The city of Mos Pelgo.
I swear it by the Gotra. (GROANS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Tatooine it is, then.
GOR KORESH: Wait, Mando!
You can't leave me like this.
Cut me down!
THE MANDALORIAN:
That wasn't part of the deal.
(GOR KORESH GRUNTING)
GOR KORESH: Wait, what are you doing?
Mando! I can pay! Mando! Mando!
(GOR KORESH SCREAMING)
(BLOWS)
(ALL CHITTERING)
All right. Hey, hey, hey!
Sorry, gang. Come on.
-You know he doesn't like droids.
-(CHITTERING)
THE MANDALORIAN:
May as well let them have at it.
The Crest needs a good once-over.
Oh! So he likes droids now.
Well, you heard him. Give it a once-over.
(CHUCKLES)
I guess a lot has changed
since you were last in Mos...
Oh! Thank the Force!
This little thing has had me worried sick.
-(THE CHILD COOS)
-Come here, you little womp rat.
-(CHUCKLES)
-(COOS)
Looks like it remembers me.
How much do you want for it?
Just kidding. But not really.
You know, if this thing
ever divides or buds,
-I will gladly pay for the offspring.
-(AIR HISSING)
Hey!
Oh, jeez!
Watch what you're doing up there.
He barely trusts your kind.
You want to give all droids a bad name?
Thank you!
THE MANDALORIAN: I'm here on business.
I need your help.
Oh, then, business, you shall have.
Care for me to watch this wrinkled critter
while you seek out adventure?
THE MANDALORIAN: I've been quested
to bring this one back to its kind.
Oh, wow. (CHUCKLES)
I can't help you there.
I've never seen any like it.
And trust me, I've seen
all shapes and sizes in this town.
THE MANDALORIAN: A Mandalorian Armorer
has set me on my path.
If I can locate another of my kind,
I can chart a path
through the network of coverts.
You've been the only Mando here for years
from what I can tell.
Where is Mos Pelgo?
I'm told there's one there.
Oh. Boy, I haven't heard
that name in a while.
THE MANDALORIAN:
It's not on any of the maps.
Because it was wiped out by bandits.
Once the Empire fell,
it was a free-for-all.
I didn't dare leave the city walls.
Still don't.
THE MANDALORIAN: Can you tell me
where it used to be?
Depends who's asking. You want to see it?
(LOUDLY) R-five!
Bring the map of Tatooine.
(BEEPS)
No, take your time. Seriously.
You just can't get good help anymore.
I don't even know who to complain to.
-Let's go, let's go.
-(BEEPS)
(SIGHS) Waiting. Okay.
This is a map of Tatooine before the war.
You got Mos Eisley, Mos Espa,
and up around this region, Mos Pelgo.
THE MANDALORIAN:
I don't see anything.
Well, it's there.
Or at least, it used to be.
Not much to speak of.
It's an old mining settlement.
They're going to see that
big hunk o' metal long before you land.
You still have that speeder bike?
Sure do.
It's a little rusty, but I got it.
(COOS)
Can I help you?
I'm looking for a Mandalorian.
Well, we don't get
many visitors in these parts.
Can you describe him?
Someone who looks like me.
Mmm...
You mean the Marshal?
THE MANDALORIAN: Your Marshal
wears Mandalorian armor?
(GRUNTS) See for yourself.
COBB VANTH: What brings
you here, stranger?
THE MANDALORIAN: I've been searching
for you for many parsecs.
COBB VANTH: Well, now, you found me.
Weequay, two snorts of spotchka.
Why don't you join me for a drink?
I've never met a real Mandalorian.
(CHUCKLES) Heard stories.
I know you're good at killing.
And probably none too happy
to see me wearing this hardware.
So...
I figure only one of us
walking out of here.
But then I see the little guy...
(COOS)
...and I think, maybe I pegged you wrong.
THE MANDALORIAN: Who are you?
I'm Cobb Vanth, Marshal of Mos Pelgo.
THE MANDALORIAN:
Where did you get the armor?
Bought it off some Jawas.
THE MANDALORIAN: Hand it over.
Look, pal, I'm sure you call the shots
where you come from,
but 'round here,
I'm the one tells folks what to do.
THE MANDALORIAN: Take it off.
Or I will.
We gonna do this in front o' the kid?
(COOS)
THE MANDALORIAN: He's seen worse.
Right here, then?
THE MANDALORIAN: Right here.
(SIGHS)
(RUMBLING)
(WHIMPERS)
(ALARM BLARING)
(SQUEAKING)
(LOWING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Maybe we can work something out.
(COOS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
That creature's
been terrorizing these parts
since long before
Mos Pelgo was established.
Thanks to this armor,
I've been able to protect this town
from bandits and Sand People.
They look to me to protect 'em.
But a krayt dragon
is too much for me to take on alone.
Help me kill it, I'll give you the armor.
Deal. I'll ride back to the ship,
blow it out of the sand from the sky,
use the bantha as bait.
Not so simple.
The ship passes above,
it senses the vibrations,
stays underground.
But I know where it lives.
How far?
Not far.
COBB VANTH: You don't
understand what it was like.
The town was on its last legs.
It started after we got news
of the Death Star blowing up.
The second one, that is.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
The Empire was pullin' outta Tatooine.
There was blaster fire over Mos Eisley.
The occupation was over.
We didn't even have time to celebrate.
That very night,
the Mining Collective moved in.
Power hates a vacuum and
Mos Pelgo became a slave camp overnight.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
-Hey, you okay?
-(GROANING)
Come on, let's get you outta here.
Let's go!
Go! Go! Go! Go!
(PANTING)
I lit out.
Took what I could from the invaders.
Grabbed a camtono.
I had no idea
it was full of silicax crystals.
I guess every once in a while,
both suns shine on a womp rat's tail.
I wandered for days.
No food, no water.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
And then...
I was saved.
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
(ALL SPEAKING JAWAESE)
COBB VANTH:
The Jawas wanted the crystals.
They offered their finest in exchange.
(SIGHS)
And my treasure bought me
more than a full waterskin.
It bought my freedom.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(BOTH GROAN)
AGENT 1: Get down!
AGENT 2: Go, go!
AGENT 3: Come on!
AGENT 4: Go! Go! Go! Go!
(DISTANT GROWLING)
(WHIMPERS)
(DISTANT GROWLS ECHOING)
(GROWLING)
(SNARLING)
(ALL SNARLING)
(SHOUTING IN TUSKEN)
(ECHOING)
COBB VANTH: (IN ENGLISH)
What the hell you doin'?
(THE MANDALORIAN SPEAKING TUSKEN)
(GROWLING HAPPILY)
(ALL SPEAKING TUSKEN)
(IN ENGLISH) Hey, partner,
you want to tell me what's going on?
THE MANDALORIAN: They want to
kill the krayt dragon, too.
(ALL SPEAKING TUSKEN)
(ALL CONTINUE SPEAKING TUSKEN)
-(GROWLS)
-(COOS)
(ALL CONTINUE SPEAKING TUSKEN)
(IN ENGLISH)
What am I supposed to do with this?
You drink it.
It stinks.
Do you want their help?
Not if I have to drink this.
(SPEAKING TUSKEN)
THE MANDALORIAN: He says
your people steal their water
and now you insult them
by not drinking it.
(SPEAKING TUSKEN)
THE MANDALORIAN: They know
about Mos Pelgo.
They know how many Sand People you killed.
They raided our village.
I defended the town.
THE MANDALORIAN: Lower your voice.
-I knew this was a bad idea.
-THE MANDALORIAN: You're agitating them.
These monsters can't be reasoned with.
Sit back down
before I put a hole through ya!
I'm not going to say it...
(THE MANDALORIAN SPEAKING TUSKEN)
(IN ENGLISH)
What are you telling them?
THE MANDALORIAN:
Same thing I'm telling you.
If we fight amongst ourselves,
the monster will kill us all.
Now, how do we kill it?
(SPEAKING TUSKEN)
THE MANDALORIAN: They say
it lives in there. They say it sleeps.
It lives in an abandoned sarlacc pit.
COBB VANTH:
Lived on Tatooine my whole life.
There's no such thing
as an abandoned sarlacc pit.
THE MANDALORIAN:
There is if you eat the sarlacc.
They're laying out a bantha
to protect the settlement.
They've studied its digestion cycle
for generations.
They feed the dragon
to make it sleep longer.
Watch, the dragon will appear.
(SHOUTING IN TUSKEN)
(WHIMPERS)
(DRAGON GROWLING)
(RUMBLING)
(WHIMPERING)
THE MANDALORIAN: They might
be open to some fresh ideas.
(THE CHILD WHIMPERING)
(LOWING)
(ALL SPEAKING TUSKEN)
COBB VANTH: (IN ENGLISH)
What are the bones?
THE MANDALORIAN: That's the krayt dragon.
COBB VANTH: And those little rocks?
THE MANDALORIAN: That's us.
It's not to scale.
I think it is.
COBB VANTH: Can't be. That's too big.
(ALL SPEAKING TUSKEN)
THE MANDALORIAN: (IN ENGLISH)
It's to scale.
I've only seen its head and neck.
It's bigger'n I guessed.
Might be time to rethink our arrangement.
(ALL SPEAKING TUSKEN)
COBB VANTH: (IN ENGLISH)
That's more like it.
Where are they getting the reinforcements?
THE MANDALORIAN:
I volunteered your village.
COBB VANTH: They attacked us
less than a year ago.
Killed half a dozen of us
by the mining camp.
I'd say I took down
about twice as many Tuskens.
THE MANDALORIAN: The town respects you.
My guess is, they'll listen to reason.
I wouldn't be so sure.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
COBB VANTH:
This here is a Mandalorian.
You know what that means?
We've heard the stories.
Then you know
how good they are at killing.
Now, this one's got a problem.
I got a suit o' salvaged armor
and the Mandalorian creed says
it's his to take.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
But I've got a problem, too.
A krayt dragon has been peeling off
our pack animals,
and sometimes,
taking our mining haul with it.
It's just a matter of time
before it grows tired of banthas
and goes after a couple of you townsfolk,
or even, so help us, the school.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
As much as I've grown fond of the armor,
I'm even more fond of this town.
The Mandalorian is willing
to help us slay the leviathan
in exchange for returning the armor
to its ancestral owners.
Well, that settles it.
There's more.
We can't take on the krayt alone.
And the Sand People are willing to help.
(ALL CLAMORING)
They raid our mines!
They're monsters!
THE MANDALORIAN:
I've seen the size of that thing,
it will swallow your entire town
when the fancy hits it.
You're lucky Mos Pelgo
isn't a sand field already.
I know these people. They are brutal.
But so is the Dune Sea.
They've survived
for thousands of years in these sands
and they know the krayt dragon
better than anyone here.
They are raiders, it's true.
But they also keep their word.
We have struck a deal.
If we are willing to leave them
the carcass and its ichor,
they will stand by our side in battle
and vow never to raise
a blaster against this town
until one of you breaks the peace.
Think it'll work?
THE MANDALORIAN: It better.
Joining forces is their only hope.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Here. Grab this.
(MAN 1 GRUNTS)
Hey! What are you doin'?
That's an explosive.
Are you trying to blow the whole place up?
-(BANTHA GRUNTING)
-What? Is that what you want?
Take it easy. It was an accident, okay?
-What do you want to do?
-It was an accident.
MAN 2: Let's go.
MAN 3: It's not going to work out.
It's gonna be great.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(DRAGON SNORING)
What'd he say?
THE MANDALORIAN: He says it's sleeping.
If we listen carefully,
we can hear it breathing.
(SPEAKING TUSKEN)
(SIGHS)
THE MANDALORIAN: (IN ENGLISH)
Let's get to work.
-(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
-(BANTHA LOWING)
THE MANDALORIAN: The Tuskens say
the belly is the only weak spot,
so we have to hit it from below.
First, we bury the charges
at the opening of the cave.
Then, we wake it up.
We have to get it angry enough to charge.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Once it's far enough out
and the belly is above the explosives,
you hit the detonator.
(DEVICE POWERING UP)
JO: Careful, Marshal.
Thank you, Jo. And you stay safe, huh.
(TUSKEN RAIDERS YELLING)
(DRAGON GROWLING)
(TUSKEN RAIDER 1 SPEAKING TUSKEN)
(DRAGON CALLING)
(ROARING)
(TUSKEN RAIDER 2 YELLS)
(TUSKEN RAIDERS YELLING)
(TUSKEN RAIDER 1 SHOUTING IN TUSKEN)
(TUSKEN RAIDER 2 YELLS)
THE MANDALORIAN: Dank farrik,
it's going back in.
(TUSKEN RAIDERS SCREAMING)
(ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
THE MANDALORIAN: It's retreating.
-I'm going to hit it.
-No, wait.
We only have one shot.
We've gotta get it out.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Now?
THE MANDALORIAN: Not yet.
It's gotta come out further.
(ROARING)
(TUSKEN RAIDERS YELPING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
THE MANDALORIAN: Almost, almost.
-Now!
-(BEEPS)
-(ROARING)
-(PEOPLE YELPING)
(ALL GROANING)
I don't think it's dead.
THE MANDALORIAN: Me either.
(DRAGON ROARING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
It's picking us off like womp rats.
Let's get after it!
(COBB VANTH AND THE MANDALORIAN GRUNTING)
This ain't doing a thing.
THE MANDALORIAN: Just keep shooting.
(COBB VANTH PANTING)
(GROWLING)
THE MANDALORIAN: There he is.
(ALL SCREAMING)
(WHINES)
THE MANDALORIAN: I've got an idea.
Get its attention.
(SCREECHING)
COBB VANTH: I got its attention! Now what?
MAN 1: Run!
MAN 2: Go, go.
THE MANDALORIAN: You still have
that detonator?
COBB VANTH: Take it! What's the plan?
THE MANDALORIAN: Take care of the Child.
-What are you gonna do?
-I don't know, but wish me luck.
(COBB VANTH GRUNTS)
(DEVICES POWERING UP)
(LOWING)
No! No, no, no!
Hold on. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
(ROARING)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(WHINES)
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
(RUMBLING)
(ALL YELP)
(BEEPS)
(SCREECHING)
(PANTING)
(CHUCKLES)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Yeah!
THE MANDALORIAN: Sorry,
I didn't have time to explain.
No need.
This was well-earned.
It was my pleasure.
I hope our paths cross again.
THE MANDALORIAN: As do I.
Oh, and you tell your people
I wasn't the one that broke that.
(SPEAKING TUSKEN)
(TUSKEN RAIDERS CHEERING)