[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 12]
[70th anniversary of Nanze University]
What are you holding
in your hands, Lu Jing?
It's a toy.
Is it for Liang Chen?
[What? For me?]
I wish to take a photo with her
while holding this.
The box
looks a lot like someone I know.
Lu Jing, you're not wearing enough.
Don't you feel cold?
No.
After all,
I'm healthy and strong.
Joy dances in the song of youth.
This beautiful voice once filled
the halls of Nanze University.
It's been six years.
That beautiful voice
has once again come back to us.
Coming next, please welcome Liang Chen
performing her song,
"When I was 18".
Ms Liang.
That was a great performance.
This is for you.
Thanks.
Ms Liang, here you go.
Your...Your hands are hot.
That's because
my blood is boiling with passion.
Such beautiful origami flowers.
I wonder who that thoughtful person is.
Maybe someone who knows
you're allergic to pollen.
How was my performance?
Incredible.
The audience wouldn't stop clapping.
And you looked really cute
in that dress.
I'm glad.
But why did you drop the bouquet
when it was presented to you?
I...I need to go to the restroom.
What's wrong?
You keep going to the restroom.
Ms Liang.
Yes?
The temperature drops dramatically
at night. Don't catch a cold.
Thank you.
I'll get going then.
Did you bring a scarf when you leave home?
Lu Jing, the song Liang Chen
sang just now was nice.
Have you heard it before?
I have.
I regret I didn't find myself a boyfriend
when I was in the university.
Those two look good together.
Let's go.
Lu Jing.
Can you teach me
how to make the roses
you gave Liang Chen?
Lu Jing.
What were you saying?
I said,
can you teach me how to make the roses
you gave Liang Chen?
Sure.
I'll send you the tutorial video.
Given how smart you are,
you'll understand immediately.
Lu Jing.
Stop the car.
What's wrong?
Shan Shan.
Why are you here alone?
What should we do, Ms Liang?
Take her home first.
Shan Shan, where do you live?
The Greenland Residential Area.
This is me.
Thanks.
No problem.
Liang Chen.
Are you joining or not?
The show is going to start soon.
Hurry up.
Answer the call, Shan Shan.
Please welcome Liang Chen and Ma Shan Shan
with their song,
"The First Dance in Winter".
[Hi, the number you have dialled]
[is unreachable.]
[Please try again later.]
[Shan Shan.]
[Do our dreams]
[mean nothing to you?]
She looks totally different
on television.
Let's go.
Which one of you secretly
asked for resources anonymously
on the university's forum?
I got you.
You didn't even hide your IP address.
What resources? Show me.
Well...
I was just helping someone out.
Baby Da Yan wants Liu Mao Yan's
memes and pictures?
That isn't me.
Not me for sure.
Which lame guy shared this?
Jing.
Why did you ask for a man's picture?
I...
Can't I enjoy seeing a handsome man?
Look at me then.
Move.
Aren't I handsome?
Beautiful Soul charity stream
on Wednesday.
It's streaming next week?
But what have I been doing?
[Do you want a go tonight?]
[I still can't play.]
[Looks like you're severely wounded.]
[Let's play together again
after you've recovered.]
He's using his meme?
Could he have learnt who I am?
Whatever.
I need to save myself.
Yeah.
Secondary account registration successful.
Playing alone is not that hard.
After learning from Lu Jing for so long,
I can do it if I try.
What a coincidence, Ding.
Don't you think so?
I actually ran into Zhu Guang
who is picking you up.
If you need it,
I can pick you up at the airport.
I'd feel bad about that.
You won't charge me, will you?
Sun,
I don't think there's anyone
who is capable of making you pay.
Hey, how could you be so honest?
It's not that I'm stingy.
I'm just poor.
You're not stingy.
You helped me set off fireworks before.
He helped me set off fireworks before.
Because of what you've just said,
I'll share with you two
the local specialities I brought home.
What a coincidence, Lu Jing.
-You're back.
-Just a while ago.
Do you miss me?
Let's hang out together
if you're free tonight.
I'm not free. I need to study.
What a poser, you little kid.
Bye.
Childish.
Come.
Come. Have a seat.
Was that boy your friend?
He's my neighbour.
An expert in computer science.
By the way,
he is Liang Chen's coach
on Beautiful Soul.
But he'd be surprised to know
who his student is.
Jia Yun.
Don't you have a job today?
My job has been cancelled.
I'm here to get the clothes
I left at your place.
You're playing Beautiful Soul
with someone?
Carry on.
Why are you spacing out?
Nothing.
Let me show you.
This is the treasure of my home town.
I had to exchange it
with my bewitching face.
I heard that it's a very nourishing
organic food.
Forget it. Save it for yourself.
How ignorant.
What does that boy do?
You mean Lu Jing?
He's a university student.
Why? Did he catch your attention?
The world sure is running on pretty faces.
He's a university student.
Is there a problem?
No.
He is back, right?
Let's have a welcome party for you.
What do you want to eat?
Will you bring me whatever food I want?
Of course.
I want to eat the braised fish
and the beef stew with potatoes you make.
Okay.
Let's invite our friends.
Sure.
You, me, Orange, He,
and
Ma Shan Shan.
Okay. No problem.
I'll keep it.
Are you sure you don't want some?
Yes.
Looks like Lu Jing is offline.
My cleverness can't save
my uncoordinated hands.
What might he be doing?
He's good-looking, smart,
and his hands work perfectly.
Maybe
I should continue to team up with him.
It's for my job.
I'm too bad a player.
It's not because of him.
It's not that I want to
play the game with him.
I'm doing this for my job.
How dedicated I am.
He got mad because I didn't
go online for a few days?
That is impossible.
How can such a good-looking boy
get angry?
[Are you there, master?]
What is it? I was taking a bath.
[I need you to guide me.]
Is your hand fine now?
[Yes.]
Two minutes.
Robots.
Maybe you should get out first.
I'll collect the equipment.
Quiet.
How can you get distracted
when you're facing strong enemies?
There aren't any robots around.
My shooting skills still depend on luck.
What can I do?
It's okay. I have an idea.
What is it?
I'll teach you slowly, step by step.
You'll get the hang of it.
Why do I feel like
someone is spying on us.
I feel that too.
What are you two doing here?
You're back?
What did you expect?
I'm busy. I need to go now.
Glad to see you. Bye.
You...
You two...
Grandma.
-Open the door.
-Coming.
Don't open the door, Grandma.
That's a salesman.
A salesman?
We must call the management.
How can they let a salesperson enter?
Ignore him.
I think he'll leave in a while.
Lu Jing, don't try to hide.
I know you're home.
You dare to flirt with a woman
but dare not open the door?
Open the door.
I know you're home.
Jing.
He sounds like Sun, our neighbour.
What did he say? You were flirting what?
Don't mind that, Grandma.
I guess...
I guess he's rehearsing for his new drama.
Rehearsing?
Grandma Lu.
-Hi, Grandma Lu.
-Hi.
-Hi, Grandpa Lu.
-Hi, Sun.
-Have a drink.
-Why didn't you let me know you're coming?
See you later.
Okay. Have tea in my room.
What do you want?
What's going on between you two?
What do you mean?
Yeah,
carry on with your show.
Do you think you can beat me with that?
I'm just guiding her in the game.
Guiding her?
Is this how you guide her?
How should I do it otherwise?
You said you'll teach her step by step.
That's not you, Lu Jing.
What's my style then?
When I started,
you abandoned me
when I wasn't paying attention
because my bad skills
were holding you back.
Did you forget that?
Yes, I did.
You...
Look at you.
You gave up your sense of shame
just to flirt with a girl?
You're being different
because she's a girl, aren't you?
Come to your senses, Lu Jing.
She's even
a much worse player than I was.
But what did you tell her?
You'll teach her slowly step by step.
Is that so?
Are you done?
If you are, I need to study.
You... How heartless you are now.
So, you've grown up enough
to know how to flirt now?
Do you hear that?
They're quarrelling,
hammer and tongs.
What's the problem?
It's only normal for boys to fight.
It'd be strange if they don't.
What's wrong with
youngsters nowadays?
They get mad with each other so easily.
In the past,
Jing often visited Sun's house.
I heard them talking about a girl.
You mean,
both of them fell in love
with the same girl?
How could Sun do this?
He's too old to fight with
a young man over a girl.
No way. I have to back our grandson up.
Let them handle it themselves.
But...
Come on.
Wait a minute.
Don't tell me you found out who she is.
Yet you have the nerve to flirt with her?
Such a footsie player.
Footsie player?
What does that mean?
That means you're really flirty.
Who did you learn that from?
That punk, Director He, of course.
Wait, don't change the topic.
What were you two doing just now?
Nothing.
Do you think I'm blind?
By the way,
don't tell her I've learnt who she is.
I don't think she'd be happy
to be found out now.
Okay.
Our conversation ends here.
I need to study.
Bye.
What's with that look?
Can't you tell?
This is a curious look.
What's going on between you and my buddy?
What do you mean?
Exactly the same reply.
You want to brush me off?
Not a chance.
I just got online
when I heard you being lovey-dovey.
Stop pretending.
It's true.
He doesn't even know who I am.
Aren't you awesome.
How did you know him?
We're neighbours.
His parents are staying abroad.
He'll visit his grandparents' place
during the weekends.
What is his hobby?
Doing exercise.
Why do you care about him?
I do not.
I was just asking.
Why do I have a feeling
that you're not just asking?
Your secret is revealing.
[Liang Chen]
Hello, Shan Shan.
Are you... at home?
Yes. What is it?
I think I accidentally left
my earphone in your car.
Yeah. I actually planned
to take it to you when I'm free.
Can I go and take it now?
Sure. Just come.
Okay.
My friend is coming. You may leave.
Who is coming? Which Shan Shan is that?
Ma Shan Shan, my university mate.
What a coincidence.
I haven't told you this.
I worked with her
in the previous film.
Awesome.
It's true.
What are you doing?
That's awesome.
Leave them alone. You don't like skewers.
Don't waste them.
Then bring them home.
Swallow them down. Get out.
-I'll leave after I finish them.
-Hurry up.
Not so fast, Orange.
-Move it.
-It is a weekend.
It's difficult to get a car.
See. No one is taking my order.
Mr Hou will be here in one minute.
Okay. I'll hold it for you.
Put on your shoes.
I...I'm leaving then.
Bye.
By the way,
come and have dinner at my house tomorrow.
I invited some friends
to welcome me back.
Enough. Stop wasting time.
Hurry up.
Leave already. Bye.
Don't come empty-handed tomorrow night.
Fine.
What a coincidence, Ms Ma.
Shan Shan, come on in.
Yeah, get in.
Hi.
Miss...
Ms Ma, did you catch
your foot in the door?
Come and have a seat.