[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Episode 11]
My stomach is aching.
Why are you having a
stomach ache all of sudden?
Are you okay?
I have to go to the hospital.
Take it from here, buddy.
Gu Fei Ming! Gu Fei Ming! You...
Mr Luo, may I take his place?
Hurry up and get ready then, you guys.
We're going up there in a minute.
You'll give her the flower on stage
while I'll give her the
souvenir, is that okay?
What the hell is this?
About that...
Maybe they didn't know Liang Chen
would come today.
Just pretend it's a bouquet
of fiery red roses.
The volume sounds fine on my end.
Liang Chen, that was a great performance.
Thank you.
You are?
I'm...
Kid, what are you doing?
Give her the doll!
What is this?
This is actually a bouquet of roses.
The roses are not ready yet.
We're using this doll for now.
[His voice.]
[It can't be.]
Liang Chen.
Lu Jing, it's time for
us to leave the stage.
Come on.
I thought all celebrities
put on airs and act aloof.
I didn't expect Liang Chen
to be so friendly.
Lu Jing, are you okay?
Why are you blushing?
It's too warm in here.
Warm? How?
Lu Jing, where are you going?
It's still a little cold
in this gymnasium.
And you're wearing so little.
Drink some warm water.
Ms Liang,
what are you thinking about?
Nothing.
The boy who gave you flowers
just now is so handsome.
He looks a bit like Liu Mao Yan.
That's right.
Do you remember we saw him
on a plane once before?
You actually remember that?
Don't tell me you have a crush on him.
A crush?
What are you talking about?
I don't have a crush on him.
Look at your lousy acting skills.
You are feeling guilty, aren't you?
Let me tell you, he's just a student.
Have a heart.
What's wrong with dating a student?
Students are
pure in thought,
passionate,
and full of vigour.
And most of all,
they are nice and obedient.
I'm speechless.
He was just giving you flowers,
and you're already imagining things.
How come you don't look so inspired
when you're composing songs?
But honestly,
there are benefits to
dating a younger guy too.
Don't underestimate younger guys.
They will take care of you forever.
Knock it off.
I'm going to check on the rehearsal.
Look at you being shy.
[Calm down. Maybe he didn't hear us.]
[Don't panic.]
[Ms Liang, wait up!]
Liu Mao Yan!
Ke Ke, we'd better go now.
We have a lot of work to do today.
Lu Jing,
Mr Luo asked for you.
I got it.
Okay.
Lu...
Liang Chen,
are you okay?
[Oh my god, this is so embarrassing.]
Ms Liang, are you okay?
Are you okay? That must be painful.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I'm perfectly fine.
The floor is too slippery.
We should report this to
the university right away.
We can't have this.
We can't have the junior students
slip and fall down too.
After all, they are the
future of our country.
Liang Chen,
do you feel any pain?
No.
Not at all. See?
I can still move my legs.
I can still turn around.
Ms Liang!
Liu, open the car door!
I haven't gotten into the car yet!
Ms Liang!
[Students are]
[pure in thought,]
[passionate,]
[and full of vigour.]
[And most of all,]
[they are nice and obedient.]
You're going to perform tomorrow.
You should get some rest tonight.
Can I choose not to attend
the homecoming now?
What do you think?
It's frustrating.
You have to face it
even though it's frustrating.
Giving flowers only takes a few seconds.
It'll be over in the blink of an eye.
That's easy for you to say.
What about my pride?
You are going to be strangers again
when it's over tomorrow, anyway.
You won't see each other again.
What else could happen?
I...
You won't understand.
Forget it.
Forget it, forget it.
[Thank you.]
He's so good looking.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You're here.
[How can you stoop so low?]
[What should I do tonight?]
[We can work this out.]
[No.]
[Nothing you say today can make me agree.]
[You're avoiding Qi Qi]
[because you don't want her to find out]
[your real gaming ability, aren't you?]
[It's none of your business.]
[Do you know I'm the number one
player on the local server?]
[You're bragging now?]
[Yes, you're a great player.]
[So what?]
[I know, it's nothing.]
[I was going to offer playing
on your behalf.]
[But since you're so reluctant,]
[forget it.]
[What?]
[Are you saying you will play in my stead]
[using my ID?]
[Lu Jing.]
[Mr Lu.]
[Please, help me.]
[Well...]
[What about giving flowers on stage?]
[You may do it.]
You have to do your best later.
Don't embarrass me.
The stronger you seem, the better.
It'd be best if you can
help me win Qi Qi's admiration.
Are you sure?
I have given you the
opportunity to give flowers.
You must do your best.
Don't mess with me.
Sure, I promise I'll do my best.
Hurry up, Qi Qi is online now.
Gu Fei Ming, you're so awesome.
It's nothing.
Two more down.
You're such a good shot.
No, no.
You hit the target every
time without missing.
Why didn't you tell me you
were so awesome?
Oh my god, Gu Fei Ming,
you're actually a top player.
I...
I like to keep a low profile.
Buddy, I'm begging you,
you need to tone it down.
Didn't you say the stronger
I seemed, the better?
You're putting me in a tough spot.
You're playing so well.
How am I going to carry her in the future?
Fine.
You...
You blew yourself up?
This is really dumb, don't you think?
Is it?
This doesn't fit your persona
as the world's top 20 player at all.
[Beautiful Soul]
Ms Liang, what are you doing?
Are you going to play
Beautiful Soul with Herman?
What's the matter?
Invite Herman now!
I want to see a top player
playing up close.
No.
I've been trying to lay off
gaming recently.
I won't play even if you kill me.
Off you go.
[Want to play a round?]
[Now's not a good time.]
[What's wrong?]
You're asking me what's wrong?
[I got hurt.]
[Which part? Is it serious?]
It's serious. Very serious!
It's so embarrassing.
[It's nothing serious.]
[I hurt my hand accidentally]
[when I was taking a shower this morning.]
[I'm unable to use the keyboard now.]
[I'm going to stream later.
Will you watch?]
[Or did you hurt your eyes too?]
Come on man, do you
really need me to watch it?
Can't you give me a break?
[Sure, I'll watch.]
Why are you still here?
Ms Liang, what are you watching?
Nothing, just a livestream.
You're watching Herman's livestream.
You didn't want to play with him,
but you're watching his livestream.
You're not being honest.
Ke Ke, I'm begging you.
Please go.
Even if I die of embarrassment,
you still won't get my inheritance.
Embarrassment?
You're dwelling on what happened today?
Ms Liang, I'm going home now.
Do you know who Liu Mao Yan is?
Yes, why?
Someone teased me today,
saying that I looked like him.
[Liu Mao Yan is mine. Mine!]
[Herman looks like Liu Mao Yan?]
[Herman - Liu Mao Yan]
[He must be a handsome guy.]
[Whether it's Liu Mao Yan or Herman,]
[They are mine.]
[Ignore her, dear.]
[they're both mine.]
Go away.
Saying you looked like
Liu Mao Yan was a tease?
Of course there was more than that.
What else did she say about you?
You want to hear a
romantic story for free?
Calm down.
[Give us an update, please.]
[Tell us the romantic story.]
[I don't believe it. Show me proof.]
Our livestream is almost over.
Tell us now. Don't keep everyone waiting.
Stop asking.
I won't tell you.
Who exactly teased you?
A senior.
Over there.
Can you tell us how you felt
when she was teasing you?
So, you guys want to know
if she has plans to court me?
I want to know too.
When I see her next time,
I'll ask her.
[Like. Comment. Report.]
[Are you sure you want to report?]
[Yes]
Let me teach you a lesson today
about life.
Otherwise, you wouldn't know
how dark society really is.
[The first Silver Tongue Cup]
[Snarky King Award goes to...]
Why are you still here?
I ate too much at dinner.
I'm trying to burn it off.
[Ms Ma, please give an acceptance speech.]
[I'm not good with words.]
[I'll say just a few words...]
Ms Liang, is Ma Shan Shan one
of the guests in the homecoming?
[A few words...]
I don't know.
Probably not.
You two were classmates.
She's a celebrity too.
Why didn't she get invited?
[Ladies and gentlemen,]
[dear leader, dear friends,]
[ladies and gentlemen...]
The university probably invited her,
but I guess
she doesn't want to attend.
Ms Liang, did anything happen
between you and Ma Shan Shan back then?
No.
You two didn't fight over a guy, did you?
What are you thinking?
Okay then. Rest well.
I should go back now.
[Yes, yes. Okay.]
[I would like to thank my uncle.]
[Because my uncle]
[introduced my parents to each other.]
[And I would like to thank my aunt.]
[Without my aunt,]
[I wouldn't have my uncle.]
[And I would like to thank
my aunt's ex-husband.]
[Because if he hadn't]
[divorced my aunt,]
[I wouldn't have an uncle]
[who would introduce my dad
and mum to each other.]
[That's a lot of people to thank.]
Shan Shan,
is that Liang Chen?
I didn't know you two used to be so close.
[Shan Shan,]
[I will become the
best singer in the future.]
[Then I will become the best
music producer.]
[Okay, let's both do our best.]
Isn't this a little over the top
for a university's Founder's Day?
Even Liang Chen is here.
That's great. It's not easy
to see Liang Chen.
Stop calling her name so intimately.
Aren't you ashamed?
You make it sound as though
you two are close.
Liang Chen.
I like the sound of it.
Here comes another one who thinks
he's close with her.
My livestream last night got reported.
Reported for what?
Spreading false information.
What information did you spread?
Did you do something
behind our backs last night?
Looks like our senior
has learned to point fingers at others.
[The report filed against streamer Herman]
[was untrue,]
[so it was dismissed.]
Ms Liang,
can you stop pulling a long face?
I really wish a robot could take me away,
so I won't have to attend
the homecoming.
Stop being glum.
It's time for us to go now. Hurry up.
Let's go, come on.
This one. This one is definitely good.
I think this one is nice.
It'll look good on Lu Jing.
This won't do.
It doesn't highlight Jing's
handsomeness at all.
This isn't as good as the previous one.
Keep looking.
Are you guys done?
This one...
Maybe I should do it myself.
Alright, alright.
We will choose the hairstyle
that Mr Liu'er
has just recommended for you.
Jing, just trust us.
We are the best and the most professional
hair stylists you can find.
For real.
So handsome.
You're indeed the Takeshi Kaneshiro
of Nanze University.
The hairstyle I chose is perfect for Jing.
Are you guys done?
Lu Jing,
are you going to get married
or give flowers?
I think Liang Chen will definitely
fall in love with him at first sight.
They will fall into the river of love,
never to escape.
They will have a beautiful love story.
Nonsense.
Love takes time.
I told you we should be sensible fans.
There must be no mistakes
with the script and process.
-Got it.
-Got it, sir.
Good.
Ms Liang, what are you doing out here?
Liang Chen! Liang Chen!
Stop looking, Ms Liang.
I've asked around.
That boy hasn't come yet.
Wait, who told you to ask?
Aren't you dying to see that boy?
I...
Liang Chen, I love you!
Alright, Ms Liang.
Let's go back to your dressing room
and touch up that face.
You still have to go out there and
take pictures with students later.
Give me some advice.
Which one looks better?
Wear the red one. It's joyous.
I think the white one is better.
White looks clean.
Zhou Zhou, which one is better?
If you ask me,
stop worrying about this.
Liang Chen has seen many
handsome men.
You think you can get her attention
just by dressing yourself up?
Naive.
Something could happen
between you and Liang Chen.
You can do it, feisty boy.
[Which one looks better?]
[Why?]
[I have to attend an
important event today.]
[I need your advice
on which one looks better.]
[How would I know which
one looks better on you?]
[I look the best when I wear nothing.]
Wear nothing then!
[Go with the white sweater.]
Bye.
He smells so nice.
It's just giving flowers.
Is that necessary?
Thank you, Liang Chen.
Next.
Three, two, one.
-Thank you, Liang Chen.
-Thank you.
Next.
Are you here to take a picture with me?
Please take a picture
of me and Liang Chen.
Thank you.
Three, two, one.
Thank you, Liang Chen.
Next.
Liang Chen, I really like you.
Me too.
Three, two, one.
Thank you, Liang Chen.
Next.
Thank you.
[Does it look like you?]
Liang Chen, are you okay?
[What?]
[I mean the box doll in the photo.]
[Does it look like you?]
The hell it looks like me!
Dear guests,
dear leaders of the university,
dear students and alumni,
good evening!
Lu Jing,
what are you holding in your hand?
A toy.
Are you going to give it to Liang Chen?
[What? It's for me?]
It's just for the photo.
This box doll
looks a lot like someone I know.
Lu Jing,
you're wearing so little. Aren't you cold?
No.
After all,
I'm full of vigour.
Ms Liang, we should go and get ready.