[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Adapted from Qiao Yao's novel]
["It's Easy To Dodge a Gun,
But Hard To Prevent a Crush"]
[Episode 23]
Our boy
has finally grown up.
I've been so worried about him
all these years.
What guy doesn't have a girlfriend
in university?
My boy is nice,
but he is a complete nerd.
A bookworm who only reads and studies.
But now, it's great.
-He's finally found a girlfriend.
-Yes.
I have to go back to my friends.
No problem, go ahead.
Okay. Bye, Grandpa.
-Bye, Grandma.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye.
-Okay, bye.
Dear, our grandson has a girlfriend now.
Do you hear me?
What's the use in hearing about it?
Let's change our clothes and check it out.
Yes indeed! Let's go.
Food is here.
Here.
Thanks.
You all have not even
touch your chopsticks yet.
It's just a joke, guys.
You're back so soon.
We have yet to eat.
An immediate emergency
calls for an instant remedy.
Okay.
Ms Ma.
Quick, taste this.
I've made a great contribution
to this particular dish.
As great as a sesame seed.
Come.
Here you go, Ms Ma.
-Thanks.
-Thanks, Jia Yun.
Liang Chen doesn't drink.
You drink on her behalf.
No problem.
Have some fruit juice.
Can you take alcoholic drinks?
You underestimate me.
Come on, cheers everyone.
To celebrate Orange's
triumph in the challenge.
Thanks everyone, cheers!
Let's eat.
Ms Ma.
Try some fish.
I made this. Try it.
I don't eat fish.
Well, that's alright.
Use mine then.
Ms Ma, try the boiled shrimp.
I made this too.
It's so delicious.
Okay.
Ms Ma.
You didn't eat the fish,
but why is there a
fish bone on your eyelid?
It's double eyelid sticker.
My dear,
do you think it's a good idea
to just show up like this?
Of course!
We have to take the initiative.
If not, we'll have to wait a
long time to get a grandchild.
That's true.
Stop hesitating, let's go.
Sure, let's go.
I'll open the door.
Grandpa Lu, Grandma Lu.
What brings you here?
We are here to borrow some rice.
We've finished ours.
To borrow rice? Both of you?
Grandpa is worried that I might
not be able to carry it.
-He's here to help me.
-Yes, to help.
Are you going to take all of our rice?
Of course not.
Just lend us what you can.
Sure, come in.
This way, Grandpa Lu.
-Coming.
-This way, Grandpa Lu.
There are so many of you here.
Everyone is here.
Please sit down, children.
Sit down.
Okay, okay.
Carry on with your meal.
We're just here to borrow some rice.
This way, Grandpa Lu.
Grandma, why are you here?
I know you're having a gathering.
So I brought a box of Doubendou
soy milk for you
to replenish your nutrients.
Grandma.
Would you look at this rice?
The rice...
Judging by your attire,
it doesn't look like
you're having a meal at home.
Take a good look with my glasses.
So bright and beautiful.
Yes, indeed.
How come I never noticed
how attractive our rice is?
You have a vision problem.
Grandma, why don't we
continue this back home?
Okay, okay.
Kids, enjoy your meal.
If there's not enough food,
we have braised duck
and pork shoulder at home.
Heaps of them.
You're welcome to it.
-Don't be shy.
-Let's go, Grandpa.
-You're all welcome to it.
-Let's go.
Okay.
Have a good day.
We'll talk at home, okay?
Sure.
We're off, then,
Here, Orange.
Grandma Lu's Doubendou soy milk.
Enjoy it.
Try it, Ms Ma.
Thanks.
Here, Ding.
[Should I go over and say hi to them?]
[No hurry, just give them some time.]
[What should I prepare?]
[A greeting gift.]
Are you two done texting each other?
Can't we just have a proper meal?
I'm sorry.
I was too loud just now.
Please carry on.
Carry on with your texting.
Here, Ms Ma.
Have a boiled shrimp.
Come, Ding. Cheers.
Dig in, Liang Chen.
Jing,
don't just keep drinking water.
Why did you come back just like that?
What else should I do?
You should send my
granddaughter-in-law back home.
Don't worry, Grandma.
Someone will send her back.
My dear grandson,
how can you be such a fool?
That was such a good opportunity.
It was the time to show your affection.
You're not like me at all.
Back in the day, when I pursued
your grandma...
Stop bragging about the past.
Tell me, Jing.
When will we get to meet
our granddaughter-in-law in person?
This is very important.
When?
In two days time?
A day?
-A day?
-You are even more impatient.
You can't keep putting it off.
Not with something like this.
If you keep putting it off,
you'll miss the chance.
-Do you understand?
-Yes.
Anyway, we really like this girl.
She's gorgeous, bright and gentle.
She's perfect.
She is very bright and beautiful.
-I like her a lot.
-You do?
Just two more days.
Two more days.
You must seize it.
-Sure.
-No procrastinating.
Come, drink your water.
Thanks, Grandma.
You are not drunk, are you, Ding?
I'm still alright.
Good job with the cooking today.
Look at all the dirty dishes.
Don't you move a muscle.
I'll do the dishes.
Sober up and we'll have a chat later.
You...
What are you implying?
Others may not be aware,
but I am.
You may look alright on the surface,
but you haven't let of Orange.
What's not to let go?
If we're not destined to be together,
what's the point in trying?
You know, destiny
is a fascinating thing.
I believe Ms Ma and I are destined
to be together.
What do you think?
Then why didn't you send her home?
Orange was here.
I had no chance.
Why don't we have a couple more drinks?
Let's drink to destiny.
It's getting late.
I've got to go.
Let me get you a designated driver.
Zhu Guang is downstairs.
I'll make a move first.
Let me see you off, Ding.
Take it easy.
Bye, Ding.
Keep in touch.
How can I help you?
I heard you have a girlfriend now.
How did you get a girlfriend so suddenly?
Is she your coursemate?
Excuse me.
Carry on.
We've known each other for so long.
Who am I to you, really?
[Lu Jing, it all begins
with Beautiful Soul.]
[Get Orange to join us.]
[Brother, let's have fireworks tonight.]
[Why are you still awake at this hour?]
[I joined the winter camp.]
[It's boring at night.]
[Please play with me.]
[I beg you, Brother.]
[You are the best.]
[Okay, I will get a couple of friends.]
Anything?
[I miss you.]
We've just met earlier, haven't we?
[I don't want to be apart
from you even for a second.]
[Do you want to play Beautiful Soul?]
[Taro, and my cousin will be joining too.]
Your cousin?
It's good for you to get
acquainted with him.
We will soon be a family anyway.
Okay, I'll stop joking.
Are you joining?
Okay.
How did you do in the exam?
Superb. I came in first.
If you count from the back.
Yes, indeed.
Here I am.
Brother, who...
Who is she?
Your girlfriend?
It's your sister-in-law.
Sister... in law?
Sister-in-law!
Brother, you're in a relationship.
How are you, kid?
Hi, Sister-in-law.
I need to tell Uncle and Aunt about this.
But Brother,
when will you take Sister-in-law home?
You have to ask her
when she will be willing
to go home with me.
Okay, let's proceed with our mission.
What's wrong with Taro?
The host is now the latecomer.
I'm here!
Well, nature's call.
You are here too, Brother.
Who says I'm your brother?
Okay, everyone is here.
Let's go.
Come over here, Chen Chen.
Stop calling me that.
There's a kid here. It's not appropriate.
I was calling my brother.
Sister-in-law, he is calling me.
Chen Chen, this is for you.
Chen Chen.
Liang Chen.
Are you calling me?
Chen Chen? Seriously?
Chen Chen.
Would you like a grenade?
Why are you coming here?
I didn't ask you to come
over, I just wanted to give....
She hit me.
Do you hear me, Lu Jing?
Ha Ha.
The two of you are so much alike.
Always bullying me.
I saw a jeep, Brother.
Coming.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Since when did you become so observant?
What are you waiting for? Get in the car.
The co-driver's seat is mine.
Sister,
you are really possessive.
Look, Lu Jing.
What are you doing?
Get in the back, now.
Okay. I'm going.
Showing off your affection online.
Disgusting.
Huh.
Let's get down. The car is broken.
I...
Orange.
After you left,
I witnessed a very interesting thing.
What is that?
A Hunanese girl came to see Lu Jing.
Who?
You have to ask him.
It's nothing. She's just a neighbour.
My foot!
That's not what actually happened.
I saw it with my own eyes.
That girl was questioning him
whether he was seeing a girl.
What did you tell her, then?
Me? Nothing.
My foot!
She was really disappointed.
She kept asking him,
"How much do I mean to you?"
You're so dangerous.
How did you answer her?
Didn't you see it?
How I answered her?
I missed that part.
You asked me to get inside.
Tell me, what did you say?
[We've known each other for so long.]
[How much do I mean to you?]
[I'm sorry, you have
no place in my heart.]
As expected of my brother!
Is that so?
I told you,
Lu Jing would never hurt you.
When did you say that?
Just now. I said it a few times
inside my head.
Good job.
Come on.
This is for you.
Such a good boy.
Don't call me that.
It makes me sound like a kid.
Sound like a kid?
You are a kid.
Say it again.
Who is the kid?
It's me, I'm the kid.
The kid at your gunpoint.
Chen Chen.
Here's a healing salve.
-Who are you calling?
Who do you think I'm calling?
You're awesome.
Have you two had enough?
You taunted this poor bachelor
in real life,
and now you're taunting him online.
Isn't that mean?
I'm mean?
Get your own girlfriend, then.
Are you provoking me?
You...
You never had a girlfriend
after all these years.
Lu Jing, if you keep provoking me,
Believe it or not, I will go after you.
No way, I won't agree
even if he agrees with it.
Are you out of your mind?
Let's go.
By the way, I'm short of a smoke grenade.
Lu Jing, can I have one?
No, because you
eavesdropped on me earlier.
Cheapskate!
Brother, I'm out of smoke grenades.
Can I have one?
I gave them all to your sister-in-law.
Ask her.
Sister-in-law, can I have a smoke grenade?
Here you go.
What's wrong with you?
This is bullying.
Just call me sister-in-law.
Go on.
Go to hell.
-Come on.
-Let's go.
[Chen Chen,]
[when will you be ready]
[to meet my parents?]
What's your problem?
Can you drop it already?
[I can't wait]
to start the next phase
of my life.
I'm tired. I have to go.
What did you say? I can't hear you.
Bye-bye.
-Bye-bye.
-Goodnight.
[Lu Jing.]
[How's your plan to study abroad]
[coming along?]
[I've got the letter of admission.]
[My admission is next year.]
[Great.]
[I know you've been preparing for this]
[since freshman year.]
[I never thought you'd be
graduating so soon.]
[In all my years of teaching,]
[I've seldom come across a student
as talented]
[and as hardworking as you.]
[Do your best.]
[I will.]
[Letter of admission]
Have you eaten?
No.
Let me check the fridge.
Do you know how to cook?
Why don't we order takeout?
Okay.
What do you want to eat?
Anything will do.
I will go ahead and order.
I need to answer a call.
Lu Jing, how about pizza?
Thanks.
I'm asking, is pizza fine with you?
Yes.
Who are you calling?
The courier.
The courier? Do they speak English?
It's for an overseas parcel.
I see.
I'll order a fruit pizza for you.
Would you like that?
Sounds good.
What about spicy pizza?
Wasabi pizza?
Sounds good.
Durian pizza?
Sounds good, too.
Why do you like everything?
But I love you the most.
What's going on?
Nothing, just want to hug you.
Are you sure you're okay?
The food delivery will take some time.
Why don't we play a game first?
Let's go.
Sit down.
What are you trying to do?
Log in.
Why are you looking at me?
Looks like your handling needs work.
No wonder you are so
slow to pick up items.
Run downstairs. Look alive.
Stop picking those up.
Are you going to sell those garbage
for money or what?
Shut up!
What are you waiting for? Just hit it!
Why are you putting your head down?
You keep mumbling beside me.
I can't hit any of them.
What's wrong?
Don't move.
I have to teach you by grabbing your hand.
Your chair
is too awkward.
Let me find you another chair.
Never mind.
Isn't this better?
Try to feel it.
This is how you handle recoil.
You didn't hit it, either.
It's a mistake.
Don't move. I'm nervous too.
The phone is ringing.
Why don't you go and answer it?
Hi.
Why must the phone ring at this moment?
Hello, what would you like?
A latte, please.
Extra coffee, extra milk.
We have a promotion right now.
Half price for the second
cup, do you want it?
Not for me. Two cups is too much.
You can share it with your girlfriend.
No thanks. She's watching her figure.
She's laying off the stuff.
Okay, please wait for a moment.
[Yesterday evening,]
[famous musician, Lin Qi, shared
an engagement photo]
[of him and his fiancee online.]
[He announced that their
wedding is coming soon.]
What does everyone in the world
have a partner
except me?
[It is said that Lin Qi's fiancee]
[is his manager of many years.]
[Their relationship was made
public three months ago.]
[In response to the wedding announcement,]
[friends and colleagues
sent their regards.]
[Lin Qi.]
[It is said that Lin Qi's fiancee]
[is his manager of many years.]
[Their relationship was made
public three months ago.]
[In response to the wedding announcement,]
[friends and colleagues
sent their regards.]
Why are you laughing?
Nothing.
It's Taro.
[Sun Bin Yu]
So annoying.
Hi, what's up?
Where are you, Orange?
I'm at home.
Come to my place at once.
Ms Ma's in trouble.
Why is Shan Shan there?
Please come over, Ms Ma is drunk.
I can't handle her by myself.
Hang on. I'll be right there.
Bye.
-What's going on?
-I'll explain on the way.
-Where's Shan Shan?
-She's inside.
Shan Shan.
Shan Shan. Shan Shan.
What happened?
Why did she drink so much?
I have no idea.
The waiter at the bar called
and asked me to go there.
When I arrived, she was already like this.
She even became sworn
brothers with the bottles.
She must've drank a ton.
She's sweating bullets.
Get a glass of water.
Okay.
Why did she drink excessively?
Sun, the hangover soup is ready.
Where is he?
Jing.
-Grandma.
-What are you doing here?
When did you come back?
Just now, Grandma.
Hello, Grandma.
Hello.
Is this kid okay?
She's just drunk. She'll be fine
after a good sleep.
Jing, why didn't you answer my calls?
Your father's been
looking for you all day.
He wants to talk to you
about the matter of
studying abroad next year.
Let's go back, Grandma.
I will explain to you when we go back.
Okay, let her drink the
soup while it's still hot.
You should return your father's call now.
Otherwise, he's going to be worried.
Okay.
Settle the study abroad thing first.
Okay, let's go back.
Are you planning to study overseas?
Why didn't you tell me?
I...
I'm sorry.
What do you mean "sorry?"
Sorry for not telling you earlier.
So if Grandma hadn't brought it up,
you would never tell me, is that it?
Here's the water.
Why don't you two go out?
Okay, Liang Chen.
Go out, please.
Let's go.
Come on.
What's the matter?
Did you two have a fight?
She found out about
my plan to study abroad.
Even I know that.
You didn't tell her?
I mean, why didn't you let her know?
I don't think it's necessary.
You don't think it's necessary?
So I'm the only one who doesn't know?
Liang Chen.
Don't just stand there.
Chase her.
Liang Chen!
[Sorry, the subscriber you've dialled
is turned off.]
[Liang Chen]
What's wrong, Ms Liang?
You've changed your clothes already?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I didn't sleep well, that's all.
Is something wrong?
Why don't you get up
and freshen up?
You have a rehearsal
with the band, remember?
Wear more clothes.
The temperature came down
last night.
I nearly froze to death on my
way here this morning.
Okay.