♪Memories of the past are always vivid♪
♪They accompanied me to take every step♪
♪On the road♪
♪Going through heat and cold♪
♪The bumpy journey
has rendered my longing♪
♪Rock solid♪
♪The same moonlight
shines on our shoulders♪
♪Even if we are far away separated♪
♪We are close in our hearts♪
♪The wind blew away the past♪
♪I look for your distant location
on the starry night♪
♪In the ocean of faces♪
♪For you, my heart burns and races♪
♪Despite its turns and twists,
fate is in my hands♪
♪May waiting convert regrets
into a happy ending♪
♪May solitary figures
find right companions♪
♪And become a pair♪
=Time Flies and You Are Here=
=Episode 3=
(The Spring Landscape Calls
Forth Nostalgia for the Hometown)
(Delicacy Restaurant)
Go ask him. Go ask him.
Don't miss the chance.
May I ask
what kind of dessert you like?
He is rather undemanding
in this aspect.
This is what you eat?
He likes
all delicious foods.
Yeah.
I like delicious foods too.
Why is Hanchen blushing?
Bossy.
It's alright. It's alright.
He is always like that.
Zhong Ziyan looks like a nice man.
Let's not make desserts
for Zhao Xiaoqian.
Let's make it for Zhong Ziyan.
His name is Zhong Ziyan?
He is the Commandery Prince's
learning partner
and he is from a humble family.
I heard his father had won
1st place in the imperial exam.
Unfortunately, his father died early,
leaving him and his mother behind.
So he had to serve the Commandery
Prince as a learning partner.
Is it that interesting
to gossip behind people's back?
Today is the birthday
of the Goddess of Earth.
The Academy
is offering Sweet and Sour Fish
to you girls.
I never knew about this benefit
of attending the Academy.
I told you
I am not a village rascal
and my father is not a butcher.
My father is a government official.
You bragger.
Like hell he is.
If you were an official's son,
you wouldn't be eating scraps here.
Your father has lost his fortune.
You!
You've even learned how to fight?
Good for you.
I won't bother with you today.
But wait for me
tomorrow after school.
Forget him. He looks so dirty.
He can't pay for your damaged shoes.
Let's go.
Be careful not
to catch any weird disease.
Very well.
I won't bother with a village rascal.
We'll deal with him tomorrow.
Come on.
My...
My father is really an official.
You don't believe me?
I'll show you my father's official token
tomorrow.
(Civil Official)
(Wujiang Prefecture School)
Young Master,
what happened?
(Wujiang Prefecture School)
Zhao Xiaoqian.
We'll get back at him.
Come on.
Congwen.
Xiaoman.
Thank you for helping me out
at the Spring Banquet.
What kind of dessert do you like?
When I was in Yuyangli,
your family looked after me.
What I did was nothing
compared to your family's help.
No, no, no.
You have returned the favor,
but I should still thank you.
I remember the Chestnut Cakes
your mother made
for students.
I like those cakes.
I didn't expect you to remember.
Sis.
What's the matter?
Will you send me home after school?
Do you remember our mother's
recipe for the Chestnut Cake?
It's not the time
to talk about Chestnut Cakes.
Remember to send me home after school.
I'll be waiting for you
at the Academy's gate.
Alright. Alright.
Keep it in mind.
You must be there for me.
Does a Chestnut Cake
contain sesame or not?
This way.
It's mine.
Yeah. Pass it on.
Let me have it.
Pass it that way.
Good.
Catch it.
Xie Xiaoman,
go up there.
Ask the Commandery Prince
what his favorite flavor is.
Ask him yourself.
You!
You are annoying.
What's in it for you?
You don't treat her
as your paternal cousin,
but I treat her as my maternal cousin.
Of course it is related to me.
Miss Xie.
Minggu.
How could you say that to Ruying?
Can you stop being pretentious?
Even my father
has heard your gossip.
Sub-prefect Xue's family
is really powerful.
The young ladies' bickering
could lead to my family's
silk document being withheld.
You!
I'll go.
You told me to stay out of trouble.
You should watch your mouth too.
Uncle has been working
on that for a long time.
I can go and ask. It'll be alright.
Don't go.
Xiaoman!
Pass it on. Pass it on.
That kick was savage.
Take her to a doctor.
Will she offer herself to him
to thank him for saving her life?
Come off it.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
You shrew!
You seek revenge
for the smallest grievance.
You just won't stop, right?
You kicked that ball, didn't you?
It's your fault
that you are weak as a chick.
And your skin is dark as Guan Yu.
How dare you!
I dare not.
You!
It wasn't me at the Spring Banquet.
You're after the wrong person.
But you tore my title deed.
So what if I did?
It was just a receipt.
Your family's land is mine anyway.
If you make me happy,
I will give it to you.
Tell me
what kind of dessert you like,
then I won't hold a grudge against you.
Why should I tell you?
Suit yourself.
You're such a sharp-tongued woman.
Do all bumpkins talk like this?
You!
Just bake whatever you want.
I'm not picky.
I'll eat anything.
Rest well.
Jerk.
Xie Xiaoman.
What's Zhao Xiaoqian's favorite food?
I don't know.
He didn't tell.
If you want to know, ask him yourself.
- I...
- Moreover,
don't make me help you
marry up.
Don't assume I am unaware
of what you did.
You!
You're here.
Are you going to make Chestnut Cakes?
What about you?
It's a secret.
Good.
Here.
Hanchen is here.
How is she?
Is my skin dark?
Why would you care about
your skin tone as a man?
What are you up to?
Planning to serve
the ball with your beauty?
Piss off.
Give me the ball.
Who is ready for a game?
Every man at Bailu Academy!
Let's play!
Do you think
Hanchen looks a bit weird today?
His tanned complexion
is tinged with red.
Chief.
Are you going to drug him?
There is no "drug" involved.
This is croton nut powder.
I've asked around about Zhao Xiaoqian.
He eats customized food
in Bailu Academy.
He even brought a cook
from the Commandery Prince's Mansion.
Then we won't have a chance to drug him.
I heard Xie Xiaoman
works at his home as a maid.
Go ask around, you two.
You made two helpings.
What are these snacks?
These Ox Tongue Cakes
are auspicious snacks
for the Cold Food Festival.
These are the Chestnut Cakes
I made for my family and seniors.
You're marvelous.
Let's go.
School is over?
It's over half an hour ago.
You should go home too.
- We'll be going.
- Yeah.
See you.
(Bailu Academy)
Doesn't your family
live in the countryside?
Go now.
Otherwise, you won't be home
until the early morning.
Your father is a pig killer.
He is waiting for you
to go home and eat pork.
Yeah. Go home.
I-I told you
I am not a village rascal.
Can't you understand?
I don't believe you.
(Civil Official)
See?
This is my father's official token.
M-my father has an official position.
He is not a butcher.
Scram!
Let's get out of here!
Little boy,
what are you doing here?
I...
I'm waiting for my elder sister Xiaoman.
Little boy,
you are Xie Xiaoman's younger brother.
Give it back.
What are you doing?
(Civil Official)
He is being naugthy.
He took our father's thing out
for fun.
If he offended you, please forgive him.
I apologize on his behalf.
You are Xie Xiaoman?
Yes.
What's wrong with that?
Are you going to participate
in the Cold Food Festival?
What do you mean?
Let me offer you an opportunity.
There will be
a cuju competition tomorrow.
Put this
in Zhao Xiaoqian's food.
Then make him eat the food.
What is this?
Croton nut powder.
Don't worry. It won't kill him.
He'll get the runs
for half a day at worst.
Let's go.
Give it back.
Lady,
you'd better do as I said.
If I don't see him
eat the drugged food,
you'll have to find
the official token in Lake Taihu.
What's more,
your father will have to jump
into Lake Taihu with you
if he finds out
he's lost the official token.
- You!
- Come on.
Don't move.
Sis.
Why did you
take our father's token?
Are you out of your mind?
Do you know how much trouble he is in
now that he's lost the official token?
Our father is in big trouble.
Do you know?
I told you to pick me up after school.
Where were you?
I forgot, alright?
Why didn't you go home after school?
We don't live in the same place.
You should be content
with living with our parents.
You make trouble all the time.
You live on the Su family's property.
Mother is worried you
may be looked down upon.
She gives you a monthly allowance
five times higher than mine.
You can afford the food
from Delicacy Restaurant.
You can afford new clothes.
However,
I can only bring the steamed cakes
made by our mother to the Academy.
My schoolmates call me a village rascal.
Li'er.
Don't touch me.
Alright. Don't be mad.
I'll try to fix
the official token problem.
Let's go home now.
Don't tell anyone about this.
Let's go home.
(The Commandery Prince's Mansion)
Xiaoman.
Mr. Liangji.
It's supper time.
The Commandery Prince said
you've been doing a good job these days.
He sent me here to look after you.
What's the matter?
Mr. Liangji.
You're a man of the world.
If a government official
loses his official token,
how will he
be punished?
It depends.
The official token is evidence
of his official position.
If those with ulterior motives
obtain the official token
and use it to do evil,
the government official
will lose his job at best
or end up in prison at worst.
Mr. Liangji.
(Maid at the Commandery Prince's
Mansion, Hongsu)
The Commandery Prince said
Xiaoman will have supper
in Dayang Room tonight.
Come on.
Let's have a drink.
Here.
Refill the wine cups.
How is it going with your desserts?
I've finished making the desserts.
Eat.
You look skinny from top to bottom.
How unattractive.
Didn't your family give you proper food?
No.
We bumpkins only eat plant roots.
Then eat more.
I don't want people
to think I mistreat my servants.
Look how scrawny you are.
Even human traffickers
wouldn't want you.
Here.
Eat more vegetables.
Have some tofu.
Eat up. Eat up.
What are you guys looking at?
Have you never eaten duck legs before?
Here.
Eat this duck head.
You, take whatever you want.
Someone eats the duck leg
while I eat the duck head.
(Energetic and spirited)
Nice. Nice.
(Score every goal in the manner
of a shooting star)
Fierce tigers on the mountain.
Flood dragons in the water.
Tigers and dragons lie
in Wujiang Prefecture School.
Come on.
We mustn't lose.
Finely dressed students at Bailu Academy
ride well-groomed horses.
They stand at the top
of the world and aim high.
Fierce tigers on the mountain.
Flood dragons in the water.
Tigers and dragons lie
in Wujiang Prefecture School.
Finely dressed students at Bailu Academy
ride well-groomed horses.
They stand at the top
of the world and aim high.
Zhong Ziyan!
Bailu Academy for the win!
All hail Bailu Academy!
This cuju competition has ten rounds.
Ten rounds later,
the team that scores more goals
wins.
(Score every goal
in the manner of a shooting star)
(Winds sweep over the pitch
where the players compete exuberantly)
Zhong Ziyan!
Hurry up.
I made
these peach blossom shortbread rolls.
It took me a long time.
Do you want to try a roll?
Boyang.
These aren't for you.
I wouldn't have the strength to play
if my stomach were empty.
I'm sorry.
(Don't eat my food. Don't eat my food.)
You made this?
I made it with little effort.
With little effort?
You didn't put in much effort indeed.
This looks ugly.
You'll eat this?
Sure.
As a gesture of apology.
You!
Eat this!
This is delicious.
Here.
Why did you make two helpings?
This tastes better than that.
- Just eat it.
- Hey...
Stop talking.
It really is delicious.
Come on. The game is on.
All hail Bailu Academy!
Bailu Academy for the win!
(Take the lead)
The competition starts now.
Move aside.
Catch the ball!
Good one!
Bailu Academy! Bailu Academy!
(Energetic and spirited)
Bailu Academy scored one goal.
The ball has hit the ground.
Round One is over.
Bailu Academy! Bailu Academy!
Bailu Academy!
Yay!
- Good one!
- Well done!
Here.
Bailu Academy scored one more goal.
The ball has hit the ground.
Round Three is over.
Wonderful!
Bailu Academy! Bailu Academy!
Wujiang Prefecture School!
- Bailu Academy!
- Wujiang Prefecture School!
Bailu Academy! Bailu Academy!
- Bailu Academy!
- Wujiang Prefecture School!
- This way.
Boyang!
Catch the ball!
Yes!
Good job!
Bailu Academy! Bailu Academy!
Round Five is over.
Break time!
Bailu Academy!
Don't get cocky. We'll catch up soon.
You were doing well in the capital.
I don't know why you
came to Wujiang Prefecture.
Well,
does losing feel good?
Damn you, Zhao Xiaoqian.
You're so impolite to me,
yet you want to marry my younger sister.
I can live without marrying her.
Idiot.
Crap.
Give me the token.
I saw what happened.
You didn't make Zhao Xiaoqian
eat the drugged food.
You want the token?
Find it in Lake Taihu.
I accidentally
toppled the dessert earlier.
That's why His Highness
didn't eat croton nut powder.
But what's done is done.
I've done everything you told me to do.
Accidentally?
You think I'm blind?
What else do you want from me?
The token is really important
to my father.
Fine.
Young lady.
Give me a kiss.
What are you talking about?
N-n-nothing.
Where is the token?
Did Shen Yan arrange all this?
Your Highness,
I'm just an errand boy.
Please spare me.
Get lost.
Wujiang Prefecture School.
Croton nut powder.
You wanted me to lose?
I'm sorry.
This is your noble way of living?
Zhao Xiaoqian.
Hanchen.
Don't touch me.
In the second half of the competition,
both teams will switch fields.
Get ready, everyone.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Really?
Hanchen.
Prepare yourself, Hanchen.
Hanchen, what's wrong with you?
The competition will start soon.
Xingzhou,
what's wrong with Hanchen?
The competition starts now.
Here.
- Here.
- Keep the goal.
Here.
Shameless.
Pass it on.
Hurry up.
This way.
Hanchen!
Pass the ball!
This way.
Go stop him.
Here.
Vile.
Get lost.
How did this happen?
- Good one!
Yay!
(Energetic and spirited)
Luck is on their side.
Yeah.
Nice shot!
Hanchen.
Yes!
Round Ten is over.
Bailu Academy scored three goals.
Wujiang Prefecture School
scored seven goals!
Wujiang Prefecture School won!
Hanchen.
As the team leader, you need to pour
three bowls of powder on yourself.
- Pour it.
- Pour it. Pour it.
Three bowls.
Pour it. Pour it.
Two bowls to go.
There are two bowls to go.
- Go on.
- Pour it.
- Yeah.
The third bowl.
Watch me.
Good.
- Good.
Why are they fighting?
(Energetic and spirited)
Yeah.
This is for trying to drug me!
Drug me! Drug me! Drug me!
Drug me! Drug me!
Stop!
This is for trying to drug me!
Drug me!
Hanchen, enough is enough!
What's your problem?
Are you done making a scene?
Yes.
Hanchen.
Xiaoman.
Hanchen, are you alright?
Zhao Xiaoqian.
I lost.
Are you happy now?
Miss Xie,
we don't know each other well.
But I can see
what happened today
upset Hanchen very much.
It's fine though.
Don't be scared.
We'll leave soon.
(Civil Official)
Your Highness.
What...
What happened to you?
How did you get so soiled?
Who dared to pick on you
in Wujiang Prefecture?
Shi Deng,
go
get the Prefecture Magistrate here.
This...
Pack up.
We'll return to the capital.
Now?
Yes, now.
But...
What happened?
Don't follow me!
Hanchen.
What is this all about?
What exactly happened?
Look how soiled he is.
And why did he
suddenly decide
to return to the capital?
Do as he said.
Pack up.
We'll discuss the details tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
No.
I'm sorry. My bad.
Move aside!
Miss, are you alright?
Su Wei.
Alright, stop looking on.
Go away.
Are you alright?
Xiaoman.
What do I do now?
You want to give someone
the peach blossom shortbread rolls?
Do you like Zhao Xiaoqian?
Hell no.
Then you like Zhong Ziyan.
I...
(The Commandery Prince's Mansion)
How about this?
Put the peach blossom shortbread rolls
in my food container.
I'll deliver the food
to Zhong Ziyan for you.
But
the peach blossom
shortbread rolls are dirty.
It's fine.
My granny said
a little dirt on food harms nobody.
We won't tell him it's dirty.
Alright. No more delay.
If we waste more time,
the Cold Food Festival will be over.
I'll get going.
Don't tell him I made these rolls.
(The Commandery Prince's Mansion)
Xiaoman.
Shi Deng.
Where is the Commandery Prince?
Someone riled up His Highness.
He is smashing things in the room.
We'll set off for the capital tomorrow.
Now he refuses to meet anyone.
Give this food container to Mr. Zhong.
Tell him
it's from a young lady
at the Academy.
He knows her.
There is one more thing.
Please deliver this message for me:
I've made a mistake
and I've learned my lesson.
But please don't
fire me.
I want to continue working here.
Mister who?
Mr. Zhao?
Xiaoman.
Take a seat.
What do you see in Zhong Ziyan?
It's none of your business.
How come you're so familiar
with their servant?
I work at their study.
Don't tell my uncle and auntie.
Why?
My land
belongs to the Commandery Prince now.
I need to redeem it.
But I just don't get along
with Zhao Xiaoqian.
I wonder when
I'll get to apologize
to him face-to-face.
Hurry up.
Hurry up. Hurry up.
You act like you haven't eaten.
Hurry up.
Pack my military texts and maps
into a separate box.
I need to bring them along.
Rest easy, Your Highness.
It has been on my mind.
We won't leave anything behind.
Your Highness.
What's with the noise?
Xiaoman came here today.
She asked me to bring this to you.
She said you'd recognize the food.
She said she learned her lesson
and wanted to continue working here.
Throw it out.
Wait.
Let me see.
Aren't these peach blossom
shortbread rolls?
Yeah.
Today is the Cold Food Festival.
This is the food the young ladies use
to express their love.
Is Miss Xie expressing her love...
For Your Highness?
We are not going then.
♪Ask the moon whether it has seen♪
♪The other end of the earth♪
♪Your feelings fluctuate
like the moon's wane and wax♪
♪Have they ever been the same?♪
♪Carried by misty clouds,
the moon came into your eyes♪
♪As a substitute for me, it appeared♪
♪Cast our eyes over the bustling street♪
♪Don't shed tears when we part♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪
♪Since our parting,
I have been recalling your look♪
♪Every night,
I miss you too much to sleep♪
♪In my heart,
I stored our affectionate past♪
♪As time went by, it faded like smoke♪
♪In my ears, rings your old whisper♪
♪Every night,
I look forward to meeting you again♪
♪On the day we brushed past each other♪
♪We got tied by a permanent bond♪