ALL NAMES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND INCIDENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTIONAL
Are you on your way?
Don't rush me. I'm coming.
Do you even know where I am?
You've been hovering around me
all this time.
What are you? My employee?
That's right.
Hurry here and finish coding.
And that will be it.
You stay right there.
This time,
let's really put an end to this.
Will you be all right, though? You'll die.
No, I won't go that easily.
The nuclear bomb will go off tomorrow.
You know,
there's one thing that made me very sad.
That I couldn't witness
the amazing explosion firsthand.
Tae-sul, do you have any idea
how long I've been waiting for this day?
Hey, Sigma. Stop, that's enough.
Even this time, you won't see it,
so don't get ahead of yourself.
Had I known I'd have to find you again,
I would've just shot you that day.
You were really fast
when running away in tears.
You should've become a professional runner
instead of an artist.
Then you probably would have
turned out all right.
Did you just scoff? What the hell?
I'm dead serious right now.
Some people just never make it
no matter how hard they work. That's you.
-Keep babbling away.
-Are you upset?
Nothing would've happened
had you kept your mouth shut.
You're still playing the blame game
in this situation?
This is why you can never make it.
You were like this even as a kid.
You tried to blame everything you did
and even your guilt on me.
The same goes for all your hate comments.
You think you're better than others
and that everyone else is wrong.
This nuclear war?
You want to say that's also my fault,
don't you?
What? Go on and say it.
Why are you all quiet? Answer my question.
-You're one to talk.
-Me?
Why? I never blame others for my mistakes.
-You're--
-That's why people hate you, you bastard.
Shut up!
You're changing your word now?
You told me to babble away.
What do you even know?
You people… You, Gang Seo-hae,
that old man who sold me the rope
and charcoal briquettes and said nothing,
the taxi driver who hounded me
for the fare when I was
running away barefoot covered in blood,
and the cops!
I slept at the park for two nights,
freezing.
Not a single person asked me
if I was okay.
Not even one person.
SISYPHUS
Taxi!
The police station. Go!
-Is that blood?
-What?
It is blood.
Hey, what happened?
Han Tae-sul… He barged into my place and--
-Did you bring your apology letter?
-He shot me.
I told you to write an apology letter,
not to fight.
-No, hear me out!
-What the heck happened?
-Hey! You punk!
-Han Tae-sul shot me!
-Han Tae-sul shot me.
-Detective, he didn't pay his fare.
-Hey, mister.
-You bastard!
He shot me!
Shut up, you prick! Stop! Enough!
Did you pay your taxi fare?
No. But Han Tae-sul…
Have you lost your mind?
Why would he shoot you?
That's…
That I don't know.
What a total lunatic.
Look, you must repent
when you've done something wrong.
What you're doing is defamation.
You piece of trash.
I told you to write an apology letter,
not to talk such bullshit!
You jerk, you'd better pay me!
-Get your act together.
-You scumbag!
-Hey, snap out of it!
-You punk!
-What's with you?
-What's your problem?
-What are you doing?
-You'd better pay me!
-Hey, you punk.
-Pay your fare!
-Hey, stop! Get him!
-Pay me at once!
I kept racking my brain.
To figure out
why the heck you tried to kill me.
I thought it was unfair.
I didn't think I'd done anything
to deserve that.
You tell me, since you're smart.
Did I do something
to deserve getting shot? Did I?
But you know,
it turned out
the reason didn't even matter at all.
Because the world
is an unfair place to begin with.
-Look! Grab this.
-That's so cool.
Even if you shoot me, I'm the bad guy.
Yes, you're right.
This world has always favored you
and hated me.
I mean, what other reason could there be?
I will not die at your hands.
Our country is under attack.
The highest level of
national security alert has been issued.
The Wolsong Nuclear Power Plant
was first hit,
and nuclear bombs are being dropped
all over the country.
Even the metropolitan area
has been hit by…
That's why you want to start a war?
People don't like you,
so you want to wipe them out?
Not all of them.
I survived, you know.
Because I'd sealed
all the windows shut to die,
I was protected from the nuclear fallout.
I ate anything that was edible.
I held out like that for two months.
It was difficult to keep track of time,
so it could've actually been
shorter or longer.
When I had nothing left
to eat or drink,
I went outside.
The outside world had become so quiet.
It was dark, even during the day.
And there was no one.
Those who belittled me,
all those arrogant show-offs
and obnoxious jerks.
They were all gone.
That moment, I realized
that those jerks were the ones
who deserved to die,
not me.
Do you know that you're a little weird?
It's too bad.
I should have paid more attention
to my employees' welfare.
I'm sorry, but you're fired, you psycho.
Let's see.
Darn it.
SHUTTING DOWN
SYSTEM BOOTING
"Maintain strict security"?
These fools. Strict, my ass.
I got in right away.
PERSONNEL INFORMATION
Six thousand employees
work in this building now.
And 300 of them have been here
since day one.
If I exclude female employees,
there are 170.
Age 53, give or take 3 years.
SEARCH RESULT: NONE
What?
MAINTAIN STRICT SECURITY
"Security."
You sneaked into my place
and wrote "Don't look for your brother."
How did you do that?
Oh.
You see,
I can get in anywhere.
Someone who can get in anywhere.
Someone who was always around me
and who could get in anywhere.
HUMAN RESOURCES
Then he must've had a high position.
Why can't I find him?
No, I got it all wrong.
Damn it.
Shit.
CLEANING STAFF ROOM
CODE OF CONDUCT
BE QUIET AND UNOBTRUSIVE
Darn it!
Hey, you must watch a lot of movies,
seeing how you like places like this.
First time down here, right?
I've been waiting for you here
all this time.
I kept dropping hints.
Had you paid more attention
to your surroundings,
you would have already found me.
Well, in any case… I'm here now, right?
Come over here.
All you do is talk like
you're better than everyone else
and act like you know everything.
Damn it.
Do you know why
everyone addresses me so politely?
Because I've worked here
since the day this company was founded.
Aside from you,
the founder of the company,
I've been here the longest.
Once again,
I won this game of hide-and-seek.
I won last time too.
The time before that too. And I won again.
I told you not to get ahead of yourself.
The game isn't over yet.
Just finish coding the uploader.
Then I'll return your brother safely
as I promised.
You jerk.
Soon, there will be drugs
that can wake him up.
We need him to get on the uploader
and go find his little brother
for this story to begin again.
Hey.
-What are you really after?
-What?
Oh, what was it?
Right!
I just can't stand your obnoxious face.
Stay away from me.
Get lost!
Those eyes…
You're no different from the other kids.
That arrogant face.
Gosh, I really couldn't stand it.
So I wanted to see, even just once,
you falling apart.
Your family, friends, business,
and even love.
If I take away everything you have,
and if you end up like me,
what kind of face will you make then?
Hey, Sigma.
Let's put an end to this today.
This could be the beginning.
The beginning and the end
are always intertwined.
Just like a poor little puppy
that chases its own tail in circles.
You'd better get used to this darkness.
Because that is…
all you have left.
No matter how many chances they're given,
the result is always the same.
Because people repeat the same mistakes
tens of thousands of times.
Regret…
That is what makes the uploader exist.
Is this also part of your grand scheme?
Of course.
Oh, I see.
Soon, the war will kill
tens of millions of people.
It was all part of your plan?
You see, the war started
with just one missile.
The one that hit Wolsong. Boom.
Then it took on a life of its own.
The Ministry of National Defense
struck the North.
Then the North struck back.
The US shot missiles at them,
and so did China.
Kaboom. Then everyone died overnight.
Do you know what's interesting?
Everything burned to ashes,
but this church survived, unscathed.
I suppose God really does exist.
That's why I built the uploader
in the basement here.
Is everything okay?
It's stable.
The data is within
the acceptable error range.
No, I meant,
with you.
What about me?
Yes, I'm okay.
I don't buy that.
How can you be okay?
Everyone up there will die tomorrow.
Right, Baltimore.
Have you given it some thought?
Eddy.
By the time we return from there,
it'll be spring here.
Why won't you go? I made it.
I told you.
There's nothing between us now.
Besides, my mom and I must stay here.
Is it because of that thing?
What do you mean?
-You want to get on that thing.
-Why would I?
You regret everything.
-Don't overreact.
-It's because of Tae-sul, isn't it?
Look at us talking about Tae-sul again.
You see?
While dating you, there wasn't a day
we didn't talk about him.
-Seo-jin, you told me to make that thing--
-Let go!
You built it because of me?
No, don't act all naive.
It was because of Tae-sul.
You want everything that he has.
The CEO position, the uploader,
and me. Am I wrong?
Loser.
This is why
you can never beat Tae-sul.
ON GOVERNMENT DUTY
This is nuts.
I only want Han Tae-sul.
I don't need Seo-hae.
So take her and leave Korea
so she won't bother me.
Over there.
What? The Hangang Bridge?
My house was there. A bunker below it.
Gosh.
What is this?
SHELTER
I think this is it.
Seo-hae! Are you inside?
Sis!
Darn it.
Seo-hae!
Sis!
Jae-sun. Is that you?
Jae-sun, I'm here!
Seo-hae? Is that you?
Gang Seo-hae!
I'm locked inside. Let me out.
Are you all right?
But I can't open the door.
Look for the keypad.
The passcode is my birthday.
It's 120930.
Over here!
How do I open this door?
There's a lever on the right.
Are you all right?
How did you get here?
I'll tell you later. Let's hurry.
Wait.
Choi Jae-sun found the girl.
The team nearby can get there
in three minutes.
Just keep an eye on them for now.
-Keep me updated on their location.
-Yes, sir.
We have 250811's current location.
South of the Hangang Bridge.
Agents in the area,
keep monitoring the suspect.
I was at home, and those
Control Bureau jerks barged in again.
I saw this car as I was running away,
so I got in.
Darn it.
The person you are calling is unavailable…
I must go to Tae-sul.
Where are we going?
-Where are we going?
-To the airport.
The flight leaves in three hours.
Let's go to my family's place.
My mom and Go-eun are waiting.
It's a house with many rooms.
-They already decorated your room.
-Jae-sun.
Oh, and there's an outdoor swimming pool.
Awesome, right?
-Pull over.
-The weather's amazing too.
The fine dust level was only 15 yesterday.
I told you to pull over!
It's a two-story house.
The entire second floor is yours.
We're planning to get a dog.
They said the neighborhood is quiet
and the neighbors are nice.
So…
-please come with me.
-Who put you up to it?
He said you'll die.
Who is "he"?
Sigma.
If I don't leave with you,
my mom and Go-eun will…
Han Tae-sul started all this,
so let him deal with it.
If I run away, everyone here will die.
Please…
Then what about you? You'll die too.
Jae-sun, Tae-sul can't do this alone.
Gosh…
If you don't do it, someone else will.
No one will appreciate this.
Why are you so reckless?
Aren't you scared of dying?
I am.
I am scared. But…
What scares me more
is surviving alone in the world.
You have no idea what it's like.
If you lose everyone you love
and survive alone,
do you think you'll be happy?
Trust me.
I'll save everyone. All of you.
I'll get out here.
Hey, wait.
Jae-sun!
Why do you keep calling?
You'll see us every day.
Mom, Go-eun, I'm sorry.
Looks like I need more time.
Why?
Mom, I put all the money
into your account.
Hey, what's going on?
Take good care of Mom. Hey, Mom.
Jae-sun!
-Mom, I'm sorry.
-Jae-sun!
ON GOVERNMENT DUTY
Don't die.
You went through hoops to return.
You should go to nice places
and eat good food.
I'll take you to all the nice places.
Where should we go first?
Jae-sun.
Jae-sun…
Go ahead and kill me.
You already killed my mom,
so kill me and everyone else.
You murderer. Kill me now!
Don't move.
I'll kill you as you wish.
The keys under the flower pot.
And the white dog in your yard.
Your mother couldn't see well,
and you cooked instant noodles for her.
Your mother…
seemed at ease
as she was breathing her last.
Get lost.
Jae-sun, hey.
Seo-hae.
Am I dying?
No, you won't die.
This can be a little uncomfortable
at first.
But once you get used to it,
it's very nice.
Go.
No.
Hey.
Has Choi Jae-sun found Gang Seo-hae yet?
Choi Jae-sun is dead,
and Gang Seo-hae's on her way to Sigma.
All right. Well done.
This is my last mission.
Making sure everything's going
according to the plan.
If anything goes wrong,
I must revise the records,
so the next Sigma can read up on it.
That's what the Control Bureau does?
When I was working at the NIS,
I was sent out to surveil
the opposition party. To collect intel.
It was something that we always did,
off the record.
That's where I first heard
about the people from the future.
I was transferred to the Control Bureau
immediately after that.
The higher-ups promised me
that they'd ensure
my family's safety
if I finished the job quietly
until the last day.
Thanks to that, I couldn't even be there
when my wife died,
and my daughter hated me.
Gang Seo-hae said
she didn't kill my mother.
So?
I want to know the truth.
Okay.
I…
killed your mother.
I also killed the future you
who crossed over.
That woman is the prime suspect.
She's an illegal entrant.
She shot and killed your mother,
who couldn't even fight back.
I lied to you
so you'd join the Control Bureau.
-But why?
-Because that's what the report says.
I only followed the instructions
in the report.
You…
You bastard.
HWANG HYUN-SEUNG CASE REPORT
SHOT AND KILLED ON OCTOBER 31, 2020
SUSPECT: JUNG HYEON-GI
In Chinese,
"fate" and "order"
share the same character.
Do you know why that is?
It's because you can't disobey your fate.
This is my last order.
Shoot me.
I've been waiting for this day.
You were recruited as a gunner,
so you won't make a mistake.
Shoot me.
Don't move.
I'll kill you as you wish.
Get lost.
I won't shoot.
And I won't go back
after killing you because of regret.
I will not kill anyone…
or beat myself up.
No. You must shoot me.
Losing a parent is like
losing a part of yourself.
You feel dead even though you're alive.
YEAR 2035
This is the place.
Hang in there. We're almost there.
Okay.
Intruder alert.
Dad.
Go. Hurry!
Move back!
If this goes off, we'll all die! Move!
-Run on the count of three.
-No.
-One.
-Dad!
Two.
Stop.
Look who's here.
Can I guess your name?
Seo-hae. You're Gang Seo-hae, right?
Who are you?
Me?
The owner of this uploader?
Sigma?
That's right.
What are you doing here?
Trying to get on the uploader?
To do what?
I'll stop the war.
How?
I will save Han Tae-sul and kill you.
Hey, did you hear that? My gosh.
You can lower your guns. Just lower them.
Lower your guns.
Seriously, you're…
How cute.
You'll kill me?
Let them go.
Pardon?
They want to cross over. Just let them go.
Hey, your father's wound looks very deep.
He won't survive the uploader ride.
You should just stay here.
No. I won't go if we can't go together.
Dad.
What? Are you worried
I wouldn't let your daughter go?
Come on. You already know
that she'll get there safe and sound.
Don't listen to him.
-Okay.
-Dad!
Seo-hae.
I'll see you later.
Oh, wait. I almost forgot.
On the last day,
meet me at the church.
Seo-hae, wake up.
Dad.
Time to go. It's your turn now.
Anything that weighs over 30kg
is not allowed in.
Microbial substances, living creatures,
and explosive materials are not permitted.
We assume no responsibility
and shall not be liable
for any injury, death, and accidents
that occurs during your trip.
Let's go together, Dad.
I don't think I can go with you.
Tell me what I told you.
First, when you arrive.
-When you arrive!
-"Start running."
Do not let anyone catch you,
no matter what.
If you get caught,
just don't say anything.
Just pretend you can't talk. Okay?
Yes. But let's go together--
Second.
Hurry up!
"Do not trust anyone."
You never know who's your ally
and who's your real enemy.
Don't trust anyone. No one. Okay?
Okay.
Good. What was the third thing?
Come on.
-Number 250811!
-Coming!
Quick. What was it?
"Han Tae-sul."
Han Tae-sul.
Stay away from him at all costs.
You must not cross paths with him.
Don't even talk to him, okay?
Then what about Mom?
What if she dies?
We all die in the end.
But I can't leave you alone here, Dad.
When you get there,
you'll find lots of good food
and all of your favorite fruits.
Real fruit, not the canned ones.
So just go.
Eat everything you want.
And do whatever you want.
Just enjoy your life.
Promise me.
-Number 250811!
-Coming!
Promise me.
If you don't, I won't let you go.
Let's go.
Seo-hae.
The war already took place,
and it'll happen again.
It's not something you can stop alone.
Forget all about it
and run away to somewhere safe.
I'm letting you go
so you can live a happy life.
I love you, my dear daughter.
You should go.
Go on.
I will meet him.
I'll meet Han Tae-sul and stop the war.
I can do it.
We can do it, Dad.
Ready for transmission.
You'll be unstable for a while
after you arrive.
Why did you hide the girl?
I saw the future.
The future where I win.
You'll get shot in the head.
I do not think that will happen.
Finish coding the uploader.
We made slight changes to the capacity.
Thanks in advance.
Maximum density, 2,000kg per…
Are you sending something heavy?
Hey.
You used this to explode the nuclear bomb.
Am I right?
It'd be such a waste to only use this
to transport those lowlifes.
We should use it for things
that can make us money. Weapons and bombs.
Weapons are everywhere in the future,
but no one to kill.
Boom.
Gosh, I did consider doing it for you,
but I refuse to help you.
Soon, your girlfriend will get shot here,
and you'll cry your eyes out.
If you'll do it anyway,
why not just do it now?
Well, I do not think that will happen.
I'm not sure if you've heard this before.
"The future is already here.
You just don't know it yet."
Gosh, such a cliché.
Where is she now?
-Current location.
-Almost there.
-She's almost here, sir.
-Get ready.
What?
You didn't know that she'd come here?
Why bother hiding her?
You guys are in the palm of my hand.
Oh, what was his name?
Right, Sun. He's dead.
I had to infuriate her
to make her come here voluntarily.
Don't get too nervous.
It'll be quick.
Why must she make such a fuss?
She can just walk in quietly.
-What?
-What's going on?
She's here.
What?
Seo-hae is here.
Yes.
How many are outside?
Everyone except for the three of us
and those at the rear exit.
But I see four.
Gosh, I'm really impressed.
You came to save this guy,
knowing you'll die.
Very impressive.
Thank you very much
for coming here voluntarily.
You can't kill him.
Dropping the honorifics now?
What about you?
Shoot me. This is a golden opportunity.
What is it?
You can't do it?
I'll tell you why you're hesitating.
Because you love him.
You love him!
You two should thank me. I worked
very hard for you two to end up together.
Remember the day you first met?
Wasn't that so thrilling?
Han Tae-sul! Get down!
The woman who saved your life,
like destiny.
Isn't it so amazing?
Don't give me that look.
Once, I missed you on purpose.
-It's natural
-She had a wound somewhere here.
to develop feelings for each other
when you go through hardships together.
While helping and saving each other
and making sacrifices.
That's how love begins.
And once it begins, it can't be stopped.
You can't help but love him even though
you couldn't avenge your dad's death
because of him.
Tae-sul.
You must think you've chased me this far
because you're smart.
You're wrong.
All you did was follow the trail
of bread crumbs that I left for you.
It's you. The copilot on that flight.
What happened? Who did this to you?
The Control Bureau.
Are you on their side?
Among the e-mails, death threats,
and malicious comments he received…
SEO WON-JU
I told them not to use that photo.
Sigma.
Seo-hae!
Your destination is 48km away.
Turn it off.
I'm sorry, sir.
How lovely is this?
You will make the uploader now. Why?
Because you love her.
From beginning to end, all of it.
It was all part of my plan.
Oh, no. I won again.
I get it now.
No.
I knew it all along.
The uploader code.
Don't make the uploader.
If you don't, we'll win.
It's over.
Shoot her!
Han Tae-sul!
Whatever happens from now on,
just trust me.
Did you not expect this?
The future can change.
Subtitle translation by: Liya Choi
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs