Are you okay?
No.
I'm not okay.
I don't want this May...
to pass by without you.
(Congratulations on Your Engagement,
Hwang Hee Tae and Lee Soo Ryeon)
Excuse me.
May I ask why you're here?
It's nothing.
Wait.
Thank you for coming
such a long way.
- No problem.
- Congratulations.
When your children get married,
- remember to invite me.
- Yes, of course.
I promise to be there.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
- Congratulations once again.
- Thank you.
Whenever you hold a family event,
don't forget to invite me.
I'll be the first
to congratulate you.
Once again,
thank you so much for coming.
Soo Ryeon.
Our guests are about to leave.
Where is Hee Tae?
It's been a while
since I last saw him.
Did he get sick or what?
I sent him home.
What do you mean, you sent him home?
Well, he wasn't feeling well
since this morning,
so I told him to go home
and get some rest.
My goodness. But still,
how could he really leave?
Can you believe this?
(Episode 6,
A Cough, Love, And...)
What's wrong with Hee Tae?
I think he came down with a cold.
I see.
Myeong Hee was coughing
all day long too.
I guess it's because
the seasons are changing.
Things were so hectic...
that I didn't even notice
her leaving.
Did you say goodbye to her?
Both of us were so busy,
so I guess she just left quietly.
You know how Myeong Hee
doesn't like to bother others.
- Soo Ryeon.
- What?
You did great today.
Thanks.
It would've been nice
if Mother were here too.
Why can't I walk you
all the way home?
It's right over there.
We're almost here anyway.
And I don't want...
You don't want Jin A to see us
and cause a fuss?
Okay.
What are you doing tomorrow?
I need to work
after going to church.
Then I'll schedule my lesson
for tomorrow evening.
So I can bump into you
when you get off work.
Oh, why don't you just hand me
your work schedule?
So I can schedule
our dates accordingly.
Sure thing.
Gosh, I guess this is why
people write song lyrics.
Since we can't talk on the phone...
or look at a picture
when we miss each other.
The nights feel too long.
Can I take this with me?
So I can think of you.
What about me?
Shouldn't you give me something too?
I don't have anything to give you.
Shall I rip off a button?
I'll take this.
Hey, over there.
It's almost time
for the curfew siren.
What are you two doing
so late at night?
I'm sorry.
If you're not going to get a room,
go home already.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
- That's how the law is.
- Yes, I know.
- Okay.
Well, I'd better go home now.
Okay then.
See you tomorrow, Myeong Hee.
Get home safe.
Good morning, Father...
I heard
you weren't feeling well yesterday.
Do you feel better now?
Yes.
Do you think you can beat me
now that you're all grown up?
Don't be mistaken.
All you can do is block my hand.
No matter what you do,
I'm always one step ahead of you.
Also...
If you ever disappoint me
as my son...
in front of people like that again,
it won't end with a slap.
Do you understand?
Sir, you have a guest.
Gosh, you must've been tired
after the engagement ceremony.
You didn't have to.
I didn't get to pay my respects
before the ceremony,
and my father earnestly told me...
to bring these gifts to you myself.
What a precious gift.
- Please thank your father for me.
- Okay.
- Is the food ready?
- Yes.
Where's Jung Tae?
Jung Tae went to a church retreat
and will be back tomorrow evening.
Let's go eat then.
- You...
- Wait.
If you're going to slap me,
slap me on this side.
What did you expect me to do
after disappearing like that?
Do you know how hard it was
to come up with an excuse?
Sorry. Something came up suddenly.
I saw you last night...
leaving with Myeong Hee.
What are you two thinking?
Whatever it is,
isn't it none of your business now?
We got engaged like you wanted,
and we'll maintain this
until the factory is completed.
That's as far as we go.
Why is it none of my business?
Like you just said,
we have to maintain this situation.
If people find out
about your relationship,
the engagement and everything else
will be ruined.
Got it.
We'll be careful from now on.
Why do you sound so carefree?
To be honest, you guys are lucky...
that I was the only one who saw you.
What if our family
or one of our guests saw you?
How would I explain it?
Why are you so angry?
Who says I'm angry?
Come inside for some snacks.
- Okay.
Oh, dear.
Show me your photo albums.
I'd love to see how ugly
you were as a kid.
I don't have any photo albums.
Is there anything you do have?
Who's this?
It's my mother.
What?
Oh, not the one you saw downstairs,
but my birth mother.
That's the only photo of her
from before she got sick.
Goodness.
Why did you shove a photo
of your mother in the corner?
Frame it or something.
Gosh.
What about you?
I didn't see a single photo
of your mother at your place either.
That's because I hid all of them
because seeing them makes me...
miss her more.
I know the feeling.
How old were you
when she passed away?
I was 12.
Goodness. You were too young.
It must've been hard
to deal with all the events.
What events?
I mean, you must've missed her
on every sports day,
school entrance ceremony,
graduation, and such.
The only event
that I had to deal with...
without my mother was
my high school graduation,
and it was hard enough.
I was only forced to attend it...
because I was the valedictorian.
Into my heart
A sheep wandering
In the dark
Here you go.
- Thank you so much.
- Enjoy.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
- Enjoy.
- Dig in.
- Thanks.
- This is so good.
- Enjoy.
They all need to be washed, right?
Give them to me.
Hye Gun.
Is something wrong?
Why are you ignoring me?
What's the matter? Tell me.
- I saw everything.
- What do you mean?
At Soo Ryeon's engagement ceremony,
I saw you with...
Hee Tae.
How do you know each other?
No. More importantly,
what's going on between you two?
Hee Tae is Soo Ryeon's fiance.
And you're her friend.
- Hye Gun.
- Does Soo Ryeon know...
what's going on...
between you two?
Hello?
Master Hee Tae, this is for you.
Me?
Hello?
Hee Tae, are you feeling any better?
I feel like we haven't spent
enough time together.
How about we meet up this evening,
just us guys?
Well...
I'm sorry, but I already have plans.
Come on, don't be like that.
Please free up some time.
I promise it won't take long.
Well...
(Resume, Hong Yong Gil)
It's my cousin
that I once talked about.
About Changhwa Pharmaceuticals,
the president seems inexperienced.
Wouldn't joint management
be helpful?
I appreciate
your thoughtful opinion,
but his father, Mr. Lee Chang Geun,
is already participating
in the management.
I don't think they'll be interested
in joint management.
This isn't like you.
Are you already trying...
to protect your in-laws?
It's not like that, sir.
Thank you.
You know the president left for
the Middle East yesterday, right?
Emergency martial law
will be expanded soon.
The boat is about to set sail.
To get into the same boat,
this is your only chance.
Mr. Hwang.
Do you think the new government...
will only last for five years?
You need to look far ahead.
You're too good
to be stuck where you are now.
You're absolutely right.
I'd like to pour you one as well.
Good.
Let me pour you one.
One more?
- Another bottle, please.
- Coming up.
Cheers.
(Mokpo Skate and Rice Wine)
This is nice.
You can slow down if you want.
You don't have to drink
as fast as I do.
Goodness, you don't have to worry
about me.
Have two, okay?
So what's your plan now?
The wedding and everything.
Where will you live?
I guess we will go with
what our parents want.
Is that also why you had
an engagement ceremony?
Your parents made you do it?
What about Soo Ryeon?
From going on that blind date
to the engagement,
did she want all of it?
Listen, Hee Tae.
Just because you don't want
this marriage,
it doesn't mean you don't have...
any responsibilities and duties
to fulfill.
I believe I'm fulfilling
all my duties.
You can't say that...
when you ran away
from your engagement ceremony.
Also, you didn't run away alone...
that day.
(Congratulations on Your Engagement,
Hwang Hee Tae and Lee Soo Ryeon)
Excuse me.
May I ask why you're here?
It's nothing.
Wait.
Why did you want to see me today?
Whatever you're up to,
you should stop right now.
Don't do anything
you can't take responsibility for.
I don't think I'm doing anything
I can't take responsibility for.
Do you even know what it means
to take responsibility?
It means to make sure
no one gets hurt by your action.
Even if everyone around you
becomes devastated,
do you think it's no problem
as long as you're okay?
How can you be so reckless?
Let me ask you something.
Are you sure you're angry
because of Soo Ryeon?
What?
You can be responsible
and do your duty.
What's more important to me
is not having any regrets later on.
The last one.
Oh, it's just you.
I thought it was Hee Tae.
Is he not here yet?
I thought you had
a tutoring session this evening.
I have no idea what's going on.
Did he forget about it?
Hold on. How did you know
I had a session this evening?
Well...
I'm here!
You're late.
I was getting worried about you.
The thing is...
I did all the homework, but...
I couldn't finish writing down
all the questions I got wrong.
My gosh,
you finished all the homework?
I gave you a lot of homework.
Good girl, Jin A.
Hee Tae, did you drink?
Music is what?
- Math!
- That's right.
Go put on a song.
Show me your fine taste in music,
Director Jin A.
Okay.
Do you want a Korean song
or a pop song?
Hee Tae.
Hee Tae, wake up.
Wake up, Hee Tae.
Myeong Hee, this is the first time
I'm seeing you in my dream.
Gosh, I guess
you haven't sobered up yet.
Mr. Hwang.
Wake up and have some hangover soup.
Why am I here?
I told you to make
soybean sprout soup.
Who'd want to eat this spicy soup
first thing in the morning?
I didn't make it for you.
Just eat your breakfast
and go to school!
This is totally making
my hangover go away.
I knew he'd have
a discerning palate!
These Jeolla Province natives
don't know how good this is.
I'm also from Jeolla Province.
Born and raised in Gwangju.
Jeolla Province is famous
for good food indeed!
That's right.
You talk like a Seoul native.
I had no idea you were from Gwangju.
I guess you rarely use the dialect.
I do use it,
but my father is adamant about me
speaking with a Seoul accent.
Of course!
No wonder such a wise man
did a great job raising his son.
When my son was enlisting
in the army,
I also emphasized to him...
that he must be mindful
of his dialect.
Fortunately, my son is
half Gyeongsang and half Jeolla,
so he can use both dialects freely.
He's like those people
in border towns!
- Border towns?
- That's right.
I'm originally from Jinju.
It's too hot!
Hey, do you have a girlfriend?
Do you have a girlfriend?
I'm asking you
if you have a girlfriend.
Hey, I heard the girls who protest
sleep around a lot.
Come on. Tell me some stories.
Especially girls
who work in factories.
I heard...
they'd sleep with any college guys.
Have you hit on any factory girls?
No, I have not.
You look like you want to punch me.
If you don't have
any stories to tell,
then make some up or something.
How dare you glare at me?
Am I eating seaweed soup
with clams or sand?
They should've removed
the sand properly!
Darn it.
- Halt!
- 1, 2!
Hey.
Take a break.
This is exhausting.
Earlier...
Why did you do that?
I was going to take it up with him
anyway.
He always speaks ill
of Jeolla Province...
in front of this Gwangju native.
Elite colleges and Jeolla Province
are his trigger points, you know.
But because of me...
It's okay.
That jerk will be discharged
in a month anyway.
It's so nice
to talk comfortably like this.
My goodness.
My best friend is also from Gwangju.
You little...
Gwangju isn't a small town
where everyone knows everyone.
- Quick.
- Okay.
(Resume, Hong Yong Gil)
What is this?
Joint management?
Don't think too much of it.
It's so the investors
can put their worries to rest.
Mr. Hwang, I'm a businessman.
I've overcome all sorts of hardships
in this industry.
Bribing people in high places...
Sure, I was prepared for it
and will deal with it.
But this is different.
You're asking me to hand over
the business to this person.
This is practically robbery
without a gun.
With a gun, I'd say.
(Resume, Hong Yong Gil)
I suggest you make a choice
that will result in less damage.
Like a true businessman.
Myeong Hee.
I hope your hangover is gone.
Who did you drink with last night?
Just someone
who makes me uncomfortable.
Oh, your work schedule.
- Were you being serious?
- Yes.
- I'm off today and tomorrow.
- Really?
Then let's hang out the whole time.
I mean, not including the night.
We can meet up two days in a row.
Can we spend the night together too?
Myeong Hee! A call for you!
- Just a moment.
- Okay.
Hey, Myeong Hee.
What time does your shift start
today?
Oh, that's great.
Then...
can Myeong Soo sleep over
at your place tonight?
Your dad was going to pick him up
on his way home from the market,
but he's not feeling well.
What time should I pick him up?
Okay.
All right.
Let's head out now.
No? Why not?
What a coincidence.
I can't believe Hee Tae's brother...
is your roommate, Myeong Soo.
Is this uncomfortable for you?
I'm sorry I dragged you here.
Don't worry.
He has nowhere else to go anyway.
He's supposed to be at a church
retreat by this evening. Right?
When he glares at you like that,
he's your spitting image.
- That's not true.
Be polite to her.
That's so interesting.
They even say the same thing
at the same time.
Myeong Soo, dig in.
But don't eat too fast, okay?
Okay.
This boy is obviously growing
a lot faster and needs more food.
Come on. He's done growing.
I was just as tall as Myeong Soo
when I was 12.
Kids who grow later end up taller.
It's all nonsense,
so don't listen to him.
Eat up now.
Here. Try it.
Hurry up and eat.
By the way,
what is your relationship?
That reminds me.
Your brother recently
got engaged, right?
Wait, are you his fiancee?
What are you talking about?
We're just...
We're just friends. Eat up.
If you're just friends,
why are you so inseparable?
Gosh, what about you and Myeong Soo?
You two are just as inseparable
even though you're not engaged.
Hold on a second.
This is the last day
you can take it easy...
before the race, right?
Is there any place you want to go?
There is a place
I want to go with all of you.
We can do that.
Where is the place?
(Ticket Office)
I can't believe the first
of our precious two days together...
is passing by like this.
It's not like we were going to spend
the entire time together.
And I had a lot of fun.
Didn't you have fun?
Do you know this feeling?
The feeling when you're eating
sweet candy...
and one of your molars is aching.
You can't really enjoy the candy...
because you're distracted...
by the pain in your tooth.
Why do you hate
your brother so much?
You have no idea
how mean he usually is to me.
To me, it looks like
you're the one being mean to him.
What?
Jung Tae may be tall,
but he's still only 12.
Do you want to fight with a kid?
Are you 12 too?
Forget it. You don't understand.
He may be young,
but he can really be...
Come on. He pretends to be mature,
but he's still a little kid.
See? Does he look
like a grown-up to you?
There are things you can't hide
no matter how hard you try.
I think Jung Tae
wants to become close to you.
That kid? To me?
Gosh. No way.
That makes no sense.
Reach out to him first.
You're a grown-up,
not a 12-year-old boy.
Soo Ryeon.
(Jaeyoung Confectionery
Assorted Gift Set)
(Declaration for Democracy)
It's not okay to print
the first draft as it is.
I made some revisions
to the draft you gave me.
Do you mean you printed all these...
by yourself?
I thought you'd need more flyers...
for the upcoming street protests
and rallies.
I got so much arm exercise...
from running the mimeograph.
Do you see this?
I can beat anything now.
After putting in so much work,
you must be disappointed.
Not at all.
I just feel bad
that I can't fight next to you.
Anyway,
I'll be printing flyers in my room.
Let me know if I can help you
with anything.
Thank you so much.
By the way,
are you okay?
What?
I mean...
Hee Tae and Myeong Hee.
She...
told you too?
What do you mean? A woman problem?
I don't mean to badmouth
your future brother-in-law,
so this is a little awkward,
but you know
his family is quite complicated.
It wouldn't hurt to look into it
before Soo Ryeon marries him.
Who knows?
He might have another woman
in Seoul like his father did.
You're going too far.
You can never be sure.
He's used to it.
Even after he gets married,
what if he seduces
an innocent lady...
and has a child with her
or something?
Enough of that.
Just bring me
last year's financial statements.
There are things you can't hide
no matter how hard you try.
I think Jung Tae
wants to become close to you.
What are you looking at?
Aren't you tired of hating me yet?
What about you?
Aren't you tired
of living with us yet?
Not at all. I love it.
I'm going to live with you
for the rest of my life.
Leech.
Let me ask you something.
Why do you hate me so much?
You give me no choice.
When someone hates me,
I can't help but fight back.
So don't show it.
Just ignore me.
Think of me as a gardener
who eats with you.
You keep pretending
you're the real son.
People call my mom a mistress
since you moved in.
They say I'm the son of a mistress.
My parents and I
are the real family.
I'm the legitimate son!
Is that what made you so anxious?
Gosh, you...
You are still a kid indeed.
(The 61st Preliminaries
of the National Sports Festival)
You're right.
No matter how hard I try to hide it,
I can't change the fact
that I was born out of wedlock,
and you're the legitimate son.
So you don't need to be anxious.
Okay?
Don't tell anyone about Myeong Hee.
I'll do the same about the retreat.
I wasn't going to tell anyone
anyway.
Really?
Myeong Hee, would other people
think that we look alike too?
Like Jung Tae and his brother?
What? Me and this little bear?
We don't look alike at all.
Soo Chan?
That must be your baby brother
you told me about last time.
He looks just like you
when he smiles.
You think so?
By the way,
why were you waiting for me?
Myeong Hee.
What's going on between you
and Hwang Hee Tae?
It's okay.
Mistakes can be rectified.
You're being fooled by him
right now.
It's...
not a mistake.
And I'm not being fooled.
Myeong Hee, Hwang Hee Tae is...
not a good person.
You should not get involved
with him.
But it is the choice I made.
All my life,
I put others first
and gave up on what I wanted.
I didn't have the courage
to do otherwise.
And for the first time in my life,
I mustered up my courage
and chose Hee Tae.
Even if people bash me for it
and hurl stones at me,
I will put up with it...
since I made the choice.
But why...
Why must you put up with people...
pointing their fingers at you
because of a jerk like him?
I'm sorry.
Just try them on.
Come on.
How pretty.
Myeong Hee, you made it.
Well, go on in.
Okay.
Hey, mister. Take this off at least.
Soo Ryeon.
Do you like Hwang Hee Tae?
Gosh, you're drunk.
What's with this random question?
Answer my question.
Do you like Hwang Hee Tae?
Why would I get engaged
to someone I don't even like?
Then what about him?
Does he like you?
I don't know. Just sleep.
Goodness.
You and Myeong Hee both. Why...
Why fall for such a jerk?
I said I can take you there.
Come on. I'm not a baby.
I told you, if I had a map,
I could walk all the way
to our home in Naju.
You stubborn rascal.
Watch out for cars.
You made sure
to pack everything, right?
Yes, don't worry. Just bring some
fried chicken next time.
You don't need to walk me out.
Bye!
I knew it!
Did you forget something again?
I'm sorry about last time.
I know it was an important event.
You two...
Do you really have to do this?
I understand you like each other.
But did you have to make it obvious
to Hye Gun and my brother too?
Must you make me look like an idiot
and cause all this fuss?
Soo Ryeon,
I'm not trying to make a fuss.
About Hye Gun and Soo Chan...
You're leaving anyway!
What?
You're leaving in less than a month.
You're only here
for a few more weeks.
But to my family and me, this is...
This all sounds too familiar.
So if I leave,
all will be good again,
like that time?
What?
Myeong Hee.
Is the priest at your church...
one of the priests who got arrested?
I've got a good idea.
Do you want to do it with me?
What is it?
(End the Oppression
of Religious Leaders!)
Hey, Hyun Ju. Read this.
Take a look.
- Read this.
- You're here.
You're early. Read this.
Kim Myeong Hee.
Come with us.
- Why...
- Come on.
Myeong Hee.
- Hey.
- What?
I heard Myeong Hee submitted
a letter of withdrawal today.
You know, because of the protest.
- But why just her?
- I don't know.
Is that...
what you thought this whole time?
It must've been awful
to have to hide it...
while acting like a friend
to my face all these years.
My gosh! You scared me.
I nearly jumped out of my skin!
You speak with the Jeolla dialect
whenever you're startled.
I wouldn't be startled
with the Seoul dialect, would I?
Goodness.
Hold on.
I came early,
but you got here earlier than I did.
I guess you missed me a lot.
No!
It's not that.
Today's our first official date.
Is there anything you want to do?
They're all just ordinary things.
What do you want to do?
Well...
If I tell you,
are you willing to do anything?
Gosh.
What?
"Love and Peace?"
(Love and Peace)
- Don't come so close.
- What?
Myeong Hee's favorite butter bread.
Goodness, Hee Tae.
What? Stop taking them.
What are you doing?
Look at you. You look so stupid.
Here. Eat all of this.
("Like the Last Wildflower")
(Resume, Hong Yong Gil)
A joint management with someone
I don't even know?
What is this...
I know.
I understand giving out bribes
is an old custom,
but getting involved like this
is an abuse of authority.
I can never allow this, Father.
Do you think I don't know that?
I had no choice this time.
No matter how filthy it is,
what can we do?
We're about to become a family,
so we must oblige.
We shouldn't let this drag on.
Let's call off
Soo Ryeon's engagement.
What are you talking about?
That punk Hwang Hee Tae...
is seeing someone else.
"Completing the lyrics for my song."
Wait. I requested this song.
Okay then.
What else do you want to do?
What else?
Oh, I need to go to Naju.
It's been a while since I went home.
All I did was call.
I'm planning on visiting
when I'm off next time.
Okay.
"Visit home in Naju."
Open parenthesis, "With Hee Tae."
What? Why would you go there?
How will you introduce yourself?
What do you think?
I'll say I'm your boyfriend.
Once I put my mind to it,
I can make adults love me.
It's just that
I don't actually do that very often.
Promise me
we'll go to Naju together.
Let's see. What else is there?
We have so many things to do.
The song you requested
sounds so nice.
What's the title?
I'll tell you if you tell me first.
Mine is Nogoziri's "A Cup of Tea..."
Not the song you requested.
I mean what you've been thinking of
all day...
to wear those sad looking eyes.
I'm making so many people suffer...
just for my own happiness.
That's why whenever I feel happy,
it feels as if I've become
a bad person.
You should've told me.
Why are you hiding your pain?
You're hiding your pain too.
In case you'll seem regretful
if I see you in pain.
I have no regrets.
But it's not like there's no pain
just because we don't regret things.
Even if we don't seem strong
or happy,
I hope
we can show each other everything.
Gosh, you're in trouble now.
I'm actually a real sissy.
I'm going to whine all day
from now on.
Sure, I'll hear you out.
Anyway, what is the title
of this song?
(Declaration for Democracy)
Let's become one
Let's gather together and become one
(End the emergency martial law!)
- Let's take a step forward
- We will continue to stay strong
- And fight for democracy
- Let's keep marching forward
What is going on?
I hope you don't get shocked.
I heard your fiance
is seeing someone else.
Since this is your son's fault,
let's not make matters worse
and end it here.
Does your daughter know
nothing about this?
If she knew that...
Would she have gotten engaged?
So, you had no idea
Hee Tae was seeing someone else...
or who that woman was?
You had no idea whatsoever?
I have no excuse.
It's all my fault for
failing to raise my son properly.
However, our families
have finally managed to be united.
How can we end everything
because of one setback?
If you give me a chance,
I'll take responsibility
and sort everything out.
I never had a chance to take
two days off like this.
I guess everyone is like this,
but I didn't have enough
vacation days to begin with.
There's this junior nurse
named In Young.
She's a newbie
and clumsy with her work...
so everyone keeps making me
work with her...
I'm boring you, aren't I?
What? No.
I was enjoying listening to you.
Keep going.
Just let me know if I'm boring you.
You didn't say anything,
so I kept blabbering.
It wasn't boring.
I'm really okay.
If you're okay,
what are those sleepy eyes?
Come on. Didn't we promise
to tell each other everything?
Hey, Sissy. How could you?
It's just that I'm anxious.
I'm so happy right now.
This type of happiness...
was never something I could have
all my life.
It's like I'm flying
really high in the air...
until I suddenly crash.
It makes me anxious.
I know it's silly and absurd.
I can't walk you all the way home
today either, can I?
See you tomorrow.
(City bus)
(Youth of May)
I'd like to report a missing person.
Has it ever occurred to you
that she might be avoiding you?
I'm sorry you came
all the way here...
but couldn't meet Myeong Hee.
Are your parents aware
that you're seeing Myeong Hee?
Why are you asking that?
The Defense Security blocked
her passport and visa applications.
I have something to tell you.
I lied.
- Lee Soo Ryeon, you little...
- Father.
Her only fault is
that she got involved with me.
It's too early to get scared.
I haven't even begun yet.
Please just let her live her life.