Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 2]
Young Master Pei, why are you still here?
the general and the Buddhist master are playing chess for a few days, so I'll wait here during this time.
This Buddhist Temple has four gates in north, south, east, and west directions.
How will you know which gate the general will leave from?
This...
Please tell me.
How can I predict what General Su thinks?
Unless... you wait outside the chamber where General Su and Buddhist Master are playing chess without stepping away.
Then I will wait outside the chess chamber without stepping a single step away.
General Su ordered that you cannot step inside the temple.
General Su only said that I cannot step inside.
He didn't say I couldn't enter.
My courtesy name is Shouyue, meaning "keeping promise," so I will definitely keep my promise.
Hey, what are you doing?
If General asks about it in the future, you will have to testify for me.
I will not step a single step inside the temple.
It isn't breaking my promise. Now that I've already entered inside,
I hope you'll tell me where the chess chamber is.
I wonder which young lady's embroidery skill
can actually turn out such life-like result.
You, you, you've really hurt me greatly.
Brother!
Brother, how
I don't know either. They are playing blind chess.
What? The general and the Buddhist master are playing blind chess?
Becuase it is blind chess, that's why others
have no idea when the chess game will finish.
Buddha, everyone says you can protect the good people.
My mother is the best and kindest person in this whole world.
Now that my mother has run into dangers.
I am very worried about her.
I am also very afraid, and don't know the future
is lucky or disasterous. Please show a sign, Buddha.
[Bad]
[Good]
[Number 19 - Good]
Isn't this the handkerchief that I embroidered?
Why is it here?
It must be that Buddha has noticed my sincerity
and manifasted a sign to help me.
What Buddha wants to say must be in this devination stick.
[Number 19 - Good]
Thank you, Buddha, for your blessing. As long as my mother is safe,
I will have no more fear.
This little girl looks so young,
but she is so skilled that she can embroider such a lifelike camilla flower.
You've waited for three days here,
but you failed at the last moment.
With such little skill,
how can you want to be my disciple?
I am ashamed, so I concede my loss.
I was going to just leave,
but I also want to know something.
Why did you change that little girl's devination stick?
Replying to General,
that little girl clearly has encountered a difficulty in her life.
Regardless of what the devination stick says,
it won't change her situation.
But a good devination stick will give her the courage to face the danger.
I saw that she was really afraid,
so I wanted to give her some courage.
Tell me then, what is courage?
Courage means
you would do something even though it cannot be done.
Years ago, General Su led two hundred cavalrymen and dared to ambush the camp of East Turkestan
and made their Khan run away in a panic.
General Li's troops came after that
and were able to kill more than 10,000 of the enemies and took more than 100,000 prisoners in a great victory.
May I ask, didn't General Su do something that you knew could not be done?
Clearly there is nothing that is for certain in this world.
It just depends on how you do it.
Excellent!
You said it well!
I'm accepting you as disciple!
Really? General Su is really accepting me as disciple?
Master, please let me bow to salute you.
My good nephew.
This nephew Pei Xingjian greets Madam Yang.
Madam, how has your health been?
No need for such formalitiy. You've endured a hard journey from the faraway Shanxi.
Yuanhua greets Older Brother Pei.
It's been many years, Mother has always mentioned Brother Pei.
We've missed you.
Greetings, Younger Sister Wu.
My father was old friends with Uncle Wu. My father died early.
When I was young and living in Chang'an, I was taken care of by Uncle and Aunt.
Uncle Wu passed away three years ago.
I was far away in Hedaodong and couldn't come to pay my respect.
This time, I came to participate in the imperial exam and will live in Chang'an from now on.
That's why I came to visit you in order to burn an incense for Uncle
and also greet Madam and younger sister.
My good nephew, you are thoughtful. Come, sit down.
Please.
This disciple greets Teacher.
It's been seven days.
I wonder if Teacher has modified
the pheasant robe well.
Teacher really has masterful fingers and divine needles.
(T/N: highly skilled)
This disciple is truly far behind.
Teacher, please teach me.
How can this disciple ever reach your level of expertise?
Your skill is already very good.
But the highest level isn't attained by the fingers,
but by the heart. Once your heart can attain that level,
your dressmaking skill will also reach a higher level.
Ultimately,
Teacher still wouldn't show me everything.
That's why you use these mysterious words
to refuse me?
If you really think so, then I don't need to explain.
This pheasant robe is enough for you to fulfill your duty.
Do not forget the agreement between us.
Do not ever mention to anyone that I have a daughter.
Thank you, Teacher, for helping me.
What Teacher has ordered me, of course
this disciple will hold it to heart.
Talented Lady Wu, you are really beautiful.
When you wear this auspicious gown, you look like a fairy from the painting.
I could not have imagined that you are so skilled at this young age.
After I've entered the palace, I will send for you
and make clothes only for me. Do you want to?
My mother has said that the palace is the most extravagant and richest place.
It has the most beautiful halls, the most luxuriant clothes,
and the most briliant jewelry.
But, it is the heaviest shackel
and the strongest prison. I don't want to live in a prison where I have no freedom.
Where do you want to go then?
Mother said that Gaochang is her hometown.
It is truly the most beautiful place in the world.
We can live a free life in Gaochang.
Your mother is right, but not entirely right.
Freedom is not only about high sky, huge land,
being carefree.
The palace is the most luxuriant place
but also the place with the most power.
Why should I talk about this with a little child?
Perhaps it's because we really get along.
I really like your personality.
That's why I couldn't help but speak of these things with you.
Liuli, don't call me Talented Lady Wu from now on.
Just call me Older Sister Wu then.
Older Sister Wu, even though I've only stayed with you for the short seven days,
but I also like Older Sister very much.
Your dream is in Gaochang,
but my dream is in the palace.
Now that you have this older sister,
but it seems that we may not be able to see each other again.
I hope that we will each get our wish.
You and your mother can live a simple happy life.
And I, will stand at the summit of power one day,
not only be the master of my own life,
but also have the freedom to discuss mountains and rivers.
(T/N: decide on national affairs)
[Hall of Gentle Breeze]
Greetings, Consort Yang.
Is there a reason for Attire Chief Lin to come here today?
This servant is here to present a gift to Consort Yang.
A gift?
Please look, Consort Yang.
This pheasant robe is a celebratory gift from the Bureau of Imperial Attire to Consort Yang.
We wish for Consort Yang to reach the seat of empress soon,
and be the motherly role model for the world.
This is a gift from the Bureau of Imperial Attire?
Yes.
This consort greets Your Majesty.
Greetings, Your Majesty.
What a most beautiful pheasant robe for the empress!
If I didnt see it with my own eyes, I wouldn't have believed it.
So you've been so anxiously eyeing the empress position?
Your Majesty, please judge wisely.
I've never ordered the Bureau of Imperial Attire to make the pheasant robe.
It-It's the Bureau of Imperial Attire that did it without my knowledge.
I am innocent. Please, Your Majesty, judge wisely
and vindicate me.
Making the pheasant robe is such a serious matter. How could you not have known beforehand?
Your Majesty, I am willing to swear to Heaven,
that I never ordered the Bureau of Imperial Attire to make the pheasant robe.
If Your Majesty won't believe me,
I am willing to die to prove my innocence!
Consort Yang!
- A'Chuan, hurry and call for the Imperial Physician.
- Yes.
You created this trouble. Hurry and admit guilt now so as not to drag down the entire Bureau of Imperial Attire.
I am a member of the Bureau of Imperial Attire. If I am convicted,
how can you stay safe yourself?
Speak.
Whose idea was it to make the pheasant robe?
In front of His Majesty, you should tell everything clearly.
Did I order you to make the pheasant robe for the empress?
Reply-Replying to Your Majesty,
Consort Yang never ordered the Bureau of Imperial Attire
to make the pheasant robe for the empress.
If she didn't do it,
who ordered you then?
Your Majesty...
Your Majesty,
it was Zhuo Jinniang.
It was this servant Zhuo Jinniang's Teacher,
the former Attire Expert, Madam An.
Madam An?
Your Majesty, this pheasant robe for the empress
is made by my teacher, Madam An, the Number One Needle in the World.
Teacher's skill is renowned in the world, and her embroidery is peerless.
Other than Teacher, no one else can embroider such an exquistely beautiful pheasant robe.
This servant would not dare to lie.
I remember this Attire Expert An.
Back then, Empress Zhangsun liked the gowns she made very much.
But didn't she receive the permission from the late empress years ago
to leave the palace?
Replying to Your Majesty, my teacher was impulsive back then
and begged the late empress to let her leave the palace.
But atter she left the palace, she couldn't handle the difficult civililan life and quickly regretted.
But she couldn't find a good opportunity to return to the palace.
A few days ago,
there were many rumors within and outside the palace that Consort Yang was about to become the empress.
Teacher must have heard those rumors and wanted to appease Consort Yang
so that she could return to the Bureau of Imperial Attire, that's why she exceeded the etiquette boundary to make this robe.
She order this servant to offer it to Consort Yang.
When Teacher gave me this pheasant robe, she only said that
it was a gown that she especially made for Consort Yang.
She told me to personally offer to Consort Yang. I didn't inspect it clearly first
and brought it into the palace.
I almost cause Consort Yang to be innocently convicted.
I should be dead. Please have mercy, Your Majesty. Spare me, Consort Yang.
I almost mistakenly blamed you.
Your Majesty.
- Guards!
- Present.
Drag out these two servants from the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Hand them to the Chief Eunuch to question their crimes.
Your Majesty, no, this incident has nothing to do with me, I'm innocent!
Your Majesty, I was momentarily careless and got used by my teacher and almost hurt Consort Yang.
Although I should die and still not clear my guilty, but, Your Majesty,
if this incident is blamed onto the Bureau of Imperial Attire and more,
won't it substantiate all those speculation against Consort Yang? Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, so that Cosnort Yang is not misunderstood by the others,
- please spare this servant and I will repay by doing a good deed.
- Your Majesty, I didn't deliberately do it.
Wait.
Your Majesty is wise. Now that you've exonerated me,
I plea that Your Majesty
will spare these two servants from the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
If they are blamed,
I'm afraid that the rumors won't cease and there'll be further turbulence.
I don't want to cause more instability
within the palace over the matter of empress conferral.
Forget it then, I'll listen to you, Beloved Consort.
I'll temporarily pardon these two servants.
But that Madam An who has left the palace
but still cause all this trouble for her shallow fame,
she is truly despicable.
I order you two to assist the Court of Judicial Review
to arrest Madam An and thoroughtly investigate this incident.
- You can atone for your guilt.
- Thank you, Your Majesty.
Dalang! Dalang! Something really bad has happened.
The Court of Judicial Review's constables are here to make arrests.
Dalang!
Hurry and bring that divorce letter.
Attire Expert An, if you don't come out quickly,
we will go inside to arrest you.
Are you the Number One Needle in the World, Attire Expert An?
Yes, I am.
To appease the noble lady in the inner palace,
you crossed etiquette boundary to make the pheasant robe for the empress. We have both witness and evidence.
Do you acknowledge your crime?
Constable, you said that I secretly made the robe,
the witness and evidence are both present,
is she the witness?
Zhuo Jinniang, apparently you made a mistake when you tried to appease your higher-ups.
That's why you hurriedly disassociate your guilt
and hurriedly push me up as your scapegoat.
We are teacher and disciple. Where is your conscience?
We were teacher and disciple.
When did you ever treat me as a disciple and teach me everything?
Now that you've committed a high crime,
the nation's law will not tolerate you,
this disciple can't help but kill family for grand justice.
(T/N: place justice above personal relationship)
Teacher.
You are a smart person.
If you don't want to drag in your family members,
it's best that you admit your guilt quickly.
What I promised you before, I'll still abide by it.
If Teacher won't recognize the realities,
and randomly accuse others and refuse to admit guilty,
then don't blame me to be
unfaithful, unjust, and unfeeling.
Where is your husband? With something this big happening,
what, we don't even see his shadow.
Here, I'm here!
Kudi Yanzhong greets Constable from the Court of Judicial Review.
Reporting to Official, I discovered this An woman making clothes at home for the palace a few days ago.
I felt it was inappropriate at that time. Although I didn't know it was the pheasant robe,
I tried to dissuade her but she stubbornly did it her way.
I immediately wrote a divorce letter at that time
to divorce this An woman. Please look, Official.
From now on, the An woman and Kudi family
will not be related at all.
Every word I've said is true.
All the servants here and the neighbors can testify.
Take the An woman away.
Get away.
Female Officer, why are you back?
The An woman has a gold needle.
- Do you know where it's hidden?
- I don't know.
A'Cao, do you know?
If Husband doesn't know,
I wouldn't know at all.
The gold needle is an important evidence of the An woman's treachery.
If you dare to hide it, the entire household is punishable by death.
I don't dare to lie. I really don't know.
Don't know?
There are all kinds of tortures in the Court of Judicial Review.
Maybe they will help you remember where the gold needle is.
Perhaps the gold needle...
Perhaps it is with the daughter of the An woman, Liuli.
No.
You can't sacrifice the whole household's lives for one Liuli, right?
That's right.
Teacher's daughter.
How could I have forgotten such an important thing?
Speak! Where is Liuli now?
Former Female Officer An with the Bureau of Imperial Attire plotted treachery.
She has been arrested for treason by the Court of Judicial Review.
The An woman's daughter, Liuli, is an important witness to this case.
Someone has reported that Liuli is making clothes in your manor.
We have been ordered to arrest her, please help us.
Constable, we do not dare to block your investigation.
However, the fourth lady at the Wu Manor is the new Talented Lady conferred by His Majesty.
How can you barge into a noble lady's residence?
Please wait a moment to let us report about this matter.
Alright, go quickly to report. We will wait here.
None of us can bear the responsibily of delaying the Court of Judicial Review's work.
Yes.
Older Brother Pei!
Younger Sister Wu.
I just bid farewell from Madam,
and I was just about to come say goodbye to you.
I've inconvenienced you during the past few days of staying at your manor.
I've already found an inn where exam candidats stay. I'm moving there today.
Please wait, Older Brother Pei, I have something to ask for your help.
Young Sister Wu, what would you like me to do?
Liuli!
Older Sister Wu, has my mother come to pick me up?
Liuli, something bad has happened to your mother.
The constable is already outside our manor to arrest you.
Right now there is nothing more important to save your life.
I have already arranged a man to take you away. You must trust him.
Older Sister Wu, what's happened to my mother?
I beg you, Older Sister Wu.
I only want to be with my mother.
Liuli, listen to me. You are still a child and you can't save your mother.
If you stay here, it will only let you and your mother
both get embroiled into danger. Even know I don't know your mother,
but you told me before that your mother told you
to go to Gaochang to live a free life.
I believe that your moother's biggest wish right now
is definitely for you to stay live and live free.
No, I only want to be with Mother.
You can't barge inside! You can't barge inside!
Hurry and go!
Go! Hurry!
You can't barge inside! You can't barge inside!
You can't barge inside!
Greetings, Talented Lady Wu.
This servant really couldn't block these constables.
I heard that the constables from the Court of Judicial Review came to our manor to arrest some criminals.
How can our Wu Manor be connected with some criminals?
Constables, search carefully.
Search every room thoroughly.
It's important to arrest the important witness to this case of treachery.
We can't help but offend Talented Lady.
Please forgive us.
We've searched all the rooms. The criminal wasn't there.
We discovered fresh signs of horseshoes near the backdoor. Shallow on the left, deep on the right.
It seems that someone hurriedly took someone or some baggage in leaving.
- Chase!
- Yes.
Liuli, I can only do this much for you.
I hope that you'll stay safe and sound.
Capture them!
Move aside!
Hurry and catch up to them! Don't let them escape!
Kind person, go ahead and let me down.
The chasers are catching up. I don't want to drag you into this.
I definitely will not drag in Older Sister Wu. Thank you both.
Don't be afraid. I won't abandon you.
Kind person, what is your name?
Saving you is a simple gesture.
Don't mention it. You don't need to worry about it.
No need to know my name either.
Hide right away.
Hurry with the chase!
We must catch up to them. Don't let them get away!
Giddy up!
Chase!
Kind person, thank you.
Catch up!
Sorry.
She is so brave at such a young age.
I couldn't keep you safe.
I can't only hope that you will survive this calamity.
Don't let him get away!
Madam Cao, do you see her clearly?
Who is she?
She is...
She is the An woman's daughter, Liuli.
Bother mother and daughter are now in my hands.
I just don't believe that I won't find the gold needle.
Take her back first.
We couldn't catch up to that horserider. His face was covered and we couldn't see his face.
When we go back, how do we report to the higher-ups what happened during the arrest?
Wu Manor is rich and powerful.
Their daughter is also a newly conferred noble lady.
It's best that we don't offend them.
Besides, His Majesty means to
keep this pheasant robe case small and manageable.
Only the An woman will be blamed.
Now that this criminal is captured in the street,
we don't need to bother the Wu Manor.
Yes.
Bring her up.
Liuli!
She only fainted.
It's no big deal.
Liuli.
Teacher, are you willing now
to use the Number One Needle and the dressmaking secrets
to exchange with this disciple whose heart is not in the right place?
Once I get what I want,
I will definitely find a way to keep your daughter alive.
Zhuo Jinniang, you've sworn the oath
that as long as I am your scapegoat, you won't drag my daughter and other innocent people into this.
I can still remember your voice, but you would reneg so soon?
Are you even a human being?
To become the Number One Needle in the World
and sit in the seat of Attire Expert at the Bureal of Imperial Attire is my life's wish.
Not to mention taking the life of innocent strangers,
I would even sacrifice my own life for it.
You are so dilusional in a frenzy,
you will eventually get your retribution.
Zhuo Jinniang,
we have nothing more to say.
- Liuli, Liuli.
- Since Teacher
won't fulfill this disciple's wish,
then don't blame me
for being ruthless.
There are still four hours until sunrise.
Teacher, you still have some time to think it over.
After sunrise, I will come to ask you again.
Teacher, you have no other choice.
If you want to livle, you can only beg me.
Liuli.
Anyone? Anyone there, prison guard?
Anyone there?
Not sleeping in the middle of night, what are you being noisy about?
May I trouble you to ask Sun Decheng from the Courtyard of Misfortune to come here.
I would like to ask him to arrange a good funeral for me,
so that I won't have a bad fate in the next life
and can be reborn in a good family.
For the sake of the gold hairpin, I'll go there for you.
But, Eunuch Sun has an odd temper.
The gold hairpin is mine regardless if he comes or not.
I am dying soon, what's the use of keeping the gold hairpin?
Please go there for me.
It's actually her.
I didn't know that this little girl seeking the devination stick from Buddha
was actually for today's incident.
That day, I kept changing her devination stick,
did I actually help her or hurt her?
Such a smart girl, staying calm during danger,
and could even arrange matters thoroughtfully.
I hope that you will survive this calamity
and come to retrieve the gold needle someday.
Eunuch Sun is here. Say what you want to say quickly.
This is the death row. Once you're in, don't expect to leave here alive.
Don't play any tricks on me.
[Sun Decheng]
Eunuch Sun, I know that
my daughter and I are dying soon.
I beg you.
After we're dead, please
select a good coffin for us,
provide some daily items for burial,
so that we won't live a harsh life
in the netherworld.
As I've accepted your payment,
I will definitely do as you wish.
The Courtyard of Misfortune is the most heartless place,
but it's also a place that most emphasizes rules.
I rely on you then, Eunuch Sun.
Since everything has been talked about, Attendant Sun should leave quickly then.
After all, this is the death row. I can't do my job if you delay too long.
Oh yes, the prisoner next to you just died.
Can you please go ahead and take away the corpse?
It'll save me from running over there to tell you.
That person hasn't totally died.
The Courtyard of Misfortune works on sending dead people off.
But as long they are still breathing, we won't touch them.
- Otherwise it would bring back luck.
- But, Attendant Sun...
He will totally die in another two hours.
I'll let my disciples come over to collect the corpse at that time.
[Courtyard of Misfortune]
Master, that prisoner was clearly dead.
Why didn't we go ahead and bring him back?
[Courtyard of Misfortune]
Because, if he dies after another two hours,
two lives can be saved.
- Mother.
- Liuli.
Liuli, wake up.
- Mother.
- Liuli.
Mother.
Liuli.
Mother, Older Sister Wu said that you were in trouble.
I was so worried.
Mother is fine.
Mother, where are we?
I want to go home.
Liuli, be good, don't be afraid.
Every word that Mother is going to tell you,
you must remember it well.
Sun Decheng from the Courtyard of Misfortune looks cold but is warmhearted.
He is a good person, and he will save you.
From now on, you must listen to him.
Do you understand?
From now on, no matter what problems you run into,
you must be courageous and strong.
No matter how difficult or how harsh it is,
you must live on.
When you grow up, you must find a way to leave the palace
and live a free life.
Eunuch Sun will help you.
You must remember this,
don't ever try to revenge for me.
Remember this, Mother only wants you to be safe,
and grow up happily.
and live a life of happiness and freedom.
Understand?
Mother, why are you saying these things to me?
I only want to be with Mother. I only want to stay with Mother
and live a happy and free life.
Liuli.
You must remember what Mother said.
Mother, I only want to be with you.
I will listen to what you say from now on.
Please don't leave me behind.
Liuli.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
''Moon Legend'' - Singer: Zhou Shen
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations, reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relenting of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫