Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 3]
That housekeeper Sun is really weird wanting to do this too waiting for them to die.
If we took it earlier, wouldn't we need to come back again?
The door is unlocked. Take them away, it's really unlucky.
Yes! Yes!  We'll deal with it right now.
It's this way. Go.
Attire Expert An! Attire Expert An!
Housekeeper Sun sends this to you.
Liuli.
Eat this, quick.
Once you ate that pill, we'll be saved.
Trust Mommy.
Alright.
Lie down.
I practiced martial arts. I must hang a little longer.
Only that way it will seem real.
It's bad! It's bad! A prisoner hung herself!
Come and save her!
It's bad! A prisoner hung herself!
What's the ruckus about?
We passed by here when we recovered the corpse.
This person was already hanging there.
It looks this mother strangled to death her daughter first.
Then hung herself.
That mother is heartless enough.
She could even strangle to death her own daughter.
It's better than suffering and getting executed.
When the prisoner are alive, they are ours to deal with.
Once dead, they belong to your Courtyard of Misfortune.
Take them back together.
Saving me from going to report it to your master.
Yes! Yes! We will take those two prisoners.
Faster!
Be all quick.
Fast!
[Courtyard of Misfortune]
All get out first. Xiao Shunzi stay.
Yes!
Why did it take so long?
If we don't give them the antidote, I'm afraid they won't be able to wake up.
Attire Expert An said to wait a little longer to make it look real since she practiced martial arts.
So I delayed a little.
What did she say?
Attire Expert An said that your master is a kind man.
He wants to preserve everything.
But forgot that this time, what he should protect is himself.
If something happens to him, neither of us will be able to live.
Attire Expert An is a virtuous woman.
She would rather give up on herself
to protect her daughter.
Protect us.
Quick. Quickly give the antidote to the child.
Housekeeper Sun.We heard the criminal Madam An and her daughter committed suicide in fear of punishment.
Since the Bureau of Imperial Attire was ordered to cooperate with the Court of Judicial Review to investigate this,
Attire Chief Lin and I must examine the corpses.
And confirm Madam An committed suicide in fear of punishment.
And that there's nothing suspicious.
If you need to examine, please do it quickly.
Since the criminal already committed suicide,
then let's go back to report on orders.
Attire chief, please wait!
I heard there's a pill to pretend death.
After eating it, the heart stops beating, there's no more breathing.
It looks like death, but after a short time,
eating the antidote, they could wake up.
Gossip! That's sheer nonsense!
Where on Earth would there be such a pill? Did you really see it?
Madam An killing herself like this,
I feel uneasy.
Attire Chief, if we cut the weed without pulling out the roots,
I'm afraid of the future trouble.
Then, based on what you saw?
Cremate the corpses. Burning them to ashes saves us from all the troubles.
Even if they took a faking death pill, they can't call back their soul.
That's ridiculous!
All the dead that came into the Courtyard of Misfortune always have been buried.
There's no etiquette for cremation. It won't do!
Even if the Bureau of Imperial Attire have extremely big powers,
You can't change the etiquette of the Courtyard of Misfortune!
My apologies, Housekeeper Sun.
[Court of Judicial Review]
The Bureau of Imperial Attire is commissioned to help the Court of Judicial Review.
That mission order,
how many heads do you have to dare resist?
I finally understand why you absolutely wanted to cremate the bodies.
When Madam An and her daughter were sent to jail,
you must have already searched their bodies.
But you didn't find that golden needle that you want.
So figured out that they hid it in their corpse.
It is said that real gold don't fear fire. You want to use the public office for your personal gain.
Once you found the golden needle, you'll take it for yourself.
Only by clearing completely this affair,
can you and I rest easily.
Otherwise, I'm afraid there will be no end to our troubles.
Take her up. Burn them together!
Xiao Shunzi!
Eunuch Sun!
Eunuch Sun, your Courtyard of Misfortune has a blazing fire.
What is it for?
Eunuch Gao asked me to notify you.
Today is the auspicious day for the newly conferred Talented Lady Wu to enter the palace.
All funeral related ceremonies are forbidden in the palace
to avoid all filthy things.
Hurry! Extingush the fire!
Zhuo Jinniang, this matter ends here.
If the gold needle isn't inside the An woman's body, it wouldn't be inside her daughter's body.
No mother in the world would let her daughter
suffer the pain of swallowing a needle.
[Hall of Sunset Pool]
Talent Lady Wu greetings Your Majesty.
May Your Majesty live 10,000 years and many more.
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
So beautiful like a peach and pear.
Pure like the autumn's chrysanthemum.
The auspicious gown you're wearing is particularly alluring but not trendy, uniquely charming.
Talented Lady Wu, I bestowed you the name of Meiniang.
Do you like it?
Meiniang thanks Your Majesty for the bestowed name.
Thank you, Your Majesty, for the compliments.
[Eternal Peace Room, Courtyard of Misfortune]
Master, after such a long delay,
will the swallowed antidote still work?
I hope this child will be lucky.
Her mother's spirit in Heaven
will bless her to wake up soon.
Xiao Shunzi, hurry, water!
Child, you're awake.
Come, have a drink of water.
Child, don't be afraid.
I am Sun Decheng,
your mother's friend.
This is the Courtyard of Misfortune.
Sun Decheng from the Courtyard of Misfortune looks cold but is warmhearted.
He is a good person. He will save you.
From now on, you must listen to him.
Understand?
Where is my mother? I want to find my mother.
Child, child, don't be anxious, let me tell you slowly.
I have to tell you something.
Your mother...
Your mother is already
not here anymore.
Child, don't be sad.
We will be your family in the future.
Don't worry, we will definitely take good care of you.
You can't cry so loud.
You are still in danger.
You must not let other people know that you're still alive.
Child.
You must learn to be strong.
Your mother's last wish
was to let you live and live well.
From now on, you are my disciple.
We'll call you...
Xiao Douzi, alright?
From now on, you must forget that you are a girl.
Forget that you are Attire Expert An's daughter.
Forget that you are named Liuli.
This is the way that you can survive in the palace.
I don't want to live by myself!
I only want to be with Mother.
Child.
Look at this.
This is left by your mother before she died.
I know that you are feeling really sad now.
But, you must know that
your mother sacrificed her own life
so that your life is protected, child.
You must not disappoint her.
You must live on and live well.
Liulu, when you open this purse,
Mother will be gone already.
You must live on.
Don't revenge for me.
Eunuch Sun is the only person that you can trust in this world.
Salute him as your Foster Father.
Leave the palace once you reach the age of 18.
Go far from Chang'an.
Live a peaceful
abd free life.
Mother...
Mother, don't abandon me!
Mother!
[Bureau of Imperial Attire]
Greetings, Attire Expert Zhuo.
Please instruct us, Attire Expert Zhuo.
[11 years later]
[Courtyard of Misfortune]
[Talented Lady Wu]
Talented Lady Di, there isn't much friendliness in the palace.
You and I were like sisters here.
I didn't know you would depart first.
I came here today to send Older Sister off.
I know that you've always been frugal.
I brought over a pretty gown.
Consider it as my last token of sisterly bond to you.
- Eunuch Sun.
- Present.
Where did Talented Lady Di get this clothing?
I've never seen her wear this before.
Replying to Talented Lady Wu,
this must be the needlework by our Physician Dou.
Our Physician Dou specializes in dressmaking and embroidery.
All the brothers at the Courtyard of Misfortune say that his skills
- can surpass that of the Bureau of Imperial Attire—
- You talk too much!
Physician Dou?
Who is he?
Why would a physician in the Imperial Academy of Medicine do needlework?
Replying to Talented Lady Wu,
this Physician Dou is the Courtyard of Misfortune's
physician that does sanitation work for the corpses.
Even though he belongs to the Imperial Academy of Medicine,
but he is stationed at the Courtyard of Misfortune.
Most of the Imperial Physicians came from renowned medical families
with a noble status.
But our Courtyard of Misfortune is a filthy place.
So the imperial physicians don't want to be assigned here.
Sanitizing the corposes to prevent contamination
doesn't require complicated medical skills.
It's the same procedure.
So gradually,
the Courtyard of Misfortune has had to find someone for this position on our own.
The master teaches the disciple.
We only need to notify the Imperial Academy of Physicians.
The more you say, the more confused I get.
So how does this Physician Dou have such an excellent dressmaking skill?
It looks to surpass the skills at the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Replying to Talented Lady Wu, there are no palace maids in the Courtyard of Misfortune.
This Physician Dou is more clever
with his hands than ordinary people.
He is also willing to mend clothings for the people here.
How can this be compared to the Bureau of Imperial Attire?
So that's how it is.
In this inner palace, it's easier to get treasures
than true feelings.
Compared to his skills,
this sense of compassion is so touching.
I want to see this Physician Dou
and thank him on behalf of Talented Lady Di.
Yes.
Who are you?
How dare you bother my meditation?
Immortal, please have mercy.
I am Xiao Shunzi and I didn't know Immortal is meditating here.
Immortal, please have mercy. I'm leaving now.
Speak!
Which coffin am I in?
If you guess it wrong,
you will come inside to stay with me.
- Xiao Shunzi!
- Don't scare me! I'm a coward.
I'll find someone who is brave to play with you, alright?
Someone who is brave?
- Who?
- Xiao Douzi. He is the bravest.
I will find him to play with you.
Stop it.
Ghost! Master!
Save me!
Save me, Master!
If you stop, I'll let you out.
What are you crying about?
Master, there is a ghost, a ghost!
Evertime I ask you to inventory the supplies,
you always get into a ruckus.
How many times have I told you?
I don't know if there are ghosts in the world.
After all these years in the palace,
I just know that sometimes people are more scary that ghosts.
Our Courtyard of Misfortune is actually the cleanest place in the palace.
What is there to be afraid of?
No, Master, there is really a ghost.
Where is Xiao Douzi?
You, Xiao Douzi, it's you playing me again.
What's this mess? I asked you, where is Xiao Douzi?
Hurry and come out.
You, you...
[Physician Dou]
I told you to hide your talent, and not show off your magnificent skill in dressmaking.
You just wouldn't listen even when I've said so many times. Watch how I'll punish you later.
Foster Father,
I pitied Talented Lady Di.
Now,
Talented Lady Wu wants to see you.
Physician Dou, raise your head.
Physician Dou, you look familar to me.
But I can't remember where I've seen you.
Physician Dou.
Don't be rude in front of Talented Lady Wu.
Don't forget your status.
Please don't blame us, Talented Lady Wu. My foster son
grew up in the Courtyard of Misfortune. He has never seen the outside and doesn't understand rules.
It's alright. Physician Dou,
how did you meet Talented Lady Di?
I did not know Talented Lady Di.
You did not know her? Then why did you make a dress for her?
Replying to Talented Lady Wu, there isn't much friendliness inside the palace.
But after Talented Lady Di died,
all the maids and eunuchs who had served her came crying to bid farewell to her.
They kneeled to thank her for taking care of them.
They also recounted many touching tales in front of the coffin.
Even though I didn't know Talented Lady Di, but I admired her.
I didn't have the heart to see her depart in a simple and old dress.
So I decided on my own to make her a new dress.
There really aren't many kindhearted people like you in the palace.
I thank you on behalf of Talented Lady Di.
In the future, if you run into any difficulty in the palace,
you can come to the Hall of Sunset Pool to find me.
I will definitely repay your favor on behalf of Talented Lady Di.
Thank you, Talented Lady Wu, for your grace.
[Eternal Peace Room, Courtyard of Misfortune]
Do you realize you almost revealed your identitiy just now and made a huge mistake?
She is the Older Sister Wu who saved me years ago.
She is a good person. She won't hurt me.
If I can reacquaint with Older Sister Wu,
then I can find that savior who took me out of Wu Manor back then.
Then I can find Mother's gold needle!
People's hearts can change. She helped you 11 years ago,
it doesn't mean that she won't hurt you 11 years later.
You know what this place is? The palace.
The biggest taboo is to reveal your weakness to others.
Your identity is your biggest weakness.
I don't believe Older Sister Wu will hurt me.
Even if she won't hurt you,
but once your identity is revealed,
it will attract deathly danger to those who had helped you and saved you.
If you reacquaint yourself with Talented Lady Wu, it will bring danger to her.
Understand?
Foster Father, I know I'm wrong.
Foster Father.
Remember it well.
Embroidery is using the needle instead of a pen.
the silk instead of paper,
using the silk threads to color.
A good result of embroidery
must reach the level of excellent in both form and style.
Compared to a famous scholar's books and paintings,
embroidery is on the same level.
Therefore, it is also called
"Elite Arts in a Lady's Room."
Qiniang.
What are you doing?
I-I-I...
give it.
Master.
I originally wanted to embroider by copying this purse.
But I don't know why, no matter how I embroider,
I just can't make it as lively as this purse.
Qiniang,
where did this purse come from?
To tell you the truth,
this embroidery style on this purse
has disappeared for many years.
The last person who had mastered this skill
was my teacher,
Number One Needle in the World, Attire Expert An.
This purse, from craftsmanship to embroidery,
is clearly what she personally made.
Eleven years ago,
my teacher committed a high crime of treason and committed suicide in jail.
Qiniang, what the An woman committed was a crime that would eliminate nine generations.
You could be connected.
Have you thought it over?
I...
Master, please have mercy. I have nothing to do with this purse. I found it.
A few days ago, I walked past the frontdoor of the Courtyard of Misfortune.
I happened to bump into a little physician.
That little physician was in a hurry.
After he left, I found this.
Then you should find that little physician and inquire thoroughly.
If this purse really belongs to him,
you would be in the clear.
Yes.
Are you looking for this?
Is this purse yours?
That's right.
How did you get this purse?
Why are you asking so many questions?
The embroidery on this purse can't even be done at the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Attire Expert Zhuo said that this kind of embroidery
has disappeared after the death of Attire Expert An.
If you won't tell me the origin of this purse,
then you won't get it back.
This purse... I bought this purse.
You bought it?
Where did you buy it?
I-I bought it from Xiao Shunzi of the Courtyard of Misfortune. If you don't believe, just ask him.
Xiao Shunzi?
You are the royal family's physician?
Wait!
You said the Attire Expert Zhuo.
Why must she need to know where this sachet came from?
Attire Expert Zhuo is the only disciple of the An Family.
This satchet was made by the An Family.
Since she saw it, he obviously must get a clear explanation.
Father! Father. Father.
Father!
Little bean. What is it that is making you so excited?
Father. It turns out that mother had a disciple.
Who said this?
Is it possible that you knew way earlier on?
Then why didn't you tell me earlier?
So it turns out that Zhuo Jiniang is the disciple of my mother.
Then she must know about my mother's past.
Maybe she also knows
who killed mother.
As soon as Zhuo Jiniang saw my mother's sachet, she immediately got people to come and get news.
You can tell immediately that this person is kind and caring.
Nonsense. Go.
I want to ask myself
Disciple knows I am wrong.
It is disciple who didn't do things well.
Zhuo Jiniang saw the sachet your mother left for you?
Yes!
You mustn't go and find Zhuo Jininang.
You cannot let Zhuo Jiniang know your real identity.
Why?
There is no why!
My good daughter,
listen to what father has to tell you. What is the point of finding her?
She doesn't know who killed your mother.
If she did know,
then would she still be alive until now?
She would have been pulled down years ago.
Listen to what I told you about not being able to be connected with people who practice martial arts.
You cannot go and meet Zhuo Jiniang either. You might harm her instead!
Right. I cannot go and meet Zhuo Jiniang.
I cannot harm her.
That's right.
I'm only afraid that even though we do not go to find her,
but she will try to come and find you.
We need to think of a plan.
We cannot let her know your real identity.
I have an idea!
This sachet, did you really purchase it from the a Hu vendor in the West Market?
Obviously it is.
If you don't believe, have a look. I have a few more here.
I often go out with my master to do some stuff.
So when I see something interesting, I will buy some back home.
And then I give some to those people who cannot leave.
I thought this sachet was pretty so I bought a few more.
Attire Expert Zhuo. If you like it,
You can buy a few more. I can give you the chepeast price.
Thank you for looking after our business.
These sachets
Do you remember which West Market stall you bought it from?
Usually the Hu Vendors will bring goods from the Western Regions to Chan An and
After they sell out, they leave. There isn't a fixed shop.
I just met it coincidentally.
Attire Expert Zhuo, if you don't have anything else,
Then I will leave first.
You can go.
Send people to the Northern Market and
Go to every single stall and find it for me.
Be it a store or a Hu vender stall,
Don't leave any one of them.
I must found out where these sachets came from.
Otherwise I cannot be at ease.
[West Market]
Have you seen these sachets before?
Have you seen this before?
No.
Little bean.
What master just says. You must remember it.
Attire Expert Zhuo is the disciple of my mother.
Then she is my family. What is there to be scared about?
Little bean!
Don't worry. I won't let him know who I am.
This way, I can emphasise more
This way, when you walk,
you are even more beautiful towards others.
- I greet Talented Lady Wu.
- Greet Talented Lady Wu.
All rise.
Check if the waist and the length of the dress fits well
Yes. Talented Lady Wu, please follow me.
You lost that sachet?
Yes. I accidentally lost that sachet a few days ago.
She said that you were so upset while searching for the sachet that you almost started crying
Is this sachet that important to you?
It is because she had money in the sachet at that time.
I have let Attire Expert Zhuo see something hideous.
You claim that these sachets were purchased at the West Market?
But when sent people to check all over the West Market, they were not able to find it.
Don't tell me you think that I am trying to snatch your business?
And so you purposely lied to me?
I do not dare. The sachet really was bought there.
that made you feel so intrigued that it made you search a whole town?
I actually want to have a look at it.
I followed master and bought one from there as.
Why would she have to by a sachet from another place?
The way to make this sachet has already been lost. Even master doesn't know.
So master wants to try and
find who made these sachets.
It's nothing.
I'm not rushed. I have more than enough time.
Think slowly. Once you have thought about it clearly,
where did you buy these sachets. And how many times did you go and buy them?
Was it from the same place,
or was it from another place as well?
I bought it many times
and I think... it was...
I think it was from one place.
Every few years, they will come once or twice.
He has weird movement and travel plans. If you couldn't find them, it's not weird either.
Who knows, he might come back soon.
So you've brought it from the same person every couple of years as he comes around?
If you put it like this, you are very close with this person?
I'm not that close. I only know their face.
No. No. No. I also know him.
After a while,
I might now know either.
Attire Expert Zhuo. Why must you need to find this stall?
I am looking at how these sachets were made so nicely.
I just want to buy some more.
I still have some left. I will give all of them to you.
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entangelments, separations, reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relentless of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫