Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
[Weaving a Tale of Love]
[Episode 1]
[The 11th Year of Zhenguan Era, Great Tang Dynasty]
(637 AD)
[Ruyi Resist Dye Shop]
Customers, please come inside.
Greetings, esteemed customers. I am the owner of the Ruyi Resist Dye Shop.
The shop is small and simple. I hope you are not slighted.
[Young Liuli]
I've heard about the dresses made by your store. Not only is the embroidery exquisite,
the design is particularly new and unique.
It's quite popular among the ladies in the officials and merchants' household,
[Wu Yuanhua]
so that it's difficult to obtain a dress.
My mother and I came here today to custom order
a most unique wedding gown in the whole of Chang'an City.
Please rest assured, esteemed customers. I am not boasting,
but the wedding gown made in my shop will definitely be the most beautiful gown in Chang'an.
[An Silang]
Don't promise too much, shopkeeper.
My demands are high.
How do you know that I will definitely be satisfied?
[Madam An]
The wedding gown I want not only has to adhere to the etiquette rules in the palace,
but it also cannot follow the stale traditional style and look dull.
It must be auspicious and opulent,
but it cannot be vulgar and old-fashioned.
It must be restrained, not intentional,
but show creativity in its minute details.
It must charm anyone who sees it and leave an unforgettable impression.
About these demands, can your shop meet them?
In the palace?
[Bureau of Imperial Attire]
You should all be more careful and cautious.
What we do at the Bureau of Imperial Attire are meticulous duties.
We cannot allow for any bit of clumsiness and mistakes from you.
Each of the embroidered items in your hands is, at least, as important as your own life.
If it's stained, wrinkled, or damaged,
a light punishment may be just a beating,
but a heavy punishment will cost your life.
To work at the Bureau of Imperial Attire, you must be nimble and agile,
have a sharp mind, and rely on your craft
to succeed.
[Embroided Bloom in Splendor]
Remember all the time, what we make at the Bureau of Imperial Attire
[Attire Chief Lin]
isn't just clothes, but more importantly, the nobility's dignity.
Whoever can make our higher-ups look good,
you will look good, too.
Attire Chief, all the consorts and concubines' clothing for the seasonal change are all completed.
[Zhuo Jinniang]
Please review, Attire Chief.
All the other consorts and concubines are all right,
but Consort Yang's clothes,
I will personally deliver them.
Could it be the rumor in the palace is true?
Consort Yang is becoming the Empress?
How is this possible?
Consort Yang used to be the Princess Consort of Prince Qi, and the daughter-in-law of His Majesty.
How can she ascend to the Empress's throne to be the motherly role model for the nation?
Shut your mouth!
How dare we discuss what His Majesty will decide on choosing his new empress?
Take care of your own mouths.
Shopkeeper, don't be careless.
My Lady  Si Niang is the daughter of  Warrior Yu of Jingzhou
She was just conferred the title of Talented Lady, and soon she will enter the palace to serve His Majesty.
We come to the Ruyi shop to custom order her auspicious gown to wear on the day she enters the palace.
It is your shop's honor. You must gather up 200% of your energy to do your very best.
To be able to make the auspicious gown for Talented Lady Wu to enter the palace,
it is a blessing that Ruyi Resist Dye Shop can't even beg for.
We wouldn't dare to be neglectful.
However, what you just said has reminded me of something.
Even though our small shop's clothes are considered high quality in the market place,
they can't compare to the elegant clothes in the palace. Our little shop is incapable.
Would Madam and Talented Lady Wu please excuse us.
Shopkeeper, you must be concerned about the payment?
Don't worry. As long as my daughter is pleased with the auspicious gown,
our Wu family will pay a high price. We won't be stingy.
Just name your price, and we won't bargain with you.
I can't help but decline.
It's really because our dressmaker has limited ability in making clothes.
Our clothes can't enter such a sacred place as the palace.
Uncle.
Uncle, why are you so humble and even put my mother down in front of others?
Older Sister, don't listen to my uncle.
I know my mother's skill.
My mother's skill is peerless in the world, and she also has the kindest heart.
If my mother is willing to make Older Sister's wedding gown,
Older Sister will definitely become the most beautiful bride in the entire Chang'an.
Younger sister is so smart. When you grow up,
I'm sure you'll be talented.
Shopkeeper, you keep making excuses.
Aren't you afraid of ruining Ruyi Resist Dye Shop's reputation?
If this gets spread out,
I'm afraid no one will say that
you decline because you look down at our payment.
Instead, they will only say that you have limited abilities and can only make common clothes.
If esteemed customers don't mind, Older Brother, you can let me give it a try.
It's just that if my skill cannot be acceptable to esteemed customers,
it's because I have inadequate ability.
Please don't drag down Ruyi Resist Dye Shop's reputation at that time.
This is the first time I've seen such a cautious shop.
Go ahead and do it. As long as you put your whole heart into it,
I won't fault you even if it isn't succesful.
I also won't shame Ruyi Resist Dye's reputation.
Thank you for your understand, Talented Lady Wu.
Our little shop will definitely do our best.
Attire Chief,
this servant has seen you looking worried these days.
Are you worried about Consort Yang's pending ascension to become the empress?
Consort Yang's status is awkward. The inner palace also always emphasizes people's respectability by rank.
We used to be neglectful toward her.
Now, it appears that Consort Yang will become the leader of the inner palace.
Our Bureau of Imperial Attire's future is...
This servant has an idea.
It just might please Consort Yang,
so that she won't blame you for past grievances.
What is the idea?
Immediately prepare for Consort Yang
a pheasant robe worn for the conferral of empress ceremony.
A pheasant robe?
But, so far it is just a rumor that Consort Yang will become the empress.
His Majesty has not sent a decree to announce it to the court and the inner palace.
If the Bureau of Imperial Attire prepares a pheasant robe for Consort Yang now,
if the responsibility is tracked down later, it is a serious crime of transgression.
It is precisely because the decree hasn't been issued
that it shows how thoughtful the Bureau of Imperial Attire is in handling matters,
and that we are loyal to the new empress.
This way, the new empress will remember how good you are, Attire Chief.
As soon as the decree to confer the new empress is issued, making the pheasant robe
will become the task for our Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Who will even care about forgiving past grievances?
This servant believes this is the best opportunity for our bureau.
If we don't do it now,
when will we do it?
You are always quiet every day,
but you have good ideas at the most critical moments.
What you say makes sense.
Too bad that the "Number One Needle in the World" Attire Expert An left the palace many years ago.
Who can be in charge of the pheasant robe for the empress now?
This servant Zhuo Jinniang will volunteer
to do this work for Attire Chief.
You?
I am the only disciple of "Number One Needle in the World" Attire Expert An.
A few years ago, after my teacher resigned from her position at the Bureau of Imperial Attire,
her whereabouts are still unknown,
the only one who can make the pheasant robe for the empress
is me, the only disciple who was personally taught by Attire Expert An.
It's a formidable job to sew the pheasant robe for the empress.
Are you perfectly certain about it?
This servant is confident.
I will let you. If, this time,
the pheasant robe you make can please the new empress,
I will definitely help you get promoted
to be Attire Expert.
This servant thanks Attire Chief.
Liuli!
Liuli! Where is she?
[Young Shanhu]
Older Sister, your embroidery skill has reached such a miraculous stage.
Your mother even lied that she has never taught you.
I am going to ask my father for justice.
Young Sister, don't be mistaken.
Indeed, my mother has never taught me.
I secretly learned it.
Don't fool me.
How can you secretly learn to have such fine skill?
This is nothing special. If my mother didn't forbid me to use needles and threads,
and she also knows exactly how many needles there are in the needle case,
I wouldn't have stolen a blunt-tipped needle which hurts my craft.
Are you talking about that gold needle,
the token that symbolizes your mother as the number one in the world?
Even though that gold needle is pretty, but it's a blunt-tipped needle and not easy to use.
But, it's the only needle that my mother won't frequently check.
So I can only make do with it.
If you want to learn, I can teach you.
But, you must not tell my mother.
You will really teach me?
Why not?
Older Sister, if you really mean it, then give that camellia silk handkerchief to me.
If you go back on your word later,
I will show this handkerchief to your mother and my father,
let them punish you. How's that?
All right then. Since you want it,
I will give it to you.
[Bureau of Imperial Attire]
Attire Chief, the pheasant robe for the new empress is completed.
Attire Chief, please inspect it
to check for any imperfections.
Attire Chief, are you dissatisfied with the pheasant robe I made?
You are "Number One Needle in the World" Attire Expert An's only disciple?
How did you not learn
even a tenth of your teacher's skill?
Back then, the pheasant robe that Expert An made for Empress Zhangsun,
after all these years,
it is still memorable to people who had seen it. But you?
It's like mud compared to clouds.
Yes.
Too bad that Attire Expert An wished to live outside the palace.
She found a chance to plea for Empress Zhangsun to let her leave the palace those years ago.
From then on, there has never been anyone in the palace who could surpass Expert An's exquisite needle craft.
Attire Chief, I will do my best to fix it.
Do your best! Do your best! Is this all you can say?
Zhuo Jinniang, I think your hard work
cannot make up for inadequate talent, and you can't handle any important work.
I think it's useless for you to keep fixing it.
It will only waste time for nothing.
The only way to save the Bureau of Imperial Attire now
is to find your teacher.
Ask her to come back and modifiy this pheasant roble for the new empress.
B-But...
my teacher left the palace many years ago.
Besides, she has disappeared. How can I find her?
This is a question for you, the only disciple of hers.
I just don't believe that, after all these years,
you don't have even a single bit of her news?
Attire Chief... I...
Don't think that I don't understand your sneaky mind.
You are afraid that your teacher will come back,
and you will be further and further away from the Attire Expert's position.
I'm warning you, Zhuo Jinniang.
This is not the time to be clever.
The Attire Expert's position is good, but you have to have the fate to be in it.
If you can't make a pheasant robe that pleases the new empress,
you can be convicted at the least with the inability to fulfill your duty, or more seriously,
the crime of disrespecting the new empress.
At that time, you will lose your head!
I...
Find your teacher, or lose your head.
You choose.
I told you, I am Attire Expert's old acquaintance and I have an urgent request.
[Kudi Residence]
This is how you treat guests at the Kudi Residence?
I've already told you, we don't have any Attire Expert An here.
Make way.
You can't go inside!
You realy can't go inside.
I am a female officer in the palace. How dare a lowly servant like you grab me. Let go of me.
This servant doesn't dare to offend a female officer, but this is a private residence.
We really don't have who you are looking for. Please be understanding.
I've run around all day, and my legs are almost broken from walking.
If I weren't totally sure, I wouldn't have come here.
Don't fool me.
♫  The world in April will be at its fullest  ♫
♫  The mountain temple is in full bloom  ♫
♫  The constant regret in spring is everlasting  ♫
♫  Don't know how it has turned out this way  ♫
Disciple Zhuo Jinniang greets Master.
It's been many years. How is Master?
Since it's been many years,
why have you suddenly come here to disturb my peace?
A'Ye, Liuli is still playing outside. She'll probably come back soon.
Go find her and tell her to come back a little later.
Don't let her bother my nostalgic chat with an old friend.
Yes.
Master, you are really observant.
To be honest, the ceremony to confer the new empress is coming up soon.
Attire Chief Lin entrusted this disciple with the important task of making the pheasant robe for the new empress.
Too bad that this disciple is incapable.
The pheasant robe that I made displeases Attire Chief Lin.
Therefore, I especially came today to beg Master
to save me, save the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
Help this disciple modify the pheasant robe.
Have you forgotten?
I left the palace years ago upon Empress Zhangsun's benevolent permission.
From then on, nothing with the palace or the Bureau of Imperial Attire concerns me.
Excuse me for not being able to help.
The one who permitted you to leave the palace
was the late empress.
But now, the inner palace will get a new leader.
If the new empress is dissatisfied with the pheasant robe that this disciple makes,
then... this disciple can't help
but let the new empress remember Master.
The new empress is well aware of Master's outstanding skill.
At that time, the new empress will issue an edict
to order Master to enter the palace to work.
At that time, if Master disobeys the decree,
it will be a crime punishable by death.
Zhuo Jinniang, are you threatening me?
This disciple wouldn't dare.
This disciple is only explaining the realities to Master.
As long as Master can help this disciple make a pheasant robe that pleases the new empress,
all of the troubles will be avoided.
You can continue to say among the civilians and live your carefree life.
This disciple will definitely
not tell anyone of Master's whereabouts.
Master, just now,
this disciple seemed to hear you talk to a maid
about a girl named Liuli.
It sounds like a girl's name.
Could she be Master's daughter?
Master, even if you don't consider for yourself,
you should consider your family members.
We haven't seen each other for ten years, but your words
have become more fierce, and especially vicious.
As it is now, it's useless to talk more.
I only have one request.
If you promise, then I'll agree to modify the pheasant robe.
Master, please say it.
Don't tell anyone that I have a daughter.
This disciple swears that I will not mention it to anyone.
If I break this oath, I will be hit by Heaven and struck by lightning.
This is good.
Leave the pheasant robe that you made here.
Come to get it seven days later. I will fix it well.
I have something else to remind you.
If you want to sit in the seat of Attire Expert at the Bureau of Imperial Attire,
then never mention me to the new empress.
This pheasant robe is totally made by you alone.
Thank you, Master, then this disciple will bid you farewell.
Seven days later, I shall return to visit you.
I won't walk you out then.
Master, I have another unreasonable request that I beg you to agree to.
Master, will you transfer the token that represents "Number One Needle" to this disciple?
If I have this gold needle in my hand, then I can rightfully
become the Attire Expert at the Bureau of Imperial Attire.
If I can sit in the seat of the Attire Expert, it will be Master's honor.
It will also be our sect's honor. Please fulfill my wish, Master.
"The valley is too deep to fill, what's the use of one needle?" (She is not talented.)
Liuli!
This gold needle is only a status symbol. It cannot be used to sew or embroider.
Tell Mom, what were you doing sneaking out with it?
Mother, you forbid me to use needles and threads.
I couldn't help but suddenly wanted to sew a handkerchief.
I thought this one needle would be the only one that Mother won't check.
That's why I took it.
Mother, I did wrong. I shouldn't have secretly taken the gold needle.
Are you saying that you took this gold needle to embroider the handkerchief?
Where is the handkerchief? Let me see.
Liuli did wrong. Please don't be angry, Mother.
This gold needle is blunt-tipped.
But you actually embroidered such a beautiful handkerchief.
You...
How many times have I told you?
Don't learn sewing! Dont learn embroidery! Why won't you listen?
Why do you make me angry?
Why?
Why can Shanhu learn sewing and embroidery,
and her mother won't scold her and hit her, and even begs Mother to teach her?
All the other girls have to learn needlework.
Why am I the only one who can't?
Learning to sew and embroider is not bad.
Of course, sewing and embroidery are not bad.
But, a common person isn't guilty, yet a common person with a jade is guilty.
An outstanding skill in sewing is that jade. My daughter,
can you understand it?
Back then, when I left the palace,
it was because of my skill
that I was helplessly involved in the life-or-death battles inside the palace.
I didn't want to participle in those battles.
I further didn't want to become
the tool used by those people to fight.
Mother.
My daughter.
The more endowed you are with this talent,
the more worried that I am.
I am really scared.
I am so scared!
[Young Pei Xingjian]
This is my entry permit.
[Su Dingfang]
Welcome, General Su.
General Su?
That is the renowned meritorious General Su Dingfang.
Amitabha, you've endured an arduous journey, General.
It's been a year. How is your health, Buddhist Master?
General, don't worry. For our annual chess game,
I will stay healthy and strong.
- Please.
- General!
General Su, please wait!
General Su.
I am Pei Xingjian, with courtesy name Shouyue.
I have long admired General Su. Please accept me as your disciple.
I don't take in disciples. Go on home.
I have studied martial training for many years, in the hope that one day
I could become a brave warrior like General Su to guard our land.
You said you've studied martial training for many years.
I'll test you a little then.
That camilla tree is blooming now.
If you can shoot down that tallest and most beautiful camilla flower with one arrow,
then I will consider accepting you as a disciple.
I will let you take five steps.
It's too close.
General.
This camilla flower is embroidered so beautifully that it appeared to be the real flower.
Young Master Pei's archery skill is excellent. Will General give him another chance?
I asked you to shoot down the most beautiful camilla flower, but you shot down a handkerchief.
Even though it's understandable, but we are not fated to become master and disciple.
You should go back.
General Su, I came to Chang'an this time to participate in the imperial exam.
But my lifetime dream is to become a general riding a horse and wielding a blade to secure Great Tang's boarders
in order to protect the people to avoid harm from family separations and chaos.
I just entered the city and accidentally encountered General.
I think this is actually fate. It's meant by Heaven's will.
General, look at the camilla tree.
There are hundreds of flowers on it.
But he shot down the one and only fake flower.
Whether this is fate or not fate,
who can really tell the difference?
Since Buddhist Master has spoken, I'll give you another chance.
I will be here for the next few days. Perhaps it's just one day,
or three, or five days.
If we are really fated to meet again,
then the fate is certain.
However, let me tell you,
you cannot step inside the temple at all.
- Please.
- Respectfully say goodbye to General.
Thank you, Buddhist Master, for saying a good word for me.
Then, based on what you're saying,
we still don't know it will be fortune or disaster after you fix the pheasant robe for the new empress.
There won't be fortune.
As long as there is no disaster, it will be a blessing from the ancestors.
Older Sister's status as the Number One Needle in the World
never brought any benefit to the Kudi family.
Now, it even endangers our entire family of old and young.
It's no big deal that we suffer,
but the good reputation of Kudi family's ancestors
should not be allowed any damage.
Husband, please think of an idea.
As things are now, you don't need to prattle.
Don't just talk. Let's think of a solution fast.
[Madam Cao]
I do have an idea, but if I tell you,
[Kudi Yanzhong]
Older Sister and Husband, please don't blame me.
Why are you holding back at a time like this? Hurry and tell us.
Husband, please write a divorce letter for Older Sister in advance.
What nonsense are you saying?
Husband, please let me explain.
Older Sister, please don't blame me as coldhearted.
I am only doing this for the whole family's sake.
Even if Older Sister can stand dragging down the entire family,
you would at least feel for your own daughter, Liuli.
Writing the divorce letter is just for in case. In case of Consort Yang isn't chosen as the empress,
Husband can show people the divorce letter that's written today,
and totally disassociate involvement with Older Sister.
This way, you can protect the whole family.
A'Cao seems to make sense.
This is just for in case. If we get through this problem, our family can still be—
Husband, you need not say more.
A'Cao really has a good scheme.
Good trick.
Husband, go ahead and write the divorce letter to break up our relationship.
It will be the best evidence for Husband
to prove your innocence later.
A'Cao is vicious.
Husband is selfish and cowardly.
Liuli, Liuli.
I don't care about staying alive.
But you are the one I worry the most about.
I must make an appropriate arrangement for you.
You have such a talent for dressmaking.
This is also fate.
It is time for me to transfer the unique dressmaking skill to you,
so that you have the skill to make a living.
This robe wasn't made by Mother.
How did you know that I didn't make it.
The birds that Mother embroider are alive and can fly.
Not like these. They don't look lively.
Liuli is right.
This robe, made by someone else, isn't satisfactory.
That's why they asked me to modify it for them.
Mother, are you going to make these birds come alive?
If these birds can be alive,
will they become noisy?
Mother, I have a solution.
How about embroidering a big bird?
Let them have a mother to watch over them.
My daughter, you have such a great talent.
I really don't know if it will be fortunate or disastrous.
Liuli, I will take you to stay in a safe place for a few days, all right?
Mother, where are you sending me to?
Don't you want to learn dressmaking with me?
If you are good,
I will teach you the skills.
Mother, you will really teach me?
Mother, can't you teach me at home?
The place I'm sending you to is a good place.
When you go there, you can make clothes for other people, just like mother does.
Mother, can't you go with me?
Greetings, Madam Yang. Greetings, Talented Lady Wu.
I impudently came to your residence so that Madam Yang and Talented Lady Wu
can personally inspect the auspicious gown that our shop has carefully made.
So quickly done?
Hurry and show me.
This is the auspicious gown that Ruyi Resist Dye Shop made for Talented Lady Wu.
Please view it, Madam Yang and Talented Lady Wu.
The peach tree is full of young sprouts. How brilliantly bright are the flowers!
[Tao Yao, Ode to Peach Blossom]
This young lady is going to marry. How fitting she will be at her future home!
Embroidering the poem into the silk, turning it into clothes.
It is indeed new and creative. It is not shallow.
This Ode to Peach Blossom is also very approriate.
Even though this Ode to Peach Blossom has a good meaning,
but the auspicious gown is embroidered only with one peach flower.
Isn't it too lonely, not as lively for a celebratory event?
If it is embroidered with a tree of peach flowers,
full of peach blossom's splendor, that's how an auspicious gown should present.
Could it be that you deliberately cut the work to neglect us?
Replying to Madam, a tree of blooming flowers may look lively,
but there is no clear difference between the primary and secondary themes.
It won't make it unforgettable to the viewers.
Even though there is only one peach flower on this auspicious gown,
it is the fruit of exquisite craftsmanship.
It symbolizes one rising up among the many.
It will let all the viewers linger and find it unforgettable.
One rising up among the many...
Well said!
In the inner palace where there are as many beauties as the clouds,
don't any of the concubines want to be one rising up among many?
Servants, bring the reward.
Madam, wait.
The collar and the sleeves on this auspicious gown
still need to be modified to be more fitting
according to Talented Lady's body.
My mother ordered me to stay in your residence for a few days
to do the finetuning work according to Talent Lady's measurements.
Once the auspicious gown is completed, and Madam and Talented Lady are satisfied,
at that time, Liuli will kneel to thank Madam's reward.
You?
You are still such a young child.
No matter how outstanding your mother's skill is,
how can I believe that a baby can make clothes?
Madam, don't look down at me. Such a small task
is easy to me.
This child...
Madam, don't underestimate this child.
She is the daughter of Number One Needle in the World.
She has been personally taught by her mother.
Madam An finished the major parts of this gown.
The child can totally take on the wrapping-up work.
That day, the one who took my measurements,
was the famous Number One Needle in the World?
Precisely.
- Why don't we—
- In that case,
just let this child stay in our manor then.
I also want to see her skills.
If you do a good job to finish the auspicious gown, I will reward you handsomely.
If you make a mistake, I will also punish you harshly. Are you afraid?
Such a small task is nothing difficult.
Madam Yang and Talented Lady Wu, please wait to see it.
Liuli, from this moment on, everything I say,
you must remember it well.
Tomorrow, I will ask Uncle to take you to the Wu Manor. Stay there for seven days
to mend the auspicious gown for Miss Wu.
Mother, are you really letting me use the needle?
This is my insight from many years of dressmaking.
I'm giving it to you.
When you are in the Wu Manor, remember everything thoroughly in your head.
After that, burn it. You must do it.
You must not show anyone else the dressmaking secrets in it.
Remember what I said.
This gold needle was bestowed to me
by His Majesty and the late empress.
It is a token that symbolizes Number One Needle in the World.
I am giving it to you. In the future,
you will safeguard it.
After seven days, Mother will come personally to pick you up.
After seven days, if it's someone else that comes to pick you up, you must not come back here.
At that time, beg Talented Lady Wu to send you to a nunnery
to seek sheltering from Buddha.
Don't tell anyone
that you are the daughter of Number One Needle in the World. Understand?
No, Mother, I don't want to go to the Wu Manor to mend the auspicious gown.
I also don't want to live there for seven days. I don't want to leave Mother!
Liuli, you must listen to Mother this time.
What I'm doing is for your safety. Understand?
Mother...
I promise you.
After seven days, I will come for you.
Mother.
Mother!
Timing and Subtitles brought to you by
ðŸ§µTeam 7ï¸âƒ£ Needles & ThreadsðŸ§µ @ Viki.com
♫  Watching the flowers bloom and fall in the courtyard  ♫
♫  How many loves, regrets, entanglements, separations, reunions must we go through together  ♫
♫  Uncover the vicious cycle of the past  ♫
♫  Fate has its uncertainties  ♫
♫  I've spent this life with brush and ink in hand  ♫
♫  Writing about what love is  ♫
♫  Borrow from the relentless of the night  ♫
♫  To exchange for the certainty of a promise  ♫
♫  There are too many bumpy roads along the way  ♫
♫  The more twists, the deeper it is  ♫
♫  Breaking up and making up is like an illusion  ♫
♫  Resembles a traveler traveling through this life  ♫
♫  Time ignores everything including obsession  ♫
♫  With the candlelight flickering indefinitely  ♫
♫  After the fire, there was only one thing left  ♫
♫  A bright moon that makes one's heart tingle  ♫