♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 10=
Looks like the punishment of singing
isn’t enough for you.
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Yuchi Longyan can touch you,
but I can’t?
I won’t run, all right?
Let go of me first.
What’s your relationship
with Yuchi Longyan?
We’re in no relationship!
We’re simply friends.
Good friends.
If you were simply friends,
why did he give you so many treasures?
Why does a bird like you need this?
He’s just generous.
-It hurts!
-Generous?
Don’t I have these
in Luofeng Pavilion?
You’re my maid.
Your belongings
are mine.
Tell Yuchi Longyan I appreciate
his generosity.
You villain!
Why did you take things for Liuying?
Oh.
Oh my!
What should I say to Longyan?
You’re so bold to come back here.
The beautiful silk!
You tore them.
The cakes.
You ate most of them.
The medical herbs!
That’s what’s left for her.
They’re for Liuying?
Well, they’re not for me of course.
Cold-blooded man.
You’re exactly the reason
why she ends up like this.
Dragon King bought these
for her to regain health.
Yet you intercepted them.
You’re so... so...
You’re rotten.
I’m no longer your maid.
Stop.
Wait.
Well,
there are a few osmanthus cakes left.
Do you want them?
No!
I can turn a blind eye
to the mistakes you made.
Besides,
I grant you the floral makeup.
Are you serious?
Of course I am.
Then I’ll...
But you have ruined
most of these things.
What am I going to tell Dragon King
and Liuying?
You’ve never been so devoted
to the tasks I gave you.
As my maid,
you don’t need to follow his order
to look after...
Liuying is my friend.
I’m willing to.
And...
And I’m not your maid anymore.
It’s not been 100 years as we agreed.
So you’re still my maid.
How dare you say that?
You never saved my life,
or cured my wounds,
not to mention
bought me osmanthus cakes.
Dragon King bought it, not you.
These are not good at all.
The silk is hideous.
One day, I’ll show you, my maid,
what real treasure is.
Really?
Well, I’m your maid
and you rarely talked so much.
So you must be thirsty.
Let me get you a cup of tea.
Show me the real treasure?
I’ll show you how to loose the bowels.
My Lord, your tea.
I’ll be waiting...
for you to show me the real treasure.
Why did my mood
change so abruptly today?
Mrs. Xu.
Sir.
-Alright.
-I want this.
Sir, how much is this?
Like usual,
the same price of last time.
Thanks.
I’ll pack it up.
Here you go.
Alright, thank you.
This painting
looks so familiar.
The lady on it
resembles you a lot.
(Suxin Drawings)
Madam, you have a good eye.
This painting is found in the woods.
I framed it after it’s sold to me.
In the woods?
Madam, look at the lines.
Smooth flows and strong touch.
The dragon is vivid
and majestic in the clouds.
But from the lady’s eyes
in the painting,
you can see mildness.
It’s truly wonderful.
Madam.
Are you alright?
I’ll buy it.
Sure.
So
it’s you in my dream.
Though you’re not in my memory,
I know in my heart
you’ll be there forever.
Liuying.
I’m committed to you,
and it will never change.
You’ll always be my Liuying.
♪Pure white sunshine♪
♪Clouds hide the moss♪
♪There comes the deer’s call♪
♪Dare not to run too fast
Steps are soft♪
♪Wind blows the skirt’s hemline♪
♪You’re in the shadow of the tree♪
♪If I don’t come along♪
♪Will you only hesitate♪
♪The leaves rustling Not too loud♪
♪The heart beats fast and deafening♪
♪Wait until the red sunset♪
♪Embrace the warm wind♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
Since we have feelings for each other,
and promise each other a lifetime,
we can get married.
I see.
To return a favor is to marry you.
♪Thick wine flows into the sea♪
Dragon King!
♪And into your heart♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
I remembered.
My memories are back.
It’s like
I had a dream.
Was it a beautiful one?
♪Like a♪
Very beautiful.
♪Thick wine flows into the sea♪
Images of people
in the dream all faded away,
except for yours.
♪And into your heart♪
It was you who watched fireflies with me
and also you who took me
above the clouds.
It’s time for the Lethe Tea.
After you drink it,
you’ll forget the past.
No.
I don’t want to forget you.
You can’t stay here.
It’s good for you to go to mortal world.
Well,
when I meet you again,
how could I know it’s you?
(Luofeng Pavilion)
When you see fireflies,
it means I’m around you.
Perhaps you’ll think of me.
I’ll do my best to remember it.
Dragon King, we’re running out of time.
Liuying.
Drink it.
Is it bitter?
Don’t be afraid.
While you’re drinking,
focus on what I’m going to say,
and you won’t find it bitter.
What is it you want to say?
I’ll tell you when you drink it.
I love you.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
Where am I?
♪Memories make me miss you♪
River of Tears.
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
Where will I go?
To the mortal world,
just across the Luofeng Bridge.
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
Thank you.
Sir, you look familiar.
Have we met somewhere?
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
My name is Yuchi Longyan.
♪It lingers around♪
I’m just a
stranger.
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
Don’t be afraid.
I’ll be watching you.
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪The fate of time♪
♪I repay with four lives♪
♪I gave you my youth♪
♪The wish in hand♪
♪It’s meant to be♪
One day,
I’ll take you to my Dragon Pool.
My Lord, they...
They burst in.
You took my personal maid hostage
and broke in Luofeng Pavilion.
Personal maid?
I’m not...
I came here
to ask for a favor.
I’d like your answer
to a question.
Is there a way
to overrule the three tribulations
on Xiahou Xue and me?
No.
Don’t turn him down so fast.
I know I offended you,
My Lord.
Please
accept my apology.
Lord Yuchi,
you vowed to protect Xiahou Xue
for three tribulations in mortal world.
It’s just the first one
and you want to disavow.
There’s no precedent.
No exception. A rule is a rule.
If you tell me how to overrule it,
I will...
I will do one thing you ask, anything.
I don’t need you to do anything.
And I will not help you with this.
Bingxing, see our guest out.
Lord Yuchi, please.
Please tell me how to overrule it.
I told you.
There’s no point begging him.
Let’s go.
You stay here.
Me?
You’re a maid in Luofeng Pavilion.
Forget it.
You’re a cold-blooded man.
I don’t want to be your maid,
let alone a friend.
I’m going back
to my real friends.
Stop.
Leave us.
If you tell me how to overrule it,
I, Yuchi Longyan, will be in your debt.
The Dragon King never bowed his head.
Is it all for
Liuying?
Yes.
Is this your reverse scale?
Who is it
that hurt you so badly?
I’m fine.
It’s me.
It’s overwhelming pain
to claw a dragon’s reverse scale out.
Unbelievable, what did you do?
Claw out your reverse scale
and incarnate it
to Xiahou Xue’s destined man.
Perhaps, you will deceive the Heaven.
I broke the oath.
Merely for a mortal girl?
Are you still the Dragon King I knew?
Do me a favor.
Find Xiahou Xue’s destined man
who lacks a thread of soul
and put my scale on him.
I can’t help you.
You have to.
I won’t help you,
unless...
The Golden Armor.
You’re giving it to me?
Take it.
To survive the thunder strike,
you almost lost your life
to get the Armor.
I just want to remind you
don’t make a choice that you’ll regret.
I will not regret
the choice I made.
Just write the Book of Fate
for Xiahou Xue.
Do you think you can be with her
by sending your scale to Xiahou Xue?
Yes, I do.
My Lord.
I have some tasty osmanthus cakes
here for you.
My Lord.
Rise and shine.
Get up.
Are you still angry with me?
I wasn’t serious about
no one loving you.
I’m here to apologize.
You can punish me or scold me,
but don’t send me
to the River of Tears and sing.
You’re sweating.
Blood.
Look who is finally back.
What’s wrong with him?
Thanks to your friend,
Lord is punished.
By Dragon King?
If Luofeng Pavilion is found impartial,
Lord will be punished with broken ribs.
He gave Dragon King an exception.
As a disciplined man,
he punished himself.
Broken ribs?
Take care of him.
My Lord.
I was wrong.
I take back what I said
about you.
You look cold and aloof,
but you’re not callous at all.
It’s me. I was wrong about you.
I was so blind.
You have to recover soon.
-When you do, I’ll...
-Shut up.
My Lord,
you’re awake.
That’s great.
Stay away.
No, I will not walk away anymore,
unless you promise you’ll not
be angry with me.
You’re pressing my wound.
Oh, sorry, My Lord.
I... I... I...
I’ll pour you a cup of tea.
My Lord, have some hot tea.
Hot tea helps you heal.
What is it?
Is there anything else in the tea?
No!
I’m sorry about the last time.
Look, I’ll take a sip first.
See? I’m absolutely fine.
I’ll get you another cup.
I drank from it.
My Lord,
thank you for letting Liuying loose.
The crack of sky net is still there.
I never said I’d let Liuying loose.
You’ll still patch it
with Liuying’s soul?
No way!
I need to tell Dragon King now.
Didn’t you say you’ll not walk away?
Even if the doppelganger can
deceive the Heaven,
you and her can’t get married.
Is that so?
All your sacrifices are in vain.
Why don’t you forget her?
Even if we can’t get married,
I’ll stay with her.
You will go to the mortal world?
Wherever she is,
I’ll be there.
She’s born. Liuying is back!
I miss her so much!
Hey, why would Liuying choose this place
to be born?
Yuchi Town.
What about it?
Yuchi.
Is it because this village has
the same name with you
that she chose to be born here?
One way or another,
Liuying chose me in the end.
Got it?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪