♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 9=
Miss.
Miss?
Liuying!
What were you thinking?
I was thinking... As I remember,
my husband doesn’t like durian,
but why did he say
that he liked it?
Is it possible that the person
you remember is someone else?
How come there’s someone else?
Nonsense.
My husband is the only man I love
in my lifetime.
What’s good about that?
It is good.
I hope I could be with him
in all my lifetimes.
In all your lifetimes?
You are not satisfied with one lifetime.
You want all lifetimes.
With the same guy!
That would be so boring.
Don’t you think so?
Take these chestnuts for example.
However sweet and tasty they are,
you’d get tired of eating them one day.
You eat meals and drink water every day,
but are you tired of that?
The mutual love
starts sweet and romantic.
After the marriage life starts,
the real love can be felt
as time goes by,
like the spring water’s sweet taste.
But I don’t know why
after we got married,
the feelings before... are gone.
That is normal
because they are two different persons.
Two persons?
I mean
when a man chases a girl,
he’s like a general on the battlefield.
After he marries the girl,
he takes off his armor and retires,
as if he were a different person.
So, they’re two different persons.
If I knew it,
I would get married later.
Looks like memories can deceive people,
but feelings can’t.
I want to know
how it feels
when forgetting everything.
With nothing to care for,
it feels good.
It does?
If you’re interested,
I can give you a cup of the Lethe Tea.
No, no, no.
Everyone comes to me
for any confusion about the human world
or the Heavenly Palace.
If I forget everything,
how can I find out your past?
Thank you, sir.
You’re welcome.
(Chronology)
I can’t remember everything
over thousands of years.
But I’m used to recording big events
in the Chronology.
I think I also recorded
what happened to you.
The Lonely Star left his post
without permission
and was dismissed
as the Heavenly General.
One of his ribs was made into a pipa,
accompanying him all the time.
To repent of his fault,
he drank the Lethe Tea willingly,
forgot about everything
and guarded Luofeng Pavilion
for three thousand years.
Only one page?
Why did I leave my post
without permission?
That’s odd.
The details were gone.
Did anyone else check on it?
I don’t remember.
But considering your temper,
you wouldn’t leave your post
for no reason.
There must be something fishy
with what happened.
So, I’ll give you a firefly rain.
Where’s he?
I’m here alone?
Don’t go!
You’re awake?
Why are you sweating?
Your hair’s wet.
You had a dream?
I dreamed about myself,
and someone else.
You dreamed of your husband?
Miss,
I found this paper dragon
in the room you lived in.
Do you still want it?
It’s... it’s mine?
It’s not?
This paper dragon is unique.
I’m the only maker in the world.
I’ll ask someone else, then.
It’s mine.
I remember
I embroidered something.
Why can’t I find it?
Who gave it to me?
I think
I forgot something very important.
Don’t go!
What exactly did I forget
in this place?
Why can’t I remember at all?
Husband?
You’re my husband, aren’t you?
Why can’t I see you clearly?
I am.
But this is a mere dream.
You’re in a dream.
Dream?
Can I feel
you haven’t changed
only when I’m in a dream?
I haven’t changed.
I know you haven’t.
The feeling that
only you’re by my side
hasn’t changed.
Now that I pledged to be yours,
I won’t ever change.
You’re always my Liuying.
Darling,
since we got married,
you’ve never talked to me like that.
I thought
you forgot how you called me before.
Liuying,
I would never forget.
I...
I remember everything.
Look.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
Darling,
after I wake up,
will you change again?
Will you be courteous to me again?
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
Everyone changes.
But...
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
But in your dream,
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
I’m always the me you remember.
♪I meet you in every dream♪
Now that it’s my dream,
I can do anything I want, can’t I?
As long as it’s your wish,
I’ll fulfill it.
♪I keep my love for you♪
I’m afraid
I wish I couldn’t wake up.
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
I also want to exchange my power
over a thousand years
for the incessant dream.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Xu Zhiyuan’s wife Liuying
is virtuous, gorgeous,
intelligent,
-Xu Zhiyuan really
-and elegant.
became the No.1 scholar
and worked as a fifth-rank compiler
in Hanlin Academy.
-He even got Liuying mandated.
-Respect this.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
-But since he became an official,
-I’m finished.
he’s been more serious.
He’s nice to Liuying, but...
How shall I put it?
They’re courteous to each other.
Luckily, they’re not cold to each other.
Being cold might be better.
Go!
Go. Be quick.
Lord Xiahou was reported
to keep closely touch
with Duke of the South.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
His Majesty was furious
and ordered soldiers
to confiscate Xiahou’s Family.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
We’re innocent! We’re innocent!
-Let go of me!
-Shut up!
-Go!
Only Xiahou Xue was saved
by Dragon King.
Have something to eat.
Why didn’t you save my parents?
My family was ruined overnight!
When I married you,
my families said you were a monster
and would bring misfortune to my family.
I didn’t believe them.
But it turned out to be true!
My family used to be in peace.
There wasn’t any disaster
until you came.
I was so stupid!
Why didn’t I listen to them?
Now it’s too late to regret!
Darling.
How are they?
Lord Xiahou is in prison.
Mrs. Xiahou...
I hear she’ll be exiled to the North.
My cousin is missing.
Why would this happen?
Could you save them?
The Xiahou Family is involved
in a rebellion case.
I don’t think...
But we can’t just watch and do nothing!
Please do something, Darling.
Governor Liu of Hanlin Academy
is my teacher.
I’ll ask him privately.
Thank you.
I also worry about one thing.
I hear
my cousin’s husband isn’t a human,
but a dragon demon!
Maybe,
he has killed my cousin.
Dragon King would never kill Miss.
Everybody says that
the dragon demon brought the misfortune
to the Xiahou Family.
But Dragon King is a good man.
He’s very kind.
Even if no one else trusts him,
I do!
Liuying,
you’re the only one who trusts me.
My Lord.
Dragon King.
He sent you this letter,
saying it will vindicate Lord Xiahou!
(Lord Xiahou isn’t involved
in the rebellion of Duke of the South.)
What do you think?
With this,
the problem will be solved.
The Xiahou Family were freed
from being executed.
But you broke heavenly laws
when you interfered
with the human world.
When you don’t tell others,
how will they know?
You and Xiahou Xue are a couple
in the name only,
but you’re not a real couple.
You faked a human body
with branches and leaves,
pretending to be her husband.
I’m afraid
you broke the promise between you
and Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
I don’t love Xiahou Xue.
All I can do is to keep her safe.
I can give her nothing more.
After practicing for a thousand years,
you’re trapped in love.
I’m afraid
you can’t get away
from the love tribulation.
If loving her is my tribulation,
I’m glad to accept it.
Drink less.
It’s the Strongest Spirit.
All I want is to get drunk.
Dragon King!
Hello, sir.
Liuying felt a bit sick the other day.
Today, the doctor checked on her
and she’s been pregnant for two months.
Dragon King!
Since when were you so close to him?
You don’t even have time
to remove the Meteor mark
on your forehead, right?
Don’t bring it up.
To remove it,
I even went to Luofeng Pavilion
to steal pipa. I...
I...
I suffered quite a lot!
You met Xue Qianxun?
Don’t bring him up.
Don’t! Don’t do that!
I can’t hear his name.
He’s an evil man!
I have something else to do.
I’m leaving.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Darling,
I brought you
your favorite Crispy Durian Cake.
Thank you, Darling.
Darling,
hope we’ll have a son.
I never knew
my life could be so long,
just like a chronic torture.
I saw you marry someone else,
get pregnant and have babies.
Try some, Darling.
Is it delicious?
I had thought
as long as you lived a happy life,
I would be relieved
and wait patiently to meet you again
after everything ended.
Unexpectedly,
even the thunder strike
wasn’t as tough as this moment.
I don’t know
when we can complete our promise.
I’ve something else to do.
Go to bed early.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
My Lord,
you can no longer
repair the crack of sky net
with your own power.
Then will I let the demons escape
from the sky net?
Liuying is pregnant.
Her husband is working in another town
and can’t protect her.
If she has a difficult labor...
She can’t drink any ginseng soup.
My Lady, please wake up!
If she can’t wake up,
I’m afraid she or her baby
might be in danger.
Lord Xu is away from home.
She’s giving birth right away.
Will we save her or her baby?
Bah!
Leave us!
All of you, leave!
Go!
Liuying,
don’t be asleep.
Did she pass out
because of insufficient strength?
It hurts!
You can’t keep protecting her soul
with your power.
You’ll run out of power sooner or later.
What do we do?
There’s strong spirit
in this room.
She shouldn’t have a difficult labor.
Is Luofeng Pavilion making trouble?
Luofeng Pavilion?
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Someone’s really making trouble.
I must send my doppelganger there.
Dragon King,
when you make a doppelganger,
your power will drop greatly!
If you’re hurt,
your soul will be hurt, too!
I can be hurt,
but Liuying can’t die.
It’s about time.
The soul is in the Lotus Box.
Bingxing, you don’t open it?
There’s no hurry.
When the woman loses all her blood,
messenger of Luofeng Pavilion
will tell me.
Then I’ll open the Lotus Box.
Yuchi Longyan, how dare you break in!
Give me her soul!
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Liuying,
you’re safe now.
You keep interfering
with Luofeng Pavilion,
we won’t let you go!
Your soul was hurt
when you forced a doppelganger.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
You risked your life to protect Liuying.
It’s...
It’s love?
What’s the value of it?
If you break off love
and never remember,
that’s your luck,
but also your loss.
Break off love and never remember?
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Let him go.
I’m sorry I failed it.
I’m sure
Qingqing told Yuchi Longyan about it.
I’m going to kill her immediately
to avoid future troubles!
Without my permission,
no one shall hurt her!
Yes.
She’s safe at last.
Dragon King,
Liuying’s exhausted.
She’ll be alright after some rest.
You’re leaving?
You don’t wait until she wakes up?
Look at you two.
He loves you,
and you love him.
But you can’t be together.
How unreasonable it is!
Silk fabrics from the Western Regions?
Fur from the East?
And these...
Bean paste cake, osmanthus cake,
and chestnut cake.
Dragon King, I used to think
it’s hard to get along with you
or get close to you.
But now I realize
you’re so considerate.
Don’t only notice the food or clothing.
The medical herbs
are the most precious.
I really admire you!
You’re a model of immortals and men.
It must be true love.
I admire you.
I’ll leave them to you, then.
Dragon King is such a good man.
Looks like the punishment of singing
isn’t enough for you.
Let go of me! Let go of me!
Yuchi Longyan can touch you,
but I can’t?
I won’t run, all right?
Let go of me first.
What’s your relationship
with Yuchi Longyan?
We’re in no relationship!
We’re simply friends.
Good friends.
If you were simply friends,
why did he give you so many treasures?
Why does a bird like you need this?
He’s just generous.
-It hurts!
-Generous?
Don’t I have these
in Luofeng Pavilion?
You’re my maid.
Your belongings
are mine.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪