♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 8=
Xue Qianxun,
you…
If my guess is right,
you failed to capture
the Immortal of Yin again?
Sorry.
Your Zisui Yangyan
has been taken away by Yuchi Longyan.
That cursed scumbag!
Come on.
Have a cup of tea.
To ease your anger.
I wonder if you can be honest with me
about one thing.
That depends.
2,000 years ago,
what on earth happened to me?
This is funny.
You’re asking me
about what happened to you?
Not to mention we’ve known each other
no more than 1,000 years.
Anyway, don’t you remember anything?
I only remember
I used to be the Lonely Star
and got punished
by being deprived of a rib
which was then made into
the Fleeting Pipa
and had garrisoned
the Luofeng Pavilion for 3,000 years.
That’s all?
Did you drink the Lethe Tea?
This tea…!
It’s not the Lethe Tea.
I often recall a green figure.
Are you sure it’s green
instead of pink?
Yes.
Then it must be…
You are yearning for amorous love.
If you want to know your past,
just turn to the Immortal of Fate.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Liuying,
what’s stopping you
from marrying my cousin?
Miss, I’m just a maid.
I don’t deserve him.
Don’t worry about that.
Father has already decided to
take you in as his foster daughter.
Later,
you can get married in the identity of
Xiahou’s younger miss.
You two will be a fine match.
Besides, you will be his legal wife
instead of his concubine.
Miss.
What is it?
I…
I wanna stay by your side forever, Miss.
Liuying.
Liuying,
you want her to be happy, don’t you?
As long as you marry Xu Zhiyuan,
both she and I will be happy.
I assure you
that I will hold
a grand wedding for you.
And
I have found you a maid.
Come in.
Nice to meet you, Liuying. I’m Qingqing.
You smell really good.
Nice to meet you, Qingqing.
(Book of Fate)
The doom of the Xiahou family is coming.
By the end of the year,
the whole family will disappear.
In that case,
is there any way
to help Liuying survive this?
This man can turn ill luck into good.
He can prosper his wife and child.
If Liuying marries him,
she can die a natural death.
(Xu Zhiyuan)
Xu Zhiyuan…
From now on,
he will take care of you for me.
Dragon King.
Do you really
want me to marry her cousin?
It is
for your own good.
I don’t think so.
He’s a good man.
And he likes you.
So what?
A marriage
needs mutual love.
Love
can be cultivated through time.
Cultivated?
But my heart has left me
and followed someone else.
There’s no heart or affection,
how will love be cultivated?
I will not marry him.
As for the memories you abandoned,
I will keep them.
Liuying.
Don’t try to persuade me.
On this matter,
no one can make the decision for me.
I never abandoned our memories.
I just want you to live a happy life.
The Star Halo!
Look!
It’s so beautiful.
Witnessed by the Star Halo,
I’m giving you our love token.
The joy and romance I brought you…
The secrets between you and me…
You will forget them all.
I will be the only one
who remembers them all forever.
You only need to remember
the memories you find
happy and beautiful
were brought…
By him.
You don’t like it?
I’ll have it.
But as I recall,
you don’t like
crispy durian cake either.
Why don’t you want to eat it?
As long as I eat it,
you will have the paper fan.
The fireflies all over the sky
I gave you
will never be given to another girl.
Liuying,
after you wake up,
you will agree to marry him.
Remember,
she loves
chestnuts roasted with brown sugar
only cooked by the pedlar
on Chang’an Street.
You need to buy two bags of them
at one time
in case she wants more
and you have to buy them again.
She loves watching petals fall.
Every time
when watching shedding petals,
she can be fully absorbed.
How could he know that?
Remember to put a cloak on her.
I’ve memorized them all.
Anything to add?
One more thing,
she’s dependent on her own bed.
Without her quilt and pillow
being around,
she couldn’t fall asleep.
Wait.
How could you know all of that?
Your miss told me that.
My miss?
She treats me so well.
Thank you, Mister.
Liuying.
Don’t you remember Dragon King
at all?
I never met him before,
but I have a sense of déjà vu.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
This is our farewell.
I won’t be able to see you for decades.
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
In my heart, however,
♪In a flash♪
today’s wedding is held for you and me.
♪I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
Here.
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like a firefly show♪
♪Bringing peace
in the sentimental world♪
♪Guiding the way like the starry night♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
I’ve practiced asceticism
for thousands of years.
I thought I could face anything
calm and at ease.
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
I never expected
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
I would be hopeless and despondent
for the first time today.
♪I meet you in every dream♪
I never expected the pain of losing you
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
could be worse than
that of the thunder strike.
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
So beautiful.
Look!
The Star Halo!
What a good omen!
Their marriage will last forever.
The Star Halo…
Have I ever
made a promise with an important person
to do something
at this moment?
Let’s make a promise.
Within three days,
if the Star Halo appears again,
you will give me a love token.
Within three days…
Liuying,
have you recalled it?
No.
She mustn’t recall it.
What if the Star Halo doesn’t appear?
Then let’s learn together
how to kiss like the humans do.
Why am I crying?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
Liuying,
I love you.
Since we love each other
and have promised each other
forever love,
we can get married, right?
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪Inseparable in this life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪The fate of time♪
♪I miss you all my life♪
♪I give you my youth♪
♪The wish in hand♪
♪It’s meant to be♪
Is it
your love token for me?
That’s my quilt.
That’s my pillow!
All right, then.
I’ll let you sleep on my bed these days.
I’ll sleep on the ground.
Shall I call you Xiaobai?
Your Highness?
Why are you here?
You were right.
Liuying is dependent on her own bed.
Now without her own pillow and quilt,
she can’t fall asleep on her new bed.
So, I came here secretly to get them.
All of her belongings
are still here?
Mrs. Xiahou said,
“The belongings of a maid
are mostly worthless.
Except for the bride’s jewels,
all the other stuff should be left
and changed.”
Humans
don’t cherish their old stuff.
I gotta go.
-I gotta bring her the quilt…
-Hold on.
Do you know where Liuying
keeps her painting?
Painting? I didn’t see it.
Maybe she has lost it.
Or maybe… She took it with her?
Do you need me to find it?
It’s fine if she has lost it.
After all, I myself
have lost her.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Darling,
the durian used to make the cakes
is from Southeast Asia.
They are very tasty.
The crispy durian cakes are tasty?
I’ll have some chestnut cakes.
You don’t like it? I’ll have it.
I remember
neither of us likes durian.
Darling. Darling?
Here.
What are you watching?
I don’t know.
I just feel that someone is sighing.
Why are you sighing?
It’s really a pity that
you don’t even touch
the osmanthus cakes.
Then you should be happy
that they are yours.
Here.
Thank you, Liuying.
Mister.
Dragon King.
Are you all right?
I don’t understand
the love between humans.
You can consult me.
What’s puzzling you?
How come the woman I love
fell in love with another man so soon?
Because you changed her memories.
Now the hero in her love story
is Xu Zhiyuan.
I did that
only to make her marry Xu Zhiyuan.
I didn’t expect
that she would fall in love with him.
But if she hadn’t fallen
in love with him,
she wouldn’t have married him.
All of this now
-was due to your arrangement…
-Shut up.
You know nothing.
This is not fair.
All of you have someone to love.
The only sad, angry and upset one here
should be me, the poor single bird.
(The White Snake’s Requital
Chapter Four)
Darling,
the durian used to make the cakes
is from Southeast Asia.
They are very tasty.
Miss.
Miss?
Liuying!
What were you thinking?
I was thinking… As I remember,
my husband doesn’t like durian,
but why did he say
that he liked it?
Is it possible that person you remember
is someone else?
How come there’s someone else?
Nonsense.
My husband is the only man I love
in my lifetime.
What’s good about that?
It is good.
I hope I could be with him
in all my lifetimes.
In all your lifetimes?
You are not satisfied with one lifetime.
You want all lifetimes.
With the same guy!
That would be so boring.
Don’t you think so?
Take these chestnuts for example.
However sweet and tasty they are,
you’d get tired of eating them one day.
You eat meals and drink water every day,
but are you tired of that?
The mutual love
starts sweet and romantic.
After the marriage life starts,
the real love can be felt
as time goes by,
like the spring water’s sweet taste.
But I don’t know why
after we got married,
the feelings before are gone.
That is normal
because they are two different persons.
Two persons?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪