♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 6=
Millions of years ago,
at the beginning of chaos,
the war between immortals and devils
caused turbulence of the three worlds.
Then, the ancient Nuwa
gathered the power of immortal and devil
and made a sky net of Yin Spirit Power
to seal the Evil Spirit.
After vicissitudes,
the sky net got loose
and cracks,
which needs to be repaired with.
Therefore, every time the immortal falls
and the soul dissipates,
Luofeng Pavilion will collect
the scattered Yin Spirit Power
and store it in the Lotus Box
in case of need.
Because the Spirit Power
has the essence of heaven and earth
which is given by ancient Nuwa,
it contains great energy.
Unexpectedly, the unconscious
Yin Spirit Power
got a divine consciousness
and naturally turned into a new soul,
imitated the immortals to go through
the immortal’s test
and secretly came to the human world.
If the one with the Yin Soul
dies in her bed,
we’ll not be able to seal her soul
by the sky net?
Yes, My Lord,
unless she dies by accident,
commits suicide
or we use force to seal her soul.
My Lord, if we don’t repair the sky net,
the Evil Spirit will escape
and cause troubles again.
The fastest way to do
is to repair it with the Yin Soul.
I’m willing to undertake
this responsibility
and go immediately to seize this soul.
Now we are talking about a soul!
Why do you say it so easily like
drinking a cup of tea?
I’d better escape as soon as possible
before they
use me to mend the net.
You still have conscience.
The Yin Soul can protect itself.
We can’t force to seize it
if it’s still in the body.
(Xiahou Xue)
Xiahou Xue?
Yes.
That girl made an oath with Xiahou Xue
of dying on the same day.
If this oath comes true…
Copy the oath of Liuying and Xiahou Xue
and put into the Oath Tower.
Yes.
The oath in
Oath Tower will always come true.
Liuying!
She is my benefactor!
I have to find a way to inform her!
I have to save her!
But Xiahou Xue is just
an ordinary person.
How about we start with her?
We’ll decide it later.
My Lord…
Your penalty.
Drink this bowl of bitter tea.
My Lord!
This is not a bowl!
It’s a pot!
I knew it! The evilest and
most cold-blooded man
in the world is him!
I thought I just needed to be hungry
for days.
Now,
I don’t even have the appetite to eat.
Wait,
now I have to tell Liuying first.
If I still have my power,
I can fly back there in a blink!
If I could turn into my real…
Why can I suddenly change back?
You even know how to paint?
That book of yours tells no truth.
Let me draw you a real Dragon King.
Here. You can also draw it.
I don’t know how to draw.
It’s OK.
It’s so beautiful.
Is that one…
me?
It’s us.
Can I
see him again?
What am I thinking about?
He is the Dragon King.
He has no time to see me.
Dragon King,
thank you for escorting me
all the way.
Liuying,
I decided not to return your favor.
You don’t need to.
It’s like a hundred years
all this time.
So, to you,
a day feels like a year
when you are with me?
One day with you is like
loving you for a hundred years.
But a moment away from you
is like a thousand years of suffering.
My feelings for you are not
from gratitude.
Liuying,
I love you.
Since we have feelings for each other,
and promise each other a lifetime,
we can get married.
♪Pure white sunshine♪
♪Clouds hide the moss♪
Do you know what a kiss is?
♪There comes the deer’s call♪
Why do you ask me this?
I read it in the book
that people in love
will use kisses to express love.
♪Wind blows the skirt’s hemline♪
♪You’re in the shadow of the tree♪
So…
So I asked you.
♪If I don’t come along♪
I don’t know.
♪Will you only hesitate♪
It doesn’t matter.
We can learn it together.
♪The leaves rustling♪
I don’t want to.
♪Not too loud♪
Liuying,
do you know what a bridal chamber means?
♪The heart beats fast♪
I… I don’t know.
♪And deafening♪
It’s OK. We can learn that as well.
♪Wait until the red sunset♪
Look! Star Halo!
So beautiful!
The Star Halo shows up.
It’s a good sign.
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
With the Star Halo as proof,
this is my token of love to you.
♪Like a thick win flows into the sea♪
♪And into your heart♪
What will you give me?
I… I don’t have anything to give you.
How about we make a bet?
If the Star Halo shows up again
in three days,
at that time,
you need to give me a token as well.
Anything can be accepted.
Anything?
Then…
What if there is no Star Halo?
♪The heart beats fast and deafening♪
♪Wait until the red sunset♪
Then, let’s learn the kiss
together.
♪Embraces the delicate breeze♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
♪Like a thick win flows into the sea♪
♪And into your heart♪
♪Thousands kinds of beautiful flowers♪
♪Are not as good as your grace♪
Why don’t you eat one?
♪Like a thick win flows into the sea♪
♪And into your heart♪
(Xia)
What’s going on?
Miss, don’t come out.
There seems to be
a wolf demon around here.
Miss! Why are you out?
-Mother!
-Miss!
-Xue!
-Mother!
Xue! Don’t come over!
Mother!
Miss! Watch out!
Hurry up! Protect Xue!
-Xue!
-Yes, sir!
-Miss!
-Xue!
Miss!
Xue!
Miss! Are you all right?
-Mother!
-Xue!
-Help!
-Are you all right?
Miss!
Xue!
-Xue!
-Miss!
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Finally, you’re back.
What’s wrong?
Miss was attacked by a wolf demon
on her way back home.
She was so badly wounded
that the physician said
she had only days left to live.
Miss!
I knew I couldn’t leave you
for a moment.
What happened?
Dragon King,
you said there was an elixir, right?
Miss Xue was attacked by a wolf demon
and the physician says she is dying.
Don’t worry.
I will go get you the elixir right now.
Don’t cry, OK?
Cultivate it with elegance.
Strengthen it with energy.
Protect it with spirit.
Give me some of your elixir.
You got hurt again?
I need to help someone.
Who is that important to you?
A person I met once.
I’m afraid it’s
love at first sight.
Stop your nonsense.
Just give me that.
Then tell me
who it is.
If you keep doing this,
I will get it myself.
Why do you always do this?
Demon and human are in
two different worlds.
Don’t go…
too far.
Miss,
you will be fine.
Dragon King said
he would help you.
Liuying.
Dragon King.
You promised not to cry.
Help her to have this.
Miss!
Dragon King,
is she alright?
Miss!
Miss… is dead.
Looks like the wolf demon
poisoned her.
The elixir can cure wounds,
but not detoxicate.
What to do? What to do now?
Don’t worry.
Her soul has just left.
I will go chase it now.
Miss!
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Annoying barrier!
Haven’t my powers been fully restored?
Is there nothing I can do
but change back to my original self?
That’s really how Lord is.
Concentrate! Focus on it!
Try again!
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Dragon King? Why are you here?
Why are you here?
I was caught by Lord of Luofeng Pavilion
to be his maidservant.
That’s a great convenience.
-Take me to find Xiahou…
-Wait.
Listen to me first.
Go tell Liuying to
protect Xiahou Xue well
and bless her a long life.
If Xiahou Xue is dead,
Liuying will also die after that.
My Lord, Xiahou Xue died by accident.
Her soul has arrived at
Luofeng Pavilion.
The oath has been recorded in
the Oath Tower.
With seven days,
Liuying will die of the oath.
My Lord,
a dragon demon intruded into our barrier
and hurt our people,
saying that he wants Xiahou Xue’s soul.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Give me Xiahou Xue’s soul!
Do you know trespassing
on Luofeng Pavilion is a felony?
In this world,
no one can stop me.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Dragon King.
Dragon King,
why don’t you go cultivate to become
the immortal dragon,
but come to Luofeng Pavilion
for Xiahou Xue’s soul?
Give me Xiahou Xue’s soul!
Or,
I will destroy your pavilion.
You can take her soul away…
My Lord!
But,
I have to go through the laws of Heaven.
Go ahead.
You have to marry Xiahou Xue
and guard her through three tribulations
if you want to take her away.
I can’t guard her through
three tribulations,
let alone marrying her.
There are no other ways
to do it in this world.
The tribulation comes once
in a thousand years.
Dragon King, you’d better think twice.
Xiahou Xue and Liuying
will die
together,
right?
How do you know that?
I’m asking you.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Yes.
Then I will take
this oath out from the Oath Tower.
The Oath Tower is built by ancient Nuwa.
Even God can’t change it,
let alone you and me.
Then, I’ll find it myself.
Her soul has been hidden as an ant.
No matter who it is,
even with a thousand eyes and hands,
no one will be able to find her.
So,
I have no choice but to say yes?
Dragon King,
(Luofeng Pavilion)
if you insist on giving up
the tribulation,
you will have to wait for
a thousand years.
Guard Xiahou Xue
to go through three tribulations.
Deal.
Will anything bad happen?
No way.
He is the Dragon King.
Everything will be fine.
Miss,
you will be fine.
You will.
They say you are the Dragon King.
You can save me, right?
And, I will marry you.
We have no other choices. Let’s go.
Dragon King, are you really
going to wait for another thousand years
before becoming Immortal Dragon?
I don’t understand why you did this.
You don’t need to understand.
My Lord,
you really allow him
to take Xiahou Xue away?
It’s a promise. Anything wrong?
But,
what about the sky net?
Liuying.
Dragon King!
Is everything alright?
Don’t worry. It’s fine.
Miss!
Miss! You’re finally alright.
Dragon King,
thank you.
I’m… I’m just too excited.
I’ll go tell this good news
to Master and Madam.
The Star Halo really shows up again!
Star Halo…
About our promise…
My parents passed away.
So, we just need a simple wedding.
But I need to say goodbye to
Master and Miss Xue.
They are like my family.
Why don’t you say something?
I’m wondering
if there is anything else
I can do for you.
Nothing else.
You and Miss Xue are all well.
I have no other wishes.
Think twice.
I can help you
to do anything you want.
Then, promise me
to protect yourself.
Don’t get hurt again.
It took you a long time to go
find Miss Xue back last time.
I was so worried.
You don’t need to worry about me
in the future.
Liuying,
you really don’t need to
worry about me anymore.
Just forget me.
Take this as a dream.
What do you mean?
I…
I can’t marry you.
That’s right.
You’re the Dragon King.
I’m just an ordinary person.
It’s not like that.
Because
I have to marry Xiahou Xue.
Miss?
Why?
Remind the Dragon King
of that no ordinary people
can know our deal.
Or, all the immortals or human beings
who know it
will be punished severely.
What I said before was just
a mistake.
Don’t take it seriously.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪