♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 5=
Well, when we
met you in the garden,
was it just after a thunder strike?
It must hurt a lot.
Yes.
It hurt a lot.
It pains here
and here too.
So at a moment like this,
she doesn’t care about that men and
women shouldn’t have direct contact.
What’s that sound?
Why is your heart pumping so fast?
In dramas,
this is love.
Dramas are not always right.
Is your heart racing?
Dumpling.
Fabrics.
My Lord.
Sleeping?
I’d like to see
what new tricks you’re playing.
I, Qingqing, have seen a lot,
and am picky about beauty.
But
this skin,
this face,
in the three worlds,
only the word perfect can describe them.
And the forehead,
full and bright,
shines the charm of man
and the luster of jade.
Wish I could
have such a forehead.
What a shame.
He has the face
that makes women jealous,
but his heart is so ugly,
unforgiving, petty!
I know it.
I’m sorry.
Lord has a generous heart.
You’ll forgive me.
I’ll go cleaning.
The girl in green…
who is she?
Look, it’s beautiful!
Yeah.
The cakes are beautiful, too.
We have some free crispy durian cakes
and plum cakes for you.
No durian cakes, please.
We’re promoting durian
because it’s from my boss’s hometown.
Any guest in our restaurant
who eats the durian cake
will get a delicate gift
made by paper-folding master Kongkong.
I want it!
Sure.
You…
Don’t you hate durian?
Why did you take mine?
I love it.
Yummy!
Thank you, Liuying.
I can’t believe he made
such a lovely thing
from a piece of paper.
It’s amazing!
I wanna figure it out.
How did he make it?
For you.
So cute!
You may flap its tail.
It moves! Amazing!
How did you make it?
Could you teach me?
This paper dragon is unique.
I’m the only maker in the world.
It’s the only one?
I’ll take good care of it.
Liuying.
I knew it.
Whenever you call my name
you’ll touch my head.
Whenever I call you,
my hand is out of control.
Like this.
Liuying.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
Bingxing.
Where are you going?
Let me guess.
It is a banquet,
an important banquet,
a banquet about peach flower, isn’t it?
The floral adornment on my forehead,
you saw it.
This is the floral adornment?
It’s beautiful!
Yes, it is.
Bingxing’s peach adornment
is always the most beautiful
in the Peach Feast.
The Peach Feast?
May I join you?
Is there something yummy?
Are there performances?
Have you done your job?
No.
Back to work.
The most coldblooded Lord in the world!
He gives me so many works
that will never be done!
I’m not interested in the Peach Feast.
I’m interested in the floral adornment.
Nobody said only the feast attenders
could have the floral adornment.
It’s dark.
We can’t get to the town tonight.
We’ll camp here for the night.
Alright.
Marble,
you’re all right now.
We’ll camp here tonight.
Come on,
sleep.
Marble!
Marble,
do you like here
and wanna stay?
If you do like it,
take it to Xiahou’s Mansion.
It won’t like it.
It’s a free creature in nature.
I can’t be selfish.
Marble,
if you wanna go,
go as you like.
It goes.
I won’t do that to you.
I’ll never leave you.
I’ll always be good to you.
Will you?
But,
I have to serve my lady, always.
Doesn’t matter.
She can’t prevent me
from returning your favor.
It's returning the favor again.
For a thousand of years, Yuchi Longyan
never breaks a promise.
Since I’ll be your man,
let’s exchange the token.
Token?
What do you want?
Fallen-flower Valley!
The book says
the love token will be exchanged
in a place like a dreamland.
Tell me,
what token do you prefer?
Luminous pearl?
How about ambergris?
Or
tear of the North Sea Shark Men?
I…
I don’t need you to return
the favor.
Hard to decide?
Is it because I am somehow
different to him?
Did you give a token to every one
of your savors?
Definitely no.
I didn’t have a savor.
You are the only one.
So, haven’t you decided yet?
Not necessary.
Your name Liuying means fireflies,
so, I’ll give you a firefly rain.
♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if the moon shone for you♪
♪Bright or dim♪
♪Fate is like a rain of flowers♪
♪Withering in the sentimental world♪
♪In a flash I picked your teardrop♪
♪Does my heart ripple with memories♪
♪Only to remember you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
So beautiful!
Thank you!
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
All theses
are far from enough to tell my love.
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
Before I marry you,
I...
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
I… I’m tired.
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
I… I understand.
The ethics.
♪I wanna stay with you in this life♪
Good night.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
You went to the feast anyway,
and I
will use your dressing case.
This one? Or that one?
Almighty God, please tell me,
which one
of the two things fits me best?
None of them does.
God replies.
God…
My Lord!
I… I’m not slacking off.
I’ve cleaned the floor.
I’m a slave girl though,
a slave girl needs to rest,
because
the book says
she squats before jumping higher,
she rests before going further.
You don’t feed me,
at least you’d allow me to rest.
-I just…
-Shut it!
Can’t I have the floral makeup?
I’m your slave girl though,
if I look better,
it’s your grace.
I’ll help you.
That’s the most glamorous smile
I’ve ever seen.
My Lord,
can you make the floral adornment?
What?
You reject?
No, no, no!
My honor.
Thank you, My Lord.
Isn’t it too close?
I need a good look at you.
Am I in my dream?
Close your eyes.
Done.
Am I the prettiest girl
in the world…
This is the meteor adornment.
Like it?
That bird needs to learn pecking order.
She dared throw me out.
Did I do anything wrong?
How could I get rid of the meteor?
Seems the meteor is her old scar.
It was a joke.
Don’t be so sad.
Because of the meteor scar,
they mock at me time and time again.
And you made it bigger.
I’m a little elf,
but I have my dignity.
I just wanted to be pretty.
Why did you do that to me!
I…
I didn’t do it well.
I’ll redo it.
No!
I was giving an order.
Close your eyes.
Turn around.
Open your eyes.
You’re welcome.
I didn’t thank you.
Don’t expect me to forgive you.
I can do it…
do it much better.
Is that so?
Next time I won’t give a hand.
Do it yourself.
Inerasable?
The mark is cast on her soul.
She’s just an elf.
That’s impossible.
Why does it
seem
sort of familiar?
It’s so weird.
I think of him
and my heart races.
I think of marrying her
and my heart beats so wildly.
(Love with Dragon)
(Love with Dragon Chapter 3)
You like the book?
It’s my favorite story.
You brought me my book.
The Dragon King on it is so handsome!
Better than me?
Certainly not.
He’s in his armor.
So heroic!
Heroic.
You…
And in the king’s banquet.
(Love with Dragon)
King?
Don’t you know I am
the offspring of the Candle Dragon,
the real King?
(Love with Dragon Chapter 6)
That dragon carries a lady and flies.
Why aren’t you afraid?
The book says
the Dragon King protects his love.
You believe in the book.
Do you believe in me?
Yes,
I do.
That Dragon King protects his love.
I protect you.
Yes.
Are you afraid now?
I’m…
I’m not so afraid.
I’ll protect you forever.
Trust me,
will you?
Yes.
Is forever possible?
Liuying, you fool,
the Dragon King is returning your favor.
We can’t get married.
It’s just a dream,
a sweet dream.
(Luofeng Pavilion)
It’s all clear.
My Lord.
Running away?
No, no, no.
My Lord, I’m not.
I just…
wanna take a walk…
get some fresh air.
I never thought about running away.
The honest will be forgiven.
My Lord, pardon me, please.
Don’t punish me with hunger!
I’d starve to death!
I’d be a bird jerky!
Save a life and
-you’ll be…
-Enough!
Why do you run away?
I have to!
In here I’m an imprisoned slave girl,
washing and cooking,
an errand girl serving your reading,
and I’m disliked for talking too much.
You took my power.
I can’t find my real me.
A bird that doesn’t fly
has no difference from a chicken.
I was the prettiest in the birds’ realm!
Look at me now!
As black as tar!
Unsightly! Disgraceful!
I know. Go back.
What is the penalty?
I’m thinking.
My Lord,
you have a lot to live up with,
don’t waste time on the petty things.
The penalty would be cleaning.
It’s enough.
My Lord,
Bingxing has located the Yin Soul.
Good.
The Yin Soul?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪