♪Do I have repeated lives
over a thousand years♪
♪Only to find you♪
♪As if all feelings were for you♪
♪Regretful or rueful♪
♪Fate is like evanescent shadow♪
♪Wandering in the sentimental world♪
♪Predestined fate starts
where my heart goes♪
♪In the reincarnation of lives♪
♪I meet you in every dream♪
♪Fly the fireflies all over the sky♪
♪In whose eyes mirrors the gleam♪
♪Glance back and don’t want to leave♪
♪I keep my love for you♪
♪I’ll never leave you in my next life♪
=Miss The Dragon=
=Episode 7=
The Star Halo really appears again!
The promise between us...
My parents were gone.
So, the wedding could be simple.
Why are you silent?
I’m thinking
if I can help you realize
any other wishes.
Then promise me
you’ll protect yourself well.
Don’t get hurt again.
It was a long time
when you looked for Miss.
I was worried about you.
You won’t worry about me anymore.
Forget me.
Take it as a dream.
What do you mean?
I
can’t marry you.
That makes sense.
You are Dragon King.
I’m just a mortal.
That’s the reason.
It’s because
I have to marry your miss.
Miss?
Why?
What I said
was just a misunderstanding.
Don’t take it seriously.
Alright.
I know
it’s just a misunderstanding.
Dragon King.
You’re going to marry Miss.
We should
keep a distance.
Miss and you
both mean the world
to me.
Are you heartbroken?
You don’t understand.
Of course I do.
I’ve watched many operas.
I know you’re heartbroken.
So is Miss Liuying.
You love each other,
but you can’t be together.
His skin.
His look.
In the Heaven, the underworld,
and the mortal world,
he’s absolutely perfect.
(Green Orchid, homophone of Qingqing)
My Lord.
Qingqing is really gone.
But she has lost all her power.
How could she get out
of Luofeng Pavilion?
Without her, Luofeng Pavilion is
much quieter.
Should I get her back with some men?
Never mind.
Miss.
Do you feel unwell?
I’ve fully recovered.
Really.
Thanks to Dragon King.
I heard that
he even fought with immortals for me.
He’s really kind to you.
Liuying, you know what?
He said he’d marry me.
I believe he’ll be a good husband.
Congratulations, Miss.
But you know,
will my parents disagree with it?
Master said that,
he was saved by a tiger demon
when he was young.
So, he bears gratitude in heart.
Madam believes in Buddhism.
She is kind to all beings.
I guess,
they’ll also think
Dragon King
is a good man to marry.
Yes.
Dragon King also said,
he’d move and live here
after we get married.
It’ll be the same as before.
Nothing will change.
Right?
Miss.
I’ll take the bowl away.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
What I said
was just a misunderstanding.
Don’t take it seriously.
I have no idea
why you said that.
But I know you didn’t mean that.
Otherwise,
you wouldn’t look away from me.
What on earth
are you hiding from me?
♪On the riverbank
A beautiful face alone under the moon♪
♪Meet like a dream♪
Alright.
I’ll pretend to believe you
and take everything
as a misunderstanding.
♪Parting is the hardest♪
♪Zither is playing melodiously♪
♪Miss you from dawn to dusk♪
You are going to marry her.
♪Sing a song of sorrows♪
I cannot
keep this painting with me.
I can only keep it in my heart.
♪A lonely toast to the good time♪
This is my love token for you.
♪How to forget in the running time♪
♪The day the person the love♪
Liuying.
I love you.
Let it end
where it began.
♪When and where to meet♪
All of that was ephemeral.
It doesn’t count.
Dragon King.
What brings you here?
Why are you here?
I...
I come to pick some fallen blossoms
to decorate Miss’s wedding room.
She’s supposed to like it.
Do you like
the fallen blossoms?
Fall like rain.
Leave fragrance in the air.
I think it’s beautiful.
Very beautiful.
Fallen blossoms and fireflies
all pass in an instant,
not worthy of lingering on.
Yes.
Dragon King.
In the operas,
on the wedding day,
bride and groom are both dressed in red.
Is it true?
In the mortal world, the red color
is a symbol of beauty and joy.
Bride and groom are dressed in red
on their wedding day
for good fortune.
Does it look good?
Yes.
Dragon King and Miss should...
Perhaps I’ve lived for too long.
For me, many mortal affairs
are insignificant like feathers.
Sometimes, a lifetime
feels like an instant,
but sometimes, an instant
is eternal.
Thank you.
I’ll keep this instant
eternally in my heart.
It’s windy and cold here.
Don’t stay too long.
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪Inseparable in this life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪Inseparable in this life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪The fate of time♪
♪I miss you all my life♪
Sorry.
I’ve promised
to love her heart and soul.
♪The wish in hand♪
♪It’s meant to be♪
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Liuying.
What happened to you recently?
Why do you look upset?
I see.
You must’ve secretly read the play.
Yes, I’ve read the play.
Don’t read it again.
By the way,
do you remember my cousin Zhiyuan?
He came here for the exam,
but accidentally fell off the horse.
My mother got him to recuperate
in the mansion.
She said you’re meticulous
and asked you to look after him.
Yes.
You blinked. You lost.
It doesn’t count.
A bug was flying by.
Immortal Ziyang.
It was dust just now.
Now it’s a bug.
Stop cheating me.
Plus this round,
you’ve lost 3,941 times in total.
I’ll tell your lord on you.
I was told that an old friend has come.
So, it’s Immortal Ziyang.
You are not blind.
Bingxing said, the repair of sky net
greatly consumed your power.
That seems to be an exaggeration.
Sorry, My Lord.
I made a mistake. Please punish me.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
You’d better punish her to be a judge
at River of Tears.
How to punish my maid
is not your concern.
Yes. Why should I meddle with
your business?
I’m off.
Immortal Ziyang.
You lost.
Alright. Alright.
I know you think highly of yourself.
You’re headstrong and thin-skinned.
You never ask for help.
If it’s not for Bingxing...
Here you are.
This is...
A love token someone gave you
a millennia ago.
Do you take it seriously?
It’s Zisui Yangyan.
As hot as dragon fire.
Of course. Wearing it,
you’ll be able to forcefully
take the Yin soul
and use her to fix the sky net.
Is it made with your power?
Of course.
You’re welcome.
You can only have it for three days.
I’ll surely get it back in three days.
Thank you, Immortal Ziyang.
Alright. You’re welcome.
I’m off.
I swear I’ll never ever
bet with you again.
This medicine is effective,
(Xu Zhiyuan)
but it hurts.
Young Master. Please bear with it.
Dragon King.
-Dragon...
-Shut up.
Why are you here?
Do you forget it?
You asked me to look after Liuying,
so I’m watching here.
Have you been here
all these days?
Day and night. Not a step away.
I’m a bird demon,
but I’m a bird of duty.
Is she
alright?
She looks very well.
But Dragon King,
you don’t look very well.
Are you sick?
I feel suffocated
and can’t breathe.
I want to fight.
Gosh.
You... Are you jealous?
Even Dragon King is jealous?
Jealous?
Jealousy is a kind of description.
How to put it? It means,
when you see
Liuying is intimidate with a man,
you wish that man could be you.
When she talks and laughs with others,
you wish you could be
the one with her.
When she’s gentle to others,
you wish you could be
the one by her side.
But it’s not you in reality.
So, you’re angry,
worried, and anxious.
You feel bad and sick.
Yet you can do nothing
but to be jealous.
You feel bad like drinking
a jar of vinegar.
Seeing is believing.
This is how a jealous man looks like.
Interesting.
-Interesting!
-Shut up.
Do you want to know
how to relieve the jealousy?
Let me think.
You can crazily smash things
or drown your sorrows with wine.
Stupid and naive.
Smashing things and drinking
cannot relieve
any of my bad feelings.
Young Master.
Keep a distance.
Stupid and naive.
How dare you!
You don’t call me along for drinking.
Why are you drinking alone?
Looks like something is bothering you.
The wine made by Immortal of Wine
is tasty
and also miraculous.
It can cure jealousy.
You want to marry this girl,
but you have to marry that girl.
This time, I come
with a worse message.
Days ago, I looked over
the Book of Fate,
and saw Xiahou’s Mansion
would be involved in a rebellious case.
Emperor would be outrageous.
Xiahou’s Mansion would be confiscated.
Men would be enslaved
and women whored.
What about others?
You should check the Book of Fate
in my library.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Your cousin will surely succeed
in this exam.
I plan to marry Liuying to him.
If Zhiyuan can really succeed,
we’ll have bet on the right person.
Even if he fails,
we’ll lose nothing.
Father.
It depends on Liuying’s will.
I don’t think she’ll agree.
She’s a maid.
Why would she disagree?
Besides, marrying your cousin
is a high honor for her.
Father, she and I are like sisters.
That’s why you should persuade her.
If Zhiyuan has a great future,
she’ll also enjoy the honor.
Don’t you want her
to have a good marriage?
More than a maid, she’s
being an attendant.
Badly, Dragon King isn’t here.
Or else, I could see him jealous again.
Here comes the devil.
Your Highness...
It’s you!
You want to flee?
Yes,
but you are stopping me, aren’t you?
How do you know I am here?
A surprise anyway.
My Lord, please spare me.
Thank you, My Lord.
What a strong power.
It’s warm. What is it?
No, it’s hot.
I got it.
With this, you can get close to Liuying
and take her soul away.
You...! You...!
You are such a human-like devil!
Liuying is a nice person.
Saving a person is better than
building a seven-level pagoda.
She’s worth
a 49-level pagoda,
even beyond the sky!
Just because she’s born with Yin soul,
you break heavenly rules
and forcefully capture her.
It’s unfair to capture her.
But to ensure the peace
of mortal world,
she must be sacrificed.
That’s an excuse!
I don’t believe it.
The world is so big.
Must her soul be used
to fix the sky net?
What if the sky net breaks again?
Get another soul?
Anyway, there’re countless souls
in the world.
No need to cherish or care about them.
Is this the so-called Heaven?
In my view,
you are the same as demons,
selfish and horrible.
Qingqing.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Dragon King. You’re back in time.
Listen to me.
It was so close.
Luckily, I watched over her closely
and got her out of the great danger.
What did Xu Zhiyuan do?
Not him.
It’s the Lord of Luofeng Pavilion.
He meant to take her soul away
with this.
Zisui Yangyan!
You have good eyes.
(Xiahou’s Mansion)
Why do you want Liuying’s soul?
My duty.
To hurt Liuying?
In your dreams.
You know it well.
You’re not my match.
Dragon King.
Why are you against me for a maid?
Look!
You’ve spoken your true thought!
You look down on maids!
You take lightly of their lives!
Your soul should be deprived
for breaking into Luofeng Pavilion.
I’ve spared your life.
But you forced me to be your maid
and sealed my power.
You asked me to practice singing
in that damp, black and cold
River of Tears.
You’re tone deaf.
Singing there, you wouldn’t
disturb anyone.
Why did you paint me
like a clown?
Do you think maids need no respect
or dignity?
But I helped you
fix your preach-blossom makeup.
He’s been as cold as ice,
now bickering with a bird demon.
It’s weird.
You punished me
and didn’t allow me to eat
to make me weak,
get sick and...
But you were lively enough to flee.
Were you weak?
You...
Continue.
It’s rare that you say so many words.
You destroyed Zisui Yangyan!
I’m letting you know
Liuying is mine.
Don’t you dare lay a finger on her.
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Don’t you dare lay a finger on her!
So, Xiahou Xue and you...
Taking back Xiahou Xue’s soul
was to prevent Liuying
from being sealed into sky net.
Liuying is the most important person
to me.
You gave up the millennium
opportunity of ascension
to protect Xiahou Xue, but...
For Liuying,
I’ll be against the whole Heaven
to protect her,
not to mention Luofeng Pavilion.
Find another way
to fix the sky net.
You are such a human-like devil.
Selfish and horrible!
Qingqing.
She’s so bold,
but why am I not angry?
♪When dream is over I want more♪
♪Memories make me miss you♪
♪I want to spend my life with you♪
♪There’s regret when we part♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪
♪I keep waiting over a thousand years♪
♪To complete our destiny♪
♪Feelings get me stuck in loneliness♪
♪I’m waiting to meet you again♪
♪Your knitted brows
can’t remove the obsession♪
♪It lingers around♪
♪If I no longer miss you♪
♪How can I repay the previous life♪