EPISODE 14
I heard Ju Kyung came to school...
- with no makeup on.
- But do you really think...
she's dating Soo Ho?
I saw her with no makeup on earlier,
and she looked worse than in the photo.
I bet they broke up after
he saw her bare face.
Who would date a girl like her?
Isn't Soo Ho a little out
of it these days as well?
Remember what happened to his dad?
He must be dating anyone because
he's not in his right mind.
I can't believe you said that.
- Let's go.
- Seriously?
- Hey, look.
Hey, you!
- Take back what you just said.
- Ju Kyung?
You must be nuts to go
around with no makeup on.
Fine. I'm dating Soo Ho.
Soo Ho is my boyfriend!
Is that good enough for you?
Does that satisfy your curiosity?
- She must be nuts.
- Yes, it looks like it.
He doesn't judge people
based on their appearances.
He likes me for who I am.
He's incomparable to girls like you
who have horrible personalities.
So don't badmouth him just
because he's dating me.
From now on, come and talk to me in person.
I'll deal with you myself. Do you understand?
And if you have time to
judge other people's looks,
why don't you use that
time to study a bit more?
Get out of my way.
They must really be dating.
I'm so jealous.
Let's go.
Hey, you're here.
- What should we eat today?
- Tteokbokki!
- I know a good place nearby.
- Really? Let's go there.
A boyfriend? Of course not.
This is a sweet ride you have.
- Your career must be going strong.
- Do you like it?
Yes.
Do you want it?
How cute.
From this moment on, you'll be my grapefruit.
But I'm her grapefruit!
My heart nearly jumped out of my chest.
I'd love to eat a grapefruit.
I love grapefruit, that's all.
Are they really dating? Lucky her.
Us dating is no longer a secret.
Yes. Today's the day I reveal
my relationship with you...
and my bare face.
Are you all right?
No.
My heart shriveled to the size of a bean.
Then why didn't you put on makeup as usual?
Go Woon once said to me,
if I hate how I look just
because others tease me,
it's the same as admitting that I'm a loser.
So from now on,
I'm only going to listen
to people who like me.
I won't care about whatever
people say about me...
when they know about me.
I won't ever run away or hide again.
That's why I'm here wearing my bare face.
I see you've all grown up.
Yes, Mom. Ju Kyung's fine. The
Divine Soo Ho is by her side.
What? The Divine Soo Ho?
So don't worry.
Are you sure no one's bullying
her? I don't need to go, right?
Okay.
Is Ju Kyung doing okay?
Ju Young says she looks okay,
but who knows how she
might be feeling inside?
She'll be fine. She's your daughter.
Why are you here?
Just go!
Gosh.
- Go! Leave!
- What's he doing?
- Go!
- Is he talking to us?
Stop trying to sway me, and just leave!
Go!
What kind of a lunatic...
Mr. Han?
"Mr. Han"?
Hello.
You're not allowed to park here.
So seeing this car parked here...
makes me feel sad.
Goodbye.
Who gets so angry over a parked car?
Does he have anger management problems?
No, he has cuteness management problems.
Gosh, look.
- My gosh.
- Unbelievable.
- Seriously?
They're so cute.
- Did you see that?
- My gosh.
I can't believe this.
My gosh.
They're unbelievable.
My gosh, I'm so jealous of her.
Ju Kyung, I worried about you a lot.
You were really cool earlier.
- Hello.
Let's go home now, guys.
Mr. Han, school just started.
Yes, I know.
- What?
You're not supposed to be in
our class, so please leave.
Mr. Han, she's Lim Ju Kyung.
Yes, I know.
- Ju Kyung?
- Yes?
Ju Kyung, is that you?
- Yes.
- Ju Kyung...
Ju Kyung, I'm so glad you're back.
I mean...
I was... I was so...
I was so worried about you.
- My gosh.
- Is he crying?
Don't cry!
My gosh.
Don't cry, Mr. Han.
Is he really crying?
I'm sorry, guys.
I just can't believe Ju
Kyung is finally back.
- Don't cry! Don't cry!
- Cheer up!
- Don't cry!
I'm sorry.
That's it for today.
Don't cry, Mr. Han.
I can't believe you thought
of coming to school like that.
What?
Are you trying to put on a show
in front of everyone in school?
Were you so desperate to attract attention?
Have you suddenly become brave
now that you're dating Soo Ho?
Soo Jin!
Are you serious?
- Soo Ah.
- Soo Jin.
You're the worst.
You should be apologizing to her on
your knees. But what did you say?
Did you seriously just say that to her?
Why should I apologize?
Because you were the one who
uploaded her photos and video.
- What's going on?
- Hey, stop him.
- That's not good.
- Should we stop him?
- Shouldn't we stop him?
- What's going on?
- You want me to stop him?
- Go on.
- Where are you going?
I bet you think...
you destroyed Ju Kyung by doing this.
But you just destroyed yourself.
At first, I tried to understand.
I figured you might've gotten angry
because you had feelings for Soo Ho.
So I thought you'd at least
be regretting it right now.
Ju Kyung wasn't coming to school,
so I thought you'd feel bad about it...
and be worried about her.
So...
I waited for you to apologize to her.
But were you always such a horrible person?
Yes.
It turns out I was.
Soo Ah!
Soo Jin.
Why do you keep crossing the line?
Is there something going on at home?
Is it because of your dad?
What does it matter to you?
I just can't seem to understand.
You were never like this.
Is this what you really want?
- Yes.
- I know you're lying.
I know you're also going to regret it.
So it's not too late.
Go and apologize to Ju Kyung.
- Apologize and...
- Don't tell me what to do.
Soo Ah.
Soo Ah, wait.
Soo Ah, I'm sorry.
Let go of me.
I'm so sorry for not telling you.
But I was worried we might no
longer be friends if I told you.
Ju Kyung, what did you take me for?
Did you even think of me as your best friend?
That's why I couldn't tell you.
But you told Soo Jin.
You told her everything,
but you kept me in the dark.
You thought I'd turn my back on you
if you showed me your bare face?
I know I may seem a little
thoughtless at times,
but how could you think I'd be so shallow?
I'm sorry, Soo Ah.
I was so eager to help you get a boyfriend,
but you didn't even tell
me you were dating Soo Ho.
Did I have to find out about him
through the online school community?
I'm sorry, Soo Ah.
What do you think made her become like that?
Nothing made her become like that.
She just chose to be that kind of person.
How could she do that to you?
Soo Jin let go of our hand.
I guess we didn't mean...
anything to her.
Let me look at you properly.
Why did you try so hard
to keep it a secret...
You'll become prettier once
you take care of your skin.
Start going to the dermatologist,
drink a lot of water, and
start taking vitamins.
Then it'll get better. Don't worry.
And you'd better tell me
everything from the start.
When did you and Soo Ho
start dating each other?
Who was the first person to
confess? Is he nice to you?
Is Lee Soo Ho, that sociopath, mean to you?
No, he's not mean to me.
You have no right to smile yet.
You need to tell me every little detail.
We'll have to stay up all night, okay?
What did this mean?
Gosh, take it off already. That's disgusting.
Didn't you give it to
me because you liked me?
What are you talking about?
Let me ask you one last time.
Don't you feel a little motivated
to let me into your heart?
- No, not really.
- No. I want you to prove it.
If you really have no
feelings for me whatsoever,
I want you to step on me.
Gosh, think about it carefully.
I'm asking you this for the last time.
I don't want to stay as his friend
only to like him one-sidedly...
like you're doing with Ju Kyung.
Hey, are you okay?
Are you crying?
I'm sure I didn't hit you that hard.
Seo Jun.
What am I going to do?
What?
Did you get rejected by Go Woon?
I like her so much.
But she doesn't like me at all.
My heart flutters every time I see her.
So how can I stay friends with her?
You're right.
I know I'll be really good to
her if I become her boyfriend.
Exactly.
I never knew how painful it
was to have a crush on someone.
Like I knew?
But do you know something?
A person who tries everything has no regrets.
Now that I've been rejected
after officially asking her out,
I think I can finally move on.
When did you two start dating?
It hasn't been very long.
Ever since the class trip.
Since back then?
Why you...
Hey. I have a question.
When was your first kiss?
During the school trip...
You idiot.
Why are you asking that?
- What?
- You jerk.
Even I think that's wrong.
You guys hate everything I do.
"The snow must have tried again and again"
"To make a flower bloom
on the swaying branch"
"It must have knocked again and again"
"It must have danced again and again"
"It must have slipped hundreds of times"
"Look at the beauty that it
finally succeeded in blooming"
"Every spring, the branches burst open"
"The most beautiful wounds
from where they were burned"
"They burst open"
"The most beautiful wounds
from where they were burned"
What do you think?
- Are you sleepy?
- Yes.
I couldn't sleep much.
I'll take a nap in the
music room. You go eat.
I can't do that. Wait
there. I'll bring you food.
No, it's okay...
What...
Hey. You're up.
When did you get here?
You woke me up.
You must be tired,
Soo Ho's cousin.
I wasn't trying to lie to you.
I wasn't fooled.
You and Soo Ho were so
obvious that you were lying.
What? You knew back then?
What? What do you want to say?
You don't look that different
with or without makeup.
How could I have been fooled?
I don't get it.
Thanks.
You're ugly just the same.
Stop teasing me.
I heard you made them...
take down my video.
Thanks.
No problem.
How cute. I'm so jealous.
I wish I had a girlfriend too.
Are you going on a date today?
Where to? Want me to tell you
some of the best date spots?
I know how to run searches too.
Those places are all advertisements.
Most of them are places
that girls can't stand.
This guy knows absolutely
nothing about dating.
Really?
Let's see which places he looked up.
Let's see.
What do you think?
- Not bad.
- You did well.
- He says you did well.
- Hold on. Wait. What is this?
- I love you so much
Oh dear
You're too pretty
- Oh my gosh.
- Hey.
You cutie pie.
You have everything planned.
Hard on the outside, soft on the inside.
- Right?
- A total softy.
- Oh dear
- Quiet.
- Our softy.
- Bye.
- Ju Kyung.
- Oh dear
- Yes?
I'm taking Ju Kyung today.
Sorry. I'll call you.
Oh no, what will you do?
- Oh dear
We'll play with you
- We'll play with you
- Oh dear
Awesome.
They look so hot in the cover picture.
How long has it been since
Crash released a new song?
You look so cute,
but you like hard rock? It's so unexpected.
- Two corndogs please.
- That looks good.
Thank you.
Let's go.
- Let's see what's in Hye Min's bag.
- Let's see.
- That hurts.
- It hurts?
- Will you beat her up for me?
- I'll kill her.
What was that? Did they just
take a kid from our school?
Where are you going?
- Ju Kyung!
- I'm starving.
Five corndogs please.
Wait for me!
Five orders of tteokbokki too.
Darn it.
Take this.
Flip and kick.
Yes. Take that.
When are you guys leaving?
Yes! Quiet. After this.
This is important. Don't talk to us.
- Darn it.
- Darn it!
Let's see how much money she has.
You said you'd leave me alone.
That you'd let me go.
That was if you had dug up dirt...
on Ju Kyung.
But you did absolutely nothing.
Am I wrong?
Hey, Park Se Mi!
Ju Kyung?
It's Dumpling.
Good timing. I've been
meaning to go see you anyway.
Let Hye Min go.
What if I refuse?
Hye Min, come here.
You're not going anywhere.
Look at her.
So you're dating Lee Soo Ho while
keeping Han Seo Jun by your side.
Our Ju Kyung has grown up.
The video and photos of you
were posted online, right?
Your life is completely ruined.
It's not like you can
be reborn though, right?
You!
Darn it.
It must be a death wish that you have.
The ones with the death wish are you three.
Take this!
This is an unfair fight!
You...
Does your mom know what you're up to?
Leave my mom out of this.
One, two, three, head!
You've grown some balls, have you?
What on earth do you have in there? It hurts.
You little cheeky...
You're dead meat!
Left... And right leg...
Punch!
- And that.
- Hey, give me a chance.
Are you seriously hitting me?
Okay!
You big fat dumpling!
How dare you.
Take that.
- And that!
- All right.
Nice!
Give me that.
You think you can take me on?
Challenge accepted.
- Bring it on.
- Go get him.
Go, Soo Ho.
You!
What? Wait!
That's it. Nice one!
- You won.
- Okay!
Soo Ho!
Take that, Hyun Kyu.
- That hurts.
- Let go, darn it.
- Let go of me.
- Let go!
What is all this? Get away from her!
Unbelievable.
- Let go of me.
- You jerk...
Hey, brother.
Who do you think you are coming
at students of Saebom High?
I'll take care of things, so get going.
So...
Thanks, Ju Kyung.
Don't ever go with them again.
Just call the police if
they try to drag you away.
Got it. Anyway, Se Mi
doesn't scare me anymore.
She seemed beatable back there.
I don't know why I've been so scared of her.
I should've stood up for myself sooner.
I know. I should've done that sooner too.
Oh, no. I just got this today!
I'm sorry for not being able to protect you.
I bet it hurt.
- Oh, no.
- Unbelievable.
Would you like to have this instead?
I normally buy two, you see.
Really? You're giving this to me?
Thank you so much!
The snacks will be on me, okay?
By the way, are you perhaps
a member of Gelatin?
Yes, a third-generation
Gelatin. What about you?
- Me too. No way!
- Really?
It's so good to meet you.
Did you manage to buy tickets...
- for the year-end concert?
- Yes, in section A.
No way. Me, too!
- Really?
- We can go together!
I can't believe it.
It's pretty, isn't it?
What a waste though.
It was a memory I never wanted to remember.
But what's different now...
is that I'm not alone anymore.
But it's late.
Are you having fun?
Have you had dinner?
You haven't been answering my calls.
Should I pick you up?
It's quite late, you know.
- You...
- Sure are...
The clingy type.
Just eat instead of peeking at my phone.
Let her have fun and relieve stress.
There's no need be like a stalker, you know.
She'll call once she finds the time.
You're obsessing.
- But I'm worried.
- You worry me more.
I was like this too during the early stages.
I'd call and text her
whenever I found a moment.
She nearly dumped me after a week.
Soo Ah said...
I was making her grow sick and tired of me.
- What?
- Even though...
you love her endlessly,
- don't let it show all at once.
That's how she won't get sick of you.
Exactly.
Wait, you should write this down.
Go home now, okay?
- Why?
- We haven't finished the chicken.
Soo Ah, are you having fun?
I've been missing you like crazy!
Sure thing, darling. I'll
be there to pick you up.
Don't make her get sick and tired of you.
Soo Ho, I may not be an expert of dating,
- but it seems to me that..
- Aren't you leaving too?
I'll pick up my pace.
I should call Soo Ho.
No.
No...
Soo Ah?
Seriously? At this hour?
Text me, will you?
I think my phone's busted.
No, it's fine. It's working just fine!
If it weren't, how would you
have been able to call me?
By the looks of it,
I can make calls, but not receive them.
You're making me feel sick and tired of you.
Just go to sleep before you kill me too.
Hey, but...
Unbelievable.
Yoo Tae Hoon!
Could he still be asleep?
GIRLFRIEND
I already mopped the floor today, so save it.
You already work hard, so I wanted to help.
- Is there anything I can do?
- No.
Still, Mom.
I'll tidy that up for you.
You're only giving me a headache, so go home.
Mom, you see,
- I...
- Ju Kyung,
check under the chair.
What? Why?
Just do as you're told, will you?
What's this?
Mom!
To get certified, you need to
pass a performance test too.
It also requires a lot of equipment,
so how can you possibly pay
for it all working part-time?
Are you saying you approve of me...
studying makeup?
Quit that part-time job too.
Now that you've made up your mind,
put in your hardest work...
and be as popular as that Selena you like.
Got it?
Mom!
Stop it. This isn't cute, you know.
I promise I'll do my best, Mom.
I love you, Mom.
Gosh, you're tickling me.
- Goodness, get off me already.
- Thank you.
- My gosh, it tickles so much.
Stop it!
Ju Kyung! Ju Kyung!
- What?
- Why didn't you pick up yesterday?
I was out having fun. Why
are you being so clingy?
You're always calling me and texting me.
I want a little freedom.
What's that supposed to mean? Are
you saying we should break up?
You're really exhausting.
What did you say?
I'm not like him. What do you
say? Do you want to hop on?
- Sure.
- Don't go.
Don't go. Don't go.
Ju Kyung.
Ju Kyung!
No!
MISSED CALL: GIRLFRIEND
What? She called me?
What a lousy dream.
GIRLFRIEND
- Hello?
- Last night...
What time did you go home?
Why didn't you call me on your way home?
I'm not asking for an apology.
But you should've called. I waited all night.
Hearing your voice makes
me miss you even more.
Let's meet up and talk. I
was just about to go see you.
- You...
- Sure are...
The clingy type.
Where are you?
My class is about to start.
I'll call you after I'm done.
What? But...
Hello, everyone.
- Hello.
You need to take into consideration...
that the human face is three dimensional.
Highlight the parts that
are more prominent...
by applying a thicker base.
And the skin is thinner
around the eyes and mouth,
so you need to apply a thinner base...
to prevent it from looking
too flat. Do you agree?
- Yes.
- Now try it on your partners.
- Okay.
Hello, I'm the person
you called. Where is he?
Over there. He's knocked out.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Joon Woo.
Wake up. Grapefruit.
Grapefruit. Grapefruit.
Did you call me?
Hey, it's my girl.
Goodness.
Or are you not my girl anymore?
After all, we've broken up.
My goodness.
What can I do to make you mine?
Unbelievable.
Don't think about running
away. You just wait.
I'll make you mine again after a year.
I can't believe this man.
INSTANT NOODLES, BUY 1 GET 1 FREE
I picked them up first.
- What...
- Let go.
Okay. After you.
- Whatever.
- You can take them.
Why does he look so familiar?
- Honey, try this.
- Co...
- Take a bite.
- Columbus Park!
Stop right there!
- What... What...
- Hey, you.
- It's Columbus Park.
- Stop!
Hey! Stop! Get over here!
There we go.
You're too pretty
What do I do?
What do you do? Just get in the car.
Okay, there you go.
How were you going to wait for a
year when you can't even last a day?
Stop!
- What's that noise?
- Please stop him!
- My gosh.
My goodness, thank you.
Mom. Dad.
Hee Kyung.
Grapefruit.
Hey, Soo Ho. Pretty good.
Hey, you're here.
Why aren't you on a date? It's the weekend.
Ju Kyung's busy.
Are you upset because you guys couldn't meet?
I'm not upset.
I wonder why she didn't meet
you even though she's busy.
She can't be sick of your looks already.
Why would she get sick
of it? Why are you here?
No reason. I was just bored.
But why do you learn
martial arts at the dojo?
I could've taught you instead.
What do you know?
There's nothing to learn.
Fighting is about instincts.
Instincts, my foot. It's all about skills.
Did you see that? It's all about instincts.
No matter how good you may be,
you can never beat someone who
was professionally trained.
- What if I take you down?
- What?
What will you do if I
manage to take you down?
You must be really bored.
The first person to take the
other person down is the winner.
The loser has to grant the winner a wish.
- What do you say?
- You'll lose everything, you know.
Just worry about yourself.
No rules. Just a three-second takedown.
Deal.
1, 2,
2.25,
- 2.5...
- You...
Are you taking your anger out on me?
Three.
Couldn't you let me win?
What do you say? Do you
want to take lessons here?
Forget it. Gosh, what are
you going to make me do?
Hurry up and tell me.
I whisper words of love
As if it's natural
You walk toward me
From afar
How am I going to express
How much my heart flutters
You
Stole my heart
From the moment we first met
And you gave me an incurable illness
I wish to be your flowerpot
I pray every day
on your windowsill
I don't care if I can't talk
I don't care that I can't ask for anything
All I need is your smile
and care from time to time
I'll be able to see you sleep
For as long as I want
- Encore! Encore!
- That was great.
- Here's your pizza.
- Thank you.
I'm never going to make a bet with you again.
- Were you hungry?
- I did Jiu-Jitsu and sang.
Of course, I'm hungry.
By the way, your vocal skills
aren't as good as before.
What are you talking about? I
have a more deep and manly voice.
Exactly. Why don't you use
that deep and manly voice...
to sing?
It's too late.
- It's not too late.
- I'm not interested.
I want you to sing again.
I'm sure Se Yeon would want the same thing.
What would you have asked for if you had won?
Do you want to know?
Let's hear it.
I was going to ask you if I
could tell Ju Kyung how I feel.
I wanted to ask for your permission.
You did?
Yes. I want to have her reject
me so that I can move on.
YOUNG MAN PIZZA
From what he said,
it sounded like he got scammed
by Mr. Won and is penniless.
He wouldn't be in Korea if he had money.
He would've fled long ago.
Still, since we handed
him over to the police,
he'll pay for what he did.
I thought I'd get my money
back if we found him.
- I'm sorry.
- Forget it.
This was fate. Take it as your lot in life.
At least we moved away
from Ju Kyung's bullies.
And Hee Kyung ended up meeting her man too.
Am I right?
She's right. If Ju Kyung
hadn't transferred to Saebom,
I never would've met my Grapefruit.
But...
when will our Grapefruit wake up?
He keeps sleeping.
Did you wait long?
No.
I should charge.
Did you order already? It looks good.
I ordered it for myself.
What's wrong? Are you mad at me?
- No.
- Then are you annoyed?
No. Do you think I'm the type
to get annoyed over nothing?
You're obviously annoyed.
I see. Okay.
You must not be happy to see me.
Then I'll just go.
Go where?
Should I stay?
What's wrong?
Why are you annoyed?
You really won't tell me?
Why? We never had a proper
date since we started dating.
I prepared all of this for you,
but you're always too busy.
Tae Hoon says I'm too clingy.
Seo Jun wants to ask you out.
I'm a total mess inside.
- What?
- I love you.
I love you, Ju Kyung.
Hey... If you say that so suddenly...
Then?
It makes my heart flutter.
How was your first day of class? Was it fun?
Yes. It's an intro class,
but everyone was like a pro.
I'm the only one who didn't
take the written exam yet.
So I have to work hard
and pass on my first try.
Should we go somewhere
after your written exam?
- Where?
- Somewhere you want to go.
Should we go to the beach?
We can take an early morning
bus to see the winter sea.
Okay. Let's do that.
Can I really not eat this?
I got it for you...
You really were annoyed.
No. I meant we can eat it
together. Both you and I.
You take a bite, and I take a bite.
You skipped your tutoring session again.
Were you not scolded enough last time?
Are you rebelling?
What is your problem? Answer me!
Give me your phone.
- Why?
- What losers do you hang out with,
that you're so undisciplined?
Or is it because you're seeing
some punk? I need to check.
- Hand over your phone!
- No.
Hand it over now!
You crazy little...
Honey.
Let's go.
Do you have it?
Okay.
I'm hungry.
Here. Dad, your rice
Thanks.
- Soup bowls.
- Please help.
- Okay.
- Here's yours.
Grapefruit, let's eat.
Here.
Thank you.
Eat up, son.
Son... Son?
Son? He's Grapefruit. Grapefruit.
Father. I'm not a grapefruit.
"Father"?
Your cheeks are all red like a grapefruit.
We don't have to call you
"Mr. Han" at home do we?
- Right, future brother-in-law?
- That's excessive.
Why did you break up because
of me? I feel bad now.
The school year's over now and I'm
moving up a grade, so it's okay.
Ju Kyung. I am so embarrassed.
Don't be. You'll be family soon.
Son.
Hee Kyung, what happened to me?
What else? You're trapped now.
Eye booger.
Eat up. Eat. Let's eat, Grapefruit.
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Seriously. I can't believe it.
- Here she is.
- Hey.
Ju Kyung, have you seen the online community?
The online community?
Look at her.
I misjudged her.
She's so selfish.
Overheard in the girls' bathroom.
Kang Soo Jin from class
2-5 is a frightening witch.
She's the one who uploaded the
video and pictures of Lim Ju Kyung.
They were best friends,
but she got jealous...
that Soo Ho was seeing her, and betrayed her.
I didn't make it up.
I witnessed another friend
lashing out at Kang Soo Jin.
She's like the villain in a drama.
What is she, a psychopath?
Talk about a top-level traitor.
- Oh my gosh.
- How could she do that?
To a friend of all people.
She betrayed a friend because of a guy?
She's terrible. I totally misjudged her.
Don't you feel sorry for Ju Kyung?
I know.
That witch.
Was she the one who took that
photo of Ju Kyung and Soo Ho?
Are you a stalker?
You're mad scary.
How will Soo Jin show her
face at school ever again?
It'll be hard.
- She's like a criminal.
- That's right.
That psycho.
I bet you think you destroyed Ju Kyung.
But you just destroyed yourself.
She's a total stalker.
She's leaving.
Where is she going?
Soo Jin!
Where are you going?
Why are you running away?
Do you still have nothing to say to me?
Don't you feel bad at all?
No. I don't feel bad.
Still,
I don't want to lose you like this.
So I want to reach out one last time.
Because I don't want to regret it later.
Soo Jin, let's not do this.
Do you think I'll take your hand?
Do you really believe we can
go back to the way we were?
Ju Kyung, right?
It's good to meet you.
Let's go.
Eyeshadow, mascara...
And both cheeks...
COSMETOLOGY CERTIFICATE EXAM
Didn't you do well?
It's all right. You'll do better next time.
I passed!
Good job.
- I passed.
- I'm proud of you.
I even guessed one correctly.
- You got lucky.
- Right.
You're squeezing the air out of me.
Tiger energy boost. Roar!
Wait, is it recyclable?
Who cares? I'm done with it.
CONTACTS, LIM JU KYUNG
You must be at ease now
that the exam is over.
This is only just the beginning.
I hear the written test isn't even that hard,
so I'll have to give it my
all on the performance test.
So much for dates then.
You should study for your exams too.
You don't seem to have been
doing much of that lately.
I've been too occupied by
a certain Lim Ju Kyung.
Just a second.
It's Seo Jun.
Hello?
Are you done with your exam?
How else would I be picking up?
Why do you ask?
I was hoping to see you.
Right now?
But I'm with Soo Ho. Can he come too?
No, just you and me.
I have something to say.
Well, this isn't a good time...
Remember the wish you said you'd grant me?
I'll text you the address. Meet me there.
Hey, Seo Jun.
- What's with him?
- What did he say?
He wants to tell me something in person.
I'll tell him maybe next time.
Go ahead.
- What?
- Talk to him.
Seo Jun!
Why were you waiting out in the cold?
Gosh, you now have a red nose.
Anyway, what was so urgent?
Let's go eat something.
This is on you, right?
You should've wished for
something more expensive.
This is what you like though.
You're right. I could have this all week.
What is it that you want to say to me?
Did you ask me out just to make me buy this?
- I need relationship advice.
- What?
Really?
I'm not exactly an expert on the subject.
Lay it on me. I'll try and be helpful.
- There's this girl I like.
- Right.
But I'm going to move on.
Why? Have you told her how you feel?
No.
But you're already moving on?
She has a boyfriend.
Why did it have to be a
girl who's already taken?
Do you like her a lot?
Yes, a lot.
Oh, dear.
Then steal her away.
Should I?
Who is it though? Does she go to our school?
Forget it. It's a secret.
You...
No way.
Is it Soo Ah?
Don't you dare steal her away. Poor Tae Hoon.
No.
- It's not her.
- It's not?
She must be some girl for
you to have a crush on.
She must be beautiful.
Yes, she is.
I have high standards, you know.
Then you should've told her sooner
and made her your girlfriend.
Do you think she would've
come to me if I did?
What good is all this now, right?
I can't really help you,
so another portion...
No, wait. I'll buy anything
here you wish to eat.
- Can we get two more portions?
- Sure.
Could she be any more clueless?
Want some fritters? What
else should we order?
It smells nice.
Option 1, 2, or 3.
Which one do you like the most?
Did I make you wait long?
I bet I owe it to your hair. It's pretty.
I called to say I was running
late, but you didn't pick up.
- I left my phone at home.
- What?
- Here.
- What's this?
This... Did you knit this yourself?
Someone asked me to do it
by handing me some yarn.
I never asked for anything.
It was just to help you ease your mind.
It's pretty though. It's
prettier than what you can buy.
Let me.
There.
- How do I look?
- Pretty.
Our bus is here. Let's go.
There.
Feeding the sheep has made me hungry too.
I heard your stomach rumble earlier.
The sheep made that noise.
I'm going to upload the
photos on social media.
NEW POST
Why aren't you uploading
a photo of us together?
What? I figured you might not like it.
I'm fine with it.
Then can I upload it?
Lovestagram. Couples trip.
Boyfriend. Healing. Couple photo.
There we go.
We look nice.
What do you want to eat?
What should we eat?
Why are you smiling?
- Are you making me look weird?
- No.
Let me see.
Let's show each other at the same time.
1, 2, 3.
What...
I thought you were good at everything.
It's cute.
It looks nice.
Let me see mine.
Looks nice, right?
The nostrils are a bit...
I'm not done yet.
Just a second. I'll reduce them a bit.
Be careful.
Watch out.
Here we go again.
Is it fun?
Hello. Long time no see.
Yes, long time no see.
Hey, why are you talking
to me with no honorifics?
Because that's how you're talking to me.
You're Ju Kyung's friend.
I'm her older sister.
You're Ju Kyung's older sister?
Yes.
Why am I seeing two beautiful men?
Am I in paradise?
Hee Kyung!
So you're that lady who
got drunk and threw a fit?
Throw a fit?
- You saw me do that?
- What brings you here?
You're a star, Seo Jun.
What are you talking about?
Don't you know that you're
all over the internet...
including Newstagram? Here. Take a look.
You stole my heart
- What about it?
- What do you mean?
You're still not interested
in becoming a singer?
Are you going to keep working here part-time?
If you want to become a cafe owner,
then I'll support your dream.
But i heard you wanted to become a singer.
Do you really think I'll sign a
contract with that agency again?
Why not?
As you already know, all
the executives got replaced.
Move Entertainment has changed.
We're not like how we used to be.
Why are you so desperate to convince me?
Because I got a hunch.
I saw a video of you as a trainee
back when I was looking for Leo.
Why don't you start singing again?
I want you to sing again.
I'm sure Se Yeon would want the same thing.
What do you say?
- Hello?
- Seo Jun, are you with Soo Ho?
- Let's take another photo.
- A photo?
- Yes.
- I'll bring your cell phone.
Just a second.
SOO HO...
SOO HO, I LOVE YOU.
Ju Kyung.
What did you write?
SOO HO, I LOVE YOU.
- Too bad you didn't get to see it.
- What did you write?
It's a secret.
- Stand there.
- Okay.
Your phone is dead.
I guess we took too many photos earlier.
We won't get to take any photos by the sea.
Why don't we come back and take
photos here a little later?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- Let's look for a charger.
- Okay.
Soo Ho!
The phone is turned off. You
will be directed to voicemail.
Why aren't they both picking up?
Seo Jun, what's up?
Are you with Soo Ah?
Ask her if Ju Kyung is with Soo Ho right now.
What? The sea?
- It looks delicious.
- Let's eat.
Try this too.
It's delicious.
I think I have two stomachs.
I ate a tone of tteokbokki
yesterday with Seo Jun,
but I can still eat more.
- Did the conversation go well?
- Yes.
He wanted to ask for my
advice on someone he likes.
Do you think he likes Soo Ah?
What?
That's going to make things so complicated.
But he said he doesn't like
her, so I should believe him.
This one is ready to eat.
Why are you laughing?
- It's a pity I can't take a photo.
- Why?
- Is there something on my face?
- Come here.
- You're good now.
- You smudged it, didn't you?
- Yes.
- Seriously?
What?
Try the noodles. It's really good.
Why won't they both pick up?
CRYSTAL CLEAR SEA, GRILLED
SEASHELLS AND COFFEE
Here.
- Aren't you cold?
- No, I'm good.
Let's come back once it gets warm.
Okay. Let's do that.
Hey.
The stuff I wrote earlier on the sand...
It was actually...
Why are your eyes closed?
Gosh, it stings. There was sand in my eyes.
- What were you thinking about?
- What?
I was thinking about the sand in my eyes.
My goodness.
- Watch your hands.
- Okay.
It's pretty.
Let's take a photo.
Sure.
I'll bring your cell phone from the charger.
Just a second.
Is it fully charged?
- Seo Jun.
- Where's Soo Ho?
What?
What are you doing here?
Why aren't you checking your phone?
What is it?
Soo Ho.
"ACTOR LEE JOO HUN IN SURGERY
FOR BRAIN HEMORRHAGE IN THE US"
- I'm sure he'll be fine.
- Yes.
He will be.
Soo Ho, it's time to go.
Go home. I'll go.
Seo Jun.
Please take her home.
Don't worry.
Soo Ho.
Don't worry,
and have a safe trip.
I love you.
I'll call you when I land.
Bye.
Oh no.
What if he passes away?
Poor Soo Ho...
2 YEARS LATER
- Let's drink!
- No one is allowed to leave early.
- Fine.
- Drink yours!
You drink first.
Shut it, all of you!
Shut it, all of you.
Ju Kyung's passed out.
Are you sleeping, Ju Kyung?
- Is he coming?
- Yes.
Why isn't he here yet? He
should take care of her.
Here he is. Over here!
- Over here.
- It's cold.
- Get over here.
- Hey.
Who made Ju Kyung drink?
- She drank on her own.
- Sit down.
Ju Kyung. Hey, Ju Kyung. I'm here.
Okay? Wake up.
- You're here.
- Yes.
TRUE BEAUTY
It's snowing here.
I hope it's warm...
where you are.
Don't wait for my calls anymore. Sleep well.
Okay, 1, 2, 3.
You kept in your feelings for two years.
Shut it, all of you!
But you lose your temper and...
Isn't it about time you
figure out how I feel?
Because I missed you.
I didn't miss you.