AUGUST 2017
I only get 30,000 won?
I paid over 300,000 won for all these.
Your sign shouldn't say, "We buy books,"
but "We only take your books for free."
-They're in awful shape.
-Next story.
-All useless. These are like trash.
-The trial for Seo,
a former chief prosecutor.
-The main issue
-No, no.
-is if the acquittal will be sustained.
-Don't you know?
-Reporter Choi is at the court.
-Take a good look.
-These look bad for a reason.
-Choi?
-Quiet, please.
-I am here
at Seo Byung-ju's final trial
-Whoever buys this hits a jackpot.
-in Seoul High Court.
-Here.
-Was the ruling made?
-And here. The notes look so perfect.
-Not yet.
-Will it be overturned?
-Study with this, and that's it.
-Anyone will make it.
-We can't tell.
But Yang Jong-hoon, the prosecutor,
stepped down as a prosecutor
to be a witness--
Give me 50,000 won, then.
-So? Did you get into Hankuk Law School?
-What?
Don't talk big if you didn't.
Yes, of course, I did.
So 50,000 won. Deal?
I was already offering much more
with 30,000 won, but I'll add 5,000 won
since you got into Hankuk University,
so 35,000 won.
-No, 50,000 won.
-I'll pay
the 50,000 won, so let me watch the news.
-But these are for law school--
-And I'm going there.
The ruling of the final appeal
of former chief prosecutor Seo Byung-ju
has just been made.
-These will get you in at once.
-The judges overturned
-the initial ruling
-You can do it.
and found him guilty of taking bribery.
Many are waiting to see if Seo will lodge
an appeal to the Supreme Court,
-waiting for the verdict.
-May I have the money now?
Are you sure I'll get in at once,
Ms. Senior?
"Ms. Senior"?
I plan on going to Hankuk Law too.
I'd get in without these,
but it seems like you need the money.
Hey, my sister
isn't going to sell those books to--
Goodbye.
Hey, wait.
BALANCE: 994,350 WON
It's about time. Finally.
I'll have six zeroes in my account!
Are you that happy
for making that money by fraud?
Fraud?
Right, about Hankuk Law School?
You're too young to know what fraud is.
"A crime when someone defrauds another
and takes property from someone."
Article 347 of the Criminal Code.
I mean, I wasn't trying to deceive him--
You didn't do anything
knowing he was fooled
to take his money.
So? I'm a fraud now?
If you don't want to be one,
you should get in.
Get in? To where?
To Hankuk Law School.
Me?
Hey, Byeol.
Do you think a law school
is like a community center?
And Hankuk Law School?
It's not for everyone.
-You're good at English.
-I'm just all right.
Millions of people are better.
But your college grades are good.
That's because Dan practically helped out
with everything…
Why do you do this to me?
You can get Dan's books back
and study again.
You said you can get accepted at once.
Hey, at once? My foot.
I made up a total lie
to get him to pay me more.
Then, you must feel sorry
for that guy, right?
Did he make me feel any sorrier?
He claims he's a big shot.
He said he'd get in without those.
But still.
And he offered the money first.
I should've made him pay twice as much.
How much more do you want?
And it wasn't just a claim. I'm that good.
How much more should I give you
to make you feel ashamed
for playing a law student?
There's nothing you can do
to make her feel ashamed.
She'd rather get into Hankuk Law School.
I'll get going then.
Byeol. Hey, Byeol!
YOUR GUIDE TO LEET
FRIDAY 7:40 P.M., MUST SWITCH
THE TIME OF DEPARTURE TO THE VICTIM'S…
You even quit to have him punished.
How do you feel now?
I feel crappy.
You testified Seo made you a request
back when you were on duty.
It was accepted
and the case was overturned on appeal.
But we still have the Supreme Court
to go to.
Do you believe the Supreme Court
could overturn the decision again?
If my testimony isn't found reliable.
I heard you and Seo
were very close as colleagues.
What happened to you two?
TRUTH AND JUSTICE ONLY BY THE LAW
Inmate 2023, it's your court day.
DONGBU DETENTION CENTER WAITING ROOM
Based on that, the police identified
Yang Jong-hoon as the prime suspect.
The on-site inspection Yang requested
will be conducted today.
The request was made unprecedentedly
by Yang, the suspect,
right before his indictment.
Yang has been pleading the Fifth
until this day.
The change in his attitude is…
Hey, Kim.
Postponing the indictment?
He said he'd admit
if we do a spot inspection.
A former prosecutor
killed his former chief.
It's a huge shame on the prosecution.
A formal briefing? No way.
I didn't say that just to Choi.
It's just something I said over a meal.
If you can't trust me,
come out for a meal.
Are you telling him about suspected crime?
Let's talk later.
You said I killed him
over his deal with Lee Man-ho
to cover up his hit-and-run.
It's not a bad story for you.
The more the media talk,
the more people will become furious
at Seo Byung-ju.
If the people feel that way,
it'll help reduce your sentence.
I know you're like this,
but you're still my senior.
I have everything set up for you.
-Article 126 of the Criminal Code.
-Publicizing suspected crime?
There's no use for that law anyway.
LAW AGAINST PUBLICIZING A SUSPECT
There's no prosecutor
who was ever indicted for doing that.
The media kept going on
about how the former chief prosecutor
was in league with a heinous rapist,
so most people are saying
they hate the deceased
more than the killer.
Let's make it so that people can see
how anyone could become furious
and would want to kill someone
during the spot inspection.
Can you free him until we get there?
After all, he's my senior.
Feeling the urge to kill Seo
in that moment,
Yang poured the entire sachet of meth
into the coffee.
It was sugar, not meth.
Stop writing a novel.
No, stop it!
After I dumped his methamphetamine
in the sink,
he went into hypoglycemic shock.
I found a single-serve sugar packet here,
not an ordinary packaging.
-You never said that before.
-He refused to testify.
He's about to talk now.
Let's just say there's sugar.
Well, excuse me.
You can use this.
It's edible collagen, for your skin.
Fine.
He passed out from hypoglycemia,
so I gave him coffee with sugar.
But it wasn't there at the scene.
The sugar packet.
We didn't find a sugar packet,
and it's not on the evidence list.
Stop trying to pull this trick on us.
It was never…
It was never here to--
It was here to begin with.
You need to cut your crap.
What is he yapping about?
Gosh.
Tell them to hear him out.
Please hear out my client--
Then, he'll need
to at least make some sense.
If it was here to begin with,
where would it go?
We already combed through the office.
It fell out of the glasses?
He rolled down the stairs?
Detective Oh.
-Check the glasses Seo was wearing.
-Yes, sir.
It was you?
Just kill me!
Turn yourself in now!
Han Joon-hwi.
11:10 A.M., OCTOBER 5, 2020,
THE DAY OF THE INCIDENT
YOU RECEIVED A NEW EMAIL
FROM SEO BYUNG-JU,
JURAE-DONG HIT-AND-RUN CASE
SEO BYUNG-JU
-Hello?
-This is Yang Jong-hoon.
Give me a second.
Let me call you back.
Now that Joon-hwi knows,
Jong-hoon will also find out soon.
WITNESS WANTED
HONGIM REAL ESTATE AGENCY
Yes, that's my real estate agency.
My husband used to run this place.
Someone else recently came by
to check too.
A middle-aged man in glasses?
No, he was a young man
without any glasses.
He was wearing a hoodie that day.
Was it him?
Yes, it was him.
HAN JOON-HWI
The video
for the Jurae-dong hit-and-run case?
Yes.
I sent it.
You were the prosecutor in charge.
DO NOT ENTER
Someone had to reveal the truth.
You met your uncle here on that day,
didn't you?
Did you have to be the one to reveal…
the truth?
Did you kill him?
Professor Yang Jong-hoon singled you out.
I asked, did you kill him?
You do have a good reason.
He left a huge inheritance to you,
a kid who isn't even his own.
Sign that in front of me…
DISCLAIMER OF INTEREST BY HEIR
unless you want to be suspected.
You betrayed your uncle.
He thought of you more dearly
than his own daughters,
yet you stabbed him in the back!
That's not for you to say.
What?
You used your kids
as an excuse to stay in the US,
you even took another lover.
I have every right to know
who killed my husband.
Asking if I killed him?
Think however you want.
There's only one answer
you want anyway, Aunt.
Sit!
You have no right to do this to me.
And don't come to see me
with something like this.
We can't prove that this belongs
to the deceased.
I request a second autopsy.
A second autopsy? Because of this?
He had a bad headache on the said day,
which hindered his mock trial class.
He could've fallen down
since his nose pad was found here.
That's just a possibility--
That's where the investigation begins.
Is this the reason for this inspection?
You're trying to postpone the indictment
by using the inspection
and a second autopsy?
The nose pad is intact
on the glasses he wore.
See?
Do you have anything else to say?
They were switched.
Mr. Seo was wearing rimless glasses
on that day.
Thanks.
But when I left after giving him coffee,
his glasses were changed
to those black ones for some reason.
He's right.
He was wearing rimless glasses
when we talked during the break.
Why didn't you keep your mouth shut
and continue to plead the Fifth?
Darn it!
The autopsy report didn't show
any brain damage--
And I wanted a photo proof,
but why is the attachment left out?
What?
It really isn't here.
They said the camera wasn't working.
Right at that moment?
You could've been suspicious.
Suspicious, my foot.
Stop insulting medical examiners.
We can't redo the autopsy.
Not only is your evidence weak,
but if we had to take out his body
from the ground,
his bereaved family will protest.
What if we don't?
I need to know clearly
who killed my husband.
Please do the second autopsy.
Prof. Yang wanted a second autopsy?
It's a sudden twist.
A second autopsy isn't easy.
If he was buried, he'd be decomposed too.
They buried him quite recently.
Professor Seo's wife
got here late from the US.
Really?
Well, if he was in the morgue, yes.
But still, he has to prove
there was a sugar packet
to prove his innocence.
You're right.
I don't really think I saw it.
The culprit took it?
To frame Professor Yang?
Am I sure of this?
Yes, we are.
If the real culprit took it,
he or she must've known Professor Yang
gave Professor Seo that coffee with sugar.
If he was going to frame Professor Yang,
knowing what happened,
isn't this premeditated homicide,
not manslaughter?
You're right.
And someone with a grudge.
A grudge? That means
it's most likely Professor Yang.
If it's not him, that means the culprit
is someone who was in there
among the testifiers here today.
She just found him first.
Professor Yang seems to be
suspicious of Joon-hwi.
-Joon-hwi?
-Han Joon-hwi?
He's suspecting Joon-hwi?
Does it make sense?
Why not? He even put up that petition.
That petition was--
He thought of him as a son,
but he still put that up,
refusing to accept his uncle.
Then, why not?
MY HUBBY
Hey, babe. I left it on silent
during the spot inspection.
-I mean it.
-But still, it can't be Joon-hwi.
I hope not.
It can't be him, right?
If Professor Yang is suspecting him,
he must have a reason.
If you're curious,
you can ask his public defender.
He's our senior.
He didn't seem enthusiastic.
Right? It looked
as if he was forced into this.
He didn't seem too trustworthy.
It'd be perfect
if Professor Kim Eun-suk took him.
-Mr. Yang.
-Did you admit to it?
-Did you confirm everything?
-Mr. Yang!
-What happened?
-Was it you?
Did you kill him?
-Say something!
-Did you do it?
-Did he break his silence?
-Mr. Yang!
-Did you do it?
-It's you, right?
-Say something!
-How did you kill him?
-Did you clarify it?
-What's your motive?
Professor Yang wanted a second autopsy?
A second autopsy?
Did he deny his charge
instead of admitting to what he did?
Was there a problem
in the initial investigation?
What problem? There wasn't a problem.
Do you admit to it?
-Do you?
-Did you do this?
Say something!
Why did he want the autopsy?
You can talk to him later!
You need to defend him
and tell them it's to prove his innocence!
What's with you?
Come here.
-Quick.
-Anything to say?
I know I can't be an attorney
as a law professor,
but at least,
let me be his public defender.
Ask the Minister of Education.
I believe the Min. of Justice stated
professors of the Legal Clinic
working as public defenders
is not a breach
of the Attorneys-at-Law Act.
If the Ministry allows,
I want to defend Yang.
Innocent or not,
this job isn't for our Legal Clinic.
People will end up criticizing and say
we're trying to protect our own.
We should protect him
if he's falsely accused.
Read this article.
The media arbitrarily reported on him
and turned him into a murderer
even before he got indicted!
When I say no,
I mean that you can't do it!
Then, quit your job and defend him!
-Vice Dean!
-Professor Kim!
I understand you two were very close
since the training institute--
It's not because we're close.
Well, I guess we are.
But I'd do the same for you
if you were falsely accused.
That won't happen, so get back to work.
PROFESSOR KANG JU-MAN
There's no use
in visiting the dean over this.
We've decided to dismiss him
once he gets indicted.
You sound as if you want him to.
Well, you're very close
to Professor Jung Dae-hyeon,
who has been
after Professor Yang's position.
If he's suspicious of Joon-hwi,
does this mean he also took
Professor Yang's laptop?
A laptop isn't easy to throw out,
so he probably hid it.
I'd hide it under my mattress.
The police will think like you,
so a locker for me.
Hiding it in my stuff
could be much better.
They'll find it during the search.
Stop talking behind a guy's back.
If you're dying to know, ask him.
He'd have to be around for us to ask.
Or you can ask him for us.
Don't you have a study group to go to?
What about our study group?
Joon-hwi won't be there.
Exactly. Where did he go?
WITNESS WANTED FOR A HIT-AND-RUN CASE
ON SEPTEMBER 10TH, 2007
AUGUST 25, 2020,
A FEW MONTHS BEFORE THE INCIDENT
LOG-IN
INBOX
CANCELLATION
OF VEHICLE REGISTRATION ATTACHED
THE REGISTRATION OF ABOVE VEHICLE
WAS CANCELLED
DATE: SEPTEMBER 11TH, 2008
MESSAGES
MESSAGE INBOX
FROM SU-MIN'S MOM
I DELETED THE VIDEO.
SUHAN BANK 107-23-154007, PARK SEO-GYEONG
SENT MESSAGES
SU-MIN'S MOM: I'M REACHING OUT
REGARDING YOUR KID'S VIDEO
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT IT.
PLEASE CALL ME.
SU-MIN'S MOM
VISIT BLOG
Joon-hwi.
I can't believe you wanted to see me.
Did you see the court?
It's probably the most fabulous mock court
in this world.
Not only will you hold mock trials,
the court will do real ones too.
We'll do the first mock trial in--
The Jurae-dong hit-and-run case.
MY DEAR JOON-HWI
07P 4295.
It was your car.
Joon-hwi.
Car number 07P 4295.
It was your car.
It was yours! It was your car!
Why?
Why did you do that?
They took the banner down.
Goodness.
Is it because of what I did?
It's not getting developed.
Lee Man-ho was the witness?
I think the deceased made a deal
with Lee Man-ho
and let him off with feeble mindedness
to cover up his hit-and-run case.
He hit him here, bang.
Vroom.
How dare a guy like me
hold his weakness
and shake your uncle around.
Yes, I did that. I did.
That was the only way I could save myself.
Hey, I'm sad about this too.
Deal or whatever, he's my savior
who let me stand here today.
The only guy who took my side is gone.
Darn it.
My blood is valuable.
About your uncle…
He kept a pair of spare glasses
in his car.
But on the day he died,
it disappeared from his car.
You're his bereaved family,
so find out if they're on the list
of evidence or his articles.
You won't redo the autopsy, right?
His family strongly insists, so…
Just have him indicted.
I can't just indict him!
-What I meant was--
-Also,
why did you miss the nose pad
in the first search?
This is a high-profile case.
So this is our fault?
-Is it?
-Whoa, wait.
Open up!
Darn it.
He wanted the case transferred ASAP.
He's the one
who leaked the case to the media!
I heard Inmate 2023 made a big scene
at the inspection.
After all, he was a prosecutor.
He might end up leaving soon.
Let's not contaminate the scene.
Step back.
-What?
-Is he dead?
Should we report this?
-He's down?
-What?
-What's going on?
MOM
The prosecution's decisive argument
will be Jamie's fear of needles.
Six months before the case,
the victim began to give insulin shots
to her diabetic mother.
So she can now inject shots herself?
That's pretty good.
But it seems more plausible
for the suspect to have killed her
out of a sense of betrayal
than her committing suicide.
How is murdering her in betrayal
more plausible than…
If he loved her,
it could happen, right?
PROFESSOR SEO BYUNG-JU
If he loved her.
I'll go to the mock court first.
Make sure you get me off.
MOM
YOU HAVE 8 MISSED CALLS FROM MOM
You think Joon-hwi is the real culprit,
don't you?
You believe he pushed my husband
down those stairs.
It's just a speculation.
We need to do a second autopsy
to know for sure.
I find Joon-hwi more suspicious than you,
Prosecutor Yang.
Once Byung-ju dies,
he'll inherit a huge amount of money.
Are you saying he wanted his inheritance?
I've lived for decades
as a prosecutor's wife.
And he has enough reasons
other than the inheritance.
He treated his uncle like vermin
ever since the bribery case broke out.
He's an ungrateful rascal
who repaid his uncle's kindness with evil.
It's too unfair
for you to be stuck in there.
We must reveal the truth
by conducting a second autopsy.
The medical examiner you mentioned before,
are you sure he's good?
What? I can't see him?
OK CIVIL AFFAIRS CENTER
I came a little too late.
Joon-hwi's aunt got here first.
-Professor Seo's wife?
-Yes.
What brings you here?
Can you let me in, too?
Someone else got in, so I couldn't.
-You can come tomorrow.
-Wait.
I have to talk to him.
Then be his attorney.
This visit is only for his attorney to--
Tell him we're interns.
Exactly.
I thought about this all night.
Regardless of the autopsy result,
finding the culprit who fed meth--
The prosecutor should.
The prosecutor framed you as the murderer,
so to prove your innocence…
-Why should I prove my innocence?
-Sorry?
-Do I have to prove my innocence?
-No, sir.
What? He'll be found guilty.
The evidence of the crime.
All you have to do
is discredit or withdraw the reliability
-of the prosecution's evidence.
-What?
If the autopsy changes
the cause of his death,
it'll discredit
the prosecution's evidence.
Is that why you wore those glasses?
The sugar packet wasn't the only thing
that went missing.
OCTOBER 5TH: 911
SEPTEMBER 23: PROFESSOR KIM EUN-SUK
Is this 911?
Please speak.
I'm at Hankuk Law's mock court.
My professor fell down the stairs
and fainted.
-Is he breathing?
-One second.
Hello?
Please speak.
HEAD PROSECUTOR JIN HYEONG-U
How did you know he talked to 911?
I told him to check the call history
with 911 for that day.
Han Joon-hwi made a call.
And he fell down the stairs.
-Did you find out?
-Sorry?
Right, yes. The police are correct.
MONITORING CENTER
As I told the police,
Lee Man-ho was at Hankuk University
that morning as Professor Seo's driver.
But he left right away.
PERSONAL DETAILS
Lee Man-ho was definitely away from school
at the time of his death.
They can trace his location
with his anklet.
Don't people cut that off and run away?
The police also thought
Lee Man-ho could've tampered with it,
so they checked every place he visited
before and after his death.
I checked everything myself, too.
Lee Man-ho has a solid alibi.
Did you want to get on his good side
by looking up everything?
I'm guessing
you didn't seem trustworthy enough
if he made me do that separately.
Does this mean
it was Joon-hwi?
SEOUL CENTRAL DISTRICT PROSECUTORS' OFFICE
We confirmed
how your uncle rolled down the stairs.
If he had brain damage,
that means he could've died
after some time has passed.
The cause of death is…
Are you also suspicious
of the autopsy result?
-How did you find this?
-I just did.
I doubt it was easy.
But nothing's impossible.
So you went to the Police University?
But you dropped out
before half a year passed.
Because of your inheritance,
your aunt suspects it was you
over Yang Jong-hoon.
Will you do the second autopsy?
What if we do? Will that be a problem?
You didn't kill him.
Did you kill him?
Did you push him down the stairs
and get rid of the sugar packet
Yang mentioned?
I thought I was a testifier.
Yes, so answer my question.
If you didn't, say so.
Do you want to leave
as a suspect, not a testifier?
-You probably can't do that.
-What?
If you have two suspects
who aren't accomplices for one case,
isn't it humiliating
for the detective and the prosecutor?
What did you say?
You'll have to let Professor Yang go
if I become the suspect.
I'm saying a second autopsy
won't do you any good, prosecutor.
Could I be excused?
I have to be in a class.
PROSECUTOR JIN HYEONG-U
That little rascal. Darn it!
Let's do the second autopsy.
Of course I don't want to do it.
But we can't let him toy with us.
Find out everything on Han Joon-hwi.
Get the warrant for the autopsy.
That's a great decision.
My gosh.
Excuse us.
Hey.
Hey, you!
What are you looking for?
What is it?
CONSTITUTION 1
Professor Kang said it's all my fault
if any of you get in there with a laptop.
Your grades are out.
Our grades? Goodness.
2ND SEMESTER MIDTERM GRADES
IN CONSTITUTION
What? Our average is in the 30s again?
Why does Professor Kang
never give out good grades?
The average for Civil Procedure Code
is five.
You get an A+ if you score over ten.
Unbelievable.
I'm sure everyone here never got
such a low grade before law school.
No way. I think I'll get an A+.
One second.
I'm awesome. I did better than Ji-ho?
How do you know my grade?
I saw you write your nickname
in the start of the year. "Fewgoodmen."
Gosh, you and your sentimentalism.
Good for you.
Are you kidding? Don't look at mine.
I have to do a little recon
before the game begins.
I need to know who's ahead of me.
Hey, but this time, I got ahead of you.
Good luck.
What?
Wait, what is this? 90-something?
"Newbeginning"?
Who's this?
Could it be…
You're right. He got 91 points.
It's Seung-jae.
HOLDOUTANDWIN: 29
My gosh, how is this grade possible?
No one got up to the 80s.
See? Even Joon-hwi got 71 points.
The one below him, 69.
Why couldn't he give me one more point?
You still did better than me.
I should do better on the finals.
NEWBEGINNING
Gosh.
No matter how well I'll do in the finals,
I'll never get A+.
Ji-ho, aren't you in danger?
I'll be fine if Joon-hwi leaves.
If he leaves?
Right. I heard he might be disciplined
by the Student Discipline Committee.
If he's the real culprit
of Professor Seo's case,
he'll naturally leave.
My gosh.
How can you think of such a thing?
It's just grades, not the bar.
Your grades are what will get you a job
at a law firm.
Grades stay for life, not exams.
Grades are more important.
Ji-ho, that's a bit harsh
as a fellow student.
Only half the people pass the bar now,
so one of you two won't make it.
A fellow?
We aren't soldiers or undergraduates.
This is a training school.
Don't you secretly wish Sol gets a zero
for turning in her test late?
What?
I'm going to kill you.
CONSTITUTION 1
Excuse me.
Where's Professor Kang Ju-man's class?
Right here.
-He's here.
-Quiet.
I'm not going to accept any objections
regarding your grades.
Do not make a trip to my office in vain.
-Who's supposed to be there?
-Han Joon-hwi.
-Joon-hwi, where are you?
-Minus one point.
HAN JOON-HWI: 69
You lost your precious point.
Over there.
Well, I'm Yu Seung-jae.
You're late, but I'll let you off.
Again, his answers were great
for this test,
as if he was reading my mind.
Turn to page 115 of your textbook.
The dispute and clash of human rights.
Like teacher, like student.
Han Joon-hwi.
He's as unusual as you.
I'm in the mood for some coffee.
I guess you won't treat me
with respect today.
Hang in there. Once you get out--
We'll extend your stay,
regardless of the second autopsy.
Why? Wait.
If his cause of death changes
in the autopsy--
There's not a lot of chance
things will turn around.
And he can still destroy evidence,
just like the missing laptop.
-I didn't hide the laptop.
-But lost it?
I didn't lose it. It was stolen.
You're going to change your argument?
I had time to think
in the detention center.
Come to think of it, I left my laptop
in my office on the day of the incident.
It was gone the next day.
It was obviously stolen.
Who'd steal that anyway?
You're right.
The one who stole it wanted it to look
as if you destroyed the evidence
to put you in a tight spot.
The sugar packet and the laptop.
Don't you think they're gone
for the same reason?
So you didn't do it?
It's Joon-hwi who destroyed the evidence.
He hid those glasses
with the missing nose pad.
We need to clarify the facts.
-We will.
-Of course we will, Prosecutor Jin.
Don't just look at what you want to see
and listen to what you want to hear.
Darn it.
Where's that case for his glasses?
Why can't they find it?
Maybe Ji-ho forgot to put the case
where he found it.
You have no time to stretch your legs.
Look at what you got me into.
Han Joon-hwi, that kid--
Don't I seem more suspicious
if you look at the hard evidence?
My goodness.
All evidence is fact.
Then just be the culprit.
Let's wait for the autopsy result.
That's all for today.
Excuse me.
I have questions on Han Joon-hwi
about the incident.
Please don't leave.
Cooperate unless you want to be summoned
as a testifier.
Why are you taking our time?
-Exactly.
-What is he doing?
That's a threat, not cooperation.
If you need us, summon us to the station.
Darn it.
When did we get this?
Why haven't I seen it?
It'd be perfect with rice,
but we're completely out right now.
Mom, I saw this man a few days ago at the…
Mom, the address!
What? What about the address?
NOTICE
LEE MAN-HO'S ADDRESS
Isn't it the house across?
Good for you, Inmate 2023.
They're redoing the autopsy.
If they're digging up a body
they buried already,
he'll get out soon.
The law school murderer sure is different.
Hey, share your secret with us
before you get out, okay?
Prosecutor Yang.
Long time no see.
I always told myself
I'll kill you first
once I get out of here,
but you came in here yourself.
Does it hurt?
It hurts, doesn't it?
I'll let you pass away very quietly.
Guard!
RESTRICTED AREA
MURDERER NEXT DOOR
LAW-CIOPATH
LAW SCHOOL MURDERER
GET OUT OF THE LAW SCHOOL, LAW-CIOPATH
GET HIM EXEPELLED, YOU'RE REAL CREEPY
YOU SMELL
WRITE ANOTHER PETITION
MURDERER NEXT DOOR
Hey, Joon-hwi.
Detectives came by.
If you need me in any way,
feel free to make use of me.
This is Kim Eun-suk.
Professor Yang? How bad is it?
-Are you okay?
-You okay?
Make sure you keep the door locked.
I'll be quick.
LEE MAN-HO'S ADDRESS
What happened?
How did he get stabbed with a knife?
Inmate 2023 was attacked
by a thug he arrested as a prosecutor.
So it was revenge?
Inmate 2023 came just as the attacker
was swearing to kill him.
Doctor, what happened?
We stopped all his bleeding,
but he lost lots of blood,
so his hemoglobin count is low.
He needs blood now.
Are his vitals stable?
We managed to stabilize him
by using dopamine and IV,
but we can't let our guard down.
We're in need of blood,
but the patient has a rare blood type,
so it's not easy to do.
If you can't let your guard down,
does that mean he could die?
Without blood,
you'll have to be prepared for the worst.
The worst? How much time does he have?
A few hours at most.
Is he Rh negative?
He's O Rh negative.
We're putting the word out
for an emergency transfusion,
so give it some time.
RESTRICTED AREA
How is he?
What's your blood type?
He'll die due to lack of blood.
Is that my fault?
He was attacked by a guy whom he arrested.
What the heck is your blood type?
Attention, please.
We're in dire need of O negative blood.
Please find a medical staff
if you can donate blood.
-No way.
-What does she mean?
Lee Man-ho lives that close to us?
Where are you right now? At home?
Mom told me not to say this, but…
Hello? Byeol?
What? Gosh.
Darn it.
Yes?
Professor Yang is in a critical state?
DIGITAL SEARCH
SEO BYUNG-JU TO BE EXAMINED AGAIN
Hey, come here.
Check your text.
-Do you know any O negatives?
-No.
-I don't.
-Do you?
This is bad.
PROFESSOR KIM EUN-SUK
WE NEED O NEGATIVE BLOOD
One, two.
Gosh.
We'll find the blood, right?
His blood pressure is dropping.
So is his pulse.
Mr. Yang!
-Get epinephrine, 2mm, a defibrillator.
-Yes.
-Professor Yang!
-You can't come in.
Please wait outside.
-Charge to 120 joules.
-Charged.
Cleared. Shock!
-Charge to 200 joules.
-Charged.
Cleared. Shock!
He's showing V-fib, doctor.
-200 joules.
-What now?
Cleared. Shock!
-200 joules.
-Charged.
Cleared. Shock!
Why aren't you at school?
Why are you here?
I came because I was worried.
You're moving right away.
You can't live here.
What if we don't?
You can't find cheaper housing
compared to this area.
I'll be more careful.
You can go back and study.
Don't get bad grades and kicked out.
If you die, die there.
Mom.
So nothing happened
since you saw him at the terminal?
If you ever run into him,
you know what to do.
Don't even look that way.
Hey.
Don't look.
Okay.
He deserves to be killed
by getting fried in feces.
I can't move since poverty is my crime.
-Run along then.
-Okay.
Let's go.
RARE BLOOD COMMUNITY
WE NEED O RH NEGATIVE
I can't believe we couldn't find
one person with O Rh negative blood type.
Those we know
are too far from the hospital.
What if the worst happens?
Please excuse me then.
Okay.
I doubt he's in his right mind.
The autopsy is probably underway.
NATIONAL FORENSIC SERVICE
-We still have no blood?
-Not yet.
What if he really changes places
with Professor Yang?
-He must've been after the inheritance.
-What?
What inheritance?
Money is a good reason for murder.
Inheritance lawsuits are the dirtiest,
you know.
Look at his scary eyes.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Be careful not to be found dead.
I was a bit late.
I should've put it back
before the police came.
If I gave it to them,
the evidence wouldn't be admissible.
Even if you gave it to them,
it'd pass as solid evidence
unless the police made you
steal this from me.
I'll wait and see what you'll do with it.
Right.
Is the autopsy over?
NATIONAL FORENSIC SERVICE
No, that's not what I meant.
I'll call you later.
What happened?
To my office, please.
Was there damage in his brain?
Is Yang Jong-hoon in a bad state?
Who's this?
This is disappointing.
You punched me
and made me lose valuable blood.
I heard he's as good as dead
unless I give him my blood.
What should I do?
Why are you asking me?
Who'd benefit the most
if Yang Jong-hoon dies
and shuts his mouth for good?
If that's you, I won't give him my blood.
I already told you.
I'm here right now thanks to your uncle.
O RH NEGATIVE NEEDED NOW
So? Should I give him my blood or not?
Don't do a thing, and stay still.
Don't give him your blood.
Professor Yang is in critical condition?
He could actually die
without a transfusion!
He won't last.
Did you push him on purpose?
Will you let me go if I tell you?
That punk scares me.
Any chance that it was manipulated?
Unless he was ordered to frame him
for drugging the victim to death.
All these circumstances and evidence
are pointing to Joon-hwi.
I killed him.
Something must've gone wrong.
This can't be.
What if we lose both of them?
Joon-hwi submitted his withdrawal letter
this morning.
I can't reach him.
The prosecution delivered
some shocking news.
Subtitle translation by Eun Sook Youn