The Long Ballad
Episode 49
Shuyu
This way
Sometimes I will be impulsive and reckless
Sometimes misunderstanding you
Fortunately you have always been tolerant
And helping
I know what you don’t like to listen to
Polite words
But I really want to tell you
Thank you
Farewell today
I don’t know when we will meet
Changge
Take care
Take good care of Changge
Wish you happiness
Brother Wei
Thanks a lot
A’Sun
You do think Mimi
Would she like it here
What if she don’t like it
When you dream of her
You can ask her
This place is beautiful, filled with greenery and water.
I think she will like it
Changge
When you went to save me in the royal city,
did you ever think that you would not be coming back?
Did you think about your life or dying
when trying to save me in Chang’an?
Actually
I saw the marriage proposal letter you wrote my mother.
Then...
What do you think
I think
that between us there is no need for formal words on paper.
As long as I have you in this lifetime, that’s enough.
Me too
Having you in this life is more than enough.
Right
How do you know General Li Jing?
Did you perhaps keep in contact with him after being brought to Dianxiang?
Actually
Before leaving Chang’an,
I made a promise with him
Brother Li
No
General Li
Brother Qin
We meet again
I’m afraid now
I am inconvenient to get together with you
Brother
No harm no harm
Brother Qin
Do you remember
When parting in Luoyang
Did I give you a word?
A benevolent heart is invincible.
Not bad
But now Princess Yicheng
Coerce Khan
Ordered all tribes
Of the grassland and the desert
Playing in the palm of your hand
Abandon the people like a shoe
That the war is spreading
Life has been charcoal for a long time
You and I are in different camps
Grassland and the customs of the Central Plains
Also different
But the people are equally afraid of war
Desire to rise
I want to know
Can Brother Qin do it for
Common people
Abandon the opinion of the state
Xie Min Yu Hang Upside Down
I have a condition
Please tell me
I want to invite Great Tang
Help me rescue Khan Yanli
Good
I promise you
Although Ashile Chubi
Is strong and belligerent
Repeated confession
But after Wei River, we can still keep our promises
Not dying
Thank you Brother Li for being righteousness
Just now
I’m behind bars
Whether in Dingxiang
Or in the central plains
Have broken their way
Don’t know
How can I help the general
A hand
I need you back to Dingxiang
Command Eagle Division
But this matter will die forever
If you want to succeed
I’m afraid it’s harder than climbing to the sky
Ashile Sun
You tricked me and are still keeping secrets from me.
Didn’t you learn anything? How dare you!
I don’t dare! I don’t dare!
I won’t dare again in the future.
A’Sun
Do you like Chang’an?
Do you want to return to Chang’an?
It’s better not to,
there’s too many familiar people and it would be inconvenient.
Where do you want to go in the future?
Haven’t thought about it yet
A’Sun
Sorry
Originally I told you that I wanted to go far away from conflict,
live a free life without burdens
and see all the rivers and mountains under the heavens together.
However with the current problems before us
I do not think I could just let go and leave without regrets.
The promise between us,
unfortunately will have to be delayed a little.
Changge
I have thought of the second promise I want.
Are you still bringing up those promises?
You should stop talking about it,
I think you should not bring up these promises.
Last time you told me your first wish and then got immediately shot by an arrow.
These promises are not lucky.
You should forget about them.
Trying to get out of what you promised originally.
This is the first time I’ve seen you act this way.
I’m not trying to get out of our bargain.
Okay fine, tell me.
This second promise
In the future I never want you to say sorry or thank you to me.
Between us there are no need for words like these.
That’s it
This second promise
Isn’t this a bit too easy.
As long as you can do this,
then it’s fine.
Well then since we’re on the topic,
you may as well tell me your third promise.
The third promise
I’ll tell you in the future.
The days ahead of us are still long.
Hao Du
Why are you here
The princess’s order cannot be violated
Isn’t your wedding coming soon?
Already worshipped
That’s good
Not right
Then you shouldn’t be here
I have to do this for Leyan
Protect the people she wants to protect
Alright alright
Prince Consort came
It’s also like a tiger with wings
Report
Speak
The East Road scout came to report
Bai Dao found traces of the Dingxiang Army
It seems that Yicheng
I want to break through the white road through the breach
Send a letter to Li Ji immediately
Block the enemy from the front
Flanking me back and forth
General Li
You sent two scouts to scout
But this other way
Not returned so far
Is it possible
What’s possible
The scout did not send a letter
Does not represent this direction
There must be no enemy
It’s also possible that the scout is attacked
Can’t come back
Like this
I will take Eagle Division to see
So you don’t have to
Delayed the army’s strength
I’ll let you go
No way
This is just my guess
May return without success
Maybe
Will you be in danger
You stay
By General Li’s side
Advise him
But
Princess
I’m afraid I can’t let you go
I wait to lead the army away
No one left in the main camp
Important news
Must be handled
Otherwise I can’t deal with it
For fear of losing the military opportunity
Prince Consort is brave and good at fighting
I don’t know if I can stay
Stay with the princess in the main camp
Handle everything
If there is an emergency
You two can work together
Act in a mechanistic manner
Changge will live up to the General’s entrustment
Will live up to the General’s trust
Did not expect
The horse riots back then
The arrogant little princess
Now carry the banner
Guarding the country
Along the way
The princess has worked hard
General flatter me
I just want to do it all
Meager force
Help the world peace
Yicheng is very cunning
Be very careful
Rest assured
She is the end of the war
This time
We must do it for Great Tang
And the whole grassland
Eliminate evil
Sun
I will go with you
Mu Jin
You just...
I am your brother
Am also the Eagle Division’s Military Counselor
How can a coach meet the enemy
The truth of warfare
There are chasers
There are still a lot of people
Turuk
Take Young Khan and go first
I’ll take care of the rest
Wait
Resolution
Kill more people?
Young Khan can’t kill people
Can live
After all by us
These subordinates do it for you
I will do the wicked
Be a good person
If you really do it for Mother
Stop here
Reduce sin
Your mother is really in vain
Your son
Scram
Turuk
Let’s go, Young Khan
Our good luck
It seems Heaven
Still on our side
What luck
I’m afraid you don’t count today
God has eyes
Let you wait here
Want revenge
Show your skills
Sun
You go first
This person
Leave him to me
Okay
Stop them
Go
She’er
A’Sun
I said
I won’t go with you
And never
Surrender to you Ashile Sun
Like you
Won’t surrender to me
Everyone back down
Don’t understand
Yes
You won’t understand
Why did Mimi die?
Not because of your arrow
But for freedom
Someone like you
Only knows to obey orders
Trample on human life
Even one’s own life
Don’t even know who I cherish
Don’t understand
Not an order
Entrusted by others
Keep promise
She’er
Must this be the case
What
I released you in Dingxiang
You are moved
Tens of millions in a while
Don’t show mercy
Admit it
You are the one with a soft heart
You
Why
I’m tired
There is only your knife in this world
To be worthy of my blood
She’er
Don’t be because of other people’s fault
Punish yourself
You are innocent
I’ll pay for Mother’s sin
Sun promised me
Let go of the brothers of Wolf Division
They are the fighters of Ashile Tribe
Shouldn’t fight for Dingxiang
You are Young Khan
Take them with you
Have lived a free life
A’Sun
I still want to fight you
Drink wine together
I don’t know if there is any chance
There will be
Wait till the war subsides
The grassland re-grows new shoots
We will definitely see you again
Go west
The farther the better
Wolf Division
Release Wolf Division
Go
General Du
The enemy set up an ambush at Qikou and blocked the mountain
Has been broken by General Li
Now the two armies are fighting
Scout again
Yes
General Li is so fast
Sui Dynasty
My second uncle hits the world
What is seeking is a rule of word
The history of Governor Gongsun has been like a day for decades
Guarding Liuzhou
What is asking for is a keeping word
But this General Li is different
Zhan Guiqisu
He used a word for illness
Kill
General Du
The heads of the various ministries accompany the felt carts
Escape from the west’ side mountain road
General Li couldn’t get out for a while
Need cavalry support
Let me go
Never let Yicheng get away
Bring more people and be careful
How about Eagle Division
Eagle Division is in Wudu Valley
Catch up with the enemy branch
The enemy leader Lei Meng has died
Tegin of Eagle Division has bypassed the besieged
Ashle Young Khan
Good. Explore again
Yes
Not good, go!
Everybody
Great Tang alliances with various tribes
For common prosperity
For long-term well-being
Yicheng encumbers you
It’s just her own selfish desires
Are you guys
Want to continue working for her?
I have no intention of being an enemy of you
If you stop the war here
You can disarm and return to the field
Go home to take care of his wife, children and parents
You can also make your tribe
Continue to live in herds of cattle and sheep
Living by the water and grass
If you are stubborn
Continue to ignite this border war
We, Great Tang
Vow not to give in
Going home to raise a child
Whoever wants to fight
Go
Then we won’t fight anymore
Report
Our army wins
General Li returns to camp
Congratulations to the general for breaking the enemy
General please rest assured
Hao Du has gone to arrest someone
He will never let Yicheng get away
Well done
Hao Du
Did you catch her?
All the leaders have surrendered
But Yicheng is not in the carriage at all
Not in position
Don’t flee by carriage
Where is she
Maybe she even thought of fleeing
Are you here to laugh at me
I’m just scared
I almost walked on
The same path as you
Useless
In order to achieve one’s own purpose
The agency is exhausted
Killed countless people
If so
I would rather be a waste
You won’t understand
You will never understand
I am the princess of Great Sui
I was born and grew up in the Great Sui
That is my homeland
I have to save it
It’s still there in your hometown
It didn’t disappear
Its land is still
Its people are still there
Besides you hurt
All its people
Just disappeared
The glory of the royal family
Are these honors so important?
Royal family
What a royal family
I’m just a clan girl
I am born
The most glorious day
I was made a princess
That day
I have never been in the palace
Never wore
Such a gorgeous dress
Praised by thousands
A hundred officials welcome
They said from today
I am the princess of Great Sui
Great Sui
Need me to go to the grassland and marry
Today
You are your company
Lei Meng
I will do my best
To guard Her Highness
Until death
I promised
This is my glory
Also my destiny
I am the princess of Great Sui
I am willing to dedicate everything for it
I am willing to dedicate everything for Yi
I don’t need your sympathy
I don’t need anyone’s mercy
Those so-called royal ladies
Even the princes
Not as good as me
They knelt down and begged for mercy
Begging for mercy
In order to survive
Leave the country behind
Only me
Thirty years
I am trapped on the grassland
Haven’t abandoned Great Sui yet
Come back
Great Sui is gone
Where can I go back
Hometown is still there
Chang’an is still there
Daxing Palace is still there
Fuli’s Tree
Was planted during the reign of Emperor Kaihuang in the Great Sui Dynasty
When I was young, my friends and I
Climb trees often
Rely on it to skip class
As long as you are willing to come back
Owned to Chang’an
I understand what the second uncle is like
He won’t kill you
If I am willing to bend my knees to survive
How can you go this way
Even if it’s you Li Changge
Will you return to Chang’an?
Yes
I thought wrong
This life
Just a humiliating joke
I won’t ask anyone for forgiveness
But I still want to thank you
Staying with me on this last journey
Grandmother
This is Chang’an
Yes
We are home
Father
Dingxiang won
Yinshan won
Father
Rest assured
I will take good care of Leyan
Father
Both Hao Du and I will be fine
You can have a good rest now
Condolences, Your Majesty
Was she in pain
Does Your Majesty mean Li Changge?
The princess has aspirations
Under the Nine Springs
Enough to rest assured
Good
Did she say anything
She said
She is very grateful to Your Majesty
What else did she say
She also said
She likes to read
In the future every year during the Cold Food Festival
Burn more books for her
I watched Princess Yongning grow up
I didn’t know
She actually likes reading
She doesn’t like reading
Doesn’t look like it
Li Yaoshi
Do you know what the crime of deceiving the emperor is
This minister knows he is guilty
But Li Changge, that girl
This minister was forced to be helpless too
Get up
What happened
Changge
Didn’t you promise me?
No more
No more trespassing alone
Know that I’m not waiting for my return
Just rush in
I know it’s wrong
Don’t be angry
Princess
The princess really doesn’t to follow me
To return to Chang’an?
General Li, what are you talking about?
Everything is already
Disappeared with the fire
Where did the princess come from?
Really determined
I am really
I lost my apprentice and broke down
General Li
If His Majesty asks after going back
You just let him
Erased my name from history books
Since then, there will be no more Li Changge
General Li
I don’t know anything
Then where are you two planning to go
General don’t ask where
Come and go anyway
All under this world
No one can escape
If His Majesty asks
Just tell him
Do whatever we want
Good
Maybe
We will meet again someday
Changge
This way, Great Tang
Is what you want in your heart
To
Then more I understand
Country’s peace
Thousands of common families live, work in peace and contentment
Country’s rich and power
Common people have no fear
Past honors and disgrace belong to the ego
Till now
Finally able to let go
Now politics
Favor people’s livelihood
Chang
The whole world
Big. Look at the Zun of the Prosperous Age
Thank you
Lives up to Great Tang
Live up to the common people