The Long Ballad
Episode 47
Your appetite is not small
I can promise you the first one
Of curing Mu Jin
As for your Father Khan
Then wait for the Eagle Division
To win the battle for me
I will naturally let
You father and son are reunited
You finally admitted
Father Khan’s illness is caused by you
Saying all this
Does it make any sense?
He is responsible for all this
I want him to sit on the throne
I had blood on my hands
Could it be that
During that time, Khan Shule
Was also your doing?
As a married woman
There is not much way I can walk
You killed She’er father
Have you considered his feelings
When have you cared about She’er so much
My son’s business
No need to worry about you
Mother
You clearly told me
Father had an illness
Why are you here
You tell me
As long as I am sincere
And pray to Sirius
Sirius will not take Father
I kneel by the river every day
Secretly pray to the Sirius God
To make Father get better
Let Father not leave us behind
Mother, speak up
I remember when I was young
Father always told me
We are men
We want to protect Mother
Be good to Mother
It’s you
If want the stars in the sky
He will also pick it for you
Mother
Why
With your father
There is Khan Yanli
I can’t
Come back to my homeland
Impossible to revive the Great Sui
But the grassland is also your home
Great Sui is gone
Shut up
The grassland is your home
But it’s just my cage
I am Great Sui’s daughter
As long as I’m alive
It can’t die
I have been away for so long
Walked so far
Our Great Sui
Will rebirth soon
Just around the corner
You are crazy
So you have been lying to me
Keep lying to me
Why
Someone
Yes
Send Young Khan back to his room
Carefully watch him
Don’t understand what you are doing?
Yes
Congratulations, Prince Consort Du
Don’t be so polite
Call me Hao Du
Hao Du, where’s Princess?
Brother Shuyu
Why are you here
I thought it was Changge
I’m here to you give things from Changge
This fan is from Changge
Embroidered by hand day and night
Is for you
And Prince Consort’s wedding gift
Where is Changge
Gone
She is afraid to say goodbye
Especially with you
So ask me to pass this gift
She told me
To her, you will always be
A bunny in heart
You must be happy
This mandarin duck is from me
Hao Du
Leyan is my forever sister
You can’t bully her
If she is unhappy
I will take her away
Rest assured
You won’t have this chance
Hao Du
I’m so scared
I will never see Changge again
Rest assured
I have inquired about
You father dispatched Li Jing
To led troops to Dingxiang
He is the one my father recommend
Plus Changge’s shrewdness
They will be fine
Leyan
I have a request
Between you and me
No need to say this
My father’s body
Is getting worse day by day
His greatest wish
Is to see us get married
If he can’t hold on to that day
I understand
Let’s go to Du Manor first
Hold a small ceremony
No princes and nobles
Only you and me
And Father
But I’m afraid I wronged you
Not wronged
To fulfill Father’s wish
Leyan thinks it’s worth it
Li Shimin has appointed
Minister of War, Li Jing
Head of the march for Dingxiang
General Li Jing
As the general manager of Tonghan Road
Huazhou Governor Chai Shao
Chief of the March of Jinhe Road
Lingzhou Governor Xue Wanche
As the Chief of Chang Budo Marching
All generals belong to Li Jing’s temperance
Arrived at Yang Mountain yesterday
How many soldiers and horses are there?
More than a hundred thousand people
There are many subordinate tribes in the Ashile Tribe
If you recruit all the troops and horses
We may not necessarily lose to that Li Jing
How was the war on the western front?
Yesterday Ashile Yugu
Defeated by the leader of Mobei
Monan Chief Yinan
Has united the ministries of the desert
Defeated so far
Ashile Tribe’s four armies
Four generals were captured alive
Although several other units promised to send troops
There is still no movement
I guess
Guess what
They have been bribed
How’s Mu Jin injury?
As the princess ordered
Mu Jin is healing
He can get out of bed without a serious problem
Good
Can let the master and servant meet
You go to prison
Bring Ashile Sun
Before letting him see Mu Jin
Let him see Yanli first
Princess
Yanli looks like this now
If Ashile Sun see this
Will it be bad?
In Dingxiang
Ashile Sun is most concerned about
is Mu Jin
and Yanli
If I don’t let him see
How could he be willing to use by me
No problem
I just want him to see
His Father Khan
How to master
In the palm of my hand
Yes
Father Khan, I’m late
Father
It’s me A’Sun
Father wait for me to get you
Don’t look at him anymore
Don’t worry
I won’t kill him
Remember what you said
Otherwise
I’ll take the Eagle Division to level Dingxiang
Then trouble A’Sun
To write a military order
Give it to Mu Jin
I only give you five days
Five days later
I want Eagle Division
In front of the Chengqi Gate of the royal palace
All assembled and obeyed
I will then cure
Your Father Khan
Careful
Sun
I knew it was you
Mu Jin
I’m late
How can they treat you this way
These are not important anymore
I’m still alive
They actually sent Commander Lei to monitor
You suffer
Brothers don’t talk about this
Sun, why are you here
You and Father Khan are in Dingxiang
How could I
Stay alone in Great Tang
What about Mimi
Mimi is here too
But she still can’t see us
I have seen Buzhen
Ashile Sun
Khatun sent you here
For business purposes
Mu Jin
This is a military order written by me
Bring it
Assemble Eagle Division
What
She’er
It’s so late
Why are you coming to me
You say
Am I the whole world
Stupidest fool
I’ll help you go back since you drank too much
You
You say
Am I the most stupid fool
My mother killed my father
Uncle Khan deliberately killed my wolf
To separate me and Sun
Now Mother poisoned Uncle Khan
And I just found out all this now
What
What do they dare to do
Don’t let me talk
All liars are liars
They all lie to me
Take care
Go
You woke up
Why am I here
You drank too much last night
Come and drink some water
Thank you
What do you look at me
You
You are so nice
She’er
I know you keep taking me
Be friends
But after all, our identities are very different
If khatun knew
Last night you were here
I’m going to be scolded again
Sorry I’m leaving now
I don’t know why
I came to you suddenly
Maybe I think you are safest here
So
If you are in a bad mood
You can still come to me
Thank you
Do you remember me telling you
To wait for me to become a Khan
I would marry you and be my Khatun
She’er
But now
I don’t want to be a Great Khan
Are you afraid of me dying?
No
Father will definitely be happy
It’s getting worse and worse
Acting on one’s own initiative
You hurriedly manage the marriage in advance
I’m not afraid of wronging the princess
Leyan said she would not be wrong
And I have already pleaded with His Majesty
His Majesty has approved
Keep everything simple
The princess is afraid of your embarrassment
To marry such a caring wife
Blessing
Yes
I must treat the princess well
Be loyal to His Majesty
Then, Father
Do you have any relatives or friends
I want to watch the ceremony together
Since you have decided to keep everything simple
Then our own family
Reunion is enough
Besides, my sick body
You don’t have to let your relatives and friends add obstacles
Nothing more
Father
You will get better
I know my body
But you
Follow Li Jing to attack Dingxiang
How good is it
Opportunities to make contributions
But you gave it up for me
Don’t think I don’t know
There is only one Father
There are many more opportunities to make contributions
I just don’t want to let myself
To
And said I’m not afraid of my death
I heard that Li Changge also went to Dingxiang
Yes
After the wedding
You leave for Dingxiang immediately
If Li Changge is dead
How do you explain to the princess
But Father, your body
You don’t have to worry about me
You arrange the marriage ahead of time
It’s already considered filial piety
Now is the extraordinary period
You must be loyal to His Majesty
Also the princess
Protect the people she cares about
This is what you should do as a husband
I understand
Then, Father
You must wait for me to come back
Dingxiang has no results
Father will not die
You never thought about
Letting me lead my troops
You just want to borrow my hand
To assemble Eagle Divisio
Great method Khatun
All’s fair in war
Tegin is a person who has been on the battlefield for a long time
Naturally should understand this
Wait until the battle is over
I will allow you
To personally meet the Eagle Division’s triumph
If you are a man
Not afraid of the consequences
Listen
The army should be here
They gathering at the gate of the palace
Take a guess
Who will swear the oath?
You make my father sick
Too sick to speak
How would he issue the order
As long as he is there
I am your Father Khan’s mouth
Why don’t we see Tegin coming out?
What’s wrong with Great Khan
This should be ask of Khatun
Wait a while
Everything goes according to plan
Roast over fire
Save Khan and seek Li Jing
Don’t worry about me
Where are we going?
Go to meet a general of Tang
Go
Princess
Why is it noisy outside
What happened
The Eagle Division defected and rescued Great Khan
They have gone out of town
What
Ashile Sun
It’s you
All’s fair in war
Princess
I was blinded by an eagle after all
You pretend to be tricked
To save Yanli
You are a woman
Naturally unable to show up to the oath
You won’t let She’er go
Won’t let me go
So
You can only show Great Khan
Good for Ashile Sun
He really is not afraid of death
Even if I don’t do these
Will you still let me go
Here
Pass on my order
Notify the grassland tribes
Eagle Division rebelled
Kidnapped Great Khan
Dingxiang cavalry can’t catch up
Great Khan died at the hands of Eagle Division
The token of Great Khan
Is in my hands
Order on my behalf
Yes
Also
Notify Ashile Tribe
Leaders of the subordinates
To depart for Dingxiang now
To arrive three days later at noon
Other I will kill a hundred
Obey
It’s a good one to kill a hundred
But since I came to Dingxiang
I never wanted to live
Even if you slander and suppress
That’s better than
Being your lackey
Rest assured
I won’t let you die in vain
I want to show each tribe
What is the end result of betraying me
Changge
If I could
I really want to stay forever
Always with you
But
I’m going to have to break my promise
Xixin Tribe is here
The people from various tribes are here too
Young Master
Why do you hit someone when you meet?
Why are you here
I told him
Don’t scold me
If it wasn’t for you
Leaving without notice
I won’t be like this
I think about it
I just can’t rest easy
That’s why I told him
Princess Tuja did the right thing
Young Master
Why are you alone
Come here to take a risk
I was so anxious to receive the news
I left the brothers of Yanxing Sect
And went ahead
Shiba is with Situ Langlang
They should be here soon
Shuyu
General Li and I
I want to help you
I didn’t expect to meet your friend
Know you are here
That’s great
We can advance and retreat together
Same tribulation
Of course
Friends should share blessings and difficulties
Don’t worry
This time we are all on your side
Will definitely help you
Saved your beloved one
Thank you all
So what do we do now
The first thing we need to do is the city gate
And with so many of us
We have to think of
A better way
Isn’t it just entering a city?
I’m good at this
This
Once upon orders
The Ashile Tribes
Will award one
Such token
To show allegiance
Just by this
You can also get in and out of the Khan’s Tent
You stole your Father’s token
Without it
How can I take you to the city?
Say it again
I take my father’s things
Why is it called stealing?
I just borrow it
Anyway, I won’t need it anymore
A piece of scrap iron
Everyone, let’s go
Kowtow
Get up
Rise
I
Right now
I feel as if
I’m dreaming
I can’t believe it
It’s true
From now on
I’m your wife
The two of us will never part
Until death
Then, wife
I swear too
Wedding night
Don’t say such unlucky words
I believe you
But
After tonight
I’m going to Dingxiang
You must go
But you must promise me
Protect yourself
Protect Changge
Assist Duke Li
Eradicate Yicheng
Father and I are waiting for you to come back
I will listen to everything you say
Where’s Xu Feng
He went to find out the news
No matter where he is
The city will have news
I have the most important thing
To give to you
And you have to do it
What’s the matter
You go buy some flour
Fruit kernel butter
All the materials for the moon cakes
Buy some more Kongming lanterns
This is the most important thing
Changge, what are you doing
Secret contact
Young Master
I know why the leaders
Are called into the city
Mimi
She’er, why are you here?
It’s bad
Khatun summoned the leaders of various tribes into the city
Tomorrow noon
To behead Ashile Sun
As a warning to others
What
No way
I will never let Sun die
What do you think
Khatun’s temper
Don’t you know
The decision she made
Who can change it
Who is so unlucky
Why Kongming lantern is lit on non-festivals
Mimi
Does She’er want to eat Yuetuan?
What
Great Khan is entrusted to General
Rest assured
I have a gentleman’s appointment with Brother Qin
Surely Khan’s life will be saved
Thanks a lot
Young Master won’t stay
Where else are you going?
The task is completed
I still have a personal matter to deal with
You guys
Mu Jin, you are too interesting
We’re brothers
You didn’t tell us
You are the only one who can save Tegin?
Just
Are you
Look down on your brothers?
Go
There are orders
Palace members are not allowed to go out
Misters
I’m Young Khan’s maid
Young Khan has a bad appetite recently
Always clamoring about eating moon cakes
I don’t know Misters
Can you go out and buy a few?
It’s not Mid-Autumn Festival
Where can I buy the moon cakes
You’ll know if you go out and have a look
If Young Khan feels satisfy
Khatun naturally will feel a lot more comfortable
The remaining money
Mister can go buy wine and drink
Okay, wait for me to change
I’ll go to the city to find it for you
If I can’t buy it
Hope Young Khan won’t blame me
Thank you, Mister
You take a look
My pot is pretty good
Five cents for Yuetuan
Selling ​​moon cakes
Five Ren Yuetuan
Get me these two packs
Alright sir.
Here
Master
How about it?
Being a teacher is better than you think
Shiba and I running quickly for days and nights
With several horses
We just arrived here
Let me say
How can a master like myself
Have such a stupid disciple
You possess remarkable abilities
Still invulnerable
Alone
Dare to break into Dingxiang
Master
Everyone else and Shiba is already at the inn
Let’s rendezvous with them
What do I need to do
Tell me quickly
At noon
In less than three hours
Take someone first
To meet with Wei Shuyu’s group
Then follow the plan
Then you be careful
You have to think it over
It’s too late to leave now
You just don’t know anything
Where is Li Changge’s letter hidden
Time is running out to save A’Sun
You really sure
You want to be enemies with your mother
No
She will always be my mother
What I’m doing
Is mitigating her sin
She’er
Leave it to me
I’m Young Khan
This is not difficult for me
She’er
Thank you
I said
I’m making atonement for my mother
And I don’t want A’Sun to die
Not right, Young Master
What are we waiting for
Ashile Sun
Will be executed right away
We are waiting for the map
Waiting for the execution stage
The residence of the young Sui Emperor
Empress Xiao’s residence
Where is Mimi’s brother?
Convenient escape path from the palace
A few more things
Guard the weak gate
Location
These places we have to
Know well in advance
How could it be so detailed
Unless
You arranged a detailed work in the palace
Could it be that Mimi?
Don’t say that it’s Mimi
Not right
It’s really her
Then...
Did I wrongfully accuse her
Yicheng has been threatening Mimi
Not only did she not succumb
On the contrary
She’s helping us