The Long Ballad
Episode 48
Not right
It’s really her
Then...
Did I wrongfully accuse her
Yicheng has been threatening Mimi
Not only did she not succumb
On the contrary
She’s helping us
Mimi
No matter what happens
I will believe you
Would you trust me
Mimi
Tell me
What happened
Changge
You fool
Still caring about me at this time
What happen?
She wants me to be in the alliance
She wants me to be at the conference
To slander you
Frame you
She even wanted me
To identify in front of everyone
Say you are Li Jiancheng’s daughter
What to do
Then do what she says
I have been
Upset about the Tang Emperor’s affairs
But I don’t doubt
His ability to do things
Even if my identity is revealed
He can also
Resolve this too
My family affairs with Great Tang
And the Princess will be present
She is the real princess
This is not a fatal point
On the contrary
If you can do it
Not only to rescued
Buzhen and Mu Jin
But still able
Make her trust you more
You mean
Of course
If this embarrass you
You don’t need to go
I am willing to inquire for you
Mimi is so brave
But
Can she really send information out?
I believe she can
Someone asked me to give you moon cakes
Before dying
Any last wish
Buried me in the grassland after I die
I want to watch it with my own eyes
Restoring peace in the grasslands
Staying away from war
Good
Then I’ll let you go there
To be a lonely ghost
Almost ready time to start
Execution
A’Sun is at the main hall
Can you believe his words?
Except for believing me
Is there any other choice?
I’m standing in front of you
Do you want me to teach you what to do?
Xu Feng
Send the message to Master and Wei Shuyu
Just say that the plan has changed
Yes
Stop!
Changge
Making trouble!
Li Changge
Release my person
Release Ashile Sun
Otherwise today
It’s your son’s death
Even if I let him go
Just rely on you
Do you think you guys
Can you leave here alive
Protect the princess
Who said I came alone
Don’t blame me for not reminding you
If you dare to move again
Next shot through
I don’t know whose head it would be
Changge said
She will kidnap She’er in front of the hall
Force Yicheng to release Ashile Sun
All guards
Will be led there
We will take the opportunity to sneak in
Split into two groups
One group to find Buzhen and Mimi
One group to save the grandchildren of Empress Xiao
Bring them all out
Yicheng has no handle
Can’t get out of the sky anymore
Whether she and Ashile Sun
Can you survive
Must let them survive
Greeting Empress Xiao
We came to rescue you
Don’t be afraid Young Masters
I’m here to save you
You
Even if I missed today
Die here
My people can do the same
Shoot Young Khan
We-fate-fate
Let go of She’er
I will let Ashile Sun go
Right now, I am in person in charge
Don’t you forget
Your son
Is now in my hands
Don’t move
If you dare to hurt my son
I won’t spare you
I’m fine
Release Ashile Sun
Release him
Release She’er
Thanks
Kill them
She’er
What do you want to do
Mother
Let them go
You dare to take a knife
Against your mother
Let them go
Young Khan
Don’t hurt Princess
You are my son
You won’t kill me
Lei Meng
Chase them
Don’t move
I won’t kill you
But I will let you lose me
Is it all for me
Now
No need now
So just now
You and Li Changge
Staged a trick on me
You know I won’t hurt you
So you use me
You really are my good son
Sentimental and righteous
Why don’t you kill me
This way you can better save Ashile Sun
You can still avenge your father
Kill me
- Come on
- Mother
If you’re not with me
You can leave
Lei Meng
Catch them
Kill without mercy
Yes
Go
Changge
Here
There seems to be with the map
I’m a little bit entangled
You heard clearly
In a moment pass through here and at the corner
Go straight forward
There will be a door
I have bolted the door
You can see
As long as you work hard later
Can break out
Just at the door
There may be some guards
But as long as you break out
You guys can escape
Us?
What about you
I can’t go yet
Buzhen is still here
You really think
I came alone
Everyone else has come
To save your brother
And you can rest assured
With my master Situ Langlang here
Gods can’t beat him
Really
Of course it is true
Why am I lying to you
Hurry up
Capture them
Yes
Mimi
Changge
Fortunately you are fine
You will be fine too
I will take you out
Buzhen
Young Master
Empress Xiao’s grandson and Bu Zhen
Have already left
Good
Help me take care of Buzhen
We agreed to leave together
I will take you with Buzhen
Go back to the Eagle Division together
I can definitely save you
I can save you
Changge
I
I really
Still want to see him again
Kill
What are you doing back
Naturally come back to save my brother
Mimi
I’m here
Mu Jin
Is it really you
It’s me
Promise me
For me
Take good care of Buzhen
We have to take care of Buzhen together
We want him to go to the market
Let’s take him to the moon cake together
There are many, many things
We’re going to do
I can’t take care of him alone
You can be alone
I crave...
Craving sugar
I will take you to buy sugar
To buy a lot of sugar
Okay
So sweet
I
I like you
Mimi
I like you too
Like very much
From the first time i saw you
I really like you
I beg you don’t let me go
Don’t let me go
Who do you say is not capable
You you you are you
Mimi
You will always be Eagle Division’s family
My Mimi
You are my man
You have to be responsible for me
I’ll take you back to the grassland, ok?
We can go to the desert
We go home
Go home
Take care of
Mimi
Don’t leave me Mimi
She’er
Mimi
Don’t you touch her
Why is like this
Why
Why don’t you protect her
And you
Everything that Mimi did
Was for all of you
Why did you guys
Not protect her
Why
You should ask your mother
She’er
Lei Meng killed her
Lei Meng
She’er
Calm down
Li Jing has brought soldiers
Coming straight to Dingxiang
Yi Cheng is destined to come to an end
Come with us
Let go
Even if I helped you
It doesn’t mean that I surrender to Great Tang
I don’t care what you are going to do
What am I going to do
Best you leave it alone
She’er
Eagle Divison is good at fighting
Our defenders were no match
They have been fled outside the palace
The rebel is just rebelling
Don’t panic
Report
Urgent
Khatun
Li Jing has approached Dingxiang
Stop speaking nonsense
Li Jing an army of a hundred thousand
Still more are on the way
How could it be overnight
They approached Dingxiang
Those attacking our tribes
Was not a hundred thousand army
But
It was brought by Li Jing himself
Three thousand soldier horse
Three thousand soldier horse, three thousand soldier horse
How could such a thing happen?
How can this be good
This this
Words from a spy agents
To deceive the crowd
Upset our military
No one is allowed to leave
Who dares to leave the palace half a step
I will kill them
Lei Meng, I’m going to kill you
Enough
Ridiculous
Really ridiculous
What are you fighting for
For me
For Ashile Tribe
Or for Princess Yicheng
She’er
Blood on your hands
Isn’t it enough?
For your so-called great cause
How many people do you have to be sacrifice
Lei Meng
Take She’er away
Someone
Take Young Khan away
Yes
Mother
Mother, let’s stop
Princess
You want to make Young Khan
Pass on my order
The three armies
Waiting at the gate of Chengqi
Protect the leaders
To leave Dingxiang together
Wolf Division is commanded by Lei Meng
Outside the palace gate
On standby
Yes
You are right
These years
I don’t have a day
That I don’t want to revive the Great Sui Dynasty
I just want to use Ashile Tibe
To come to fight for me
That’s why I endured the humiliation
To preserve the status of Khatun
I married four Great Khan
I not only want my son
To become the king of the grasslands
But to even let him overthrow Tang Dynasty
Rebuild the Sui Dynasty
It’s a pity
In the end I actually
Lost in the hands of my son
You say
Is this ridiculous
Am i in the world
The most failed mother
If because of me
You become what you are today
I hope you
Never had me
I suffered for a lifetime
In the end, to exchanged this sentence
Never had me
Good
Very good
From now on
I’m no longer your mother
You are no longer my son
Shut up
Take She’er away
Withdraw
Why aren’t you leaving
Where the princess is
Is where Lei Meng will be
Presumptuous
I want you to lead immediately
Wolf Division
And Dingxiang cavalry
Escort She’er away from Wudu Valley
I have leaders
There are people to cover
Since I will break through
The princess wants to turn away the enemy by herself
Let Young Khan survive
Hurry up
Lei Meng swore to follow the princess
Whenever and wherever
Win or lose
Life or death
I want you and She’er to leave
Protect him from the grassland
To a safe place
This time
Forgive this subordinates can’t obey
Are you going to disobey me?
I dare not
I just want to keep the princess safe
Until the last moment
I am subordinate
That escorted the princess away from Great Sui
Traveled all the way to the grassland
Thirty years
I have kept guarding the princess
All right
Take She’er and go
Protect him with your life
Can you do it
Promise me
Okay
Go now
The sooner the better
Commander
Why haven’t you set off yet
I won’t go
Now is not the time
For you to play tricks
Live well
Only this way
I’m worthy of the princess
Where’s my mother
I know she is your mother
Too late
Take him away
Dare you
Young Khan
I want to go in and find my mother
Stop being hypocritical in front of me
Can I still trust you, Young Khan
The princess’s plan is ruined
If you are not the princess’s son
I would have kill you
Take him away
Let me go
-Young Khan
- Mother
Let’s go
Let go
Let’s go.
Go.
Stop
Brother Qin
It seems that Dingxiang Palace
Has been successfully raided
Brother Li
Where’s my Father Khan
Come with me
Father Khan
How’s it going
General
Toxicity has invaded the internal organs
Since Khan Yanli is in good health
He was able to survive till now
But
To lead soldiers to fight again
I’m afraid it is...
Toxins in his body
Is it possible to force out
It is difficult to completely remove
But if care over time
He can resume speaking
His action can also be restored
Father Khan
Father
Sun will keep you for the rest of your life
My, my son
Father
Sun has ordered the Eagle Division to assist the Tang Army
To defeat Dingxiang
Yi Cheng uses the Ashile Tribes
To constantly provoke disputes
Don’t know
How many grasslands soldiers
Lost their lives
To win against Dingxiang
We only have to unite with the Tang Army
Over the years, the grassland has been conquering
Blood flowed into a river
People don’t have a living
The grassland people are too tired
Let them recuperate
Return the world to peace
Alright
Father
We are going to stop the war
You take Buzhen back first
I want to be alone
Stay with Mimi for a while
Buzhen
Let’s go
You like sweets, don’t you
I brought you candy
Get up for candy
Eat the candy Mimi
Please eat the candy Mimi
It’s really sweet
So sweet
I promised you
I’ll buy you sweets from now on
I promised you something
I will do it
Wait till all things
All settled down
I can stay with you
So everyone is here
Young Master Wei
You make it easy for me to find you
The general has something to call me
Xiao Hou and others have packed up
This mission is of great importance
It’s better to start as soon as possible
What the general said is extremely
Shiba
Xu Feng
Since General Li is here
Then next
You just follow Wei Shuyu
Escort the grandson of Empress Xiao
This matter is very important
There must be no mistakes
Yes
What about after the escort?
After the escort?
Don’t ask me
Where do you want to go
Shiba acknowledge Master
And will not separate
Let’s put aside the identity of Shiba
You have to ask yourself
Where do you want to go
I will listen to Master
That’s good
Then I will kill you now
Tell me your answer
I don’t know
Young Master
Don’t embarrass Shiba
I want to embarrass her
She can’t be like this in life
Following me
Shiba
Tell me your answer now
I want to try
Live a free life
With friends
Friends
Ok then
I’m leaving now
Originally, this time I
Is here to save the son-in-law
My task is done
I am withdrawing first
I have to teach this one
Two apprentices
You reminded me
Hurry on this trip
I forgot to tell you
Something about me
I accepted a little apprentice
You have a young sister
Last time we
When looking for comfrey
Swordsman Situ
Was playing with Yuanniang at home all day
I didn’t expect to find Yuanniang
Singularity
Is a martial arts wizard
So Yuanniang
Was tricked into worshiping him as a master
Even tricking kids
It’s not
What are you talking about
How can I lie?
Yuanniang likes it very much
Don’t you like it very much
Originally
You are my big disciple
It stands to reason
Should I save this light rainbow sword
For you
But what
Your master
To me back then
Qian reminded Wan to say
Say you must not break
Inheritance of Yuenv Sword
Being a teacher is very stressful
I know it as a teacher
You in the future
There must be no time
Swordsman
So just put this
I will give it to Yuanniang
Don’t choose to be a teacher
Actually
I should thank you all the more
Always take care of Yuanniang for me
Hope her life
Can be safe and sound
This is also considered
Consolation for Governor Gongsun and his wife
Rest assured
Me and Old Man Sun
Will definitely take time
Take Yuanniang to see you
Then everyone
There will be a period later
The time is long in the future
Changge, what about me
Zhenzhu
The two armies are about to fight
I’m afraid I can’t care for you
I will send someone
Send you back to Monan
Thank you
Also thank you your father
Changge
You are leaving me
It’s not
You haven’t been home for so long
Your father must miss you very much
Wait until later
I’ll talk to your Brother Sun
And go see you together
Brother Sun
You must come visit