[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 33]
Father,
I brought him back by mistake.
By mistake?
What do you mean by mistake?
You have nothing to do with this anymore.
Go back to the Terminator Sect.
Why should I listen to you?
I need to protect my brother.
Don't you know that I am
a spirit artifact for Gongmu Lie?
Go back to the Terminator Sect.
I am
a spirit artifact!
Do you want me to send you back then?
No, I don't want that.
I can go by myself.
Tell me if my brother is ok.
He is fine.
He has nothing to do with you.
Will you leave or not?
I'll go right away.
Look after my brother for me then.
I'll leave then.
Don't threaten me with your light!
Father,
have you sorted it out there?
Sorted?
It's just a beginning.
Qianqian,
are you really ok?
Get your hands off me.
I'm alive again.
- I'm alive again.
- Let go of me.
I was so worried that
- if I couldn't come back...
- Lianrou is watching us.
How would you cope?
Let go of me!
Lianrou, I...
Although
I'm not from the Illusory Demon Sect,
I can still read one's mind.
The first person he looked for after he woke up
must be the one he really cares about.
I've told you.
One's feelings can change.
It's not good.
But this time,
I agree with your choice.
Qianqian,
why are you crying?
Why are you crying?
Don't cry.
The man I love is Yuxin.
He's also called Yiyuan.
It's always been
him and him only.
What're you talking about?
But you loved someone else.
You've changed your mind.
Yes.
I have. But I  don't love her anymore.
Am I ruthless?
Am I a heartless rat?
No.
I broke up with you.
Remember?
You felt that no one liked you
and I was nice to you. So you started to like me back.
In fact, I am kind of nice to everyone.
The man I love better be a real macho.
You're not my type.
A new guy
came here recently.
I think I quite like him.
Feeling sad?
You're not her cup of tea.
How about you?
You're my type.
Me, too.
A lot of problems
were solved with the help of Master Hua.
But here we have more problems.
Right?
I'm getting used to this.
Brother.
Qianqian has told me about it.
I am Yuxin.
I grew up with you.
Brother.
Yuxin, I miss you so much.
No matter who I am,
we'll never split up.
Never.
Yiyuan,
tell me about your
resurrections.
Well...
I don't understand it myself.
I haven't figured it out yet.
Let's leave it for now.
What do we do?
Let's go and find Yushi first.
I'm worried about her.
Ok.
How about Chu Li, Du Shaoyang and Tang Siqi?
We just leave them?
I believe my grandpa and Uncle Hua
have all sorted it out.
Don't you think, when we were
attacked at the Purple Mist Sea,
the Golden Force let Tang Siqi and Du Shaoyang
escape on purpose?
Yeah.
Let's go now.
Yushi.
[The Ling Town]
- Yushi.
- Sister.
Are you alright?
Yushi.
Qin Lie.
You promised to marry me.
But you never kept your word.
All you care about is your dream.
You never took me seriously.
Then why do you pretend to love me
and keep pestering me?
Why don't we just break up?
What's wrong with her?
The Supreme Voodoo Insect.
Sister,
calm down.
That's so nice of you
to call me like this.
If my memory serves me right,
you already knew who you were
when you came out from the Graveyard.
My memory came back to me long ago.
I know I am Ling Xuanxuan,
not Pan Qianqian.
So who is my lover, Qianqian or Xuanxuan?
Do you have to talk about this now?
I gained my divine sense in the Graveyard.
I remembered everything.
But you wanted me to stay as Pan Qianqian.
You didn't want me to be sad.
So I kept pretending it
so that you wouldn't worry about me.
I would rather die than not be able to
call you my sister.
Since we love each other so much,
why don't you come along
and help me exterminate
the Human Race who betrayed us
and make our race great again?
Yushi,
you wanna kill me?
Anyone who stops me from rejuvenating my race
shall be killed.
You guys should back off.
I owe you.
You shall kill me.
But it's not their fault.
It's only between us.
However,
I'm afraid that you won't be able to
kill me even if I am just by myself.
The Spirit Pillar.
The Imaginary Pillar.
Qin Lie,
how's my sister?
[Inside the Imaginary Pillar]
This is
a sea of leaves of heart?
What?
You didn't know about this?
Isn't this your own pillar?
I've never been here before.
How could you confine me in the pillar
you know nothing about?
I don't want to confine you.
I just want to cure you of the Voodoo poison.
Yushi,
don't you think it's strange?
I thought only you
are able to grow
these spirit herbs?
It's full of leaves of heart.
What?
How would I know about this?
Have I seen them anywhere?
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
It's full of leaves of heart there.
Can't you see them?
No, we can't.
Yiyuan,
could this have something to do with
your resurrections?
The first time you died,
you said you saw Wuchun and a kid.
What about the second time?
I can't remember.
What is he doing?
Growing herbs.
Leaves of heart are poisonous. Do not touch them.
Yushi,
what did you see?
I was willing to be your shadow,
chasing after your light.
I was willing to wait for you every time
you travel far away.
Yushi, you remember it.
You woke up?
Look how pleased you are.
Qin Lie,
Those days are gone now.
Do you remember what I told you?
When the second volume of
the Scripture appeared,
I saw something.
I saw myself killing you.
It seems that
you already owed me ten thousand years ago.
After all this time,
I still need to kill you again.
Yushi,
since you can open the second volume,
why don't you have a look at
what happened ten thousand years ago?
There's no need.
I remember it.
That kid was me.
Chubby little kid, running and growing herbs.
I was the one who grew the leaves of heart.
Leaves of heart?
They were grown by me. Got it?
No.
Kill me! Kill me!
What?
I can save Yushi!
I know I can!
Come on.
How?
I don't know.
I'll know if you kill me.
Come on.
Come on!
I want to take my own life
but I can't do that.
I need your help. Kill me!
Are you infected by the Supreme Voodoo Insect too?
Wake up!
Yiyuan.
Why?
Because I believe him.
Then I should be the one to kill him.
You love him.
You can't do this.
I don't.
Yiyuan.
Will he come back to life again?
His body is getting cold.
Just wait a while.
Are you cold?
Is he dead?
I don't know.
But he is infected by the Voodoo Insect.
He can't be dead then.
He did it!
What do you mean?
A man like this
doesn't deserve your tears.
That's none of your business.
I just want to know
if I really had feelings for you.
Get out.
I don't mean to offend you.
Why are you following me?
I need an answer.
I want to know
why I liked you.
That's funny.
You don't know
that yourself?
What is love?
What does it mean to us?
It's just like a snowflake.
It melts away as soon as
you reach out and catch it.
I've changed from Xie Jingxuan to Tang Siqi.
I've been pursuing my love.
I didn't expect it to be so hard,
so excruciating.
I was always over the moon at first
whenever I saw him
and was thinking of him.
I felt happy for him.
I worried about him.
I worried that he couldn't fulfill his dream,
that he wouldn't give in when he should.
I worried that he might be bullied by others,
that he might give up on himself.
I didn't dare to ask how he felt
or what he was thinking.
I am not what I used to be.
I became humble and timid.
After all this time,
I know he won't be Qin Lie's match.
He will betray all of us one day.
I've been worried about
when that day will come.
I can't have both love and friendship.
What should I do?
Kill him and forget about your love.
Otherwise, he will kill you.
The chaos will end forever.
I tried to kill him.
But he saw through my tricks.
He wanted to kill me later on.
Why do we have to end up like this?
Do you want me to help you?
Yes.
What do you want?
You never had any women before.
How would you know what love is?
If you are afraid,
you can back off any minute.
Close your eyes.
Feel what you want to feel.
Feel what I want you to feel.
Father, will he understand love this way?
I would have understood it so long ago
if it could be done with just a kiss.
You can't do it
without knowing the causation.
You want to give memories back to him then?
Shouldn't he understand it by
himself as an artifact?
He is the son of Zhu.
Congratulations on my son's return
after the cultivation.
[Ten thousand years ago, the Revered
Thoughtful Mountain in the Surah Realm]
Congratulations on your
Golden Legion of Titans, father.
Your work has finally paid off.
Qianjie, are you enlightened?
[Zhu You, the Master of Spells]
I've been through a lot.
I've seen birth, death, diseases, love,
hatred and departure.
I've had luck, help and justice.
I've known it all.
Love is the biggest
challenge in the world.
You've also understood it?
When I first arrived in the Colourless Realm,
I met a lady.
I heard both of our heartbeats
when we were together.
I started to know this was love.
I understood why ordinary people
were stuck in love.
Have you ended it?
Yes, I have.
Love is indeed wonderful.
At the end of the day,
it's mere a tiny personal joy.
The deeper you're lost in it,
the more likely you will lose control.
You understand it only if you get away
as soon as possible.
You're my cleverest
boy among the three.
I named you 'Qianjie'
because I hoped
you could go through all the hardships
and achieve your dream.
The Spirit Wisdom of Titans
hasn't been developed.
I'm willing to become a spirit artifact
to lead the Golden Legion and
fight against the God Race.
If you want to achieve great things,
you need to climb this mountain
and walk through the Gate of Steps.
Every hardship you've gone through
will would be represented on
each of the steps.
Can you step over them?
Yes, I can.
Qianjie, you're leaving.
Yes, Sang Ying.
Will you remember me?
No.
Qianjie, I don't expect you to marry me.
I just hope that you can always remember me.
I loved you because I want to give up love.
Let's just forget each other.
Love is hard to get
and hard to forget about.
You only experienced love.
You haven't understood it.
I feel sorry
for Sang Ying.
You are a disgrace.
I might as well end it for you
since you feel so distressed about it.
It really is you.
What do you mean?
Why do you do this to me?
[Inside the Imaginary Pillar]
Qin Lie.
Yushi.
I'm sorry.
It's alright.
You're just lost.
Let me take you home.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing is more important than
taking your hand.
So silly of me.
This is not the Ling Town.
We're inside the Thunder Pillar.
What gave me away?
When I took your hand,
your palm was cold.
Yes.
Every time you took my hand,
my hand always got warm and my face would blush.
I even felt like my heart was on fire.
No wonder it's the Supreme Voodoo Insect.
Even the Spirit Pillar can't treat it.
Yushi,
I can't let you go out.
You think you can trap me here?
Yushi.
I said I would stay with you forever,
no matter what.
If I couldn't protect you,
I would die with you here.
Kill him.
Yushi.
What's this?
My blood.
The blood of the Queen of the Nether Race.
You will take my order.
Once I'm going to kill Qin Lie,
you will kill me immediately.
You can't have any hesitation.
I worried that because of the Voodoo Insect inside me,
you wouldn't be able to kill me.
I was wrong.
You're always determined.
It's just I didn't expect
you would die with me.
How could you be so hard on yourself?
I hate it when you're so calm.
This is the first time you've cried for me.
There must be another way.
I have a place in your heart.
I have no regret.
It's a pity that
I still don't know
what happened to us ten thousand years ago.
Did we fight against each other
or did we forget each other?
It doesn't matter anymore.
What matters is that
in the future,
no matter where I go
and what I go through,
you will always have a special place in my heart.
You will experience what I see
and feel the way I feel.
[Ten thousand years ago, the Deserted Spirits Realm]
I've already restored this place.
You can leave now.
I want to know the whereabouts of my father.
You didn't keep your promise.
That's the only reason I came here.
I won't give up without fulfilling my goal.
You ignored my determination.
Tong Xin?
What is he doing?
Growing herbs.
He is Tong Xin,
the essence of all plants.
Tong Xin.
He is so hostile. Grow some herbs for him.
Terrified?
He is not terrifying.
The leaves of heart are.
They're poisonous. Don't touch them.
The spirit stones in the Deserted Spirits Realm
have existed ever since the universe was created.
They're shiny and transparent,
small and exquisite.
They reflect people's minds
and their emotions.
Your anger not only
just comes from your determination.
It has something to do with your promise.
You haven't kept yours.
Who are you?
It's nothing noble that so many people
plotting against a child.
Wuchun,
take him away.
Now it's better. No fights and all.
What's this place?
The Deserted Spirits Realm.
Our people live here.
This can be turned into a shooting star.
Have you seen it before?
Who were those people just now?
Why would they want to kill me?
I can't tell you.
Hiding the truth from me.
Lying to me.
You're just like them.
You're all bad people.
You must be sad.
I am angry.
I believe you are.
But it's mainly sadness that you feel.
You're sad that you aren't trusted.
They don't trust you
no matter how cruel the truth is.
Because you can't protect yourself yet.
If one day
when you're powerful enough,
but they still won't tell you the truth,
You can come to me. I will tell you.
Really?
How far can they fly?
How far do you hope they can fly?
How far do you wish you can fly?
Will you come and visit me
before I get powerful enough?
Yes.
You are not lying to me?
People at the Deserted Spirits Realm
will keep their promises.
You've been waiting for me.
You didn't keep your promise.
That's not true.
You forgot me then?
I am busy.
I am the next Mother of Earth.
I need to practise every day.
Liar! You have nothing to do!