[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 34]
[Ten thousand years ago,
the Deserted Spirits Realm]
You broke your promise.
I didn't.
So, you have forgotten about me.
I was quite occupied.
I am going to be the Mother of Earth.
I need to practice every day.
You liar. You have got plenty of time.
Otherwise, how do you explain that?
You have been spying on me?
Are you...
Are you thinking about me every day?
Say it.
Do you think about me every day?
Yes.
Then why didn't you come to find me?
I can't tell you.
You can't, you dare not.
You are just as hypocritical and cowardly as them.
Wu Chun isn't hypocritical or cowardly.
I forbade her to see you.
Why?
I met your mother
Xuan Luo once before.
My mother?
Human and the Divine Race are at daggers drawn.
As a valorous general of the Divine Race,
Xuan Luo broke the rules
and fell in love with Gongmu Hao of the Gongmu family.
Then they had you.
However, the two bloodlines in you
are not able to merge.
The ruthless blood of the Divine Race
totally suppressed the human bloodline.
But with this comes a blessing.
It is also because of the double bloodline
that you can live till this day.
Every step you take
would be arduous like oil burning on fire.
Thinking about this,
your mother named you Lie, meaning burning.
Where is my mother now?
She was cursed by the Divine Race for breaking the taboo.
Her hair went gray overnight and she was going to die of old age.
When I met with her,
you were still a baby.
But she was already very old.
She asked me to send you
to be raised in the Gongmu family
and keep you safe and sound.
I have never heard of her again since she left.
If the two bloodlines in you can merge,
you will become a major threat to the Spirit Realm.
Your grandfather took up all the hardship and pressure
to keep you in the family and raise you up.
However, he was a spirit artificer.
there is always a time when he went out
to collect materials for his work.
Each time he left you,
he would ask me to protect you in the dark.
About those who tried to kill me,
are they human or from the Divine Race?
They are human.
From the Golden Force of the Surah Realm.
Now you should understand
why I forbade Wu Chun to see you.
The Mother of Earth and the son of the God of War
can't fall in love with each other.
If this is known by the evil,
before you two enjoy some time together,
there will be imminent disasters.
But now,
you already fell in love.
Whether you want to fight to be together
or to go your separate ways
is up to you.
I guess your mother is right.
There is no good in it at all
for you to see me.
The reason why I didn't go
to see you
is not that I didn't dare to defy my mother.
It is because
I thought you have already forgotten me.
Since your grandfather sent you
to cultivate the Spirit Pattern Pillar,
you were not alone.
You were always together with
the girl called the Night Fairy.
You were peeping at me as well.
You were the son of the Master of Spells
of the Ancient Masters.
Since you ruined your cultivation because of love,
your father tried to kill you in a rage
but couldn't bear to do it.
So, he sealed you
in the Spirit Pattern Pillar of the Gongmu family.
He hoped you could keep cultivating yourself.
But then the Gongmu family was destroyed.
Gongmu Lie was put to sleep
and I followed him.
Did you see all of this
during a blink of eyes just now?
Yes.
How could this happen?
Because you are Sang Ying.
You kissed me.
You are saying that
I am the girl who fell in love
with you ten thousand years ago?
I came to demand a payback after ten thousand years?
That's correct.
Therefore, you cross me in everything
and I dislike you in every aspect.
Are you sure the person you saw was me?
It was you.
What on earth do you want from me?
What do you mean?
For no reason at all,
you just kissed me.
I wanted to help you.
Help me?
You were trying to make me
head down the same path I took years ago.
Even if you can't recall what happened before,
I know that
you must be Sang Ying.
I...
Save it.
Just tell me what do you want.
Let's end it all.
Alright.
Go to the Graveyard of Gods with me
and destroy the remains of the voodoo master.
You have my word.
But if it doesn't work to destroy the remains,
the thing between us
will still be written off.
It's a deal.
We need the Demon Sealing Tombstone
to go to the graveyard.
Do you have it?
Let's go.
Father, Sang Ying is Tang Siqi?
No, she isn't.
Do it now.
Shaoyang.
I knew that you would do this.
So what?
I learned directly from Jiang Yan.
You are no longer a match for me.
My jade ferule may not be able to kill you.
But my father's boomerang can.
So, you really can do this.
I guess you are not cruel-hearted enough.
You didn't use your full power.
Evils must be pulled up by the roots.
Shaoyang.
Siqi.
Go.
I'm sorry.
Why did you save him?
I wanted to save him
and also die in your hands.
Why?
For the debt.
Ten thousand years ago, you owe me your love.
Now, ten thousand years later, you owe me a life.
I know that
one day
you will capture Shaoyang,
I only wish that
you can think about me
and the life you owe me,
and you can give him a chance.
I want to use my life
in exchange for the last chance for him.
Is it really worth it?
There is no worth it or not.
It is only about love or not love.
Then don't love.
Siqi,
forget about him.
Qianjie,
you still don't understand.
You don't know that
love is not about forgetting.
It's about keeping it
deep down in your heart.
Qianjie, will you remember me?
Yes, I will.
Though we don't have the chance to be together,
I will remember you forever
deep in my heart.
Now you have been enlightened.
Cutting off your love is not to forget
but to bury it deep in your heart.
Am I really Sang Ying?
No, you are not.
No, I am not.
I told you that
I am not a skittish woman.
No, you are not.
Find a quiet place
to bury me.
Where do you want it to be?
I'll leave the choice to you.
Okay.
Zhu, Qianjie has been enlightened.
You can rest assured.
Father,
why didn't you save Tang Siqi just now?
Tang Siqi dared to love or hate.
She knew how to express her affection the most.
I used her to enlighten Qianjie.
But it is such a pity
that such a girl died.
You only saw her death
but didn't see her renascence.
The person who buries you today
will be the one who bears love for you then.
Chongming,
do you admit your guilt?
What gilt?
Your daughter dared to spread the rumor
that Gongmu Hao, the God of War, is still alive.
This is a felony offense.
You know the best about
whether he died or not.
Gongmu Hao is surely dead.
That's why I convicted you of spreading false rumors.
You will go and repent
at the Six Heaven Fire Formation.
We are always in the wrong.
You did this for the Scripture of the Nine Hells.
She would die in the Six Heaven Fire Formation
or lose all her cultivation at least.
You made the mistake
and still try to sling mud at me?
Six Heaven Fire.
Wu Chun.
You can't go.
Get out of my way.
Stay.
Twelve Spirit Pattern Pillars
have merged in me.
You won't get through me.
But these spirit pillars are mine.
I would die to make you stay.
Why did you make such a scene?
Why did you fight against them?
What did they do wrong?
Your father already died with honor in battle.
But Wu Chun spread the rumors,
saying that he is still alive.
She must be plotting something.
I asked her for the whereabouts of my father.
But Wu Chun never gave me a clear answer.
What do you mean by spreading rumors?
Or is it because you are guilty?
How dare you!
I haven't condemned you for your sins.
What sins do I have?
I imposed a ban before that
people in the Spirit Realm
are not allowed in the Deserted Spirits Realm
without permission.
We don't need to obey unreasonable orders.
You are the one who violated it.
The two of you will be punished together.
Then try me.
Gongmu Lie, don't fight him.
Sheng Xie.
Six Heaven Fire.
If you don't repent,
the Gongmu family will receive the same punishments
as the Deserted Spirits Realm.
Mother.
Gongmu Lie, don't.
Today, with the power of the Divine Race,
I will break open your Six Heaven Fire Formation.
If you want to die,
you can die together.
If you can get out,
what would you do?
Fight against him with my life.
It's casting away your life.
I won't regret it.
Do you know why
the Master of Heaven used
the Six Heaven Fire Formation?
Because he knows
only the Scripture of the Nine Hells can break it.
If I use the scripture,
I can definitely make it out.
But all of my cultivation would be gone.
You can't.
Gongmu Lie,
forget about me.
I missed you for ten years.
How can I forget about you?
After ten years of waiting,
we only get together for a moment.
It's not worth it.
A moment
means a whole life.
What the Master of Heaven fear
is the union of the Gongmu family
and the Deserted Spirits Realm.
If you forget about me,
he would spare you.
I'll remember the love to the end of my life.
Unless you are able to make me forget about you.
You have a spirit artifact in you.
Can you lend me that?
What do you want?
You...
With the royal blood of the Nether Race,
I hereby cast a spell.
As long as the spell exists,
Gongmu Lie will never fell in love with Wu Chun.
How ridiculous.
How can a spell
stop my love for Wu Chun?
If it can't,
I'll use my life to pay it back.
How cruel you are!
Yes, I am.
How can I
break the spell?
Unless
you hate me.
Otherwise, it will not break forever.
Wu Chun.
Your honor,
after all, Gongmu Lie is the son of the God of War.
It is not appropriate to kill him.
It's my lack of discipline for him.
I am willing to take the punishment for him.
I beg your honor to spare him, otherwise...
Otherwise, what?
The Gongmu family will not let things lie.
What are you doing, what are you doing?
I kindly helped you and spoke for you.
But now you are saying this.
You sad old fool.
Hua Tianqiong,
I think you are here purposely to stand up for them.
You two are playing the carrot-and-stick approach.
Good for you.
You honor,
I only pledge my loyalty to the Surah Realm
with no connections with the Gongmu family.
I am just thinking about the big picture.
In the battle between human and the Divine Race,
though the Divine Race retreated in defeat,
we barely won a victory.
The four big families had taken a great hit.
People in the Spirit Realm
suffered heavily and
are still recovering from it till today.
It is indeed not a good time to pick a fight
and stir up internal turmoil.
So, tell me,
what should I do?
He can be spared from death,
but can't escape the punishment.
Gongmu Lie shall be put to sleep at barren badlands
and can't be awakened without your honor's permission.
What should I do with Wu Chun?
Wu Chun is willing to be put to sleep with Gongmu Lie.
She will not wake up without your honor's permission.
This sounds reasonable.
Since he was born,
I grounded him in the Forbidden Grit Realm
assuming that I could protect him this way.
But I didn't expect that
still, we came to this today.
Thank you for saving
the life of my grandchild, Master Hua.
I was just thinking about the big picture.
Please.
You are the spirit artifact forged by Lie himself.
Go with him.
Go.
Sheng Xie, you asked to be sealed with him yourself.
Don't forget me.
Qianjie.
You didn't stay in the spirit pattern pillar
because you are worried
that the Surah Realm wouldn't give it up
and do something secretly,
and you want to follow and protect him?
No need to say it out.
Wait, and me.
Mr. Gongmu, Wu Chun worries that
that black energy hasn't all been absorbed by me.
Some might still be lingering in his body.
I can go and accompany him.
Much appreciated.
Everyone,
please.
Lie,
go and sleep for a while.
When the time comes,
I will awaken you.
I didn't hear anything.
When Qianjie is enlightened and
able to form the Armor of the God of War,
he can help Lie lead the Legion of Titans.
Tong Xin was formed from a leaf of heart.
He can rid Lie of poison and help him recover.
My girl,
why wouldn't you go to sleep?
Do you have some unfinished issues?
No, I don't.
You cast a spell on Gongmu Lie?
Yes.
And?
Nothing more.
And what?
Nothing.
Mother,
if I can never see you again,
I want to thank you for your love and benevolence.
Good.
It turned out that
I cast the spell myself.
I am the one who banned you from loving me.
But I already fell in love with you.
After I am gone,
you can miss me
but don't feel sad for me.
I hate to see this for you, Qin Lie.
You were so innocent.
Xuanxuan,
live on and live well.
Sister.
Tong Xin.
Why did you show up here?
I didn't show up, I woke up.
I died several times and I was awakened.
Not just me. He woke up as well.
What?
You don't recognize me without a long face?
I am the son of the Master of Spells.
I wanted to forge a spirit artifact with my own body,
however, I wasn't enlightened and failed.
Your family has a reputation for making artifacts,
so, I was entrusted to you for my cultivation.
Since you are a spirit artifact,
why did you cross us in everything?
I was lost in love.
I wanted to use the pillars for my cultivation,
but Gongmu Lie was obsessed with you.
How could I be enlightened then?
He is the one to blame.
Qin Lie,
I now can form into a spirit artifact
to command the Legion of Titans.
When you are awakened one day
and you need me,
I would spare no efforts to help you.
Thank you a lot.
Right,
there are two more things.
Du Shaoyang has acquired all the
voodoo energy left of the voodoo master.
Moreover,
Tang Siqi is already dead.
I killed her.
But she died because of Du Shaoyang.
I assume
you must have known about the true identity of him.
Yes, I have.
Good.
I am going back to reunite with my big brother.
It is the fate that brought us together.
Take care, everyone.
Wu Chun,
I will see you again after you are awakened.
I thought it was Yuxin.
However, it was not Yuxin but Yi Yuan.
But Yi Yuan is also Yuxin.
Actually, it was neither of them, but Tong Xin.
What a mystery!
My love was so strong and vigorous.
The story is even stranger than yours with Qin Lie.
I am really thrilled.
A saying goes that it is not a life in vain.
Xuanxuan,
go to sleep for a while.
I am not tired.
I just feel a little troubled.
When I think of him,
should I talk to the sky asking that
Yuxin,
how are you?
or say to the forehead of Qin Lie that
Yuxin,
how are you doing?
I think
I should say it to the forehead of Qin Lie.
But will he be
reluctant to lend his forehead to me?
Thank you.