A NETFLIX ORIGINAL SERIES
♪ Amado mio ♪
♪ Love me forever ♪
♪ And let forever ♪
♪ Begin tonight ♪
♪ Amado mio ♪
♪ When we're together ♪
♪ I'm in a dream world ♪
♪ Of sweet delight ♪
BANK OF SPAIN
5 YEARS BEFORE D-DAY
♪ Many times, I whisper ♪
- ♪ Amado mio ♪
- Hello.
♪ It was just a phrase ♪
♪ That I heard in plays ♪
♪ I was acting a part ♪
♪ But now when I whisper ♪
♪ Amado mio ♪
♪ Can't you tell I care ♪
♪ By the feeling there ♪
♪ 'Cause it comes from my heart... ♪
Good morning.
I have an appointment
with Mr. Mario Urbaneja,
governor of the Bank of Spain.
Alfredo Kesmann,
from Rating Trust Corporation.
[woman] One moment.
You're very kind. Thank you.
♪ Amado mio ♪
♪ Love me forever ♪
♪ And let forever ♪
♪ Begin tonight ♪
- Excuse me. Where are you going?
- Hello.
And you?
Do we know each other?
I'm asking you where you're going.
I have an appointment with the governor.
Where are you going? For a walk?
It's a beautiful day.
You were told to wait down here.
- Mmm.
- Someone will get you.
Well, no one came, so I'm going up.
I know the way.
- [woman] Mr. Kesmann?
- At your service.
- Pleased to meet you.
- [Berlin] How are you?
Sorry for the wait.
- The governor will be with you shortly.
- Excellent.
- Come with me.
- Thank you.
- Have a lovely day.
- May I join you?
With pleasure.
[machine beeping steadily]
[Paquita] Get some rest.
Ssh.
It's you.
I'm the head of intensive care.
Don't worry. I used to be a nurse.
I'm going to the bathroom,
but I won't be long.
Thank you.
[Gandía] Mutt.
[Nairobi gasps]
I told you I was gonna kill you.
[rapid beeping]
["My Life Is Going On"
by Cecilia Krull]
♪ If I stay with you
If I'm choosing wrong ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ If I'm losing now
But I'm winning late ♪
♪ That's all I want ♪
♪ I don't care at all ♪
♪ I am lost ♪
♪ Lost my time ♪
♪ My life is going on ♪
Where did he go?
Rio, where did he go?
Rio, fuck!
Where did he go?
Up the stairs.
Stockholm, Denver, stay here.
Don’t let anyone get near the door.
If the hostages get out, we’re fucked.
Got it?
- Got it
- Come on.
- Okay, Helsinki, Bogotá, with me.
- [Helsinki] Let's go.
Everyone get on your fucking feet, now!
[beeping]
- [Helsinki] What's wrong?
- [Denver] Face away from the door!
Oh, fuck! Nairobi.
Something's wrong. Run!
[Helsinki] Nairobi, we're coming!
[Gandía grunts]
[muffled cries]
- Nairobi, we're coming!
- [Helsinki] Nairobi!
[grunts]
Argh!
[Helsinki] Nairobi, we're coming!
[Tokyo] Nairobi, hold on!
[Gandía panting]
[grunts]
[gasps]
He was trying to kill her.
Her pulse is 162.
Nairobi! Nairobi, are you okay?
Nairobi. It's okay. It's okay. Breathe.
- Breathe, Nairobi.
- [Nairobi] Gandía got out.
Bogotá.
Bogotá!
Stay here with Nairobi.
If he comes back,
you blow off his goddamn head.
You understand?
Helsinki, let's go get him.
- Take care of her.
- We'll find him.
[tense music]
From now on, all the rules have changed.
Nobody gets up, nobody moves,
nobody eats
without a fucking direct order!
You guys are fucked, Denver.
You guys are completely fucked!
I can’t believe him.
- You got something to say, Arturito?
- Yes.
You guys are not invincible anymore.
No, you're not invincible.
They're not invincible!
Arturo, shut up!
Or what?
Or I’ll empty my gun into your head.
- Things have changed around here, Mónica.
- [Stockholm] Yeah.
We're here,
and now we are
the mother fucking resistance!
Come on, Miguel. Come on!
We are the resistance! Hey?
We are the resistance. Our resistance!
[all chanting] The resistance!
The resistance!
[all gasp]
Resistance, my fucking balls.
[panting]
Everyone on the fucking floor right now!
[Berlin] So that’s it, Sergio.
We need to figure out
how the guards will react.
How the guards will react,
exactly how long they'll take
bringing the governor to safety,
and how they'll position themselves.
It's all in the protocols.
That’s true. We have the protocols,
we have the theory,
but we could use a little bit of practice.
And how do you intend
to obtain this practice?
[Berlin chuckles]
By creating a minor security crisis
and watching it all from inside.
You're going into the lion's den?
And the lion will protect me.
Whose identity are you planning to steal?
[Palermo and Berlin laugh]
They’ll think your brother is a genius,
a big deal.
a risk analyst
from Rating Trust Corporation
who previously worked for Bacher & Bacher,
and before that, Standard and Risk.
The person
whose identity we're stealing...
is someone... brilliant.
A Spaniard...
who's been living in New York
for the last 20 years.
[Berlin] Alfredo Kesmann.
A true genius.
Also, we have a few really terrific
suggestions for the economy of Spain.
- The governor will appreciate them.
- Yeah.
[jazz music playing]
May I sit down?
Of course.
But you could also stand and wait
for the governor of the Bank of Spain.
[Berlin] Hmm.
I presume you're
the chief of security for the governor.
Affirmative.
[clock chimes]
In some ways,
you and I are in the same line of work.
We both analyze the risks.
I think we're very alike, don’t you?
No.
We're not alike at all.
I analyze risks
so I can save peoples lives.
You do it to make money.
It's not the same.
See, we are alike.
You also seem perceptive and very...
observant.
What risks do you see here
at this exact moment in this room?
Purely out of curiosity.
If I had seen any risks in this room,
they'd have been gone already.
You understand that.
[footsteps approaching]
Mr. Kesmann.
- How do you do.
- How are you?
- Very well, thank you.
- Shall we sit?
Yes, please.
Would you care for a coffee, Mr Kesmann?
Well, a black Ceylon tea
with cardamom would be incredible.
- If not, any black tea's fine. Thank you.
- It's my pleasure.
If I had a coffee right now, I'd go loco.
[Sierra] Okay. All set for your statement.
Go ahead.
I do have a question
before we get started.
I don’t know if it’s relevant, but...
I’ve been thinking about it a lot
and wanted to ask you, Alicia.
Ask away.
What's it like when you go home?
I mean,
you get home from work
after...
torturing a kid like Rio
who you’ve made stand for days
in a cell that's smaller than a closet,
shitting and pissing himself.
Then you go home... to Germán.
That’s what I wanted to ask.
You don’t mind they call you
a torturer in the press.
But Germán...
Because Germán is a really good person,
what does he say when you come home?
Does he ask you,
"How was your day, honey?"
Do you kiss him and...
you hug him?
What then?
Does he hug you? Kiss you?
Do you fuck?
Because I think you make him sick.
[beeps]
See, the truth... Well, It's been about
two months since Germán hugged me.
Since he hugged me, since he kissed me,
or made love to me.
To be precise, not since I cremated him.
They pulled a white sheet over his face,
they rolled him down to the morgue
in the hospital,
and that’s where the hugging stopped.
[Tamayo] Alicia, what are you doing?
He's dead.
Cancer...
of the pancreas.
The kind where they tell you
you have two months,
and it's two months.
I was getting fat.
He was thin.
I was pink,
and he was yellow.
It consumed him.
Life grew inside me,
and death grew in him.
But I guess that's cancer.
Do you know the last thing he said to me?
Can you believe his last words were...
"Turn on the news."
I thought he was gonna give me
one of those speeches of his
because you know he was really eloquent,
and he was really creative too.
And he said, "Turn on the news."
Turn on the news!
I mean, he was full of morphine,
of course,
so I guess that was affecting him.
That was it.
[uneasy music]
I'm very sorry.
- Alicia, can we go outside for a moment?
- Yeah, yeah. I'll go.
[Sierra clears throat]
Antoñanzas, you stay and watch Murillo.
Don't let anyone in.
For Christ’s sake, why didn’t you tell
anyone about this before?
What would that get me?
A little bit of pity?
Oh, Alicia...
I feel for you, but I don't think you have
the capacity to lead this case right now.
[tense dramatic music]
[gasping]
[grunting]
[Gandía] I'll take this.
And this one as well.
Relax.
Try to die without making too much noise.
[gasps]
Helsinki! Helsinki!
[grunts]
Hold on! Bogotá!
[Tokio] Bogotá!
Come to the library!
Helsinki, stay with me.
- Stay with me! Hold on.
- [Nairobi] Go!
[Tokio] Bogotá!
Argh!
Bogotá! Bogotá, please!
[Tokio] The library, Bogotá!
Argh!
Bogotá, hurry!
Help me!
We've got you!
We've got you, Helsinki!
Take this. Go on.
[gasping]
Stay with us!
Come on!
Cut the rope!
Stay with us! Come on!
Come on! Cut the fucking rope right now!
- Stay with us, Helsinki!
- [panting]
[panting]
Gandía!
[Bogotá] Motherfucker!
[man] Hey, shut up!
I said no talking!
No talking!
[Arturo] Amanda.
- How are you feeling?
- Better.
- I feel a little more calm now.
- That's great.
If it's okay, I think I'm ready
to go join the others.
Don't worry about that now.
What's important is your recovery.
- Okay.
- Okay, let's check your pulse.
Oh. Oh, man, this is way too fast, Amanda.
It's signs of a serious anxiety attack.
Do you have agitation?
Agitation in your chest?
Well, a little, yes.
No, that's normal.
It’s one of the symptoms.
You're very lucky because...
I've got something for you. [chuckles]
Here. This stuff works miracles.
Why don't you take three?
But isn’t that too much?
It's just a little stronger than Valium.
- Are you sure?
- I swear.
I just took four.
- Okay.
- There you go.
One at a time. One at a time.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Okay, everyone, listen up.
Everyone!
Okay.
Most of you here didn’t get to meet, uh,
my husband...
Germán.
According to the colonel,
this concerns you all.
Well, he died.
[soft murmuring]
Tamayo...
thinks I'm in no condition
to lead this operation.
But the truth is,
there's no one better for the job than me.
No one.
Because I don't wanna go back
to my house...
and open my fridge...
or the mailbox...
because I'll see his name written down
and all our photos.
That's why I'm such a fucking robot
calculating 200 million plays per minute
against the Professor.
And that's what this heist needs
right now.
And that's what I need right now too.
Anyone care to say something to me?
No?
So let's have a little fun.
Let's get to work!
[Denver] Rio.
Tell me why you couldn’t shoot him.
I don't know.
I just froze.
- [Tokyo] Why did you freeze, Rio?
- Because I'm not a fucking killer.
You don’t have to be a killer.
I can’t look a guy in the face,
shoot him in the chest
- and pretend nothing happened.
- Shoot him in the leg!
- I can’t!
- Then knock him to the ground,
or throw him against a wall,
or whatever you need to do...
Listen to me.
I couldn't do it. I couldn't move!
He told me he had a family.
And he didn't have a gun.
I couldn’t do it!
Why couldn't you do it?
Tell everyone why.
You couldn’t do it
because you’re fucking traumatized!
And I told you,
but you didn’t fucking listen.
It's because of you. Yeah, you.
You almost killed Helsinki and Nairobi.
Denver, stop!
Rio warned us,
and Helsinki and Nairobi are alive.
That’s what's important.
[Helsinki] There's something else
more important.
How did he get free?
- You took Gandía to the bathroom.
- Yes.
- And you put the cuffs on good?
- Of course.
Of course, he did.
Of course, he did!
The only thing that's clear here is that
something isn't adding up in your story.
Tokyo, how does a handcuffed guy get out?
Nairobi, do you have any ideas?
Have any ideas? What?
Nothing, right?
Then I think there’s something here
that smells like bullshit.
Are you saying I’m a traitor?
- I don't know. Tell me.
- No!
Just say it.
[Bogotá] It's our fault.
Maybe we shouldn’t have left
the kid on guard,
since he's dealing with PTSD.
Rio isn’t the traitor.
[Professor] And we have
a more urgent problem.
Listen carefully.
The biggest threat is Gandía
communicating with the outside.
They could coordinate an attack
from inside and outside simultaneously.
What's the plan, Professor?
He needs to be killed.
Who?
Him.
[Professor] We are not killers.
Then we're gonna be corpses.
We’ll get rid of the governor’s personal
guards during the first hour of the heist.
They'll be the ones who leave the bank
with the State's secrets.
And that's the end of the problem.
[Denver] I said get the fuck out there!
That bastard isn't gonna leave
with the secrets.
No one move.
He won’t listen to our orders.
And Santiago?
Did he have time to leave the bank
after setting up that fun mess?
Yes.
- It looked like an accident.
- That explosion was magnificent!
I’ve brought the latest country
credit risk reports from my agency.
But... they're not published
until next month, no?
Yes, we’re still working on them,
but these are close to the final versions.
They're not very encouraging.
They’re going to affect
the rate of your public debt.
- Any recommendations?
- Officially, liquid assets in the bank,
anti-inflationist measures.
You know, standard procedures.
If you'll allow my personal opinion
that will never appear in this report...
gold.
Excuse me?
Increase your reserve of gold.
It’s the only safe currency that's still
on the rise, so bring it here...
to the vault in the Bank of Spain.
It’s the only choice that will give you
a guarantee in this market.
Look...
2008 was nothing.
Now the debt crisis is on its way.
Are you suggesting I...
gamble the entire national reserve...
on one single color?
No. I'm telling you
to bet everything on the winning team:
the gold.
[explosion]
[Governor] What’s happening?
[Gandía] Stay calm. Everything's okay.
Was that an explosion?
Guards to the governor’s office. Everyone.
Exterior security, this is Gandía.
Activate red alert.
I repeat, activate red alert.
Seal the bank doors.
- [man] Anything outside?
- No, I don't see anything outside.
- Where was the explosion?
- [man] In the basement, sir.
Judging by the smell,
it could have been a gas leak.
Copy that. Don't seal the doors.
I repeat, don't seal the doors.
We still might need to evacuate.
Maximum security alert!
Everyone put your vests on. Do it now!
[rock music]
They have military weapons in there.
I think he caresses them all afternoon,
longing for the moment
he can pull the trigger.
[Palermo] The guy was a green beret, eh?
Three years in the military,
but before that,
he was the personal bodyguard
of the Minister of the Interior.
He was deployed for operations
in Iraq and Lebanon,
and those are just the official ones.
Because in the six years that he was
a member of the special ops corps,
there isn't a single record
of his movements, and that means...
black ops, secret missions.
The guy’s an assassin, Sergio.
He’s an assassin.
Have you found the weapon supply?
[Tokyo] No, not yet.
We’ve searched everywhere,
and no sign of any weapons.
I don’t know about the guns,
but the handcuffs were in the library.
[Bogotá] That bastard took them off
on his own.
[Berlin]
He'd be like a kid at Disneyland.
We kill him, or he kills us.
I saw him too.
And I think it's pretty clear...
If he gets the chance,
he'll kill us all like space invaders.
When you face him, act decisively...
in self-defense...
but without hesitation...
because he won't hesitate.
He's a ruthless ex-mercenary.
Relentless.
And he’s going to try and kill you.
What are you gonna be doing over there?
I’m going to tie everyones hands outside
so they don't break the truce.
That...
and I'll make them think
we’re stronger than ever.
Okay.
The most important thing you've gotta do
is take a long, deep breath.
That's real good.
- Tell me something you really enjoy.
- The sea.
The sea's perfect,
and a great choice for this exercise.
Shut your tiny eyes.
Great. Okay, Amanda.
Imagine it’s a beautiful
and hot day in the summer.
You're down at the beach
near the shore,
with both of your feet in the water.
Can you feel it?
Yes, I feel it.
Now we’re on an air mattress,
floating in the water.
The sea wind breezes...
across the shore...
and the palm trees dance,
and it smells like summer.
[Amanda] I feel so sleepy.
Let the sounds of the sea drift you away.
The beautiful sea.
Amanda...
Then...
[peaceful relaxing music]
[beep]
[line ringing]
[Sierra]
If you're calling to negotiate, press one.
If you're calling to surrender, press two.
If you're calling to ask what I'm wearing,
press the pound sign.
- I see I reached you at a good time.
- Yes. Today's been absolutely precious.
I’m glad because I'm not sure
how you'll take the news
I'm about to share with you.
To be honest, I’ve already shared this
with the national press.
I imagine they’ll call you soon to check
the verity of the truce,
and I was hoping you’d confirm it.
And why would I do that?
Because if you don’t do that,
I’ll let them know
you faked Lisbon’s execution,
and that she’s being held illegally,
and you refuse to bring her
before a judge.
I don't think a judge will mind.
I also have recordings
of the supposed execution.
That son of a bitch.
I could tell them how you're negotiating
with her to arrest
or not arrest her daughter and mother
in Southeast Asia.
But to be honest, just between you and I,
you're too late for that move.
You'd better tell the three CIA agents
at the police headquarters in Mindanao
and the Spanish consul,
Mr. Leopoldo Gis Bornay,
arriving in Manila
to coordinate the operation... [chuckles]
...save that tax money for something
more productive,
and maybe you'll save yourselves
from looking like fools.
You love hearing yourself talk, don't you?
You sound like a radio host.
Get to the point.
What is it you want?
I need to feel certain about the truce.
I have one person fighting
between life and death.
And I don't trust your word anymore.
Confirm it to the press.
And so you can demonstrate your good will
and raise the morale and spirits
of those inside, including the hostages,
I’d like to request one last little thing.
[apple crunches]
[epic music playing]
[Tokyo] News of the truce
was all over the country in minutes.
It made for great headlines.
But the photos were even better.
The Police delivered eight paellas,
fourteen loaves of bread
and eight cases of wine to the door.
It looked like we were throwing a party.
Fuck, this smells good, man.
But inside the bank,
it felt like a prelude to a funeral.
What you can't see is usually more
important than what's in front of you,
and Gandía, who was about to fuck up
our lives, was invisible.
Stockholm and Rio searched the first floor
and there’s no sign of Gandía,
so listen carefully.
My blind spots are the basements.
Helsinki takes the east one,
and you go west.
[tense music playing]
[Professor] Tokyo.
I've just lost the cameras
inside of the bank.
All of them.
You're on your own.
[Tokyo] Things we can’t see
affect our lives much more than we think.
[Nairobi] Hello, nurse.
[Bogotásighs] Okay.
Let’s give it a little look.
[Nairobi groans]
And to think I would never
have even considered trusting you.
- [Nairobi groans]
- Why?
'Cause you're from that boy band
with Palermo and Berlin.
And 'cause you act
like a typical macho asshole.
[all laugh]
A big macho, but a good guy.
Strong like a castle.
- [Bogotálaughs]
- The truth is, he's sensitive.
I’m gonna give you an injection,
Nairobi, sweetheart.
Another one?
- You don’t give her a break.
- They're antibiotics.
There’s still risk of infection.
[chuckles] You’re amazing, Paquita.
I was the one
that asked for the injections.
Well, if the orders
come from the patient...
[both chuckle]
Remember when I said...
that I wouldn't touch you
with a ten-foot pole?
Uh-huh.
Well, I’ve been thinking.
So hold on. That was a very clear
declaration of your intentions.
Wasn’t it, Paquita?
When you...
said that pole thing,
I was already yours.
See, now I can absolutely picture you
walking...
dressed in all-white,
coming from over there,
- saying, "I do! I do!"
- Okay, okay, okay.
- The party, the drinks...
- Okay, hold on.
Calm down.
Don't get too excited because...
you and me,
I'm not just gonna be another wife.
[Tokyo] The things we can't see
are the things we obsess over the most.
He's not here.
For instance,
when you begin to doubt someone,
it's very difficult to stop.
Rio.
Why don't you have any scars
from the torture?
And you don't look like
you lost any weight.
How did he get away, Gandía?
Why are you asking me this?
Because you lied.
Because you didn’t tell us
everything about the torture,
and the Professor told you to be precise.
Why did you only tell me?
I need to know why.
Wanna know why?
Why me?
Because there's so much horrible shit
in my head that I can't sleep.
Because I didn’t want to remember it
or have any of you pity me.
Because I didn’t want to describe
how I was crying so desperately
in that coffin
that the only thing I wanted...
was to be in my bedroom
and hug my mom,
who I thought wouldn’t see a single piece
of me again in her life
because she wouldn’t even have
a body to bury.
- Rio...
- I cried so muchthat I was having spasms
and I hit my head against the the coffin.
Sand fell in my eyes,
but I kept crying.
Enough! Enough!
Is that it?
Is that what you wanted me to tell you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[Stockholm] It's okay.
Calm down. Calm down.
[Rio] It doesn’t matter.
Yes, it does.
I'm sorry. I’m terrified.
- I don’t know what I’m saying.
- Ssh.
I’m gonna make you trust me.
Rio...
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to kill Gandía.
[Tokyo] We search for what we can’t see,
and often we forget
that even though something's invisible,
it can still see you,
and that's when you're in trouble.
[Palermo] Now we're talking, baby!
Very good, baby.
Look how happy everyone is now, huh?
Look at all their precious faces.
Why would anyone else
start a mutiny now, baby? How marvelous!
I can feel the magic in the air, created
with a simple paella and some tasty beer.
A round of applause for the kidnappers!
Stop fucking around,
and shut your fucking mouth, now.
You need to let me go.
I smashed his head in with a stick.
If you leave me tied up here like a lamb,
you're murdering me yourself,
you son of a bitch. Let me go, please.
Why would he kill you now
if he didn’t when he escaped?
Nothing to worry about.
The others are gonna find him.
Oh, great. They're looking for him.
Good to know.
That's great.
It's also really good to know
that they left you here
to be in charge of the babysitting.
[Palermo] Hmm...
What an excellent decision, no?
Who made that one?
They sent Rio.
They sent the Mozart of computers
to go after an assassin, a professional,
the most dangerous one in Spain.
Ah, brilliant.
A spoiled, traumatized kid
who couldn't even pull a trigger.
Holding hands with your ex-wife,
walking around crying
in the Bank of Spain.
Quite beautiful.
He'll slaughter them one by one.
Why don't you fucking understand
that the one in charge is Tokyo?
It’s not about operating on Nairobi.
It’s about survival, brother.
Come here.
- Come here.
- [Denver] What is it?
What the fuck do you want?
[sighs]
Look...
I know you have a lot of love for Tokyo.
I know you went through a lot together.
But do you really think
she's the leader we need right now?
With your hand to your heart...
do you really trust Tokyo?
You have to let me go, my brother.
You know it's the right thing to do.
You have to take me upstairs.
You have to let me go.
Come on. Hey.
Shut the fuck up!
Matías, you're in charge.
So close!
[Denver] Rio!
Rio!
Where are you going?
I’m gonna go kill
that fucking son of a bitch.
Stop!
I’m sorry about earlier.
This whole thing's a fucking mess.
I want you to know that I'm absolutely
sure that you’re with us.
And I know you'd never betray us.
- Now let's go get that son of a bitch.
- Let's go.
[dramatic music playing]
[mysterious music playing]
- [beeps]
- [door opens]
[door closes]
- National Police. How can I assist you?
- This is César Gandía,
chief of security
for the governor of the Bank of Spain.
I’m calling from a secure line
belonging to the Ministry of the Interior.
Can you confirm you see it?
[woman]
Yes, it's a line from the Bank of Spain.
Exactly. Connect me to the operational
command center on the outside of the bank.
Absolute priority.
[phone ringing]
- Yes?
- [Gandía] This is a top priority call.
- I'm César Gandía.
- Who?
The chief of security for the governor.
- Connect me to Colonel Tamayo of the CNI.
- Yeah. Of course. Colonel!
It’s the chief of security
for the governor.
- All right. Clear the room.
- [Antoñanzas] Everyone clear the room.
This is Colonel Tamayo.
Colonel, I've managed to escape.
This is Gandía.
Where are you calling from?
From the panic room.
I can monitor all their movements
with the internal
security and surveillance system.
I’ve pulled out the exterior connections
so those bastards
can’t see you from the inside.
Awaiting your instructions.
For the moment, remain inactive.
Right now, we're in the middle of a truce.
What truce, Colonel?
How long is this truce?
There’s more than 24 hours left.
We can’t break it.
It’s been published everywhere.
Colonel, in 24 hours,
these bastards will be in Singapore.
Launch a coordinated attack with me.
Together, we can cover
both of their flanks.
In ten minutes, it'll all be over.
My hands are tied, Gandía.
The President doesn’t want
any more battles in the center of Madrid.
Sir, I have automatic weapons,
grenades, everything.
I’m not sitting still
waiting for them to escape.
I didn't sign the truce.
Do you understand me?
Officially, I can only order you
to wait and remain inactive.
Even though that’s not
what I’d like you to do.
And what does that mean?
That everything you do
will just be considered self-defense.
There won't be any legal problems.
If you eliminate them all,
you'll be a hero to me,
to our investigators
and the government of this country.
Understood, Colonel.
Good luck.
[Tokyo] The most important moments
are the ones that make you realize
there's no turning back.
You’ve crossed a line,
and you're stuck on the other side now.
And whether you like it or not,
everything is about to change,
so you hold on to the present,
as if you could stop the disaster
from coming.
[Sierra] How are we doing? [sighs]
I guess I won't surprise you,
but we got to Mindanao,
and your mother and daughter
weren't there anymore. Ta-da!
I’d congratulate you,
but you know what?
I’m not going to.
Because the thing is, little Rio,
before he went into the bank,
gave me the names
of all your transporters.
And he hasn't told the Professor.
I was listening, you know?
How long do you think it'll take until
he gives me your mother and your daughter?
[cell phone ringing]
- [Antoñanzas] Professor.
- Yes, Antoñanzas?
I don’t know how to tell you this,
and I know I shouldn’t, but...
But what?
[tense music playing]
People are gonna die in there,
on Tamayo’s ordersin cold blood.
- It's a crime.
- What’s going on, Benito?
Gandía, the chief of security
for the bank, called the tent.
He’s in a panic room
full of military hardware.
Where is the panic room?
I don't know, but it has cameras,
and he can see everything.
Tokyo.
- Tokyo.
- Professor.
Listen to me.
Gandía is armed. He has a panic room.
- What?
- He has a panic room,
so he’s watching you
and knows where you are.
You have to get everyone together.
Tokyo?
[closing theme music playing]