("Singer Jeong Se Yeon Suspected of Bullying")
("Multiple Victims Accuses Se Yeon of Bullying")
(A number of witnesses are posting evidence of Se Yeon's bullying.)
(Lee Soo Ho)
The phone is turned off...
Do you have anything to say to your victims?
Are the claims true?
Please say a few words to your disappointed fans.
What do you have to say for yourself?
- Do you have any words? - Over here!
Where are you going?
To Soo Ho.
What?
He'll believe in me. His trust will be enough...
to get through to his dad.
- Then, let me go with you. - Please say a few words
to your victims!
- Mr. Jeong! - Please say something to your fans.
(The late Jeong Se Yeon)
Se Yeon...
(Episode 4)
I'm sorry.
Soo Ho.
You must be happy even after killing your friend.
Is it because of the helmet?
No.
- I came to eat with you. - Seriously?
Seo Jun!
Are you serious?
Hit me.
Go ahead and hit me.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Back away from each other!
Seo Jun, what's the matter with you?
You wanted to be an idol star, but did you quit...
and decide to be a gangster instead?
How dare you start a fistfight at school?
Right, sir? I was totally shocked myself.
I saw them fighting each other,
and I almost threw up what I was eating.
- Get lost! - Yes, sir.
Goodbye.
What if this causes to gather a school violence committee?
Do you want to get expelled?
I started the fight, sir.
My goodness, Soo Ho.
Why are you defending him?
My gosh, you took a leave of absence because of your mother's illness,
and this is what you do?
Your mother must be extremely upset because of how you behave.
I can already guess why your mother got sick.
Sir, I think that's enough.
My goodness. Soo Ho already agreed to forgive him.
So let's wrap it up.
There's no need to gather a school violence committee.
Don't you think so?
You punk!
Soo Ho, you have a math competition in two days.
So you should take good care of your condition.
You can go back to your classroom.
You punk!
What's with that look? How dare you glare like that!
- You little... - Sir, that's enough.
Hurry up and apologize!
Are you okay?
Oh, you got hurt.
You should've broken an arm or something.
Then I would've won the math competition.
Get lost if you're going to talk nonsense.
Or you should've just beat him to a pulp.
You should've taught him a lesson so he'd never bother you again.
Why did you even bother to learn Jiu-Jitsu?
You may be tall,
but you're weak on the inside just like in elementary school.
What happened between you and Seo Jun?
Is this about Jeong Se Yeon?
Hey. Apply this.
I heard the two guys fought because of her.
Are they in a love triangle? Unbelievable.
What's going on?
I heard you got asked out by both Soo Ho and Seo Jun.
Which one are you going to choose?
Come on. Tell us.
What are you talking about?
Let's hear the drum roll.
Is it going to be Soo Ho or Seo Jun?
Which person are you going to choose?
- Who will it be? - Tell us.
Just go vote for Eighteen on "M Countdown".
It's not what you think. Why would they like me?
Maybe they just fought because they hate each other.
- No way. - No.
But here's the question. Why did Mr. Han...
sit next to Ms. Lim?
- That's what I want to know. - Cut it out.
Gosh, that's enough. Let's just believe what she says.
Go back to your classes.
- My gosh. - Why?
Just get out of here.
- Get out. - My gosh.
You're going through this because you're pretty.
If an average-looking girl was sitting there,
no one would've started such a rumor.
It must be exhausting.
I can't believe this is happening.
When it comes to stuff like this,
it might've been better when no one even cared about me.
- It's Soo Ho. - Soo Ho is here.
- What's going on? - What happened?
Soo Ho.
Can we talk for a moment?
Who do you think you are to mess with Seo Jun?
You audacive punk.
- "Audacious". - It's audacious.
Is that the right word?
Whatever.
What will you do if Seo Jun gets disciplined because of you?
You held him by his collar first, so it was self-offense.
- "Self-defense". - Yes, it's self-defense.
Is that what it is?
Are you pretending to be gangsters?
Where do you think you're going?
You're crossing the line.
- He's crossing the line. - Don't stop him.
- What should we do? - Do you work out?
- My gosh, will you step in already? - Okay, you got it.
Gosh...
My gosh, you little...
That's enough.
It's like you guys are here to catch a pig.
You darn punks!
Are you fighting again?
- Hello, sir. - It's not what you think.
- Be quiet! - Why did he have to overreact?
You guys are always in a group looking for trouble.
- We were just working out. - Cut the nonsense!
I can tell you never work out!
Hey. My gosh.
Let's see what you've got.
Soo Ho, I let you off the hook because I didn't want to kill you.
- Seriously. - I don't think he can hear you.
I'll go tell him.
- Soo Ho! - Man Sik... Man Sik.
I... I have a muscle cramp.
- A muscle cramp? - I have a muscle cramp.
- Let's go! - Call 911.
- Are you okay? - The back of my neck hurts.
Hello?
Seo Jun.
What do you want from me?
What do I want?
Stay out of my sight.
If you don't want to see me, don't come near me.
I have no reason to avoid you.
You brazen punk.
But then again, that's who you really are.
That day,
when Se Yeon came to see me...
What?
Isn't it too late to give me an excuse?
Do you know...
what that poor guy said to me that day?
He said...
you'd believe in him.
Without even knowing that you're a cold-hearted and selfish jerk,
he counted on you and ran over to see you.
So don't ever...
say his name again.
Bring Se Yeon back.
Bring him back!
Bring Se Yeon back, you jerk!
(Prince Comics)
(Lim Ju Kyung's spot. Sit without permission, and get a hairy butt!)
Are you crying?
("The Cursed Mask")
Is it because the story is scary?
It's okay. Don't cry.
It isn't scary at all.
Look, I'm a squirrel. A squirrel.
Isn't that funny?
Meow. I'm a cat.
You're smiling. I'm a squirrel.
I'm a squirrel.
Did you know? If you cry then laugh,
you'll get a hairy butt!
I'm a squirrel. A squirrel.
A squirrel.
Soo Ho.
I was walking by and saw you inside.
Here. Drink it.
I saw Seo Jun leave earlier. Did you clean all by yourself?
Why did you let him leave?
Why were you fighting like little kids?
Never mind. I shouldn't talk.
I just fought with my brother not long ago.
I fight at least once a day myself.
When my brother and I fight,
our mom makes us do something to make up.
"I love you."
We have to say that...
and clip each other's toenails...
- like this. - Toenails?
If you clip each other's toenails, it gets all tickly.
So you naturally make up.
Did you just laugh?
I've never seen you laugh.
No, I didn't.
I don't know what happened,
but if you need someone to talk to later on, just let me know.
You can vent to me.
There's nothing I can't do for the Divine Soo Ho.
What? The Divine Soo Ho?
The kids said your nickname was the Divine Soo Ho.
Didn't you know, Divine Soo Ho?
I'm not divine.
Don't call me that.
Why not? You are the Divine Soo Ho to me too.
The merciful divinity that keeps my no-makeup face secret.
Are you that worried?
About what?
Your no-makeup face.
Don't all girls look different with makeup on?
Don't say that to other people.
I'm extreme. It's like night and day.
I can't really tell.
Are you blind? How could you not tell?
I studied and practiced so much to create that look.
I'm transforming this face.
Did you hurt your lip?
That must hurt.
Don't read adult comics.
You should go home. Look at the time. Go. Get going.
- It's not even 8pm. - So go home and study.
A student shouldn't be at a comic book shop.
You get bad grades, don't you? What place are you in?
I do not!
Who's after Sejong the Great? Three seconds.
- 1, 2, 3. - Gojong...
What happened to the 400 years? You really must have bad grades.
Go home. Go.
- Wait... - Go home and study.
She says whatever she feels like.
Oh my gosh.
That's so dangerous.
Ju Kyung.
Me? What?
Are you going out with Soo Ho?
I am not.
- Are you really not? - Definitely not.
Looking at you, I don't think you are either.
What? What did he see?
- Oh my gosh. - Look.
- Is her nose bleeding? - It's so red.
Darn it.
Hey, hey, hey, Lee Soo Ho
Hey ho, hey ho, yahoo
Hey.
He'll never play along no matter how much My Hoonie tries.
This classroom looks like my pimples.
I don't know when they'll pop.
I said to buy me food. What's taking him so long?
Is he shy?
I'll give him one more day.
The function of x is seven.
So what's the value when x is six?
Naturally, it's seven.
Because the value of the function is always seven.
Okay, who wants to solve the next problem?
I'm the fool for asking.
How about our math geniuses, the Soo-Soo couple?
Come out. Problems 1 and 2.
And...
our new girl. Lim Ju Kyung. Try problem three.
No. No way.
Hey. Soo Ho.
Help me.
At least the rule.
Divine Soo Ho.
I knew it.
You'll win the math competition this year too.
The principal has high hopes for you.
You have to do well.
You need to feel the pressure, okay?
It changes the mood of the school board.
Okay?
This is the limiting value of my despair.
Ju Kyung?
The problems are different. What's the point in looking?
Right?
Seo Jun must know the answer.
Seo Jun, come out and solve it for her.
That won't work on me. Come on out.
Yes.
Why you...
Hurry up.
I guess I can't go to college by flunking math.
Just get good scores on other subjects.
I'll never make it into college.
Why don't you join our math academy?
Both Doo Jin and Soo Ho take classes there.
- Should I? - Yes.
My mom did tell me to find a math class to take.
Then join us. You can join our study session too.
I couldn't be more grateful.
Soo Ho, want to join a study?
We have room for one more.
No.
My mom will only approve if you study with us.
Then tell her I am.
You want me to lie to her?
Just join us instead.
He's always playing hard to get.
It's what I expected.
It'll be just us three and my Hoonie.
Got it. We'll begin the sessions once Ju Kyung joins our math class.
Skip classes to go on dates with Tae Hoon...
- and you're out. - Got it.
By the way, I gave your number to the guy I'm setting you up with.
- Already? - Yes.
He'll call you soon. Anyway, look.
Isn't he handsome?
It's about having a good personality.
Meet him a few times before you date him.
But I'm not ready for this yet.
Maybe I should meet him to be free of all these rumors?
That's right. Nice thinking.
He's already head over heels for you.
What...
Why are you...
The comic book store.
You read a lot of them, you know.
How you're top of the class is a mystery.
Here. Good luck on your exam tomorrow.
I don't have a sweet tooth.
I see.
I heard that you're competing with mathletes from all over the country.
What are the questions like? The ones from our mock CSAT tests?
Do you get quizzed on unions and intersections of sets?
I bet that's all the math you know.
As if. That's what we learn in freshman year.
What's the formula for the equation of a circle?
Math is my weakest subject.
Which king ruled after King Sejong?
Ambushing me by changing the subject...
makes me forget what I know.
You don't know, do you?
(Ji Woo Hyeon)
The blind date guy texted me.
Hi, I'm Ji Woo Hyeon.
When should we meet?
Will you go on a blind date when you barely study?
Life experience can also teach you something.
(Hi, I'm Lim Ju Kyung.)
Besides, who knows?
I may get to receive private lessons...
from my boyfriend who attends Hanguk University.
Getting a boyfriend could lead to better grades.
How about tomorrow? When are you free?
Tomorrow?
People go on blind dates in the evening, right?
No, during the day when it's bright outside.
Oh, I see.
I prefer midday.
- You seem thrilled. - As if.
This is because you and Seo Jun chose to argue in my face.
It led to weird rumors.
Why did you agree to the date when you don't want to?
It's not that I don't want to. I'm just nervous.
You see, it'll be my first time...
being alone with a guy outside of school.
What about me then?
Seriously? How could you grab my face...
like it's some pumpkin rolling down an alley?
I have eyes, a nose, and a mouth.
Hey. It's the movie I wanted to see.
I thought you were off to the comic book store.
What's with him?
Good luck on your exam tomorrow.
(VIP Ward)
- Mom! - Seo Jun?
Did you meet with the doctor?
Why did you come here instead of going home after school?
Don't tell me you rode your motorcycle here.
I told you I was done with it.
Ms. Mi Hyang, why are you being a worry-wart?
What did the doctor say?
The transplant is taking well...
and my numbers are all good.
I was told not to skip my medicine.
That's great! We should grab something nice to eat...
- and call Go Woon out. - Maybe next time.
I have someplace to be today.
Where?
Must you make a mess in here like this?
These are the candles I made at the culture center.
Hand them out to your regulars.
I'll try selling them officially if they respond well to them.
Can you please not do anything officially?
But I love the calming scents.
I only receive aroma oil massages, you know.
What's the scent, Mr. Lim?
The scent is from flowers of ylang ylang trees.
It's especially good at...
lowering blood pressure and balancing your hormones.
- Ylang ylang... - Scoot off, will you?
Sure, I'll hurry off.
Gosh, how handsome.
Just gazing at him will get you your fill.
- Why keep nagging him though? - If it weren't for his looks,
I would've dumped him years ago.
Unbelievable.
You're back as Ju Kyung again.
I honestly couldn't tell with all the makeup.
That's some magical power you have.
It's called the Ju Kyung Magic.
I washed my face, so give me a facial.
I already told you I can't. Besides, I'm super busy.
Go home and study.
But it won't take long.
Hyun Sook!
My gosh. Mi Hyang, is that you?
What on earth is he doing here?
But I have no makeup on.
This is my son.
Hello, ma'am.
My gosh. Goodness gracious.
How on earth can one be so handsome?
There's my second daughter...
Are you out of your mind? What are you doing?
Get up, Ju Kyung!
Lim Ju Kyung?
You look way better now that you're not on dialysis.
Surgery went well thanks to my doctor.
I got lucky.
I'm happy for you.
Have you been well, Hyun Sook?
Of course., I have.
Unbelievable.
Mom, I'm going home.
Will you frighten the neighbors at this hour?
Wash your face first.
Then I have to put on my makeup at this late hour.
Being that pretty must make you popular at school.
You must be close to Seo Jun since you're classmates.
No, we're not.
They can be starting today then.
You both clearly have everything going for you.
Since we said hello, come by the house tomorrow.
I'll cook you a meal.
But I'm studying with friends tomorrow.
She's going on a blind date.
A blind date at your age?
Now I get why you desperately wanted a facial.
Come on. You only get to be young once.
I'd love my Seo Jun to have a girlfriend,
but all he loves to do is riding his motorcycle.
Although, he quit recently.
He rides it all the time.
- He sped... - Hey!
He sped past me...
and almost hit me too.
Are you kidding me? You promised.
How can I not ride what I own? Riding the bus is a waste of money.
So much for the tough-guy act.
He's as soft as my brother in front of his mother.
You leave me with no choice.
Ju Kyung, could you do me a favor...
and stop him from riding his motorcycle?
Let me know immediately if you ever spot him on it.
Mom, there's no need to...
So you'll break our promise?
Could you do that for me?
Of course. I won't let you down.
I guess I can't hang around here with no makeup on anymore.
I almost got caught.
Hey, you.
You'd better not say anything funny to my mom.
What... What do you mean? About your motorcycle?
- I already promised your mom... - And?
What do you mean "And"? What else is there?
- That you got beaten up by those... - What?
If that's not it...
What else could you have done wrong?
That you almost got disciplined for fighting with Soo Ho?
I will never tell her any of that.
I'm really good at keeping secrets.
He's a real troublemaker.
This is hilarious.
When you go on blind dates,
you're not able to look at a mirror in front of your date that often.
"I have a blind date today."
"So let's try wearing a different color."
"I should try a different kind of makeup."
I'm sure some of you think that way.
Hey, you. No. Don't use that color.
Stop moving right now.
Even if it's a special day, you shouldn't wear...
This isn't the eye shadow that I normally wear.
Then your makeup will look really awkward,
and it'll turn out bad.
Just stick to the stuff that you normally use.
Instead, emphasize the details,
and do your best to look lovely.
"I've heard a lot about you, Woo Hyeon."
"Woo Hyeon"? Isn't that too friendly?
Or should I call him by his last name?
No, that's a bit weird. What should I call him?
[VIU Ver] tvN E04 'True Beauty'
"Ju Kyung Going On Blind Date"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
Synced with Subcake Android
They all look similar.
Isn't this the outfit that Mom bought for her recently?
Who are you, you punk?
She didn't take off the tag.
(Math test hours, From 15:00 to 16:30)
Who is he? He's really handsome.
- My gosh, who is he? - He's so good-looking.
Soo Ho.
- Did you study a lot? - Who is that girl?
What's there to study?
You're so annoying.
You act like you didn't study, but I bet you'll ace the test.
Aren't you sick of saying that every time we take a test?
Your grades are the second most popular subject...
after mine among my family members.
I take my test here. Good luck.
Thanks. You too.
Hey.
Don't do better than me. Just get a moderate score.
I'm sitting by the window.
Hello.
It's nice to meet you. Take a seat.
Okay.
You look prettier than your photos. I almost didn't recognize you.
Gosh, that can't be.
I'm serious.
- Can I speak to you comfortably? - Sure. Go ahead.
What do you want to drink? The bubble tea is delicious here.
Yes. I like it.
You just made my heart flutter. Did you just say you like me?
I meant I like bubble tea.
It was a joke.
Welcome.
- 1 popcorn and 2 colas, please. - Okay.
I'll buy this. You paid for the movie tickets.
Today's our first date, so I'll pay for everything.
That way, I'll get to see you next time.
"Next time"? Does that mean he wants to meet again?
Here's your popcorn.
How quick.
Are there no customers?
That darn jerk.
- What's going on? - What is he doing?
Hey, I can't see anything.
Who are you?
Do you know him?
No, how would I know him?
I'm sorry.
Gosh, I shouldn't be here right now.
Ha Ru!
Dan Ho! Dan Ho!
What are you doing?
Go away.
I'd walk you home if I could, but I have a school gathering.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. You should go.
Thank you.
Will we able to meet again?
What?
Sure.
Was I too straightforward?
I'll contact you later.
Have a safe trip home.
Okay.
Bye.
Why am I being a loser?
What's the matter with me?
Hey, baby. Where are you?
I'm already here.
Ta-da.
- Hey, honey. - Baby, when did you get here?
Did I keep you waiting?
I missed you so much, so I came early.
Let's go.
How was it? How did he look? What did you guys eat?
What's his personality like? Are you going to meet him again?
You're asking me so many questions. He did ask if we could meet again.
It looks like you might hit it off.
(How was it? How did he look? What did you guys eat?)
Did you get home? I miss you already.
He just texted me. What do I say? How should I reply?
Hey, calm down. Don't reply right away.
Wait until you text him back.
I can't do that. He'll get upset if he thinks I'm ignoring him.
Don't even look at your cell phone. It's time to play hard to get.
"Playing hard to get"?
Doesn't it hurt? Are you sure it feels nice?
Yes.
- Does it feel good? - Yes, it does.
So you won't contact me, is that it?
Should I just go to the school?
I'm home.
That looks good.
Where did you go dressed up so pretty?
That dress.
I...
I haven't seen it before.
It's pretty.
Thanks.
You went on a blind date, didn't you?
You're going out already?
A blind date?
Mom. Soo Ah says...
you can push off studying, but you don't push off romance.
Give me a break.
If you'd study and get into college, I'd set you up...
with a boy like Seo Jun.
- Seo Jun? - He's a total delinquent.
A delinquent? Ju Kyung, no. Not a delinquent.
What do you mean? He's such a kind boy.
Mi Hyang was hospitalized for months after her kidney transplant,
and he took care of her the entire time.
He worked several jobs to pay for his tuition, his spending money,
and his mom's hospital bills.
Really?
He'd be perfect if he didn't ride a motorcycle.
Mi Hyang is very nervous about that.
Her husband died in a car accident.
Don't let Seo Jun know that you know.
- Really? - Yes.
If he's such a good son, why won't he listen to her?
- Hello? - Congratulations.
- Darn it. - You've been selected...
That's not the call I want.
You morons! Do you want to lose your lives as collateral?
I'm so mad.
Give me that. Darn it.
I keep losing more and more.
Mona Lisa,
I feel your pain.
Oh my. It's hot.
Gosh!
When sparks fly up again,
we'll go steady.
No.
Anyway, she told me to buy her food.
That's refreshing.
Did something good happen to you?
Did someone ask you out?
Well. Actually...
I went on a blind date.
I think it went well.
Nice. You're all grown up. You're even going on blind dates.
My makeup skills turned my life around.
- Anyway. - Yes?
How long do you have to wait before replying to play hard to get?
Soo Ah told me to wait for a long while.
It has been 30 minutes.
I don't play hard to get. I just go forward.
Don't make him wait. Reply right away.
- Right? - Right.
I take it back that I miss you.
Actually, I have a girlfriend.
I'm a piece of garbage. I wanted to cheat with you.
I apologize.
What's this?
You were rejected.
Who rejects a girl like that?
Rejected?
- I was rejected? - I mean,
if he doesn't like you, he should say it wasn't meant to be.
That's all.
What garbage.
I see.
I was rejected.
No wonder.
How could I get a guy with this face?
Blind dates rarely work out.
Forget him.
Nice.
"Hello. You told me to buy you food,"
"but I'd be taking your precious time,"
"so it would be rude of me. I'll reimburse you instead."
"Send me your account number"?
What? What account number?
You were rejected.
Rejected?
He rejected me?
No guy has ever done that to me.
You can get rejected with a face like that?
Then how much prettier do I have to get?
Seriously.
Let me take a dump, will you?
Get out!
How do I tell Soo Ah that I was rejected?
Caught you red-handed.
What are you doing?
Your mom said to stop riding your motorcycle.
I'm seriously dumbfounded.
You shouldn't ride it if your mom tells you not to.
Are you my mom's Mafia?
Mafia?
- You mean "spy". - Same difference.
They're both bad guys.
You're not the only one who has one.
I have one too.
Delete it while I'm being nice.
Hey. Hey, Seo Jun! Seo Jun!
- What? Get away from me. - Delete it. Delete it now!
I wasted so much energy.
You were about to put your face stamp on my uniform again.
Sorry.
Don't let your eyes wander.
What?
I mean, don't get distracted.
- You should study instead... - There you go again.
I memorized it all.
Taejo, Jeongjong, Taejong, Sejong, Munjong, Danjong, Sejo
Yejong, Seongjong, Yeonsangun, Jungjong, Injong, Myeongjong, Seonjo
- Honey. - Yes?
Aren't you going to protect my face?
Don't get too close when we take selfies.
It's obvious when I edit it.
I feel like I'm going out with two girls.
The Soo Ah in front of me and the Soo Ah on Stargram.
Then break up with the one in front of you, and date via DM.
No.
How can I break up with someone this cute?
Ju Kyung with a fling.
A fling? It's not a fling.
I thought you were meeting again.
Didn't you hit it off?
Well... I heard from him after I chatted with you.
And...
he's kind of weird.
Why? What did he say? Let me see.
Here.
"I take it back that I miss you."
"Actually, I have a girlfriend."
"I'm a piece of garbage. I wanted to cheat with you."
"I apologize."
- What a punk. - Were you rejected?
How do you get rejected so quickly?
- How does that happen? - It's too quick.
Love isn't that easy.
So funny.
That high school girl? I'm not sure.
She has a nice body, but her face is okay.
But she's so naive.
She'll be really easy.
I'll play with her for a bit.
Who are you?
Hey!
Take that back right now.
I take it back. I take back everything I said.
I take it back. Satisfied? Okay, then...
(Sung Nyung)
(Third Auntie: Home yet? Miss you.)
What's your problem?
Hey! Ouch! Wait!
That hurts. I have a bad shoulder.
You scumbag.
Ta-da.
Nice.
What is he doing? Is he showing them my picture?
- What is that? - Oh my gosh.
- Really? - No, no.
For real?
What...
- Hold it right. - Hey!
Hey.
Darn it.
Ju Kyung!
Hey! Ju Kyung!
Give it back when I'm being nice. Give it back.
I said, give it back!
- Hand it over. - Hand over what?
I saw you take it.
- What are you doing? - I could ask you the same thing.
Stop!
You're about to fight in front of me again, right?
Please don't.
Here's your key.
Now get away from each other. You go that way and you go that way.
And I'll go this way!
Our tutor makes it easy to understand.
Will my days as a loser in math finally be over?
You can do it, you know.
So don't give up. We both shouldn't.
- Got it. - So Soo Jin,
can my friend from Shinhwa High for Boys join?
Shinhwa High for Boys? Who is this so-called friend?
A trillion question marks are dancing in my brain right now.
Why let a stranger join us?
Isn't it obvious? For Ju Kyung to flirt with.
Dating is a must
Marriage is optional, amor fati
What on earth? I thought you weren't interested.
I never said I wouldn't join though.
- What? - My gosh.
The two smartest kids in our class are in our study group.
We're like the Avengers.
How can you not know the basics?
Well, that's how I am.
As N tends to infinity, it ends up being N over N squared.
That's 1 over N, so the limit value is 0.
Meanwhile, if it's N squared over N, the value will be N...
which will go to infinity.
- What is it? - How can you fit all this...
in the small head of yours?
How smart are you? Do you have an IQ of over 150?
Why can't you focus even for a few minutes?
I bet you have a two digit IQ. FYI, a dolphin's IQ is 80.
- Are dolphins that smart? - Work hard...
if you want to be smarter.
Focus.
So what will the answer be?
Lucky her.
When did you and Soo Ho get so close?
He's not the type to help others study.
Is this what you call being close?
- From his standard. - Well, you see...
Actually, I don't know why.
Maybe it's because I'm pretty awful at math.
Trying to show off, is he?
Guys, to celebrate our first study session...
- Let's go karaokeing. - I'm in.
You've been waiting for this, haven't you?
Come on, let's go!
You're not going, are you?
A few minutes won't hurt.
- Jjin, jjin, jjin, jjin, it's real - Jjin, jjin, jjin, jjin, it's real
- It's the real deal - It's the real deal
- The real deal is here - The real deal is here
- Jjin, jjin, jjin, jjin, it's real - Jjin, jjin, jjin, jjin, it's real
- It's the real deal - It's the real deal
- We'll love with passion - We'll love with passion
- Cheer up, baby, cheer up, baby - Cheer up, baby, cheer up, baby
Cheer up!
A girl shouldn't give out her heart so easily
You'll end up liking me more
No, I'm all right, so don't feel burdened
I don't have a boyfriend anyway
But why haven't you said anything yet?
- When I see you - When I see you
- Every time I see you - Every time I see you
- Like a cold dish of naengmyeon - Like a cold dish of naengmyeon
- The noodles are icy - The noodles are icy
- Still, I love you - Still, I love you
- Nice! - Hey, yo!
- Sweet young lady - Hey, you, hey
- You - Hey, fire!
My friend
At times, I forget
I meet with friends like I'm not fazed
Gosh, he's good.
He could be a singer.
Too much
- The song sounds familiar though. - The longing feeling
Where have I heard it before?
How do you do?
How have you been?
It doesn't seem
Like I'm all right
Being away for so long brought me back to new faces.
- You're so handsome. - I'm in awe!
We should all grab dinner sometime so that I can learn their faces.
Let's have a seat then.
- Shall we begin the meeting? - Sure.
In memory of Jeong Se Yeon...
on the first anniversary of his death,
we propose the release of an album.
Rather than promoting the comeback N-6IX...
without Se Yeon,
we believe it'll be better to comfort his fans and teammates...
with a night to remember him.
These are the song we found in the file Se Yeon left behind.
Se Yeon wrote the lyrics...
and the song was written by someone named Leo.
I like the song.
Leo, is it?
The songwriter's identity is still a mystery,
so we've been trying to track him down.
Isn't that Seo Jun's motorcycle?
Is he somewhere nearby?
I was right.
I see he rode it again.
This darn motorcycle.
Han Seo Jun, you jerk.
I'll mangle it up.
What do you think you're doing?
What? It's nothing.
What did you do to my motorcycle?
I didn't even touch it.
Darn.
Hey, come here for a second.
What? Why?
What is it?
I thought it'd be better to talk here.
- Must it be said in secret? - Yes.
Hold on. Seo Jun, is that you?
You of all people?
Surprise.
You piece of crap.
You...
Why did he of all people had to show up here?
Hold on a second.
Why did you bring a girl down a dark alley?
Get going.
What do I do?
- What... - Get him!
- Get him. - Stop!
Get back here!
Get back here.
- Stop right there. - Hey!
Get back here!
- After them. - Darn it.
- Stop! - Over here.
- Get them. - Where are they?
Seriously?
Where did they go?
- What the... - Where did they go?
Wait. He goes to Saebom High too.
They're gone. The coast is clear.
Hey, I told you to leave. Why did you drag me away?
What would those guys think?
What would they think?
Wouldn't they think it's weird if we ran away?
Are you dumb or what?
I saved you from trouble, and you call me dumb?
Hey! Do you know who comes after Sejong the Great?
- Gojong. - What happened to the 400 years?
- You're dumber than I am. - What?
Who are you? Why did you chase us?
Where are you going?
Are you Seo Jun's friend?
Or are you his minion?
- Get out of my way. - Come on.
I'll let you leave if you call him here.
- Why should I do that? - I'm sure he'll show up...
if his friend calls.
- Don't you think so? - He won't answer my call.
Then let's check.
Take his cell phone.
Let's see. Just a second.
It's here.
Did you just stop me?
Let go.
Gosh, seriously?
What are you doing?
- Get up. - Where do you think you're going?
Let go. Let go!
You little punk.
- Hey, hold him tight! - Hold him!
- You go. - My gosh.
- I'm sorry! - Are you kidding me?
You aim for the top, I'll aim for the bottom.
Get off me! Get off!
Let go!
Let go of me!
Hey, hold onto him!
Hold him tight!
Hold onto him! Stay still!
You must be out of your mind. Do you have a death wish?
What are you doing?
Darn it. Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Hey.
What do you want?
Can you lend me money?
No.
My friends left with my bag because I didn't show up.
My cell phone and wallet are all in my bag.
Good going.
I saved you, so just think of it as repaying me.
Can you please just lend me the bus fare?
Repay you? Are you joking?
No. You can walk home.
You cold-hearted jerk.
Hey.
Hop on before I change my mind.
Really?
Thank you.
How do I get on this thing?
Like this?
Hold on tight.
(Prince Comics)
Here. Thanks.
If you really thank me, delete the photo.
Ju Kyung.
I went through all that mess to make sure they don't meet.
Were you guys married in your past lives?
It's you again?
- Why did you give her a ride? - What about you?
Why were you waiting for her?
Okay, guys. Why don't we all go home?
It's late.
You go that way, and you go that way.
Let's go different ways.
Hey.
Hee Kyung.
What am I seeing?
Why am I seeing two beautiful men?
Am I dead?
Am I in paradise?
Hee Kyung.
Let's go!
I'll help you guys make a debut!
Hee Kyung.
This is crazy.
Will you please wake up?
I'll kill you if you puke.
Let's take her home.
Why do I need to go? Hey.
Why do I need to help?
My gosh, darn it.
Hee Kyung, you're dead once you wake up.
Let's go!
Shut her mouth. Just try shutting her mouth.
Come on!
Let's get going!
We're home. This is it.
Thank you so much.
I'll never forget this, guys.
No!
I'm so sorry.
I'll wash it nice and clean. No.
I'll just burn this and get you a new one.
I'm so sorry. Bye, guys.
Soo Ho.
Do you like Ju Kyung?
- What? - Don't you like her?
What about you?
Why do you keep hanging around her?
Do you like Ju Kyung?
I think I might.
(Unstoppable energy)
(Test ID: Lee Soo Ho)
What are you doing? Where are you going?
(Unstoppable energy)
Do you like Ju Kyung?
Here. Take it.
- What? - You told me to stop...
riding my motorcycle.
Did you hear that?
Starting from today, I'm only going to listen to you.
What was that? Did he just ask you out?
Does Seo Jun like Ju Kyung?
I can't believe this.
Seo Jun.
Don't go.
- Let me just... - Just don't go.
(We thank Kim Hye Yoon and Lee Jae Wook...)
(for their special appearance.)
(True Beauty)
Sit.
- You put on that mask... - Pork cutlet.
Now Lee Soo Ho and Han Seo Jun?
I'm going to punch your mouth.
What?
Look at that!
Don't run away because you're scared.
Hey.
It was all my fault.
But don't toy with Ju Kyung.
Oh no.