[country banjo music plays]
[engine spluttering]
♪ And it's one step forward, baby
Two steps back ♪
[continues on radio]
♪ Two steps forward, baby ♪
♪ Three steps back ♪
[wind howls]
Well?
Dead as our sales were last week.
Deader.
[chuckles] Great.
Just fucking great.
Huh! Yeah, shit happens.
But somebody'll come along
and give us a lift.
Nobody's gonna come down this cutoff.
Nobody, except idiots like us.
We never should have taken this road.
[sighs]
Radiator's done for.
Did you happen to check the water
back in Phoenix like I asked?
Yes, and it was fine.
Well, if it was fine in Phoenix,
then it wouldn't be dead now.
No, don't try and put this on me, old man.
You're all, "There's no stretch
of this land I haven't been to, son."
Yeah, you're a real American explorer.
Shouldn't you be putting that
in the radiator?
It's dead, son.
There's no coming back from dead.
Not even for a Plymouth.
Right.
So, what do we do?
[groans] We can rest the night here.
And just before dawn,
when the weather's cooler,
we start walking.
Walking?
All the way back to the last station?
Yep.
That's great. [sighs]
That's just... [shouting] fucking great!
♪ Down ♪
♪ Don't you lay your body down ♪
♪ Don't you lay your body ♪
♪ Down ♪
♪ Mm-hmm. ♪
[wind howling]
I'm sorry about earlier.
It wasn't your fault.
I just get bitter sometimes.
The days of the door-to-door salesman
are fadin' fast.
[chuckling] Come on.
You know what I think?
It's all in the attitude.
The right attitude can sell anything.
Well, you certainly got plenty of that.
Reminds me of the sea.
Never seen the ocean.
Have to take your word for it.
Did you know that millions of years ago,
this desert was a sea bottom?
All of this was water,
full of fantastical creatures.
The world's an old place.
And for a long time,
it was nothing but sea.
Nights like this, it gets me wonderin':
If the ghosts of people
can haunt a house,
well, why can't the ghosts of creatures
haunt where they once lived?
[laughs] I have no idea what the hell
you're talking about.
[yawns] I'm gonna sleep in the back seat.
You can take the front.
It must have been nice back then.
Just swimming around
without a care in the world.
[electrical buzz]
[radio static]
[whale singing]
What?
[gasps]
- [whispering] Wake up.
- What?
Shhhh. Look.
[younger man] Holy shit!
[laughs] Wow!
You ever seen anything like this?
Never.
[younger man laughs]
[younger man] It's...
It's beautiful.
It must be something like you said.
Ghosts of an older world.
Boo!
[laughs] Did you see that?
- Hey.
- Oh, my God! [laughs]
I can feel them!
[laughs]
This is so cool.
Hey, hold on a second, boy.
[laughs]
What are you doing?
[shouts] I'm going up there!
[shouts] Don't be crazy!
[younger man shouts] I wanna swim!
[laughs]
[chuckles]
Hey, come back down here!
What?
[older man shouts] Hey!
Look, behind you! Look!
Hey! Look!
Goddamn fool!
Look out!
Behind you!
Look!
[gasps]