[man] I had that dream about
your sister again last night.
Oh, it was me and her in the scrub
behind the mess hall. [grunts]
She's biting my neck. [snicker]
I swear to God, we are going at it
like fucking animals, bro.
[grunts repeatedly]
I don't even have a sister.
Then why do you get so mad
when I dream about fucking her?
- Hold up a sec.
- Hu-ah!
[sniffs]
[man via radio] Decker? Talk to me, bro.
[gunshot]
Contact!
[growls]
[man via radio] Decker,
you got eyes on the fucker?
- [gunshot]
- Argh!
[Decker panting]
Three four five degrees,
one five zero yards,
small structure, white side, level...
- [man via radio] You all right, Decker?
- Yeah.
Fucker almost shot my dick off.
[man] Hmm.
Well, if he could hit a target that tiny,
we should sign him up on our side.
[laughter]
You can't sit here.
I don't see any reserved signs.
I said, you can't sit here.
The corps turned to shit when they started
lettin' you animals wear the uniform.
Look, my buddy took a bullet
for you guys today so... back off.
Yeah, see, and I don't trust anything
that bleeds that much and then walks away.
- Unnatural is what you are.
- Unnatural?
I can stalk my prey by scent alone.
I can run for miles while you need
to ride in a stinking Humvee all day.
I can see clearly on a moonless night,
while you cling to your flashlight
as soon as the sun goes down.
You ask me,
there's not much natural in that.
You fuckin' dog soldiers.
[clears throat]
No disrespect, Sergeant...
but if you call us dog soldiers again...
I'll rip your arm off
and beat you to death with it.
You wanna try it?
[growls]
Come on.
Smells like dog shit in here.
[rock music plays]
You know what I think it is?
Jealousy.
Mm-hmm.
Those guys know that
if the brass cut us loose,
we'd have this shit cleaned up
in three weeks.
I think it's more complicated than that.
No, you're right.
They're fuckin' terrified of us, too.
[chuckles]
Claws and blood, baby.
They don't understand us
any more than they do this fucking war,
which is why we don't belong here.
Look, I don't like every asshole
that calls himself an American,
but it's still my fuckin' country.
You hear me, boy?
[mimics drill sergeant]
Do you hear me, Cadet?
Stand up straight!
We are here for duty, honor and country,
Momma and apple pie.
I'm just here to make sure
you don't get your dumb ass killed.
Your dumb ass.
I think you're both here
because dogs gotta hunt.
- Sir!
- At ease.
We're rotating squads at
the forward operating base.
Sobieski, you're with the outgoing squad.
Try not to piss off any of the regulars
while you're up there.
[scoffs] If they're smart,
they'll be trying hard not to piss me off.
- Is that right, tough guy?
- Uh-huh.
Now, remember, honey,
[tearfully] if you need anything,
- I'll be right at the top of that hill.
- You're so full of shit.
- And you're an idiot.
- [man] Let's go.
[Sobieski shouts] Claws and blood, baby!
[crickets chirping]
[distant gunfire]
[distant shouting]
- I need head count from the rear.
- [man] Copy!
Fire Team leader,
make sure your team is up.
- [man] Yes, sir.
- [Decker] What's the situation?
Fuck if I know.
Call came in about intruders
inside the fire base perimeter,
then comms went down.
- So the Major's sending us in.
- I'm going up there.
- Like hell you are.
- I can get to that fire base in minutes.
It'll take this relief column an hour.
Dog soldier's worried about his own kind.
Fuck off! Those are men up there.
Doesn't matter what kind.
- Go.
- [grunts]
[shouting] We'll be right behind you,
and we're plugging anything
that comes down that hill on four legs!
[panting]
[electric crackling]
God damn it. Sobieski.
[Commander] Eleven dead.
Torn to shreds.
Taliban's not supposed to have werewolves.
How the fuck did it get past your pal?
He took out Sobieski first, sir,
then moved on to the others.
What use are you people
if you can't even sniff out your own kind?
I've got his scent now.
I can track him.
[Commander] Good. I want him alive.
[sniffs]
[Decker sniffs]
You gettin' anything?
Nothing. He isn't here.
[Commander] Shit.
Sodula, you honor me with another meeting.
[sniffing]
[growls]
[roars]
- [bones cracking]
- [grunting]
[growling]
[growls]
[roars]
[roars in pain]
[bone crunching]
[distant howling]
- [announcement] First Battalion...
- [truck drowns out announcement]
- [sniffs]
- [man] Just what the hell are you doing?
You're not a soldier.
You're a fucking animal.
I may be an animal,
but I'm done wearing your leash.
See you in the wild, my friend.