[crickets chirping]
[squeaking]
Five minutes to objective.
Stay sharp, metalheads.
Copy that! Countdown to mayhem.
- We gonna let Rookie in on this?
- Depends.
- Hey, Rookie, your balls dropped yet?
- What?
Fuck you, Sui. I'm ready.
You'll get your chance, boy, don't worry.
We on schedule, Bob?
[Bob the Robot] Affirmative.
It appears the cargo is in the front car.
Hey, Hawk, what are we stealing, anyway?
It's a microchip, kid.
[Hawk] Wanna know what that
looks like? Your head's full of 'em.
[Bob] Don't forget
to look out for guards in the rear car.
[thumping electronic music plays]
[Hawk] Contact.
Move up and match velocity.
In position.
I got a position for you.
Really? Does it involve shoving my gun
- up your ass?- [laughs]
- [Hawk] We good to go, Bob? - [Bob] Roger that.
The target is in the blind spot.
You got till it reaches
the other side of the tunnel to get in,
- make the grab and get out.
- Move out.
Sui, Rookie, plant the magnetic mines
on the guard car.
[sarcastically] Great idea, boss.
Give the high explosives to the lunatic
and the new guy.
What could go wrong?
Ah, shut your grease trap. I got this.
[Sui] Last one.
- [squeals]
- Ah, shit!
[beeping]
[tires screeching]
[alarm throbs]
- What the fuck was that explosion?
- Hate to say I told you so.
Give us some covering fire, Kali.
On the roof!
[groans]
That does it.
[Kali] Wait! Just blow the mines...
- [roars] -...you suicidal fuck.
We're almost at the tunnel.
We need to blow those mines now!
Sui's not... clear.
[Sui] Don't worry about me.
Do it, Hawk!
[beeps]
Whoa!
Well, that wasn't so...
hard.
Hawk!
[Bob] Shit, did I mention
the automatic guns?
[engine roars]
No, Bob, you didn't.
Okay, let's pick it up.
If this truck makes it through
that tunnel, we are all fucked.
[Sui] Rookie, get your lug-nuts up here.
[Bob] Uh, wait a second.
I'm getting a new energy reading.
Oh, shit.
Uh, fellas? I think Bob missed
another detail about the defenses.
What do you mean, Kali? I don't...
Holy fucking shit!
Hey, that was my friend
you just dismantled,
you giant walking dildo.
[menacing music plays]
Rookie, get below deck now.
Ohh.
Looks like this is your stop, big guy.
- [Sui laughs]
- [tires screeching]
Huh?
Kali, look out!
Kali!
[shouts] Fucker!
[Bob] It's too heavily armored.
You'll have to get inside
and take out the defense CPU.
Rookie, blow its brains out.
- Copy that.
- [beeping]
[siren blares]
[slowed] M-o-t-h-e-r-f-u-c-k-e-r!
[Rookie panting]
[Sui] Come on! You little pussy!
God damn it, Rookie!
What are you waiting for?
Destroy this fucker's CPU.
[grunts]
[shouting] Oh, fuck!
[gasps]
[doom-laden music plays]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[alarm blaring]
[somber electronic music plays]
[groans]
[whirring]
[approaching engine]
[Bob] Holy shit, what a mess.
What happened, Rookie?
Mission accomplished, I guess.
I've got the chip, but...
everyone else...
[chuckling] Don't worry, kid.
I cried my first time too.
Sui? What?
Bob always makes a full backup of
our brains before each mission.
And Sui's brains, well, they don't take
too much space on the old hard drive.
I thought you were all dead.
You should have read your contract, kid.
Now come on, let's get outta here.