[woman] Like millions of others,
I'd heard Zima announce
the unveiling of his final work of art.
Over the years, I'd asked many times
for interviews and was always rejected.
Now, for whatever reason,
Zima Blue had requested to speak with me.
I couldn't decide whether the blue was
a closer match to the sky or to the sea.
Neither, really.
Zima Blue, it was a precise thing.
Little is known about Zima's history.
It was said that he started his art career
in portraiture,
but for Zima, the human form
was too small a subject.
The search for deeper meaning
caused him to look further...
to the cosmos itself.
That's how the mural work started.
They were undeniably brilliant.
One day, Zima unveiled a mural
that had something different about it.
In the middle of the canvas
was a tiny blue square.
- The square was just the beginning.
- [crowd murmurs]
[Claire] Over the next several decades,
the abstract shapes changed
and became more dominant.
But, always,
the shade of blue was the same.
It was Zima Blue.
Before very long, Zima unveiled
the first of his entirely blue murals.
It was considered by many to be
as far as Zima could take things.
They couldn't have been more wrong.
When most people speak about
his Blue Period,
they mean the era of
the truly huge murals...
but Zima was just getting started.
It was a certain level of spectacle
that made Zima truly famous,
- even to those with no interest in art.
- [crowd murmurs]
But fame was never the point.
In spite of all his success,
Zima was still dissatisfied
and what he did next was, for many,
too extreme a sacrifice to make for art.
- [Zima] Glad you could make it, Claire.
- [gasps]
How was the flight?
Relax, Claire.
Hi.
Some people find me intimidating,
but they quickly get over it.
It's been over 100 years
since I've spoken to the press.
I've invited you here because
I want you to help me tell my story.
Shall we take a little walk?
[Claire] He was a handsome man,
even after all his transformations.
There was a planet called Kharkov Eight.
It specialized in
illicit cybernetic modifications.
He underwent radical biological procedures
that enabled him to tolerate
extreme environments
without the burden of a protective suit.
His eyes could see in any known spectrum.
He no longer breathed oxygen.
His skin was replaced with
pressurized polymer
and so he ventured forth
to commune with the cosmos.
But what Zima eventually realized
is that the cosmos was already speaking
its own truth
far better than he ever could.
My search for truth has led me here,
to what will be my final piece.
At last, I understand the thing
I sought through my art.
And what does this swimming pool
have to do with that?
It's not just any swimming pool.
Long ago, it belonged to
a talented young woman
with a keen interest
in practical robotics.
She created dozens of robots
to do odd jobs around her house,
but she was especially fond of the one
she'd created to clean her swimming pool.
The little machine toiled endlessly,
scrubbing the ceramic sides of the pool.
But the young woman wasn't satisfied
with the job it did.
So she gave it a full color vision system
and a brain large enough to process
the visual data
into a model of its surroundings.
She gave it the ability
to make its own decisions,
to design different strategies
for cleaning the pool.
She continued to use the machine as
a test-bed for new hardware and software.
And by stages, it became more aware.
Eventually, the woman died.
The little machine was passed
- from one owner to the next.
- [electronic whirring]
They added things, made modifications here and there
and with every iteration, it became more alive.
Became more...
me.
- [gasps]
- This is that same pool.
I had it dug up. Moved here.
But you're a man with machine parts,
not a machine that thinks it's a man.
Sometimes, it's difficult even for me
to understand what I've become.
And harder still
to remember what I once was.
[exhales]
The blue of the tiles...
Zima Blue, the manufacturer called it.
The first thing I ever saw.
This was where I began.
A crude little machine with barely enough
intelligence to steer itself.
But it was my world.
It was all I knew, all I needed to know.
And now?
[crowd gasps]
[cheering]
[Zima] I will immerse myself.
[cameras click]
And as I do, I will slowly shut down
my higher brain functions...
[crowd gasps]
un-making myself...
[gasps]
leaving just enough
to appreciate my surroundings...
to extract some simple pleasure from
the execution of a task well done.
My search for truth is finished at last.
[gasps]