[screaming]
[sighs]
- [screams]
- [gunshots]
- [crows cawing]
- [dogs barking]
Oh...
Oh, man.
[screams]
- [gunshot]
- [screams]
[gun shot]
[heavy panting]
[window squeaks]
What?
[mechanical throbbing]
[banging]
[mechanical throbbing stops]
Oh, fuck!
[dialing number]
[operator] Emergency services.
What's your emergency?
Hello? I think I saw a murder.
- Location, please.
- I think the killer's after me.
Right. Location, please.
Yes, the hotel. Oh, fuck!
The Blue Henderson. The Blue Harrington?
The Blue Harrington?
But, no, wait.
It's the building right in front.
He saw me from the window.
I was in the hotel, he was not.
- Second floor?
- Ma'am?
- No, third floor.
- What's your name?
- Just send someone.
- Ma'am, we...
- Shit! Okay.
- [dialing number]
[recording] You have reached
the number of...
[in Russian accent]
Yeah, it's Vladimir. Leave a message.
Vladimir, I'm on my way there.
Please be there.
Shit!
[sighs deeply]
Oh!
Okay.
[pounding dance music playing]
About time you got here!
What the fuck, bitch?
Sorry, yeah.
You are fucking late!
You missed your show.
I cannot believe you.
- Yeah, I know. I just...
- Just shut it.
This is a fucking disaster!
I mean, look at me.
I just saw a murder.
- Ew, gross!
- Okay.
I mean, you always have
the most bizarre excuses.
- Okay.
- Just come in and get ready.
Okay, I wanna dance. Fuck!
But I need to see Vladimir.
- Is he here?
- Yeah, he's here.
- Fuck!
- Somewhere, I don't know.
Oh! Hi. Hello, young man.
- Are you a member?
- No.
Oh, you're not? It's okay. Don't worry.
You wanna see some pussy?
[pounding dance music continues]
Make some room, bitches.
May I have your attention,
please, bitches?
Because our next dancer is here.
Finally, yeah.
Zawora.
[mic feedback]
[industrial dance music plays]
[heavy breathing]
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [music muted]
[gasps]
[panting]
[yells] Vladimir!
Vladimir.
Hey...
- [woman moaning]
- [Vladimir laughs]
Fuck. Vladimir?
- What?
- Shit!
[Vladimir] Okay, stay.
[panting heavily]
[gasps]
- [woman screams]
- [man groans]
Fuck!
[wheezing]
[woman] Aaah!
- [man] Wait a second!
- [woman screams]
[man] Just fucking wait!
[woman screams]
[car horns honking]
- [crows cawing]
- [woman screams]
[man] Hold on. Wait a second.
Yeah. Fuck!
Just wait a fucking minute!
[woman screams]
[man] Wait!
[gasping and wheezing]
[door squeaks open]
[man coughs]
[door closes loudly]
[breathing heavily]
[footsteps approaching]
[loud breathing outside]
[keys jangle]
[lock clicks]
- [object falls to floor]
- Oh, hi.
Hi. Let's just talk.
- Just chill out.
- [gun cocks]
Oh, shit!
[man] Let's just talk.
[woman screams]
- [man grunts]
- [woman screams]
[gunshot]
- [woman screaming]
- [man grunting]
- [man] No!
- [gun shots]
[heavy thud]
[woman breathing heavily]
[window squeaks]