♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaf clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage
and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away all loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 29=
Wifey,
I have a question for you.
If,
I mean if.
If we're dating now,
we love each other so much,
and I treat you super well,
but all of a sudden I realize that
I have cancer.
Although I really love you,
I will have to keep distance between us
to not put any burden on you.
If you find out,
what would you do?
I don't think you'd be that noble.
I'm just asking a question.
What if it really happens?
If it really happens,
I'd never leave your side
and stay with you.
I knew it.
But I don't know
whether that's right or wrong.
Why do you ask
this question all of a sudden?
No reason, just casually chatting.
Let me see.
Are you really sick?
Do you have cancer or something?
I'm very healthy.
I'm in great health.
Then why did you...
Do you want to give it a try?
Let me down.
What are you doing?
Good morning, Boss.
I told you
to not come.
How can I
let you drive?
Let's go.
Have you had breakfast?
Yes.
What's wrong?
You're blowing hot and cold.
I'm a little tired.
Don't talk to me.
Okay, take a nap then.
Manager Wei.
Zhao Yan.
I heard that
Mr. Xu Jr. dumped you.
Is this work-related?
I find this pretty weird.
He just brought you up
to the top floor to be a secretary.
And now he doesn't even say hi
when he sees you at work,
pretending he doesn't know you.
This attitude change...
You're such an attentive person.
There are no secrets
at work.
Everything happens in this one building.
Everyone in the building
finds out instantly
if someone dates someone
or
someone dumps someone else.
That's just you.
Unlike me,
I don't know anything.
Okay.
Since you're back,
adjust your mindset
and work.
Okay?
But Zhao Yan,
I have to say this to you.
You have to know your place.
Mr. Xu Jr. is different.
He's up here
and you're down here.
That's the difference.
You know?
Manager Wei,
I just realized that
your current position doesn't show
your full potential.
You should be a paparazzi.
You'd be leading the field.
I'll give it a try if I have a chance.
But as of now,
get me a cup of water.
Why?
I'm your boss.
And I'm ordering you to get me a cup of water.
Right now.
Bring it to my office.
I...
Mr. Xu.
Why are you here?
Wei Zi Zhao.
You
don't deserve to be the department manager.
Listen up, everyone.
From now on,
Wei Zi Zhao and Zhao Yan
will swap positions.
Zhao Yan
will be your manager.
Understand?
Greetings, Manager Zhao.
The weather's so nice. Let's go.
Um...
Congratulations, Manager Zhao.
That
is pretty sweet.
(Did I)
(cross the line just now?)
(I hope I didn't upset you.)
(You've never been this charismatic before.)
So charismatic.
Take a break and have some food.
Did I tell you that I wanted to eat?
Take this to the client.
I can...
Okay.
What's wrong with Boss?
Did you do anything wrong?
Boss,
it's break time.
I want to have lunch with you
and get some sun together.
I'm busy.
Do you plan on treating me like this forever?
What did I do wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
Then why are you acting like this all of a sudden?
Although you're on lunch break,
I'm still working.
Get out.
Boss's condition hasn't been good recently.
I agree.
It's scary.
Come on, let's work.
We'd better not get caught,
or we'd be scolded again.
Poor Xiao Ning.
(You already skipped lunch.)
(You can't skip dinner again, right?)
(I don't have time.)
(You haven't tutored me)
(in a long time.)
(Let's talk about it tonight.)
Yan Yan.
You haven't left yet?
I was waiting for you.
Why were you waiting for me?
Come to the hospital with me.
Why?
There's no why.
You must go.
I was just talking about a what-if scenario.
Look how strong and healthy I am.
How could I possibly be sick?
Then why did you
say strange things like that?
I was just casually bringing it up.
Then just
consider it a check-up.
But I'm healthy.
Why do I need a check-up?
Then just take it as a
premarital health screening that we didn't have
before getting married.
If you're not going, then don't come home tonight.
I'll go. I'll go.
So speaking to you nicely doesn't work.
I just didn't think that you would
care about me this much.
You love me so much, don't you?
You're acting like a whole different
person recently.
Do your work.
This shouldn't be
how you talk to your girlfriend.
You're here to get tutored.
But...
Do your work.
I don't want to do it anymore. Don't have the mood.
You won't even talk to me.
Why should I do it?
Are you here to learn?
Are you not going to become
an architect designer without me?
Then what about
everything you told me before?
Was it a joke?
Jiang Xiao Ning,
this is your path.
No one can take it away from you.
If I were you,
nothing
will ever
make me change my mind.
I wasn't serious about what I just said.
What's wrong?
Did something happen to you?
Tell me.
We'll face it together.
It's getting late.
You can leave early
if you're done.
Ice Cream.
What happened?
According to the observatory,
we'll have a supermoon
in three days if the weather is good.
The supermoon is a once-in-a-century phenomenon
and will be visible to the naked eye.
(The supermoon is coming.)
It will be
the closest the moon will be to the Earth
in three centuries.
If you miss it this time around,
you'll have to wait until
2125 for the next time.
Let's watch it together, Wifey.
I have to work overtime.
You're the manager now.
You have the final say.
Let's take Gu Chuan
and Jiang Xiao Ning.
Just like what we did when we watched
the ephemeral plants.
The four of us will watch the moon and drink.
Maybe take some pictures and have
conversations about life.
That would be nice.
You have to do your check-up first.
Talk about it later.
(In-patient Department for Cats)
Someone sign this please.
I got it.
Doctor,
how is the cat doing?
We have to observe it for a few more days.
Thank you.
Don't worry, we'll try our best.
Let's go back first.
Ice Cream,
stay strong.
We'll come get you home
once you're well.
You got this.
Let's go.
Hi, sign this for me please.
According to the observatory,
we'll have a supermoon in three days
if the weather is good.
The supermoon is a once-in-a-century phenomenon
and will be visible to the naked eye.
It will be
the closest the moon will be to the Earth
in three centuries.
If you miss it this time around,
you'll have to wait until
(The supermoon is coming.)
2125 for the next time.
Did you hear that?
There will be a
once-in-three-centuries supermoon.
(You should always stay this happy.)
(This is how your life should go.)
(Full of hope and happiness.)
(Xiao Xu)
Hello?
Xiao Xu.
Do you have time today?
Come have lunch together.
I just learned to make Dynamite Stir-fry Shrimp.
Come and give it a try.
I don't have time.
It's just lunch.
You can go once you're finished. I won't keep you here.
Okay?
I've been busy.
Wait till I have time.
Then,
what about I bring it to you?
Hello.
Do you mind
getting Tang Xu for me?
Okay, one moment, please.
Hey...
Hear me out.
I've told you countless times.
Don't come here looking for me.
Okay?
I'm only here to bring you food.
I've been very annoyed recently.
I beg you to not come here ever again,
alright?
Do you know
how these people
would judge me every time you're here?
How?
Me.
The son of a criminal.
You hear that?
Please, I really haven't been having
a good time recently.
Please don't make it worse.
Alright?
I'm going to go. You can go home.
Okay.
You must be Uncle Tang.
I'm Xu Cheng Ran.
Xu Guo Xiang's son?
You don't look alike.
I look more like my mom.
Are you leaving?
Let me drive you home.
There's no need.
I have time.
I'll drive him home.
I thought the Financial Department
is verifying your accounting records.
You'll probably be working overtime.
Let me do it.
Let's go, Uncle Tang.
Don't forget to eat.
Uncle Tang,
I can see that you treat Tang Xu very well.
Xiao Xu
treats me well too.
He's just
too busy.
He doesn't have time.
He has been struggling a bit
these days.
How did you recognize that
I'm his father?
I've seen pictures of you.
If you want to
ask me anything,
just ask.
How did you figure out that
I have questions for you?
Or else,
why would you drive me home?
I've only heard about the event regarding
Jiang Xiao Ning's father, Jiang Guang Da.
But I don't know the details.
You were directly involved.
You must know the details.
I'm just curious.
I want to hear it from you.
Did Jiang Xiao Ning's father
really embezzle money?
Uncle Tang.
Has your father ever mentioned me?
No.
Your father,
Jiang Guang Da,
and I
were co-workers
at the same company.
Your father was our boss.
I know.
How would the boss
not know if someone working for him
embezzled public money?
So you're saying that...
If the water of a pond is dirty,
the fish in there
wouldn't be any cleaner.
Mr. Gu,
I thought you had changed a lot
the last time I saw you.
How come this time...
Things change.
Then for the design...
No more changes.
Okay.
I mentioned to you last time that
you would need some documentation
to purchase a cemetery plot.
Such as death certificate,
cremation documents...
I'll have all those.
(Organ Donation Registration Form)
(Organ Donor: Gu Chuan)
(Signature: Gu Chuan)
(Patent Transfer Agreement)
(Transferor: Gu Chuan)
Doctor,
how is its recovery going?
Not good.
The bacteria have already entered its kidneys.
It hasn't eaten for days.
According to the current situation,
it should stay in the hospital
for a few more days.
Please make sure that it's cured.
Don't worry.
I'll try my best.
But
I can't guarantee you anything.
It all depends on how it reacts.
Stay strong.
We'll help you
get better no matter what.
Keep it up.
(Jiang Xiao Ning)
Are you still at the hospital?
Ice Cream isn't
doing well.
Listen to whatever the doctor says.
Accept the reality.
I'm sure it'll be okay.
The things that are meant to happen
will always happen.
No...
How can you say something like that?
At a time like this,
can't you just say something
comforting?
Jiang Xiao Ning,
those words
won't solve any problems.
Maybe,
you really just have to accept it.
Ice Cream.
It's okay.
Stay strong.
I'll take you home when you're better.
Chuan,
what exactly do you want to do?
I'm just trying to get things ready
before I die.
Aren't you okay
for the time being?
I have already contacted
other researchers who study
the mechanical heart.
People are looking for solutions.
You talked about death
when you got the Jin An Award.
Jiang Xiao Ning spent so much effort
to change your mind.
Why are you doing these crazy things?
Are you really planning for your
funeral arrangements?
I don't know when
my life will come to an end.
I don't know when I'll die.
It's better to be prepared
than to panic
when the time comes.
For the past ten years,
all I have is doing the work
that I love...
You have me.
Of course,
I also have you
and my parents.
But other than that,
my life is so boring.
Ten years ago,
we went through the car accident together.
Destiny got us to meet again
to give me a reason
to continue living.
I just didn't expect that
I would have to say goodbye
to this world so soon.
It's too cruel.
Chuan,
I don't believe that
there is no one better
than Dr. Peer in this world.
Everything will be solved
when we get in contact
with other mechanical heart researchers.
If that's the case,
then why didn't the funders of the lab
invite them over?
Life won't last forever.
I'm very fortunate
to live ten more years than I was supposed to.
If you think that you can get away
with saying all that,
you're wrong.
Take all the bollocks back.
I'm going to burn
all of these bollocks documents.
I ask you to come today
to ask you to do me a favor.
I won't help you.
If you don't help me,
I'll ask others to help.
Don't worry.
I'm just trying
to be prepared.
Just
do your brother a favor.
Help me make these arrangements.
Okay?
So is this what
you think would be the best
for your parents and Jiang Xiao Ning?
Have you ever thought about
what they really want?
Jiang Xiao Ning did so much for you
these days.
What about you?
What did you do for her?
Hello, Boss.
Are you not up?
I've been waiting downstairs
for a while.
You're already at the studio?
The colors of the glass
will match the different areas
they correspond to.
This isn't just to make the appearance
more synchronized.
The refraction of the light
will help emphasize
the differentiation
of these areas.
The look will be different
based on
different weather conditions.
On our end,
we have to first confirm that
the glass has the right color and material.
Only after this step,
can the construction team start working.
Cheng Dong,
you'll be in charge of this one.
Yes.
Boss,
the food is here.
Who let you in?
You told me to
get food for everyone.
Do you think
this is the right time to come in?
I'm sorry.
I'll take it out now.
What happened?
I don't know.
Mr. Gu is
the original Mr. Gu again.
Maybe this version of Mr. Gu
is the true Mr. Gu.
Is that some tongue twister?
You don't understand.
Also,
I'm not satisfied
with this design.
Who made this?
(I have things to tell you.)
What's wrong?
What do you want to say?
Your attitude.
You're ignoring me.
You don't look like
you like me at all.
You have to apologize to me
for all that.
Why are you like this all of a sudden?
If there is anything,
you can talk to me about it.
Maybe I won't be able to help.
But at least,
we can face it together.
You've been avoiding me these days.
You stay far away
even you're tutoring me.
I'm used to being alone.
I don't feel comfortable
when someone else is in my house.
What do you mean?
You told me that you like me.
Now you're telling me to leave.
Gu Chuan,
I'm a simple person.
I'm okay with you disliking me.
And you can deny
my value as a person.
But I'm
a living person.
You can't just
tell me to come and leave whenever you want.
Do you not think that this is not okay?
So you want to break up with me?
Then tell me.
I've always thought that
I'm the most unlucky person.
But after I met you,
I thought that
all the bad luck I've experienced
was to make it possible for me
to be awarded with this jackpot called you.
♪Guide me forward♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
I've had too much on my plate recently.
♪Total strangers during our first encounter♪
♪Why does my heart beat so fiercely♪
Then,
can you give me a reason
to convince me?
♪Who is it♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
I'm sorry.
♪Returning to life in time♪
I don't want to hear your apology.
I know you have a lot on your plate.
I know you have a lot of work.
But you promised me
to treat me well.
Yes,
I did promise you.
Don't give up on me.
Don't push me away, okay?
♪Soulmates♪
Mr. Xu and Sister Yan Yan
invited us to
watch the supermoon together.
Let's join them.
♪Who is it♪
Wifey,
this wig
is getting
more and more uncomfortable.
Help me take a look.
Not bad.
It's all grown out.
It grew back?
You can take it off soon.
That's great.
It's itchy. Can you scratch it for me?
I feel like a female monkey
is picking fleas for the male monkey.
Who's a female monkey?
Have you seen a female monkey as pretty as I am?
Why don't you go sit with him?
You had a quarrel?
He has a lot on his plate.
He's just overwhelmed.
How are the results?
All normal.
So there's no problem.
Yes.
I told you I'm healthy.
You were worrying for nothing.
You're sick?
Hear this.
Your bro
asked me what I would do
if he gets cancer.
For no reason.
Wouldn't you think that there's
something wrong with him?
Why would anyone
want to jinx themselves?
Aren't you dumb?
Yes, I'm dumb.
Dumb.
Did you watch some random soap drama
and put on a show for me?
What drama could I watch?
I'm not a naive young girl.
What do you mean?
So I would be a naive young girl
if I watched dramas all day?
You're the young girl.
I'm naive, alright?
Don't be mad.
Wifey, chill.
Harder on this side.
Gu Chuan.
They had a quarrel.
Give them some space.
No...
Shut up.
You have a mouth, huh?
Keep massaging.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
I have something to tell you.
We're here
to watch the supermoon.
Don't make things
too awkward.
You can tell me
when we get back.
We should break up.
I said
we should break up.
Why?
We're from
two completely different worlds.
Maybe
some coincidental things happened
and it made me feel like
I like you.
I'm very clear-headed now
and I know
how I truly feel.
I didn't want to make it too blunt.
But I realized that
even though you felt
my emotions,
you didn't understand what I meant.
So I'll say it in a
more straightforward way.
We're not for each other.
Didn't we make a deal before?
I'll fix whatever I'm doing wrong
if you tell me.
I said we're not a good fit for each other.
What do you want to fix?
But before...
Why aren't we a good fit?
This joke isn't...
I told you, we're not a good fit for each other.
Why are you still pestering me?
♪Not alone, if you miss me too♪
♪Perhaps we won't forget♪
♪The box is full of memories♪
Xiao Ning.
Gu Chuan,
I'll get back to you later.
Xiao Ning.
♪The pinky promise we made♪
Yan Yan.
Wait for me, Yan Yan.
♪We'll definitely meet again if we
don't say goodbye♪
♪I'll wait for you to come back at the same place♪
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪