♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow
that fills up the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing,
please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth,
flying towards fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness
that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and
let's count down to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 30=
Are you Mr. Gu?
You need a driver, right?
Gu...
You were right.
But this isn't the only way
to get
to any part of the world.
I'm emboldened by drinking.
All my gratitude
can be expressed with this hug.
Boss, give me your hand.
Hold on.
Can I be included
in your future plans?
That's because
I like you.
I'd like to buy something from you.
What?
Your smile for today.
How could you do this?
I wasn't mentally prepared.
Am I dreaming?
I can tell you this again
in all seriousness.
Jiang Xiao Ning, I like you.
Hello.
Do you need help?
No, you can go.
I'm tired.
Don't talk to me.
Eat something and get some rest.
Did I say that I wanted to eat?
Take this to the client.
I'll go.
Don't give up on me.
Stop pushing me away, okay?
Yan Yan!
Where's Xiao Ning?
Is she all right?
Gu Chuan wants to break up
with Xiao Ning.
Why?
How would I know
the reason?
Look, Xu Cheng Ran.
Your stupid friend, Gu Chuan.
I'm going to kick his ass!
Yan Yan.
Calm down.
Hear me out.
Gu Chuan has his own reason.
What is it?
Does he also have cancer?
You two sure are good friends
to come up with the same excuse.
It's not like that.
Gu Chuan...
(Insufficient Charge)
I'm going to find him.
Go on.
Don't ever come back if you go.
Chuan!
Why are you doing this?
You love her.
Why do you
have to torment each other?
Chuan!
Shoot.
(Charging)
You gave me a real scare.
I thought
you were gone.
Gu Chuan, tell me.
What are you trying to do?
You won't even recharge it.
Do you have a death wish?
If you keep this going,
I'm going to beat your up.
Fine.
Even if you don't care
about your own life,
you should at least
think about my feelings.
At least,
be responsible to me.
I'm begging you.
Stop hurting me.
I'm not young anymore.
My heart can't take
such a big blow.
Boss.
Good morning.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
Good morning, Boss.
♪The destined one♪
♪Guide me forward♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
♪We are total strangers
meeting for the first time♪
♪Why does my heart beat so fiercely♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
There's nothing in the fridge.
I'll make do with the ingredients
and make you a bowl of vegetable porridge.
This isn't right.
You don't know
how to take care of yourself at all.
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪
Hello?
Come to the hospital now.
The doctor said Ice Cream is dying.
(Ai-Bi Pet Hospital)
How is it?
Finally, you came.
Ice Cream's condition is getting worse.
We've tried all possible means.
There's nothing I can do now.
Are you saying
that we should transfer him to another hospital?
I'll be honest with you.
Its organs
are failing.
Even if you had him transferred,
it wouldn't change the fact.
Here's my suggestion.
Euthanise him.
Euthanise him?
No.
I disagree.
Is there no other way?
It's the only option.
The decision is in your hands.
I agree.
Who are you to decide?
You can discuss it first.
Look at him.
He's suffering.
Since there's no hope,
why not let him go
and set him free sooner?
Are you trying to take away
his final moment?
It's his most painful moment.
How do you know he's suffering?
He may be using this time
to say goodbye to the world.
Perhaps, he doesn't want to leave.
That's why he's still holding on.
Whatever the reason,
it's his own choice.
He doesn't have a choice.
Besides, he can't talk.
He can't tell you
how painful it is for him.
I can tell
he doesn't want to leave.
He wants us to save him.
How about this?
I'll talk to the doctor
and see
if there's a better option.
Ice Cream.
You'll be fine.
I'll be with you.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
You'll get better. I'm sure.
Should we
give him a name?
Look.
Your last name is Gu,
and mine is Jiang.
Gu Gu.
Jiang Jiang.
I disagree with that name.
How about Ice Cream?
We found him
when we were having ice cream.
How about Ice Cream?
(Pet Euthanasia Consent Form)
(Pet owner’s signature: Gu Chuan)
Come on. Pick up the phone.
Gu Chuan.
Give Ice Cream back to me.
Pick up the phone.
You're back, my baby Ning.
Xiao Ning.
Here. Eat up.
Mom.
This is for Ning Ning.
(Want to come and have a look at Ice Cream?)
Aunt, take care of Grandma.
I'm going out for a bit.
Jiang Xiao Ning, where are you going?
(2016-2020, Ice Cream)
(Pet Cemetery)
I have something to say to you.
I didn't prepare anything
but I don't want to go
to the office anymore.
So I can't hand in
the resignation letter to you myself.
I hereby
give you my verbal resignation.
You should continue to work there.
I muster up the courage to be with you.
I didn't care
what people thought of me.
But I realized
I was wrong.
Indeed, a mechanical heart is cold.
It's no use no matter how hard I try
to warm it up.
When you broke up with me,
I thought it was an act of impulse
and that you were just throwing tantrums.
I thought
you would surely come back to me.
Everything
would go back to how it was.
But
what happened with Ice Cream,
you really let me down.
You don't care
how others feel at all.
That's right.
That's me.
You finally admit it.
Well.
Let's hit the brakes
on our relationship.
Is there still hope?
There's no other way.
And all his organs
are inflamed.
It's suffering.
You can think about it.
I agree.
I agree with euthanasia.
(Pet owner's signature)
(Pet owner’s signature: Gu Chuan)
Hold on.
(Pet Euthanasia Consent Form)
♪People who think alike♪
♪Are pushing the gears♪
♪Ah~Ah~♪
♪Turn around♪
♪The destined one♪
♪Guide me forward♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪
What do you think?
His hair is soft, right?
Why does it
keep staring at me?
He likes you.
He knows he has found a good owner
and he'll live a good life.
Why are its toys are all
pink?
Girls love pink.
Don't you like it?
But Ice Cream is a tomcat.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Wake up.
It's me,
not Jiang Xiao Ning.
Stop dreaming.
If you don't want her to go,
get her back.
Jiang Xiao Ning is a reasonable person.
If you tell her everything,
she'll forgive you.
Your heart data
has been up and down these days.
The fluctuations
are greater than ever before.
Shall I move in with you?
I'm worried about you living alone.
I'm fine.
Go back to the office.
My dear Chuan.
Look at you now.
Stop worrying about the company.
If your condition isn't taken care of,
I can't be bothered with anything else.
Do you have any news
of Jiang Xiao Ning?
How is she?
I have asked Yan Yan.
She has no idea as well.
If you're worried,
you should
call her yourself.
I was just asking.
Get a good rest.
Without you at work,
it won't go bankrupt any time soon.
(I have to get used to the days without her.)
Director Xu.
You wanted to see me?
About the company that I gave you.
You can't just leave it dormant.
There's no business lately.
Besides,
isn't that company
used for money laundering?
It's exactly
because of that,
you can't just leave it dormant.
It's too obvious.
Got it?
I'll need your help
with another transaction soon.
Director Xu.
The scale of the operation
of the branch office is small
and the transaction dates
are too close.
I'm afraid if we keep doing it,
our accounts will be audited soon.
Use your noodle.
Think of a way.
Got it.
Well, I'll figure things out.
Go.
Director Xu.
About that incident,
I beg you to trust me once again.
Do I not trust you enough?
It's not that, Director Xu.
Besides money laundering,
I can do
other things that can benefit the group.
If you give me free rein
and let me run the branch,
I can make it prosper.
Director Xu.
Trust me.
I can make more money for you.
I won't let you down again.
What matters is to find your own position.
Got it?
Just do what you're doing
and do it right.
What do the group's affairs
have to do with you?
It's none of your concern.
Do you not understand
what I said?
I understand.
Mr. Tang.
Get lost.
Get lost!
Hello?
When are you free
to come back?
I'm not sure
if you still want some of these things.
I'll see if I have time tomorrow.
Hi, what would you like to drink?
Give me two of those.
Two cups of cherry and berry?
Yes.
A moment, please.
Hold on.
It's fine.
I'll have two of those.
Your aunt and your grandma are asleep.
Thank you.
Go home.
You don't have to stay.
What is it? Trying to kick me out?
You'll need an audience to watch you cry.
Look, Jiang Xiao Ning.
No matter what happens in the future,
don't ever turn off your phone again.
Do you know
how worried I was
when I was looking for you?
I didn't want to
but as soon as I turned it on,
I would start wondering
if he had contacted me.
Was his phone broken?
Was there no signal?
Was there a bug problem on WeChat?
I kept expecting to hear from him.
Have you told your aunt?
Not yet.
I didn't want her to worry.
I came home
only after I had cried my eyes out.
I'm afraid she will find fault
with Gu Chuan after seeing me like this.
He has put you through so much pain,
and you're concerned about him?
Has he considered how you feel?
This is your first love.
I thought
you had found your Mr. Right.
But turns out, he's a scumbag.
He didn't even have the guts to ask for a breakup.
I never thought
my first love would end just like that.
It feels like it was just yesterday
when I mustered up the courage
to confess to him.
But
that's how first love is supposed to be.
There's no happy ending for it.
It's not that you have bad taste in men.
It's Gu Chuan's fault.
I don't blame him.
The only thing I was mad about
is the way he handled Ice Cream's situation.
I don't blame him
about us.
Did you cry too much that you lost your mind?
Regardless,
it's all over.
The only thing I can do
is to accept it.
Don't you want to teach him a lesson?
You might think
that I'm a fool in love
to believe him in everything.
But I know
what kind of guy he is,
his character
and his personality.
He never meant to hurt me.
Come on. Look around you.
You were dumped.
In public!
How could you act
like nothing ever happened
and you're still fooling yourself?
♪My eyes are tearing up♪
♪I have so much to tell♪
♪The secrets will remain untold♪
♪Make it last forever♪
♪The case will be full of memories♪
♪The meaning will withstand
the passage of time♪
♪The lively boy passes by on the car♪
♪The belief when we made our promise♪
Ice Cream.
♪I was so in love with the silhouette♪
♪We'll meet again
if there is no farewell♪
♪I'll stay here, waiting for you♪
Let's think about tomorrow.
I have a family to support.
I'm planning to find a job tomorrow.
Why do you need to find a job?
Your current job is good, right?
Don't you love
your current job?
Why should you quit?
Sister Wen Wen did tell me
to be careful with workplace romance.
Things would be awkward after the breakup.
I'm not afraid of what people say.
I just dare not face Gu Chuan.
What's there to be afraid of?
Listen to me.
Go to work.
Keep showing up in front of him.
Let's see who gets drained first.
I'm not as tough
as you are.
I prefer to save myself
one last bit of dignity.
But you have
a tough best friend.
Also, when you were
doing part-time jobs,
you endured all kinds of hardship
and did all sorts of embarrassing stuff.
And now
you're talking about dignity?
Take my advice.
Go.
Go to work.
But I don't want to put Gu Chuan in a bad spot.
Xiao Ning.
Can you stop being so sensible?
Whenever I see you
being so sensible,
it makes me feel
sullen
and so mad.
I find it so unfair to you.
Do you know that?
Go to work.
It's a must.
If not, I'll break up with you.
Go to bed.
Xiao Xu.
You're here. Come on in.
Come on in.
I just want you
to come back and take a look at these things.
It's been a while
since you last opened the storeroom, right?
So I thought
of cleaning up the place.
When I opened it,
I found all these.
Look.
These are your trophies,
honorary credentials,
and also
Certificate of Merit.
The video game.
This is a picture of you and Ning Ning.
That's right.
Since you were a kid,
you've been
a really good kid.
Be it your studies
or any other aspects,
your mom and I
never had to worry about you.
You know what? Back then,
the happiest thing for your mom and I
was to attend the parent-teacher meetings.
Sorry.
If it hadn't been for me,
you would have a better future prospect.
I was the one who ruined it.
I know things must have been tough
for you
all these years
although you were living in a rich family.
Like you said,
Xu Guo Xiang was nice to you.
But still, it's nothing like home.
I can only imagine what it was like
to live under someone else's roof.
Sorry.
If you're not working late tonight,
stay and have dinner.
So you agreed?
It's fine.
I'll buy some nice ingredients.
Wait for me.
(Job boards)
Sister Wen Wen.
Xiao Ning.
I'm back.
How are you? Is everything okay?
I'm...
not doing great.
What happened?
Did you fight with Gu Chuan?
Where is he?
He's probably at work.
I...
I resigned.
You resigned?
You were right.
After the office romance ended,
things do get awkward.
I've been thinking about it lately.
I have no courage to go back to work.
Jiang Xiao Ning, that's so silly of you.
A relationship is about two persons.
Why are you the one
to bear the consequences after the breakup?
Why are you the one to resign?
But I...
But what?
Since you had the courage to confess to him
and to start a relationship,
you should have the courage
to face the consequences.
I don't know
why he broke up with you.
But resignation
isn't advisable
unless he sacks you.
But if he did,
he wouldn't be the Gu Chuan
that I knew.
So, you mean I should go back to work?
A breakup simply means a different way
to get along with each other.
Since he can accept it,
why can't you?
I'm afraid...
Of what?
It's not like he's bedridden
in the hospital
and has sunk into depression
that he can't take care of himself.
He still goes to work like usual.
Why are you
putting yourself through hell?
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪