Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
The Long Ballad
This is a work of fiction.
Episode 16
Starting today,
you're just a slave in the Eagle Army.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to disappear from Tang.
I have the final say in deciding whether I'm dead or not.
What you say is useless.
That depends on your capability.
Keeping me by your side...
is like raising a tiger.
It makes no difference.
Make sure you survive first...
before you are worried about that.
The law of survival on the grasslands...
is only the strongest survives.
Behind me...
is Shuozhuo...
that has been looted but the people escaped the battle unscathed.
Behind it...
is endless mountains.
Beyond that...
is my homeland, a million miles away.
Chang'an.
In the end, I couldn't go back there.
In the past, you achieved glory for the motherland.
Now, you're just a slave.
Li Chang Ge.
Even I feel bad for you.
Fuju Inn
After receiving the order,
I hurried here right away.
Please give me your instructions, Commander Hao.
Follow Ashina Tribe at once.
I want to know what happened to Li Chang Ge in the end.
Should I kill her?
If she colludes with Ashina Tribe,
kill her.
What if she doesn't?
Ashina Tribe won't keep her.
Yes.
Send whatever news you have...
through the pigeon.
You may leave.
Yes.
The people dearest to me...
were all slaughtered like pigs and dogs.
The place I was born and raised...
banished me.
I felt like dying every single day.
But I had to do what I had to do.
Once this is over,
it won't be too late to kill me.
Noble and integrate
Li Chang Ge.
I hope you can sacrifice for the people.
Recently,
all the county offices around the kingdom...
are secretly looking for the princess.
However, the portrait that was sent to the capital...
looks nothing like the princess.
Furthermore, the princess lost in the four states in the north.
Until now,
we haven't heard anything yet.
Your Highness.
Princess Yong'an is very blessed.
Didn't Li Chun Feng make a prediction...
that she'll come back safely?
I hope so.
Lately,
I always dreamed of...
Le Yan and Chang Ge when they were younger.
Both of them...
were hanging around in the garden.
I waved at them...
but they couldn't see me.
I called out their names.
But they couldn't hear me either.
Worse,
they kept running away.
Your Highness...
worries too much.
That's why...
Your Highness had weird dreams.
Your Highness, I'll get the imperial kitchen...
to make some soothing soup for Your Highness.
Will those two girls...
be further away from me?
No.
They will always be...
the most daring daughter and official to you.
Perhaps at this moment,
no news is the best news.
That's right.
Your Highness, there is urgent military news.
Ashina Tribe suddenly attacked the north border.
The chief commander, Sima Tu...
and the governor of Shuozhou, Gongsun Heng...
were killed in the battle.
When did it happen?
No one reported it!
Ashina Tribe besieged the city.
The frontier couldn't deliver the message.
Hao Du sent his men to speed things up.
Five horses were sacrificed...
before the news reached Chang'an.
Send our army there now to regain the north region.
Make sure we chase the Ashina Tribe out of the border.
After that,
the troops will camp at the same place...
to comfort the people in the north.
Yes, Your Highness.
Mr. Du.
I need to talk to you.
You always know your own mind.
What do you want to discuss with me?
Mr. Du, don't be sarcastic.
You and I are the ministers of the imperial court.
It's good to have someone to discuss with.
Furthermore,
I really need a favor from you.
Just tell me what it is.
As you know,
Princess Yong'an is missing in action.
It's His Highness's biggest concern.
The portrait of Princess Yong'an...
has been sent to all local government offices...
for a secret investigation.
However, Princess Yong'an is nowhere to be found.
But we didn't receive any news...
from the north.
I'm just worried.
What do you want me to do?
People in the north...
have never seen Princess Yong'an before.
Your godson is in the north, right?
Although Wei Shu Yu...
allegedly lost her,
at that time,
your godson, Hao Du...
was with Princess Yong'an.
The more collaborative the effort,
the better.
Furthermore, under your guidance,
- your godson is already... - That's enough.
Talk properly.
Don't flatter me.
Since His Highness...
has entrusted you with this case,
you should work on it.
Yes.
Eat up.
Here.
What's the point of keeping him here?
If you ask me, I'll just kill him.
- Hold on. - Here.
Leave it there.
Give me more.
Here.
Where are you going?
I didn't expect to see you here.
Here.
Actually, the Eagle Army...
isn't too far from Shuozhou.
It's near a river and there are trees.
You'll get used to it.
Eat up.
Let me tell you.
If His Highness didn't care about you,
I wouldn't care about you either.
My goodness.
Your friend is insensible.
I think you're wasting your effort on him.
Look at that body.
I don't think he can survive in the grasslands.
No, he'll survive.
How do you know that?
He is someone who has a strong desire to live.
He won't be defeated...
so easily.
It looks like...
you know him very well.
But I think...
you're just the enemy to him.
It doesn't matter.
You've never treated me so nicely after all these years.
That person...
has been following us for a long time.
I know.
He's here to see Shi Si Lang.
Do something for me.
What are you doing?
Let go!
Listen to me.
You're our slave.
Just do whatever I tell you to do.
What?
Are you refusing to work?
You must have a death wish.
Take him away.
Cut him into pieces and feed him to the dogs!
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Let go!
Come on!
Elder Qin.
I feel bad for Yuan Niang.
She has been homeless and travels with us for so long.
Not at all.
She has the best father and mother in the world.
How is Shuozhou doing?
I heard that...
the Ashina Tribe has left.
Someone from the imperial court will come and take over the rest.
Aside from that...
"Aside from that"?
Are you going to tell me...
about Young Master?
He failed in the assassination.
He was killed.
I see. He's...
He's too strong and impulsive.
It's easy to destroy those who are strong and impulsive.
If...
Stop it.
I think Young Master...
is still alive.
He's still alive?
Since Ashina Sun...
made a promise with Governor Gongsun,
he won't kill him for sure.
Perhaps he has brought him to the grasslands.
Let's not wait any longer.
- Let's look for him. - In the grasslands,
they have spies everywhere.
We can't barge in as we like.
Let's take care of Yuan Niang first.
We should use our previous connection...
and see if we can get some information.
Then I'll make a decision.
Someone has been executed by Ashina Sun.
Li Chang Ge.
Perhaps this is the best place for you.
Why are you here?
That's my question for you.
Losing the princess is a serious matter...
yet His Highness didn't blame you.
I'll find Le Yan for sure.
I'll wait and see.
It has been so long.
You didn't return to Chang'an.
Are you looking for Chang Ge?
What happened to her?
She's dead.
How did she die?
Did you kill her?
Tell me!
Wei Shu Yu.
Do you plan to sacrifice yourself and your family...
just to avenge your lover?
After killing you,
I'll kill myself to atone for it.
Do you think that His Highness...
will punish the Wei family just for you?
Then why didn't you do it?
When Li Chang Ge was alive, you couldn't do anything.
Now that she's dead,
you found the courage to take revenge.
I guess,
that's because you know that since Li Chang Ge is dead,
your family's glory won't be affected.
Even if you want revenge,
you've come to the wrong person.
I didn't kill Li Chang Ge.
It was done by Ashina Tribe.
Ashina Tribe?
Ashina Tribe invaded Shuozhou.
Li Chang Ge was captured by them.
With that temper of hers,
do you think she can survive?
I can't believe you went after me with him.
From now on,
we're no longer related.
I won't rely on anyone else but myself.
Le Yan gave me an amulet. But what's the point?
In the end,
I failed to protect both of them.
That's enough.
Li Chang Ge is no longer here.
Make sure Princess Yong'an is safe.
Also,
I received a message from Chang'an.
They want me to stay at the north border...
to look for Princess Yong'an.
Obviously,
they don't trust you.
I'll make sure I find Le Yan before you do.
It doesn't matter.
I won't compete with you.
But I'll give you a hint.
In Shuozhou, Li Chang Ge...
is the Commandant of Light Chariot known by everyone.
If Princess Yong'an is in Shuozhou,
there must be a trace of her.
So, your trip to Shuozhuo...
is in vain.
Fuju Inn
What happened last night?
Why did you knock me out after covering my head?
Why didn't you kill me?
Last night, a slave died for you.
Take him away.
Cut him into pieces and feed him to the dogs!
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
- Let go of me! - Come on.
Let go!
Come on.
Don't move.
Hurry up.
What is Ashina Sun doing?
I don't get him either.
If I were him,
I would have lost my patience a long time ago.
What a slave.
You're already challenging the limit of Eagle Army.
If I don't torture you,
you won't know how great we are.
You look fragile.
What's the point of bringing you back?
Yunzhou County Office
This way, please.
Excuse me.
Are you the magistrate?
Where do you come from?
You can't even recognize the magistrate.
Magistrate, I need a favor.
How dare you!
You have no manners.
He has work to attend to.
Move.
Magistrate.
You are the magistrate of Yunzhou.
If I didn't have an urgent request,
I wouldn't be so bold.
Go.
Hit the drum if you are seeking justice.
What brings you here?
Please listen to me.
I can't reveal my identity there.
If you don't mind,
can you help me send a message to Chang'an...
or Luoyang?
Who are you?
I'm Princess Yong'an.
I accidentally got separated from my guards.
After the siege,
I escaped to this place.
Magistrate.
If you could help me get home,
His Highness will reward you heavily for sure.
Do you have any proof?
Proof?
When I got separated from my guards,
I didn't bring any tokens.
But I really am a princess.
The title was conferred by my grandfather.
Do you have any carry-on piece from the palace?
Handmade items from the palace that is easy to recognize.
All of them were taken away from me.
Where did you get that information from?
You're quite nimble.
There is indeed a secret order from the imperial court...
to find a princess in secret.
Just because you claim that you're a princess,
it doesn't mean that you are one.
I knew that my father would look for me.
Magistrate.
I'm really a princess.
Trust me. It's true.
Magistrate, please! Please send a message to Luoyang!
You can be sentenced to corporal punishment for imitation.
- I'm really a princess. - You two. Arrest her!
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Magistrate!
Magistrate...
Why don't you believe me?
What are you waiting for? Arrest her!
That's enough.
Let her go.
She's just a poor thing who doesn't have a choice.
It's very chaotic here.
The new governor will be here soon.
I don't have the time to deal with a refugee.
Be careful.
Hongfa Textile Workshop
Father.
Why didn't you come and fetch me?
Are you abandoning me?
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
If you have too much energy,
you may go for a run.
I just don't get it.
What do you plan to do with Shi Si Lang?
You tried so hard to save Shi Si Lang.
Now, you're just ignoring him...
and let him be bullied by everyone.
You're getting weirder.
The more I pay attention to him,
the more he will suffer.
Rather than making him hate himself,
just let him hate me.
You are really odd!
Did he bewitch you?
Should I summon a shaman?
Do you want to clean horse manure?
Why should I?
I'm Eagle Army's military adviser.
Can you at least let me save my face?
He has to get a foothold...
in the Eagle Army on his own.
I can't be monitoring him all the time.
He's just a witty-minded man from the Central Plain.
Is he even worth the effort?
He is not grateful to you at all.
I don't need him to be grateful to me.
I just want him to live.
Your Highness and Military Adviser.
The slave that you told me to keep an eye on has passed out.
You're exhausted from protecting Shuozhou.
You didn't eat or drink throughout the journey.
You don't want to live anymore.
What's wrong?
Are you afraid that I might do something to you?
I'm not interested in a woman like you.
How do you know?
I found out when I saved you at the river.
Since you want to hide it,
I didn't bother to expose you.
You've been playing me this whole time.
Think of it however you want.
Your Highness.
This is the medicine you asked for.
The shaman said you're worrying too much.
Hence, you have weak energy.
If you don't want to die,
take the medicine.
Take the medicine.
Li Shi Si!
I'm surprised at how weak you are!
People in Shuozhou are sound and safe.
I have kept my promise.
It's your turn now.
Don't forget...
your life belongs to me now.
What a joke.
You want someone from the Central Plain to serve you.
Why don't you just kill me?
You'll regret it soon.
I won't repeat myself.
Take your medicine.
Is that how you solve problems?
It's better than enduring a life of humiliation.
Since my life is in your hands,
you don't have to humiliate me!
Humiliate you?
I just don't want you to die so easily!
Li Shi Si.
You'd better find a way to survive.
Do it so that you can live long enough to kill me one day soon.
Do it so that you can avenge Gongsun Heng!
Avenge?
Yes.
Avenge.
Avenge Gongsun Heng.
Avenge the troops and people of Shuozhuo.
Have you forgotten about it?
Gongsun Heng is ridiculous.
How could he trust a coward?
If I were you,
I would gain a firm footing in the Eagle Army at all costs.
I would gain the trust of the people around me at all costs...
and wait for the right time to strike!
If you don't want to let him down,
you should clench your teeth and live.
Being able to entrust the lives of the civilians in Shuozhou City...
to a Tang princess...
and commit an act of benevolence...
is considered a happy ending for me.
Shuozhou
In the city,
there are thousands of families.
I can't let them down.
But in the end,
I'll have to let my wife and daughter down.
Dou!
It's not just about avenging Governor Gongsun.
It's not just about avenging Shuozhou.
Yes.
How could I die just like that?
How could I die here?
It's easy to die.
Living has always been the hardest.
Go!
Stop.
Let's go.
Don't go there.
We came from that direction.
Yan Er is not there.
Let's go to Yunzhou.
Go!
This is the magistrate's office!
Both of you can't go inside without permission!
Magistrate.
We're ordered by Crown Prince...
to look for Princess Yong'an.
We need your people.
What can I help you with?
Just let me know.
Send your people...
to all the hideouts of refugees...
to look for the lady in the portrait.
Yes.
This...
Have you seen her?
Where is she?
She didn't have anything that can prove her identity.
I thought she's a refugee.
So I sent her away.
No matter what it takes,
you must find her!
Yes, sir.
Where are you going, Madam Chai?
- I'm taking a walk. - Are you leaving?
Your embroidery is awful.
You need to work on it to make money.
- All right, I get it. - No need.
Madam Xiang.
How is your business?
It's good.
You should burn more incense.
The pepper cookies are fragrant and crispy.
You're finally here.
- Yes. - Give me three of those.
There are so many of them.
- Three cookies are not enough. - Nonsense!
They should be grateful that they have food to eat.
They don't deserve pepper cookies.
Hurry up.
- I'm hungry. - All right. Hold on.
There are so many of them.
Look!
We're not doing charity.
Go somewhere else to beg for food.
I have money.
I want to buy some cookies.
You scared her.
One cookie is three cents.
Don't think that it's expensive.
The war is still going on.
The price of food is about the same.
Here, this is your cookie.
Young lady.
In broad daylight,
are you going to do that for a cookie?
Young lady!
I'm an honorable man.
It's three cents for a cookie.
I won't ask for anything else.
No. I'm afraid that someone else might steal it.
That's why I keep my pouch in the innermost layer.
I see.
I can tell right away that you know nothing about sewing.
What is that? The embroidery on the pouch is so ugly.
I think...
this is the prettiest pouch.
All right. Hold on.
Here's your cookie.
- Thank you. - All right.
Hey.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I've had something dirtier before.
If you don't mind,
I'll give you half.
I'll give you some.
- I didn't mean any harm. - Hey.
Nowadays,
kind-hearted people get bullied.
What are you waiting for? You should check your pouch.
You even thought of sharing the food with him.
You must be a fool.
Come and take a look.
My pouch.
My pouch!
Stop right there!
Give me back my pouch.
You can take the money.
Right.
Here. This is for you.
It's so ugly. What's this?
My hands got pricked in order to make that,
and you're even complaining that it's ugly.
- Forget it then. - It is ugly,
but I like it.
Chang Ge.
Where are you?
Have you seen the lady...
on the portrait?
No.
Have you seen this lady?
This lady in the portrait,
have you seen her before?
No.
- Have you seen her before? - No.
You!
- No, I haven't seen her. - Are they...
Are they after me?
- You! - Stop right there!
After her!
- Stop right there! - Stop right there!
- Stop right there! - Stop!
After her!
You lost your money.
Why are you following me?
They want to arrest me.
What did you do?
I didn't do anything wrong.
They accused me of pretending to be the princess.
Why did you do that?
Young lady.
Are you a fool?
I'm not pretending to be a princess. I really...
Open the door!
Coming.
Are you going to pay me if you break the door?
It's still daytime.
What's the rush?
Are you here to buy clothes?
We're chasing after a girl.
I saw her walking on this street.
Have you seen her before?
We're looking for her.
Yes, I have.
This lady was pickpocketed on the street earlier.
She went after the perpetrator, heading south.
Sir, what did she do?
Is she a robber?
This area is not safe lately.
- Search the place. - Hey!
Sir!
Great virtue brings happiness
What's the matter?
- I don't know. - What's wrong?
- We didn't find anything. - We didn't find anything.
She's not there either.
Sir, as I said, she's not here.
My textile workshop is operating.
You simply look around the workshop.
It will leave a bad impression.
That's enough.
If you see her again,
inform us right away.
Of course.
Let's go.
You're smart.
At least you hid in the tank.
Thank you for the help.
I thought you wouldn't save me.
That's enough.
You don't seem like a bad person.
They have nothing better to do.
You're just pretending to be a princess.
Do they really have to do that?
Ma'am.
I'm not pretending.
I'm really a princess.
All right.
It doesn't matter if you're a princess or a lord.
I need to get back to work.
You should go.
Ma'am.
If I go out right now,
I'll get caught.
I beg you.
Please let me stay here for one more day.
All right.
Go inside and get changed.
Don't blame me when you get sick.
Thank you, ma'am.
So this is the grassland.
It's so vast.
Madam Su Yi Li.
Do you have more cheese?
- Please keep some for me. - Sure.
Come to my tent later.
You can have as much as you want.
Your Highness, are there any presents for us?
Ye, everyone gets a present.
Ya Luo.
Your Highness, the herbs are ready.
Here they are.
Take a look.
It's not bad.
- Here, Your Highness. - Take a look.
Help yourself.
- There are presents! - I want this.
This is good.
- Look. - Let me see.
Uncle Shi Min, where is my reward?
- Where is my reward? - Where is my reward?
- Stand still. - Where is my reward?
Stand still and close your eyes.
Close your eyes. Close them.
What about me, Uncle Shi Min? Where's mine?
- Give it to me - I only have one pony.
- I'll give it if you can reach it. - Give it to me, Father!
Give it to me.
Father!
Uncle Shi Min!
Father, don't go against your words.
Father!
Uncle Shi Min!
Give it to me, Uncle Shi Min!
You promised me!
- Here, let me help you. - Thank you.
Not bad.
That was fun.
Hey!
You're good in Cuju, right?
This is for you.
Can we have the ball?
Here.
- Stop right there! - Come on!
Wait for me!
Slow down!
- Give it to me. - No.
I'll send the present home for them.
- Hold it properly. - Can you take it to him?
The pay is so low.
Madam Zhang, you should consider yourself lucky.
At least we still have work to do.
We won't be starving to death.
That's not bad.
You're right.
It's getting difficult to use the machine.
Yes.
Madam Chai.
You finally hired someone.
I found her on the street.
She'll leave tomorrow.
Greetings, everyone.
What are you looking at?
Get back to work!
She's so pretty.
What kind of salutation was that?
I don't know. It looks nice though.
Exactly.
Greetings, everyone.
That's not correct.
It's like this.
- No. - That's what she did.
You'll sleep here tonight.
You have to leave tomorrow.
I don't feed people for nothing.
Thank you, ma'am.
I will repay you someday.
Thank you.
What should I do tomorrow?
Yunzhou County Office
What did you say?
I didn't hear it clearly.
Please pardon me.
Princess Yong'an...
We lost her.
It's fine if you can't find her.
What do you mean you lost her?
We saw a lady who looks like her on the street.
But she got away.
A lady who looks like her?
How did she run away?
Mr. Wei, we'll keep looking.
However, Princess Yong'an has feet.
We are unsure...
whether she's still in Yunzhou or not.
How dare you absolve yourself?
Yes.
We'll keep looking.
- I'll look for her tomorrow! - I'll look for her tomorrow!
- Get lost! - Get lost!
Yes, sir!
Yan Er.
Where are you?
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
The Long Ballad