Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 18
Go.
Stop it!
Aren't you the new counselor?
What do you want?
You think you can boss us around, because Tegin treats you well.
We have our own rules.
Even it is Tegin, he must obey the rules!
So, you want to meddle in this too?
How about...
Well.
Let's have some drinks.
Leave!
Are you deaf?
Piss off.
Stay and wait.
Wait here!
Wait!
I...
Thank you.
Get it off your dirty face.
I'll help you.
You are so beautiful.
Some drink?
I'm Li Shisi.
What's your name?
Mimi Guli.
You look different.
You aren't from Ashile Tribe?
I am a slave sent to Ashile Tribe.
I only have the clothes for men.
Take them for now.
I'll get changed.
Okay, go ahead.
I'll wait you outside.
I finished.
What's in your clothes?
I...
I am sorry.
I..
I promise I will never steal!
I'll never do this again!
Please don't expel me.
I can do a lot of things!
You see, I can clean the house,
and I... I can do the laundry and cook.
I can do anything, see!
And I am a fast worker.
Don't steal anything from now on.
I will take care of you.
Have some rest here.
This is my bed.
I'll be off for a while.
Don't answer even someone calls you.
Take a thread with the right.
Cross your hands.
Pass from the middle one.
Then take one with the left.
Very good.
Flip it.
You want to play this.
Li Leyan, are you stupid?
Look at others' work, and tell me what you've done!
You really piss me off.
I... I just want to unfasten the threads.
If you can't finish, no sleep tonight.
Are you sent by God to ravage and challenge me?
I am so mad.
Come on.
Anyone helps her!
I am so confused.
You've learned for days, and what have you got?
Who?
What are you doing?
I am doing housework.
You did all these?
If you don't like others help you organize your stuff,
I won't do it again!
I am sorry.
Don't throw me out please.
It's her!
Li Shisi, you can't leave this woman here.
What if I insist on keeping her?
Are you going to kill her?
It's not necessary.
Just throw her out.
I beg you.
Don't throw me out.
If I can't stay here, I will be eaten by wolves.
Even if I can manage to escape,
if the Great Khan finds that I'm an escaped slave, I will be killed.
Please.
You talked too much nonsense.
Go.
No!
You...
Are you a dog?
Why did you bite me?
You...
Enough.
Sun.
Tegin.
Could you give me this slave?
You may leave.
According to my rules, it is bad to have things with ears and mouth.
Since I am the one who work for Tegin,
I will manage my people properly.
You don't trust me?
I'm leaving.
I... I was bitten for nothing.
Are you fine?
Did you catch a cold?
How about I get you some Kumiss?
Just a second.
Sun.
Though you agreed Li Shisi to be your counselor,
you shouldn't trust him unconditionally.
Why?
We don't really know him.
I do know Shisi.
And he isn't from our region.
Shisi is now.
But the people from the Central Plains are full of tricks.
Sun, I don't mean it.
How are you?
I'm fine.
Let's have some warm soup.
It's good for health.
Why is the soup only for me?
How about yours?
I'm not hungry yet.
Have it now.
You go first.
I don't have an appetite.
When you finish it, get some sleep.
The bed is small, just put up with it.
Don't worry.
I'll sleep on the ground.
You should go to bed early.
It's good for your recovery.
Whatever.
But you don't have to be alert.
I won't hurt you.
Mom, don't leave me, mom!
Mom.
My mom.
Mom, please come back.
I'm so cold.
Buzhen, don't move.
Buzhen?
Who is Buzhen?
Li Shisi, I'm coming.
Not a good time.
Please wait.
Wait.
Hey, you!
Wait!
Stop!
Stop! You!
I've got something to tell you.
I've got things to warn you too!
Dare you walk around camps again!
Don't go to Sun Tegin's place.
What's wrong with you?
Don't come closer.
Are you going to bite me again?
I warn you just to stay there.
Otherwise, I won't be nice.
I really have something to tell.
As I am living with Counselor Li, the food isn't enough for us.
You must prepare more for us.
Don't bother me!
Go and find your Counselor Li.
Time for a meal!
Right.
Come on.
Have more drink.
Drink!
Have more, more!
Why are you here?
Counselor Li is ill.
He shared with me the last food we had.
We need something to eat!
For every tent, food quota is set.
You've taken yours.
No more for you.
Get out of my way.
You...
The mutton will be ready soon.
Have a seat.
By the way, do you guys like to use this?
I used branches to make a pair.
Hope you'll like it.
Do as locals do.
I don't use it anymore.
But I like your present.
Thank you.
In return, do you want anything?
Me?
Is it Buzhen really from your family?
Do you want to be free and go back to your family?
My family has been invaded by Ashile Tribe.
People died, or left.
I don't have any family members.
So, I'm grateful for staying with you sincerely.
So the same to you.
The same?
Are your family...?
Yes, they are all dead too.
They were killed by the enemy.
Forget all these worries.
Now that we have met each other, it's truly destiny.
From now on, I am your family member.
Here, take the big one.
I'm so tired.
Almost done?
How about taking a break?
I agree.
So tired.
Me too.
Are you tired?
Don't you know tomorrow is due day?
Have you finished the work?
If you can't finish it, just get out of here!
Go back to your work!
Ms. Zhang?
Don't bother me!
Li Leyan!
Did you do it on purpose?
Look what you did!
Get out!
Get her out of here!
Move!
Quick!
Get out!
You! Get out!
Kick her out right now!
Out!
Leave here!
Do you think Li Leyan is a real fool?
How can she be so silly?
Right, so much trouble.
Finally we finished Mr. Hu's order.
Let's have some rest.
My neck hurts.
Why is she here?
Right, why?
Why didn't you leave?
Why?
Ms. Chai.
My sincere apology.
Please give me another chance.
Please!
Ms. Li, you're so determined.
Here, I do need someone like you!
Well.
Is that what you expect me to say?
Just act nice, then be a free-rider?
You're daydreaming!
Right.
Later, I will meet with Manager Hu.
I'm begging you.
Just leave.
We don't have room for you.
Find elsewhere to bother anyone else.
Why are you crying?
Look at them.
They've worked overnight just because of you.
They want to cry too!
Yes.
Tears can't give you money.
You need to work hard to make a living.
If I were your mom, I would die already.
Leave here now.
You'd better find a tree and get hanged.
People like you are nothing good for society.
Only a waste of food.
Well.
Is she alright?
Won't she commit suicide?
Who can tell?
Why are you looking at me?
If she has the courage, it's still a good ending for her.
She is a loser.
Good for nothing in the world.
Alright, girls!
Get some sleep.
Right, so tired!
Let's go.
Go to rest.
Have you heard it?
The slave of the counselor kicked Mu Jin out of anger.
Really?
True!
This slave is bold.
Mu Jin is so weak.
She got something.
Poor Mu Jin.
He was humiliated.
Smell good?
Why does it smell so good?
My kid likes it very much!
Mimi Guli.
Are you going to wash your man's clothes?
Yes.
I...
Well, Mimi Guli.
We've heard you kicked Mu Jin.
He is the counselor.
Hope he didn't bother you.
Not at all.
Dare he bother me!
What a relief.
Go to wash.
Yes, right.
See you then.
See you.
Take your time.
What's wrong with you?
Pick it up.
I won't.
You and Li Shisi have humiliated me!
Look at you.
Now you seem easy and relaxed.
It is because you're weak.
Watch your tongue!
Right, you're so weak!
It's you.
Dare you say it again!
Who is weak?
You!
You hurt me.
You're a bitch.
No, it's you!
You!
You're shrew!
It's you!
You and Li Shisi are evil-minded.
Who?
You two.
How dare you scold Shisi!
You can't kick me.
Too far.
You can't.
Bastard!
Why did my heart beat so fast?
Mu Jin, are you a fool?
She is with Li Shisi.
What are you thinking about?
Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Changge.
It is said that when people get hanged,
their tongues will become so long.
If I find you in dreams,
will you be scared?
Too much bullshit.
Do you still commit suicide?
By doing this, you can be hanged.
What you did can only exercise your neck.
My husband, years ago, thought he couldn't take care of our family.
So he hanged himself to end everything.
Is your life so worthless?
Why are you going to kill yourself just as you're told?
If you really want to die, nobody can stop you.
But if you want to live, nobody can block you as well!
You should rely on yourself.
Get it?
Well, well.
It's alright.
Alright. It's alright.
My words were a bit harsh.
I am sorry.
Thank you, Ms. Chai.
Manager Hu, check out this new pattern.
Come, come here.
Pattern from the West.
It's really popular.
Right.
Very nice.
Look at it, this embroidery.
There are golden threads.
Look at the stitches.
How tight!
Right.
Good.
This is your order.
I've heard Ms. Chai's blankets are smooth.
Why aren't the stitches for my order smooth at all?
We could have done better if you give us much time.
Would you take it please?
Right, please.
Well.
Who made this?
This?
Well... I told you not to follow me.
It's her work.
Manager Hu, it's her work.
Right, Ms. Li.
Did you make this?
Yes, it's me.
Perfect.
How wonderful!
I'll take it.
Miss.
Could you make more?
I'll buy all of them.
With a good price!
As long as you do, I'll buy the clothes all together.
This girl is our embroider.
As for this handkerchief, as long as the price is good,
you can have as many as you want.
Deal!
You can name the price.
You're great.
Here, take a date.
Take it.
Take two.
Just take them.
Why did Tegin invite me to have grilled mutton leg tonight?
Your slave had a fight with Mu Jin becasue of this.
You're also my counselor.
I hope they feel I've treated you fairly.
Have you grilled mutton legs for Mu Jin?
No.
It's my first time.
When I was a kid, my father grilled it with me once.
I was determined to grill my own.
It ended up a great mess.
All were burnt.
Then for the burnt part, my dad ate them all.
Later, I learnt how to grill.
I don't want to fail him again.
I didn't expect there's such a story between you and your father.
When I was little, my father still cared about me.
But afterwards...
Let's move on.
Tell me about your father.
I have nothing to share.
He was very busy.
I see.
Because he was the crown prince.
It's normal that he was busy.
How did you know?
In Youzhou you had access to the Governor Mansion,
I knew you were privileged.
Later, I heard they called you Princess Yongning.
Then, I've realized everything.
Since you knew who I am by then, why didn't you reveal my identity?
Is it for taking advantage of me?
Right.
I used you.
I suffered a lot because of you.
I saved you in Changan, Youzhou, and Shuozhou as well.
Now we are on the prairie.
I am grilling a mutton leg for a slave like you.
I've made full 'use' of you.
Well.
Did you forget everything?
No.
Take it.
Anyway, I'm regarded as dead in Tang.
I have nothing to be afraid of.
From now on, I'm not Li Shisi.
My name is Li Changge.
I like this name, Changge.
Changge.
♫ Which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into an eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
What's she doing?
Does it mean she'll commit herself to me?
It's already late.
I'm at least a man.
Is it appropriate?
Hey.
Changge.
Changge?
What happened?
Why are they so close late at night?
Mr. Shisi, what happened to you?
I have no idea.
All of a sudden.
Are you sick?
Have some rest.
Blood?
Why is he bleeding?
Mimi.
Let me keep you warm.
What happened to him?
Did he get hurt?
No, don't worry.
He's fine.
He... He looks awful.
As I said, he's fine.
But, he looks like he's dying.
He is hurt!
I told you he's fine.
But he's...
What does it mean?
Really?
I told you so.
You're treating her differently.
Did you know that she is a woman?
You're not frank or honest anymore.
Changge is weak.
We need to treat her with a lamb.
Changge?
Her name.
So Mr. Shisi's real name is Changge.
How many secrets did you hide from me?
Tell me more.
Sun.
I thought you're a man.
I've even decided to marry you.
Why are you laughing?
Don't laugh.
I'm really upset.
Mimi.
You can still be my family member.
There's nothing different.
But still it's different.
How so?
I think it's not because you're good at the disguise.
You really don't treat yourself as a woman.
In this world, men need to fight and protect their domains and women.
Whereas, women are responsible for fertility
and protecting the senior people and the kids.
But you use men's ways to fight with them,
while using a body of woman.
What's in your mind?
I have no ideas as well.
What makes a man?
What makes a woman?
I've never really thought of it.
My masters are men.
Manage the country by making policies,
and protect it by leading armies.
They are big figures with great talents.
But what's the difference between me and them?
My father's wife and concubines are women.
They are in the finest dresses and look so gorgeous.
They are considerate and attentive.
But what does it matter with me?
Anyhow, you should rest at home for these days.
Don't suffer with them in the wild.
One more thing.
Since you've lied to me, your name can't be Mr. Shisi.
My name is Li Changge.
Li Changge.
So, did Tegin Sun know this secret already?
Then he's keeping it for you.
Does he fall in love with you?
Nonsense.
He thinks I'm useful for him.
So he cares about me a little.
How do you feel now?
You'll feel good to keep the underbelly warm.
What are you waiting for?
Move it!
To carry the wool is the easiest task.
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
What are you waiting for?
Come and help me!
I'm coming.
Be quick.
Look at the wool.
It gets everywhere.
Take it off!
And here.
Look at your head.
Wool Yan.
You got the wool everywhere.
Wool Yan, are you really stupid?
I just asked you to carry the wool.
Look at what you've done.
Ms. Chai, I...
Look at your hair.
Oh my.
Seriously.
Look at you.
This fool knows nothing.
How can she live like this?
Right.
Thank you!
You're my saviors.
Thanks to your help, I can make it through.
It's the first time I heard that title.
She is not referring to you.
Think about your poor salary.
You're not valuable at all.
Not valuable?
Our wool fabrics are for the use of the government offices.
They might even become the carpets in the palace.
You've worked so hard,
but they might not cherish every stitch you made.
Nonsense.
Those in the palace don't bother by food and clothes.
They won't know how much hard work behind.
The god is fair.
The royal family is supported by the people.
They'll get whatever they want.
So, they need to take the responsibility to protect us.
For us, though we're poor, it's fine if we can feed ourselves.
Am I right?
Yes, indeed.
We just mind our own business.
If we can do, just do it.
If we can't, then sleep.
For the royal members, they won't sleep if they fail.
All we want is the little salary every month.
Indeed.
Mind your business.
Don't skip this question.
Ms. Chai.
- Right.
- Go back to work.
When was the last raise?
Stop. Answer me about my salary.
Let's talk about it?
No raise is fine.
But give us some seasame cakes.
She's right.
Stop.
Stop there!
Leyan, I'll find you!
Go.
Go!
Mimi.
You are a woman.
Don't work so hard.
From now on, you can ask me for help.
I'll help you carry the water.
Don't look down upon me.
You see.
Be careful.
My clothes.
Don't take...
What's wrong? Too heavy?
No...
My foot.
You're bleeding.
I'm so unlucky.
Who left the nail here?
I'm fine.
Don't be frightened.
Go back first.
Let me take some break.
I'll bring you home.
Leave things here.
Be careful.
I'm fine. I mean it.
Take it slow.
Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
You just got better a bit.
Don't get sick again.
Take it easy. I'm not that weak.
Save it later when it gets colder.
You've done nothing for me so far.
I don't bargain with a loss.
Be relieved, Tegin.
I'll finish three promises for sure.
Do you have anything to demand today?
I just passed by after patrolling.
Alone?
Where is your slave?
She's washing clothes.
She has a good life, as she met a master like you.
We aren't master and slave.
We are friends who care about each other.
In a lifetime, people around will leave one by one.
To trust the new, and farewell to the past.
These are difficulties in life.
I feel luckier than her.
So lucky that I met with someone I care about.
Me too.
Tegin, go for patrolling.
Otherwise it'll be too late.
How about joining me?
You don't know much about this region.
When the night comes, I'll take you somewhere.
But I wonder if you have the gut.
Why not?
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter ♫
How beautiful!
I found it when patrolling.
Do you like it?
It'll be my last time to see fireflies this year.
We can see them again next year.
Who knows where we are then.
Will we be available to see fireflies again?
If you want to see them next year,
just tell me and that's it.
Wherever I am, I'll keep my promise.
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
I don't think I can make it.
Besides, like fireflies, such wonderful creatures are ephemeral.
Why shall we expect them?
♫ It is sleepless ♫
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad