ALL LOCATIONS, CHARACTERS,
ORGANIZATIONS, AND INCIDENTS
DEPICTED IN THIS DRAMA
ARE ENTIRELY FICTITIOUS
But could you not teach me?
Not teach you what?
How to break up.
You can teach me everything else,
but could you not teach me that?
Can you just…
like me?
Please.
Please, Ms. Oh.
Why are you crying?
You're breaking my heart.
I'm sorry for breaking your heart.
I can't believe
you're apologizing right now.
Go ahead and cry. Cry all you want.
EPISODE 14
I wasn't trying to avoid you.
I was going to get Su-bin for you
because it seemed like
you had been waiting.
I keep embarrassing myself
in front of you.
By the way, how did you end up
meeting Su-bin?
I'm sure Su-bin will tell you but…
I see.
You did a good job.
Sometimes, I think to myself
that it'd be nice
to have a certain type of friend.
But that means I feel like
I'm lacking something.
I think I was looking back
on my childhood years
hoping I also had someone who would
stand up for me like I did for Su-bin.
But of course, I'm not proud
that I almost smashed her car.
I thought I was a bit more mature.
Or maybe I am, considering the fact
that I didn't throw the brick.
Anyway, you shouldn't have
gotten the wrong idea and cried.
I was scared I might lose you forever.
Is your finger okay? Is it bad?
Well…
I'm not allowed to drink for a week.
-That's bad.
-It really is, isn't it?
Can't I even have a sip?
I don't think so.
You should say it's okay.
It's not okay to say it's okay.
I also haven't done this before,
but apparently,
it's normal for couples to fight
and make up awkwardly like this.
-Does that mean--
-It means we're okay now.
From now on, I'll try harder
to get rid of all the obstacles
so that we'll only have problems
between ourselves.
How? Are you going to get disowned?
-That's a bit too much.
-How so?
That's a bit too much.
I'll make sure you only get disappointed
because of me.
It's not like I always get disappointed,
you know.
I'll come to you once I make sure
no other person has the power
to cause any problems between us two.
Does that mean we can't meet until then?
We weren't able to meet that often anyway.
I was just worried
that someone might take photos.
"Photos"?
I see.
That just gives me a better reason.
I don't want us to spend
an uncomfortable time together.
Then why don't you come over
for some ramyeon?
We'll have the house to ourselves.
All of a sudden?
This stuff always happens unexpectedly.
I haven't been on a bed in a long time.
Does Yeong-hwa make you sleep
on the floor?
-In this cold weather?
-He lets me sleep on the sofa.
He's just like you.
Do you always have to talk back like that?
Aren't you going to respond?
Hello?
You told me not to talk back.
Gosh, you know that's not what I meant.
Seriously.
Come to think of it,
I don't think I ever wanted a certain type
of person to be there for me.
I see.
I just wish
you were with me, Ms. Oh.
Who do you think
will end up living with me forever?
Me?
No, that's not what I meant.
Don't get too ahead of yourself again.
No it's me. Myself.
-Oh, I get it.
-And you. Yourself.
You should've been specific.
So
you need to take good care of yourself
and fix yourself
whenever something breaks.
I really want to get along with myself.
I don't want to love myself too much,
but I don't want to be
too hard on myself either.
I think it's important to work hard
on keeping a good balance.
I want you
to love yourself a little more.
That's how we can keep
a long and healthy relationship.
Okay, I will.
I'll try.
You always try so hard.
How about
a kiss
to lighten the mood?
Oh, right.
When are we going to eat ramyeon?
My gosh.
What's the matter with you?
Are you hungry?
You invited me over for ramyeon.
My gosh.
I totally forgot how lame you were.
NO MINORS
Will she accept my apology?
I feel like she won't.
I should have listened to her.
Gosh, I didn't even get to
give her a gift.
Ms. Seo, I'm working really hard
on my painting.
Isn't that a given?
She replied. I thought she'd ignore me.
Don't talk to me about anything else
other than the painting for now.
If you miss me,
just look at the photo you took last time.
You didn't come home last night.
-Yes.
-Where…
Seon-gyeom.
Okay.
Are you not coming home again?
Where will you be… Seon-gyeom!
Does he also not want to talk to me?
JUST WHEN THE VIEW OF THE SCHOOL
WAS GETTING BORING
Back then, I didn't even
get to talk to her about art.
But at least that's allowed now.
That's a relief.
Seo Dan-ah speaking.
I know I'm in front of a vending machine.
What do you want?
Nothing.
Then will you at least let me
take a photo of you?
You won't let me talk to you about art,
but I need inspiration.
Do whatever you want.
Okay.
Just stay natural. Don't turn around
even if you hear me taking a photo.
You're so annoying.
Take a good photo.
I should've asked her
to look at the camera.
It's fake. She wasn't born today.
She was born before Myeong-min,
but Dad only registered her birthday
after he was born.
How did he know about the birthday party?
And how did he know she was at my school?
Is it because he follows me?
He knew just by looking at this?
He's unbelievable.
Thank goodness it was Tae-woong.
I'm a complete lunatic.
I was so thoughtless.
Let me delete this first.
Let's regret what I did inside.
It's freezing out here.
I didn't know you had an appointment.
He didn't answer my calls, so I just came.
I see. He's not in his office right now.
Should I leave a memo?
No, I'll come back next time.
Honey, what brings you here?
Will you please excuse us?
I need to talk to her for a moment.
Thank you.
Don't you think it's rude
to show up unannounced like this?
What do you mean it's rude?
Don't be so cold.
That darn punk is the one who's rude.
How could he cause a scene
at the golf course?
It was a very important gathering for me.
I guess my son is doing well these days
seeing he had the energy to cause a scene.
Did you come here to tell on him?
Shouldn't you talk to him?
All you ever do is work.
When is your movie shoot going to end?
You really need to take it easy.
How can I when I keep getting offers?
And I want to play every role that I get.
My schedule's fully booked
until the end of the year.
You'll have a lot of events to attend
from now on.
So try to meet me in between.
Free your schedule
so that yours doesn't overlap with mine.
Don't you know what my job is?
I can't just free my schedule.
You and your darn acting job.
I'm trying to make you the first lady!
My life isn't yours.
I worked really hard
to get to where I am now.
And I'm busting my ass
to maintain my position in this industry.
I'm the star of my life.
I've always been the star,
but you keep treating me like I'm a prop.
Do you know that?
How is your life yours?
-What?
-How can you be so irresponsible?
Why did you marry me?
And why did you have kids?
-Then why don't we get divorced?
-You darn little…
Listen, Ji-woo.
Do you think you can get a divorce
just because you want to?
Get to your senses, Ji-woo. Please.
I really want to do a good job.
I want to do the best job ever.
I've always been great,
but this time,
I really want to be outstanding.
Let's do this.
"Code Name Candy."
A wild rose. Drug dealer.
Is she an undercover agent?
Do you want some?
Who are you?
Who do you want me to be?
"I don't care who you are.
I want to go with you.
Please take me with you."
Go inside.
You must be new.
How old are you?
You speak so casually for someone
who doesn't know my age.
I'm eight.
I'm seven.
I'll talk casually now that I know.
Okay, my little angels.
It's time to give out food.
Hey, teach the new girl how to do her job.
I'm already busy with mine.
But I just got here.
You want me to work already?
My little angels, just do as you're told.
Oh, right.
-Is she new?
-Yes.
Say hello. He's going to be your boss
starting from today.
He's Anthony.
I found her today.
His name's Anthony.
You're quite bold to laugh
in front of your boss.
I won't laugh.
That's his real name.
It's An Son-hwi.
-Ms. Oh, open the door.
-What?
Who is that?
I'm cold. Open up before I break the door.
Ms. Seo, you're not allowed
to come to my house.
And don't say no one's ever
said this to you.
I'm so frustrated that I can't sleep.
-Are you busy?
-Yes, I need to read a script.
"Code Name Candy?"
My gosh, just come inside.
I told him he's not allowed to talk to me
about anything personal,
and he's been ignoring my calls.
So you're angry at him
for listening to you?
He used to be so clingy before.
Why is he ignoring me now?
I don't get why you came here
if you weren't going to listen to me.
I came all the way to the neighborhood.
I couldn't just head home.
He doesn't seem to be home though.
-You're scaring me.
-Maybe he went off the grid
to add finishing touches to his painting.
This is why I hate so-called artists.
They see themselves on high horses.
Yeong-hwa works alone,
so you can understand his confidence.
Maybe he's upset
about the whole birthday debacle.
There was no debacle.
I just told him to clean up.
It wasn't Yeong-hwa's fault though.
Of course, it was.
I specifically told him
no birthday parties.
Why must he always
follow your order though?
I may ignore others,
but others shouldn't ignore me.
Unbelievable.
Judging by your words,
it's like you see Yeong-hwa as an object.
You are no different.
But he is mine. He wanted to be.
He's cheesier than I thought then.
Yeong-hwa…
is not some object.
This has probably been
your attitude all along.
You should apologize to him first.
And how do I do that?
-Do what?
-Apologize.
I never had to do it before,
and no one ever told me to.
Are you boasting right now?
When was the last time I apologized?
I think I was seven.
Talk about feeling your blood boil.
Maybe it's due to the stress.
It wouldn't be that hard
to figure out where he is,
but what if I scare him again?
Then try not to be.
Yes, Mr. Jeong.
You just texted me? Got it.
Type in the address
that was just texted to me.
Hurry. We'll hit the freeway soon.
What the hell is going on?
You must still be hung over.
We'll stop at a rest area.
Hold on.
Did you bathe me and put clothes on me
while I was asleep?
It's not like you refused.
I only thought you were being kind.
You really are scary.
Exactly. I might scare him
if it's just me.
What about my work though?
I have your laptop
and the script you were reading.
Seriously?
What…
What the hell is this?
What about you? How dare you run away?
What? Me?
If you run away,
I'll have to break your leg
since I can't break your arm.
How sweet of you.
Yeong-hwa, she just threatened
to break a limb.
Take that off.
Here?
The hat. I can't see your face.
I see.
My mom got hurt,
so I had to rush down here.
She was stung by a bee.
By the way,
how did you know I was here though?
Hold on. How did you find out
about my parents' place?
Gosh, you seriously terrify me.
-Only now?
-I thought you'd be,
so I came with Ms. Oh today.
You're still terrifying.
The time it took you to drive here
is a waste for you,
so why are you here?
She must have hurried here
because she felt guilty.
He's the one at fault.
You weren't picking up. So what now?
Just a second.
Yeong-hwa, get back here!
Sure, Dad. I'll be right there.
Got it.
I need to head to the bee farm.
It's fine.
I'll wait here with Ms. Oh.
But I don't want to.
Don't bother me while I work
and spend some time together.
My love life you may mess with,
but not my job. I'll kill you.
No one's ever threatened me before.
You and all your firsts.
Are you kidding me?
Why drag me here anyway?
I needed an excuse.
For what?
Someone could be tailing me.
People in my world
actually do those things.
I'd have nothing to say
when accused of messing around
with a college student.
They'll accuse you
of knowing that it's wrong.
Perceptive as always.
You have it hard, don't you?
Now I feel bad for you.
So when will we head back today?
And where will we stay if we don't?
This proposal is the worst.
It'll be taken out.
Stop annoying me and say you have a plan.
Mi-joo, Ms. Seo!
Yeong-hwa, hi.
Let me know when you decide.
If you don't, I'll walk back to Seoul.
Get going then.
You're the first to--
Enough. Just go.
About four years ago,
we asked you to transfer to our team.
We meet again.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
It's what brought me here today.
Woo-sik has set notable records,
but we're worried about his future.
Is he looking for a team
that pays a salary?
We're aware that
there won't be a scouting fee
if he doesn't make progress in two years.
But please take a look
at his physical stats.
Right here.
He's healthy enough
to be just as good again.
I see.
I'll be honest with you.
We have an issue with one of our athletes.
Are you saying you need a story
to cover up that issue?
And an athlete
to fill in the gap for a while.
It's best to fight fire with fire.
If it's a salary he's after,
then we'll be more than generous.
It could better the image of the team.
You'll be the only team
that took Kim Woo-sik in.
We'll be more known for
taking in a whistle-blower.
People's views rarely change
once you're labeled.
Do I
remind you of my assault charge?
No, that's not what I meant.
Please just answer the question as is.
I remember you as a silver medalist.
You have been one for a long time.
And that's how Woo-sik will be remembered.
He's only a whistle-blower
among the people in this field.
The public sees him as a victim
who was kicked out from his team.
So the fact that you only want him
to fill in for someone
doesn't matter at all.
He can prove his worth
with his records and achievements.
All right. I'll talk to my bosses.
Thank you for hearing me out then.
I heard that Assemblyman Ki
is organizing a team.
Is that not an option?
I'm not sure he'll accept Woo-sik.
But he's a compassionate family man.
He never forgets his roots as an athlete
and helps athletes who need financial aid.
I'll get going then.
Sure.
-Take care.
-Thank you.
-Hey, Woo-sik.
-Seon-gyeom, how did the meeting go?
I've made them know you're out there,
so we'll weigh the options
when offers come in.
Sure. So when will you get here today?
I have another meeting,
so I'll be there once I'm done.
Got it. Take your time then.
Not if I want to train you.
Well…
There is no rush.
See you soon.
I'd like it to be more certain.
Right.
Send me the material via email, then.
Thanks for letting me see you.
I'm quite busy too, so I'll keep it short.
It's all right.
How about some tea?
I thought about it
as a mother with two kids myself
and figured that you should know.
Eun-bi has the yips.
YIPS, SUDDEN LOSS OF SKILLS
IN EXPERIENCED ATHLETES
-Really?
-She cried.
She seems to be under great stress.
So I wanted to ask you this.
Why don't you join our agency?
-But I'm not an athlete anymore.
-Not as an athlete, but as an agent.
It's been two years
since the agency opened
and we need an agent
to care for the athletes.
Eun-bi's condition
made me realize our need to even more.
And I'd like that to be you.
The agency's strong and we'll soon
send out a hiring announcement.
I have to say that this is quite sudden.
But you're not appalled or disgusted?
If that's all,
then I'd like us to work together.
Why waste your natural talent?
I'm not asking for an answer today,
so please consider my offer.
Got it.
A corner shop used to be there,
but it's gone now.
What else? Over there. That was…
Ye-jun's place. I mean,
that's where Ms. Dong used to live.
Meanwhile, I was born and raised
in the house you saw me at.
So you grew up in a pretty
and free-spirited neighborhood.
No wonder I'm pretty.
Your mouth is just as free-spirited.
I heard from Tae-woong that
you were born on a different day.
Sorry I got ahead of myself.
Sure.
I forgive you.
When's your real birthday then?
I'll throw you a proper party that day.
-I'm back to being angry.
-I won't fold on this matter.
When have you ever folded on anything?
Okay, no party then.
We'll just quietly celebrate it together.
You in?
You just know how to
shut me up, don't you?
My real birthday isn't for a while though.
I don't care.
The date will someday draw near.
Just like the distance between us.
Where should I sleep tonight?
What do you mean by that?
What do you think I mean?
That you have no place to sleep?
Should I book a room?
What…
You came here without
even booking a room first?
You're killing me!
Jeez.
I didn't have time to do any research.
Will you book me a room then?
Well…
This is a joke, right?
Yes, so don't let it kill you.
It's all right.
I don't mind being excited over it.
What did you find?
She was at some woman's house?
Who?
Someone pretty?
How did they seem?
Questionable?
Okay, got it. Keep an eye on her.
Sure.
Dad!
Why did you come? You're probably busy.
Please don't say that.
Nothing takes priority over family.
Have things
gotten worse lately?
This seems to be happening a lot.
It's not enough to kill me.
Even if it is my time to go,
I'll hang on until Dan-ah marries.
This isn't the time for jokes.
I mean it.
Damn.
You should live a long life, Dad.
Dad!
My youngest came
despite his busy schedule.
I cleared everything for the day.
I'll stay here by your side.
It'll be lonely to be on your own.
Sure. I'd get lonely.
My youngest is the sweetest.
Does Dan-ah know?
Sir?
Why would she need to know?
It's better to keep women in the dark.
Is she someplace dark?
Sir?
How is it that your Korean is still awful?
Never mind.
Anyway, I heard she's been fooling around
with some younger kid.
-You know, right?
-No. Sir.
I don't know.
Sir.
Pick one and stick with it.
Either use honorifics or don't.
You told me to be formal with you.
Sir.
Damn it.
Anyway, take care of Dad.
I need to get back.
Damn that charity running event.
Everything Dan-ah does is a nuisance.
All she does is cause trouble.
That reminds me.
I know you're the biggest idiot,
but I'm sure you know this much.
Who do you think your share belongs to?
Me?
Well…
The moment you carry out that right,
people will find out
that you're an illegitimate son.
You like being a K-pop idol.
And I'd hate to ruin
my little brother's future.
I wouldn't blink an eye, but still.
I'm going to let you be.
Here…
Always keep that in mind.
Got it?
All right.
I booked the best rooms I could find,
so save the commentary.
Don't worry.
I can pounce on you,
but I'll kill you if you do.
Why would I do that?
Worry about yourself
since Mi-joo will be upstairs.
-Wait, are we going to stay together?
-Yes, together.
That's right. Mom, please.
Come on. Just this once.
Let me stay at a friend's just this once.
Please. I have friends that aren't Ye-jun.
I won't ask you to pay for my work today.
It's now or never for me, Mom.
Mom, please. Just this once.
I knew she was crazy,
but not to this extent.
She even scared me at one point.
Since you're there,
it'd be nice to get some fresh air.
But I need to work.
The air is too cold to face alone anyway.
I miss you.
I know. What a bummer.
It sure is a bummer.
What can we do about it?
Isn't it obvious?
Since you can't be here,
you'll take a selfie and send it.
-But--
-Send it right away.
What on earth?
Who am I seeing?
Pretty, right? Use mine as reference
and take yours again.
I should at least
be able to tell it's you.
"No matter how lonely and sad…"
"I won't cry."
I see you're unharmed, Candy.
So, how's the situation?
Not good. It seems like Anthony caught on.
The man's pretty perceptive.
It's not good, then.
Terius, why are you sweating in the cold?
Do you have hyperhidrosis?
This kind of operation is a first for me,
-so I must admit I'm nervous.
-I see.
Then you most certainly
have hyperhidrosis.
Also, about Eun-bi's campaign ads.
Decline the cosmetics and jewelry ads.
-Unless we receive a new plan--
-Just the two of us?
Of course, I know it's your day off.
She's killing me.
You're on a date? So what?
You want to resign?
Don't be ridiculous. I'm hanging up.
-Ms. Seo.
-I'm busy.
Let's go out for a walk.
It's exhausting to watch you work.
Then don't watch.
The ocean is really pretty.
Prettier than you?
Not really.
You're finally looking at me.
You're looking at me
with those puppy eyes.
Take me out for a walk. Woof.
I haven't been to an ocean in a while.
What will happen to us
once I pour out my heart
into my drawing and finish it?
Then you'll be done.
Then…
can you give me what's inside you?
And what's that?
Your heart.
That's neither visible nor useful.
Why would you want something
that's intangible?
Fine, then.
I'll just take it myself.
And how will you do that?
I think I know where your heart belongs.
How would you know something I don't?
You keep making time to see me.
You're doing that…
because you can't control your heart.
That's how most hearts are like.
Yeong-hwa.
I've helped fulfill your goal.
So what's your dream?
Not breaking up with you.
I'll make that dream come true.
So help me out.
Are you asleep?
I'll pounce on you.
He must really be asleep.
Why aren't you sleeping?
I don't want to waste my time,
so I'm grabbing onto it.
Rock-a-bye, baby
On the treetop
When the wind blows
The cradle will rock
Drive safe.
What about you?
Shouldn't you go to school?
That question is long overdue.
Exactly. Why would he go
during the weekend?
He didn't come here during the weekend.
I came on Friday. I had no class.
I'm going tomorrow morning.
I have school and charity.
-I'll see you then.
-Did you sign up?
Okay.
-What's going on?
-Why?
Jealous much?
Give me a strand of hair.
Not the one on your shoulder.
-That's disturbing.
-What for?
Who knows if we are related?
That would be tragic.
It'll only be a DNA test.
Your father is away.
When can I see him?
He wasn't here last time either.
I have something to say.
You won't be for the time being.
He doesn't want to see you.
I'll come back next time.
Seon-gyeom.
Just apologize to him.
That girl too. Just once will be enough.
Are you saying
that this has happened
because I refused to stoop?
Had you done it just once,
he would've let you be for now.
But you didn't.
You brought this on yourselves.
WHEN HUNGRY, BANG
COULD YOU RECOMMEND A MOVIE
THAT'LL PUT ME TO SLEEP?
Can you recommend a movie
that'll help me sleep?
Shouldn't you ask me
how my trip was first?
I was taken hostage for the past two days.
Ms. Seo tends to enjoy doing that.
What?
Did you text me
so that you could side with her?
I'm not telling you any movies.
Then I'll just try to sleep.
See you in my dreams.
They're your dreams, not mine. Whatever.
DNA TEST RESULT
PROBABILITY OF PARENTAGE: 0,001
That's good.
At least we won't be linked biologically.
BASTARD IDOL
ATOZ
BASTARD 2
Can you please not call me?
Dan-ah, there are rumors about me.
"An idol group member is a bastard son
of a conglomerate."
Are you saying that this is about…
Why now?
The chairman is on a business trip.
But someone else is being suspected.
Maybe we're in the same boat.
Okay, hang up for now.
Come in.
-Ma'am, there are articles--
-I heard.
What are the details?
Is it just about Tae-woong?
They are only speculative,
and none pointed to Director Seo.
I'm the only one anxious here, aren't I?
If people take the chairman
for a promiscuous man,
it'll ruin Seomyung's image.
Once I take over, I'll be the one
who will have to get rid of that image.
Tell the headquarters to prepare
the press release.
One bastard is more than enough.
He really enjoyed being an idol.
What? Get ready for the afternoon meeting.
Yes, ma'am.
Is this necessary?
Until you get into university.
I thought you were busy?
And the gym is still closed.
This is your fault.
You should've been studying, not boxing.
And why boxing of all things?
You would've been against
any kind of sports.
-You can do it later in university.
-I want to do it now.
I know you'll just keep pushing it back.
Why are you supporting
all the other athletes but me?
This is a double standard.
Do you even know what that means?
It's when your standards double
and become worse.
This is exactly why
I'm telling you to study.
Get in. You'll be late.
I was shook up to see this on my way here.
They're going to post articles about them
having an affair?
They agreed not to post it
until it's been confirmed.
What should we do?
And we can't ask her directly either.
Why not? We can.
You better not.
If you do, I won't be your friend.
We were never friends to begin with.
She's been unstable these days.
You can't ask her that.
Then I'll call Seon-gyeom.
Would you like it if I asked you
about your brother's scandals?
I don't give a rat's ass
about whom he's dating.
Could this be why
she broke down last time?
Bastards, love affairs, and even assault…
Do we need an exorcism?
-That might be a good idea.
-I beg to differ.
Mr. Jeong, look for an exorcist.
We must do that.
I wonder if he's getting rid
of the obstacles.
He wouldn't beat him again, right?
He's already so fragile.
When will you send me your selfie?
Or will I see you in person tomorrow?
Would that be possible?
Have a good run tomorrow.
I'll do the same.
You can do it, Oh Mi-joo.
Hello, sir.
Your father wants to see you tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
What time exactly?
I have to lead a track and field
tomorrow afternoon.
He'll send someone else instead of you.
Tomorrow may be your last chance.
SEOMYUNG CHARITY MARATHON
Why would you run yourself?
I'm glad it's an afternoon run.
It's less of a burden.
Whoever scheduled this did a terrific job.
Sorry you can't run with Seon-gyeom.
I told you that's not why I'm here.
And can you stop talking
as if he's still your athlete?
Earphones? You seem quite relaxed.
Someone will be accompanying me.
You'll be on the phone with him?
-You're really something.
-Hello, ma'am.
-Hello.
-Hi.
-I'll see you later.
-Okay.
-I heard you visited many times.
-I did.
I had something to say.
Chairman Seo Myeong-pil
will be here soon for a cup of tea.
I'll be done before then.
Stay until then.
You dug your own grave then
because of Woo-sik, hadn't you?
-Why didn't you run?
-Because I couldn't.
I assaulted
my juniors.
That matters now?
Of course.
You're helping the very kid
who ruined your life.
I was going to ignore it,
but I can't anymore.
Remember the track and field team
I was going to make?
I'll scout him under the condition
that no one else will.
And you too. As his agent.
Isn't that what you're doing right now?
But why out of the blue?
If my son is raising an athlete,
he should succeed.
There's a catch to this, right?
Formally apologize to the chairman.
That's all.
Can you give me your word?
This is the two kilometer mark!
-Mi-joo, where's Seon-gyeom?
-What?
Not sure. Maybe in the front?
-Water?
-No, thanks.
SEOMYUNG CHARITY MARATHON
Mi-joo, did you just arrive?
There's no one here, right?
It means you're lagging behind. Good luck.
You're almost there.
You can do it.
-Thank you.
-Keep it up.
You're almost there.
You can do it.
You can do it!
Ms. Seo.
How did she find me?
I'm not even surprised anymore.
What? Ms. Seo…
Ms. Seo, are you okay?
Ms. Seo.
Don't do that. My head's ringing.
Did I just…
You collapsed. I should call 911.
-I should call.
-Don't call them.
-I want--
-Then the medical center?
-Get on my back.
-My face.
-What?
-Cover my face.
Your face? Damn it. Grab my neck.
Did anyone see me?
Where's my phone?
No IV drip, no hospital.
But you're looking for your phone?
It's just tachycardia.
Hey.
Are you serious?
I can't just get any IV drip.
Where's my phone?
I should check with Mr. Jeong--
Okay, let me do it. Just lie down.
You better not tell anyone about this.
-If I get humiliated--
-Why would you be?
You're just sick, so why worry about that?
If you're sick, say so and take a rest.
Be quiet. My head's ringing.
I didn't talk that loud.
-Leave.
-No.
Mr. Jeong, Ms. Seo collapsed.
We're at the temporary medical center.
Okay.
What kind of life are you living?
What happened that day
was quite memorable.
I'm sorry for my rudeness that day.
A man should have a punch.
I heard you're looking after an athlete.
He's a former junior of mine.
He's rehabilitating due to injuries,
but he's indeed a rising star.
Once I form the track and field team,
they'll join us.
It's nice to see how close you are.
His job goes well Ms. Seo's.
I guess they're meant to be.
She's running that agency
just to kill time.
Nevertheless, it seems to be doing well.
It is a waste to just throw it all away.
Once they get married and he joins us,
it'll be nice to see him
take over the agency.
He's very responsible and hardworking.
-Goodbye, sir.
-Goodbye.
I thought an apology was enough.
Did I demand more from you?
What is this about my marriage?
I don't care who you date.
I can't afford to be concerned
about that anymore.
Do you mean I can date whoever I want
as long as I get married?
Running should be the one and only
useless matter in your life.
Grab this opportunity.
If you miss this chance,
you and Dan-ah will never be able
to get married.
-Father--
-Do you think your love will last?
It's bound to end anyway,
so I'm giving you the due date.
Can you please… Please.
I guess Woo-sik will forever train
without a team.
Then he'll disappear thanks to you.
This is my final act of kindness.
Will you abandon everything for love?
Or will you end it when the time comes?
Gosh.
I want to quit. I'm about to die.
You're doing fantastic.
You can take one more step.
Run.
Forget everything and focus on running.
You ran so well last time.
Was it because you were robbed?
Maintaining your pace
is very important when running.
You can slow down if you're struggling.
Just don't give up.
You can do that as an adult, right?
Can we have one more bottle of soju?
One more beer, please.
Okay.
-One more soju, please.
-Okay.
Your arms are
the most important when running.
Fling them backward
to get the momentum going.
That'll make it easier.
Loosen your shoulders.
-Please ring this up.
-Coming.
Excuse me.
-Do you need a bag?
-Yes.
What happened? Tell me.
How could you beat her up like that?
You should be grateful
her mother let this pass.
Or else, you would've been kicked out.
Why did you do it?
What was the reason?
Don't you know how serious assault is?
I'm excited to be running with you.
Come to think of it,
I don't think I ever wanted a certain type
of person to be there for me.
I see.
I just wish
you were with me, Ms. Oh.
You ran so well last time.
Was it because you were robbed?
No.
I'm running so that I won't be robbed.
SEOMYUNG CHARITY MARATHON
I completed the race, right?
I can't believe I did it.
I'm so excited.
Me too.
Is the race over?
Yes.
What about you? Did you finish soon?
Gosh.
They're so mean.
They could've waited for me.
But I did.
I waited
until I could see you.
This is my first time trying pork belly.
-You have my blessings for once, Ms. Seo.
-"Fair as milk," right?
From that film festival.
Ms. Yook didn't ask you
to break up with him too, did she?
They said I could date anyone I wanted
as long as I've married you.
How am I the only one not to know?
Why don't the three of us get married?
It will be much easier that way.
I can't believe this.
There's no telling what they're thinking.
Should we just go
kneel before her and beg?
Why? You've done nothing wrong.
Gosh, you're making me blush.
-Is this true?
-Gosh.
How dare they call my athlete
a gold digger?
We're collecting the malicious posts.
We'll do everything we can
-to see that they're punished.
-May.
This is just screaming, "I love you."
I love you, Ms. Seo.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs