[English subtitles are available]
Wh… What was that?
That loud noise just now...
Was that thunder?
That was a thunder spear.
What on earth happened?
Something must've happened
and caused that noise.
It's so... quiet.
Am I.... dying?
[Attack on Titan]
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Angels planning disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
[#75 Above and Below]
I told you that
we’d get together soon again for dinner.
It turned out exactly as I said.
Right, Commander Pixis?
I'm grateful for your quick response.
You prohibited the military from
making any resistance
and assembled all your soldiers
here in Shiganshina as we requested.
You left me with no choice knowing
you dosed people with that spinal fluid.
We might turn into Titans at any moment.
There is no better place for us to be than
here, where all civilians have been evacuated.
Moreover...
What else can I do while I’m held at gunpoint?
Please forgive me, Commander.
My son and I have had that wine.
Since when did you decide to betray…
There is no need to answer him.
Please forgive me.
Looks like the earlier you switch sides,
the better your position here will be.
That white armband you wear so proudly
is a symbol indicating you're a Yeagerist, right?
Then I'm guessing the red indicates those
who were forced to submit
after learning that they'd drunk
the wine tainted with spinal fluid.
And finally, the majority are fools like us
who drank the wine unknowingly,
so we are wearing black armbands.
It’s just like what Marley would do.
Didn’t Marley control your homeland
with the same method?
We’ve learned a lot from our enemy.
Including how to make new
enemies, as it turned out.
Aren’t you the ones who
refused to let us join you?
We decided not to trust visitors
who came in bearing tainted wine.
I don't even know if that was
a wise choice or a foolish one.
You people are both foolish and wise.
If you had trusted us and Zeke,
the world could have been saved by now.
Did you say the world?
Isn't your plan to put Zeke and Eren
together and cause a small-scale Rumbling,
so as to show the nations of the world
that they can't lay a hand on
this island for the next fifty years?
But that’d only save this island.
Yelena?
It's already too late. Zeke already
gave you enough time to think it through.
And in exchange for his mercy,
you tried to stab him in the back.
Zeke is a god who will save the world.
You will be punished for that.
So there’s nothing we can do but wait and see?
Would you like some tea?
Thank you.
Armin, can you get out of here
with your Titan power?
I can't.
I can only blow this town up.
Colossal Titan can't do
something that agile.
I can’t do what Eren did.
So why did Eren beat you up?
Can't you tell us already?
He hurt Mikasa with his words.
So I attacked him, and he fought back.
Huh?
He hurt Mikasa with his words? What did he say?
-Well...
-Stop it.
It's fine.
No, it's not.
Tell us how he hurt her.
Hey, that’s enough, Jean!
That means he already turned
into a total piece of shit.
He already lost sight of who he is,
to the point that he'd pointlessly hurt
the two people whom he used to care about most.
If he was still sane, I doubt he would
do something like that for no reason.
Maybe he had some sort of hidden motive.
Long time no see.
Heroes of Shiganshina.
It pains me that
we must reunite at a place like this.
Hey...
You're on their side, too?
Get us out of here!
You all put me under arrest and
dragged me all around the island.
Do you think I’d just listen
to you guys like that?
Just sit and wait here until
Zeke and Eren come into contact.
You...
Good for you, Yelena.
You must be pleased that
everything went well.
Through you, Eren moved
according to Zeke's plan.
You got your attack on Marley.
You’ve gained the Eldians’ support,
and you’ve taken control of the military
with that spinal fluid-infused wine.
Now you have the Eldia nation and
the power of the Founding Titan.
You can finally destroy Marley and
get revenge for your motherland.
That is the true reason why
you came to this island, isn't it?
We helped improve this island.
This primitive island was a century behind.
Huh?
It’s all because
you want to live a luxury life here!
Once you become the rulers of this island…
You got tricked and lost. That's all.
Griez...
Seems like you just got promoted
as Yelena's servant by betraying us.
You little rat!
Are you stupid?
You're the real traitor who
sided with the devils!
What?
You were smitten with some
devil-blooded potato-grubbing girl!
I will kill you!
Stop it, Niccolo!
You talked about that girl to me every night.
I was a fool for thinking you'd come back
to your senses after that whore died.
What the hell did you just say?
I will put it in a way you can understand.
That whore was the daughter of a de…
Yelena?
I apologize for his rudeness.
This island no longer needs
those who would curse you as devils.
And please believe me.
Our true intention is never as
hollow as taking revenge on Marley.
It is to sever the chains of hate from this world
and save not only Eldia, but Marley as well.
I will explain everything to you
without holding back.
Zeke's plan of saving the world...
The euthanasia plan.
But they're devils...
Why must this happen to me?
Hey, you brat who killed Sasha.
What do you want?
If you want to save Falco, work with me.
Work... with you?
How?
I want you to radio for help.
Lure out the spies
who've infiltrated the walls.
Don't move.
Gabi, stay quiet.
Ms. Pieck!
Quiet.
So, you are Eren Yeager,
right?
[Currently Shareable Information]
[Year 845, the first residential district in Paradis island that was reached during the operation to retake the Founding Titan.]
[For five years after the destruction of Wall Maria, the area became a Titan's habitation.]
[After the operation to retake the Founding Titan failed, the hole on the wall got blocked by Eren Yeager, and the condition of the area is unknown ever since.]
[For this operation, Cart Titan and Jaw Titan will use their high mobility to infiltrate the island.]
[To enter Shiganshina, the southern side of the island is this operation's first objective.]
Gabi.
Point that rifle at Eren.
Gabi!
Eren.
Take your hands out of your pockets.
What if I don't?
I will pull the trigger.
And I'll blow up your head.
Have you never seen that?
You won't even have time to transform.
So?
What are you waiting for?
If don't shoot me,
what’s your purpose of being here?
What if I refuse to take my hands out?
You won't know what will happen,
not until your brains…
No, I know
you won't shoot me.
You don't have the permission
to kill the Founding Titan.
Your order is to retrieve the Founding Titan
no matter what.
Even now, you still have to turn into
a Titan first before you gulp me down.
Right?
Ms. Pieck!
Gabi.
Do not pull that trigger!
If you breach such a severe military law,
your family in the internment zone would
have to pay the price alongside you.
Yes, I can't shoot.
I doubt I can eat you alive either.
Anyway...
Ms. Pieck?
You found my Titan's tracks I left
when I snuck in here, didn't you?
My plan was to get as near as I can
before you could react. I was lucky.
But there's another reason I couldn't shoot.
If you can use the Founding Titan, I figure
you might be able to defeat Marley.
You won’t go against the world
without any chance of winning, right?
But aside from the power of the Founding Titan,
what else do you have?
Ms. Pieck? What are you saying?
Gabi. Put the rifle down.
Then what do you want?
To free the Eldians from subjugation
by Marley and the rest of the world.
I want to get my family out of
the internment zone as soon as possible.
I became a Warrior so I can get my father, my one
and only family, a proper medical treatment.
My father survived,
but he'd been living in misery since
he learned that my tenure would end soon.
Before I die and leave him all alone,
I want to show him a brighter future
for Eldia with my own hands.
And to do that, I need to crush Marley.
I will help you with anything,
if that's what it takes to kill all Marleyan.
The mastermind behind
the attack on Marley was Mr. Zeke.
You too, Ms. Pieck?
What have we been fighting for?
I thought that if the world realized
we were good Eldians...
....someday... Eldians would be free!
Are you a traitor just like Zeke?
Gabi.
Are we Marleyans? Or are we Eldians?
What do you think?
We are.... Honorary Marleyans...
No, we're the Subjects of Ymir.
That is our inescapable truth.
No matter what we call us,
we are people who can become Titans.
Like what you saw in Fort Slava, someday,
the Titan power will no longer work.
In other words, Marley will be
done with us and kill us all!
No matter how you prove you're
a good Eldian, they will never let us free!
We must win our rights with our own hands.
Prove it.
If you're really going to join
our side, show us some proof.
I will tell you where my allies
are hiding in this town.
How?
Just take me to the rooftop.
I can show you where they are.
Fine.
Won’t be able to bear children…?
Yes. That is Zeke's euthanasia plan.
No more pain will come to this world
due to the existence of Titans.
Slowly... and peacefully.
No, wait. How can that be peaceful?
If the population of Subjects of Ymir
keep shrinking until it vanishes...
Only the elderly will be left
during this country's last years!
How can our country be protected by then?
You think all other countries
will just stay silent?
It will be just like what it has always been.
The Rumbling will act as a deterrent force,
so both the Founding Titan and the royal
family need to be maintained.
Fortunately, Queen Historia has
already been blessed with a successor.
Until that child passes from this world,
a few Subjects of Ymir must inherit
the Founding Titan.
And you think that it's fool-proof?
Fool-proof? Absolute?
No nation out there has such a thing.
All countries have their problems.
But there is one thing that's certain-
the great threat of the Titans.
The fact that two men stepped forward to put
an end to this history of blood and tears.
Zeke and Eren.
I don't know how many millennia
human history still has,
but will anyone who can accomplish
such a feat appear in the future?
Those brothers will be remembered as
symbols for thousands of years to come.
Just like we still talk about the ancient gods to this day.
Even after their death, they will shine
like the sun as the saviors of humanity…
Is something wrong?
I didn't know... they had
such a noble intention...
I'm so moved.
That's great.
I'm happy that you understand.
Yelena!
Please come right away.
We have intruders!
The enemy has infiltrated the base!
I’ve lost one man!
It's the one with the Cart Titan!
What?
But it’s said she betrayed Marley.
What's happening?
What's with the noise outside?
Does this mean I'm now officially
part of your group?
After you hand us the other
intruders, that is.
Until then, you and the kid will be cuffed.
If you transform into a Titan,
she will get smashed into pieces.
It's fine.
I'm sure she will understand soon.
So that small woman is
a Marleyan soldier?
She's on our side?
Hey there!
Umm...
Where's Falco?
Falco's here, too.
But he ingested some of Zeke's spinal fluid.
What do you mean?
Who knows?
Just that some of that wine
got into his mouth.
Could it be at that time...
Gabi?
It's my fault...
Again...
I see.
So you took control of the military
using Zeke's spinal liquid.
Do you know why Zeke has such
a unique ability?
Who knows?
Do you?
No.
No one knows.
Except for Zeke.
I always think that Zeke is a liar.
But four years ago,
I confirmed my suspicions.
Because when he saw you,
he told the truth for the first time.
"Please believe me."
"I understand you."
"Eren, I will surely save you one day."
I believe he'll tell you the secret of
his power because he wouldn't lie to you.
And maybe that secret...
...is connected to how to draw out
the power of the Founding Titan.
Oh my.
You shaved your goatee?
It looked great on you though.
Eren.
You shouldn't trust that woman.
She's too dangerous.
Yeah.
I don't trust her,
and she doesn't trust me either.
By the way, you are still not going
to use the Founding Titan's power?
Where's Zeke?
You will find out soon.
Show us.
Where's the enemy?
Over there.
What happened?
It started...
The Titans...
...are moving!
Mr. Galliard?
It’s not as easy as I thought.
Ms. Pieck? Didn't you betray us?
Gabi, you seriously think I would
betray my friends?
But you said we won’t have a future
even if we keep serving Marley.
Look.
I don't trust Marley.
I trust my friends whom
I fought alongside.
The signal is up.
Pieck and Galliard have exposed
that bastard's location!
That's the Founding Titan.
Time to get revenge for Liberio!
We will end him right here.
Come.
Reiner!
♫ In an instant ♫
♫ In an abandoned world ♫
♫ If you can’t fly, please tell him ♫
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes
I will be immortal ♫
[You've been waiting…]
[All this time…]
[From 2,000 years ago…]
[For someone…]
[Attack on Titan]