[English subtitles are available]
[All places, characters, firms and events
depicted in this show are fictitious.]
Hey.
Why are you sitting here?
Where's Ha-eun?
At my sister's place.
I need to ask you something.
Come sit.
Is there something
between you and Chef Ryu?
You're not like him, right?
I'm not like Han-seo.
Right?
But...
Shouldn't you keep your distance then?
When he contacted you again,
why didn't you ignore it?
You said he's a friend.
Because he is a friend.
Then you should've kept some distance.
That would've been best for me and him.
What happened in college?
You said something about making a mistake.
What did you do?
Honey.
It was literally a mistake.
What kind of a mistake?
If it was a mistake, you could tell me.
Why can't you tell me?
It's nothing. I'm not like that.
I said I'm not like that!
Why can't the both of you
just leave me be?
I'm not like that!
Then...
Do you...
Do you love me?
Honey, do you love me?
I love you.
[Episode 13]
The banner and
placard designs are confirmed.
What about the products and shopping bags?
The bags were delivered
to the hosting company.
I'm going to order the products tomorrow.
No shortages?
I've requested a hold-off,
but I'll check again.
-Okay.
What's a hold-off?
Oh, a hold-off.
We take the product off the list
so others can't order it.
Is it accepted all the time?
Not all the time.
-Usually...
-Mr. Ko.
Ask questions after the meeting.
We don't have all day.
Why fired up all of a sudden?
I want to join the KLAR Team.
I want to work under ABM Chae.
You have a good eye.
Okay then. Do your best, okay?
Okay.
That's BM Choi.
She's from the European branch, right?
Yes.
I guess she's taking over
the Europe TF Team.
What's the Europe TF Team?
Let's continue.
Okay.
Thank you for accepting this position.
I was worried that you might not
want to stay there any longer.
You promised me full authority
over this project.
So it wasn't hard to say yes.
I did that because I trust you.
I've read the team
management plan you sent me.
I can count on you, right?
The Chairman has high hopes, too.
Just get ready.
Make me a director
once this project is over.
Let's have dinner together later.
I'm sorry. I have a prior engagement.
How about tomorrow?
Sounds good.
Okay.
Working off-site?
[Yes, I'm away right now.]
[Weren't you coming tomorrow?]
Yes, but I got bored, so I came early.
When will you come back?
I'll just wait here.
[I have dinner plans, too.]
[Just wait for me at home.]
Okay then.
See you at home.
You can use fast delivery service
with our team code.
The delivery man will be in the lobby.
Okay.
Excuse me.
Ma'am.
Hello. You're Senior Yoon's mom, right?
Do you remember me?
Oh.
In the hospital.
The fruit basket guy.
Yes, I'm the fruit basket guy.
Are you here to see her?
She's not in the office.
Yes, I heard.
It's my fault for not calling ahead.
Are you leaving now?
Yes.
Maybe we'll meet again.
It was good seeing you.
Ma'am.
You don't have to give me a ride.
I'll pass by the place anyway.
You are not uncomfortable, right?
I'm good. I appreciate it.
Is off-site duty that frequent?
Senior Yoon?
She's always out and busy.
Does she do all the work by herself?
We have a lot of off-site work.
We have to go to stores and training.
Today, there was a shoot.
I didn't know until I worked here,
but there are so many tasks.
Also, Senior Yoon is good at her job
so everyone calls for her.
My Song-ah is that good?
Yes.
She's very well-known in this field.
She gets offers from other companies too.
She's always been ambitious.
She was never negligent, whatever she did.
She has to accomplish
what she sets her sights on.
She's always been like that
since she was little.
-Really?
-Yes.
She wanted to be the top one in her class,
so she had me sit with her
and studied all night.
Oh, it was so hard.
Why did she want me there
when she was the one studying?
She wouldn't let me sleep.
You know, I'm living by myself.
My parents and I live apart.
So I have to have dinner alone.
Would you like to eat with me?
If that's okay with you.
I don't want to eat alone.
Are you sure?
Song-ah did say she'll be eating out.
What do you like?
I'll take you anywhere you want.
There's a good BBQ house around here.
There's a Chinese restaurant
and an Italian restaurant here, too.
None of that.
The...
I forgot the name.
Hot pot?
I saw it on TV.
Do you know a good hot pot place?
Of course. I know all the good places.
Let's go to a hot pot restaurant then.
Okay.
Oh, that's nice.
I love soju.
Me too.
I love living in Europe.
But soju just doesn't taste
the same over there.
Pork belly, too.
Tell me when you're craving
this again before you leave,
I'll treat you.
Man.
It seems like yesterday
that you showed up as an intern.
Now you're sitting here with me.
How's work? Still having fun?
It's fun.
You're a strange one.
Work gets boring once you
hit your three-year mark.
But you still find it fun?
There's something
I've been thinking about.
What is it?
The work is fun,
but when I think about five
or ten years from now,
I don't see a huge change.
What I do and what
a general manager does...
They are not that different.
That's right.
Newbies like it because
they can be hands-on.
But the higher you get,
the less accomplished you feel.
It was the same for me.
You too?
Of course.
That's why I asked
to get assigned overseas.
Thank you.
-Enjoy your meal.
-Thank you.
This is the mild broth.
This is the spicy broth.
Which one do you prefer?
I'll go with the spicy broth.
The spicy one?
Okay.
-Here you go.
-Oh, thanks.
It's better if you eat it
with peanut sauce.
How is it? Do you like it?
It's good.
So this is how it tastes like.
Eat as much as you like.
Please tell me if you need more.
I'm sure you're popular
since you're so sweet.
I'm not sweet to just anyone.
Well...
It's because you're Senior Yoon's mother.
She's trained me
since I joined the company.
I've learned a lot from her.
So this is nothing.
You must be close with Song-ah then.
I think so. We're a trainer and a trainee.
Can I ask you something?
Is she dating someone?
Huh?
Are you okay?
Yes.
Yes, I'm okay.
So? Is she dating someone?
That has to do with her private life.
That's her private life.
You should eat this.
If it's overcooked,
the meat will become tough.
Let's eat together.
Yes. I'm eating, too.
[So?]
What was it like?
Did it help to be in Europe?
It might be a bit exaggerated,
but it was the best decision
that I've ever made.
It's new and dynamic.
Is it a lot different from here?
Everything is different there.
We're the top player here
but not over there.
It's hard just to get a spot
in a department store.
But we can get the best spot here.
So it was really a hard job.
But there's so much more
for me to accomplish.
And I learned more that way.
It sounds fun.
That's where trends start.
During the past few years
staying in Europe,
my views of how the market works
and the product development have changed.
When you showed interest last time,
I was hoping that you'd come to join me.
It's a good opportunity to grow.
What's done is done.
What if another opportunity comes up?
I need a color makeup expert on my team.
If you're interested,
I want you to take the job.
Is it too sudden?
I want you to think about it.
I'll give you enough time.
[You said five years?]
Yes.
One or two years to set things up.
And another year or two to settle down.
It'll take at least
five years to be stable.
You can let me know by next week.
Chew it over.
Also,
call me if you have any questions.
Thank you for the ride.
I should've paid earlier.
No, I wanted to treat you.
Thank you for eating with me.
Me too.
Except for my daughter,
nobody's offered to buy me
dinner in a long time.
I see.
If there's something else
you want, let me know.
We can eat together.
Again?
Why would we see each other again?
We might.
Your bag.
Oh, my.
You left your bag in my car.
Good grief.
I can't lose that.
No, you can't.
It's heavy. Here you go.
Thank you so much.
Sure.
Mom.
Huh?
Sweetie!
What are you two doing together?
I ran into her in the lobby.
I gave her a ride since I was leaving.
I see.
Thank you.
Get home safely.
Okay, Senior Yoon.
Let's go, Mom.
Give me your bag.
Bye.
-Goodbye.
-Bye.
Drive safely.
Yes, I'll do that.
Thank you.
Sure.
-Let's go inside.
-Okay.
Go home.
Yes, I'm leaving.
Okay, thank you.
Take care.
[Go.]
Oh? Ma'am!
Hi.
How have you been?
Isn't your appointment tomorrow?
Yes. I just came a day early.
You said you met him at the company.
Why are you so late?
Oh, we stopped to have dinner.
I didn't ask.
He was the one who suggested it.
Why is your bag so heavy by the way?
You're staying for a few days?
Yes.
You told me to take a break
from the restaurant.
I'm bored watching TV all day by myself.
Can...
Can I stay here for a few days?
Since when did you ask
before doing anything?
Do whatever you want.
What's that, Ga-young?
They're nail stickers.
You want to try them on?
Can I?
Sit. I made you one, too.
Maybe next time.
Why not? Let's do it together.
Huh?
How do you do this?
Well, I'll do it for you.
This is so easy and pretty.
By the way...
You know, that young man?
He's very kind, unlike his peers.
Is he interested in you?
I'll use this one.
Okay.
Please finish her nails.
Mommy.
Are you sick?
Hmm?
Do you have a fever?
I don't.
Then does your heart hurt?
Did Daddy make you upset?
What makes you think so?
Jae-young told me.
When I make him upset, his heart hurts.
Because he likes me a lot.
Since you like Daddy a lot,
your heart will hurt if he upsets you.
Yes.
Daddy made me upset.
You want me to punish him?
You?
Yes. A daughter always takes mommy's side.
You know I love you so much, right?
I know.
I love you so much, too.
I love you, Mommy.
I love you too.
[Senior Yoon Song-ah]
[Are you asleep?]
[Not yet.]
I didn't call because of your mom.
[She's sleeping now.]
She said you had dinner with her.
Yes.
Did she say anything else?
Why?
[I was careful,
but I might have let something slip.]
She's not suspicious?
She's suspicious of all the men around me.
Don't worry.
That's a relief.
How was your evening?
Did you have a good time with BM Choi?
Yes.
I did.
I guess she really likes you.
She's my role model.
She made me believe in this company.
Then she's my role model, too.
You made me believe in this company.
Introduce me to her later.
Okay.
Hyun-seung.
[Senior Yoon?]
I'm tired. I should go to bed.
Good night.
Okay.
This looks good.
You know the banner
has to go there, right?
Make sure it stands out.
Okay.
-Go.
-Okay.
Write that down.
Let's go.
Let's place some on the tables, too.
Do that.
Let's play on the light coming in.
Enhance that.
Since this is the entrance.
That's a lot so make sure
you're on top of it.
Products will be set up
on the day of the event?
Yes. It'll start at 6 a.m.
They said it'll take about two hours.
That's enough time to get ready.
Make sure you're on top of everything.
Okay.
Are you going to do
market research with him?
Yes.
Have fun training.
Go home after you're done.
Okay. See you on Monday.
Have a great weekend.
Bye.
There's a popup store for a new brand.
Let's go there.
Okay.
There's a good souffle pancake place here.
Souffle? Where?
You like it?
Not me. My girlfriend does.
Do you want my list of must-eat places?
I check them out for a hobby.
Yes, please.
Your card has not been registered.
Thank you.
Song-ah?
Sorry for the wait. I had to go to HR.
No worries. I just got here.
Here are the products you needed.
Thank you.
Wait.
I thought this might help.
See you later.
[Transfer Application for Europe Office]
What do you have to say to me?
Don't even think about apologizing.
I'm not going to accept it.
Yeon-seung,
I didn't mean to hurt you.
What did you mean to do then?
Were you going to keep deceiving me?
-Yeon-seung.
-Don't say my name.
I'm disgusted you acted like
you were a friend.
I was blind.
Stay away from me.
From my husband, too.
Wow, it looks good.
Hold on.
Try it.
It's good.
You don't even like sweet food.
It's good when I have it with you.
Let's go eat something you like next time.
After we're done with everything you like.
By the way...
This turtleneck.
Does it look good on me?
It does.
I love men's turtleneck look in winter.
That's why I wore this.
You said you like turtlenecks,
so I filled my closet with them.
Did I say that?
In passing, during an office dinner.
So what do you want to say?
My boyfriend looks good.
Okay.
What do you want to do together?
Like what?
I want to experience
all four seasons with you.
I want to see cherry blossoms in spring,
the ocean in summer,
the fall leaves in autumn
and the snow in winter with you.
For the next spring,
let's go see cherry blossoms together.
How about you? What do you want to do?
Whatever you want to do.
Be careful of what you say.
What if I want you
to stay with me forever?
See?
You are too honest as always.
If you're not,
you wouldn't be the Yoon Song-ah I know.
I love it when you say you like something.
You really mean it when you say that.
I'm reminded of that time again.
When you said you like me.
I was so happy then.
Say it one more time.
I like you.
I really like you.
You've got something on you.
Your beauty.
Stop it.
-You are here.
-Yes.
Why did you ask me to come early?
When did you start dating Song-ah?
Hey, I just got here.
Cutting to the chase right away?
It was pretty recent.
Look at you. Do you like her that much?
I feel like I've got the whole world.
That's what I feel.
Did you ask me to come early
just to ask me that?
Not just that.
I want to tell you about
the man I'm dating now.
He's Director Lee Jae-woon.
Director Lee Jae-woon?
The one I know? Chairman's grandson?
Yes.
I just found out recently too.
And that Lee Hyo-joo is his sister.
Does he know I'm your brother?
Not yet.
I wanted to tell you first.
Okay.
Hello.
What's wrong?
Keeping me out of the loop again?
What are you talking about?
Of course not.
You crept up, that's why.
I thought I saw a ghost.
I was caught off guard. Come, sit.
I warmed up your seat.
Is something wrong, Yeon-seung?
No.
How's the food?
My team's got a new intern,
and he told me about this place.
He knows all the good places.
It's nice.
Can we trust him?
I tried one of his recommendations.
It was good.
With who? Song-ah?
Song-ah?
Who's that?
Oh, well...
She's my girlfriend.
I've got a girlfriend.
Ji-seung busted me the other day
when she came by.
Really?
You really didn't leave me in the dark?
Why would I?
I always tell you two everything.
No.
You two have always been like this.
You're always like this.
You tell Ji-seung first all the time.
And you act like you don't know anything,
when you do know everything.
What am I?
You don't want to tell me anything?
Why?
Am I not as trustworthy as her?
You think I'll mess things up if I know?
What are you talking about?
That's not why...
Why do you treat me like that?
I'm your sister, too. So why exclude me?
Why is everyone making a fool of me?
I'm leaving. I don't like the food.
-Yeon-seung.
-Hyun-seung.
Let her go for now.
Why won't it come off?
Give me an excuse.
I've paid back whatever I owed you,
with my performance at work.
If that's not enough,
I'll pay you back in money.
Why didn't you tell me
you were in a relationship?
If I told you,
would things have changed?
-Of course...
-Of course what?
You think Hyo-joo would've walked away?
It was my choice.
I could have everything
if I chose Hyo-joo.
Much more than when I
pretended to be your friend.
But I was stupid.
I would've been treated
like a dog no matter what.
Thanks to you,
I'm not doing so bad for myself.
So I chose to be free.
Oh, really?
You never thought of me as your friend?
You know the answer to that.
Not even once.
From the very beginning.
That makes things easier.
I don't need your money.
Mark my words.
I'm going to ruin you.
Whatever you want to do,
I'll make sure you don't get it.
As you said, I helped you
to where you are now.
So I have the right to bring you down.
Don't show up in front of Hyo-joo.
Did you hear from Jae-shin?
Are you going to starve yourself?
You could seriously get ill.
Just let it go.
He's done with you.
He already moved on.
You met him, right? Where is he?
Come to your senses, Hyo-joo.
You want Grandfather to disown you?
I told you.
I can't live without Jae-shin.
The only thing I'm scared of
is not having him.
I'd rather die.
Even if you tried,
he won't see you anymore.
It's really over.
Bring him to me.
Now.
He has to say that to my face.
Tell him that.
I'm not eating a single bite
until he comes.
[KLAR Celebrates 20th Anniversary]
[Sales & Charity Event]
Did you get the stickers?
No.
Myung-jin.
You know how to use the cash register?
Yes, my parents run a grocery store.
I've used it since I was little.
Okay.
You must be better than us.
But you have to stay alert.
If you mess up,
it'll be a disaster.
Don't worry.
Manager Kwon.
We're missing the "Paid" stickers.
What?
Call Song-ah right now.
Okay.
What if she already left?
Hold on.
Oh, I have them with me.
I saw them lying around at the office.
[Thank goodness.]
[Where are you right now?]
We're at the parking lot. We'll head in.
Okay.
Hyun-seung.
The "Paid' stickers are in the paper bag.
Can you get that?
Okay.
[Transfer Application for Europe Office]
What is it?
Oh, that.
Let's talk about it later.
It's for whitening,
wrinkle treatment and sunblock.
It's been dermatologically
tested for sensitive skin.
I'll take this.
Oh, that one.
Just a second.
Here you go.
You can go to the counter to pay.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Please find me one of these.
Sure. Just a second.
It has high coverage but it's matte,
so make sure your skin
is moisturized before applying.
[KLAR Celebrates 20th Anniversary]
[Sales & Charity Event]
Nice.
What a hectic day.
Let's clean this up and go eat.
What should we have?
Beef.
Again?
Aren't you sorry for the cows?
Huh?
Why doesn't it line up?
What's wrong?
Mr. Ko.
Yes?
How did you enter the sales?
The inventory doesn't match what's left.
What? I thought I did it right.
Why? Is something wrong?
He might have mixed up
some of the barcodes.
What do we do?
We have to find the wrong data
and fix it one by one.
Open up all those boxes again.
I'm sorry. I'll stay behind and recheck.
That'll take forever.
It's a two-man job.
I'll stay behind, too.
Myung-jin,
didn't you say you have finals tomorrow?
It's okay. I'll finish this up.
Your finals are more important than this.
I'll stay with Hyun-seung then.
I'll help, too.
Just have the two of them do it.
They work well together.
Okay.
Song-ah and Hyun-seung. Thank you.
After you wrap it up,
go eat something good.
Let's go to dinner now.
Okay.
Use this to check things off.
-Okay.
-Thanks.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Did BM Choi suggest the Europe TF Team?
Yes.
Have you already decided to go?
Is that why you have that folder?
I haven't decided anything yet.
Why didn't you tell me about this?
This is more important to us
than that offer you got.
I wanted to get my head straight.
If I'm not going,
there's no need to
mention this and trouble you.
What if you decide to go?
Do I just have to accept
whatever you decide?
Of course not.
What is it then?
I already told you.
I'm not sure whether
it's the right fit for me
or if I could stay overseas for that long.
How long would you be gone?
Five years.
Five years?
Is it supposed to be that long?
It's a new project, so it takes time.
But five years...
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you sooner.
I'm sorry I talked to you
that way earlier.
I was just taken aback.
You have to make your decision
by the end of this week?
Yes.
I'll think hard, too.
Five years is really long.
But even if you go, we're not breaking up.
No matter what.
Bye.
Morning.
Have fun today, Ha-eun.
Okay.
Daddy.
You like Mommy a lot, right?
Yes.
Mommy is a very good person.
So hurry up and tell her you're sorry.
Mom's heart is hurting
and so my heart hurts too.
Okay.
I won't hurt her anymore.
See you later.
See you.
Bye.
[If I marry this man,]
at least I won't be
shouting echoes in the air.
No matter how long we live together,
we'll have to face each other.
[Yeon-seung.]
She seems genuine.
Unlike you.
How much longer will you deceive her?
Do you...
Do you love me?
What are you home this early?
What about the clinic?
What is this?
Open it.
[Divorce Agreement]
Honey.
The house and the clinic.
You can have them all.
You can raise Ha-eun.
I'll give up my parental right
if you want me to.
-I'll pay you monthly for child support.
-Honey.
I'll make sure it's enough.
-If you want more...
-You said you're not like him.
If you aren't, why are you giving me this?
I'm not like him.
Then what's this?
I don't want you to suffer.
I don't want to hurt you.
You don't want me to suffer?
Maybe you want to
run away and be guilt-free.
I didn't peg you as a coward.
I'm not suffering.
There's nothing to be hurt about.
So there's no need for a divorce, right?
[So...]
[She hasn't eaten anything yet?]
Okay.
Please keep an eye on her.
[Bring Jae-shin to me.]
[He has to say that to my face.]
[Tell him that.]
[Lee Hyo-joo]
[Make a clean break.]
[Don't try to soften it.]
I came to talk to you face to face.
I thought about where we went wrong.
This is the place where
I agreed to be with you.
I didn't hate the things
you could give me.
I got greedy.
But...
I couldn't accept your feelings.
I couldn't reciprocate.
You knew that.
That's why you were insecure.
And I pretended not to notice.
This is the end of the road for us.
It's better for you this way.
And for me as well.
Why is this better for me?
I need you.
You can't force your feelings on someone.
What else can I do then?
What do I have to do to get you to see me?
I'll do anything.
Tell me what I have to do.
Don't do that.
Find someone who accepts you
for who you are.
[Employee of the Month]
[ABM Chae Hyun-seung]
Wow, Hyun-seung.
You saw the company magazine?
You look good.
You don't look like a marketer.
You look more like a model.
Ask the PR Team for the original one.
They will give it to you.
Get that, frame it
and hang it up on the wall.
I was featured here too.
Hold on.
Where did that frame go?
I guess my wife threw it away.
Manager Kwon, can you sign this off?
Okay. Get that framed.
You look good.
[Lastly, what do you
want to achieve here?]
I want to create a beauty trend
that leads the domestic
as well as the global market.
Yes.
The best thing about joining this company
is that I found my role model.
Just like I found mine,
I want to become
a role model to my juniors too.
That's my personal goal.
Thank you.
That's a wrap for the interview.
The senior that influenced you
is ABM Yoon Song-ah from your team, right?
How did you know?
I have a feeling.
She gave an interview similar to yours.
[She said she wanted to
create her own brand.]
[That she wanted to grow.]
[I remember it because I was impressed.]
[Did it help to be in Europe?]
It was the best decision I've ever made.
It's new and dynamic.
[You know what?]
[I think you can grow a lot more.]
But to do that, you need new experiences.
[I'm not going.]
[I'm not going to Europe.]
Really?
You can do that?
You're still here?
Manager Yoo.
I left something here.
What's on your mind?
You want to get a cup of tea?
Are you torn about the Europe TF Team?
How did you know?
There are no secrets here.
Words get passed around.
Whether you go or stay,
whatever choice you make,
there will be regrets.
So choose what you will regret the least.
I hope you don't go.
Your dreams.
Your goals.
I know all of them
and I'm sorry to say this.
But I'm not confident enough
to let you go so far away.
So...
Don't go.
Song-ah.
I'm sorry.
I want to go, Hyun-seung.