[English subtitles are available]
[All places, characters, firms and events
depicted in this show are fictitious.]
Don't go,
Song-ah.
I'm sorry.
I want to go, Hyun-seung.
I thought about it a lot.
The more I thought about it,
the more I wanted to go.
I want it.
I want to try.
And I want to do it right.
The time I have with you right now
is precious to me.
But I think I'll really regret it
if I give up the chance.
I'm sorry for being selfish.
You really want to go?
Understood. Go then.
Let's do this.
Long distance relationship won't be easy.
But if we're focused on our work,
five years will go by quickly.
It's not like we won't see
each other at all.
We can video chat.
We can coordinate holidays too.
It's just five years.
Let's give it a go.
Thank you.
I promise
I'll try very hard to make this work.
I can do this.
[Episode 14]
You bought clothes for Ha-eun again?
She already has a lot.
It looked so pretty.
Thank you. She'll love it.
Did you come to give me this?
I wanted to see you, too.
Don't worry about the other day.
I was having a bad day.
We deserved it.
The man I'm dating right now
is Hyun-seung's director.
Really?
His girlfriend works there, too.
That's how I found out about them.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you sooner.
I won't make you feel left out again.
Alright.
By the way,
you look pale.
You didn't look well that day either.
Are you feeling okay?
I couldn't sleep.
Is something wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
I'm tired because I didn't
get enough sleep.
You don't mind leaving early, right?
Yeon-seung.
When you want to talk,
I'll always be here to listen.
I'm in your corner.
I'll see myself out.
[Main Conference Room]
Did you all see the transfer notice?
Song-ah will go to
the Europe TF Team today.
Things are hectic there,
so the transfer is very rushed.
We haven't decided on her replacement yet.
Hyun-seung.
Yes?
Do you want to work
with color makeup again?
Me?
You started in that part.
I'm asking you since there's a spot.
If you want, you can
take over from Song-ah.
In that case, we need
someone else to fill his seat.
I'll go to color makeup.
I feel like it's a better fit.
Hyun-seung, prepare for the handover then.
And Song-ah,
BM Choi wants you to
work for both teams this week.
Did you hear?
Yes, I'm aware.
I believe you can handle it.
I expect a smooth handover.
Okay.
When are we throwing
a farewell party for Song-ah?
We should, but Song-ah's so busy.
Let's do it when she's free.
Thank you.
It feels strange, doesn't it?
Yes.
The transfer is so sudden.
Shall we begin the meeting?
Okay.
Thank you.
Are you still thinking about
your mistake during the charity event?
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have volunteered to do that.
You paid the price for my mistake.
That wasn't that bad.
We face many unexpected challenges here.
What you did was nothing.
Also, there are worse situations.
Like a delayed new release
or a cancelled promotion.
Everyone's forgotten about your mistake.
So snap out of it.
You were proactive,
and that's what matters.
Don't get discouraged easily
if you want to survive.
Okay.
Thank you.
Drink your coffee.
Thanks for the coffee.
The coffee tastes terrible.
Don't drink it. I'll go tell them.
Wait.
Oh, this one's mine.
I'm sorry.
I saw this on TV and wanted to try it.
It's nice in Seoul.
I get to try all these things.
They have this in Chuncheon, too.
I can't go by myself.
Make some friends then.
Go take classes or something.
Hang out with your neighbors.
Okay.
By the way, what's the occasion?
You rarely call me out for a meal.
I'm being transferred
to the European branch.
I have to leave next month.
Europe?
You're going abroad?
For about five years.
That's wonderful, Sweetie.
You're not going to stop me?
Why would I do that?
You're going because you're capable.
Next month is pretty soon though.
Why the rush?
Can I really go?
I'm trying to change.
I feel bad for what I've put you through.
I'm not going to be unreasonable anymore.
I've put away your dad's letters.
And his pictures too.
Are you sick again?
Why?
You think I've changed because I'm dying?
I know how much you suffered.
The least I can do is try to change.
I'm going to try being a good mom now.
Can I stay in Seoul until you leave?
I promise I won't be a bother.
Suit yourself.
We should've eaten Korean food.
You'll miss it once you're there.
Let me know what you want to eat.
I'll cook it for you.
Okay.
I'll catch up with you later.
Ji-seung!
What are you doing here?
Hmm?
Oh, Director Lee?
Yes.
Ji-seung!
Oh...
Chae Ji-seung.
Chae Hyun-seung.
Your names are so similar.
I didn't even notice.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
I didn't want things to get awkward.
My brother learned about us
just recently too.
What are the odds?
I knew there was a reason I liked you.
By any chance,
did I mistreat you in any way?
I hope I was always fair to you.
Not at all.
Please treat me as you did before.
No special treatment.
It's more comfortable for me.
Still, let me know
if you're having a hard time.
I'll help in any way I can.
And...
Hope you help me out, too.
Yes.
Let's dig in.
Okay.
Enjoy.
Try this first.
This is their specialty.
Thank you.
I'll keep you updated about
the products in development.
That's the most important thing.
Okay.
Oh...
How was lunch with your mother?
What did she say when she heard the news?
She said that it's wonderful.
She wished me good luck.
That's great.
You were so worried.
Since she found out I knew about Dad,
I guess she did a lot of thinking.
Had I known that earlier,
I would've discussed this
with her a lot sooner.
Anyway,
I'm glad it went well.
Right,
I don't know if it's
appropriate to say this,
but your mother is very cute.
She's like a little girl.
My mom?
If she needs anything while you go abroad,
let me know.
Okay.
I want to look at you as much as I can.
Can you go home a bit late tonight?
I have to go to the TF Team after this.
At this hour?
I also have to go through
the handover process.
I know!
Let's spend the weekend together.
Hmm?
Why are you getting a divorce?
And on top of that,
you're giving her
the house and the clinic!
Did you cheat on her?
I've said what I needed to say.
Don't contact Yeon-seung.
-How dare you!
-No!
Impudent prick.
How dare you behave like this!
Divorce?
What's the reason?
What in the world have you been doing?
Whatever the reason is,
there will be no divorce.
There will be.
I've made up my mind.
You prick.
Gosh!
Here.
Good girl.
[Mother-in-law]
Hello, Mother.
Hold on, please.
Woo-hyun said that?
I don't know what he did wrong,
but can you forgive him
and move past this?
[Think about Ha-eun.
You can't divorce him.]
We are never getting a divorce.
Then why did Woo-hyun say that?
[Mother.]
I have to watch Ha-eun.
Don't worry. Please tell Father that too.
You're going out?
Yes.
I'm meeting someone.
Who are you meeting?
The young man from work?
He's your boyfriend, right?
No!
Yes.
He's my boyfriend.
I knew it.
Who buys dinner for a co-worker's mother?
Anyway,
you have good taste.
Wait.
What happens between
you two when you leave?
He's okay with it?
Yes.
It must've been a hard decision.
It's not easy for
the person being left behind.
There are challenges when you're together.
It'll be even tougher if you're apart.
I have to go.
Make sure you eat something.
Go have fun.
Go.
It's cold. Let's go.
Okay.
[Good morning.]
[What would you like to order?]
Just a second, please.
What do you want?
A hot americano.
Two hot americanos, please.
[Okay. Please pull up at the front.]
Okay.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Here.
I like the aroma.
I like you more.
Me, too.
Before you begin making your rings,
please choose one of the designs.
Okay.
What do you think suits us the most?
How about something simple like this?
I like it simple.
Is this popular?
What size is my finger?
Do you know?
I don't.
Let's find out.
-No. 24?
No, that's too big.
It is.
Sorry.
Careful.
Ready?
Yes.
-Dunk it in the water.
-In the water...
That's pretty.
Yes.
I think mine's done.
[BM Choi Eun-Jung]
Answer it.
Just a moment.
Hello?
Right now?
I'm sorry.
Go home. I'll call you after I'm done.
You said it won't take long.
I'll just wait here. Take your time.
Okay.
I'll be done as soon as possible.
Sorry.
It's okay.
It's good.
Just add more information here.
Which part?
Here.
Break down customer segmentation
into smaller groups
and add other factors.
Also, provide more basis
for linking each target group
to the respective distribution platforms.
Okay.
Get it started.
Are you done? I'm still here.
[I'm sorry.]
I think it'll take longer.
It's okay. I'll wait.
I don't know when I'll be done.
It might be better to wait for me at home.
[It's cold, too.]
Okay. Don't worry about me.
I'm sorry.
We need to talk.
Why did you say that to your...
What happened to your face?
How could he hit you?
Do you really want to divorce me?
If you want a divorce,
tell me this one thing.
You said you're not like Han-seo.
Is that true?
Yes.
It's true.
I'm not like him.
We just clicked and got close.
I didn't know he was like that.
When he told me,
I might have felt
some unexplainable feelings.
But it was just curiosity.
That was it.
There's no way I'm like him.
I've never felt anything like that again.
So that means I'm not like that.
I don't like men.
Stop sleeping in the study room.
Ha-eun knows we're having problems.
I don't want her to suffer, too.
What are you doing up late?
I don't know what to do.
To me,
Jae-shin is everything.
He's my everything.
How can I possibly let him go?
It's all my fault.
I left you alone when we were kids.
I sent you to the States by yourself.
I wanted to make up for that,
so I gave you everything you wanted.
That's my biggest mistake.
I shouldn't have left you alone.
If it's hard to let him go right now,
focus on what you can do then.
If you start looking after yourself,
you'll learn to let him go
eventually.
Good work today.
Let's do the rest tomorrow.
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Do you want another one?
I'm sorry. I was so hungry.
I thought you went home.
I wanted to see you just a bit more.
We don't have a lot of time left.
But it was cold outside.
It wasn't that cold. Don't worry.
Okay, I won't do that anymore.
Hmm?
Have some kimchi.
Hyun-seung,
the copy machine is broken.
I forgot to call General Affairs.
I'll call them.
I can take a look. I've fixed one before.
No, Myung-jin. It's okay.
I get nervous when you say
you can do something.
I really know how to fix it.
I can do it.
I know you can do it.
But you don't have to.
You really want to do something?
Yes.
We'll receive an essence sample
from the courier soon.
Can you go down and get that?
Yes, sir!
Okay then.
Stop messing with him.
Yes, stop.
It's funny.
I'm glad he looks like his normal self.
The office seems empty without Song-ah.
We need her replacement.
I'm still looking for one.
Hi, this is Chae Hyun-seung from KLAR.
Oh, hello.
There's a sealing issue with Renew Stick?
Didn't we fix the issue
before we go into production?
Yes, we did.
But what's manufactured now
is below standard.
Quality Assurance checked twice.
They said it's no good.
This is going to be
a freebie for a promotion.
Didn't the department store
notify the customers already?
The event is taking place this weekend.
How are we going to replace 100,000 gifts?
Do we have to cancel the event?
Then it'd become a bigger problem.
The department store is throwing
a huge beauty fair this time.
What did the lab say?
This is their mistake.
They're flustered, too.
They sent staff to the factory.
And what?
That's not going to get the problem fixed.
Can't they do their jobs right?
The blame will fall on us.
Calm down, Yoo-sun.
Manager Yoo.
Can we remanufacture on time?
We need to know
if the issue can be fixed first.
It'll be safer to find other free gifts.
Hyun-seung,
find out what we can use
as gifts right away.
-Yes, sir.
-Check if extra production is possible.
Okay.
I'll make some calls here.
Me too.
Is there anything
you can produce by tomorrow?
We have a big event,
and this is an emergency.
Tomorrow?
No way.
The lines are full.
Could you give us a single line?
Please?
I understand it's urgent,
but there's nothing I can do.
It's event season.
The lines are being run to the max.
You'll have to ask elsewhere.
Hello, this is the distribution team.
[100,000 pouches in two days?]
[The delivery date is
two weeks from now, isn't it?]
You're right but we're in a pinch.
You said you have the materials.
Could you move up the production?
But we have another
delivery deadline to meet.
[Production Team]
How about a portion of the full volume?
We have an important event,
and this is really urgent.
We might have to cancel the event.
So could you please think about it?
[It's just not doable.]
We're really swamped, too.
I'm sorry.
Alright. Okay.
Mr. Park, don't shout. Come on.
You know we didn't want this to happen.
Watch your blood pressure. Hello?
Hello!
What a temper.
I don't know how he's in sales.
It's a great idea.
Develop one product that will be a hit
and focus on the online market.
A cosmetic brand could have
hundreds of products,
but most of the sales still
come from the key items.
As you read in my proposal,
this venture will focus on
making a few key items
and generate sales
higher than most brands.
If that could happen as you say,
it'd be great.
It sounds possible but...
I'm sorry.
I don't think this is right for us.
[Investment Proposal]
I'm sorry,
but may I know the reason?
Well...
By any chance,
is it because of
Director Lee Jae-woon from KLAR?
You knew?
I had a hunch.
I already got turned down several times.
They all seemed very
uncomfortable like you did.
I'll be honest with you.
Mr. Lee,
it will be hard to find an investor.
Director Lee is pulling
all the strings to hinder you.
It'll be easier for you to give up.
There has to be someone he can't reach.
Thank you for your time.
I'm sorry.
Hello, this is Lee Jae-shin.
Yes.
I was wondering if you
read my investment proposal.
Yes.
[We turned down
Lee Jae-shin's investment proposal.]
I know it wasn't easy. Thank you.
See you soon.
I'll call you.
What are you doing here?
Don't you ever work?
You're more important than work, you brat.
You look pretty now.
I've always been pretty.
Lies.
Take care of your brother now!
You want something to drink?
Ji-seung.
Should I get a divorce?
We were never madly in love
like everyone else,
but I've never once doubted.
I always believed he loved me.
Some people are vocal like me,
and others love quietly
and awkwardly as he does.
So I...
When he...
He always said thank you
instead of saying he loves me.
Turns out it was all
because he felt guilty.
You know what's funny?
I was deceived for eight years.
He might have deceived me all our lives.
But when I see him struggling
to come to terms with this,
I'm just worried about him.
If we get a divorce,
then...
He'll have to struggle all by himself.
It's so heartbreaking.
What am I going to do?
Hey.
Are you still busy?
Yes.
[Is something wrong?]
Oh.
Nothing. I just wanted to hear your voice.
[I'll let you get back to work.]
Okay.
Song-ah.
Yes.
[So you're telling me]
that you haven't found
a replacement gift yet?
That's right.
We're looking into all avenues,
but it's just impossible
to get 100,000 new gifts.
What's the alternative?
We can't cancel the event.
For now, we can either
give out random freebies,
or send out the original
promotional gift after the event.
Either way, it will result in
numerous complaints.
We have the whole day to decide,
so let's think about which is better.
And I want a report
on the projected additional cost.
Yes, sir.
You need to make a decision now.
We can't keep Sales waiting much longer.
Let's go with random gifts.
If we send them out later,
we'll get more complaints.
Let's double the value
for the gifts instead.
Do we still have
the leftover freebies from before?
Yes.
Okay.
You did a good job.
This is your first big emergency.
It's okay.
There are worse things in the world.
I'll go report to Director Lee.
Hello.
How about we send the pouches
over the next few days?
Of course!
Of course, that's fine.
Sir!
We'll get 30,000 pouches on Thursday
and another 30,000 on Friday.
The remaining 40,000 will be
dispatched on Saturday.
Okay. Sounds like the event is a go.
Yes, I think it'll go smoothly.
When we tested the pouches,
people responded well.
I don't think we'll hear
any complaints at the event.
Good job.
I'm glad you've stopped the disaster.
I'm very sorry.
This won't happen again.
I'm sorry, Manager Kwon.
Let the Sales Team know about this.
I'll inform the Sales Director.
Okay.
Alright, sir.
Manager Ahn.
Hey, you're here.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Oh, he's out.
For the pouch shoot.
Right.
It was his first time,
so he must have gone through hell.
But everything's okay now.
Did something happen?
You don't know?
There was an issue with the Renew Stick.
We almost had to cancel the event.
Hyun-seung made calls everywhere,
and he pushed the pouch production
and saved the day.
That's a relief.
I guess he didn't tell you
because you'd be worried.
Perhaps I shouldn't have said anything.
No, it's fine.
Right?
I'll see you later.
Okay.
[Temporarily closed]
I won't have much to prepare
as you're leaving everything behind.
They're all newly purchased.
You won't have any problems.
Where are you going by the way?
You're selling
when the store is doing well.
I figure you're moving
to an even better spot.
I wanted to get out
of the city for a while.
I'll see you when we sign the contract.
Sure, I'll see you then.
Let's go.
What is a good time for you?
How about Saturday?
It's the divorce paper you wanted.
I signed it.
All that's left is your signature.
Thank you.
Woo-hyun,
I want to tell you something.
It doesn't matter who you are
or who you love.
You are the same
Kang Woo-hyun that I love.
If...
Even if
what your friend said to you is true,
that's not wrong.
That's not abnormal.
I'm worried about you.
I see you spend your whole life
torturing yourself with those thoughts.
That won't happen.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Do this for me then.
Do it as a last favor for me.
For once in your life,
open your heart to yourself.
See what's inside.
If you think you can't do it alone,
I'll be by your side.
How could I do that to you?
I want to do it for you.
That's who you are to me.
If you even cherished me at all,
please do as I ask.
Until you can accept yourself for you are.
Just until then.
This is delicious.
It's been a while since we shared a meal.
Are you eating these days?
You look slimmer.
I ate well.
Don't worry.
Hyun-seung,
I heard there was an issue
with the Renew Stick.
You heard that?
It's all resolved now. Don't worry.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I was too busy?
You had a lot on your plate.
I didn't want to add to that.
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
You must have been so worried,
but you hid it from me
so that I wouldn't worry.
It's fine.
Things worked out anyway.
I'm the one who's being selfish.
But you're paying the price for it.
You always put me first.
You hold back. You keep silent.
I'm always taking what you give.
I do that because I want to do it.
Listen.
Holding back while waiting is nothing.
I'm more upset and worried
to see you feel this bad about it.
You know how you can make me feel better?
Don't think that way.
[I'm the one who's being selfish.]
But you're paying the price for it.
If you want to say something, say it.
Well...
Are you okay?
No.
How could I be?
I've loved him for years.
But...
I will be fine.
I'm going to give myself
all the love I gave him.
I'm going to work a lot more.
We're going to get very busy.
Are you up for it?
Absolutely.
Here.
[Hot pepper and mayo chicken]
It's hot but good, right?
Yes.
So good.
You're such a scaredy-cat.
It's coming out again.
Please don't do that.
Come on, focus.
No.
Go.
Why is he so slow?
- Goal!
-Pass.
-Goal!
-Son Heung-min...
It's Son Heung-min.
Are your fingers still asleep?
No, it's my shoulders.
-Your shoulders. I see.
-Yes, my shoulders.
I think they're good now. Let's go.
-Stay still, right hand.
-Hey!
What happened? That was weird.
Did you try to take my controller?
It was an honest mistake.
Hey!
Stop lying.
You're a cheater!
What do you mean a cheater?
My hand! Stay, right hand!
What are you doing?
Man.
So? Do you like it?
Perfect.
It's so beautiful that I want to save it.
Don't worry. Wear it as much as you want.
From now on,
you have to wear only what I make you.
Hold up.
It sounds like you're saying
you'll be by my side forever.
You're too good of a catch.
I'm not letting you slip away.
Yes!
Gosh!
-Hooray!
-What are you doing?
Yes!
Put me down!
Hey.
Let's not think of it as five years.
Think of it as a few months.
There's summer leave. I'll go visit.
We can meet before the new year too.
It won't feel that long then.
Okay.
A few product releases,
and it will soon be summer.
Promise me.
Don't feel unsure.
Don't feel guilty.
Take what you need
and buy the rest over there.
I will.
Want me to pack you gochujang?
Oh, laver! Take some laver!
Hold on. I'll go buy some.
They have it there.
There are Korean restaurants, too.
Just in case.
Wait. I'll go buy some.
You said you're going to Paris?
Yes.
Promise me you'll visit.
I'll put you up.
You better not shove me in a hotel.
What am I going to do now
when you're gone?
I'll be so bored.
You won't have time to be.
You have to win the Gold Button.
Huh?
What Gold Button?
You thought I wouldn't know
if you wore a mask?
I came across your videos at work,
and I could tell it's you
by the sound of your voice.
You're good.
I am, aren't I?
You just wait.
While you're in Europe,
I'll definitely win the Gold Button.
Sure, go get it.
I can't wait to see it in person.
Get packing.
I'm glad I get to sleep
next to you before you leave.
Stay until I'm set to leave.
I'll feel sad if I see you leaving.
Your boyfriend is sending
you to the airport, right?
Yes.
Living abroad is hard.
Even if you're far away,
I feel better knowing you
have somebody to lean on.
While I'm gone,
I hope you can find someone to lean on.
Whether that's a friend or someone else,
I want you to have someone
to trust and rely on.
It's too late for that.
It's nice.
Having someone to take care of you.
I just feel bad that
I can't give him enough.
Not as much as I receive.
That's normal.
You want to offer as much as you receive.
I want to give more to you, too.
Let me give you a hug.
Huh?
What?
Come here.
Oh, dear.
My sweet girl.
[Three years later]
Manager Chae.
Yes, sir.
About your new request...
Do we have to support the Sales Team?
It'd be a nice gesture.
They helped with our sales last month.
You said you'd help out
with their promotional items.
I did?
I don't remember though.
If I promise, I have to do it. Okay.
Alright, sir.
Hyun-seung.
Are you coming to the gathering later?
Min-seong will make a fuss if I don't.
He'll probably barge into your place.
We've had monthly gatherings
for the past four years.
That's because he's
the president of our group.
Want to take over?
Me?
Yes.
No, thank you.
Manager Chae,
you have a training meeting.
Okay.
I'll contact you afterward.
You got everything we need?
Yes, I got everything.
Everyone in the Europe TF Team
is getting promoted.
They deserve it.
Yoon Song-ah is in my year group.
She'll become a general manager soon.
When will I move up?
Hyo-joo.
Yes?
Are you going to keep on
working after marriage?
Of course.
I've worked hard to build my career.
If you oppose it,
then this is a waste of my time.
Oh, not that.
Do whatever you please.
My parents would love
their daughter-in-law working.
Who says I want to be
their daughter-in-law?
Over here, CEO Lee.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
That's okay. I came early.
Thank you for coming to meet me.
I went on a blind date.
You look like you've been doing well.
I've been doing great myself too.
As you said, I'm doing well without you.
I can tell.
Take care then.
[When are you coming? Hurry up!]
I'm on my way.
I'm about to cross the street.
You keep this up and I'm going home.
[Alright, you brat.]
[Grace us with your presence, please.]
Alright, I'll be there soon.