(Gwangju,
Korea Railroad Corporation)
Father, I need to use the restroom.
I'm...
moving to Seoul...
with Hwang Hee Tae.
I heard.
You're smiling?
Kim Myeong Hee.
How can you...
smile at me right now?
Soo Ryeon.
You must have a lot on your mind...
now that you're actually leaving.
No.
Soo Ryeon,
you remind me of myself...
when I was young.
If you let fear rule your life,
you'll be daunted
by more and more things...
to the point
that you can't do anything.
And if that happens,
you'll become even more fearful.
(Episode 8,
After the Door Closes)
When you get there,
don't get dragged into trouble.
Go straight home.
Okay.
You must've been uncomfortable
because of me.
I'm sorry.
No, not at all.
Take good care of Soo Ryeon.
I will.
Goodness. I'm not on the verge
of dying or something.
What's with the faces?
Soo Ryeon.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yes, of course!
Your troublemaker daughter
won't be around anymore,
so take care of your health, Father.
Well...
I don't want to make you cringe,
so let's skip the hug.
I'll get going now.
Soo Ryeon.
Come back anytime
if things don't work out.
(Seoul)
I can't believe he left like this.
(Math Notes)
Hee Tae!
He had to go back to Seoul
because he lives there.
Did you think
he'd live here forever?
Good grief. You're being ridiculous.
Are you sure
you don't want to head out with me?
I told you I'm not in the mood
to go anywhere!
What do you mean?
Get ready for school!
You're not even in your uniform yet!
- No!
- Get moving!
You probably won't cry like that
when I die!
Oh, dear. She's crying
as if we lost our country again.
Myeong Hee, are you...
Hey, Myeong Hee. What are you doing?
Why are you washing the sheets
first thing in the morning?
What's up?
Oh, I have to visit my hometown
for a few days...
to take care of something.
Then leave your sheets out.
I'll wash them for you.
What? Oh, okay. Thanks.
Right, can you look after Jin A
while I'm gone...
- Sure thing. Have a safe trip.
- Okay.
End the martial law!
Denounce media corruption!
- Denounce media corruption!
End the unlawful firearms training!
- End the unlawful training!
- This is a democratic nation!
- End the martial law!
- Until Mount Baekdu is worn away
- And the East Sea runs dry
- May the Lord protect
- And preserve our country
- Mugunghwa, the whole of Korea
- Such a splendid land
(We Refuse to Attend School)
(End the Martial Law)
(Protect Democracy)
- Guarded by her people
- Ever may Korea stand
- As the pine atop Namsan Peak
- What are you doing?
- What?
Nothing.
We should walk a bit more
to hail a cab.
Stick close to me.
- Mugunghwa, the whole of Korea
- Such a splendid land
- Guarded by her people
Come in.
Okay.
Why don't you have any stuff here?
It's practically an empty house.
I sold everything.
The bathroom is over there...
and that's the storage room.
Hey.
Isn't today your overnight shift?
Why are you already here?
Well, I had nothing better to do...
and I felt sorry for
skipping work last time.
Did you clean this whole room
by yourself?
Oh, you didn't clean up
the supply room yet, right?
No. Not yet,
but it's too big to clean
on your own.
Hey.
What...
What's with her?
Hey!
Sorry.
Are you going somewhere?
I have to go somewhere briefly.
- Why?
- What?
It's nothing.
Oh, right. There's no food here.
There's a restaurant down the alley.
If you don't want to go alone,
you can order.
Order two servings if you need to.
I have money for food too.
Oh, right.
I'll leave it here then.
Wait.
Never mind, see you later.
Okay.
(Kim Kyung Soo)
Hey, that book
you guys were reading...
(Submit a Petition
to the Government and Press)
(Boycott All Classes)
Hwang Hee Tae?
It's been a long time.
Yes.
What brings you here?
You have no business here.
I wanted to ask
if anyone has heard from Kyung Soo.
Can you reach him, by any chance?
Hey.
How dare you ask
how Kyung Soo is doing?
I guess you can't.
Then good luck with your coverage.
By the way,
I haven't told anyone yet...
about what kind of person
your dad is.
I'm still a reporter, you know.
Did you think I wouldn't find out?
Tell them.
What?
Tell them they'll turn out
like Kim Kyung Soo...
if they get involved with me.
Tell them to stay away from me...
if they don't want to ruin
their lives.
Go ahead and spread the news.
Hello?
Isn't this Hwang Hee Tae's number?
Yes, it is.
I'm glad.
He never answered,
so I was wondering if he moved.
Can I talk to Hee Tae?
Oh, he's not home at the moment.
Really?
Do you know where he is?
I'm not sure.
Then do you know when he'll be back?
I'm not sure about that either.
May I ask who you are?
What's your relationship
with Hee Tae?
I'm not sure.
I'll call back next time.
Where have you been all day,
you slacker?
Something came up at home.
Your family seems awfully busy
all the time.
The National Sports Festival
is less than a month away.
My brother went to Seoul today.
Hee Tae?
With my sister?
No. With his fiancee.
Then...
what about my sister?
He won't come to Gwangju anymore.
So they really did fight.
Gosh, you made this on your own?
You should've woke me up.
I can do the dishes.
It's okay, I'll do it.
I have some business outside.
What about you?
Me?
I don't know.
I'll try to come back
as soon as possible.
You should do...
what you have to do too.
Okay, I will.
Let's eat.
There's nothing left to do.
I'll call you later. Okay.
Send this
to the judicial scrivener...
and this to the accountant.
What about the papers
from the Medicines Agency?
Oh, here.
By the way,
the site manager asked...
if you can visit the site today.
I need to go to the office today.
Then tell him I'll drop by
sometime tomorrow morning...
I thought I made it clear...
that I refuse to accept
a joint management.
I'm just trying to help.
The situation has changed
since last time.
Will you be able to handle
Changhwa Pharmaceuticals...
on top of Changhwa Industrial...
on your own?
If I need your help,
I'll ask you myself.
Must I make you ask for my help?
What about the favor
Soo Ryeon asked of you?
Oh, that.
Do you mean
her friend going abroad to study?
I don't think it's time for you
to be concerned about a girl.
How can I trust and follow you...
if you can't keep a promise
about one girl?
Well, the thing is,
it's actually not
such a simple matter.
Then is a joint management
a simple matter?
Trust is developed...
only when both sides
can put their faith in each other.
But it seems to me...
you're just trying
to force me to put my faith in you.
Gosh, I'm starving to death.
Look at how skinny my tummy looks.
I hope we can eat meat today.
My gosh.
Why are you looking at my tummy
and mentioning meat?
Myeong Soo!
What? Myeong Hee!
Ta-da.
Here. Take some to your coach first.
You go. My sister brought it.
Little bear.
Hurry up and eat some
before Myeong Soo comes back.
- Thank you for the food.
Here, Jung Tae. Go ahead and dig in.
You should eat a lot
if you want to grow taller.
Come on.
How could you start without me?
Too bad. Come here and dig in.
Gosh, this is so good.
You didn't have to see me out.
You should get ready for training.
You brought fried chicken
as you promised.
This is the least I can do.
Goodness.
My gosh, little bear.
Look at all this oil on your mouth.
Why did you and Hee Tae break up?
What are you talking about?
How could we break up
when we're just friends?
Come on. I even brought you chicken.
What are you pouting for?
I was hoping
you and Hee Tae would get married.
What? Get married?
Marriage is stronger
than engagement.
Plus, if you got married,
you wouldn't go abroad.
All right.
Maybe I should give up on it,
after all.
Give up on what?
Studying abroad.
Since my little bear
hates the idea so much,
I should probably forget about it.
You're teasing me, right?
I'm serious.
Maybe I should just
go and watch you compete...
in the Sports Festival.
When is it again?
Are you sure
you're not fooling with me?
Are you really not going
to study abroad?
Seriously?
Goodness.
"Consequently, the student council
held an emergency meeting,"
"where they had a heated discussion
for an hour and a half..."
"before coming to the decision
to disband."
"They also persuaded
the student demonstrators..."
"around Seoul Station to disperse
and go back to school."
Gosh, those darn cowards in Seoul.
What a way to lose momentum.
If they've backed down in Seoul,
will all our efforts go up in smoke?
Nothing's changed in Gwangju.
Kwan Hyun...
finished talking to
the police commissioner.
The police will cooperate...
with today's torch protest.
I'm sure more citizens
will be participating today.
Let's hurry up and get prepared.
- Yes.
(Guarantee workers' rights!)
(Release all prisoners
of conscience!)
(End the martial law!)
Goodness gracious.
Just smash it all, why don't you?
What is it?
Are you angry about Seoul?
Do you know that
Lee Soo Ryeon is in Seoul now?
She's in Seoul?
Did she protest
at Seoul Station yesterday?
It's not to protest,
but to get married to your friend,
Hwang Hee Tae.
What? Who said that?
There are no secrets
in this small town.
So she didn't even tell you?
What about Myeong Hee?
After being so harsh to Myeong Hee
and taking Soo Ryeon's side,
are you worried about her now?
I don't know. I can't reach her.
I'm sure she's pretending
to be fine somewhere.
I'm sorry, Myeong Hee.
Have you been waiting long?
Not at all. I just got here.
I'm the one who asked to meet,
but I couldn't get here on time
because something came up.
I'll have the same as her.
My gosh,
why are you in such a hurry?
- Catch your breath first.
- Thanks.
So? Why did you want to see me?
Myeong Hee,
your passport application
is being processed again.
My friend at Foreign Affairs
just confirmed it.
You don't have to worry
about my departure anymore.
I won't be able to leave
this year anyway.
Actually, I asked around a bit.
There are other ways besides
the Catholic Foundation scholarship.
These are not
the only options either.
It's fine.
Even if I get a passport,
I still have to wait for my visa.
If you don't want to go abroad,
you could study in Korea.
I'll support you.
Starting with preparations
for the exam...
Soo Chan.
I'm really fine.
I'm not.
I was being nosy and...
Because of me, you...
Come on.
How many times must I tell you?
It's not your fault.
If you keep trying to help me,
I'll only feel worse.
Myeong Hee.
Can't you just...
let me help you?
I can't stand this.
I'm doing this for my own good.
So can't you please let me help you?
You've already given me enough.
Even if you give me more,
my hands are already full.
Trust me, I'm really fine.
Don't worry about me.
We're good to go!
To Hyehwa-dong, please.
- It's a warm, sunny May day.
- Sure.
As we get started,
here is a song
you might want to share...
with someone as sweet as sunshine.
Wait. I requested this song.
I have no regrets.
But it's not like there's no pain
just because we don't regret things.
Even if we don't seem strong
or happy,
I hope
we can show each other everything.
I can sing for you sometime.
Can we meet again
before the flowers wither?
Then I'd love to.
Myeong Hee.
Do you want to go out with me
just until the end of May?
I'm not okay.
I don't want this May
to pass by without you.
Welcome.
("Troubling Political Situations
Due to Protests")
More than 100,000
took to the streets.
How could they tell us
to go back to school?
What is the council even thinking?
They don't want to give
the government an excuse.
They actually brought armored cars.
Weren't you scared?
To be honest, I was relieved
when we were told to disperse.
I didn't say I wasn't scared.
But no matter how scared we are,
there are things to get done.
- They must get done.
- Right?
Don't you agree?
Guys.
Hold on. Lee Soo Ryeon?
Soo Ryeon, is that you?
Sang Min?
My gosh, it really is you.
I can't believe it.
Did you come here for
the Seoul Station protest yesterday?
- What?
- All the way from Gwangju?
If only there was someone like her
on the student council.
Right, guys?
Are you here alone?
Come and sit with us. Come here.
No, thanks. I...
What is it?
Are you waiting for someone?
Hey, by any chance,
did Won Seok come here with you?
Sang Min, I'm sorry.
What?
(Honam Building)
Hey! Do you have a death wish?
Get out of the way!
You're home late.
I have to step out for a minute.
Where are you going?
I have something to do.
What is it that you have to do?
It's a personal matter.
See you later.
Hwang Hee Tae.
Are you doing this to punish me?
What?
I know you are.
You blame me for everything.
That's why you're ignoring
and avoiding me...
to make me feel uncomfortable.
Let's talk when I get back.
Why?
Am I not even worth
fighting anymore?
Just hit me or something.
Be sarcastic, yell at me,
or get angry like you used to.
Then what?
What difference does it make?
Then what about this?
If you keep avoiding me like this...
and pretend I don't exist,
what difference does that make?
- I never avoided...
- You don't have to do this!
I know too.
I know everything is my fault.
I'm responsible for what happened...
to both Myeong Hee and you.
I know it so well...
that it's driving me crazy!
- So just insult me.
- Soo Ryeon.
Blame me. Get angry with me!
Soo Ryeon!
I've never blamed you for anything.
Ever.
Okay?
Let's go.
I have someone to introduce to you.
So she was the leader
of the labor union strike?
I didn't know you were so famous,
Seok Chul.
So the reason you came to Gwangju
in the first place...
and went on that blind date was...
Yes.
She's being transferred tomorrow.
With the ambulance and everything,
there are many arrangements to make.
Ms. Jang Seok Chul's guardian?
Stay here. I'll go sign some papers.
It looks like a child's hand, right?
Her hands are so thin...
that I sometimes have trouble
sticking needles in them.
I can't believe such a petite woman
got up to something so huge.
The world is never going to change.
She sacrificed herself for nothing.
She should've known
how scary the world is.
I'm sure she was scared.
Pardon?
That's why what she did is...
even more remarkable.
She did what needed to be done...
even though she was scared.
End the martial law!
- End the martial law!
Release the arrested students!
- Release the arrested students!
Guarantee farmers' rights!
- Guarantee farmers' rights!
Hey, there! Hold the torch up!
You'll burn the man's hair.
Yushin remnants, step down!
- Yushin remnants, step down!
- Until Mount Baekdu is worn away
- And the East Sea runs dry
The rally is supposed to end today.
But to prevent it from recurring,
the leaders should be...
Not yet.
Hello, Defense Security Command.
Salute.
I'll be on my way immediately.
I've been urgently summoned
to the headquarters.
Stand by until I get back
from Seoul.
Hey.
Hey, Hwang Hee Tae.
Hey!
What is it?
Wake up.
There's a place I want to go to.
Goodness. I thought...
you wanted to go to some cool place.
You country bumpkins
are so predictable.
You all want to check out
the palaces,
Myeong-dong, Deoksu Palace...
My goodness.
Look at you talking
as if you're not a country bumpkin.
I never said that.
I'm actually enjoying this,
and that proves...
I'm still a country bumpkin
after all.
Hey, Country Bumpkin.
What?
You should go...
back to Gwangju with Seok Chul.
I can't go back
until my father says that I can.
What's the real reason?
Your father...
or Myeong Hee?
Let's head back home.
If it's because...
you're afraid
Myeong Hee would be hurt,
just go back to Gwangju.
I said I won't.
Hey, Hwang Hee Tae!
She said she's scared.
Myeong Hee is scared of me.
Are you dumb?
Do you actually believe that?
Myeong Hee is...
She's not scared of you.
She doesn't want you to get hurt.
She said
that's what she's most afraid of.
What?
Your father is what?
What do you mean?
That's why I wanted to...
apologize to you...
before you left.
I guess we were
on the same wavelength.
Why should you...
apologize to me?
You know, that incident years ago.
I blamed you.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't your fault at all.
I guess I needed someone to blame.
Your friend here is such a loser.
Right?
What about Hwang Hee Tae?
Does he know about all this?
Did you tell him?
Myeong Hee!
- Will you suffer alone again...
- Soo Ryeon.
If I stay with him,
both of our lives will be destroyed.
And if that happens,
he'll think it's all his fault,
just like you beat yourself up
for what happened to me.
So...
you tell him on my behalf...
that he doesn't have it in him
to destroy anyone.
So?
Are you afraid
Myeong Hee would ruin your life?
No, right?
She feels the same way.
So you're both okay with it.
Then what's the problem?
No.
Myeong Hee will be hurt in the end.
Seriously.
You guys are two peas in a pod.
Fine, you decide
whether you'll go back or not.
I'll be on my way now.
Let's part ways here.
They say couples always break up...
if they walk along the Deoksu Palace
stonewall together.
Hwang Hee Tae.
Let's please not get dragged
into each other's lives again...
and just wish each other
all the best. Okay?
(Hansaeng Hospital)
Shouldn't you go to Gwangju anyway
to oversee everything?
Just go with us.
We can take one guardian
in the ambulance.
(May 17, 1980,
Guardian, Hwang Hee Tae)
No, I'm not going.
Well, all right then.
I'll call you
when we arrive in Gwangju.
- Please take good care of her.
- No problem.
(Hansaeng Hospital)
Did she really say
she's no longer going abroad?
Maybe it's just something she said.
Did she seem okay?
All right.
Okay, good luck with the training.
Bye.
Gosh, you scared me!
Did you have to creep up on me
like that?
What did you just say?
What?
What did you say? Going abroad?
She worked very hard for years
to prepare for it.
I heard she got accepted
to the school this time.
But the last time she was here,
she seemed distraught,
so I'm thinking maybe...
(Account Number, Balance)
Gosh, when did this happen?
(Seoul)
(Emergency Room)
Please sign here to confirm
that you've received the patient.
Sure.
(Patient Transfer Form)
(Hwang Hee Tae)
(May 17, 1980,
Guardian, Hwang Hee Tae)
(Kim Myeong Hee)
Father.
Hey, Myeong Hee.
I'm sorry I keep changing my mind.
I know you suggested it
to help me out.
Don't worry about it.
The scholarship program chooses
new recipients every year.
You can apply again next year.
No.
I've decided against...
studying abroad.
Did something happen?
Nothing happened.
I just don't want to go anymore.
My little brother is
still very young.
And going abroad won't solve
all my problems.
After causing all the fuss...
I'm sorry.
I'm actually happy for you.
Pardon me?
Why did you want to study abroad?
You said you had no reason
to stay in this country...
because nothing
was keeping you here.
I'm assuming you changed your mind
and decided to stay...
because you found a reason to stay.
Am I wrong?
I did find...
one reason,
but it's gone now.
I can't even leave now,
but it's gone.
It's okay.
Whether you go abroad or not,
if a door closes,
another one always opens.
What if it doesn't?
I've lived my whole life...
behind closed doors.
Even now,
it feels like every door
around me is closed,
and I can't sleep...
or even breathe.
It may seem dark at first,
but a door will open soon.
It will open for sure.
Myeong Hee.
I promise.
No.
I know.
I already heard why...
you had no choice but to say no.
I know I shouldn't have come.
Whenever I think of you,
I know...
that I'll eventually cause you pain.
But I want to be with you...
and stay by your side.
Can I come closer, Myeong Hee?
Hello?
Hey, Hye Gun.
It's me, Lee Soo Ryeon.
Hey, Soo Ryeon. What...
I heard your photo studio
is a hideout for runaways.
Do you have room for me too?
It's broken.
It's no use trying to tweak it.
Hold on.
I'm almost done.
Recently, Korea's second...
You could open up
an electronics store...
in the mountains someday.
An electronics store?
That sounds nice.
My dream was to become
an engineering professor...
until my mother fell ill.
Then you should get
a doctorate degree...
before you open
an electronics store.
Whether I open an electronics store,
work at a construction site,
or stow away on a ship in Busan,
I'm fine with anything...
as long as I'm with you.
When I was a kid,
I liked turning the dial
like this...
more than listening to the radio.
Whenever I turned the dial
slowly like this,
I sometimes heard...
a faint signal
that sounded unfamiliar.
That signal seemed...
like me.
A signal that no one listened to...
and floated around aimlessly
in the universe...
with no sound or color.
Until you found me like this.
Me too.
Before I met you,
I couldn't hear anything.
You really...
don't have to be scared
of anything anymore.
Hey.
Maybe your friend died.
He should've already answered
by now.
But someone else answered yesterday.
Just hang up
and call him again tomorrow.
It's time.
Round them all up.
As of 24:00 on May 17, 1980,
the emergency martial law
is in effect...
throughout the country.
Considering the recent movements
of North Korea...
and the ongoing disturbances
in all parts of the country,
the entire nation is deemed
to be in an emergency state.
On these grounds,
it has been decided...
that the emergency martial law
is in effect nationwide...
starting 24:00, May 17, 1980.
Hye Gun.
What?
(Youth of May)
Why are you doing this?
Drag them all off!
He made you start a rebellion,
didn't he?
You promised you'd leave with me
in the morning.
Are you saying
we should leave in this situation?
Leaving my patients behind?
Yes, let's just leave.
Even if you throw yourself
into that mayhem,
nothing's going to change.
There are things I can do.
"Stabbed by a bayonet?"
There are patients waiting outside.
This is a neurosurgery case.
Call the surgeon.
- Hee Tae!
- Please call someone!
Jin A, please. Please come back.