[English subtitles are available]
[Love Scenery]
[Adapted from Qiao Yao's novel]
["It's Easy To Dodge a Gun,
But Hard To Prevent a Crush"]
[Episode 19]
I want to sing rock songs.
First,
your throat hasn't fully recovered yet.
Second,
we don't think changing your style now
is a good idea.
As for me, I hope that you can
think it over.
I've thought about it.
I want to join the show.
Nice to meet you, Liang Chen.
Nice to meet you, Director Ma.
I have too much on my plate,
that's why I'm late.
Have a seat.
Director Ma, I came to see you today
because I heard
The Journey of Music Lovers
is recruiting challengers.
Are you interested?
I have always wanted
to break through my own style
and give rock music a shot.
But rock music
is not your style.
The truth is,
I've hit a roadblock
in my song-writing journey.
I really want to make a breakthrough
and rediscover my passion for music.
So I really wish
I can get this opportunity.
I also hope that you'll consider it.
Liang Chen,
if you really can join this competition,
it's a great pleasure.
How about this?
The production team will consider it.
I'll give you the answer as soon as I can,
alright?
Sure. Thank you, Director Ma.
What are you doing here?
You didn't go to the homecoming,
so I got you a memento
and brought it here.
Come in and take a seat.
[Nanze 70th Anniversary]
This book seems very familiar.
I bought it when I was in university.
Didn't you give me the same book?
I guess you keep it on your bedside.
How did you know that?
I guess this book is great
at helping you fall asleep.
Is something bothering you?
You came all the way here.
I don't think it's about the memento.
It's nothing.
Do you know The Journey of Music Lovers?
Yes.
Are you going to join this show?
I want to give rock music a shot.
Rock music?
It doesn't seem to match
the image your agency sets for you.
But you also know
that I only wish to sing
the songs I want now.
I remember back in university,
when you were
making "First Dance of Winter,"
you were really cranky.
My Toybob almost went bald
because you kept rubbing it.
I have a live cat there.
Take it.
To get back at you
for writing such a challenging song,
I secretly added
a lot of coriander in your takeaway.
So it was you.
I thought I was so unlucky that month.
I don't eat coriander,
but it was in all my food.
It's sad
that we didn't really finish this song.
So I came here today
to invite you to join my band.
Well, you know, Orange.
I'm not making music anymore.
This is an opportunity for me,
it is also an opportunity for you.
So,
let's start over again, shall we?
I'm sorry, Orange.
I can't do this.
I hope you can respect my choice.
Shan Shan, I heard you're quitting school.
Is that true?
Why are you giving up on your dream?
I can't make music anymore.
I can't do this.
Are you giving it up
because of Lin Qi?
You don't understand,
you don't understand.
You don't know anything.
You don't know anything about me!
Do you know how hard it is for me?
I can't even listen to music now.
As soon as I hear music,
even if it's just a note or a bar,
I will think of him
and everything we had together.
And this place,
every day, every minute, every second here
is full of notes.
Everything is about music,
everything is about him!
I can't take it anymore!
Shan Shan, I will stay by your side.
I will help you get over him.
Leave me alone.
Are you giving up
on our dream now?
Just because of that jerk?
[Why am I being so paranoid recently?]
What's the matter with you?
You seem to have something to say.
Meng Lan Zhi is also releasing an album.
Her agency has been playing this news up
for several times, hasn't it?
What now?
Is she releasing an album every month?
She's fighting for resources
with you again.
What resources do we have in common?
You'd better see it for yourself.
Director Ma
does have an extraordinary taste in music.
She's joining
The Journey of Music Lovers too?
Has she learned
about your interest in joining,
so she horned in?
I don't think so.
You don't think so? This must be it.
She and her team always
like to play things up.
There's no way she'll let go
of this chance.
Do I have to react every time
she plays something up?
Am I stupid?
I hate this kind
of stupid publicity stunt.
[Meng Lan Zhi versus Liang Chen.]
[The Journey of Music Lovers.]
[Quota of participants.]
Hello.
[Liang Chen, where are you?]
I've just reached my apartment.
[Do you want to watch the sunset?]
Now?
[By the lake.]
Alright, wait for me.
Let's go.
Go up first.
I'll go out for a while.
Where are you going?
I'm meeting my friend!
Why did you come here all of a sudden?
I read
some stupid stuff on the internet.
I'm worried about you.
It's nothing.
I've learned to live with it.
Don't worry.
Soon,
there will be new news.
And this news will die down.
What's the matter?
Liang Chen,
you are a bit different
from what I thought.
Like how?
You're much better than I thought.
Hello, Jia Yun.
Take it out.
-What?
-Hand it over.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Wait. You...
How could you take my stuff?
Give it to me.
Liang Chen.
Jia Yun,
how did you find me so soon?
Ke Ke told me you're nearby.
How did you know
that a reporter was following me?
Someone told me you were targeted.
Sorry for making you worry.
Liang Chen,
I may not have the right to say this,
but as your friend,
I must remind you.
What if I hadn't got here in time
and those photos went out?
You may not care
about the news right now.
But that boy, can he handle it?
I've never thought about this.
In that case,
you should think it over from now on.
Just now Jia Yun was looking for you,
did he find you?
He sent me home.
Why do you seem upset?
No. I'm just exhausted.
I'll cook something for you.
Hello.
[Are you home?]
Yes, I am.
[I'm sorry.]
[I almost got you into trouble today.]
It's me who should apologise.
I was insensitive.
[Rest early.]
[Bye.]
I'd like to thank you
on behalf of Liang Chen.
No one needs to do anything
on behalf of Liang Chen and me.
Do you mean
by causing her trouble?
Thank you for asking.
For the trouble I caused,
I will fix it myself.
Ke Ke, when you open the door,
check who that is.
Qing, what are you doing here?
So much has happened today,
I came to see you.
Qing, please sit.
I didn't expect Meng Lan Zhi
would ride the wave again.
Don't worry. I'm fine.
Yeah.
Meng Lan Zhi won't make any impact on you,
but not others.
Qing, just get to the point.
You've been very close
with a boy recently.
Not me. I know nothing.
Do you really think that I'm insensitive
and won't notice anything?
I'm quite close with him,
but I should also have
my own normal social life.
He's still a student, isn't he?
Do you have any idea what he will face
if the media exposes him?
Pressure from public opinion aside,
the attention he gets
will be enough to turn
his life upside down.
The memory card in the reporter's camera
has been taken away.
This problem has been solved,
but can you make sure
the same thing won't happen again?
I'm not saying that you can't date,
but you have to calm yourself down now
and think about
the consequences and impacts
caused by your relationship with him.
Don't hurt other people
and yourself.
Got it.
It's been a while.
You're here.
I'll have the same three dishes.
Thanks, mister.
It's been a while
since you last came here.
Exactly, exactly.
Is that Sun Bin Yu?
I think so.
Let's take a photo.
Look. That's him.
We found him! He's here!
Come here, come here!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Hurry up. Hurry.
What are you doing?
Go back!
What the hell is this?
What's the matter?
There's a rumour online
saying that you lead a promiscuous life
and are having illicit relationships
with several men.
She's out, she's out.
Come, come.
Who are you?
Do you know Liang Chen?
I don't know who Liang Chen is.
I'm just getting groceries.
Just tell us something.
Hello, Taro.
Orange, help me!
What's wrong?
Some culprit spread rumours online,
saying that you always
come to my neighbourhood.
They even revealed my address.
I only went to get breakfast,
they secretly photographed me.
Now I'm stuck outside like a dog.
If I had known this,
I would've dressed up.
I'm a mess right now.
Someone revealed your address
on the internet?
No. They revealed my neighbourhood.
I'm not sure how they got my address,
[but they found us so soon.]
Taro, I'm sorry.
I got you into this.
[What are you talking about?]
I'm an actor, after all.
[It's given my popularity
quite the boost.]
Speaking of which, Orange.
This is all very strange.
Someone must've planned this.
You'd better watch out.
Where are you now?
I can ask Ke Ke to pick you up.
Forget it, forget it.
If... If you come here,
that means our relationship is real.
I'll figure something out.
Bye.
Alright.
Are you kidding me?
I look so ugly in this!
You even turned me into a meme?
Do you think I never surf the internet?
Report. I'll report everything!
Darn it!
Maybe I should explain it to Ms Ma.
She must never think
that there's something
between Liang Chen and me.
[Hello,]
[the number you're calling]
[is currently switched off.]
She switched her phone off again?
Maybe I should go to her house.
[Liang Chen went to a drama actor's house
late at night.]
[Is she seeing him?]
[Are Ding Jia Yun and Liang Chen
just friends?]
[Is Liang Chen having
illicit relationships]
[with several men?]
Hey,
defamation is a criminal offence,
please mind your language.
-There you are.
-What is going on now?
I've drafted a legal letter and statement.
If the statement can't suppress
those scandals,
we will issue the legal letter.
Okay.
Liang Chen,
these news are obviously trying
to slander you.
Did you offend someone?
Isn't that obvious?
Besides Meng Lan Zhi,
who else could do that?
Why would she do this?
I think she's determined
to join The Journey of Music Lovers.
Just ignore her.
Are other people being affected?
I've contacted
those guys in the scandals.
All of them have been harassed
to some degree.
Remember to treat them to a meal.
Who else has been harassed besides Taro?
Jia Yun,
and the male staff
who's been working closely with you.
Nowadays, the media would do anything
just to get the headlines.
They couldn't wait
to find every single man
who's related to you in any way.
You may not care
about the news right now.
But that boy,
can he handle it?
Nice! Nice!
What are you looking at?
I won't be playing. I'm taking a break.
He Ye.
Come.
[Hello,]
[the number you're calling]
[is unavailable at the moment.]
[Please try again later.]
[Where are you now?]
Ladies!
I'm coming!
This is so awkward.
Last year,
I wanted to be as slim as lightning
and blind your eyes.
But now, I'm as fat as a wall,
and I'm blocking your view.
Who's there?
Ms Ma!
What do you want?
I... I...
It's all Liang Chen's fault.
I was chased around by my fans
and blocked by reporters.
Now I have nowhere to go!
Look, I even lost my shoe.
I'm pathetic.
You have animal slippers too!
They fit me just fine.
Ms Ma,
I knew you'd help me.
From now on, all the house chores
including sweeping and cooking
will be on me.
You won't regret it.
What happened to Liang Chen?
Tell me everything and get out of here.
Liang Chen, catch me!
Watch out.
[I can't ruin his life.]
[Why didn't she answer my call?]
Drink some soy milk for nutrition.
Life is bitter. Have some candy.
Come here, come here.
Look.
I thought Lu Jing has been acting strange.
They must've had a fight.
But looking at them,
it seems they've made up.
And now they're showing affection.
Why is this drama so complicated?
What's wrong?
What else?
I had a fight with Qi Qi again.
It's annoying.
What do you think the girls are thinking?
Why would they ignore someone
all of a sudden?
I know, right?
What are they thinking?
We were walking on the street,
but Qi Qi said it was too windy
and she was cold.
But I looked around,
and it was not windy at all.
Then she was upset.
A few days ago,
as soon as she saw me, she asked me
if I noticed anything different about her.
How would I know?
So I asked her,
did you gain weight?
Then she blocked me.
She never talks to me up until now.
You've had a hard time.
I know, right?
You know me well.
We're both men, after all.
No, no. We are different.
Why is that?
Forget it. You won't get it anyway.
You're right.
We're different.
I have a girlfriend,
but you're single.
How are we the same?
Ouch!
Ouch...
Why are you leaving already?
What's going on?
Are you mad because I said you're single?
Come back, come back.
I'll share my experience with you.
They've just made up,
and they're fighting again.
Judging from Lu Jing's expression,
he must be really mad.
Love is hard. It is so hard.
Qi Qi.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Qi Qi, who would be so sweet?
Could it be Gu Fei Ming?
I... I have no idea.
Why would no boy
be so sweet to me?
This tree is very tall.
It must've taken him some time.
Chubby,
where's Gu Fei Ming?
Gu Fei Ming is in the school hospital.
Wasn't he just discharged
from the hospital?
Why is he in the hospital again?
He fell down
when he was putting this stuff up.
Qi Qi!
Be gentle. Please, be gentle.
Have you not eaten?
Doctor, harder!
What happened? Are you hurt?
It's nothing.
I just sprained my ankle.
Don't cry, Qi Qi.
I always sprain my ankle.
It's nothing. I'm serious.
Really?
Really.
Doctor, please be gentle!
My arm is also dislocated.
Gu Fei Ming, have you lost your mind?
It's done. Are you hurt anywhere else?
Over here.
You're fine.
Will I lose my memory?
Don't worry. You won't lose your memory,
but you might have dementia.
Alright, young lady.
We'll leave your boyfriend to you.
We're leaving.
Are you hurt anywhere?
Qi Qi, have you forgiven me?
Silly,
why are you so stupid?
Shan Shan, why did you come here?
Surprise visit.
Come on in.
It's been a while
since you last tried my cooking.
It's time to show you my improvement.
Are you sure?
Don't hurt yourself.
Then you'll have to send me
to the hospital.
Don't worry about it.
I saw the news on the internet.
Don't get the wrong idea,
there's nothing between Sun Bin Yu and me.
They made it up.
Don't believe it.
I... I know.
I know you two well.
I'm just here to see you. Are you alright?
I...
I'm fine.
Those were groundless rumours.
I won't take it to heart.
That's great.
Stop it.
They're barely edible now.
[Regarding the recent
malicious misrepresentation]
[of Liang Chen’s private life
and other false statements,]
[our agency reserves the right]
[to take appropriate legal action.]
[Please do not believe in rumours
or spread them.]