How does it feel?
Like it's someone else's.
It isn't.
The criminal organization
known as LAF
is targeting Captain Vasant,
one of our military liaisons.
-LAF?
-Yeah, they're high-powered.
We lost contact with Vasant's plane
just after it took off.
We need you to make sure
that LAF doesn't deliver on their threat.
Vasant's plane has already entered
Tunisian airspace.
US military cannot be seen
operating out there.
I got it.
You guys fly low, drop me off,
I fly up to intercept.
No treaties violated.
First Lieutenant Torres,
our intel officer,
will be helping on the ground.
And Sam, this has to be subtle.
Subtle. Got it.
Sam, Torres here.
Sending intel to your HUD right now.
I'll be your boots on the ground, sir.
I got eyes on a plane. Any sign of LAF?
Nah. Nothing yet.
But I'll keep tracking the chatter.
They've already hijacked the plane.
Oh, we're gonna need to call some people.
Okay, switching to plan B.
Hey!
Redwing, engage.
Captain Vasant? Let's get you out of here.
Sam?
Oh!
Redwing, get 'em off our ass!
Keep going! We're close!
If we get to the border,
he's not gonna follow.
-What's up?
No!
All right, heads up!
You're about to fly into Libyan airspace.
And I assume
they have a problem with that.
Yeah, yeah. A big problem. A big problem.
-How long I got?
-Ninety seconds.
Aw, shit. He's outnumbered.
Sam, we gotta fall back!
We got to call it off!
We gotta find another way!
I just did.
Merde!
Whoo!
Yeah!
-Thanks.
You could try to reroute that
to the other…
Hey, could you not?
Oh.
I've been working with the Air Force
for six months now.
Every time ops touches him,
he gets all glitchy.
Well, you know, those poor techs
can't keep up
with a billion returning IP addresses
-and your sick-ass Stark-level tech.
Hey, Avengers.
He knows Arabic.
Wait, can you say that again?
Hold on a sec.
-All right. Come on.
Anyway, these LAF crews, man,
they're tryin' to take advantage of
all the chaos and make some money.
And that I get, but there's…
Oh, bam! Right there!
You see these guys?
They're guys you gotta worry about.
I've been stumbling onto
their manifestos on message boards.
They're called the Flag Smashers.
Is that a new thing?
Bad guys give themselves bad names.
There's a lot worse names than that one.
But basically, they think that
the world was better during The Blip.
Trust me, it wasn't.
Trust me. Every time something
gets better for one group,
it gets worse for another.
Yeah. Essentially, these people, they want
a world that's unified without borders.
So, you could see
why a lot of people are into that.
Yeah, but keep an eye on it.
If anything gets serious, you let me know.
No doubt. I'll… I'll, uh…
I'll track the online chatter,
see what they're saying. Yeah.
I do gotta ask you, though,
'cause online there's just been
a lot of stuff about Steve, actually.
Um, crazy, crazy conspiracy theories.
So, some people…
Some people, they think
that he's in a secret base on the moon
looking down over us.
Yeah. Well, I can assure you,
those people,
you don't have to take seriously.
But you didn't, like…
fly him to the moon?
-Nah.
-Oh…
Had to check.
Oh, oh, I got you, man.
-Thanks. I'll get you back next time.
-All right.
-So, where are you off to?
-Washington.
What are you doin' there?
Moon stuff.
Oh!
Steve represented
the best in all of us.
Courageous, righteous, hopeful.
And he mastered posing stoically.
The world has been forever changed.
A few months ago,
billions of people
reappeared after five years away,
sending the world into turmoil.
We need new heroes.
Ones suited for the times we're in.
Symbols…
are nothing without the women and men
that give them meaning.
And this thing…
I don't know if there's ever been
a greater symbol.
But it's more about the man
who propped it up,
and he's gone.
So, today we honor Steve's legacy.
But also, we look to the future.
So, thank you, Captain America.
But this belongs to you.
Thanks again for coming forward
with the shield, Sam.
It was the right decision.
Take a walk?
Yeah, I've been at home.
My sister and my nephews, man.
When I left, they were babies.
I come back and they're little men.
-It's crazy, you know?
-Yeah.
Well, you should bring 'em out
to D.C. sometime.
I'll teach 'em how to fly.
-You know, I mean, the right way.
Crazy that nobody's
gonna be carryin' the shield.
Hey, we went
for 70 years without anybody
carryin' it when Steve was on ice.
So, I think we'll be all right.
That was a different time, Sam.
I see you're gonna make me ask.
Why didn't you take up the mantle?
When Steve first told me about the shield,
the first words I said were,
"It feels like it belongs
to someone else."
Hmm.
That someone else is Steve.
World's a crazy place right now.
People are…
Well, nobody's stable.
Allies are now enemies.
Alliances are all torn apart.
The world's broken.
Everybody's just looking
for somebody to fix it.
Yeah.
It's a new day, brother.
I'll be in touch.
I mean… Thank you.
-Oh… Well, that's done.
-Yeah.
Half hour before last call?
I can't, guys.
I have to prep for tomorrow's session.
-Really?
-You…
Ooh!
Hail HYDRA.
Shit.
Please.
I didn't see anything.
So, Mr. Barnes,
are you still having nightmares?
James, I asked you a question.
Are you still having nightmares?
No.
We've been doing this long enough
that I can tell when you're lying.
Well, you seem a little off today.
Did something happen recently?
No.
You're a civilian now.
With your history, the government
needs to know that you're not gonna…
It's a condition of your pardon.
So, tell me about
your most recent nightmare.
I didn't have a nightmare.
Oh, come on. Really?
You're gonna do the notebook thing?
Why? It's passive aggressive.
You don't talk. I write.
Okay. Okay.
I crossed a name off
the list of my amends yesterday.
Don't worry. I used all your three rules.
Senator Atwood.
She was a HYDRA pawn for years.
Helped her get into office
when I was the Winter Soldier.
And after HYDRA disbanded,
she continued to abuse
the power I gave her.
Make this go away.
If Congressman Lockhart wants to speak up,
silence him for good.
So, rule number one,
you can't do anything illegal.
What the hell?
All I did was give some intel
to the aide to convict her.
And I wasn't involved in anything else.
Rule number two?
What was rule number two?
Nobody gets hurt. It's a big one.
Then why isn't it rule number one?
I didn't hurt anybody.
Come on!
Remember me?
I promise.
And what about
rule number three?
The whole point of making amends
is to fulfill rule number three.
You know, you're a cynic, Doc.
Of course, I completed rule number three.
I am no longer the Winter Soldier.
I am James Bucky Barnes…
And you're part of my efforts
to make amends.
So, you did it all right,
but it didn't help with the nightmares.
Well, like I said, I didn't have any.
Look…
one day, you're gonna have to open up
and understand that some people
really do want to help you
and that they can be trusted.
I trust people.
Yeah? Give me your phone.
You don't have ten phone numbers
on this thing.
Oh, and you've been
ignoring the texts from Sam.
Look, you've gotta nurture friendships.
I am the only person
you have called all week.
-That is so sad.
You're alone.
You're a hundred years old.
You have no history, no family…
Are you lashing out at me, Doc?
Because that's
really unprofessional, you know?
When did that start?
Yelling at your clients?
The notebook. That's great.
All right, give me a break.
I'm trying, okay?
This isn't…
This is new for me.
I didn't have a moment
to deal with anything, you know?
I had a little…
calm in Wakanda.
And other than that, I just went
from one fight to another for 90 years.
So, now that you've stopped fighting,
what do you want?
Peace.
That is utter bullshit.
You're a terrible shrink.
I was an excellent soldier,
so I saw a lot of dead bodies,
and I know how that can shut you down.
And if you are alone,
that is the quietest, most personal hell.
And, James, it is very hard to escape.
Look, I know that
you have been through a lot,
but you've got your mind back,
you are being pardoned.
I mean, these are good things.
You're free.
To do what?
Hey, hey, hey! Hey!
What? What?
Your can isn't even half full.
Why don't we just share?
-What?
-You don't gotta body me, Yori.
-It's Mr. Nakajima.
-Okay.
-Mr. Nakajima!
-Okay. Mr. Nakajima.
Hey! Hey! Yori, what's goin' on?
I thought we're getting lunch.
Unique is putting his trash into my trash.
It's trash.
-And the time has come for me to smack…
-Whoa!
-It's just trash.
-Hang on.
Hey, man. I'm Unique.
It's like Monique, but it's got
a "U" in there for uniqueness.
-That's absurd.
-Okay, sorry.
Yori, you can't keep
fighting with your neighbors.
-Come on, let's get some food.
-No, go away.
But Izzy.
We always go to Izzy on Wednesday.
-I'm not in the mood today.
-Hey, what if I buy?
Fine, but no talking.
Take a look.
Nobody made it past 90 this week.
So young. Such a shame.
You guys didn't order the usual, huh?
Feeling a little adventurous?
You should ask her out.
Mm-mmm…
He would like to take you out on a date.
Maybe to bingo or a night of pinochle?
Pinochle. Yeah.
-I'm really sorry about him.
-Why are you sorry?
-I'm game.
-Wow.
-Tomorrow night, then?
-Tomorrow night's great.
Just maybe not pinochle.
-What's wrong with pinochle?
-Yeah.
I have a shift,
but if you wanna come back here,
I should be done around 10:00.
I can't believe you did that.
It's a dance to these things.
You can't… You gotta warm up
and I haven't danced since 1943…
it feels like.
What's wrong?
He had a job with a consulting company.
And, uh,
he was working abroad and he was killed.
The police said
"Wrong place, wrong time," but…
I will never know
what really happened to him.
I felt it was strange.
In here.
This, too, Mom?
Yeah, all of it, baby.
And we're taking that one
to the soup kitchen.
So, put that one over there.
Blue for the snapper,
orange for the whitefish.
Uncle Sam!
What's up?
That's right!
Uncle Sam, you're back early.
What's goin' on?
You got Mom's sneaky look on your face.
How you gonna try to read me
when you know I'm the one that reads you?
You gotta marvel at it.
Baby being held together
by duct tape and prayers.
It'll be fine. It just needs to float
long enough for me to sell it.
I thought we were gonna discuss
if we were selling it.
We did.
And then you were off fighting
Doctor Space Cape or whatever
while I was holdin' it together
for five long years.
Now that the world
is going back to normal,
this thing's gotta go.
We grew up on this thing.
It's not just Mom and Dad's
name on it, Sarah.
This thing is a part of our family.
You know the situation we're in.
This is why I prefer
not to dwell on it in front of everybody.
Well, what if we don't have to sell it?
Can I talk to you?
-What's good, Big Sam?
-Oh! What's goin' on, man?
-I'm trying to live like you.
-You know it.
-Off to save the world again?
-Nah.
Come on, Carlos.
I'm around here more than you.
I'm always reppin' NOLA.
When you gonna let me
borrow the wings, man?
As soon as you give my sister back
that $100 you borrowed.
-That's cold. Now, loan me a hot $50.
-Yeah. I'll loan you $50.
-Sam, the boat's gotta go.
-Wait.
No, let me finish.
I'm doin' everything I can
to keep this business afloat.
And every day I'm making $5,
and spending $10.
-So, why won't you let me help?
-No, don't start with that.
We made a deal before Daddy died.
You're out there. I do things my way here.
Right. But you tangled the house
into this when you took those loans.
Forgot how hard you hit.
Sarah!
Look, and don't hit me again.
What if you had money to fix it up,
make it nice so you can charter it
when you're not out working the waters?
Do you know how hard it was for me
to come to terms with the situation?
Why would you dig this up?
We can take a loan
and consolidate everything.
It'll take down your monthly.
-What?
-You think I didn't try the banks?
They're in with all that big business.
Yeah. But now you have me.
Don't, Sam.
-I just got good with this.
-All right.
-Maybe it is time for us to move on.
-Either way, just let me help.
I'll set the appointment.
Look, I won't let you down.
We can turn this shit around.
Trust me.
To the rescue?
Always.
Now, let's get some dinner. I'm hungry.
Well,
if that's not the most adorably
old-fashioned thing
anyone's ever done.
Grab a seat, I'll be done in a few.
Okay.
So, have you dated much since
half the fish in the sea came back?
Not really.
I, um…
tried the whole online dating thing.
It's pretty crazy.
A lot of weird pictures.
What kind of weird?
I mean, tiger photos?
Half the time I don't even know
what I'm looking at. It's…
It's a lot.
You sound like my dad.
Mmm…
Wait, how old are you?
A hundred and six.
What's up with your gloves?
I, um…
have, uh…
Poor circulation.
Hmm…
-Let's play a game.
-Yeah.
-You like games?
-Love 'em.
We keep some games around
for boring shifts.
I'll go grab a couple of beers.
What are you doing?
I'm reading your mind.
Please don't.
B-8, sucker.
-Uh, hit!
-Drink! Come on, drink.
All right. Okay.
Wow, you really can drink.
Yeah, well…
Do you have any siblings?
I have a sister. F-4.
Miss. Drink.
Are you close with your parents?
I was.
They passed away.
Um, D-5.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Um, miss.
I think it's really sweet
you're spending time with Yori.
It's been hard for him his son died.
I think not knowing how it happened
is the hardest part for him.
Mmm, it really messed him up.
You know how you call a guy
whose wife died a widower?
Or, if your parents die, you're an orphan.
You know, there's no word
for someone whose kids die.
Because it's the worst thing
that could happen.
Yeah, excuse me.
You good?
Hey, what are you doing here?
How was the date?
It was… It was good.
Forgot I owed you for lunch.
There we go.
Get the plates moving.
Get some rice in there. Come on.
Oh, lined up perfectly.
You always gotta do the most, huh?
I don't play
with these White folks.
Look, I know you're worried, all right?
But I did the research. I ran the numbers.
-You think this is gonna work?
-I know it will.
And then we can renovate the kitchen.
Now, you said you wanted
to sell plates on the weekends, right?
That's great. You can introduce
some of Grandma's recipes and…
Shit. We gotta go.
Wait, the appointment's in an hour.
There's no such thing as on time.
You're either early or late. Pick one.
Okay. Now you're
really doing more than the most.
All right, boys, I love you.
Now, Mr. Liu's gonna watch over you
and no video games.
-Love you. Bye.
-Bye.
Yes, video games.
-Three, two, one.
Go, go, go!
He's getting away!
Sorry. Uh…
Hey, hey, hey!
I don't know how jurisdiction works here,
but I'mma have to place you under arrest.
Sorry, I keep thinking.
Did you used to play for LSU?
-Do I know you from somewhere?
I don't know. Do you?
I do. But where?
Come on.
-I knew it. Falcon!
-Yeah!
Yes! Yes! Man! Oh…
I didn't want to say anything. You know…
I always wanted to be an Avenger.
Oh, man, it's a dream come true, you know?
That's amazing.
Like, keeping my family's business afloat
by changin' to
a fishin' and charter model.
I've always wondered…
How do you guys make a living?
Those guys or the guy sitting
in front of you tryin' to get a loan?
Both.
I mean, your financials
are all over the place.
Is there some kind of fund for heroes?
Or did Stark pay you when he was around?
My condolences, by the way.
Thank you, but no,
it doesn't really work like that.
There's a tremendous amount of goodwill
and because of that,
people are inclined to help,
-which applies to the business.
-Yeah, right.
But were you living off
of goodwill this whole time?
I don't get what you're going for here.
Are you trying to help us,
or indict us?
You have no income
over the last five years.
How can you have income
if you don't exist?
Sarah.
Uh…
I've been gone
like several billion other people.
But if you look at our plan,
I have government contracts,
so, that's proof of earnings.
And I know for a fact
that we qualify for a SBA loan.
Under the old terms, sure.
But these days, what,
with everyone just showing up,
well, things tightened up.
Funny how things always tighten around us.
Easy there. Look, I'm on your side.
After all, he's a hero.
Is there any chance,
and you could say "no,"
that I could get a selfie
with your arms out?
-Are you serious?
Mr. Wilson, Mrs. Wilson…
Miss. I'm a widow.
Ms. Wilson.
I know your family
has banked with us for generations,
but we cannot approve you.
I'm truly sorry.
We're gonna get that loan. I don't care
if I have to go to every bank in the city.
Sam, stop!
I don't want to deal with this again.
That's what life is,
dealing with things.
You are so out of pocket for that.
Don't forget, you joined the Air Force.
You didn't see everything
Mom and Daddy dealt with.
I knew they weren't gonna help us.
It's not their job.
Those people don't know who Daddy was,
and he was a giant.
I don't care. I'm not gonna quit.
What are you trying to prove?
And who you trying to prove it to?
-I swear, after Daddy died…
-I knew that was gonna come up.
I never hid what I thought. You had
to go off and fight armies and monsters.
And I appreciate that,
but you don't get to come back here
and try to right your wrongs
just because you couldn't
deal with what was going on here.
You don't know what happened
these last five years.
I was alone with two babies
and I survived.
I'm the one
who kept that boat from sinkin'.
Yeah, well, half the boat's mine
and so is the house.
We're not sellin' our family's legacy.
You gonna do me like that
when you know I'm right?
Yep!
Okay.
Oh!
Come on, baby.
What you got for me?
Come on! Come on!
Shit!
So, this is the leader
of the Flag Smashers, huh?
Yeah, real nice guy.
I thought you were
supposed to be monitoring them online.
I was. I did.
But you know sometimes you gotta
get your hands dirty,
-or a broken orbital.
You're lucky that's all you got.
He's strong.
He was. I mean, bro,
they went dark as soon as it was all over.
But that's their M.O.
We gotta keep our eyes and ears
to the ground till they pop up again.
Anything else happen outside the video?
No, man. My face was in the dirt
before I knew what was happening.
Why? What are you thinking?
Nothin'.
Wait. You don't think he could be a…
Look, I'll circle back to you.
-Let's keep this between me and you, okay?
-All right.
Oh, my God, Sam.
You better look at this.
Unrest,
in the wake of recent events
has left us vulnerable.
Every day Americans feel it.
While we love heroes who put
their lives on the line to defend Earth,
we also need a hero
to defend this country.
We need a real person
who embodies America's greatest values.
We need someone to inspire us again,
someone who can be a symbol for all of us.
So, on behalf of the Department of Defense
and our Commander-in-Chief,
it is with great honor
that we announce here today
that the United States of America
has a new hero.
Join me in welcoming
your new Captain America.