World's a crazy place right now.
Alliances are all torn apart.
The world's broken.
Symbols are nothing without the
women and men that give them meaning.
Thank you, Captain America.
But this belongs to you.
Tell me about your most recent nightmare.
Look, I know that you
have been through a lot,
but you've got your mind back,
you are being pardoned. You're free.
To do what?
Oh, bam! Right there!
You see these guys?
They're guys you gotta worry about.
They're called the Flag Smashers.
They want a world that's
unified without borders.
So, this is the leader
of the Flag Smashers, huh?
He's strong.
Oh, my God, Sam.
You better look at this.
Join me in welcoming
your new Captain America.
Reliving the glory days?
I remember sneaking into this locker room
before each game to see you.
It's probably why we always won.
You nervous?
-Who, me?
-Mmm-hmm.
Never.
I've been a captain before,
obviously, but this is different.
This is…
Everybody in the world
expects me to be something.
And I don't wanna fail them.
-I know.
-Yeah.
Be yourself.
Yeah.
They're gonna love you.
Good luck.
-Love you.
-Did he puke yet?
-Not yet. You're up.
-Copy that.
-Good morning.
Good morning, America.
Good morning.
No, you're Captain America, you're not…
John, Captain, uh…
Captain America.
And that's why you failed drama class.
-Can you believe this?
-I know, right?
-Yeah.
-Two weeks ago we're prepping the team
for a special ops
mission in Chile, now this.
Don't get me wrong,
this has been great,
it's been great,
but it's been a lot of handshakes,
a lot of suits,
a lot of speeches,
and senator meetings,
and I just wanna do the job.
-This is the job, John.
-Yeah.
All of it is.
Star-spangled man with a plan and all that.
It's always been in the job description.
Listen, this suit,
it comes with expectations, brother.
Mmm-hmm.
You can't just punch your way
out of problems anymore, you know?
Mmm-hmm.
Time to go to work.
Thank you.
Ladies and gentlemen…
Your new Captain America!
Good morning, America.
Yeah!
Thank you so much for coming.
This has gotta be fun, though,
coming back to your high
school after so much has changed?
-John Walker!
-Oh, it's great. We're…
Oh!
Yeah.
John, I think the first
thing everyone wants to know
is what is it like being Captain America?
Do eagles fly overhead wherever you go?
Uh, yes.
Yeah, that and flags tend to
start majestically waving in the wind.
And how's the tour been?
I know they did a big
rollout for you, right?
It's the greatest honor of my life.
Um, but I'm just a little shocked, I think.
How did a guy like me end up here?
Oh, wait, wait, wait. "A guy like me"?
Somebody's being a bit too humble.
For those of you who aren't
familiar with his résumé,
"John Walker, first person in American
history to receive three Medals of Honor,
"ran RS-One missions in
counterterrorism and hostage rescue."
The government did a
study of your body at MIT,
and you tested off the charts
in every measurable category.
Speed, endurance, intelligence…
Look, here's the thing, uh,
I'm not Tony Stark,
I'm not Dr. Banner, okay?
I don't have the flashiest gadgets,
I don't have super strength.
But what I do have
is guts.
Something Captain America always had,
always needs to have,
and I'm gonna need every ounce of it.
Because I got big shoes to fill.
Did you know Steve Rogers?
I was two years out of West Point
when Steve came back on the scene.
I followed his career
very closely as an Avenger.
I like to think that I
modeled my work after his.
You've always wanted to be a hero?
I liked that what I was doing
\would make people feel safe.
Steve Rogers was the kind
of guy who could do that,
he gave me hope.
Even though I never met him,
he feels like a brother.
Wow.
Seems like a good guy.
-You met him?
-No.
Thanks for doing this on such short notice.
Yeah. No sweat.
I'm just finishing up the checklist.
You'll be all good to go
once you land in Munich.
-Shouldn't have given up the shield.
-Good to see you too, Buck.
-This is wrong.
-Hey, hey, look, I'm working, all right?
So all this outrage is gonna have to wait.
You didn't know that was gonna happen?
No, of course I didn't
know that was gonna happen.
You think it didn't break my
heart to see them march him out there
-and call him the new Captain America?
-Steve didn't want this.
Oh, my God.
What do you want me to do?
Call America and tell 'em
I changed my mind? Huh?
Yeah, right.
It's a great reunion, buddy, be well.
You had no right to give up the shield, Sam.
Hey.
This is what you're not gonna do.
You're not gonna come here
in your overextended life
and tell me about my rights.
It's over, Bucky.
Besides, I have bigger
things to deal with now.
What could be bigger than this?
This guy.
His connections with rebel organizations
all over Eastern and Central Europe,
and he's strong.
Too strong.
And?
Well, he's been connected to this
online group called the Flag Smashers.
Now, Redwing traced them to a
building somewhere outside of Munich.
-So that's where I'm going.
-Well, I don't trust Redwing.
-Hold on a minute.
-You don't have to trust Redwing,
but I'mma go see if he's right.
'Cause I have a feeling they
might be a part of the Big Three.
-What "Big Three"?
-The Big Three.
-What Big Three?
-Androids, aliens, and wizards.
-That's not a thing.
-That's definitely a thing.
No, it's not.
Every time we fight,
it's one of the three.
-Who are you fighting now, Gandalf?
-How do you know about Gandalf?
I read The Hobbit in
1937 when it first came out.
-So you see my point?
-No, I don't. There are no wizards.
-Doctor Strange.
-Is a sorcerer.
Aah!
A sorcerer is a wizard without a hat.
Think about it. Right?
I'm right.
I just came up with that. It's crazy.
But that's not the point.
These guys aren't magical.
They use brute force like you,
the incredibly annoying guy in
front of me with the staring problem.
-I'm coming with you.
-No, you're not.
One minute to drop off, Sam.
So what's our plan?
Great. So no plan.
Thirty seconds!
-Enjoy your ride, Buck.
-No, you can't call me that.
Why not? That's what Steve called you.
Steve knew me longer,
and Steve had a plan.
Fifteen seconds to drop.
I have a plan.
Really?
What is it?
Great.
Where's the chute?
We're at 200 feet.
It's too low for a chute.
I don't need it anyway.
You sure about that?
Yeah.
I have all of that on camera.
You know that, right?
Get out of my face, Sam, or I'll break it.
Okay, head north. Come on.
Oh-ho-ho. Don't hurt him.
You're doing the staring thing again.
They're in there.
-Where's the guy?
-I don't know.
I think they're smuggling weapons, though.
-Well, I think you could be right.
-Hmm.
But there's only one way to find out.
I see a clear path. I say we take it.
We're not assassins.
I'll see you inside or not.
Hey, come on, man.
I'm just messing with you. Come back.
Look at you. All stealthy.
A little time in Wakanda
and you come out White Panther.
-It's actually White Wolf.
-Huh?
All right, I'm inside.
Therefore, way ahead of you.
It's not great, but very doable.
Huh?
-Hello. How are you?
-Good. What did I miss? Nothing.
-All right, let's go.
-No, wait.
I got a vibranium arm.
I can take them.
And I can fly.
Who gives a shit? Wait.
-I want to see where they're going.
-There's two people.
-You only see two?
-That's what I saw.
-Let me see what Redwing sees.
-All right.
Let's see what Redwing…
Oh, look at that.
How many people you see now?
One, two…
Oh, here it comes again.
-Four. Five.
-Yeah, five. Yeah.
So they're strong. Whatever.
-All right, let's go.
-No, no, wait.
Shit.
All right, let's move.
Let's move. Yeah.
There's an eighth person.
I think they have a hostage.
They're stealing medicine. Vaccines.
Hi.
Bucky, talk to me.
What's goin' on?
Found the hostage.
You okay?
Shit.
I always wanted to do that.
Good of you to join the fight, Sam!
Sam. John Walker, Captain America.
Lemar Hoskins.
Looks like you guys can use some help.
That little girl kicked your ass.
John, where you at, man?
Could have used that shield.
Get off of me.
Those were all Super Soldiers, Sam.
I know.
You're welcome, by the way.
I'm okay. I'm okay.
That was a bad idea.
-Sorry about Redwing.
-No, you're not.
What's going on in that
big cyborg brain of yours?
It's computing.
You know what? I can actually see it.
I can see the gears turning.
Oh, they're malfunctioning,
shutting down. Yep, they're on fire.
We gotta figure out
where the serum's coming from.
Yeah. And how in the hell after 80 years
are there eight Super
Soldiers runnin' loose?
So that didn't go as planned, huh?
Okay.
Let's keep going.
Look, at least we know
what we're up against now, huh?
And we're pretty sure
it's one of the Big Three, so…
-Aliens, androids, or wizards?
-Pretty sure.
There's no such thing as wizards.
-Then it's aliens, or androids…
-Or Super Soldiers.
-Shit. Super Soldiers, for real?
-Yeah.
Wow. All right, well,
then we gotta work together.
That's not happening.
I think we stand a much
better chance if we all just…
Just 'cause you carry that shield,
it doesn't mean you're Captain America.
Look, I've done the work, okay?
-You ever jump on top of a grenade?
-Yeah. Actually, I have. Four times.
It's a thing I do with my helmet.
It's a reinforced helmet.
It's a long story, but, any…
Look, it's 20 miles to the airport.
You guys need a ride.
Guys. Gary, stop. Get in.
Okay, so we've got eight
Super Soldiers on a bulk supply run.
Why?
They say their mission is to get things
back to the way it was during The Blip.
-Maybe they're just trying to help.
-They had a funny way of showing it.
That serum doesn't exactly have
a great track record. No offense.
We need to figure out where they're going.
How'd you track 'em here?
The Flag Smashers?
Uh, no, we didn't track them,
we tracked you, uh, through Redwing.
You hacked my tech?
Sorry. It's not exactly hacking.
It's government property.
Kind of the government.
Does he always just stare like that?
You get used to it.
Okay, look, you know,
things have gotten kind of, uh…
Chaotic.
Yeah. The GRC, they're
doing the best they can
to get things up and
running smoothly, post Blip.
Reactivating citizenship,
social security, healthcare.
Basically just managing resources
for the refugees who
were displaced by the return.
The Global Repatriation Council
does all that. I get that.
So why exactly are you two here?
Well, they provide the
resources and we keep things stable.
Yeah, violent revolutionaries
aren't usually good for anyone's cause.
Usually said by the
people with the resources.
We got a lot of resources.
If you guys, if you
joined up with us, we could…
-No.
-I got mad respect for both of y'all.
But you were getting your
asses kicked till we showed up.
-Who are you?
-Lemar Hoskins.
Look, I see a guy hanging out
of a helicopter in tactical gear,
I need a lot more than Lemar Hoskins.
I'm Battlestar. John's partner.
"Battlestar"?
Stop the car!
Look, I… I get it, okay?
I get the attitude, I do.
You didn't think that the
shield was gonna end up here.
I get it, Bucky.
And I'm…
I'm not trying to be Steve.
I'm not trying to replace Steve.
I'm just trying to be the
best Captain America I can be.
That's it.
It'd be a whole lot easier if
I had Cap's wingmen on my side.
It's always that last line.
Let's go.
You must be famished.
-Very hungry.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, we are hungry.
-Okay. My wife and I cooked.
It's an old family recipe made
with the finest chicken livers.
Please serve yourselves.
-Anything you want. Anything. You ask me.
-Um…
There is some coffee here and some crackers.
-We're okay. Thank you.
-Uh, anything we can do for the cause.
Please follow me.
You're becoming a bit of a legend.
I hear more and more people talk about
the freedom fighters who are pushing back.
They call you Robin Hood.
Every day more people love you.
You'll find refuge wherever you go.
My wife and I made this just for you.
Everything is completely clean.
-Okay.
-She made it nice and cozy.
-Thank you. Yeah!
-You're welcome.
Oh, my gosh, beds.
That's real nice.
This has your name written all over it, bro.
Hope you feel comfortable.
Thank you.
-Too small.
-Shit. They're already looking for us.
I'm wiping our aliases off
any public traffic sites now.
Karli. We can't stay here for long.
Six months ago would you have imagined
people supporting the cause like this?
We're not playing no more.
We can't let these assholes
who were put back in
power after The Blip win.
The GRC care more about the people
who came back than the ones who never left.
We got a glimpse of how things could be.
I need to know that you're all committed,
because after tomorrow,
there's no going back.
Yeah. One world.
One people.
-One world.
-One people.
-One world!
-One people!
You all right?
Let's take the shield, Sam.
Let's take the shield and do this ourselves.
We can't just run up on the man,
beat him up, and take it.
Do you remember what
happened the last time we stole it?
-Maybe.
-I'll help you in case you forgot.
Sharon was branded enemy of the state,
and Steve and I were
on the run for two years.
I don't know about you,
but I don't wanna live the
rest of my life la vida loca.
We just got our ass handed to us
by Super Soldiers, and we got nothing.
Not entirely true.
There is someone that you should meet.
-Hey, it's Black Falcon. What's up?
-It's just Falcon, kid.
No, no.
My daddy told me it's Black Falcon.
Is it because I'm Black and I'm the Falcon?
Well, technically, I mean, yes.
So are you, like, Black kid?
I got him, right?
Whatever, man.
Whatever.
We're here to see Isaiah.
Nobody named Isaiah live here.
Look, we just want to talk to him.
You must not hear what I just said.
You ain't getting in this house.
Y'all can leave now.
Tell him the guy from
the bar in Goyang is here.
He's gonna know what that means.
All right, wait here.
Nice kid.
How do you know this guy?
I used to.
We had a skirmish during the Korean War.
Today's your lucky day.
He said he wanna see for himself.
Isaiah?
Look at you.
This is, uh, Sam.
Sam, this is Isaiah.
He was a hero.
One of the ones that HYDRA
feared the most. Like Steve.
We met in '51.
If by met, you mean I
whupped your ass, then, yeah.
We heard whispers he was on the peninsula,
but everyone they sent
after him, never came back.
So the U.S. military dropped me
behind the line to go deal with him.
I took half that metal
arm in that fight in Goyang,
but I see he's managed to grow it back.
I just wanted to see if he got the arm back.
Or if he'd come to kill me.
I'm not a killer anymore.
You think you can wake up one
day and decide who you wanna be?
It doesn't work like that.
Well, maybe it does for folks like you.
Isaiah, the reason we're here
is because there's more
of you and me out there.
-You and me.
-And we need to know how.
I'm not gonna talk about it anymore.
You know what they did
to me for being a hero?
They put my ass in jail for 30 years.
People running tests,
taking my blood, coming into my cell.
Even your people weren't done with me.
-Isaiah…
-Get out of my house!
Let's go, man, let's go.
-Sam…
-Why didn't you tell me about Isaiah?
How could nobody bring him up?
-I asked you a question, Bucky.
-I know.
-Steve didn't know about him?
-He didn't. I didn't tell him.
So you're telling me that
there was a black Super Soldier
decades ago and nobody knew about it?
Hey.
What's up, man?
-Is there a problem here?
-No, we're just talking.
We're fine.
Can I see your ID?
-I don't have ID. Why?
-Man, seriously?
Okay, sir, just calm down.
I am calm.
What do you want? We're just talking.
-Give him your ID so we can leave.
-No.
-We're just talking.
-Is he bothering you?
No, he's not bothering me.
Do you know who this is?
Hey, these guys are Avengers.
Oh, God, I am so sorry, Mr. Wilson.
I didn't recognize you without the goggles.
I'm really, really sorry about this.
The…
Guys, just wait here, okay? Just…
I didn't… I didn't tell anybody
because he had already been through enough.
Mr. Barnes,
there's a warrant out for your arrest.
Look, the president
pardoned him for all that.
Not for that. You missed
your court-mandated therapy.
It's like missing a check-in with your PO.
I'm sorry, Mr. Barnes, you're under arrest.
Sam. I've heard a lot about you.
I'm Dr. Raynor. I'm James's therapist.
So nice to meet you.
Thank you for getting him out.
That was not me.
Christina.
-It's great to see you again.
-You gotta be kidding me. You know him?
Yeah, we did some field ops back in the day.
I heard you were working with Bucky,
so I thought I'd step in.
Bucky's not gonna be following
a strict schedule any longer.
We haven't finished our work.
Who authorized this?
Um…
He's too valuable of
an asset to have tied up.
Just do whatever you got to do
with him, then send him off to me.
Got some unfinished business, him and I.
You too, Wilson.
I'll be outside.
James, condition of your release,
session now. You too, Sam.
-That's okay. I'll be out here with…
-That wasn't a request.
So…
Who would like to start?
All right, look, Dr. Raynor?
I get it, why you want me to
talk to Freaky Magoo over here.
But I'm 100% fine.
It is my job to make sure that you're okay.
And so, yeah, this may
be slightly unprofessional,
but it's the only way that I can see
if you're getting over
whatever's eating at you.
-This is ridiculous.
-Yeah. I agree.
See? Making progress already.
So, who wants to go first?
No volunteers?
Wow. How surprising.
Okay. We're going to do an exercise.
It's something I use with couples
when they are trying to figure out
what kind of life they wanna build together.
Are you familiar with the miracle question?
-Absolutely not.
-Of course not.
Okay, it goes like this.
Suppose that while you're
sleeping, a miracle occurs.
When you wake up,
what is something that you would like
to see that would make your life better?
In my miracle, he would…
he would talk less.
Exactly what I was gonna say.
Isn't that ironic?
You guys are leaving me with no choice.
It's time for the soul-gazing exercise.
-I like this better.
-Oh, God. He's gonna love this.
-Yeah, I'm ready.
-This is right up your alley.
-Turn around. Face each other.
-You should really enjoy this.
I'm going to.
-I know you are.
-Yeah.
-Sam. Face each other.
-Let's do it. Let's stare.
-Get close.
-This is a good exercise. Thanks, Doc.
All right, good.
All right, get close.
Come on, a little closer.
Which way you want to go?
-Right or left?
-Why're your legs open?
You know what? Fine.
Here. You happy now?
-All right.
-Good. Fine.
-We're locked in.
-That's a little close.
-Very. What you wanted, right?
Guys.
Good. Now look at each other.
You need to look at each other in the eyes.
There, you see?
That wasn't so hard.
Wait, what are you doing?
Are you having a staring contest?
Just blink. Sweet Jesus.
All right, James,
why does Sam aggravate you?
And don't say something childish.
Why did you give up that shield?
Why are you making such a big deal
out of something that
has nothing to do with you?
Steve believed in you.
He trusted you.
He gave you that shield for a reason.
That shield, that is…
that is everything he stood for.
That is his legacy.
He gave you that shield, and you
threw it away like it was nothing.
-Shut up.
-So maybe he was wrong about you.
And if he was wrong about you,
then he was wrong about me.
You finished?
-Yeah.
-All right, good.
Maybe this is something you
or Steve will never understand.
But can you accept that
I did what I thought was right?
You know what, Doc?
I don't have time for this.
We have some real serious shit going on.
So how about this?
I will squash it right now.
We go deal with that,
and when we're done,
we both can go on separate,
long vacations
and never see each other again.
-I like that.
-Great.
Well, let's get to work.
Thanks, Doc, for making it weird.
I feel much better.
I'll see you outside.
Thank you.
That was really great.
I know that look. What's wrong?
What was rule number two again?
Don't hurt anyone.
Goodbye, Doc.
Well, I feel better.
I feel awful.
Gentlemen.
Good to see you again.
Look, if we divide ourselves,
we don't stand a chance,
you guys know that.
So what do you got?
Well, the leader's name's Karli Morgenthau.
We've been targeting civilians
who've been helping
Karli move from place to place.
They geotagged a location,
then scrambled the signal.
But our satellites have
found their symbol popping up
in various displaced communities
all across Central and Eastern Europe.
We think she's taking the medicine
she just stole to one of these camps.
Well, there are hundreds of those
all over the planet since The Blip.
So I guess you'll have to look real hard.
Good thing I have 20/20 vision, huh?
-Where is she now, Walker? Do you know?
-No, we don't know, Bucky.
It's only a matter of
time before we find out.
Things are really intense for you,
aren't they, Walker?
Take it easy.
Look, Walker's right.
It is imperative that
we find them and stop them.
But you guys have rules of engagement
and all kind of
authorizations you have to get.
We're free agents.
We're more flexible.
So it wouldn't make
sense for us to work with you.
A word of advice, then.
Stay the hell out of my way.
Damn it! We gotta move out now.
-They found us.
-How much time do we have?
-None. It's The Power Broker's men.
-Everybody, grab what you can.
I can give you time.
I'll hold them off.
Thank you.
One world. One people.
Let's go!
All right,
stop right there. Freeze!
Hit him, open fire.
They got away.
So what are you thinking?
Well, I know what we have to do.
When Isaiah said "my people"…
Oh, don't take that to heart.
That's not what he meant.
No, he meant HYDRA.
HYDRA used to be my people.
Not a chance.
-Walker doesn't have any leads.
-I know where you're going with this, no.
He knows all of HYDRA's secrets.
Don't you remember Siberia?
So you're just gonna go
sit in a room with this guy?
Yes.
Okay, then.
We're gonna go see Zemo.