They're stealing medicine. Vaccines.
Hi.
Shit.
We've got eight Super Soldiers
on a bulk supply run. Why?
They say their mission is to get things
back to the way it was during The Blip.
Maybe they're just trying to help.
That serum doesn't
have a great track record.
So you're telling me that
there was a Black Super Soldier
decades ago and nobody knew about it?
You know what they did to me?
People taking my blood.
- Isaiah…
- Get out of my house!
Let's take the shield, Sam.
Remember what happened when we stole it?
Maybe.
Sharon was branded enemy of the state,
and Steve and I were
on the run for two years.
Steve believed in you.
So he gave you that shield, and
you threw it away like it was nothing.
- Shut up.
- He was wrong about you.
And if he was wrong about you,
then he was wrong about me.
We've been targeting civilians
who've been helping Karli move.
Our satellites have found
their symbol popping up
in various displaced communities
all across Central and Eastern Europe.
- Walker doesn't have any leads.
- I know where you're going with this, no.
He knows all of HYDRA's secrets.
Don't you remember Siberia?
Okay, then.
We're gonna go see Zemo.
When half of us came back,
it was time to rejoice and reunite.
The Global Repatriation Council
knows that for many it wasn't that easy.
So much has changed.
But we're here to help you find your way.
Helping you back
into your homes and jobs.
Helping you navigate changes
to society, laws, and borders.
Helping you get back
to the way things were.
GRC, the Global Repatriation Council.
Reset. Restore. Rebuild.
Let's move.
Don't give him a second
to delete, shred, or breathe.
- Sir, my name is John Walker.
- Hey, stop!
You're hiding a criminal named
Karli Morgenthau. Do you know her?
Lemar, need a translator.
Ask him if he knows
Karli Morgenthau and the Flag Smashers.
- He says he doesn't know.
- Bullshit. That's bullshit.
We know she came through here.
Now where'd she go?
Do you know who I am?
Yes, I do. And I don't care.
It's a waste of time, man.
We ain't gonna find 'em.
You heard anything back
from anybody at Langley?
Nah.
Karli must be funneling
something from someone I can't see.
Listen, she's giving displaced
people shelter and medicine.
- I know.
- That kinda thing creates loyalty, man.
I know you want this. I get it.
But we've literally
tried everything we can here.
So has Langley,
and we keep drawin' blanks.
So we bet on someone
who's got a better hand.
- He's just through that corridor.
- Give us a sec.
- I'm gonna go in alone.
- Why?
You're an Avenger.
You know how he feels about that.
It's not like you two were known
for frolickin' in the sun together.
He was obsessed with HYDRA.
We have a history together.
Trust me. I got it.
Those days are over.
I know.
I just wanted to see how the
new you reacts to the old words.
Something is still in there.
At least you were not conscious
for most of your imprisonment.
That time wasn't exactly a picnic.
For what it's worth, I'm sorry.
It was never personal.
You were simply a
means to a necessary end.
Someone recreated
the super-soldier serum.
I need to find out who.
You are assuming HYDRA has
something to do with this,
which is why you came to me,
which means you are desperate.
Luckily for you,
I know where to begin.
What are you talking about?
You wanna break Zemo outta jail?
Where are we, Buck?
Have you lost your mind?
We have no leads, no moves, nothing.
What we have is one of the most
dangerous men in the world behind bars.
We also have eight
Super Soldiers that are loose.
Zemo's gonna mess with our minds.
Especially yours. No offense.
Offense.
Super Soldiers go against
everything he believes in.
He is crazy, but he still has a code.
I've been on the wrong side
of that code and so have you.
He blew up the UN, he killed
King T'Chaka and framed you for it.
Did you forget that?
You think the Wakandans forgot about it?
It's a rhetorical question. They didn't.
I know why this matters to you,
but it's pushing you off the deep end.
We don't know how
they're gettin' the serum.
We don't even know how
many of them there are.
Let me just walk you
through a hypothetical. Can I?
- What did you do?
- I didn't do anything.
What's the book you're reading?
Machiavelli.
The weakest point in any system
isn't the software,
the hardware, it's the meatware.
The human element.
Now, in this lockup,
it's nine to one, prisoners to guards.
And if two prisoners start fighting,
then the protocol says
four guards have to respond.
So why would two prisoners
randomly start fighting at that moment?
Who knows? There could be many reasons…
But the point is, these things escalate.
Lockdown procedures
would have to be initiated,
and with all those bodies
flying around left and right,
wouldn't be hard to
slip down a hallway or two.
And if the fire alarm got tripped
while the prisoners were being separated…
…someone could use the
chaos to their advantage.
I don't like how casual
you're bein' about this.
This is unnatural. Are you…
And where are we, man?
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
- No, listen.
- What are you doin' here?
I didn't tell 'cause I knew
you wouldn't let this happen.
- What did you do?
- We need him.
- You're going back to prison!
- If I may…
No!
Apologies.
When Steve refused to sign the
Sokovia Accords, you backed him.
You broke the law, and you
stuck your neck out for me.
I'm asking you to do it again.
- I really think I'm invaluable…
- Shut up.
Okay.
If we do this, you don't make
a move without our permission.
Fair.
Okay, Zemo,
where do we start?
So our first move is grand theft auto?
These are mine. Collected by
family over the generations.
I spent years hunting people
HYDRA recruited to recreate the serum.
Because once it's out there,
someone can create an army of people…
like the Avengers.
I ended the Winter Soldier
program once before.
I have no intention to
leave my work unfinished.
To do this, we'll have to
scale a ladder of lowlifes.
Well, join the party.
We've already started.
First stop is a woman named Selby.
Mid-level fence I still have a line on.
From there, we climb.
So all this time you've been rich?
I'm a Baron, Sam.
My family was royalty until
your friends destroyed my country.
Please.
Apologies if that's a little warm,
the fridge is out.
But I will see if there is
some good food in the galley.
It's good to have you back, sir.
You don't know what it's
like to be locked in a cell.
Oh.
That's right. You do.
Why don't you tell us
about where we're going?
I'm sorry.
I was just fascinated by this.
I don't know what to call it,
but this part seems to be important.
Who is Nakajima?
If you touch that again, I'll kill you.
I'm sorry.
I understand that list of names.
People you've wronged
as the Winter Soldier.
Don't push it.
I've seen that book.
It was Steve's when
he came out of the ice.
I told him about Trouble Man.
He wrote it in that book.
Did you hear it? What'd you think?
I like '40s music, so…
- You didn't like it?
- I liked it.
It is a masterpiece, James.
Complete. Comprehensive.
It captures the
African-American experience.
He's out of line, but he's right.
It's great.
Everybody loves Marvin Gaye.
I like Marvin Gaye.
Steve adored Marvin Gaye.
You must have really looked up to Steve.
But I realized something when I met him.
The danger with people like him,
America's Super Soldiers,
is that we put them on pedestals.
Watch your step, Zemo.
They become symbols. Icons.
And then we start to
forget about their flaws.
From there, cities fly,
innocent people die.
Movements are formed, wars are fought.
You remember that, right?
As a young soldier sent to
Germany to stop a mad icon.
Do we want to live in a world
full of people like the Red Skull?
That is why we're going to Madripoor.
What's up with Madripoor?
You talk about it like it's Skull Island.
It's an island nation in
the Indonesian archipelago.
It was a pirate sanctuary
back in the 1800s.
It's kept its lawless ways.
But we cannot exactly
walk in as ourselves.
James, you will have to
become someone you claim is gone.
Karli!
You better come upstairs.
There's not much time.
You should be with her now.
She'd want that.
I'm sorry.
We have to fix this.
I'm the only one who looks like a pimp.
Only an American would assume
a fashion-forward
Black man looks like a pimp.
You look exactly like the man
you're supposed to be playing.
The sophisticated, charming African rake
named Conrad Mack, aka the Smiling Tiger.
He even has a bad nickname.
Hell, he does look like me, though.
You smell this?
Yeah, what is that? Acid?
Madripoor.
No matter what happens,
we have to stay in character.
Our lives depend on it.
There's no margin for error.
High Town's that way.
Not a bad place if you wanna visit,
but Low Town's the other way.
Let me guess.
We don't have any friends in High Town.
Here we are.
Is that the Winter Soldier?
Hello, gentlemen.
Wasn't expecting you, Smiling Tiger.
His plans changed.
We have business to do with Selby.
The usual?
Ah.
Smiling Tiger, your favorite.
I love these.
Cheers, Conrad.
Mmm.
I got word from on high.
You ain't welcome here.
I have no business with the Power Broker,
but if he insists, he can
either come and talk to me…
New haircut?
Or bring Selby for a chat.
A power broker? Really?
Every kingdom needs its king.
Let's just pray we stay under his radar.
- Do you know him?
- Only by reputation.
In Madripoor he is
judge, jury, and executioner.
Didn't take much for him
to fall back into form.
Stay in character or
the whole bar turns on us.
Selby will see you now.
Thank you.
You good?
You should know, Baron.
People don't just come
into my bar and make demands.
Not a demand. An offer.
A lot has changed
since you were here last.
By the way, I thought you were
rotting away in a German prison.
How did you escape?
People like us always
find a way, don't we?
I'm sure you've already
figured out what I'm here for.
You're taller than
I'd heard, Smiling Tiger.
What's the offer?
Tell us what you know
about the super-soldier serum.
And I give you him,
along with the code words
to control him, of course.
He will do anything you want.
Now that's the Zemo I remember.
I'm glad I decided not
to kill you immediately.
Yeah, you were right to come to me.
Arrogant, but right.
The super-soldier serum
is here in Madripoor.
Dr. Wilfred Nagel is
the man you wanna thank. Or…
condemn, depending on
what side of this you're on.
The Power Broker had him
working on the serum, but…
things didn't go as planned.
Is Nagel still in Madripoor?
Oh.
The bread crumbs you can have for free,
but the bakery is gonna cost you, Baron.
And before you get all cute, don't
think you can find Nagel without me.
Answer it.
On speaker.
Hello?
Hey, um, we need to
talk about this situation.
It's been drivin' me nuts.
What situation exactly
are you talkin' about?
Are you high?
You know what situation,
it's the only situation me and you have.
What situation, Sarah? Say it.
The damn boat.
And watch your tone. Okay?
I let you slide at the bank.
The bank. Yeah.
Laundered so much…
Yeah, they'll come around.
If that was the case,
then why'd they dog you out, Big Time?
Yeah, you damn right I'm Big Time.
You'll see when I have that banker killed.
Cass! What'd I tell you about the Cheerios?
I don't have time for this!
Sam, I'm sorry. I'll call you back.
"Sam"?
Who's Sam?
Kill them!
They're gonna pin this on us.
We have a real problem now,
so leave your weapons and follow my lead.
This is not good.
- Shit!
- Come on!
I can't run in these heels!
You seem to have a guardian angel.
Well, this is too perfect.
Drop it, Zemo.
Sharon?
You cost me everything.
Sharon, wait.
Someone recreated the super-soldier
serum and Zemo had a lead.
That explains why you guys are here.
And Selby's dead.
So what are you doing here?
I stole Steve's shield, remember?
I also took the wings for your ass,
so that you could save him from him.
I didn't have the Avengers to back me up.
So I'm off the grid in Madripoor.
Don't blow smoke.
I was on the run, too.
Was. Is. Big difference.
I don't speak to my family anymore.
I can't.
- My father doesn't know where I am.
- Listen…
Sharon, we need your help.
Please.
This isn't over.
I have a place in High Town.
You'll be safe there.
Looks like breaking all
those laws is treating you well.
I thought if I had to hustle, might as
well enjoy the life of a real hustler.
You know how much
I'll get for a real Monet?
Deactivate your hustle mode.
You sell fake Monets.
No. She means real. This gallery
is specialized in stolen artwork.
Monet. Van Gogh. Classics.
It's true. You know, half the artwork
in museums like the Louvre is fake.
Real stuff sits in places like this.
Okay, guys, I see what you're doing.
You're more worldly than good old Sam.
Yeah. What's Google say?
- No shit.
- You guys need to change.
I'm hosting clients in an hour.
Much better.
What's going on, Sharon?
You don't ever wanna come back home?
They'll lock me up if I
step foot back in the States.
Madripoor doesn't allow extradition.
Look, I'm sorry I didn't call,
but after The Blip and the chaos, I just…
Look, you know the whole
hero thing is a joke, right?
The way you gave up that shield,
deep down, you must
know it's all hypocrisy.
He knows. And not so deep down.
By the way, how is the new Cap?
Don't get me started.
Please. You buy into all
that stars and stripes bullshit.
Before you were his pet psychopath,
you were Mr. America! Cap's best friend.
Wow. She's kind of awful now.
Karli Morgenthau and at least
seven others have taken the serum.
You guys really should steer clear
of all of this for your own safety.
We know it's a risk, but we won't leave
until we find the
one who cracked the code.
We got a name. Wilfred Nagel.
Nagel works for the Power Broker.
We need your help, Sharon.
I can get your name cleared.
You haggling with my life?
- Not like that.
- I don't buy that.
You pretending like
you can clear my name.
Okay, maybe it is hypocrisy.
Maybe you're right. What happened to you.
But I'm willing to try if you are.
They cleared the bionic staring machine,
and he killed almost everybody he's met.
- I heard that.
- I don't trust charity.
All right, a deal then.
You help us out,
and I get your name cleared.
Well, I sell to some
pretty connected people.
Lay low, blend in, enjoy the party.
Try to stay outta trouble.
I'll see what I can find.
Trouble.
Hey, guys. I found him.
Here we go.
Madripoor could give
New York a run for its money.
They know how to party.
With that bounty on your head,
the longer you're in Madripoor,
the less likely you're ever leaving.
All right. He's in there.
Container four-two-six-one.
I'll watch while you guys talk to Nagel.
But hurry. We're on borrowed time.
Hey, Sharon.
You sure this is the right one?
It's completely empty.
Positive. It has to be.
- I'm comin' home, baby
- Come on home
Comin' home, baby, now
You know I'm waitin' here for you
I'm comin' home now, real soon
You've been gone
Comin' home, baby, now
You don't know what I'm goin' through
I'm comin' home, I know I'm overdue
- Since you went away
- S'pect me any day
- How I feel, too
- Now real soon
- I'm comin' home
- Come on home
Comin' home, baby, now
You know I'm prayin' every night
Everything is gonna be fine
Please come home
- I'm comin' home, baby, now
- I want to feel you hold me tight
'C'pect to see me now, anytime
- When I'm in your arms
- Arms…
Dr. Nagel?
Who are you? What do you want?
We know you created
the super-soldier serum.
Get out of my lab.
Hey!
You know who he is, right?
This is Baron Zemo.
I know you've heard of him, too, right?
You seem like a pretty smart guy.
So you better become
conversational real quick.
How about a counter proposal?
Make me a better offer and I'll talk.
Guys, we have company.
Every bounty hunter in the city is here.
We gotta go!
Okay. Okay.
I was brought into HYDRA's Winter Soldier
program to pick up their work
after the five failed
test subjects in Siberia.
When HYDRA fell,
I was recruited by the CIA.
They had blood samples
from an American test subject
with semi-stable traces
of serum in his system.
After much labor, I was able to isolate
the necessary compounds in his blood.
I was a god.
I did what no other scientist
since Erskine was able to do.
But mine was going to be different.
No clunky machines or jacked up bodies.
Mine was going to be subtle, optimized,
perfect.
How have we never heard about this?
Because…
Before I was able to complete
my work, I turned to dust.
Then when I returned,
it was five years later,
program had been abandoned,
so I came here.
The Power Broker was more than happy
to fund the recreation of my work.
How many vials did you make?
Twenty.
Karli Morgenthau stole those, so…
I can only imagine
what the Power Broker has
planned for that poor girl.
- Where's Karli now?
- I don't know where she is.
But a couple of days ago,
she called and asked if I could
help someone named Donya Madani.
Poor woman has tuberculosis.
Typical of overpopulation in
displacement camps like that.
Well, what happened to her?
Not my pig. Not my farm.
Is there any serum in this lab?
No.
Now what?
Guys, we're seriously outta time here.
No!
What did you do?
Anybody see Zemo?
Let's go.
All right! Wait for my signal!
Damn it!
And you like living here?
It's not terrible.
Ah!
- I thought we were going left?
- You went the wrong way!
I was clearing the way!
I came out first. You had to follow me.
- And where are we now?
- Guys, not the time!
- I'm out!
- This is a barricade.
It's in every action movie!
- Go.
- Come on. Let's go.
Buck!
Let's go!
Hello…
Supercharged.
You're going back to jail.
- Do you want to find Karli or not?
- He's right. We need him.
And there's two of us,
and at least 20 of them.
- Fine. But if you try that shit again…
- I wouldn't dream of it.
Well, that was one hell of a reunion.
Come back to the States with us.
I can't. Just get me
that pardon you promised me.
Thanks for everything.
You're not gonna move
your seat up, are you?
No.
We've got a big problem.
Actually, a couple of them.
I'll tell you in the car. Let's go.
There's another entrance
around the corner.
Have you thought about
taking some time to mourn?
- Look, we don't have to do this right now.
- Yes, we do.
Did you ever think you'd
end up here, doing this?
I was always scrambling for a way out.
Even thought about jumping in with
the military, at one point, but, uh…
apparently mob security
in Madripoor paid better.
I always thought I'd be a teacher.
Like Mama Donya.
Maybe, like, History or Art or something.
Professor Karli Morgenthau.
- Bit of a tough profession in Madripoor?
- Never thought I'd end up there,
but then when everybody returned,
and we got put out on the street,
I knew it was the only place
that had something that
I could use to protect us.
Do you remember how scared
we were when we took the serum?
Felt like my veins were on fire.
Prayed it'd kill me.
But it was worth it,
because this world is ours.
Should have been Mama Donya's.
We'll use all of our strength to
give it to the kids in those camps.
You know, the Power Broker is gonna
catch up with us eventually, right?
That's not a problem.
Nagel was killed in Madripoor.
We've got the last of the serum.
The Power Broker is
about to come begging.
So we just have the one
fight ahead of us then?
I'll take those odds.
Maybe you get to be a
teacher after all this is over?
Maybe.
We've got all we need here.
You said that Sam and Bucky were
here on the same day this happened?
Correct, do you think they had
anything to do with him getting out?
- Thank you.
- What?
So, you seriously think Sam and Bucky
would've broken Zemo out of prison?
That's exactly what I think they did.
They were desperate for leads like us.
Come on, man.
You know we can't accuse 'em
of something without evidence.
Which is why you and I are just
gonna run with this one for a minute.
Okay, so I take it what happens next
isn't a strictly
on-the-books type thing, is it?
Lemar, if we get the job done,
you think they're
gonna sweat us on the how?
Donya Madani. She's a refugee, yeah.
- Okay, I'm on it.
- Okay. Call me if you get a hit.
Will do.
Thanks, Torres.
You okay?
Yeah.
Just thinking about all the
shit Sharon had to go through.
And Nagel referring to
the American test subject
like Isaiah wasn't even a real person.
Just makes me wonder
how many people have to get steamrolled
to make way for this hunk of metal.
Well, it depends on who you ask.
That hunk of metal saved a lot of lives.
Yeah, I get that. All right.
Maybe I made a mistake.
- You did.
- Yeah.
Maybe I shouldn't have put it in a
museum. I should have destroyed it.
Look, that shield represents
a lotta things to a
lotta people, including me.
The world is upside down,
and we need a new Cap,
and it ain't gonna be Walker.
So before you destroy it,
I'll take it from him myself.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
Thanks. Good work.
They found Madani…
Dead.
She died in Riga,
a city near the Baltic Sea.
I have a place we can go.
I, for one, am looking forward
to coming face to face with Karli.
Oeznik, we're changing the course.
Hey, Diego! Lennox! Second van.
It's the motherlode.
Enough for a whole camp.
They're just sitting on this stuff.
All right. We good?
Filthy Flag Smashers.
You had six months' worth of supplies,
just sat there in that building.
Don't you understand?
We're fighting for our lives.
- Karli, aren't you taking your car?
- No.
Put your seat belt on. Now!
Shit!
There were still people in there.
This is the only language
these people understand.
I heard what became of Sokovia.
Cannibalized by its neighbors
before the land was cleared of rubble,
erased from the map.
I don't suppose any of you
bothered visiting the memorial?
Of course not.
Why would you? We are here.
I'm gonna go on a walk.
You good?
Yeah. I'll see you guys in a bit.
You dropped something.
I was wondering when
you were gonna show up.