[English subtitles are available]
Gabi! Hey! What's wrong?!
Hey! Get hold of yourself!
What's wrong? What happened?
She suddenly started wailing in pain.
Hey, young miss, are you okay?
Gabi, that's enough!
What’s your purpose of
running away from here?
They would kill us eventually.
That person is worried about you.
How can you trust those devils?
We can't trust Zeke either.
I trust no one!
Bad dreams?
If only it had all been just a dream.
I heard Gabi and Falco's voices.
Where are they now?
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Angels planning disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
(#70 Counterfeit)
We've made it pretty far.
We’ve been running all night, after all.
Hey.
You should take off your armband.
It’ll give us away.
Regular citizens won't recognize
this armband anyway.
But the soldiers would.
Just take it off already.
There are no soldiers
in a rural countryside like this.
If you keep it on, people
will find out sooner or later.
We don't have any clue
on how to get back to Marley.
It’s impossible to get back.
I just want to find Zeke and confront
him before I'm captured and killed.
I wanna ask him if he really betrayed us…and Marley,
and why he did that!
You can do whatever you want.
You don't have to come along with me.
Is that so?
I’ll take your advice, then.
I will toss this away for you.
Give it back!
Ugh!
What are you doing?
This thing is useless in here!
I'm a good Eldian!
Without that, I'm no different
from these island devils!
What are you talking about?
Have you gone crazy?!
Then leave me alone!
Why... did you follow me?
There is no reason for you to die.
What are you two doing?
It's so early in the morning.
Where did you two come from?
I... don't want to say it.
We were tired of staying at home.
We finally managed to run away and get here...
That's why...
We can't go back now.
I see.
You must be hungry.
My house is nearby, so come with me.
Please wait here.
Yes.
We can take that horse and escape.
What the heck are you saying?
We must run further away.
They will track us down here
sooner or later.
Also, I can't eat alongside
those damn devils.
You are really...
Sorry for the wait. Come in.
Ah, thanks.
We will.
I will talk. Don't say anything stupid.
So you kids ran away from home?
What’s that?
It’s south Marleyan accent?
Nice to meet you.
We're siblings. I'm Ben and she's Mia.
We have our reasons
to run away from our parents.
If there's anything we can do
to help, we will gladly do it!
Please let us stay
here for a few days!
We beg you!
You kid shouldn't lower
your head like that.
Welcome to Blouse stables.
You can stay as long as you want.
Come mere and eat some breakfast.
You must be tired.
You may lay down after finishing that.
Lisa... this kid...
Sorry. You must've gone through a lot.
No...
I'm sorry for my sister's behaviour.
Thanks for the meal!
Delicious! This tastes great!
It's really good.
Go ahead and eat, Mia.
I would like to congratulate you on
the success of your campaign against Marley.
The leaders of Hizuru have nothing but praise
for the bravery shown by the nation of Eldia.
I'm honored by your words.
Welcome to the most dangerous
island in the world.
Yes.
Our objective today is to witness
how dangerous it really is.
Is that the observation
unit I've heard so much about?
Yes.
It's the world's first flying boat, using
the iceburst stone as its fuel.
We shall take a good look at
the power of the Rumbling on it.
Rumour says Eren Yeager is in prison,
and all the volunteers have been arrested.
Is that true?
Please, Hange, explain to us.
Why did you force evacuation order to
all residents in Shiganshina district?
Wasn't it the Corps who made Reeves
company responsible for its reconstruction?
consult the Police Brigade.
Hange!
Yeager's victory has opened
a path to our future!
He proves us that the Eldians can survive now!
That means the relationship between him
and the Corps matters to all Eldians!
Hange.
You once said you would give
information to the taxpayers.
Have you changed your stance on that?
The situation has changed!
Information has a different meaning
now that we're connected to the world!
We understand that you're
in a difficult position, Hange.
So please look at us in the eye
and say it's okay for us to believe in you.
Everything we do is for
the sake of the Eldian people.
So it's you guys who leaked
the info about Eren?
Holger, Wim, Louise.
You recruits, and Floch.
Why did you do that?
Because Eren ought to be freed.
He hasn't done anything wrong.
He’s faced countless colossal
enemies and grasped victory.
That victory is the overwhelming power
named the Rumbling
which is also our ticket to survival.
Eren saved the lives of the
citizens of the New Eldian Empire.
No one can guarantee that the Rumbling
can save us as we expected it to.
To be frank, it's nothing more than
a story you heard from a stranger.
That's only because you're keeping
Eren locked in the prison.
Do we have the time to
waste on this?
At this rate, our great victory
will be all for naught.
The one that should lead this nation
is Eren Yeager.
You need to release him immediately.
Mmm..
You might be right.
Specifics aside, I was the one who made
the decision to see Zeke's plan through.
I should be held accountable.
Which is why I can't allow
any more insubordination.
You all will be prosecuted for the crime
of leaking information about Eren.
Bring these four to the detention room.
I will gladly go if it leads to
victory for humanity within the wall.
The stage always needs someone
to fill in this role.
Even if I leave, another
will come to take my place.
Do your best, Hange.
I'm tired.
No.
There's still more I need to look up.
Is this the cell you were locked in, Mikasa?
Eh? No.
I see.
What a shame.
Ah, but I don't regret violating
military regulation.
If Survey Corps' goal is to win, that means
rules are not always absolute, right?
Stop it, Louise.
You will only extend your sentence.
Ever since that day you saved me...
I haven't changed a bit.
When I saw you defeated a Titan
with human strength, I realized
that you can't save anyone without power.
I learnt that it's okay for us to
fight against unjust violence.
Ever since that day, I’ve been trying
my best to be just like you, so I...
Why did you join the Survey Corps, Mikasa?
If it's for Yeager,
then you should free…
I only have one thing to tell you.
You should shut your mouth.
It's all fine now.
Mikasa.
Ten months ago,
during the banquet celebrating the
opening of the trail system in Torst district,
the guard assigned to you
was suddenly changed...
...into Floch Forster.
He accompanied you to your lodgings
just as the festivities were winding down.
He's currently detained for
divulging secret information.
Also, your lodgings were located a few dozen
kilometres away from Eren Yeager's place.
Somehow right around that time, Eren began
to take more unauthorized actions.
Anyway, I'm pleased to have an excuse to
speak with such a beautiful woman today.
Gabi!
Gabi…!
How did it end up like this?
Could it be the work of the devils?!
Well, I'm sure it's because of the horse.
I bet none of the horses here
would let you ride them away from here.
We never learned how to
ride a horse anyway.
We can't get any information
in a countryside like this.
I believe it's better to avoid doing
anything reckless and just blend in.
What are you saying?
We should lay low and wait
for help here.
I'm sure the army from all over the world
will come to attack this island.
I'm sure my brother and Reiner
will come to save us.
Aren't you mad at Zeke?
We had a traitor right next to us!
There's nothing we can do.
Also, why Mia?
Why must I be your little sister?
Does it matter?
Guys.
Time for lunch.
You two sure are fast learners.
And strong, too.
Really? Thank you very much.
I see that people who work here are
young, including you, Kaya.
Yeah.
Because they are orphans.
Is that so?
The Queen's policies provide support
to children with no place to go.
This is where the kids who lost
their parents four years ago are gathered.
Looks like you haven't admitted your sin.
Eh?
Have you forgotten the horrible crime
people of this island committed against the world?
Only when every single
Eldian understands his sins
will the path to atonement open.
Does that have anything to do with
children losing their parents?
Of course.
No matter how good you may try to act,
your sin is too big for you to escape from.
Is that what they taught you in Marley?
How could you say that
to the person who helped you!
- This is about basic history.
- You're still saying that?
Wait, what did you just say?
You two are from Marley, right?
-Why?
-Why what?
Well, I mean, you said that yourself.
Eh?
Ah!
So you’ve known from the very beginning?
Eh?! Since we first met?!
That's really embarrassing!
Why didn't you tell us?
That's so mean, you know.
Eh?
What are you doing?!
The devil has showed her true form!
I knew something was off!
There's no way island devil
would be this nice!
C'mon, are you idiot?!
Hey!
What are you guys arguing about?
This is bad!
Mia is jealous that her big brother
is stolen away from her!
Looks like Kaya is getting
along with them.
They do seem to have cheered up a bit.
Sheesh.
It's dangerous, so don't play
around with that tool, okay?
Yes!
Why?
This is the village I used to live in.
A Titan came here four years ago.
Everyone in the village ran away
after seeing that Titan.
All while leaving my handicapped mom behind.
I couldn't do anything so I just sat there.
I was here... listening to the
sound of my mom getting eaten.
My mom was eaten alive.
Eventually, she couldn't even
say anything.
She kept screaming until
she lost her voice.
There are human outside the walls
and they call us a race of devils, right?
But I can’t understand why
the world despises us like that.
Mia, Ben, tell me.
What did my mom do?
What did she do that
makes them hate us so much?
That’s because of all the mass killing you
people did for thousands of years!
Thousands of years?
How could you forget that?!
The Eldians ruled and oppressed the world for
thousands of years using the power of Titans!
They stole the culture of other races,
forced them to have children they didn’t want,
and killed countless human beings!
Stop acting like the victim here!
But my mom was born and raised here.
I don't think my mom did
anything awful like that.
As I said, the problem is the sins your
ancestors committed a hundred years ago!
A hundred years ago?
Then what kind of sins have we committed?
Just recently you people trampled my city.
My mom was killed four years ago.
It has nothing to do with her!
Like I said, your ancestor has slaughtered
people around the world…
My mom didn't kill anyone!
Hey, Mia! Answer me properly!
Why must my mom suffer
such a painful death?
There should be a reason for it!
If there's none, why?!
Why must my mom
get eaten alive like that?!
Tell me! Why must she get killed?!
Tell me! Why?!
It's for reconnaissance.
The incursion on Paradis four years ago
was a reconnaissance mission
preparing for a large-scale attack.
Your mother got wrapped up in it.
Your mother didn't commit any sin.
I'm sorry.
You just leaked military
top-secret detail.
Why are you apologizing to her?
Thank you for telling me that, Ben.
But it's wrong for you to apologize.
You just happened to be born in Marley.
So how did you escape
from that situation?
A girl older than me came in
swinging an axe from our yard
and fought the Titan.
No way! That was too reckless!
Yeah.
In the end, she shielded me with her
own body to let me escape.
If she was still alive,
she'd never abandon two kids like you
who have nowhere to go.
Just like she didn’t abandon me.
We've been invited to a restaurant
where a Marleyan works.
If I bring you there, maybe you
can find a way to return home.
Why?
I want to become someone like her.
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes
I will be immortal ♫
After investigating the remains
of the Beast Titan,
we found parts of Zeke's body
that was exploded into pieces.
However, it's not enough.
All we found were his limbs.
He made it look like he died
to deceive us.
We believe Zeke has allied with enemy forces
on Paradis and escaped on their airship.
This modified anti-personnel
vertical maneuvering gear
uses Marleyan technology.
And the airship they stole for their
escape required military training to pilot,
especially at such a high
degree of proficiency.
He must've snuck them onto
the survey ship to Paradis four years ago.
His comrades in the Eldian
restorationists, that is.
Dammit!
We fought together all this time.
But he's actually a traitor?
Of course we have no intention
to let this end here.
Within the next six months,
the global military alliance will conduct
mopping-up operation against Paradis!
Six…Six months?!
Is that how long we have to wait
to rescue Gabi and Falco?
Those two are the best warrior
candidates we have now.
I believe losing them will
be a great loss to Marley.
It will also take a lot of time to train
the next batch of warrior candidates.
But the chance of winning is slim
if Marley attacks Paradis on its own.
We must wait for the allied forces to gather.
Zeke must be thinking the same thing.
That the Marleyan army won't attack
immediately after taking such a massive blow.
And he's not the kind of person who just
going to wait with no plan for six months.
We can't wait for the global allied
forces to be ready!
We must attack Paradis
island right away!
Just whom must we hate?
Just what is it that we must resent?
We should've already been
used to getting our belief shaken.
Next Episode: Guides