♫ Nowhere to escape. ♫
♫ No bough to alight. ♫
♫ Retrograde with smile. ♫
♫ Never give in. ♫
♫ Forget about the youth. ♫
♫ I've never been afraid of loneliness. ♫
♫ I also shed the tears of regret. ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot. ♫
♫ To the distance. ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger. ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken, ♫
♫ I will keep flying. ♫
♫ Following the light, ♫
♫ I'll forget you. ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness. ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night, ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad. ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet. ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness. ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 38
What happened?
We are afraid of you now.
So we are here to give you some presents, and make peace.
My captain pays his respect to you, Tegin Sun.
Is this from Pusa?
Yes.
Mobei was obtrusive and ignorant, which led to public wrath.
My captain was really sorry for that.
So he is asking for forgiveness from Ashile Tribe.
These are our gifts.
Please say some good words for Mobei to Great Khan.
As long as it is done, more valuable gifts would be here.
Of course.
It's priceless.
Please cherish it, Tegin Sun.
Let me have a look.
What so priceless?
No worries, Tegin.
Our captain would never make a fish of one and flesh of another.
Why mine is so small?
This is good!
So big!
I never saw such a big one before.
Who wants your stone?
Send these to my place later.
Okay.
I will divide.
I am the most impartial one here.
Go.
[Meet at Wild Wolf Hill at midnight]
So you are just going to have a date after all these?
She must have something important to tell me.
I will go to see her tonight, you guard here for me.
[Copy that...]
[Copy that, be there or be square.]
What?
Just this?
Any problem?
She is asking for a date.
Sun!
Did you ever hear a phrase, "Express your love through words"?
We know each other, so we don't need this.
So you don't have to write something more?
Then what should I write?
What?
Should I teach you this?
You can write anything you want to say to her.
Fine, I won't look.
Just write it down.
Don't peep!
Fine, fine.
Keep writing.
I won't peep.
So fast!
Don't you need to write more?
It's not necessary.
Don't peep!
Okay, fine, I know.
Tegin Sun said that he would be there on time tonight.
This is?
I have no idea.
He just asked me to send this back to you.
Thanks.
Captain.
Already checked the box?
Anything private?
What a surprise!
This famous Ashile Sun is such a tender man!
[I miss you.]
♫ Along this way ♫
♫ who can say she has never been shy and missed anything? ♫
♫ Look at the color of the sky ♫
♫ It's so beautiful on your eyebrow ♫
♫ Look at you in my eyes ♫
♫ You make my heart rate rock ♫
♫ which puts my hair in a mess ♫
♫ When I look at you ♫
♫  I can feel that ♫
♫ it's a kind of warmth that I have hoped for so long ♫
♫ I hope so much that you were me ♫
♫ The eternal song ♫
♫ would be sung loudly when I feel lonely ♫
♫ So I hold your hands tight ♫
♫  All the lights ♫
♫ would light up the immense sky ♫
Senior Qin told me that you decided to stay at Mobei.
If I was not for treating my people,
I would have caught you back earlier.
What?
You used face powder today?
It's from Zhenzhu.
Maybe I touched it accidentally.
Smells good?
It seems her taste is not so good.
Then I would not let her use it later.
Back to our business.
Why is Eagle Division here?
Because of military orders.
Asking those who just recovered from the plague to fight...
It seems that Khan's Tent just wants to wipe out Eagle Division.
Changge.
You know that I never want to think bad of him.
But that's the fact!
If you are asking me to betray Ashile Tribe,
and Great Khan,
then I can't.
I owe him for bringing me up.
I can't break faith with him.
What about Eagle Division?
What can it do?
I have no choice.
You do.
I ask you to meet here tonight, just want to tell you,
you have a third choice apart from betrayal and hibernation.
He agreed?
He would reply in two days.
I warn you.
If I didn't get the reply I want in two days,
you would not live to the third day.
Sun.
Bear Division is asking for us,
they have something important to discuss.
Go.
Why do you look so terrible?
Did you stay up late?
Let me in!
I have to see Mu Jin and Tegin Sun.
Let me in, I'm here for important business!
Mimi?
Let her in.
You can't trust Bear Division.
You would die!
Sun.
I've checked.
Just like Mimi said,
the bolts and slings should have been aimed at the desert,
but the angle is lowered now.
It can't be such a big mistake.
Obviously they are aiming at us.
It's an urgent situation.
Say something!
Let me think about it.
What to think about?
In past days, dare Tu Kashe to do that?
He must be instigated by someone else.
Shut up!
Even if we win this time,
we survive the war,
and he lets us go, what about the next time?
And in the future?
Only if Eagle Division vanishes, could they stop their attack to us.
You guys leave for a moment.
I need to be alone now.
Let's go, Mimi.
Mimi, I have a question.
I know your question.
I have something to tell you later.
The reason why I know this
is that I am a spy sent by Khan's Tent.
And?
And...
the boy which infected Eagle Division
looks so much like my brother Buzhen,
so she knew that I would definitely save him.
So... you have a brother?
He is still in their hand as a hostage.
They even asked me to destroy the gromwell,
or they would kill him.
You saved Eagle Division,
and you are our benefactor.
I promise,
I would find ways to help your brother out.
I don't even know if he is still alive.
No matter he is alive or dead,
I would do it for you.
Sun and I will go to see Tu Kashe first.
Don't worry.
You will always be our family,
you will always be my Mimi.
Mu Jin!
Follow me.
I have to leave now.
You're here.
Just these food?
I'm afraid that these are just enough for three days.
Just for those weak soldiers in Mobei,
isn't it enough?
Mobei asked for peace and gave us gifts.
What do you think of it?
We will accept the gifts,
and also fight against them.
Tegin is quite a trustworthy man.
I will start the fight tomorrow.
I will use my 10,000 men to wipe out 5000 cavalrymen of Mobei.
And then take the chance to besiege Mobei.
How do you think of it, Tegin Sun?
Okay.
But that's not enough.
So your opinion?
You start the fight tomorrow,
and they will have a whole night for preparation.
If they store up energy and strength,
and get into fight tomorrow,
your odds to win would not be high.
So your plan is... We can tell them the battle is tomorrow,
but we will secretly start the battle tonight.
Sneak attack?
Taking advantage of their slackness,
and unpreparedness, we will make a surprise attack on them.
Okay. As you say.
Young Khan.
Let me in.
I have to see Uncle Khan.
Forgive me please, Young Khan.
Great Khan is having rest now.
He ordered no one should disturb him.
I'm here to pay for a visit, can't I?
Don't put me in a pickle please, Young Khan.
Sher.
Mom.
Wait.
Uncle Khan said we shouldn't meet privately.
Now this order is invalid.
What?
When?
Why did no one tell me about it?
Great Khan just told me in person.
What happened?
No.
I...
I just can't accept it at once.
You will get used to it.
You are my son.
We should not be separated actually.
But why... why did Uncle Khan permit it?
Maybe...
Your Uncle Khan didn't feel the importance of kinship until he fell ill.
Then it's been a long time since I've left him,
I should visit him now.
Besides, I have something to ask him.
Your Uncle Khan just drank medicine, he is asleep now.
You can ask me anything, it's the same.
Go ahead.
Uncle Khan dispatched Eagle and Bear Division to fight Mobei.
What about my Wolf Division?
So what?
This chance should be my Wolf Division.
In the battle in Weishui,
Wolf Division had no distribution.
This has been a joke in the other two tribes.
Now we need a battle to prove ourselves.
This time, I will ask for a fight to Uncle Khan.
I will successively attack Mobei for Uncle Khan.
Sher, do you remember what I told you when you were young?
Lack of forbearance in small matters upsets great plans.
The most important thing for you is to save power.
As long as you have strength, and hold up to the last second,
you will have a chance to win.
Uncle Khan sent me out immediately this time,
to go on an expedition at the border.
As soon as I come back, I have to prepare for the move of the court.
And I have to clear up the desert.
These are all too fast!
It's not like the style of Uncle Khan.
Let me show you something.
The Great Seal!
Khan is badly ill,
he has asked me to keep this.
From now on, the whole Khan's Tent will be under my control.
What?
You think your mother isn't competent to do it?
No.
Just...
Sher.
You should feel happy for me.
From now on, I don't need to endure the humiliation.
You can see me whenever you want.
You can go anywhere you want.
Isn't it great?
Your Uncle Khan is seriously ill,
so he can't be at labor anymore.
From now on,
maybe this Great Seal,
the whole Khan's tent,
and this grassland would all be controlled by you.
You have to be prepared.
Okay, go back to have a rest.
Don't think too much.
Are you ready?
Tegin Sun, yes we are!
Tonight would be a hard time for Eagle Division,
we will cooperate well with you.
I will lead Eagle Division to attack from the north,
and Bear Division from the south.
We will attack from both sides.
Wonderful.
Great!
Eagle Division!
Yes!
Follow me!
Will Tu Kashe fall into the trap?
Will we succeed?
No worries.
Everything is under control.
Today is coming to an end.
Do you think you can be alive tomorrow?
The sunset is so beautiful.
Don't wet my blanket please, captain.
Report!
Captain! The man from Eagle Division is here.
Bring him in.
Yes!
Mimi?
Changge.
Mimi.
Why is it you?
Long story.
I just saw Tegin Sun.
He asked you to pass some word to two kings.
Go ahead, what is it?
Help Eagle Division fake death.
He would like to give a chance of success to the desert tonight.
What are you talking about?
Ask Yinan here.
Or would I do it myself?
Tegin.
When shall we start?
Just wait.
The more they are consumed, the easier for us to clear them up.
Bear Division!
Yes!
Follow me!
Go!
Stop.
Where is Eagle Division?
Ambush!
We are trapped!
Why are they the armies of Monan and Mobei?
So bad, we are trapped!
Retreat!
Report!
Come on in!
How is it?
Ashile Bear Division has already been trapped.
Two kings from Monan and Mobei led the armies to attack from both sides,
Bear Division has been defeated.
What about Eagle Division?
Eagle Division has faked to fight on the battlefield according to the plan,
they have all retreated, with no one got injured.
They could draw such an elaborate layout in just three to four hours,
the desert is so talented!
This is a kind of strategy in the Central Plains.
Pusa and Yinan have no idea about it.
Her idea again?
So scary!
Sun!
Don't you need to think twice of it?
This woman is so awful.
I'm afraid that you would be cheated by her.
Boring...
Tegin, urgency!
Tu Kashe was covered by soldiers of Bear Division,
he rushed out of the circle.
He can't go.
Who is it?
Sun!
What do you mean?
Are you going to betray Great Khan?
I just want to live.
I also hope Eagle Division can survive too.
Do you deserve it?
You are just a low-priced nobody!
You are just a slave.
If it was not Great Khan, could you have lived till today?
I would never forget his grace of bringing me up.
But in the future,
I will return to him in my way.
Bah!
Just in this way?
You Eagle Division are all bad men!
And you, Mu Jin!
You are shameless!
You guys won't live till tomorrow!
I will report everything to Great Khan.
You have no chance to live till tomorrow!
Don't talk big.
It doesn't matter.
Tu Kashe, you can't leave tonight.
His Highness asked me to report to you that we succeeded.
Just wait for Eagle Division coming back.
Thanks.
Since our plan has succeeded,
it's time for me to go back.
Back to where?
Eagle Division or Khan's tent?
Mimi.
Actually, I wanted to ask you why you knew
that Bear Division was going to attack Eagle Division.
You are a kind girl.
Or you wouldn't have said that.
If you have any problem, you can tell me.
We can find ways together to solve it.
I told you.
I have a brother.
Yes, you told me that it was Ashile Tribe who killed your families.
Your brother is dead.
He is alive?
You mean... he is at Khan's tent now?
No, in Dingxiang.
It's Yi Cheng...
She threatened me by my brother's life.
And forced me to stay in Eagle Division.
Changge.
I had no choice.
I prefer to die.
Mimi.
You never harmed Eagle Division, but helped it.
Now it no longer exists, you are free too.
How could I be free?
If my brother is still alive, he must be waiting for me to save him.
Mimi.
We will discuss together about your brother when they come back.
Just remember,
Eagle Division are annihilated, you are dead too.
Nothing could threaten you now.
Forget all the things in the past.
From now on,
let's start a new life.
A new life...
Can I start a new life?
Mimi in the past has been dead,
you will be a brand new Mimi in the future.
You can do anything you want freely.
Wait for them to be back,
and we will find a way together to help your brother out.
Sun.
Wait.
Hand me your helmet.
Eagle and Bear Division are both annihilated here.
I need a physical evidence.
Mu Jin,
it's not necessary.
Sun.
Someone has to go back to report.
We have never been separated from each other.
Only if I go back alone, and tell them you are dead,
can they believe it.
You have to be safe.
No worries.
Even the plague didn't take my life, I can't be dead easily.
In this way,
you can't see Mimi for long time.
It's okay.
I also have some selfish motives this time to go back.
Take care.
Go!
Mimi!
Where are you going?
You see?
When I go back,
I will cheat those in Khan's tent.
You can't go!
They won't let you go this time!
Mimi.
Believe me.
I will come back.
I promised you that I would find a way to help your brother out.
But Dingxiang is strictly guarded,
you are alone.
How could you do that?
Take me with you, okay?
Mimi.
I am a man.
A man should do his job.
You promise me,
be safe.
And wait for me.
♫ Those years ♫
♫ we made our wish together ♫
♫ Forget it.  Did you forget it? ♫
♫ Only I was left ♫
You are my man,
you have to be responsible for me.
So you have to be alive and come back!
♫ And condense to sand ♫
♫ Your shadow cannot be left ♫
♫ I hope to continue our destiny in our next life ♫
♫ Even if it's just a handful of sand ♫
♫ We have a moment for us ♫
♫ For the rest of the road ♫
♫ Let's go down together with a smile ♫
♫ You drop down in my eyes ♫
♫ and condense to sand ♫
After getting back, I will never leave you again!
♫ I hope to continue our destiny in our next life ♫
Go!
♫ Even if it's just a handful of sand ♫
I will wait for you coming back!
♫ We have a moment for us ♫
♫ A moment for us ♫
Everything comes to an end.
I'm here to take you back.
I've been worried last night.
I was afraid if the plan would be changed.
I was afraid if Tu Kashe would find your trick.
I was afraid if you would be in danger.
But, thanks, Sun.
You are back safely with a great victory.
I'm back.
Later,
Eagle Division would never exist.
Neither does the Tegin of Eagle Division.
Do you regret?
This is the best result.
Eagle Division would never be disturbed by those interests or disputes,
nor would it be manipulated by others as a slayer.
Although Eagle Division doesn't exist now, you can't repudiate a debt.
What debt?
When you recommended yourself as my military counselor,
you promised me three things.
Are you going to deny it?
I thought that you had forgotten it.
I'm Li Changge.
I never break my promises.
Since you have put it forward, you already have your idea, go ahead.
I am not sure yet.
But the first, I have thought of it for a while.
Could you be more girlish in the future?
You mean...
I lack femininity?
No, no.
How could it be? I...
I am worried about you.
I am worried that you always fight regardless of your own life,
and plan it effortlessly.
Little counsellor,
give me a chance,
and let me be your man.
I will protect you in the future.
But I know you are like a wild horse.
You have your own world.
I respect you.
I would never stop you from anything you want to do.
But no matter in what situation,
you can't risk your life,
nor can you leave without telling me.
No matter what happens, we will face it together.
No matter if it's wind or storm, or swords or arrows,
Me, Ashile Sun would fend against it.
Clear?
This...
I'll go and see.
Sun!
Sun! Don't scare me!
Help!
Please! Help!
Sun!
Who are you?
Eagle Division and Bear Division are completely annihilated.
Why are they dismantling tents?
Are they going to remove?
What happened?
Two main forces!
How could they be annihilated?
Ashile Sun! What is he planning?
What can a dead man plan?
Sun is dead,
I have no reason to live.
You can kill me whenever you want.
Sun is the god of war on grasslands.
No one can kill him!
What can valiancy do?
He can't escape from a back stab!
So many people here want him to die!
Even so,
Sun asked me to go back with his last breath,
he asked me to notice Khan that the desert tribes have united.
Ashile Tribe must pay attention to this.
The desert...
Good!
I will make them pay for Ashile Sun's death!
Khatun.
Stand up.
What a pity for what happened on Eagle and Bear Division!
I'm afraid if Khan can't accept his son's death,
his situation would become worse.
So after he is better, I will tell him about it.
Great Khan is ill?
For a few days.
Now he even can't talk.
What disease?
I don't know what he is suffering from.
Grand Witches are helping him effortlessly.
What a pity!
I haven't told Tegin Sun about it,
they have been separated in two worlds.
By the way,
you just said that there's a secret in Tegin Sun's death?
Don't be afraid.
If there's really a secret in it,
Great Khan will be on Tegin Sun and Eagle Division's side.
Khatun.
There is a traitor in Eagle Division.
All the people are dead because of her.
I am to blame.
I was obsessed with her.
I shouldn't have taken her to the battlefield.
She attacked Sun in his back.
Who is she?
I have no idea.
When I decided to ask her, she killed herself with her sword.
Till now, no one knows who sent her there.
I'll tell this to the women and children of Eagle Division.
Please pass this on to Great Khan.
The desert tribes rebelled,
Khan sent Eagle and Bear Division to encircle and suppress them.
But unfortunately, they fell into an ambush.
What a pity!
Isn't it familiar to you, Khan?
Would you want to look at it carefully?
It seems that you are not seriously ill.
You still can see that it's Ashile Sun's helmet.
I've been thinking about him day and night.
Now he can stay beside you now.
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you. ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter. ♫
♫ Entwist your figure, ♫
♫ and lock it into my tender dream. ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the longing flows. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ which burns down the wastelands in my heart. ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which freezes everything between you and me. ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time. ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds. ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon, ♫
♫ layer after layer. ♫
♫ It turns into eternity. ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night. ♫
♫ It is sleepless. ♫
The Long Ballad