EPISODE 11
My lord, the book reader is here.
I am your new book reader,
Hong Dain.
Sit.
Dain.
I like your name.
Did you bring the book?
Yes, Lord.
Do you know what kind of book that is?
I heard a woman named Geumwon wrote this
after traveling to Geumgangsan.
Correct.
You must still long for Geumgangsan.
Why do you think so?
The book is a travel journal
to Geumgangsan,
and the painting on the wall
is Gyeomjae's painting of Geumgangsan,
so I simply presumed.
I am impressed.
All I have left are memories.
"The peaks flaunt their beauty,
but the longer I look,
more extraordinary they become.
As if a lotus flower carved
from white jade,
its glow reaches
the Big Dipper and Altair,
making one believe pure spirit
of heaven and earth
and splendid vitality of nature
radiate from this place.
Suddenly my heart feels pure,
and I feel as if I can soar above the clouds
accompanied by a divine immortal.
I stand here and look down
on the various peaks,
and I realize this peculiar scenery
is extraordinary,
and of all the peaks, Birobong
is the most outstanding."
Lord.
Who sent you?
I beg your pardon?
Your appearance is too good
to be a mere book reader.
I do not understand.
Mentioning Gyeomjae
and trying to gain my favor
tells me someone sent you with a goal.
If you value your life, tell me.
Who sent you?
Now!
You are mistaken, Lord.
Do you still refuse to talk?
Fine, as you wish, I will kill you.
My lord! What is happening?
It is nothing. Leave.
It was a test.
Had someone sent her,
she would have spilled the name by now.
Continue reading the book.
Mix them well so it is unnoticeable.
Carefully!
Sir.
Stop.
He has decided to assist us.
So I've heard.
You are an outstanding archer?
You are too kind.
Would you mind demonstrating your skills?
What is that?
Ordinary archery is boring.
When it comes to archery,
drinking can only enhance your skills.
Am I wrong?
One bowl per arrow.
The match ends when the rice wine is gone.
Bull's-eye!
No, sir.
You lose complete control when you drink.
Whether or not I lose control,
it is too late to step down.
This is out of my hands.
Bull's-eye!
Bull's-eye, bull's-eye.
When he shoots, he is good.
Bull's-eye!
Yes, yes.
We won, we won.
You won.
That was entertaining.
Sir, it is over.
You can put your bow down.
It is not over.
Oh no. You're drunk.
Lord Seong.
What are you doing?
Move, move.
Put him in jail,
and flog him thirty times
the moment he wakes up!
- What?
- Yes, sir.
Wait.
Sir, I apologize.
Consider him a dog at this state.
A dog, not a man.
Please forgive us.
Bye, guys.
No way.
His Majesty, the King.
Your Majesty,
Chief Royal Secretary Jang Taeseung
has committed a crime by hiding
a follower of a traitor.
Punish him by removing from his office.
- Punish the Chief Royal Secretary!
Your Majesty, Chief Royal Secretary Jang
is an evil man.
He is using the royal agent
to distort the opinions of your subjects,
and thereby alienating Your Majesty
from the rest of your officials.
I can no longer stand aside
and watch his sly tongue
take control of the government.
Please consider our opinion, Your Majesty!
- Please consider it, Your Majesty!
I understand your concerns.
I have summoned the royal agent,
so the truth will be revealed.
Please stand.
Royal Chief Secretary Jang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What shall I do?
How much longer must I ignore them?
Are you truly an accomplice
of the traitor Prince Hwiyeong?
Tell me the truth.
Prince Hwiyeong became a traitor
not by treason but by taking his own life.
He admitted his treason by that very act!
I am suspicious...
Of his death.
Are you defending that traitor?
I will gladly accept
any punishment you name for me.
However, the royal agent will return
with the answer to my question.
So I beg you
to let the royal agent return safely.
We are here.
Sir.
Have you been well?
It is you, Sunae.
You survived.
It is a long story.
I am sure.
Who are they?
They saved my life.
This is the master potter.
I am Seong Ibeom.
Sit.
So, you want to settle here?
Yes, sir.
How did you make your living?
He was a hunter.
How dare you lie to me?
You answer.
I was a robber.
Lord Ibeom.
Why would a robber come here?
I would like a new start.
Please let me stay, sir.
This will be enough to run this village.
Do you expect us to feed ourselves
with the money you stole?
A rich man in Chungcheong-do
was planning to bribe a minister
with that money to win the governorship.
If I had not interfered, that money
would have reached the corrupt officials,
including ministers and state councilors.
Please consider the villagers.
Lady Dain!
Lord Seong!
Help me put him down.
Careful, careful.
Oh, he reeks.
Chunsam, how could you
let him get this drunk?
The provincial office people made him
get drunk to shoot arrows,
so how could I stop him?
Rice is as expensive as gold,
but the officials are making wine with it?
That is disgraceful.
Yes! Those disgraceful men.
I will make my appearance
as the royal agent.
Chunsam, let's go.
Where are you going?
Let us go, let us.
Lady Dain, I will go and get some food
for his hangover.
How dare you?
Do you think you can dump that drunk
on me and escape?
You sure are
the sharpest person in Joseon.
Unless you want to hold a funeral,
go get some water.
Now!
Lord Seong. Lord Seong.
Dain, is that you?
Yes, it is I.
Everyone I hold dear is leaving me.
Will you also leave me?
Well, I guess we will no longer have
a reason to see each other
after we complete this mission.
You are drunk, so you should go inside
and get some sleep.
Did you know?
There is a wine that can help
erase your memory.
You mean a drunken dream?
It is just a story.
Yeah,
I guess people drink hoping to forget.
Nothing is more painful
than being unable to forget
what you wish to forget.
I know that feeling.
Nothing is more painful
than being unable to forget.
I am sure she has not forgotten you.
Sunae! Take a look at this!
My heart!
- That looks delicious!
Thank you.
I can't wait to eat.
With the shortage of rice,
we were not eating well,
but thanks to you, everyone can eat
as much as they want.
- Thank you!
It is my pleasure.
Enjoy.
Lord Ibeom, how do you like this place?
Is it okay?
Well, it is not bad.
Then why do you hide your feelings?
What do you mean?
Try smiling.
It is a good day.
What is good about it?
We are able to eat and laugh with others
without any concerns,
so it is a good day.
I smiled. Happy now?
This is how you smile.
Smile.
Here.
I am being generous.
Thank you.
Boss!
How long has it been?
What brings you here?
What are you two doing here?
We are staying
with one of Sunae's acquaintances.
Have you been well?
Are you working as a blacksmith?
What?
Yes.
Have you been well?
How is Sunae?
We are well.
What are you doing there?
Who is he?
He is the man I told you about
the other day.
Oh, so he's the brilliant robber
you talked about.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I am Jeon Gyesu.
It is an honor to meet such a famous man.
I know everything.
What you have accomplished
is quite impressive.
I do not understand what you mean.
Let us pretend we never met.
Come.
Seong Ibeom,
you must not understand this place
very well because you just arrived,
but settling down here will not be easy.
If you need help,
come find me at the forge.
There will be no need for that.
Let's go.
What if we end up as food for arrows?
I have never shot an arrow before,
so what am I supposed to do?
Sh.
Sir, what is it?
Hold!
Put your bow down.
What?
Show yourself.
What took you so long?
There are robbers everywhere,
so we took a long detour.
Bring it!
They are all there. Take them.
Take the rice!
Yes, sir.
Oh, and tell Lord Bae he owes me a drink.
He is making a fortune,
but he never shows appreciation.
I will tell him.
Sir, isn't this rice
an offering for Buddha?
Bae has been deceiving the governor.
He is bold beyond measure.
"Now that I have seen the grandeur
of heaven and earth,
human existence seems rather trivial."
Shall I stop reading?
Everything is vain.
But you are the governor
of Jeolla-do,
the position of every official's dream.
What is the use of power and authority?
I am house-ridden due to my skin disease.
Hearing that from you
reminds me of a story.
What story?
It is a story...
Of an official who worked at the palace
a very long time ago.
Tell me.
He was intelligent
and had the most beautiful face
that the king wished
to have him by his side.
The king had a son,
and he wanted to
become king so desperately
that he decided to kill his father.
In the dead of night,
the prince used that very official
to lure the king to a deserted place,
and killed him with a sword.
The prince took the throne,
and rewarded the official with great
fortune and a high government position.
But because he knew his secret
of killing his own father,
the king sent the official
to a far away countryside.
While on the road, the official became
parched and wanted to drink water.
He was about to drink water at the stream
when he saw his own reflection
in the water.
It was no longer his beautiful face,
but the face of a petrifying beast.
Why did the official's face change?
The official wished to tell people
the secret of the king's death.
But he could not do it because he knew
he would lose his life.
The guilt of having to keep the secret
of the death of the king,
who treasured him,
transformed him into a horrid beast.
Why did you tell me that story?
You and I share one thing in common.
In common?
Yes.
For a very long time,
we both lived in pain.
What do you mean?
Being unable to forget
what you desperately wish to forget
brings unspeakable pain.
That memory brings you pain, does it not?
What memory?
The memory of that day
which torments you.
The day Prince Hwiyeong died.
You!
Who are you to Prince Hwiyeong?
Tell me the truth, Lord Kim.
Do you not see how it is ruining you?
It is time for you to tell the truth.
You!
Is anyone outside?
Yes, my lord.
Take her and put her in prison.
Come in!
Tell me the truth, Lord Kim.
Lord Kim!
Lord Kim, tell me the truth!
Lord Kim! Lord Kim!
What took you so long?
Is something wrong?
The governor is enraged
because of a book reader.
What? I will go now.
You are dismissed.
- Yes, sir!
- Now.
Chunsam.
Yes, sir.
Rice is as valuable as life to people,
and I cannot let them continue
play tricks with it.
Will you announce yourself
as the royal agent?
Yes, and I will force the governor
to confess the whole truth
on what happened to Prince Hwiyeong.
Go and find Dain.
Yes, sir.
What?
What are you waiting for?
Sir, what is Lady Dain doing there?
No!
So the book reader
they were discussing was Lady Dain?
Oh, how could she?
There is no time. I will announce myself,
so you go and bring the station guards
as quickly as possible.
Yes, sir.
The book reader has been imprisoned.
And we have delivered
the offering for Buddha.
The head monk said
your illness will be cured soon.
Is something on your mind?
Lord Kim.
Leave now!
Yes, my lord.
Geez, he's so ill-tempered.
That is why he is not getting better.
What do you want?
Who are you?
I have caught a fox.
A fox?
Didn't you know
that a fox that borrowed
the tiger's authority
has been running the provincial office?
What?
Man, this is my first time
pitying a corrupt official.
The rice offering for Buddha you have
collected forcibly from the people
has been fattening the pockets
of this man.
What?
Who are you?
Me?
I am a royal secret agent.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
Lord Kim Manhui?
What is he doing here?
This is maddening.
Darn it.
Lord Choi.
Where is the royal agent?
Lord Kim, Lord Kim, have you summoned me?
Did you deceive me and steal
the rice offering for Buddha?
How did you...
The royal secret agent told me
of your deception!
Royal secret agent?
You!
How dare you deceive me?
There is no need to be too upset.
This is all your responsibility.
You are using grains mixed with sand
to provide high-interest loans,
eventually pushing people
out of their homes.
Tie them up, and take them out.
This is an order from a royal agent!
- Yes, sir.
Lord Kim, I am innocent!
- Lord Kim, forgive me, Lord Kim!
- Lord Kim!
How does it feel to face the truth?
Facing the truth
can be frightening and unfamiliar.
But you cannot avoid it, can you?
I do not understand what you mean.
You must know about Prince Hwiyeong.
I came here to learn the truth
behind his death.
Prince Hwiyeong...
My lord! A seonjeonkwan
arrived from Hanyang.
What?
What brings you here?
Criminal Seong Igyeom
shall obey the royal command!
Get on the ground!
Criminal?
What do you mean?
Criminal Seong Igyeom colluded
with Jang Taeseung to forge King's order,
ignored his duty as a royal agent,
and conspired with Hong Dain,
a follower of a traitor.
Therefore, his position
as a royal agent is withdrawn,
and he must return to Hanyang.
Confiscate his horse acquisition tablet.
Where is the girl?
The girl named Hong Dain.
Conspired with a traitor?
Who is this traitor?
They found Prince Hwiyeong's belonging
in Dain's room.
And that put the government in turmoil.
What?
Prince Hwiyeong's okro?
Are you doing this for a measly okro?
When I was in Hanyang,
I've received
dozens of okros from high officials.
Come to think of it,
were you not one of my customers?
You!
You are the one who mentioned
Prince Hwiyeong to me first!
You must be associated with him!
Everyone knows about Prince Hwiyeong.
You prefer rumors and stories
over what your people have to say,
so I merely obliged.
What?
I have never seen such insolence.
Royal Agent Seong Igyeom, answer this.
She has accompanied you on your missions,
so you must know who she is.
If you tell the truth,
the charge against you will be cleared.
I will tell the truth.
It was I who ordered her to investigate
the case of Prince Hwiyeong.
Everything she said and did
was under my direct order.
Why did you provide the justification
for him announcing himself?
Reporting that both the royal agent
and the girl committed suicides
during the transport
will raise suspicions.
Lord Kim, you take care of the girl.
That is my father's wish.
When the royal agent asked
about Prince Hwiyeong,
I hesitated for a moment.
Should I recite the story everyone knows
or should I tell the truth no one knows?
Are you going to betray us
after all this time?
That would depend
on what Lord Kim Byeonggeun does.
How dare you mention my father's name?
Who made it possible for you
to take the auditor's position?
I cannot put my fate in the hands
of the Chief State Councilor forever.
Don't you know what happens to traitors?
Do you think killing me
will bury the truth?
I have proof that Prince Hwiyeong
did not commit treason.
Where do you think
that proof will go once I am dead?
Do you want to take everyone
down with you?
I have nothing more to lose!
You are a fool.
If you turn your back on us,
who will keep your family alive?
Why did you do it?
I only told the truth.
What is wrong with that?
I am sorry, Lord Seong.
I ended up putting you in danger.
I am fine.
And this is not the first time.
I will go and tell the truth.
About what?
That I am responsible for everything.
Do you understand what you are saying?
It means you must risk your life.
Do you truly think that will help me?
Lord Seong,
I am Prince Hwiyeong's daughter.
I am the daughter of a traitor.
I know.
Then renounce me.
Only then will you live.
I do not care who you are.
You belong to me.
A royal agent's attendant
belongs to the royal agent.
To whom else would you belong?
That is correct, Lord Seong.
I belong to you.
Bring the prisoner Seong Igyeom.
Lord Seong.
Why are you only taking him?
I am following the King's order
to bring the royal agent back.
Lord Seong, Lord Seong.
Wait here.
We will meet again.
I will return.
Give me a few nights, would you?
Sir.
I trusted you and left you in control
of the provincial government,
so how dare you betray me?
Please spare us, Lord Kim.
We were planning on giving you
all the profit we made.
That is the truth.
Be quiet!
The story of robbers,
was that a lie too?
No, Lord Kim.
We did lose some of the rice to robbery.
Several of my men were attacked
by those robbers.
If that is true, go and get the rice
you lost to them.
If you fail, I will chop your heads off
as your punishment.
Do you understand?
- Yes, Lord Kim!
- Yes, Lord Kim.
Do you have any plans?
We must visit every house
and collect rice.
What?
Shortage of rice
has already caused an outcry.
There is no justification for it.
When did we ever have
justification for taking rice?
We are about to lose our heads,
so why are you concerned for them?
Gather your men.
What?
You were rather good,
but you drove yourself to an early grave.
What happened to the royal agent?
Do not concern yourself with him.
You will meet him soon.
What do you mean?
The Chief State Councilor has
ordered me to kill you,
so do not blame me.
It is not because of the lack of rice
offered to Buddha
that your willness cannot be cured.
What?
Do you think Buddha will accept
the rice offering
that came from people's blood and tears?
Please save the royal agent.
If you return to being their dog,
the rest of your life
will be stained with blood too.
You!
We'll see what you say
when there is a sword on your neck.
What is this?
Move aside!
No! Don't!
Let go!
No, no! Not there!
Please don't go there!
You can't! No!
No!
Sir, please don't! Please!
No, sir!
You!
Who are you?
You found what you came for,
so you should leave.
Mommy!
Are you all right?
My children will starve to death.
Sir, what brings you all the way here?
The rice offering to Buddha
was stolen recently.
We are not associated with those robbers.
I heard robbers have been giving away
the rice they stole.
That is not true.
Do you intend on starving
everyone to death?
I will go and speak to the governor!
Let us take a break here.
What is he doing here?
You have arrived.
Do you know him?
I do.
Does that mean
you were the owner of that gold mine?
You caused me so much damage.
Make sure you leave no evidence.
Yes, my lord.
I will return to Hanyang
and report to His Majesty
that the royal secret agent
took his own life while being transported.
You!
Lord Kim said that he has the evidence
to prove Prince Hwiyeong's innocence.
You must find out what that is.
Once I obtain the evidence,
what should I do with Lord Kim?
Get rid of him.
Yes, my lord.
Let us go.
Let go of me.
Kim Manhui!
Let go!
Oh, your high and mighty face is a mess.
Your spirit that commanded the world
with the horse requisition tablet is gone,
and all that is left is for you
to beg for your life.
Ask me to spare you.
That is serious nonsense.
Did you also kill Prince Hwiyeong?
Needless bravery
and uncompromising temperament.
You and Prince Hwiyeong are quite similar,
so he will be happy to see you
in the other world.
So Prince Hwiyeong was murdered.
I will have another company
on my journey to the other world.
Lord Kim Manhui ordered you to kill
everyone who knows the truth
about Prince Hwiyeong's death.
Kim Myeongse, me...
Who could be next?
You!
How dare you try to trick me?
Get away! Get away!
Sir! Sir!
Are you all right, sir?
Were you waiting for me to die?
Lord Choi!
Lord Seong!
Die!
Lord Choi! Lord Choi!
Lord Choi.
Are you all right?
I lost him. I am sorry.
I'm sure he will return.
To this place?
No, to me.
Sir.
Where are you going?
I cannot let this be.
What? What will you do?
I must go and see him.
I have been waiting for you.
PRINCE HWIYEONG, LEE HAN,
YOU ARE TO RAISE AND TRAIN AN ARMY
TO STOP THE INVASION FROM FOREIGN VESSELS
AND THE LOOTING OF ROBBERS
Father.
When did my daughter become a grown woman?
I must report this to His Majesty.
Come to Hanyang with me tomorrow.
Dain is still at the provincial office.
I must go to her first.
But you are no longer a royal agent.
Wait,
you want to go back there in this state?
You cannot.
I cannot lose another person
who is important to me.
The same goes for you, Chunsam.
Return to Hanyang with Lord Choi.
What?
We had to face death
several times until now,
and you have impressed me enough.
I will come with you.
And so will I.
It may be dangerous.
His Majesty ordered me
to protect the royal agent.
I must send the rice offering to Buddha.
Make preparations.
Lord Kim, it is Bae.
Enter.
Is the rice offering ready?
Yes.
Take this to the temple along with it.
What is this?
It used to belong to the temple,
so I am returning it.
I will not tolerate another mistake.
Of course, Lord Kim.
What did you learn?
They will behead Dain at noon.
What? Behead her?
Sir, what do we do?
Behead her at noon.
I must go to the provincial office.
Sir, where are you going?
He knows what to do.
What?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Come.
Who are you?
Chunsam.
Yes, sir.
Lock the door.
Execute the punishment.
Headsman, enter!
Where is the headsman?
What happened?
He is yet to arrive.
What? The headsman is not here?
You fools!
There he is.
Hurry up and go inside!
Here is the headsman!
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Where is the evidence?
The evidence to prove
that Prince Hwiyeong was not a traitor.
I do not know!
If you refuse to tell me,
I will take your head
and use that as proof.
Please spare me!
A gang of robbers stole all the rice
and is now after my life.
It was Ibeom who took the rice.
I will start searching for Ibeom tomorrow.
What is this?
I thought there was gold inside.
Do you know that man?
He is the man who bought
the rice offering.
The robbers must be planning
on making a deal with him.
What are you doing?
I must get in there.
I am Hong Dain, a merchant from Gimje.