"Tell the truth!"
A suspicious group of men
attacks the royal secret agent.
They murder all the policemen,
including the royal agent.
It has been a long while
since the royal agent was dispatched,
but there is no news, and the government
falls into a state of confusion.
Meanwhile, here is our hero Seong Igyeom.
He is gambling.
He doesn't seem to have a serious bone
in his entire body,
and he and Honglang,
the top courtesan in the city,
got off on the wrong foot.
She is actually Hong Dain, a female police
who is working undercover
as a courtesan.
She is the Chief Royal Secretary's spy.
Meanwhile, the Chief Royal Secretary
searches for a new royal agent
under the king's secret order,
but he just can't find the right man
when he receives information
on Seong Igyeom.
He has gone astray for some reason,
but Igyeom was exceptional enough
to win first place at the state exam,
so he picks him
to be the next royal agent.
He sends Dain, whom he can trust,
to join the royal agent's entourage.
That's how the female police Hong Dain,
Assistant Advisor Seong Igyeom
and his servant Park Chunsam
begin their somewhat unusual journey
as the royal agent's entourage.
Their first destination
is the town where the former royal agent
Park Cheolgyu disappeared.
The three begin each of their missions.
Dain goes undercover as a courtesan
and gets information.
Chunsam goes around the town,
listening to people.
Igyeom hunts and kills the wild boar
that was hurting people
and builds friendship with the sheriffs.
Meanwhile, Dain visits Sawol,
the courtesan whose name was written
in the former royal agent's journal.
Without a word, she leads them
deep into the forest,
and she was about to tell them something
when an arrow that appears
out of nowhere hits her.
Sawol was pregnant, and she gives birth
with the last bit of energy
before passing away.
Igyeom visits the blacksmith
who made the arrows to find the killer,
but he had already been killed.
When Dain mentions Sawol's death
to the other courtesans,
they tell her she was pregnant
with the Little Sheriff's son.
The entourage begins to investigate
the place Sawol took them to earlier.
Soon, they find the former royal agent's
horse requisition tablet and his body.
Little Sheriff who helped attack
the royal agent, and get rid of his body
was about to kill the witness Sawol
but spared her life when she told him
that she was carrying his child.
The moment
all the puzzle pieces came together,
they are apprehended
by Little Sheriff and his men.
The men are sent
to a mine for hard labor,
and Dain is forced
to take them to the baby.
But the place she takes the sheriff
is not where the baby is
but where Assistant Royal Guard
Choi is. Dain escapes with his help,
and they leave to rescue the rest
of the entourage.
The place of hard labor
is an illegal gold mine
the government doesn't know about.
The innocent men
who were brought here by force
were being used to line someone's pockets
in a place where
there are no human rights.
Dain and Assistant Royal Guard Choi
arrive at the gold mine,
and they disguise themselves
as wine sellers and infiltrates the mine.
Moreover, they successfully feed them
wine laced with numbing drugs.
They are about to escape
when Little Sheriff appears with his men.
At that moment, together with Dain
and Assistant Royal Guard Choi,
the men who were forced
to hard labor join them to fight.
And after they subdue
Little Sheriff and his men,
everyone returns to the town.
When Sheriff is about
to kill all the babies
to cover up all their crimes,
a loud voice is heard,
one everyone was waiting for.
"Here comes the royal secret agent."
He solves the case, earns the trust
of the King and gets a promotion,
but something nags at him.
It was the fact that he failed to uncover
the true owner of the gold mine.
So Igyeom goes
to interrogate the sheriffs,
but he hears
the shocking news of their suicides.
When he visits the man
who found the bodies,
he had also been killed by someone.
Leaving the uneasy feeling behind,
he takes his mind off the case
and gets ready to lead a normal life
as a high official.
But he is shocked
when he sees a wanted poster
of a gang of bandits that had been raising
havoc in Jeolla Province.
It was his younger brother Ibeom.
A few years ago, Igyeom went to Hanyang,
took the state exam,
placed at the top, and returned home.
But while he was away,
his beloved was imprisoned
for apparently seducing men in town,
and had fled with Ibeom,
who had fallen in love with her.
It was impossible to believe,
but when he caught up with them,
something even more tragic
was waiting for him.
Years passed without him knowing
whether or not they were alive,
but he learns that his brother had become
the leader of a gang of bandits.
Igyeom pays a visit
to the Chief Royal Secretary
and asks him to send him as
the royal secret agent to Jeolla Province.
Meanwhile, Dain hears that
the seonjeonkwan who witnessed
her parents' deaths is in Jeolla Province,
and the three of them
begin another journey.
Their first stop is a place where men
from all walks of life have gathered.
A gambling house.
But they run into the sheriff
who was demoted a long time ago
because of Dain's investigation.
They successfully get away,
but Igyeom spots his younger brother.
He goes after him
as if possessed by a ghost
when he also spots his beloved.
That is when he is apprehended
by the sheriff's men,
and when they are about to be killed
in a deserted forest,
arrows come flying.
The arrows were from the gang of bandits.
And Igyeom's younger brother Ibeom...
"It has been a long time, Brother."
Appears.
EPISODE 7
So you are all in this together.
You will never leave this town alive.
I will kill every one of you
by tearing your limbs apart.
Just you wait.
We finally meet.
It's been a long time, Brother.
I did think that we would meet again
as long as we're both alive,
but I never expected for us
to meet this way.
Of course.
Ibeom.
Brother.
What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I understand, so please stop.
What are you doing? Huh?
I am doing what I must.
What you must?
Robbery is what you must do?
I heard that you've been robbing noblemen
throughout the country.
Those noblemen were not noble.
They were corrupt and made themselves rich
by imposing heavy taxes on people.
How does that justify robbing?
I only returned what was taken from them!
You once asked me
to change the world with you, did you not?
But then again,
you were wandering in the gambling house,
so you must have changed quite a bit.
That was...
Fine. Let me ask you one thing.
Was it you who killed Lord Lee
and his family?
No.
When we arrived, they were already dead.
That was not your doing?
I have never killed innocent people.
You would not believe anything I say.
You know me well.
It must be difficult to believe,
but we only take money.
We do not take people's lives.
And is that something to be proud of?
You are shameless.
I do not believe it was you.
If you had slaughtered those people,
you would be gone by now.
Did you target the gambling house
because you couldn't rob Lord Lee's house?
Why do you ask
when you do not believe me?
You...
Then make me believe you.
Why did you run then?
What happened?
Sunae!
- Sunae!
- Get them!
What is the use of dwelling in the past?
Just accept me as I am right now.
Does that mean the rumors are true?
Did you really
fall in love with Sunae,
abandon your position,
and flee with her?
Think what you want.
What happened to Sunae?
You must forget about her.
She passed away.
I will not blame you for that.
Come with me.
You expect me to go back
to being the noblemen's slave?
I refuse.
Do you think I would let you leave?
We have drifted too far apart.
We are leaving, so do not look for us.
Seong Ibeom!
You cannot change the world
with robbery.
Remember that.
Okay, okay.
Destiny brought us together,
so why not make introductions?
I am Park Chunsam.
A little smile won't kill you.
Doesn't frowning all day
hurt your forehead?
Let's not do this.
Take off your masks, so we can talk.
Boss.
Chunsam.
Yes, sir.
Look after my big brother.
What?
Oh, of course.
Come.
- Yes, sir.
"Look after my big brother."
He thinks he's so great.
Lord Seong.
The magistrate must think
we are working with the bandits.
We should leave town for now.
Come.
Magistrate.
Where are they?
Who?
Those bandits!
Those thieves...
Magistrate,
you must try to calm down for now.
Forget it!
Gather all the patrolmen.
Now!
Yes, sir.
The bandits are skilled in martial arts.
Apprehend them with any means.
And among them is a girl dressed as a man.
Make sure to bring her to me alive.
- Yes, sir.
Lock the town down
and search for the bandits!
- Yes, sir!
What is wrong?
Lord Seong, what are your plans?
I am postponing my appearance.
The bandits did not kill Lord Lee.
When they arrived,
the people were already dead.
Right?
I didn't think Lord Ibeom
was responsible...
Do you believe his words?
They are bandits.
You must not forget that.
I have thought it through
to reach that conclusion.
But...
Will you give me your trust?
I will.
Sir, what did you talk about
with Lord Ibeom?
He told me to put the past behind me.
Was that all?
He told me about Sunae.
He did?
Is Lady Sunae doing well?
Sunae is dead.
What?
Let us go to the temple.
We will spend the night there.
Come, Lady Dain.
What took you so long?
You must be hungry.
Sunae.
What is that smell?
I made chicken soup.
I knew it. It smells amazing.
Go ahead and eat.
- Yes, sir!
- Yes, sir.
Come with me.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing is wrong.
I heard people were murdered in town.
Did you go down to the town?
I went down to buy...
Have I not told you
to refrain from going out?
Go and pack your things.
Is there a problem?
The problem is...
Me for getting you involved in this.
Why would you say such a thing?
If you want to blame anyone,
blame me.
Isn't this life hard for you?
You are acting strange today.
Did something happen?
Go in and get some rest.
Seong Ibeom!
You cannot change the world
with robbery.
One cannot change the world
You haven't changed a bit, Brother.
Are you having trouble falling asleep?
My eyes just opened.
Why did you come out?
Here.
I did not have the chance
to give this back to you.
What's wrong?
Oh, my hand feels numb
because of what happened earlier.
Let me see.
It's nothing.
It is not nothing.
How does it feel?
Is it better?
Yes, it is much better.
Ouch.
Why? What's wrong now?
This hand hurts too.
What?
But you didn't use this hand.
Oh, my arm.
How's that?
It feels much lighter.
But earlier,
I bumped into something very hard,
and I cannot lift my arm.
Are you having fun?
Right. Thank you.
It's late.
You should try to get some sleep.
Dain.
Yes?
The man you are looking for,
are you in pain because of him?
I would have to meet him to know.
What will you do when you meet him?
I will ask for the truth.
Just as you did.
Aren't you afraid of that?
I am.
But unless I face the truth,
I will end up living my life
in bigger fear.
If I may be so bold,
do not try too hard.
The pain of losing the one you love
is not something you can overcome.
True.
If you would rather be alone, tell me.
Aren't you tired?
I am perfectly fine.
I must be mistaken.
Is this your way of offering comfort?
Is this really true?
Would I dare lie to you, Your Majesty?
Your Majesty,
the Chief Royal Secretary is here.
He may enter.
Have you called for me, Your Majesty?
The royal secret agent is living
in hedonism and has been seen gambling.
That is slander, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, he was also seen
gambling with eunuchs while he was here,
causing moral corruption in the palace.
You know that very well, do you not?
Your Majesty, summon the royal
secret agent and punish him gravely.
Lord Jang.
You should have chosen wisely.
How could you put a morally corrupt man
in charge of His Majesty's work?
Why are you so concerned of a royal agent
a thousand miles away
when there are so many
morally corrupt officials in the palace?
I beg your pardon?
Did you really send a royal agent
to learn about why people are angry?
Are you sure there isn't
an ulterior motive?
Is there a reason why
you are so afraid of the royal agent?
What? Afraid?
Chief Royal Secretary Jang!
I will send a man to find out
if the appeal is true or not.
If the royal agent has committed a crime,
he will receive punishment,
but if it was a false accusation,
banjwayul will be applied.
How dare he.
Father, will you let him
get away with that?
It is not time.
We must deal with the royal agent first.
The royal agent?
Send a messenger to Seoyong.
He must arrive first.
Yes, Father.
Your Majesty, I am afraid to say
Chief State Councilor Kim
knew of the royal agent's moves
even before the seogye arrived.
I do not believe his every word.
However, since an appeal was submitted,
I must get to the bottom of it.
Please send a man to the royal agent.
Whom can I send?
Your Majesty, I shall
devote my energy into protecting you!
Do you know the royal agent?
Not at all, Your Majesty.
Then you would be even more impartial
when reporting on the royal agent.
Y-Your Majesty.
Am I wrong?
I am eternally grateful, Your Majesty!
Lord Jang.
I believe in you.
Your Majesty.
Over there.
What is going on?
They are being taken because of debts.
Debts?
Are they all?
They are only some on the list.
Where are the rest?
Well...
They either fled or took their own lives.
How could they be so irresponsible
after taking someone else's money?
Song Junam.
Yes? Yes, Magistrate.
You owe over 300 coins,
including interest.
How will you pay it back?
Well, Magistrate, we borrowed
the money from Lord Lee,
so why were we brought here?
So, now that Lord Lee is dead,
you were happy thinking that
you didn't have to pay your debt.
And now you're wondering why I am
asking you to pay your debt. Is that it?
No, that is not it.
You are an ingrate!
Maybe it wasn't the bandits.
Was it you who killed Lord Lee
to get out of your debt?
What? Sir.
Listen carefully.
Since Lord Lee's death,
his fortune has been reverted
to the government office.
Therefore, your debts have been reverted
That is unreasonable.
Unreasonable?
Did you expect your debt to suddenly
disappear with Lord Lee?
You are truly shameless.
Guards!
Punish this wicked man by flogging!
- Yes, sir!
Sir.
Sir!
Flog him until he learns his lesson!
Sir.
Lead us to your house.
You cannot return home by yourself.
Try to walk a little.
He's collecting the money
people owe the late Lord Lee?
That is unreasonable.
How much do you owe?
I owe about 300 coins.
What? 300 coins?
Is that all gambling debt?
I wasn't into gambling at first.
I had to borrow money
to pay the jabyeokse.
Then someone told me
of the gambling house,
saying I could pay my debt off at once.
Afterwards, as you know,
I fell deeper and deeper into debt
because of gambling.
You fool!
Are you saying Lord Lee
continued to lend money
to men who got addicted to gambling?
Yes, he was happy to hear
that we were gambling.
Because the gambling house was his.
Men quickly became addicted to gambling.
And so did I.
Was there no policing?
The reward for turning a blind eye
must have been sweet.
Don't be surprised.
This is just the beginning.
Don't stay cooped in here.
Come and enjoy yourself.
That must be why the sheriff
frequented the gambling house.
He is extremely crafty.
He took over the gambling house
just after Lord Lee's death.
What if the opposite was true?
The opposite?
What if the sheriff, in order
to take ownership of the gambling house,
killed Lord Lee?
No.
When we arrived, they were already dead.
The bandits must have given him
the perfect cover for his crime.
I must visit Lord Lee's house.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
It is very quiet.
The whole family was massacred,
so people are afraid.
Sir, must you go inside?
Every crime scene holds clues.
There are no people around,
so it will be safer.
What? They are always quarreling,
but now they're perfect partners.
For you to come in like this...
Sir, something doesn't feel right.
Let us split up and look for clues.
Yes, Lord Seong.
Sir?
It doesn't feel right.
Sir!
Lord Seong.
Lord Seong, something doesn't fit.
This does not look like a place
where a massacre took place.
I felt that too. It is immaculately tidy.
It's as if someone cleaned it.
I found these in the shed.
Those are the strips.
Yes, they must have made these here.
To think a rich man like Lord Lee
making these strips...
Professional gamblers sometimes use
the patterns on the strips
to read the other players' hands.
He probably made them to prevent that.
Sir! Come here! Sir!
What is it?
Sir, try this kimchi.
It is delicious. There's rice too.
You...
Oh.
We got robbed, and I can't remember
the last time we ate.
We need to eat.
You are right.
We should eat.
I will cook the rice.
Stop.
Should you take other people's things?
Yes or no?
Get up.
Think of all the innocent people
who lost their lives here.
Yes, I guess you're right.
So let us remember the dead
as we eat this food.
Thank you!
Oh, darn it.
Sir, what about Lady Dain?
There is plenty of rice and kimchi,
so she will eat if she gets hungry.
Right?
Let us eat.
Delicious.
Why won't they ask me one more time?
Haven't they heard of
"The third time's the charm"?
"You haven't eaten all day
so have just one bite."
Is that so hard to say?
You heartless people.
You idiots!
Magistrate, we locked the town down
and searched every inch of the mountain,
but we could not find them.
They must have left the town.
Did you see it?
What? No, I haven't, but...
Those thieves would not have left
empty-handed.
I will give you three days.
Find their traces at least.
Yes, Magistrate!
Boss!
This is what is left of the money
we gave to the poor.
Divide it among yourselves.
There is enough for you
to buy your own land.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
The time I told you about is today.
- Boss!
- Boss, you can't do this.
Boss, how could you do this
without talking to us first?
When we first got together,
we began this work in order to live
as decent human beings.
I think it is time to stop.
Boss.
Thank you for everything.
Go and live normal lives
without having to be chased.
Sunae!
What is it?
Please stop him.
He wants to get out of this business.
Get out of this business?
Is he going to quit robbing people?
Yes! This is all because
of what happened yesterday.
If he hadn't met his older brother...
Older brother?
We met Boss Ibeom's big brother.
Is it true?
What do you mean?
Did you meet Lord Igyeom
at the gambling house?
Yes, I did.
How...
He looked healthy.
Isn't that what you wanted to ask?
He asked about you.
What did you say?
I told him you died.
Why did you do that?
I thought that was the best thing
I could do for him.
So put him behind you.
Sir. Sir?
Be quiet. Go to sleep.
I am too scared to go to sleep.
Silly man. What is there to be scared of?
What is it?
Over there, over there.
Over there what? What?
The door shook.
I mean it.
That's because it's windy!
Rattle, rattle.
Let me get some sleep! Please!
Oh, I'm starving.
I hope they didn't eat everything.
Whoa.
Kimchi should be eaten by hand.
I hope they don't wake up.
What was that?
Why is this so hard?
Lord Seong?
Is that you, Chunsam?
What ghost? Geez.
Let me join you.
Oh, and you call yourself a man?
What was that sound?
Dain?
Why? What is it?
It's a ghost.
Dain!
A ghost.
You don't look like a vengeful ghost.
What are you?
Please help me.
Oh, my heart is still pounding.
Tell me. Who are you?
Why are you here?
Start talking.
Can you please give us some privacy?
Lord Seong, can I borrow
the horse requisition tablet?
My name is Hong Dain.
We are not robbers,
and we are not from the government office.
Would you look at this?
Do you know what this is?
It's a horse requisition tablet.
The man you saw earlier
is a royal secret agent.
And I am in his entourage.
We came to find out
why everyone in this house died.
What is your name?
I am Lee Aeran.
Aeran.
Why are you here?
I am a concubine's daughter of this house.
Then was Lord Lee your father?
So why are you here alone?
Can you tell me
what happened that night?
I didn't see anything.
Where is the girl?
She just fell asleep.
I see. Who killed everyone?
She was hiding
behind the rice chest the whole time,
so she did not see what was happening.
We have no way of proving
the sheriff's crimes.
But there was one thing she knew.
Every month on the day of the full moon,
a cart arrived at this house.
In the cart were chests filled with coins,
and Lord Lee divided them up
and sent them out.
Enough coins to fill a cart?
Was it the profit from the gambling house?
Tomorrow is the day of the full moon.
After sending the money out,
Lord Lee always wrote it down.
A ledger. He left a ledger.
If we find that, we'll know who received
money from the gambling house.
How do we know where the ledger is?
There is one place
even the bandits never got to rob.
The gambling house.
Chunsam, go to the gambling house
tomorrow and find the ledger.
Yes, but where is the ledger
in the gambling house?
There is a woman who manages that place.
She will know.
But am I going alone?
Yes.
I am going to steal the money
coming out of the gambling house.
I will come with you.
- No.
- What?
- Then I'll go with Chunsam.
- Yes.
- That is a worse idea.
- What?
You stay here.
Why are you leaving me out?
Don't you trust me?
It's not that.
It's too dangerous.
Come to think of it, I'm hurt.
Are you saying I'm okay
to be in danger?
You...
Do as I say!
Then let me go with you and keep watch.
You will need every help you can get.
Boss!
Sunae is missing.
Boss, did she say
she was leaving without us?
Don't worry about her.
You guys go.
I'm coming with you!
I will follow the cart.
You go and find the ledger.
Yes, sir.
You stay here.
Are you sure?
Don't worry.
Wait.
What if we miss each other?
Meet me back at Lord Lee's house.
Be careful.
Do you know where the gambling house is?
Gambling house?
I don't know.
If you want to flirt,
go to the courtesan house,
not here!
What's a big deal
about my groping your bottom?
What?
Take him and teach him a lesson,
so he will never come back here.
Yes, ma'am.
Maehyang! Maehyang!
That filthy animal.
Look who's here.
I was wondering if you were dead or alive.
But how bold of you to come back here.
Why are you dressed like a man again?
You want to gamble?
I don't.
But I heard there is a ledger in there.
A ledger?
What about the ledger?
Oh.
Chunsam.
Let go of me!
You're a strong woman.
Oh, what are you doing?
What do you want?
Stay still!
What are you doing?
That's...
Watch her.
But Lord Igyeom said
you should keep watch.
I am much more familiar
with the inside.
Anyway, it won't take long.
Who are you people?
Do you think you could get away with this?
You will get hurt!
I may not look like much,
but I grew up in this business!
Chunsam,
shut her up. She's too loud.
Yes, Lady Dain.
Huh? Huh?
Why "Huh?" Oh, you're too loud.
What are you doing?
Hey! Hey!
Stop!
What happened?
I was attacked by the bandits.
They are robbing people over there.
Help us.
How many are there?
Two.
There is a big bounty on their heads.
This is my lucky day.
Come.
What about him?
It's not our problem if he lives or dies.
Watch the cart. We will get the bandits.
Where are the bandits?
What happened?
Magistrate?
Magistrate? Magistrate!
Be quiet.
Wait.
I'm going to the gambling house.
I'll pay you back.
Where is Maehyang?
I don't know.
Find her.
- Yes, sir.
What?
You!
Don't come any closer.
You have gone mad.
Don't come any closer!
I will kill you.
Fire! Fire!
Get out if you don't want
to burn to death!
- Fire!
Where? Where?
Get out! Get out!
Chunsam.
Lady Dain.
Come.
Okay.
Chunsam?
Sir, what brings you here?
How do you feel?
I can walk now.
Take this.
Get medicine with this.
But you don't have any money.
Don't worry.
I took this from the sheriff.
What?
So, the man the magistrate
put a bounty on was you?
Yes. Are you surprised?
Of course I am.
How much is the bounty?
I think it was 100 coins.
Only 100?
Once I give out that money I stole
to the people, my bounty will increase.
Kill Royal Agent Seong Igyeom
and cover it up.
Where is the royal agent?
Dain.
Chunsam.
Sir!
Sir. Sir.
How did it go?
Don't even get me started. Lady Dain...
I found it.
This is the ledger with the recordings
of all the transactions.
Take a look at this page.
Yes.
All the money is going to the sheriff.
It was only a part of the profit
until recently,
but now all of it goes to him.
I was right.
What happened to the money
from the gambling house?
I stole it and hid it.
You two are unbelievable.
But the money and the ledger
may not be enough to prove
that the sheriff killed Lord Lee.
I have a plan.
Let us prepare for our appearance.
Let us go, sir.
I think I am hallucinating.
What's wrong?
Sunae.
Right? But isn't she?
Isn't she Lady Sunae?
It has been too long, Lord Igyeom.
Is it really you?
Let me see you.
What took you so long?
I am sorry.
I thought you were dead.
Lord Ibeom did that to protect me.
Were you with Ibeom?
Yes.
Come with me.
I need to hear what happened to you.
Wait, sir.
Seong Igyeom!
Who are you?
I apologize for interrupting
such a tender moment.
You.
You look better
than when you were doing hard labor.
You are the man who pretended
to be the mine owner.
I was hoping to apprehend you,
and here you are.
How should I thank you?
I should've killed you then and there.
- Chunsam.
- Yes?
Take them and go to the temple.
Sir.
Now!
Yes, sir.
Get them.
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Assault and rape.
He took his time to torture her to death.
It must be from a personal grudge.
It is getting more vicious.
You mean there are more victims?
Two women were found dead,
and one woman disappeared and is missing.
Are you even trying
to capture the culprit?
We are doing our best
to investigate, but...
While you were taking your time,
another woman got killed.
As a royal agent,
I will investigate this case myself.