Sawol!
Sawol, Sawol.
Who's there?
Stay with me, Sawol.
My baby...
Save my baby, please.
Sawol.
Wake up, Sawol!
Sawol. Sawol!
Sir!
Is anyone there? Open this door!
We need help!
Who's there?
What is the matter?
There is no time!
She has lost too much blood.
If we remove the arrow, she may die.
Please save my baby.
Go and bring the midwife.
The amniotic sac has ruptured.
She is in labor.
There's no time.
She cannot give birth in this state.
Neither the mother
nor the baby will survive.
Then are you going to just sit and watch?
Sawol, the baby is coming.
You must hang in there.
What are you doing?
I will assist her with childbirth.
Help me get prepared.
Can you do it?
I have never tried it,
but I have assisted before.
Fine.
Sawol, hang in there.
Not yet. Push!
Push a little bit harder.
Please... Bury me in that place.
The baby is coming.
Just a little bit more.
Sawol.
It is here.
Sawol, it is a boy.
Sawol, what did you see?
Why did you take us there?
Sawol.
Wake up, Sawol.
Sawol!
Sawol...
I share no responsibility
for this woman's death.
This woman was murdered.
That is something you must report
to the government office.
We need your help.
I understand.
It will be daybreak soon so come with me
to the government office.
Thank you.
It's already midday, so where are they?
What if they got into trouble again?
They haven't returned?
No.
I wonder why.
His Majesty will be furious.
I'm the only one
who is fulfilling his duty.
- I need to go out for a while.
- Sure.
- I'll help you later.
What? Why are they back?
Those darn men.
You!
You! I warned you
never to show your face here again!
Actually...
Be quiet!
What happened?
It is nothing.
They were asking about you.
Me?
Yes.
Sheriff ordered us to bring you
with utmost care.
Sheriff?
No. Never!
Sir.
- Sir.
If we fail to bring you,
we're all dead meat.
So, why did you
summon that courtesan late at night?
I did not summon her.
She paid me a visit.
This courtesan visited you? Why?
She was about to tell me
when an arrow flew in and hit her.
An arrow flew in, you said?
Is this what killed that courtesan?
That's correct.
That's called a steel tip arrow,
and I was told they're made to order.
You will be able to catch the culprit
by getting a list of suspects
who bought the steel tip arrows
from the bow and arrow maker.
This is the arrow you used
when you killed the wild boar, is it not?
If my intention was to kill her,
why would I have gone to the doctor?
She was alive then.
The doctor will confirm it.
Is he telling the truth?
Yes, he is.
I understand.
Return home for now.
Once the investigation begins,
I will summon you back.
You must find suspects first...
I understand. You may leave.
Thank you for your help.
What is a doctor's job?
I am only disappointed
that I could not save the woman's life.
How did it go?
All I tried to do was to save a life,
but I almost got framed for murder.
What are you going to do with the baby?
What else could we do?
We should look after him
for at least a while.
Give him to me.
Good boy, good boy.
He is hungry.
He needs to be fed.
What are you looking at?
Find someone to nurse him.
I have an urgent business to take care of.
But...
I must pay a visit
to the bow and arrow maker.
Here.
I am going to the courtesan house.
I will feed the baby,
and find out more about Sawol.
Someone may know the identity
of the boy's father.
There must be a reason why
she had to die.
I agree with you.
Stay safe.
Dain!
Yes?
We're finally working as a team.
Haven't you noticed
I've been making all the efforts for that?
How sweet her words are.
Did you get it?
Yes.
These were the officials who belonged
to the Office of Military Staff Guards.
Do you know who was in charge
of escorting Prince Hwiyeong?
Well... I am not sure of that.
Kim Myeongse?
Is this the governor of Jeolla Province
Yes, that is he.
He is the envy of every young official.
He started to climb up the ladder
about ten years ago
and got rich by serving as an auditor
for two consecutive terms.
I apologize.
But why do you ask?
Good job.
Of course.
Is there something you want to tell me?
You are the one who must talk.
I heard you gave something
to the chief secretary.
Well...
Tell His Lordship this instant!
The Chief Royal Secretary was looking
for a former seonjeonkwan.
So I only gave him a list of names.
You did not only give it to him.
A military staff guard...
What was the reason?
I do not know the reason.
You handed over a list of officials
without knowing why?
And you... Received money for it?
Well, I...
I have committed a grave sin!
It is only grave if you stay silent.
Tell me.
What else did you talk about?
He asked which man on the list
escorted P-Prince Hwiyeong,
and I told him I did not know.
That is all!
Prince Hwiyeong?
Please wait here for a moment.
Sure.
You've gone mad!
On top of impersonating a royal agent,
you're meeting the Sheriff?
Chunsam, if Lord Igyeom finds out...
Welcome.
It is an honor to have you as my guest.
I am Kang Inchung,
the sheriff of this town.
Good.
You asked to see me?
Being a royal agent is difficult,
and it does not pay well.
Now that you are in my town,
you must give me a chance to treat you.
Treat me?
This is not much, but please accept it.
What is this?
Isn't this gold?
Please put in a good word for me
with His Majesty.
Forget it.
Gold to me is like stone!
That is even better.
What?
Pretend those are pieces of stone
and take them, won't you?
I am not mad, so how could I?
These are pieces of stone, stone.
These are pieces of stone.
It's gold.
Are you here to order a bow?
What are you doing? Why?
Are you in?
My good man!
Wake up!
Thank you.
Oh, how precious.
Where did you find this infant?
- What a sweet creature.
- He is adorable.
May I hold him?
Obviously someone abandoned him
because they didn't want to raise him.
Like you?
Be quiet, girls. He might hear you.
He's Sawol's baby.
Where is Sawol?
I-Is she dead?
She was a good girl.
This is all his doing.
This is all whose doing?
Are you serious?
Fine!
We call that man the Little Sheriff.
The Little Sheriff? Kang Jonggil?
How could a pregnant courtesan
stay at the courtesan house?
He made sure Sawol could stay here.
His father would have been furious
had he found out,
so he hid her here.
Look after the baby.
If he cries, feed him.
Are you in?
Are you in there?
Sir, what brings you back here?
Take it.
Pardon me?
What is this?
Open it.
This is gold.
You are correct.
This is too much.
No, thank you.
With this, you won't go hungry again.
Take it for the sake of your boys.
Thank you, thank you.
Get back to what you were doing.
Goodbye.
Lord Seong, I am glad you are here.
I have something to tell...
The bow and arrow maker is dead.
What?
The man who killed Sawol is destroying
any and all evidence.
Do you have an idea whom it might be?
He is an expert archer.
How many man could there be in this town
who uses a custom-made bow
and can hit a target in the dark?
Kang Jonggil?
Yes.
But something is odd.
How could he kill a woman
carrying his child?
What?
Sawol was pregnant
with Kang Jonggil's child.
Let us talk inside.
So why did he kill Sawol?
Sawol knew something
about the previous royal secret agent.
When she tried to tell us, he killed her.
Our only witness is dead.
What horrible thing could he have done
to kill the woman
who was carrying his child to hide it?
The royal secret agent?
Kang Jonggil becomes disgusting
when he gets drunk,
so Sawol always dealt with him.
She could have heard something
about the royal secret agent.
He says all sorts of things
when he gets drunk.
When he's inebriated,
he will even criticize his own father,
so if you nudged him a bit,
he might tell you something.
You mean ask him directly?
Yes.
Let me try it.
No.
No?
The risk is too high because
we do not know how he might react.
But this is the quickest way.
Alcohol is best for finding out
how one feels inside.
Do you think he will tell you?
I am Honglang.
Winning over a man's heart
is like taking candy from a baby.
Do you think all men are that simple?
Some men are like me.
W-What are you doing?
What are you trying to do?
With you, it's not that I have failed.
I chose not to.
Do you think I would fall for you?
The Little Sheriff is here.
Do not get yourself in trouble.
We meet again, sir.
Sir, let me pour you a drink.
This tastes especially sweet tonight.
Sir.
She's having fun, isn't she?
Please stop.
Stay still.
Sawol is dead, I hear.
Yes.
Do you know who killed her?
How would I know?
Yes, she got herself killed.
What do you mean?
How dare she be in league
with a royal agent?
Sawol was in league with a royal agent?
Where were you last night?
I was here.
Liar.
Tell me what you saw.
Sir, I do not understand what you're...
You've been in league
with a royal agent as well!
You filthy bastard.
Tell me, why did you kill Sawol?
You are meddling.
Do you wish to end up like him?
Did you kill the royal secret agent?
Tell me. I asked you if you killed him.
Do you think I killed him?
Then try to prove it.
You!
Lord Seong.
Come.
Sir.
Get them!
That way! Get them!
Get them, get them!
This way.
Take him to a safe place.
Thank you.
Go.
Go to the tavern and see Chunsam.
What about you?
You go ahead.
I refuse to go alone.
I will catch up with you soon.
I will hold you to that.
Of course.
So, who's first?
What are you waiting for? Get him!
Hey, this is cheating.
Lady Dain, what happened?
Where is Lord Seong?
Why do you have a baby?
Take him.
Whose baby is this?
It's a long story.
Let me catch my breath.
Where is Lord Seong?
He is fighting with Kang Jonggil's men.
What?
But what if something happens to him?
Don't worry about him.
You don't know him well enough,
but growing up,
he was the best fighter in his town.
Instead of studying, he practiced
martial arts with his younger brother.
I'm sure many of them are hurt by now.
If you kill me,
you won't make it out of here alive.
Kill you?
Do you think I would make it that easy?
I will make sure you live in pain
for the rest of your life.
You won't get away with this!
I will remember this!
How did he place first on the state exam
if all he did was fight?
Lady Dain, once a man
finds love in his heart,
he can do anything.
He fell in love?
Yes.
But that was how the tragedy began.
Tragedy? What do you mean?
Nothing happened.
Tell me.
So Lord Seong is...
You're back.
Sir, how are you feeling?
Are you hurt?
Don't worry.
If there is one thing I hate,
it is getting beaten by someone.
Let us go inside.
I haven't done this in a while,
so I ache everywhere.
Where does it hurt?
Let me see.
Ouch.
Why did you get involved?
I have my own ways
of taking care of things.
I regret not beating them even more.
How could you say that
when you are hurt?
If I am in this state,
imagine the kind of state they must be in.
Are you inside?
Who could that be?
Maybe it's someone Kang Jonggil sent.
I will go and check.
Who's there?
Oh! Madam, what are you doing here?
Madam?
I thought about it,
and I must return this to you.
Don't.
I am with him.
What did you come here to return?
Sir.
Your kindness is enough for me.
Please take good care of him.
I was going to tell you, but...
What is this?
Please calm down.
Actually, I got them from Kang Inchung.
What?
Please let him explain.
Tell us the truth.
What happened while we were gone?
I deserve to die, sir.
I impersonated a royal agent.
And I accepted the bribe
the Sheriff offered.
I am sorry.
What? A bribe?
It wasn't for me.
A widow and her children were starving,
so I had no choice but to...
Sir, please calm down.
How dare you accept a bribe?
Sir.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
How are you feeling?
I'm sorry, Lady Dain.
I deserved it.
Let me see your face.
No, I am fine.
Let me see.
That looks painful.
You are the only one who cares for me.
Tell me the rest of the story.
What story?
That tragedy.
What happened
after Lord Seong fell in love?
He was happy.
But it was brief.
Lord Seong had to leave
to take the state exam,
and the two of them had to part.
But I heard Lord Seong
won the highest honor.
He did.
But when he returned,
everything was different.
Sir!
Wait, sir!
Lady Sunae was imprisoned,
but Lord Seong's younger brother
who was working at the government office
took her and fled with her.
Shoot them!
Sunae!
Get them!
Sir!
Don't shoot.
What are you doing?
Get him out of my way.
Wait!
Why was Lord Seong's beloved imprisoned?
According to rumors,
Lady Sunae began seducing men in town.
after Lord Seong left.
And she was imprisoned because of that.
One of those men was
Lord Seong's younger brother.
So Lord Seong's beloved
and his younger brother were intimate?
I haven't seen them since then,
so there is no way to confirm that.
Now there are just rumors.
How could that be?
After that day,
he became a completely different man.
Lady Dain!
Where are you going?
I'm alone again.
Why did I bring that fool with me?
How dare he impersonate a royal agent
and accept a bribe?
Gosh! I am furious.
Why are you looking at me like that?
It's nothing.
You are a good man.
Are you drunk?
If it hadn't been for you,
I would've gotten killed.
Thank you.
Oh, that.
It is too soon to thank me.
We still have much work to do.
Sir!
I deserve to die.
Stand up.
Pardon me?
Sir.
You are...
Fired from the royal agent's entourage.
Pardon me?
And the moment we return to Hanyang,
you will be punished for your crimes.
Sir!
Lord Seong, Chunsam made a mistake,
but he is regretting it.
Please show mercy.
Separating public and private businesses
is a virtue every royal agent must have.
I came to punish corrupt officials,
but my own man has committed a crime,
so I must punish him accordingly.
Sir.
When that imbecile
claimed he was a royal secret agent,
Kang Inchung bribed him
instead of killing him.
So why did he have to kill Park Cheolgyu?
There must be
something bigger they're trying to hide,
on top the death of a royal agent.
Is anyone there?
Father.
Did you play another hunting game
with the prisoners?
He had committed kangsangjoe,
and deserved to be beheaded.
What?
How could you do something that insane
when we need every manpower we can find?
Go to the next town
and bring back laborers.
Do you understand?
Yes.
He is burning up.
He doesn't look very well.
Baby, if you are sick,
tell us here it hurts.
This must be a very serious illness,
or he couldn't be crying so hard.
We better take him to see a doctor.
Doctor, please take a look at this baby.
Oh, it's you.
But I have an urgent patient.
Take a second and look at him.
You are the one who saved his life.
Let me see him.
Lower his temperature by putting
a piece of cold cloth over his forehead,
and feed him when he wakes up.
Is that all?
He was crying as if he was dying.
That is how all babies do.
His mother's dying wish
was for us to save him,
so he won't die that easily.
That little guy almost gave me
a heart attack.
Sawol's dying wish. Her last words.
Please... Bury me in that place.
Sir, what's wrong?
There must be a reason why
Sawol asked us to bury her in that place.
I need to visit the forest.
Sir.
I will go.
I will go too.
No, Chunsam, you stay here
and look after the baby.
But... Lady Dain!
What are you doing?
The baby is crying.
But... But...
I'm not a nurse.
Oh, it's okay.
All finished.
How do you feel?
I feel much better.
Next time, be punctual.
I apologize.
People brought in a baby all of a sudden.
You must know too.
The courtesan who was killed
by an arrow,
it was her baby.
What do you mean?
That girl died.
Yes, she died.
But she gave birth just before her death.
I used every medical techniques I have
to save that baby.
Is that true?
That baby is alive?
Yes.
He is such a handsome boy.
Where is the man who brought the baby?
Bury her here?
Get rid of him.
Come.
Move them here.
What are you doing here?
Do you know that royal agent?
I asked if you know him!
He said he would find my little brother.
You were in league with the royal agent.
I am with child!
I am with your... Child.
Sir, what's wrong?
Special Advisor Park.
Special Advisor Park!
Special Advisor Park...
You dug your own grave.
I will bury you here, as you wish.
You! Do you not fear the punishment?
How dare you raise your voice to me?
Take them to the government office!
- Yes, sir.
Dain!
Lord Seong!
Oh, how can a little guy like this
poo like a horse?
Are you smiling?
I want to cry.
I will wash this clean. Just wait.
What's that?
He always gets himself into trouble
whenever I'm not looking.
The man who brought you
to the Office of Special Advisors
was me.
I was very impressed
by your confidence even in the presence
of me and other officials
when I first met you.
You never cease to impress me.
The rumors of your self-indulgent
lifestyle, drinking every day,
were true.
What happened to the man
who placed first on the state exam?
I was wrong about you.
How can you trust people?
People are the one thing
you should never trust.
Seong Igyeom.
Do you know why a country falls?
It is because people stop believing
in their country
once they witness officials like you.
Lord Seong.
What is it?
Don't lose faith until tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
What is happening tomorrow?
Royal Guard Choi is coming.
What do you mean? I was never told.
Well, he is not coming here to see you.
Anyway, when he arrives tomorrow,
he will become suspicious of my absence
and come looking for us.
Tell me the whole story.
Why is Royal Guard Choi coming
to see you without my knowledge?
Are you keeping something from me?
Well...
I was ordered to report your activities.
What?
You were spying on me?
I wouldn't call it that.
That means you did not trust me.
Chunsam stabbed me in the back
and now you.
I cannot trust anyone.
I had no choice.
You were a scoundrel before.
What? A scoundrel?
But things are not that bad now.
So I should be grateful?
When Royal Guard Choi arrives tomorrow...
We will be dead by then.
I got stabbed so hard
that I am fully alert.
I have a clever idea.
Is anyone there?
Anyone! Help me! Please!
What is all the ruckus?
Help, please. He is dying.
What is wrong with him?
It looks like diabetes.
He may die without treatment.
Please take him to a doctor.
Hurry!
Just wait.
Oh, he's dying!
Oh, poor man!
Who knew he would die so far from home?
Oh, how tragic!
I found it.
Why aren't you opening the door?
That's enough.
What?
He is going to die in the morning.
So this is better.
This is a thousand times better
than getting his head chopped off.
Wait!
How could you be so cold?
Even if he is going to die tomorrow,
he should receive treatment!
Wait! Don't go!
Is he gone?
He's gone.
Was that your clever idea?
The guard fell for my acting.
Had your performance been better,
it would have worked.
I have been making a living being a spy,
so how could you criticize my performance?
I could have done a better job than you
with just one foot.
Is he gone?
What was that?
I didn't do it like that!
This is how you do it!
That's enough.
Oh! If Chunsam were here,
I would be out by now.
You call that acting?
Oh, he's dying!
Unbelievable.
Are you home?
Are you inside?
Sir.
I have a favor to ask.
I am desperate.
Could you please look after this baby
for just a while?
I know I am asking too much,
but I have urgent business.
I will.
Let me have him.
What is the baby's name?
Name?
He doesn't have a name yet.
I see.
I will take good care of him.
Thank you.
You're not curious?
Why won't you ask me anything?
I wouldn't dare
ask about what you do.
If I could be of any help to you,
I will happily oblige.
But I have a favor to ask of you too.
Tell me what it is.
You must come back,
and give this baby a name.
I will do that.
Goodbye.
Who are you?
Here.
Magistrate!
Oh!
My Lord!
I have not heard from you,
so I assumed you went back to Hanyang.
I came because I heard members
of my entourage were imprisoned here.
Where is everyone?
Where are the prisoners?
It was the little sheriff.
The little sheriff?
Young Lord ordered them to be taken
to the hunting ground.
What?
This place is...
What's the matter?
You've come.
Why do you look so surprised?
This isn't your first time here.
Why did you bring us here?
Don't you already know?
So I can go hunting.
What is he talking about?
We are his prey.
What?
Killing us will not make
your despicable crimes disappear.
You are brazen.
Would you rather die after being tortured?
I have a special torture for girls.
Put that hand on her
and you will never be able to use it again
as long as you shall live.
You are quite brave
for a man facing death.
Which of you will go first?
I will go first.
No, Lord Seong.
Sure. It is better to get it over with,
so you go first.
What?
Dain.
Yes?
Run in a zigzag pattern.
You'll be able to buy time.
Even so, death would be inevitable.
Everyone dies someday.
And that day is today?
I said I didn't want to join
the royal agent's entourage,
so why did he send me here?
Dain, do not forget what I said.
What are you waiting for?
Bring her.
Go ahead, run.
Hurry!
Do you really think you can stay alive
running so slowly?
How interesting.
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Where is Lord Seong?
I sent him to Hwaeomsan.
You only brought two.
Only two?
They are fit and strong,
enough to replace a hundred...
You aren't humans here.
You guys are insects.
Insects?
This insect has a question.
There must be a way to escape from here.
What? How?
You must go and rescue the royal agent.
I cannot go without an order.
If His Majesty tells you to die, will you?
If that is what His Majesty wishes...
Chunsam, draw your sword.
Maybe I will bite the hand that feeds me.
I'll be that dog today.