Bring her.
EPISODE 4
Go ahead, run.
Hurry!
Dain, run in a zigzag pattern.
You'll be able to buy time.
Do you really think you can stay alive
running so slowly?
How interesting.
Sir!
Are you all right?
I thought I was going to die.
Would I let you die?
You're unbearable.
Stop right there!
We should go.
Yes.
Here comes the royal secret agent!
What is going on?
Do not worry! I am here!
That moron.
He is no help at all.
What happened here?
Father.
I have no choice.
Men! Apprehend them!
- Yes, sir!
What are you doing?
My horse requisition tablet!
If you resist, the royal agent dies.
Bring them.
These two are useful so lock them up.
As for this girl, kill her.
Wait!
What now?
A child of your blood is alive.
What? What are you saying?
My blood?
Sawol gave birth to Kang Jonggil's son
before she died.
Is that true?
I asked if that is true!
She knows where the boy is,
so promise you will spare her life,
and you can have the boy.
If you are lying,
I will tear your limbs apart and kill you.
Bring them all!
- Yes, sir.
Was that why you could not kill
the girl named Sawol?
I am ashamed.
A tiny seed can grow into a massive tree
to stand in your path of success!
I will take that girl
and get rid of the child.
- Father!
- Do as I say.
Do you really think of him
as your blood?
No.
You are pathetic.
You take the other two
and bring them to Hwaeomsan.
Yes, Father.
I'm sorry, sir.
How dare you impersonate
a royal agent again?
I was only trying to save you.
I almost escaped, but...
I am here again, thanks to you.
I had no idea
they killed the royal secret agent.
Who could've thought they murdered
a royal agent and buried its body?
But Lord Seong, are you really
going to hand the baby over to them?
The moment I give them the baby,
they will kill him as well as all of us.
The baby will live.
Actually, we will all live.
What do you mean?
Look around.
The prison cells are completely empty.
Don't you find that odd?
Prisoners were all sent to the labor camp.
They even framed
innocent people to send more.
Yes, that widow, she said
her husband was sent to do hard labor.
Could that be the same place
where Sawol's younger brother was sent?
They said we were useful.
They will send us to the labor camp.
But sir, what about Lady Dain?
What will happen to her?
They are looking for the baby,
so they won't kill her for now.
Dain, do as I tell you.
Lord Seong!
Stay alive and return to Hanyang.
You must stay alive too, Lord Seong.
If we meet again, I will...
Be quiet!
Lord Seong! Lord Seong!
You come with me.
Governor Kang Inchung imposed
heavy taxes on his people
and bribed people of power.
Is this true?
Your Majesty, you need to know the reason
why Governor Kang did such a thing.
The reason?
Does wickedness require a reason?
I am immensely saddened to report to you
that the man Governor Kang bribed
was the royal agent you sent recently.
What?
Chief State Councilor Kim!
Are you using unconfirmed rumors
to create chaos in the government?
There are previous cases
of royal secret agents demanding bribes
as an excuse for inspections.
The reason why local government officials'
corruption is becoming more serious
is because the royal secret agents
who inspect them
are generating corruption
in the local governments.
Your Majesty, Chief State Councilor Kim
is leaping to a ridiculous conclusion.
So what is it that you want to say?
If this royal agent's corruption
is confirmed,
replace him with the man we recommend.
Are you saying
the man you recommend is reliable?
Chief Royal Secretary Jang!
Are you trying to insult us?
Enough!
Summon those involved
in the incident and investigate.
Those who offered the bribe
and those who accepted it
will be removed from office,
and everyone who were involved
will be demanded to take responsibility.
You look terrible.
Who could have known
that the royal agent accepted bribes?
We are yet to confirm it,
so we will talk about that another time.
You should learn to read people better.
His Majesty is very concerned.
Are you concerned, Lord Kim?
What?
You're using rumors about the royal agent
to cover up the governor's crimes.
Is this a false rumor too?
I hear you have been making inquiries
about the Prince Hwiyeong incident.
What good would come from
being associated with a traitor like him?
You should watch out for yourself.
Come.
We are here.
Where is the baby?
He is in there.
Give me a moment,
and I will bring the baby out.
No. I need to see him with my own eyes.
Lower me down.
Where is the baby?
W-Well...
Attack him!
- Yes, sir.
Where is Lord Seong?
What happened?
It's a long story.
If you wish to live, talk.
I asked where Lord Seong is.
I sent him to Hwaeomsan.
Hwaeomsan?
Why?
Tell me!
I send all prisoners there.
What is the reason?
They need laborers.
I just send them because they need men.
I have nothing to do with them.
There is something I must give you
on behalf of Sawol.
Aren't you coming?
I am.
It's these two.
Just two?
What do you mean?
I told you over and over again
we need more men,
but you only brought two.
Only two?
Look at them.
They are fit and strong,
enough to replace a hundred...
Do you want him to end up in bed
before he goes to work?
Let them in!
- Yes, sir.
He is a spirited one.
Breaking him won't be easy.
Move!
Move.
Move along! Move!
Sir, are you hurt?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Get up.
Now!
I'm sorry.
Sir, where are we?
Everyone looks lifeless,
as if they are about to die.
Everything was the royal agent's idea?
Yes, he told me to tell Kang Inchung
that I would give him the baby
and bring them to you instead.
He said then I could live.
So was he taken away
after he sent you to me?
Yes.
Hmm...
We will return to Hanyang.
We must go to Hwaeomsan.
We must save Lord Seong first.
We must report this to His Majesty first.
What if something bad happens
to Lord Seong?
He is not as weak as you think.
It will become dark soon
so let us find lodging.
Listen to what I say carefully.
No one here cares about what you did
in the outside world.
In here, you are not humans
but bulls, pigs,
chickens, and insects.
Insects?
Understand?
Just remember three things.
First, do as you are told.
Two...
This insect has a question.
Where are we?
Why did you bring us here?
What should we do?
Chunsam.
Second, talk too much
and you will be beaten.
Third, try to escape and you will die.
You are here to pay for the crimes
you have committed.
Keep your mouth shut
and do what we tell you to do.
Understand?
Yes!
It's gold! It's gold!
Everyone, stop working!
I heard about this
when I was working in the palace.
The rich local noblemen mine gold
and keep it for themselves
without reporting it to the government.
It is called jamchae.
Jamchae?
The bribe you received from the sheriff
must be from here.
This was all about gold.
Special Advisor Park was murdered,
trying to report this.
This place...
Is hell that was created by the greed
of corrupt men.
Are you writing a letter
to Chief Royal Secretary?
Yes.
Tell me what the Royal Agent
has been doing.
At first, I thought the royal agent
was a very unusual and peculiar man.
Happy?
But as time passed by,
he grew even stranger.
Stupid.
He treats his servant like a friend
and tries to help the weak despite danger.
Why did I bring that imbecile?
He admits faults.
Separating public and private businesses
is a virtue every royal agent
must possess.
A man who takes responsibility
for himself.
I have never met a nobleman like him.
You must like him very much.
Come. Hurry!
Hurry!
Sir, what do we do now?
Now that I know everything, I must leave.
How?
There must be a way to escape from here.
Don't try anything stupid.
When one tries to escape,
everyone starves for three days.
There were those who tried to escape,
but they all failed.
They all returned as paraplegics
and eventually died.
It is impossible
to escape from here by yourself.
You are correct.
No one can escape by himself.
That is why I need everyone's help.
Give up making plans to escape,
and get some sleep.
Do you want to work here
until the day you die?
I will go.
I will escape from here
and return with men.
Oh, as if you are some royal secret agent.
Hey!
Do you know who this man is?
Who is he?
He's...
He's a...
A very good man.
As if he's Buddha.
That's enough.
Sir! Something terrible happened.
What is it?
Father, are you all right?
An assassin was waiting for me
at the place that girl took me.
An assassin?
Where did they go?
They must have gone to Hwaeomsan.
Go and bring all the newborns in town.
Newborns?
Yes! Your son!
Do not rest until you arrive.
Yes, sir.
Give me some more.
Oh, look at this.
This is barely enough
to keep me breathing.
They call this a meal?
At least it's good. Try it.
Where are you going?
We are out of time.
You must go and rescue Lord Seong
before it's too late.
I sent words
so the order will arrive soon.
That will take too long.
We are out of time.
I cannot go without an order.
Then you stay here.
I will go alone.
How can a woman like you
go there by yourself?
Then come with me.
I must wait for His Majesty's order.
Of course.
If His Majesty orders you to die,
will you?
If that is what His Majesty wishes...
Oh, forget it!
Just go.
I am going there by myself.
The royal agent must have had a hard time.
Move!
Hurry up!
Are you all right?
Go and take a break.
Who gave you permission?
It's you again.
He could die.
I am the master here.
Get up.
Careful.
If I can't use you, there is no reason
for you to stay alive.
If you are the master, act like one.
How much longer
will you harass the workers?
I should cut off your tongue first.
Watch and see what happens
when you bite the hand that feeds you!
Someone told me that I'm like a scoundrel.
Maybe I will bite the hand that feeds me.
I'll be that dog today.
You.
No!
Sir, sir.
Won't you please forgive him?
What?
He may appear perfectly normal,
but he deserves your pity.
He fell from a jujube tree
when he was young and hurt his head,
so he doesn't know what he's saying.
As his master,
please show him mercy and...
Stop!
You're back, M'lord.
What is going on?
It's nothing.
A few workers caused a disturbance,
and I was sorting it out.
Your eyes are still alive,
so you must be a recent addition.
Why did you cause a disturbance?
The workload for the weak is too severe.
If you committed a crime,
you must pay for it.
Some have been brought here wrongly.
Is that so?
Fine.
If there is anyone here
who was brought wrongly,
come out right now.
I will send you home.
I was...
Did you see that?
There is none.
Thanks to your ill-advised bravery,
everyone will starve.
If you cause another disturbance,
you will lose your head.
What are you waiting for?
Get to work!
Sir, could you please
try not to stand out?
What good could come
from standing up to them?
I am a royal agent,
so how could I watch people suffer?
I am someone who is suffering too!
That was close.
Why didn't anyone come out?
If anyone did,
they would've lost their lives.
You will soon learn.
Who is that man?
I don't know.
Some say he is the owner of this place,
and some say he was sent here
by someone high up.
No one knows for sure.
But he is someone of power.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
M'lord.
How ridiculous must they think of you
to act out like that?
I am sorry.
Bring me the goods.
Yes, M'lord.
The quantity is especially small.
There was an epidemic,
killing a lot of men.
If you are short of men,
increase the workload!
Pardon me?
Yes, I will do that.
I will take this today,
but next time,
make sure you twice the amount ready.
Yes, M'lord.
May I ask you something?
Is this the road to Hwaeomsan?
Yes, it is.
I heard there are many men working there.
Do you know what they are doing?
I don't.
Why do you want to go there?
Someone I know has been taken there.
You better not go there.
I have seen many men go in,
but I am yet to see anyone come out.
Hurry up!
Oh? We are missing one.
Someone is missing.
What?
Search everywhere!
- Yes, sir.
The old man Kim is missing.
Could he have?
Listen carefully.
If one of you escapes,
one from the rest will be killed,
and if two of you escape,
two will be killed.
Please spare me!
Watch carefully.
No, no.
M'lord!
What? He died?
Over here.
Toss him outside.
- Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Out of my way!
Step aside!
I didn't expect this...
I would like to ask you one question.
What is it?
Do you still want to escape from here?
What if I do?
I have an older sister.
She was pregnant,
and she must have given birth by now.
She said she would name the baby
Yunsu if it's a boy
and Yunhui if it's a girl.
I want to meet the baby in person.
Is you older sister Sawol?
Yes. Do you know my sister?
Sawol passed away.
What?
What do you mean?
She was killed by the sheriff's son.
Sawol gave birth before she died.
Did the baby survive?
Where is it?
I left the baby with someone I can trust,
so you don't need to worry.
You must leave this place alive
for the sake of that baby.
Sir.
He is dead.
What is that place?
It is heavily guarded,
so they must be hiding something.
What could they be hiding
so deep in the mountain?
Whatever it is, it must be something
dangerous enough to cost people's lives.
We must figure out a way
to get in there.
There is a proper process for everything.
His Majesty must hear...
Dain,
how do you plan on getting inside
without any decent plan?
I am going to take a look around first.
They change shifts
at six a.m. and six p.m.
Those are the only times
we can hide from them.
But the term is too short
for you to be able to reach the gate.
Has anyone tried to escape before?
There were a few.
So? What happened?
Well...
Don't come! Don't come!
Ouch! That's hurts.
Sir, we wouldn't make it
because of the guards.
What are you up to?
Oh, my heart.
I am finished.
I'm all done.
Hurry up and move.
Yes, sir.
Hurry up and get up!
If you have finished eating, get up.
I will use them.
What is that?
It is a numbing drug.
Lord Choi,
you must speak like a slave.
Like a slave?
Yes.
"What is that?"
Have you ever heard of a slave
speak like that?
Must we do this?
Lord Choi,
this look suits you much better.
Why are you taking my baby?
It is just an infant!
Out of my way!
Sir, no!
My baby! My baby!
We are going to Hwaeomsan.
Stop! Stop!
What is this?
This must be the place.
Who are you?
Reveal who you are.
Reveal who I am?
Can't you tell?
I am from the tavern in town.
I heard you need supplies here,
so I came to do business.
Supplies?
Dolsoe, show them.
Dolsoe.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, I didn't just bring these
for you to only look at.
Here.
But...
We shouldn't drink on the job.
Oh, don't be silly.
Just try it.
It will give you energy,
so it's basically medicine.
And you are not monks,
so why live like one
in such a beautiful place?
Nice.
Come with me.
You may go inside.
What?
You will be paid.
Oh, thank you.
No slave is allowed inside.
Oh, how handsome you all are!
I should have come sooner.
Have you no fear?
Why did you come here?
I heard this place is full of men,
but since you are deep in the mountain,
you are always in need of wine and meat.
That is correct.
But haven't you heard this?
Like what?
People my come in,
but they never leave.
Dain!
For a slave, you sure are brave.
If you don't want to see this girl die,
you better not put up a fight.
Drop the sword!
Oh, please.
Try harder.
Dain.
Yes?
Was this a part of your plan?
The thing about plans
is that they often go south.
Why did you drop your sword?
The letter must have reached
Hanyang by now.
Your Majesty...
Chief Royal Secretary Jang,
where are you going in such a hurry?
I was on my way to see His Majesty.
I heard a messenger arrived
at the Royal Secretariat.
Is that why?
You must have your hands full
with the State Council business,
but now you want to look
into the Royal Secretariat?
Why? Is it a secret?
Of course not.
But I should report to His Majesty first,
don't you agree?
Something must have happened
to the royal agent.
Is this true?
Royal Secret Agent Park Cheolgyu
was murdered,
and the royal agent who was investigating
has been taken to a labor camp?
Murdering a royal agent is an act
of defiance against the throne.
Hurry and send a seonjeonkwan
to apprehend the traitor Kang Inchung
and his son Kang Jonggil!
How dare you speak
to your master that way?
I learned it from you!
I am your master! What did you say?
You!
Stop it right now!
You fools asking for a beating or what?
My life is miserable
because I have a bad master!
I treated you with respect and...
How dare they!
Unlock the door.
You still think you are a nobleman?
What?
Show some respect!
I could die any moment,
so why should I?
How dare you!
Good job.
You must return before dawn.
Our lives depend on you.
I promise to return.
Chunsam, come.
Yes, Igyeom, let's go.
I apologize.
Let us go, sir.
There really is a girl here.
Who are you?
Yes, if you don't put up a fight,
it's no fun.
How dare you!
You bastard! Stop it!
Dain, Dain!
Dain, pull yourself together.
Lord Choi!
Dain! Dain!
Dain, what happened?
I don't know.
That was really close.
The numbing drug has worked.
We must find Lord Seong. We must hurry.
Yes.
Just how much did they drink?
Sir, we are here.
If we get through that gate,
we can get out.
Let's go.
Yes.
Kang Jonggil?
Where are the guards?
What a mess.
A courtesan named Honglang
is hiding here somewhere.
Search everywhere and find her.
Honglang?
Is he talking about Dain?
You come with me.
Yes, sir.
What is this?
Intruders!
Hey, you!
Have you seen a girl here?
- No.
- Yes.
What?
- No.
- Yes.
Yes, I saw one.
Where? Where did you see her?
- Over there.
Where?
Is she really here?
Sir.
Tell me!
Sir!
What?
It's you again.
What are you waiting for?
Whoever brings me his head
will be awarded with gold.
Sir.
Chunsam, draw your sword.
What?
Sure.
What are you waiting for?
Attack them!
Lord Seong?
Lord Igyeom!
Who's there?
Do you know a man named Seong Igyeom?
We are here to find him.
Do not be alarmed.
We are his entourage.
Entourage?
Did the man named
Seong Igyeom send you?
Yes.
But where is he?
He left a little earlier,
saying he will bring men.
So, who is he anyway?
Sir!
Isn't this when you say,
"Here come the royal secret agent," no?
I would love to hear it.
Shout it out loud.
Here comes the royal secret agent!
- Here comes the royal secret agent!
Yes, I am a royal secret agent.
Look at me.
Will a royal agent kill a man?
Are you sure you are a man?
What's going on?
Out of my way!
You!
You filthy insects...
Get them!
Fight!
Go!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Run!
Dain!
No!
Sir!
Dain!
Come!
Darn it.
Give up.
You cannot escape.
Let her go.
Fine. I will let her go.
Dain!
Here.
Do not let go.
Lord Seong, it's hopeless.
Let go of me.
Lord Seong!
No!
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Why are you crying?
I once asked Dain about you.
She said you treat
your subordinates as friends
and protect the weak.
Dain is good at reading people.
She must be.
She saw something I never did.
He has the trust of the king,
so he will become our enemy in the future.
Do you know the easiest way
of defeating your enemy?
Work for me.
Miok, are you out there?
Marriage?
That's great.
You got promoted,
and now you're getting married.
I offer my congratulations.