EPISODE 13
So, this was what you were searching for.
Do you know how much humiliation
I suffered because of you?
I will kill you very slowly
and very painfully,
until you beg me to end your life.
Lord Seong.
Sir, are you all right?
I am fine.
You pest!
Stop. He is an important witness.
Witness? What do you mean?
Is he...?
He is the one who murdered your father.
Sir, I found this in his hand.
Take it.
This is what you were searching for.
Prince Hwiyeong was not a traitor.
Lord Seong.
Sir, you must hold on.
I will fetch a doctor.
My entire body feels weak.
I am sleepy.
You cannot fall asleep, sir!
Chunsam.
I would like to rest.
Lord Seong, Lord Seong!
Sir! Sir!
- Wake up, Lord Seong.
- Sir!
No! No!
Chunsam, hurry and go fetch a doctor.
I will.
No! No!
Lord Seong, Lord Seong.
Lord Seong!
No, no, no!
Out of my way! Out of my way!
Chunsam.
L-Lord Ibeom.
This way.
Igyeom!
Lord Seong, Lord Seong.
Is this the man
who harmed the royal agent?
Yes.
Take him.
Yes, sir.
We must move him.
Come with me.
Doctor, Doctor!
Boss!
Doctor, he needs help.
He was hit by an arrow
and lost much blood.
Get in, bastard.
That is the man!
That is the man who attacked us!
You!
Stop it!
He is an important witness.
I want to end his life with my own hands,
but to clear the royal agent's name
and find the man behind everything,
we need him.
He will receive just punishment,
so please let us take him.
I beg of you.
I am finished. He should get rest
for now and not strain himself.
Thank you.
I should go.
We owe you.
Thank you for helping.
Do not mention it.
Please look after my brother.
Wait.
Lord Igyeom always thinks of you
and worries for you.
When he wakes up, please tell him
he should free himself from the burden.
Your Majesty, please give us your order.
Must the Chief Royal Secretary...
Be executed?
Feigning King's command
and creating disturbance in the government
with the daughter of a traitor,
no other crime is as grave as these.
Please give us your order.
I will consider it for the next few days.
You may leave.
Your Majesty, execute
the Chief Royal Secretary,
and restore order in the government.
Stop!
Do I not even have the freedom to decide
on a matter such as this?
A man's life depends on my decision.
Does it not deserve more caution?
As you wish, Your Majesty.
I brought you good news.
His Majesty has allowed you
a few more days to live.
Are you eternally grateful?
Although you are imprisoned,
is it not better to be alive than dead?
Lord Kim,
do you fear death that much?
What?
Whichever crime you frame me to kill me,
I am without one bit of shame,
so I will face it with my head held high.
But would you be able to do the same?
I doubt it.
Lord Seong.
Are you awake?
What happened?
You lost consciousness,
so your younger brother brought you here.
Ibeom?
Yes.
Please lie back down.
You must rest.
No, we have no time to waste.
Get ready. Let us return to Hanyang.
Sir! Sir!
Sir!
You are hurting me. Stop.
What happened to your handsome face?
You are ugly.
That is enough.
I can kill you this instant.
Kill me.
Will you not have any regrets?
I will not.
You were born a man but lived as a beast,
but you still have no regrets.
Confess all of your crimes
before His Majesty.
And I will give you
the chance to live as a man.
I do not know what living as a man is,
but you can do it, to live as a man.
I cannot believe my ears,
you rude bastard.
Stop.
We have a long journey,
so we must hurry.
Get ready.
Yes, sir.
Do you still wish to start a revolution?
The royal agent was here,
so the governor will pay for his crimes.
That remains to be seen.
Boss!
There is a strange rumor.
What strange rumor?
They say Governor Kim Myeongse is dead.
What happened?
There are no details,
but everyone in the provincial office
has been ordered to remain silent
to prevent disorder.
Boss, now that he is dead,
should we not hold a feast?
Stop the foolish nonsense.
Whoever it is, a new governor will arrive.
I am concerned what kind of man he is.
Sir, drink some water.
You go ahead.
Lord Seong.
Get him some water.
What?
Sir, he tried to kill you,
so why...
Look at him drink.
Is your thirst gone?
There are many in this world
who suffer from burning thirst.
I am the man
who brings them a sip of water,
and you are the man
who steals that water.
Who do you think is living as a man?
Let us go.
- Yes, Sir.
- Yes.
Your Majesty, have you decided?
Do as you wish.
Your Majesty, I am happy to hear that.
Bring the prisoner!
Prisoner, hear this.
According to the King's command,
your limbs will be severed,
and they will be scattered
around the country.
How do you feel?
Can you still face death
with your head held high?
Remember my death.
Your death will not differ much from mine.
Let me see if you can still say the same
after your head has been cut off.
Headsman, chop his head off this instant!
Yes, my lord!
Here comes the royal secret agent!
Royal secret agent?
But h-he was...
What happened?
Did you not say he was dead?
Are you all right?
It is I, Dain.
Dain,
is my head still attached?
Yes, it is.
Good, good.
What happened?
Father.
Lord Kim Manhui,
you look as if you have seen a ghost.
How dare he...
That's...
Honglang?
You!
How dare you appear here
as a royal agent?
It is the royal agent's duty to go
where there are corrupt officials.
I must follow the King's command
and appear in the palace,
If there are corrupt officials
in the palace.
Corrupt officials?
What kind of trickery are these followers
of traitors using?
Guards! Apprehend them!
- Yes, sir!
His Majesty, the King!
Special Commander Kim Manhui,
lift your head.
Royal Secret Agent Seong whom you reported
to have taken his own life returned alive.
Report how this happened.
Your Majesty, I...
In that case, Royal Agent Seong Igyeom,
you speak.
I have received the suicide note
he claimed you wrote.
Your Majesty,
it was all Lord Kim Manhui's ruse.
Lord Kim Manhui
framed me and attempted to kill me
while I was being transported.
And he ordered the murder of Kim Myeongse,
the governor of Jeolla-do.
This is slander, Your Majesty.
Look at the person
who accompanied the royal agent.
That person is not a man but a girl.
That girl is the one who had
the traitor Prince Hwiyeong's okro,
Your Majesty.
Prince Hwiyeong was not a traitor.
How dare a prostitute interfere?
Are you the girl named Hong Dain?
Your Majesty, my name is
Lee Yeongsin.
I am Prince Hwiyeong's daughter.
How dare you lie?
Her words are true.
Your Majesty, I am ashamed to say
that I took her in
after Prince Hwiyeong died.
Are you truly Prince Hwiyeong's daughter?
I am, Your Majesty.
This is the secret letter
the late king presented to my father.
"Prince Hwiyeong Lee Han,
you are to raise and train an army
to stop the invasion from foreign vessel
and the looting of robbers."
Is this not the late king's royal seal?
Yes, Your Majesty.
After my father returned
to his hometown of Okgu,
he witnessed people suffering
from invasions by overseas vessels
and looting of robbers,
and he could not remain a bystander.
So in order to protect them,
he received permission to train an army
from the late king.
How could this be?
You said Prince Hwiyeong was advancing
to Hanyang with his army!
I was only concerned of your safety,
Your Majesty.
Stop lying.
You were afraid of Prince Hwiyeong
whose influence was growing.
And you had him killed
and reported that he took his own life.
Just as you did with me.
What is it?
You have walked a long way,
so you should rest a while.
I am fine. Let us go.
I must speak to you about something.
You men go ahead without us.
Yes, sir.
What is it?
Is this one of Kim Byeonggeun's ploys?
I had nothing to do with this.
Who are you?
It will be over soon.
You did not say
you were planning on killing him!
Go and report that he took his own life
because he was afraid of his plans
for treason being discovered.
I am not responsible for this death.
Who deceived him and brought him here?
Toss him over the cliff.
- Yes, sir.
You are an accomplice.
So take what happened today to your grave.
You will be rewarded handsomely.
Is this true?
Your Majesty, it is all a lie!
How dare you attempt to
frame me with a single letter?
I have a witness
who can attest to all this.
Chunsam, bring him in!
The witness is here.
Who is he?
There is a man
who knows him better than I do.
Explain to His Majesty who this man is.
What do you mean? I do not know him.
Did you not order this man to kill me?
You!
You are a royal secret agent,
but everything you say is a lie.
I have other witnesses.
Summon Assistant Royal Guard Choi.
How can we summon a man who is missing?
Missing?
What do you mean?
Did you also kill him?
I did not.
Special Commander Kim, answer.
How did you know of the disappearance
of Assistant Royal Guard Choi?
What did you do with him?
I do not know.
Special Commander Kim ordered this man
to kill Royal Agent Park Cheolgyu,
Kang Inchung and his son Kang Jonggil,
Governor Kim Myeongse
and Prince Hwiyeong Lee Han.
Witness, speak.
Is that all true?
Yes.
Your Majesty, these treacherous officials
framed the loyal Prince Hwiyeong
and used it to gain government posts
and harmed your subjects and country
with illegal deeds and filthy greed
for many years,
so please punish them severely!
Following my family's lineage, I have been
establishing the royal family's authority,
so how dare you!
Enough!
Chief of Royal Investigation Bureau,
listen.
Apprehend Kim Byeongguen
and Kim Manhui this instant!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
how could you believe his words?
- Your Majesty.
- You impertinent bastard!
You have ruined me! You have!
Watch your words.
I am Joseon's royal secret agent.
And you have committed high treason.
Your Majesty, it is not true!
It is all a lie!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, Your Majesty!
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN
Good work.
You have made it possible for me
to renew the government.
Your Majesty, I only fulfilled my duty
as your royal secret agent.
However, I do have one wish.
Tell me what it is.
Due to Governor Kim Myeongse's tyranny,
the people of Jeonju lived in starvation.
Please order
the provincial storehouse to be opened
and the food distributed
to the hungry people.
I will do that.
Did you say you are Lee Yeongsin?
Yes, Your Majesty.
I owe you and your father a great debt.
Thank you for not giving up.
Your Majesty.
Prince Hwiyeong is no longer a traitor.
And your position as a member
of the royal family will be restored.
I cannot compensate for the years lost,
but I do hope
this will provide some consolation.
I am eternally grateful, Your Majesty.
Lord Seong!
Lord Seong.
Do not call me Lord Seong any longer.
What? Why?
You are a member of the royal family.
It may feel awkward at first,
but you must behave
according to your position.
You must call her Lady Yeongsin, no?
What?
I am not wrong, am I?
Do you now agree with me, Lady Yeongsin?
Lord Seong, I am not interested
in being a member of the royal family.
No one in this world is born
into the position they desire.
We must all live
according to the fate we were given.
Use your position
for the people suffering in poverty.
That is my final request to you.
Yes, I will remember that.
Sir, that was great of you.
I am great.
I did not become a slave
because I wanted to.
What is the meaning of this?
Out of my way!
It is His Majesty's command to search
the prisoner Kim Byeonggeun's home!
Over there!
Prisoners, accept the King's command.
Prisoner Kim Byeonggeun framed
Prince Hwiyeong Lee Han
of treason and falsely accused him
and illegally mined gold and traded it
for personal gain.
For these crimes, he is sentenced
to exile in Gimje.
As Minister of Personnel,
prisoner Jo Pilha
accepted bribes for personnel management,
accepted gold from Kim Byeonggeun,
and turned a blind eye to his crimes.
For these crimes, he is sentenced
to exile in Bukcheong.
What?
Prisoner Kim Manhui ordered
the murders of Prince Hwiyeong
and Royal Agent Park Cheolgyu
and he also conspired
to murder Royal Agent Seong Igyeom
who uncovered his crimes.
These crimes are grave,
so he is sentenced to beheading.
- Father.
- Take the prisoner Kim Manhui.
Beheading?
Investigator, free me!
I must speak to His Majesty!
How dare you lay your hands on his body?
Let go of him!
Let go!
Manhui! Manhui! Manhui!
Father!
- Manhui! Manhui!
- Father!
Manhui!
Father!
- Manhui!
- Let go of me!
Manhui! Manhui!
What happened to Manhui?
Listen carefully!
There will come a day when you regret
not killing me!
I am already regretting it.
Thank His Majesty.
Had you not been royal to the late king
and teacher to His Majesty,
you could not have avoided beheading.
Go!
Yes, sir.
Come!
Here, here, one person at a time.
Take your time.
- You must be hungry.
- Come here and get some rice.
Here, here, take your time.
One person at a time.
Igyeom kept his word.
What?
Sir, is this truly our house?
Being a royal agent was worth it.
You got promoted to section chief
of the Ministry of Personnel
and received a mansion of a house!
Thank His Majesty.
Your Majesty, I am eternally grateful.
- Welcome, my lord.
What?
My well-being is in your hands.
- Yes, my lord.
Of all the service
a woman provides for her husband,
not being jealous is the best conduct,
so do not be dissatisfied
even if he has a hundred concubines,
do not be angry
no matter how much he loves his concubine
and respect him even more.
Please sit straight.
Yes.
ADMONISHMENTS FOR WOMEN
When will you ever finish
studying "Admonishments for Women"?
Court Lady Kim,
why must I study this book?
You are a member of the royal family,
so you must conduct yourself
according to your class and dignity...
Lady Yeongsin!
Oh, yes.
The mission must have been draining.
Chief State Councilor Jang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
It concerns me that Yeongsin
is living by her lonely self.
Yes!
How about finding the perfect spouse
for Yeongsin?
I beg your pardon?
Find a groom for Yeongsin.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Lord Jang, this is the section chief
of the Ministry of Personnel.
Yes, come in.
Have you summoned me?
Sit.
Take a look at these men.
What do you think?
Are you appointing new officials?
Kang Taewon is an expert on the Odes
and the Histories and writes beautifully.
He is careful, meticulous,
and never makes mistakes.
Jeon Yeonggyun is a martial arts expert
and is high-spirited.
He was a fearless boy who led the hunt
for the tiger that threatened his village.
Oh, did he?
What is it?
Appoint this man.
Kim Jeongguk needs no description.
On top of possessing the strengths
of the two previous men,
he is humble
and is respected by his peers.
Is he?
So this man would be
a perfect groom for Yeongsin.
Yes, he is.
What?
What did you just say?
His Majesty asked me to find
Yeongsin a spouse.
A spouse?
Yes.
So I will recommend this man to...
You must let me finish.
He is a mean drunk and enjoys gambling,
and most of all,
his countenance is unpleasant.
You said earlier
that he needs no description.
By any chance, are you...
Yes?
Feeling disappointed, nervous,
and concerned?
Do not worry.
I will find her a good man.
Oh, by any chance, are you...
Yes?
How do you feel about Yeongsin?
I mean Dain.
I do not understand.
As your spouse, I mean.
What?
Never mind.
I meant nothing by it.
How could you consider her a woman?
Am I wrong?
Y-You are right.
That is nonsense.
How silly of me.
Let me see, his countenance...
Let us take a look.
Welcome.
Oh, you are a handsome couple.
Are you shopping for your wedding?
No.
Yes, please find something
for my bride.
Oh, her hair ribbon is worn.
How about this one?
Lord Ibeom, I am fine. Let us go.
Make way!
Here comes the governor!
Lord Ibeom, that man...
Sh.
Step aside!
Here comes the governor!
Step back!
This is a terrible twist of fate.
Go home.
I need to see some people.
I heard the former governor suffered
many headaches because of robbers.
Is that true?
Yes, robbers are wreaking havoc
in the village.
Was it those men who stole
the governor's fortune?
Yes, it was.
What were you doing?
I am ashamed.
Why is no one reporting these robbers?
They give what they stole to people.
Because of that,
no one speaks about them.
Whoever they are,
how gutsy of them.
It will be fun to capture them.
Do you not agree?
Yes, I do agree.
They are all cooperating with the robbers,
are they not?
Now that I have come here,
I will make all efforts toward
correcting the past evils
and reforming customs of the people.
Do you understand?
- Yes, my lord.
Did you know the new governor
has been appointed?
I have made some inquiries
about him.
When he was the magistrate of Cheongju,
he forced his people to hard labor
to build a reservoir.
That bastard never paid them.
He charged taxes on the reservoir water
and collected money from the people.
What is the matter?
I worked for him.
So you must know him well.
What kind of man is he?
He is a cruel man
who tortures people
who committed petty crimes to death
and took advantage
of women of lower status.
There is not an ounce of humanity in him.
I will keep an eye
on the provincial office.
He must be plotting something.
Why are you out here?
Did you have dinner?
I prepared dinner for you
so go inside and eat.
I will go inside and start eating.
Lord Ibeom.
Lord Ibeom, what do we do now?
I never thought I would see him again.
Do not worry.
He does not know we are here.
That is...
My arm is about to ache. Take it.
Thank you.
It is beautiful.
Let us go inside. I am hungry.
Yes.
Step back!
Here comes the governor!
What is he doing?
Apprehend him.
- Yes, sir.
You!
Did you not hear the announcement
of the governor's march?
He seems to be a mute.
A mute or not, he violated the custom.
Detain him.
- Yes, Lord Byeon.
- Yes.
Take him away.
What was that?
That boy!
Apprehend him!
Was it you?
Let go of my father.
Is that man your father?
He may be young,
but his crime cannot disappear.
You filth.
Yes, yes, since you are his father,
you should be punished instead.
Get him.
- Yes, my lord.
Father! Father!
You!
Father! Father! Father!
That is enough!
You are Seong Ibeom!
Lord Ibeom!
She is...
Apprehend them all!
What are you waiting for?
Run! Run!
After them!
- Yes, sir!
Are you all right?
This is very interesting.
I am very glad I came here.
The rat was hiding here.
Yes, so I was up against three men.
I punched one and the next,
pulled my shoulder back,
and punched the third one to the ground.
I grabbed one by his collar
and asked,
"Where is the royal agent?"
Where was he?
He was apprehended by that evil sheriff.
Oh no.
What happened next?
Who am I?
I can run like the wind.
I ran and ran as fast I could
and chased after them.
I caught up with them, and guess what?
He was holding the royal agent hostage.
Oh no.
Then he pushed the royal agent
down the cliff.
Oh, how terrible.
But who am I?
I ran like the wind and grabbed his arm.
Why? Wait.
I am about to get to the main part.
I was holding on to this arm
with dear life, shouting,
"Sir, you cannot die!
I cannot replace you!"
My shoulder was about to be dislocated,
and I pulled up him, shouting,
"Sir, you cannot die!"
And at that moment,
a sword appeared next to my neck.
"What is this?"
And I swung around, and,
oh, it's Lord Igyeom.
Oh, sir.
Go, go!
Hurry up
and go home.
Go, go.
Hello, sir.
Come with me.
What?
Where are we going?
To Dain,
I mean, we are going to Lady Yeongsin.
Why?
I have a message to deliver.
Come.
It was getting exciting.
Lady Yeongsin, if we get caught,
the court lady will kill me.
Jeomsun, everyone dies.
What?
I will come back soon,
so you stay here under the blanket.
I have told everyone
that I don't want to see anyone today.
My lady, my lady.
Oh, wait.
Do not get caught.
Or you and I are both dead.
What?
Yes, my lady.
Sir, it is that house.
Yes.
Lady Yeongsin, you have a guest.
What do I do?
She says to not let anyone inside!
He said his name is Seong Igyeom.
Whoever he may be, Seong Igyeom or not,
she does not wish to see him!
What's taking so long?
Did you say your name is Seong Igyeom?
I am Seong Igyeom.
What did Lady Yeongsin say?
Whoever he may be, Seong Igyeom or not,
I do not wish to see him!
That is what she said.
What? That cannot be true.
Please excuse me.
Tell her I will....
Wait here.
Sir, she must be no longer
interested in you.
You should have taken better care of her
during your secret mission!
What is this?
That is enough.
She knows we are here,
so she will come out soon.
Let us wait.
I knew this would happen.
I knew she will come out soon.
Lord Seong! Chunsam!
Is no one home?
Who are you?
I am here to see the master of this house.
Oh, the men who used to live here?
They have already left.
Left? Where did they go?
I would not know.
What is this about?
It is nothing.
How could he not tell me?
After all I have done for him.
Yes, I should forget him.
Men can be so ungrateful.
How could he not tell me?
Why is it so dark?
Sir, how much longer will you wait?
Fine. Let us go.
Come.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Sir, you must forget.
Forget what?
I mean Lady Yeongsin.
It is not like that.
Oh, I know you are fond her.
Am I wrong?
How could you be so bold?
I am not fond of her!
You are not fond of her! You are not.
You love her, you do.
How dare you!
When I get my hands on you...
I hear you are now a section chief
of the Ministry of Personnel.
Congratulations to you.
But what brings you here?
I had business to do near here.
Where have you been?
There was someone I wished to see,
so I went to see him.
You must have made up your mind.
So, who is he?
He has a warm heart.
He is courageous
and has a strong sense of responsibility.
He can be cold sometimes,
but he always puts others before him.
It was a feeling I had never felt before
from another person.
Was there such man among them?
Is it Kang Taewon?
No.
Jeon Yeonggyun?
Oh, is it Kim Jeongguk?
I said no!
Regardless, do not be mistaken.
All men hide a sly fox inside them.
No one knows
when that sly fox may come out,
so you best be cautious.
Do you know whom I was describing?
I do not care. Good luck with you.
It is you!
Me?
Yes, you.
The man you were describing was me?
That is correct.
Yes, I am like that.
You are an excellent judge of character.
By the way, do you have one too?
What?
What do you mean?
A sly fox.
You said all men hide it inside them.
And you are a man.
Oh, that?
I do have it.
So would you be a fox hunter in my heart?
Fox hunter?
Is there something else I can be?
I am sincere.
Then, how about this?
We still have an unfinished business
that is quite important.
I wanted to tell you before completing
the mission, but there was no chance.
Have you forgotten already?
The bet you and I made.
You promised to do what I ask.
Oh, the bet we made at the gambling house?
Yes, tell me what you want.
What I want...
Is for us to remain together
even after the mission.
Is it too much to ask?
Why did you wait to tell me that?
That was my intention from the start.
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Have you not heard anything
from your brother?
I am hoping no news is good news.
Was he there as well?
They were together.
Apprehend them,
even if you have to kill them.
Deliver this message.
All the girls will be beheaded.
There is only one thing to do.
What is it?
"He is tyrannizing under the pretext
of capturing robbers."
I will assassinate the governor.
The man in the office is changing,
but the tyranny is getting worse.
We must change the world
in order to survive.
You want to go on another secret mission?
Will you not regret it?
I'll probably regret it.
I have learned
there are paths one must take
despite knowing there will be regrets.