I am Hong Dain...
The scoundrel?
What? Scoundrel?
Wait, you're...
Honglang?
You're the royal secret agent?
You... You!
There she is. Get her!
Who are they?
Run!
EPISODE 2
Sir, why are we running?
I don't know!
This way, this way!
Who are they?
Well...
By the way, are you really
the royal secret agent?
Here, look. Satisfied?
I was expecting someone grand
but I guess not.
What?
Has the Chief Royal Secretary really send
a courtesan to accompany me?
A courtesan? I'm a female police.
A female police?
Not a hostess?
A hostess?
Are you trying to cross the line?
Then explain to me
why you are being chased in daylight.
They must have figured out what I am.
What did you do?
My job was to keep an eye
on the Chief State Councilor.
You could be executed for that!
We lost her.
Let us return to the courtesan house.
I must apprehend the Head Courtesan.
- Yes, sir.
Let me properly introduce myself to you.
I am Hong Dain, here to join
your entourage.
It was the Chief Royal Secretary's order.
You will need a woman to carry out
your secret mission,
so I am sending a female police.
Have her infiltrate the courtesan house
and find the girl the agent wanted to see.
She's in possession of key evidence.
So...
He sent you?
That is correct.
Completing the mission aside,
I am unsure of a woman being able
to survive the journey to our destination.
Let me tell you in advance.
If you fall behind
or hinder the progress of my journey,
I will leave you behind.
And on top of that, from now on,
I will be giving orders.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir. I will not forget.
After all we have done,
she is still not talking.
I don't think she knows anything.
Wake her.
Please don't kill me.
Please let me go, my lord.
Let me ask you one last time.
Who put you up to this?
What do you mean?
Please let me go.
Please let me go, my lord.
Father.
Make sure this does not leak
and get rid of any evidence.
Yes, Father.
What's that?
What is that over there?
Sir!
This is so nice and cool.
Come and join me.
You are acting like a fool.
A gentleman must always mind his manners.
Let us go before the sun goes down.
We should look for a place
to spend the night around here.
Sir, here's a deserted house.
It looks haunted.
Take the master bedroom.
I will take the small one.
I said I will give the orders!
You take the small room.
We will take the master bedroom.
That's what she just said.
Anyway, goodnight.
Goodnight, Lady Dain.
Ma'am... Ma'am...
Unbelievable.
Oh!
What do I do?
What is he doing?
Oh!
Oh, how refreshing!
Oh, whatever. I should leave.
Wait, you... You!
Sir.
I will leave first
so please close your eyes.
S-Sure.
Close them tightly.
If you open them, I will kill you.
Are you all right?
You couldn't have been born
a female police.
How did you become one?
It was not my choice.
Then?
The Chief Royal Secretary
made me into a female police.
How do you know him in the first place?
He took me in.
And saved my life.
Is there a story behind that?
Father!
I will return soon.
Give me a few days.
Mother...
It has been a long time,
so I don't remember very well.
Our clothes are dry so let us go back now.
He must have sent you
because he trusts you,
but I don't know anything about you.
Is even Hong Dain your real name?
Is that important?
I need to know who you are
to be able to trust you.
Just because you know someone
doesn't mean you can trust them.
By the looks of how hesitant you are,
I guess you have something to hide.
That night when you were
at the courtesan house,
you didn't look that honest either.
It is wrong to judge a man
by his appearance.
You don't know
what kind of a man I am on the inside,
so I forgive you.
I want to avenge the death of my parents
for they were innocent.
The late king's nephew Lee Han,
Prince Hwiyeong,
took his own life while being transported
to Hanyang under the royal order
for the charge of conspiring
to commit treason.
Only a single line of record
for a major incident
such as Prince Hwiyeong's death...
I heard someone was killed by the beast
after going to get firewood.
I am miserable because it comes down
to the village every night to eat
and destroy all my crops.
We barely have enough to pay taxes
to the government office,
and now we must deal with a wild boar.
Isn't that wild boar being just like
the Big Sheriff and the Little Sheriff?
Oh, stop it. What if someone hears you?
Let's go.
A wild boar that kills people...
Let us visit the government office.
Yes, sir.
This is the place
the Special Advisor wrote about
in his journal.
I don't see anything special though.
We will find out once we investigate.
Make way!
Pardon me, who is that man?
Don't you know the Little Sheriff?
A sheriff is a sheriff,
so what's a little sheriff?
How frustrating.
He is the son of the Sheriff.
In this town, the Little Sheriff is king.
Do you understand?
Sir, what should we do?
First...
Let us eat.
Yes, sir.
Sir, what should we do first?
Let's arrest all the corrupt officials.
Silly man.
Making such a fuss will lead to mistakes,
don't you know?
Chunsam, meet with the villagers
and find out how they feel.
There must be problems.
Yes, sir.
Honglang...
I mean, Dain, go to the courtesan house
and find the girl named Sawol
and find out where the Royal Agent is.
Yes, sir.
Then what will you be doing?
I am...
Thinking of making a friend.
Enjoy your stay.
Oh.
Oh, nice.
I will be able to sleep
comfortably tonight.
Oh, how nice.
Why are you guys standing around
so awkwardly?
Are you uncomfortable?
No.
How dare you lie down like that?
Where are your manners?
Oh! I can sleep out in the dog house,
so you two can sleep in comfort here.
- Chunsam!
What is it? What?
We have a full day tomorrow,
so rest here in comfort.
What he said.
Sunae!
Sunae...
What is it?
What is going on?
Oh, he is dreaming.
He does that sometimes
so don't worry about it.
He was calling for someone.
Sun, Sunae?
It's Sunae. A long time ago...
It's better if you don't know.
And pretend not to know anything.
He is calling for a woman
even in his dream.
I am in disbelief.
Oh, we are losing daylight.
You don't know anything about women.
It takes women a long time to do anything.
So men must be patient.
How much longer...
Is that really Lady Dain?
She's like a fairy.
Don't you agree, sir?
Don't be silly!
Not everyone in a dress is a fairy!
We cannot waste anymore time
so hurry up.
Dain, follow me.
Yes, sir.
I can't stand him.
What do you think?
She's a true fairy, no?
She can dance beautifully,
and she plays the gayageum
better than Hwang Jini.
Everyone can do that.
Twirl around.
Say "ah."
Ah.
My goodness.
Not bad.
So, how much do you want?
Two thousand coins.
Two thousand?
Two hundred, two hundred.
Is that a joke?
You could buy this courtesan house
for two thousand coins.
Are you mad?
I didn't say two thousand.
I said two hundred. Hundred.
You said two thousand.
Here, two hundred coins.
I am being generous.
You are not as expensive as I thought.
Take her.
Come with me.
Yes, ma'am.
Oh no.
Sorry.
How rude.
You look over there. You, there.
Sir.
Keep looking.
Please show mercy
for the sake of my children.
My mercy has limits.
Do you know how much tax you owe?
Sir, my husband's 49th day
memorial rite has just finished.
So how can you charge military tax
to a dead man?
Your husband is not the only one
on the military roster.
What?
My little boys must serve in the military?
They have nothing,
not even a bowl of rice.
What?
Damn it.
Fine. I will give you one more day.
Unless you pay,
I will sell your children!
No, sir, not my children,
please, sir, have mercy.
Stop it!
- Mom!
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Mom.
That bastard.
She is new. Her name is...
What was it?
I am Honglang.
All good?
Now play nice.
Honglang?
Your name is so tasteless.
Hey, come here.
Geez, it's the same everywhere.
Why? Are you the boss here?
How dare you!
How did you survive with a face like that?
You should clean the toilet for now.
Then I should start with your hole.
What did you eat today?
What? You little...
I'm going hunting.
Do you have anything nice?
What are you planning on hunting?
I am planning on hunting a wild boar.
You don't look like a hunter.
Do not judge a man by his appearance.
This is steel tip arrow I made myself.
Steel tip arrow?
I make these only for special orders,
but you could kill a wild boar
with one strike with this.
Lift them up.
Hey, lift them up higher.
Lift them up high.
Seriously.
Hey, you.
What?
Is there a girl named Sawol here?
Sawol? Why do you want her?
Just answer me.
Where is Sawol?
Sawol cannot work right now.
Why not?
After she got pregnant,
she has been mentally unstable.
Pregnant?
Who are you?
Are you Sawol?
Didn't you meet a royal secret agent?
Get out!
Sir.
Oh, sir.
Sir, where are you going?
You will see.
What are you going to use the bow for?
And what is this hoe for?
Nothing beats a gift
when trying to make a friend.
Wait.
Dig a hole over there
big enough for a man to lie down.
What?
What are you planning on burying there?
And why are we here?
I came to bury you.
What?
I heard Kim Manhui and his minions
were chasing after you.
Yes.
Did they discover your identity?
They saw our faces,
but they didn't seem
to know much about us.
That concerns me.
I will let the Chief Royal Secretary know,
so you keep a close eye
on the Royal Agent
and report everything.
He is unpredictable.
I agree.
I think I've met every type
of nobleman out there,
but he is unlike any other.
Why? Did something happen?
He looks sane one moment
but mad the next,
and he looks mad one moment
but sane the next.
I cannot read him.
I see.
As the poem goes, the bright moon
is filling the empty mountains.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
You seem very relaxed.
This is no time to sit around.
You should go and see for yourself.
You have no idea how much suffering
these people are experiencing
because the officials are taxing
everyone, even children and the dead.
You really have no idea.
Forget it.
Where are you going?
I'm going to pee.
I'm going.
It is sensitive to smell and sound
so make sure you go far away.
Sure, sure, Royal Agent, sir.
Geez, who goes hunting at night?
Help! Help!
Help Chunsam!
It's a wild boar!
No!
Help!
Sir, the boar, the boar!
The wild boar!
Sir! Help Chunsam! Help!
Get out of my way.
Get out of my way!
Whoa, I thought I was dead.
This one is enormous.
What are you going to do with this?
I told you. It's a gift.
What?
So this is the one that was causing
a havoc in my town?
So, who caught this?
Sir, it is he.
I am Seong Igyeom.
Oh, so you caught
this monster by yourself?
By the looks of it,
you are not from this town, are you?
I was passing through
when I heard of
the mountain boar harming people,
and I wanted to be of help.
That is truly praiseworthy.
I caught it, I did.
And what were you doing all this time?
You went through much trouble
so relax and enjoy yourself today.
I am honored, thank you.
Keep this hidden.
The horse requisition tablet?
Why are you giving this to me?
I don't want my identity to be discovered.
The Royal Agent was investigating
the father and son duo.
They must be hiding something.
I am going to find out what that is.
Yes, sir.
Do you have a plan?
You must enter the tiger's lair
to catch a tiger.
A true royal agent
does not fear for his life.
I am touched.
Please enjoy the feast.
Thank you.
Sir!
You must be new.
Come and sit next to me.
You serve him.
I am Honglang.
Let me pour you a drink.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
- I...
- Here.
Let us drink.
Of course.
Bring more wine!
Yes, sir.
Stay.
Let me pour you a drink.
Oh, I must be drunk.
My hands are slippery.
I do apologize.
It is fine.
Bring me water to clean my clothes.
We will bring new food.
Come.
But I should help clean...
I apologize.
What are you doing?
Wasn't it obvious?
I was teaching the pervert a lesson.
Are you here to enjoy yourself?
Oh, do not misunderstand.
I am here on official business.
Official business?
You couldn't stop smiling,
sitting between two courtesans.
Why didn't you dance
like the last time?
I was acting.
Couldn't you tell?
No, your acting was so natural
that I couldn't tell it was acting.
Do you think anyone can be a royal agent?
Enjoy.
Father!
No, I'm not your father.
Who are you?
Oh, good boy.
What is this for?
It's nothing much...
Did you do hard labor
with my late husband?
Hard labor?
No one has returned alive from there,
but you look perfectly well.
Let me see.
Did you put together something
for me to collect?
Not yet.
Please give me a few more days.
I have given you many chances!
Hey, grab the boys.
Yes, sir.
No! Please!
Who are you?
This is too much.
This is robbery!
How dare you call
legitimate tax collecting robbery?
What? Legitimate?
Oh, that is a pile of dung.
Dung?
Apprehend him!
Yes, sir.
Hey, hey, hey, apprehend whom? Let go.
Let go of me!
Goodness, no.
Horse requisition tablet?
A horse requisition tablet!
That's a horse requisition tablet!
No, no, this isn't
a horse requisition tablet.
I am sorry.
Here comes the royal secret agent!
Oh!
Please spare us!
Instead of trying to help
this poor family,
what do you think you're doing?
We are just following orders.
What? Following orders?
You treacherous little men!
I will give you one last chance,
so do not show your faces here!
Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
If I hear rumors of a royal secret agent
appearing in this town,
I will find you
and tear your limbs apart.
Have I made myself clear?
- Yes, sir!
We will never forget!
Then get out of here!
Yes, sir, yes.
Go!
What are you waiting for? Let's go!
Leave!
Get out of here!
Hello, hello.
So...
I will go and pee.
You are very reckless.
You did this
to become friends with that man?
Did you find Sawol?
Well, I did find her,
but there is a problem.
What do you mean?
She is pregnant, and she looked
as if she is out of her mind.
Did she remember
meeting the Royal Agent?
Bringing that up made her
raise her guard against me.
Maybe...
You seemed to had too much to drink,
so why don't we call it a day?
Who are you?
You seem very drunk. Let us go.
You caught a wild boar
while passing through?
Did you honest think I would believe that?
I saw a mark, and I could not let it go.
You are very full of yourself.
I like you.
Come with me.
I want to take you somewhere.
Where is that?
I will show you something interesting.
Sure.
Don't go.
I'm getting a bad feeling.
Are you concerned about me?
This isn't out of concern.
I fear you might make a mess of things.
Nothing can be done without taking risks.
That goes for both you and me.
Sir!
E-Enter.
We are in big trouble, sir.
A royal agent, a royal secret agent
is here.
What? A royal secret agent?
Are you certain?
I am.
I saw the horse requisition tablet
with my own two eyes.
And his manner of speaking and behavior...
He is a royal secret agent for sure.
Bring me my wagon.
No, no, no! Get my horse ready!
Yes, sir.
Are there animals to hunt here?
Just wait.
Who is he?
He attacked a nobleman to steal food.
Why should I let a beast of a man live?
So what are you going to do?
Do you know the best kind of hunting?
It is human hunting.
Let him go.
Do you know who I am?
Punishment for kangsangjoe is death,
KANGSANGJOE: CRIME OF DISOBEYING
THE MORAL CODE DESIGNATED BY CONFUCIANISM
but I will show you mercy.
If you get to escape past that target,
you are free.
Go.
Run!
It's your turn now.
Hurry. He will escape.
Do you want to let him go?
Hurry.
You are fantastic, sir.
We almost missed him.
Why? Does that peasant scare you
more than a wild boar?
Get rid of him.
- Yes, sir.
Tell your captain that I am here.
The government has sent
another royal secret agent.
What should I do?
Whoever gave the order,
they are moving faster
than I had anticipated.
Royal secret agents.
They are pesky little things,
like mosquitoes.
Do not mind him and make him join us.
You mean bribe him?
What if there is a problem?
What else could we do?
Then there will be bloodshed.
What is the progress on recruiting
construction laborers?
Well, finding manpower is...
What is your job?
If you cannot find a few laborers,
how could I trust you to join me
in accomplishing my great work?
Give me a little more time.
I will send people to you.
Are you in there?
Who is it?
I want to talk to you for a brief moment.
Don't do this. I don't know anything.
It's about your little brother Dongsu.
His name is Dongsu, isn't it?
Dongsu? Do you know my little brother?
Yes, I read the journal
the Royal Agent kept.
Why was your little brother taken?
It was them.
They will kill everyone!
Whom do you mean?
Who are they going to kill?
Save my brother! He is innocent.
Okay. Calm down.
We can help you.
The Royal Agent has sent me.
Royal agent?
A new royal secret agent arrived in town.
He is staying at the tavern
so come with me.
Come.
What made you so scared?
What's wrong? What happened?
Bring me wine!
I'm sorry.
But we really need you.
Sawol,
this is the journal
Lord Park Cheolgyu has left.
I hope you read it.
You're back.
Where is Jonggil?
At the courtesan house.
What? Bring him this instant!
You had too much to drink.
Is something on your mind?
There is no need for your concern.
Pour me a drink.
But where is the man who left with you?
Why did you come back alone?
For a lowly courtesan,
you ask too many questions.
Sir, there is a problem.
You must return to the government office.
What is it?
Well, I cannot tell you here.
Leave.
It's a royal secret agent.
A royal secret agent?
Well, I mean...
There is a royal secret agent in town.
How do you know?
I met him.
That is nonsense.
He is dead.
He is dead?
Yes, he is already dead.
But I met him this afternoon.
And he died already?
What?
Father.
Enter.
There is a royal agent in town.
Could the courtesan whose life you spared
be responsible for this?
You should have killed her.
Lord Seong! Chunsam!
Lord Seong!
Lord Seong...
Lady Dain, is something wrong?
Chunsam, Lord Seong is...
Yes?
Lord Seong is...
Lord Seong!
What is it?
Are you all right?
I thought you were dead.
Me? Why would I die?
Kang Jonggil said
the royal secret agent was dead.
What?
So I thought you died.
The royal secret agent is dead?
So if he didn't mean you,
he must have meant the Special Advisor.
It is too early to say.
We need evidence.
Sir, you should report this
to the palace tomorrow morning.
Since you are safe,
I will return to the courtesan house.
Are you going to let her go alone?
Do you expect me to go with her?
Of course.
You really don't know anything
about women, do you?
She is a proud woman,
but her eyes welled up
because of you,
and you still don't see it?
And now you're sending her back alone?
How frustrating. Suit yourself.
You can be so dry.
Hey.
Dain!
Dain.
What is it?
It is dark so I will walk you there.
Pardon me?
Is this a part of your official business?
Of course it is. Official business.
Come.
By the way, Dain,
were you crying
because you thought I was dead?
What? Cried? Who cried?
You did.
What?
I did not! I didn't.
And why is that so important?
How infuriating.
It made me happy,
knowing there is a person
who would cry for me when I'm dead.
Sawol.
Sawol?
Sawol, what are you doing here?
Don't worry.
This is the royal secret agent.
Don't be afraid.
What happened?
What happened here?
You saw something, didn't you?
Tell us what you saw.
That night...
Sawol!
Sawol.
Who's there?
Stay with me, Sawol.
My baby. Please save my baby.
Sawol.
Sawol, stay with me, Sawol!
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
What is it that you saw?
Why did you take us there?
I warned you never to show your face again
in this place!
The Sheriff asked me to bring you
with utmost care.
You crazy idiot!
If Lord Igyeom finds out, you're finished.
The only witness is dead.
They are destroying any and all evidence.
He is an expert archer.
Do you have an idea who it is?
When you get him drunk and ask,
he might tell you something.
I will deal with him.
It's too dangerous.
I'm Honglang.
Winning over a man's heart
is a piece of cake.