EPISODE 14
What I want...
Is for us to remain together
even after the mission.
Is it too much to ask?
Why did you wait to tell me that?
That was my intention from the start.
Lord Seong, it must be curfew hour.
Come with me.
Are they gone?
Yes.
This always happens to us wherever we go.
That is why we are a match made in heaven.
I think they are gone.
Sir! Sir!
Where did he go?
Get him!
Stop right there!
You!
Use your words.
I am Park Chunsam,
and when I tell you my story,
you will be shocked.
Am I to go in there?
This is not right.
Get in? Yes? Sir, sir!
No, no!
Sir, sir, sir, sir.
I had a good reason.
Please let me go.
Be quiet.
Didn't you know that the curfew hours
are from nine to five in the morning?
Sir, sir, sir.
My master is a section chief
of the Ministry of Personnel.
Please get him for me.
What section chief?
You will be flogged tomorrow.
Flogged? Flogged? That can't be!
Flogged?
Wait! Sir!
We are here.
Already?
Yes.
You should go.
I will after I see you go inside.
I will go inside after I see you leave.
In that case, I will go.
Be careful.
A patrolman might catch you.
I am not an easy man to catch,
so do not be concerned.
Goodnight.
Over here, over here!
Can you please go and get someone for me?
Are you listening to me?
You!
What good is
having a section chief for a master?
He is never there when I need him.
Sir! What took you so long?
I have been waiting.
Chunsam.
Sir.
Open the door.
Go inside.
Why are you coming in here?
Wait, wait.
Sir, what happened?
They caught me.
What? But you are
a section chief of the Ministry...
Be quiet.
Spending one night here
is not a serious matter.
I mean, how could you end up here
when you are a section chief
of the Ministry of Personnel?
Sir.
Sir!
This is a beautiful night.
B-Beautiful? Beautiful?
Wait,
did someone hit you on the head
on the way here?
What are your eyes doing?
You bastards!
What grave crime did my master commit
for you to turn him into an idiot?
You bastards!
Chunsam.
Yes?
I think I have turned into an idiot.
Sir. Oh, lord.
You fools!
You bastards!
Have you lost your mind?
You became a section chief only recently,
so how could you get yourself
locked up at the patrolmen's post?
I apologize.
Do you know how difficult it is
to reach that position at your age
and earn His Majesty's trust?
Did you not know every official
in the palace is watching
every move you make?
When I was your age...
Every hour of every day,
I was concerned
for the security of Joseon...
Are you laughing?
I apologize.
You are impossible.
Oh no.
I apologize. My mind was elsewhere.
It is not polite to let your mind wander
when you have company.
During the tea ceremony, one must pay
attention to one's attitude and actions,
so what were you thinking about?
May I speak?
Light conversation is allowed
during the tea ceremony.
Was there ever a man you loved?
Are you all right, Court Lady Kim?
A man?
How could you even ask?
How could a court lady
fall in love with a man?
So there was none.
Are you implying there is a man you love?
I am not certain.
But when I think about him,
my heart starts pounding.
Even when my eyes are closed,
I can see his face clearly,
so I toss and turn all night long
until the sun comes up.
Is this what people call love?
This is enough for today.
What? Do you mean that?
Your mind is elsewhere,
so how could you pay attention
to my teaching?
My lady! My lady!
Take care of yourself.
Take care.
My lady, take a look at this.
What is this?
This is your new dress from His Majesty.
Try it on.
How do I look?
You look beautiful.
My lady, this dress was made with silk
from Jinju that was offered to the King.
It sure is beautiful.
Do I look good in this?
Of course. It looks perfect on you.
Have you waited long?
I thought I might turn into a statue.
Come.
Why are you in such a hurry?
When I am with you, time passes quickly.
I made this with my own hands.
You can cook?
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
This reminds me of the secret missions.
Back then,
even a rice ball tasted so delicious.
True.
I made this because I could not forget
how it tasted back then.
Since returning from the secret mission,
even the tiny wildflowers in the field
that I never cared for in the past
capture my eyes.
How does it taste?
It is very delicious.
Right?
Rice balls are hardly ever bad,
don't you think?
Is that so?
The rice is not fully cooked.
Lord Seong, do you think everyone is well?
After my report to His Majesty,
an official was sent to open
the provincial storeroom,
and give rice to people.
That is good to hear.
You saved many lives.
I could not have done it by myself.
Well...
Have you not heard anything
from your brother?
I am hoping no news is good news.
Lord Seong,
I am certain he is well.
How do you know these men?
Oh, yes.
I almost made a deal with that man.
You were going to make
a deal with a robber?
Pardon? R-Robber?
I did not know he was a robber.
I thought he was an average blacksmith.
Blacksmith?
Was he there as well?
Yes! They were together.
For a fugitive, he is bold.
You go and apprehend these men
and everyone associated with them
even if you have to kill them.
Yes, my lord.
Come.
Sir, it appears they have fled already.
Have you seen these men?
No, I have not.
I have not.
Stop.
Have you seen these men?
No.
Look at them properly.
Oh? He is...
Do you know him?
He bought something from me.
He came with a woman who was selling pots.
A woman who sells pots?
Go and bring Lord Bae.
We must go to the potters' village.
- Yes, sir.
The provincial guards
who were questioning people have left.
Ibeom, we should move.
Where did they say they were going?
They said they were going
to the potters' village.
Lord Ibeom.
There is no time.
Meet us at the village shrine.
We must stop by the village.
Provincial guards are coming!
Provincial guards!
What brings you here?
Where are the robbers?
What robbers?
We received a tip about
your collusion with robbers.
Search everywhere!
- Yes, sir!
What is this about?
What are you doing?
Come out!
Everyone, be quiet!
They are not here either.
Take the girls instead.
Yes, sir.
When the robbers return,
deliver this message.
Unless they show themselves
to the provincial office,
all the girls will be beheaded.
Do you understand?
Take them!
Yes, sir.
Are you all right?
Wait, wait.
Are you all right, sir?
Get away!
This is all your fault.
We shouldn't have taken in
such suspicious folks.
Mother, calm yourself.
I am fine so look after the kids.
Mother.
What happened?
They took all the girls.
Unless you show yourselves,
they will kill all of them.
Many are injured.
I will stay here and look after them.
Sunae.
They are searching for you.
You must flee.
Ibeom, we must go.
If anything happens,
come to the village shrine.
I will.
Let's go.
Okay.
You will not survive if you go.
He is right.
What would come of it if they killed you?
There is no other way to stop them.
There is only one way.
What is that?
It is getting rid of the governor.
But that is too dangerous.
We are standing at the edge of a cliff.
We must choose
between jumping off
or turning around and fight.
Which will you choose?
I will fight.
Now that we are here,
I want to keep going.
This is very peculiar.
The governor of Jeolla has requested
for soldiers to be sent
to suppress the gang of robbers
that is wreaking havoc,
but another report claims the governor
of Jeolla is tyrannizing,
using the robbers to excuse his behavior.
Which one do I believe?
The governor of Jeolla-do
was appointed less than three months ago.
Whichever side is telling the truth,
there is clearly a problem.
How about sending an inspector?
Lord Jang, this is the section chief
of the Ministry of Personnel.
Come in.
Lord Jang,
I have something I must tell you.
You look concerned.
It appears that we might need to dispatch
a royal secret agent again.
Did something happen
in a local government?
Two appeals arrived from Jeonju
with completely opposite claims.
I need a man to investigate
which claim is true.
Was not a new governor appointed
to Jeonju recently?
Yes, Byeon Haksu who was the magistrate
of Cheongju was appointed there.
Byeon Haksu?
Yes.
May I see the appeals?
Here they are.
"He is tyrannizing under the pretext
of capturing robbers."
What will you do?
I will return to where I belong.
When will you send a royal secret agent?
I will send one
as soon as I find the right person,
so help me find someone.
Me?
Is that not your job?
Yes, Lord Jang.
You are correct, Lord Seong.
I belong to you.
Thank you
for returning alive.
It is to remain together
even after the mission.
That was my intention from the start.
Do you mean that?
You want to go on another secret mission?
Yes, please give me your permission.
You do not have to volunteer.
His Majesty will select a man.
I made a promise with the people there.
I asked them to give me their trust
for I would get rid of everyone
who is untrue and corrupt.
They must be waiting,
believing in the promise I made.
Will you not regret it?
Probably.
I'll probably regret it.
But you still want to go?
I have learned
there are paths one must take
despite knowing there will be regrets.
Have you waited long?
No, I just arrived.
Lord Seong,
did you not say
you have something to tell me?
I did.
Is it of something important?
It is important.
Does it have something to do with me?
It does.
I am prepared, so you may start.
How may I begin?
You can tell me.
Well...
I am not certain I can say this.
I do not care what it is.
I will do as you say.
Do you mean that?
Yes, so tell me.
Pour it all out.
Why is it so difficult?
Why is it so difficult to say
"She is my woman!"
What do you mean?
Were you not going to propose to me?
No, I was not.
What?
You were not?
I was about to tell you that I have been
appointed a royal agent again.
And...
Royal agent?
There seem to be a problem in Jeonju.
Ibeom is there,
so I cannot turn a blind eye.
I am sorry.
I brooded over this all night, but...
Do not say that.
You must go.
Do become a royal agent
His Majesty can trust
and people can respect.
When this is over, please be my wife.
That was what I wanted to say.
Chunsam.
Yes, sir.
This secret mission
will be even more difficult.
I'll just have to risk
my life a few more times.
That is why
I am giving you the freedom to choose.
You don't need to come
if you don't want to.
What? Do you mean that?
Yes, you may choose.
Since you are going,
I, Park Chunsam, will not.
I will stay behind and man the house.
Yes, I understand.
Wait!
Are you really leaving like this?
You are not being yourself.
You should grab me by my neck
and force me to come with you.
I always felt guilty
of putting you through everything.
Sir.
Why is he acting like that?
I still cannot go.
How could I go there?
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN
Chunsam, what is this?
The royal secret agent is leaving,
so how could I, Park Chunsam,
an indispensable member of your entourage,
stay behind?
Chunsam.
Sir!
Sir, sir.
You are all I have.
Sir, are you crying?
I am not crying.
You look like you are crying.
Hey!
You cried, you did.
Be quiet!
So, what is your mission this time?
Something is happening in Jeonju.
I will know once I get there.
But since Lady Dain,
I mean, Lady Yeongsin.
Since she is not here, it feels lonely.
Do you not agree, sir?
Let's go.
But I did see you cry.
Come!
My lady, a proposal of marriage
has arrived.
Who is it from?
He is the chief scholar's son.
He is? That is great.
I must tell Chief State Councilor Jang.
My lady, I feel I have fulfilled my duty.
What is it?
Are you not pleased?
He has never met me before,
so why did he propose to me?
You are His Majesty's relative,
and since Chief State Councilor Jang
is a father figure to you,
who would not want you?
Is that so?
Is Lord Kim Byeonggeun inside?
- Yes, sir.
The governor of Jeolla-do
at my humble house?
How did this happen?
Come inside.
Yes, Lord Kim.
Seeing you reminds me of my late father.
He would have been so proud
to see you as a governor.
My father always told me never to forget
the grace your father showed us.
From what I hear,
you must be in a predicament.
After the royal secret agent left,
I am unable to collect as much taxes,
so it is difficult to raise funds.
Who says you can only collect
rice and textile?
What offers their bodies
when they are alive
and offers their belongings
when they are dead?
Do you mean slaves?
That is the source
of all noblemen's wealth.
You should move to a different house.
I am in charge of keeping an eye on you,
so it would not matter
where I keep my eye on you.
I need your wisdom.
My Lady, it is Court Lady Kim.
Do not be surprised to read this.
I must apologize to you,
but please keep this a secret
from Chief State Councilor Jang.
I am leaving to meet the man
who has taken my heart
for I believe he needs me.
But more than that,
in this moment,
more than anything else in the world,
I need him.
Is anyone home?
Who is it?
We are passing travelers.
We are ashamed to ask,
but can we please stay the night here?
Y-Yes, come inside.
It is not much.
No, this is amazing.
Thank you.
If I may ask, is your husband away?
He passed away a few years ago.
Oh no.
If you need anything, let me know.
Thank you.
Poor woman.
It cannot be easy for a woman to live
in such a deserted place all alone.
Let us eat.
Yes, sir.
I have to pee.
Where is the outhouse?
Outhouse...
One looks sturdy
and the other is handsome,
so you will make a lot of money
when you sell them at the slave market.
Slave market?
What was that?
Are they awake?
Sir, wake up, sir.
They are conspiring to sell us.
Sir, sir.
Dain...
Dain, Dain.
What is he saying?
Sir, sir.
Sir, I am so sorry.
We must leave right now.
One, two, three!
Wow, they fled.
They were quick like rats.
This secret mission will be filled
with hardships too.
At least we escaped alive.
By the way, sir.
Yes?
Were you having a bad dream earlier?
You were like this.
Dain was in my dream.
What?
How scary.
We finally arrived in Jeonju.
We did.
We have returned.
Let us get some food first.
I am hungry. Come.
Yes, sir.
Oh.
Oh, welcome!
Hostess, get us two rice and soup.
No rice wine?
No.
Why is this place so empty?
Oh, don't even start.
Oh, it's depressing.
Let us sit.
This country is full of robbers.
They are all determined to drain us dry.
Darn it!
You should watch what you say.
Watch what I say?
Everyone knows it is true.
Be quiet!
Starting with the King,
they must all be rooted out.
Darn it.
What are you waiting for? Drink.
How dare he criticize His Majesty?
I ought to...
Stay.
If you can't criticize
the king over a drink,
what joy would you have?
Enjoy your food.
Sir, what will you do now?
I need to see Ibeom.
Sir, isn't that Lady Yeongsin?
What?
Over there.
It must be someone who looks like her.
Sir.
What now?
Over there, over there!
Dain...
Lady Yeongsin!
It is her.
Why are they here?
Lady Yeongsin!
My Lady! My Lady!
Sir.
Lady Dain!
- Hey!
- It's Lady Dain!
- Sir, she is here!
- No!
I found her! I did!
Sir!
What are you doing here?
Why do you think?
I came after you.
Why did you run? I am out of breath.
Because you came after me.
Return to Hanyang.
No.
I cannot.
I am not the woman you used to know.
Is it not obvious?
That is why I am telling you to return.
There must be many
who are worried about you in Hanyang.
Think about them.
Is this how you treat the woman
whose lips you've kissed?
Wait, what? Kiss?
You kissed her lips?
What is she saying, sir?
How could you...
Oh, goodness gracious.
Who steals a kiss?
What? Steal?
People might misunderstand.
Misunderstand?
Did you say misunderstand?
Fine, fine.
I give up.
Sir, she is already here.
If you could force her to return,
she wouldn't have come in the first place.
Yes, Chunsam, you are correct.
Do you still not know me?
When you are here,
you are not a noble lady.
I know.
I came as Hong Dain,
a member of your entourage.
So, as you have in the past,
just call me Dain.
Personal feelings must not interfere
with official business.
Official and person businesses must be...
Of course.
And I ask you to do the same.
I am a member of your entourage.
Oh, yes.
Chunsam, here.
Chunsam, this is for you.
For me?
How unexpected.
What is this?
This is a compass.
Why would you give me
such a precious gift?
I bought it as a present for someone,
but I don't need it anymore.
Thank you, my lady.
Is that someone, by any chance, me?
You?
Yes.
Why do you think it's you?
How ridiculous.
Let me see that.
What do you mean?
She gave this to me,
so I must treasure it.
I said let me see it!
You want to steal this too?
Hey!
- Stop stealing things!
- Give it to me.
This is mine!
Give it!
My lady!
No!
Let us go.
Lord Byeon.
Oh!
- Have you been well?
- Lord Byeon, welcome.
Oh, yes, yes.
Let us go inside. It is cold.
Careful, careful.
The governor entered the courtesan house.
Well he's having fun, isn't he?
How many guards?
There were eight guards
and sedan chair porters.
We will stick to our plan.
Lord Ibeom.
Has anything happened?
Many got injured,
but compared to those who were taken,
they are doing better.
You look upset.
Is something wrong?
When I leave,
evacuate with the villagers..
What?
Lord Ibeom, tell me what is happening.
I will assassinate the governor tonight.
No!
You will never make it
into the provincial office.
Byeon Haksu is drinking
at the courtesan house this very moment.
You said you would never kill.
The man in the office is changing,
but the tyranny is getting worse.
So we must take action
and change the world in order to survive.
Lord Ibeom.
Do not worry.
I will return alive.
You must keep your word.
Am I the only one drinking again?
Lord Kim.
Welcome.
What is happening?
You sent a man to fetch me.
Sit down and have a drink.
Leave us.
What are you waiting for?
What is it you want?
Your insight is remarkable.
I collected taxes from a slave
who was pretending to be a peasant.
Although I do not know
how he built his fortune,
he was as rich as the robbers.
And I confiscated
all of his fortune.
I owe it all to your advice.
Look at this.
These coins are lovely, are they not?
This is a symbol of my gratitude.
You are pathetic.
What is the meaning of this?
Is that pittance enough to satisfy you?
Watching what you do tells me
you are the perfect prey
for the royal secret agent.
R-Royal secret agent?
The king has been hunting down
idle officials such as you.
At this rate, you will
soon be removed from your office.
Listen carefully.
If you do as I say, the seat
next to His Majesty will be yours.
What should I do?
Return home and sober up.
Next time, instead of sending a man,
come in person if you need me.
The seat next to His Majesty.
What is happening here?
Lord Igyeom.
Lady Sunae.
Sunae, what happened here?
The provincial guards beat people
and took them.
We were getting ready to evacuate
in case they come back.
Was it under the pretext
of apprehending robbers?
Yes. How did you know?
There was an appeal.
Where is Ibeom?
Well, Lord Ibeom is...
Sunae, the reason why I came here
is because two different appeals
were submitted to Hanyang.
I need to know which is true
to resolve the problem of this place.
Lord Ibeom said he will
assassinate the governor.
What?
Is that true?
Yes.
We must stop him.
If he kills the governor,
they will think all the evils in this city
came from the robbers
and send soldiers from Hanyang.
What?
No! We are not robbers.
I know.
Lord Igyeom.
Yes, what is it?
He said it is tonight.
The assassination of the governor.
He said the governor is
at the courtesan house.
The courtesan house?
So he must have gone there.
I should have stopped Lord Ibeom.
Do not worry.
Ibeom will be safe.
Chunsam, look after Lady Yeongsin.
Yes, we will return to the tavern.
Lord Seong.
I am sorry for getting you involved
in something like this again.
Do not say that.
But you must return safely.
I will.
I am sorry for shouting at you.
I had no choice.
Why are you leaving so soon?
No, no, for the time being, I must...
Go inside. It is cold. Go.
Next to His Majesty.
Let us go.
His Majesty.
Who are you?
What is happening?
Drop your swords!
Where are you going?
Get them!
Gyesu!
Are you all right?
Hurry up and get Byeon Haksu.
Boss!
Boss! Boss!
Are you all right?
You are...
The wound is deep. Do not speak.
Where is Ibeom?
Who are you?
I heard you were looking for me,
so I came.
You! Seong Ibeom!
What trickery did you use this time
to become the governor?
Did you embezzle tax money from people
and offer it as bribe?
Or did you erect a stele
with fabricated achievements?
You!
You fled for a pathetic girl,
and now you aim a sword
against your former boss?
But then again,
what else could a man of such low birth do
but become a robber?
Hold your tongue!
Did you say robber?
Are you not the true robber
for extorting taxes and deceiving people?
You will regret this.
Do you truly believe
you can get away with this?
What I regret is...
Not killing you sooner.
Stop!
Withdraw your sword.
Brother.
Leave that man to me.
I cannot.
I am doing this for you.
There is no need for that.
I must kill that man
for the good of people.
Seong Ibeom!
Do you think killing that man
will resolve everything?
You do not know what is happening here.
Sunae asked me
to stop you.
The governor submitted an appeal
claiming robbers are wreaking havoc.
His greed and wickedness must be revealed.
Only then you could be freed
from all the resentment and rage.
Did you come here as a royal agent?
You asked me before to trust you.
But look around. Nothing has changed.
Do not try to stop me.
Think of the people who look up to you.
Step aside!
Ibeom!
He needs a doctor!
Guards! Guards!
Lord Byeon!
Where are they?
Where are the provincial guards?
Get them!
One of them is injured,
so they cannot have gone far.
Go and apprehend every one of the robbers!
- Yes, sir!
Open the gate!
Seong Ibeom, you bastard.
Stop!
Brother.
Brother?
Seong Igyeom?
You brothers are rascals.
Where is the doctor?
He is not far from here.
Come.
It is time for you to leave.
Show some respect.
You better not beg for my help later.
Come.
Is anyone home?
Anyone home?
Ibeom.
What is it?
He needs urgent care.
Come in.
Hurry.
What about you?
Do you want to get caught?
Go inside. Now!
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Hey!
Answer my questions.
I heard that the people associated
with the robbers have been imprisoned.
They were sent to the slave market.
Slave market?
There is a market where they trade slaves.
Where is that?
I must find out about the slave market
in order to appear as a royal agent.
And we must rescue those
who are held there as captives.
Yes.
Do you have a plan to save them
from the slave market?
Is there a product you are looking for?
Everything we have is of fine quality.
Then I will buy them all.