Chunsam.
Darn it.
Hi, there.
Get him! Get him!
Where?
Get him!
EPISODE 9
What?
Stop!
Stop, stop, stop.
Stop playing!
Your mask is that of a butcher,
but your clothes say otherwise.
Are you playing a nobleman-like butcher?
Or are you trying to be
a butcher-like nobleman?
Chunsam.
Yes, sir.
Let me see that.
You are...
Lord Seong, what is happening here?
Ask him.
This is Lord Kim's son.
I know.
So, tell me.
Why did you go to that house?
I was passing by
and stepped inside by chance.
Is that a crime?
You covered your face
to a place where you stepped in by chance?
Is covering my face a crime?
Lord Seong, if there is no evidence,
I suggest we free him
before this gets out of control.
You were searching for something
in that house.
Tell me. What were you searching for?
I heard a woman died,
so I thought I should stop by.
The owner is gone,
so I did not need permission to go inside.
I thought I might find
something interesting.
Something interesting?
Who knows?
There could be a money chest hidden there.
What?
What is happening here?
Lord Kim.
Father!
Father.
What are you doing?
Why is my son on the ground?
Well...
Your son was searching
through a dead woman's house
with his face covered.
He spotted me and fled,
so I apprehended him
and was interrogating him.
Are you saying my son is the culprit?
Did you kill that woman?
No, Father. I did not.
You got your answer, so untie him.
Lord Seong, he's not going
to be answering anymore questions.
We will get another chance,
so let him go for now.
Untie him.
Yes, sir.
Why is everyone fussing
over a peasant girl's death?
What was that?
- Lord Seong!
- Sir!
What on earth are you doing?
Tell me.
Why did you go to that house?
What are you waiting for?
Who dares to attack him?
Challenging the authority of a royal agent
is considered treason, don't you know?
Tell me now!
Please spare me.
The class difference
does not exist before death.
What right does your son have
to look down on people
and belittle the death of one?
Take him.
I will not let this be.
Come.
Lord Seong, do you think that man has
something to do with Miss Gwiseon's death?
He is definitely hiding something.
I am sure he killed her.
How can you be sure?
First of all,
he's a prick.
He's irritating.
If I could, I would love to lock him up.
Even if you did, he would be freed
due to lack of evidence.
Kim Daegwang.
I need to know what kind of man he is.
What is the progress on the interrogations
of the officials who received bribes?
They all confessed their sins.
Was there anyone who conspired with them?
I have interrogated on the matter
as you ordered,
but no other names beside
those on the ledger were mentioned.
How is that possible?
Did you execute proper interrogations?
Chief Royal Secretary Jang!
How dare you speak before His Majesty?
I am ashamed, Your Majesty.
Chief of Royal Investigation Bureau,
keep an eye on whether or not
they change their statements.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Chief Royal Secretary Jang.
Chief Royal Secretary Jang!
Does it please you to humiliate me
before His Majesty and other officials?
Lord!
Do you truly believe
the prisoners' statements?
What?
Do you think I am a fool?
Calm yourself.
Are you interfering with the business
of the Royal Investigation Bureau now?
What would people outside think
if we stall the investigation?
It is time we close the case.
Everyone is eager to close the case,
so how can I not be suspicious?
Why, why that... How dare he!
His Majesty gives him too much liberty,
and that went to his head.
When one's faith is great,
the feeling of betrayal is also great.
Let us have a drink.
Thank you for your hard work.
You are too kind.
I should say the same for you.
The most urgent issue has been dealt,
but I am concerned about the future.
Lord Jang has His Majesty
wrapped around his little finger.
Father, how long will you continue
to let that crafty man run wild?
While that crafty man is busy playing
with his royal agent,
we will find his weakness
and end him.
Yes.
Let us drink.
That bastard!
The king is behind the royal agent,
so how could you compete with him?
Maybe that royal agent came after you
because he wants a bribe.
That was not it!
He really tried to kill me.
That royal agent. How dare he.
How do I get my revenge?
We must drive that royal agent
out of our town, so we can breathe.
Should we kill him?
Don't. You will only make matters worse.
You want to voluntarily walk
into the enemy's lair like a fool?
Use your head.
So what are you suggesting?
Just drink.
That girl with the royal agent.
She seemed quite nice.
Yes.
Oh, look at you.
You had your heart set on something else.
There are plenty of girls here.
Oh, since she is from Hanyang,
you're thinking she must be different,
aren't you?
Sir, sir.
This is bad.
What is bad?
I have to go.
Then go.
Come with me, please.
The atmosphere here is spooky.
I cannot go alone.
How come a grown man
cannot go to the outhouse alone?
Just this once.
I have to go, so please come with me.
Please, I beg you.
That felt great.
I can finally breathe.
Sir, is something wrong?
I am a royal secret agent,
and I had to stand guard
while you took a dump.
I feel ashamed.
When you go, I will stand guard for you.
Get lost.
Why?
I said get lost.
I will stand guard for you.
Stop it!
Who's there?
My heart!
What is the meaning of this?
What are you doing here?
He and I had a private conversation
as one man to another.
A private conversation?
Something like that.
What are you doing with a knife
so late at night?
Well...
Someone was watching you?
Yes, a man was watching me.
It really wasn't you?
What are you insinuating?
I told you the mood here is creepy.
Maybe it was that.
A ghost.
A ghost?
Yes, every government office
has its own ghost, people say.
Magistrate... Magistrate...
This is why you cannot go
to the outhouse by yourself.
It is late, so go to sleep.
Oh, he might come back,
so keep that silver knife close to you.
Lord Seong.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Lady Dain, what's that?
Magistrate...
Oh, stop it!
- Come with me.
- Yes, sir.
Aren't you coming?
You go ahead.
Magistrate.... Magistrate...
I said go.
You come too.
Lord Seong.
Aren't you tired?
I am fully awake.
I will stay here, so you can relax.
Lord Seong.
I am here.
Aren't you scared?
What could scare a grown man?
You were terrified of that snake.
Hey.
I was ever so slightly surprised.
I am your attendant,
so I should be assisting you,
but I feel it is the opposite.
I agree with you.
I must be unfortunate.
When it comes to being unfortunate,
I am second to none.
Two unfortunate people together...
No wonder my secret mission
is filled with misfortune.
But I don't mind it.
Aren't you going to sleep?
I am fully awake.
Liar.
You fall asleep the moment
you lay your head on your pillow.
Dain.
I don't mind it either.
You failed to handle the royal agent.
You have worked for me for over a decade.
Where is the man who was once called
the Spirit of Death?
I feel ashamed, Lord Kim.
You risked death
and came back for my punishment.
You are naive.
How can I kill the dog
that returned to its owner?
I will give you one final chance.
There is a girl named
Hong Dain who is with the royal agent.
It is she.
The courtesan Honglang
who spied for Jang Taeseung.
A girl on such a rough
and dangerous mission?
Didn't one of my men see her coming
out of Jang Taeseung's house?
Yes, Father.
If we investigate her,
we might learn of Jang's weaknesses.
Jang must have been
providing for her, keeping her hidden.
Sneak into his house
and thoroughly search Hong Dain's room.
I need to know who she is.
Yes, sir.
Lord Seong.
What if you catch a cold?
Sir, you slept out here?
He slept here to protect you.
Lord Seong. Lord Seong?
Where am I?
Go inside.
You might have a stroke.
What? Am I all right?
Yes, you are all right.
Chunsam, what were you doing?
How could you sleep inside
when Lord Seong was out here?
When does he ever listen to me?
To be frank,
you and Lord Igyeom have
already slept together,
so why did he sleep outside?
Slept together?
I am an unmarried woman.
When you sleep in the same room,
that is sleeping together.
Come and sleep together with me.
Am I all right?
How dare he?
I will pay a visit to the herb seller.
He is the only acquaintance
of Miss Gwiseon,
so he may know something.
Chunsam, keep an eye on Kim Daegwang.
Yes, sir.
And Dain, someone came after you
last night, so you will join me.
I am all right.
No, it is still dangerous.
Wait, what about me?
I am not in danger?
You are a big man,
so why are you so scared?
You think someone's going to hit you?
Who would dare to hit Park Chunsam?
Am I the kind of man who would
let someone hit me and get away with it?
I am glad to hear that.
Yes.
Let us go.
- Yes.
- Yes, sir.
Ibeom,
can we stop for a break?
Sure.
Sit down.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Let me see your foot.
I am fine.
You've been walking in this condition?
It is getting dark. We must hurry.
Stop right there.
What could this be about?
I am sure it has nothing to do with us,
so don't act rashly.
Yes.
Let me see your identification.
Is something wrong?
There has been a murder,
and we are looking for evidence.
A murder?
You are not from here,
so what brings you to this remote place?
My mother-in-law is gravely ill,
so I am traveling to pay her a visit.
By the way, have we met before?
Well, I have never been here.
No, no, I am sure I have seen you.
Where was it?
I am not well.
Is there a place we can lodge?
There is a town down that way.
Thank you.
They have an injured woman with them,
so they cannot be bandits.
Let us go.
Pardon my intrusion.
Come.
Are you all right?
I can walk.
They keep watching us.
Get on my back.
No, they will be suspicious.
If a husband turns his back
on his injured wife,
that would look suspicious.
You should let him carry you.
That would be helpful for us.
In that case, thank you.
Anyone home? Is anyone home?
I don't think anyone's home.
It is an herb gatherer's house.
The gatherer must be out
looking for herbs.
Sometimes it takes herb gatherers days
before coming back home,
so let us go inside and get some rest.
We are of similar backgrounds,
so the gatherer will understand.
Lord Ibeom, where are you going?
I will go down to the town
and get some food and medicine.
I will go.
Look after Sunae.
I will be back shortly.
Yes.
What brings you to my humble abode?
I came to ask you something.
Please come inside.
There was something odd.
Tell me.
Before she died, Gwiseon came to see me.
She handed me a bunch of herbs
and said she was quitting herb gathering.
For what reason?
She did not tell me.
Do you know a man named Kim Daegwang?
Yes, I introduced him to Gwiseon.
Introduced him? What do you mean by that?
He came to me and asked
if I could get opium poppies for him,
so I told him to visit Gwiseon
because she can find anything.
Opium poppies?
He mistook opium poppy tea for water.
Lord Seong, that means...
Yes.
In that house,
Kim Daegwang was searching for...
Opium poppies.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
Go.
What brings you here?
You won't even look up?
What is this about?
The man who just left,
why did he come here?
He left empty handed,
so he couldn't have bought a mask.
It's none of your concern.
Just tell me.
I don't know what this is about,
but I can't talk without compensation.
What? Are you a thief?
There are those who steal
from common folks,
so this is nothing.
Take it.
He ordered a mask.
A mask? What kind of mask?
I am making it right now.
Why are you making that mask?
Darn it. Take it.
What is the reason?
Someone needs it, so I'm making it.
I mean who would wear such a creepy mask?
Your eyes.
Fine. But there's no more of it.
Take it.
Courtesans mostly buy these.
Courtesans? Why do they buy that mask?
How annoying.
Here, take them all.
Now tell me everything.
I do not know why.
What?
How could you say that
after taking all my money?
I told you I did not know.
I cannot believe this.
I haven't introduced myself,
so you must not know,
but the royal secret agent...
Royal secret agent?
I am with the royal secret agent.
I'm Park Chunsam.
Go to the courtesan house.
I overheard what
the courtesans were saying.
They said that they send courtesans
to a secret banquet.
A secret banquet?
Oh, my heart.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
Wait, are you looking for someone?
Looking? I'm not looking for anyone.
Really? I thought you were looking for me
because you've been following me.
Me? I was following you?
Yes.
Why would I follow you?
That's nonsense.
I wouldn't know. But you would.
What?
I don't really know.
I will tell you.
Was it Kim Daegwang who killed Gwiseon?
Because of opium poppies?
I suspect him too,
but we need proper evidence.
Now tell me.
Why were you following me?
It must've been the royal agent's order.
Why are you hitting me
when you already know?
The royal agent is after me?
I feel like I am a big shot.
Sir.
Lord Seong, stop pacing.
What is taking Chunsam so long?
What if he is impersonating
a royal agent again?
I doubt that.
He would be lucky if he doesn't get
beaten up.
Sheriff, I am glad to see you.
Is something wrong?
Sir.
Chunsam.
What happened?
What happened to your face?
I caught him trying to steal my money.
No, that is not true.
I would never steal, sir.
Do you have proof?
I saw it, and that is proof enough.
What?
You humiliated me and my father
based on circumstantial evidence
and accused me of killing that girl.
Sheriff, put this thief in prison.
Lord Seong, too bad you seem to
be having a hard time in this town.
I think it's time for you to leave.
If you do, I will let your servant go
and drop the suit.
How dare you threaten a royal agent?
There is no need for that.
What is the punishment for thieving?
It is 100 flogging.
Flog him 100 times.
What? 100?
No!
Chunsam!
However, before that takes place,
I must speak to your father.
Why do you need to speak to him?
I must tell him his precious son
is addicted to opium poppy.
What do you mean...
The very thing you were searching for
at Gwiseon's house, I mean.
If he learns you were searching for
opium poppies at an herb gatherer's house,
he will be so pleased.
Fine.
I will forget about today's incident.
What already happened cannot be forgotten.
Chunsam! Chunsam!
That hurts!
I thought you were dead.
I almost died.
Ouch, that hurts.
Stay still.
Since you are putting
the ointment on me,
it feels like the pain is melting away.
Really?
Isn't that too much?
Can you move up?
- Up?
- Yes.
There? A little more?
- There?
- Yes, that's nice.
What?
How dare you act like a hero?
Sir, I swear on all of my ancestors.
I did not steal his money.
I know.
You knew, and you still
told them to flog me?
You did not get flogged.
You are so harsh.
You don't know
what kind of ordeal I suffered.
I do know.
Can't you see I am fighting my anger?
Hitting you is like hitting me.
He will not get away with this.
Kim Daegwang ordered a mask,
so I looked into it,
and it was to attend a secret banquet.
A secret banquet?
Yes, you must wear a mask to get in.
A secret banquet
where you must wear a mask.
And I heard that they bring
courtesans with them.
I need to visit the courtesan house.
Isn't the owner of the house dead?
She is.
Who are you?
Sunae, they must be
the owners of this house.
I apologize.
We were passing by,
but I got hurt, so we were resting.
Please forgive our intrusion.
You think we own this house?
Do we look like we live here?
The richest man in town
must look like an herb gatherer to her.
There is something we need to find here.
We were supposed to get it
from the owner of this house,
but she died.
What are you looking for?
Munho,
there is something even nicer here
than what we were looking for.
How about we take it with us?
Yes, that is not a bad idea.
What are you doing?
Just get your stuff and leave.
I am the kind of man who must get
what I want.
Come here.
Leave while I am being polite.
You idiot.
Get on your knees.
Mandeok.
Sunae.
Come in.
You are muscular.
Sir, is this your first visit here?
I've always wanted to come.
You girls leave
and get us the head courtesan.
Sir, are we not enough for you?
We will take good care of you.
Come and have a seat.
Sit, sit. I've wanted to sit.
Park Chunsam.
Go and get the head courtesan!
I said to get her.
I did not say leave.
I heard you were asking for me.
Sit down.
I heard that you send courtesans
to the banquet.
I beg your pardon?
I do not understand you.
The secret banquet
where you wear a mask.
I have never heard of...
Would you rather be taken
to the government office and be tortured
than to talk right now?
I do not know anything.
Look here.
Is this how you want to end up?
He has the patience of a child,
so you better talk now.
Hey.
I cannot go there.
I heard you send people there.
Are they your courtesans?
No.
All I did was introduce the opportunity
to the prostitutes.
Tell me what you know.
You can make money there
and enjoy opium poppy,
so I heard everyone wants to go.
Opium poppy?
Something smells fishy.
What do you need to do to go there?
Mandeok.
Mandeok, what happened here?
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect Sunae.
Where did she go?
They took her.
They? Who?
He said he is the richest man in town.
You must hurry and find her.
We don't know what they might to do her.
Lord Jang is still awake.
You must hurry.
Lord Jang.
Is someone here?
No.
Do you need something?
No. I came out to get some air.
You may go.
Yes, sir.
I found an okro used by
the royal family in her room.
If we find the owner,
we will be able to find out who she is.
It is made with gold,
so it must be a token of affection from
an idiotic member of the royal family.
This is...
What is it, Father?
This belonged to that man.
Who?
Prince Hwiyeong.
What? Prince Hwiyeong?
He might get suspicious,
so I will go in alone.
What are you looking for?
I am a new courtesan,
and I need a mask for the banquet.
May I ask you a question?
Who is the richest man in this town?
The richest man?
Lord Jeong is the richest man here.
Even the dogs know that.
Lord Jeong?
Where is his house?
You look dreadful.
You look terrible too.
What are we doing?
Lord Seong, are you dressed?
Must we do this?
We must do this to catch the man
who killed those women.
It won't take long.
Where are your masks?
Sir.
Over there.
Put your mask on.
Yes, sir.
Is everyone here?
Follow me.
I brought the women.
Let them in.
Come here.
Are we short of women?
No, I will go and check.
Let us get started.
Enjoy yourselves tonight!
Let us have a party.
What did you eat to make your body
feel as tough as a rock?
Oh, I don't know.
This is what I like.
This is...
I brought what you have been waiting for!
Oh, it is finally here!
Yes, yes.
What are you waiting for?
I want to talk to this girl
in a more private manner.
Me?
Come with me.
Come, come!
Enjoy yourselves.
Let us go!
Come, come, come, come.
Come, come!
Drink.
Wait.
It is no fun without this.
Drink.
Sir,
there is a drinking style
that is popular in Hanyang.
Would you care to try it?
Drinking style?
Yes.
Show me.
But I cannot...
Do it alone.
To tonight.
Yes.
Cheers.
This way.
Sir.
Sh!
Did you bring the money?
Yes. Here are 30 coins.
I can only give you half for that.
What do you mean?
This was what I paid until recently.
The girl who grew opium poppies died.
What? How?
She got killed trying to report us
to the royal agent.
The price will continue
to climb for a while.
Do you want it or not?
I'll take it.
Who are you?
Is Gwiseon the person you said
who grew opium poppies?
Royal secret agent?
Sleep tight.
What are you doing there?
I had to pee.
Hurry up and go inside.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Take off your mask.
I would like to see your face.
No.
You are sweet.
There is no one here, so it is fine.
Still, I cannot.
What are you doing?
Please don't. It is not proper.
Well, I understand.
Is this what you want?
What is that?
What else?
Take it.
Opium poppy powder.
There isn't much time.
You can't.
Stay still!
Don't do this. No.
Stop it.
Stop it! Stop!
What?
I can't take this anymore.
Why are you screaming?
Come here.
I need to teach you a lesson.
Stop it!
What are you doing?
Come here, you.
Ouch, that little...
Ground opium poppy.
It is late,
so how come your son
is nowhere to be seen?
I do not know.
He was always serious about his studies,
but I do not know where he went tonight.
Do you know anything?
Tell him.
Well, actually,
young master said he would kill me
if I tell anyone.
Where is he right now?
This is paradise.
I have prepared something exciting
for you tonight.
Are your pockets full tonight?
Bring her in!
This is a safe one.
Are you sure?
I heard a royal agent is in town.
He won't stay here forever.
He will leave soon.
Will you lose this chance
because of that royal agent?
We will begin with 100 coins.
Hundred!
One-fifty!
Two hundred!
Two hundred coins?
Anyone else?
Take off her mask,
and I will raise it to 300.
Sure.
We will start again at 300 coins.
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
What are you doing?
I am the royal secret agent!
You stop right there!
I will rescue Lady Sunae.
This is an okro.
That is Prince Hwiyeong's okro.
Who was that with a dokkebi mask?
Where is he right now?
Are you going to let
that royal agent run wild?
I will make my decision.
That traitor's belonging was found
in your home.
But that girl must know.
The girl named Hong Dain.
Summon that girl
and the royal secret agent.
Is that true?
I think something happened.