EPISODE 6
Do you have unfinished business with me?
I am here to negotiate with you.
Negotiate?
Fine. But what is that you are holding?
Don't you know who this is?
I don't.
I hear he's very famous.
He's the leader of a gang of bandits
who are robbers.
Is that so?
Doesn't he look like someone?
I don't know him, so why do you keep
asking me?
You leave me no choice.
I will see the Chief of State Councilor
and tell him who this guy looks like.
How does he look like me?
How?
I never said he looked like you.
Honglang, you!
I can get another copy of that.
Come inside.
What is it you want?
Take me with you
on your secret mission.
That is all I ask.
Did the Chief Royal Secretary send you?
No, he does not know about this.
Then how did you know?
Were you eavesdropping?
That used to be my job.
Tell me the reason.
There is someone I must meet.
Someone you must meet?
Who is that?
If you allow me to join you,
I will tell you another time.
Why don't we help each other out?
I can help you find your younger brother.
Lord Seong, are you inside?
Lady Miok, what brings you here?
I came to discuss something with you.
Is someone inside?
Oh, those?
There's no one in there.
Please consider it.
Did you get a concubine already?
Concubine?
She looks like she has been around.
So, do you like her?
She's not...
You have a graceful figure,
but your tongue is vulgar.
What?
How dare you...
Calm yourself down.
Do you expect me to take such humiliation
from a lowly girl like her?
She deserves your respect.
What?
Come.
It looks like the wedding is off.
I am glad.
I was planning on turning her down anyway.
You win.
Is anyone inside?
Hey.
Your Majesty,
Special Advisor Seong Igyeom is here.
Let him enter.
Your Majesty.
You suffered great ordeals
on your last secret mission,
so I am grateful you have volunteered.
I am infinitely honored, Your Majesty.
The greedy and tyrannical local officials
have devastated the lives of my subjects,
and driven by severe poverty,
they turned to robbery.
Someone must put a stop to that.
Royal Secret Agent Seong Igyeom,
go to Chungcheong and Jeolla areas
where robbers are raising havoc,
and observe the tripartite disorder
of the local government officials,
and console my subjects' hearts.
I, Seong Igyeom, will obey your order.
I received a report of a robbery
of a nobleman's house in Chungju.
Start your investigation there.
I will see you again.
What is this?
It's your second mission.
A second mission?
What happened?
I went to pay a visit to the guard
who found the bodies,
but he was already dead.
What?
It has begun again.
What do you mean by that?
I mean their terrible illness.
They eliminate
whatever stands in their way.
So the reason why they killed the guard...
He saw something he shouldn't have.
What could that be?
That the prisoners' deaths
were not suicides but murders.
Let us hurry. Dain is waiting.
What? Lady Dain?
We are going with Lady Dain again?
Yes, we are.
That's great.
Are you pleased?
Of course!
Wait. Sir, you're not...
I'm not what?
I mean, Lady Dain...
What about Dain? What?
Fine! She begged me to let her join us,
so I took a chance and said yes. So what?
Are you implying that
I have feelings for her?
Sir, do you have feelings for Lady Dain?
But you just...
I was about to ask you if you want
to take her as your servant.
Forget it. Let's go.
Feelings...
Lord Kim, what brings you here?
You belittled my father
and humiliated my sister.
Humiliated her? What do you mean?
Be quiet. Everyone!
- Yes, sir.
Teach him a lesson.
Lord Kim, what are you doing?
Where are you going?
Chunsam!
Sir!
Sir, sir!
Stop it!
We are leaving.
Sir.
Sir, this is not a good way to start.
Must we go?
Be quiet.
What? A royal secret agent?
Yes, I saw his horse acquisition tablet.
It must be
the Chief Royal Secretary's doing.
Father, this might be our chance.
What chance?
This may be our chance to get rid of him.
You said he will become our enemy.
Have you forgotten about Park Cheolgyu?
Going after a royal agent
may complicate things even further.
Do you know where he went?
I put a tail on him.
We must find out about his mission.
Keep a close eye on him.
What took you so long?
We are running very late.
Lady Dain, we were about to leave when...
Hey!
Let us go. We have a long journey ahead.
Yes, Lord Seong.
Lady Dain, go ahead.
What is my second mission?
Pay a visit to Governor Kim Myeongse
of Jeolla Province.
For what reason?
He is one of the few men who knows
the truth about Prince Hwiyeong's death.
Find out the truth.
Does it have something to do with Dain?
You will find out when you return
after completing your mission.
Tell me the reason.
There is someone I must meet.
Sir, what are you waiting for?
Come.
Dain, are you inside?
Dain.
You are like a father to me.
The kindness you've shown
by taking me in and raising me,
I could never repay.
I will be your burden no more.
Oh, that stubborn girl.
Let us rest here.
Yes, sir.
Chunsam,
do you know anything
about Lord Seong's younger brother?
Lord Ibeom?
Yes.
Of course I do.
Although he is his half-brother,
Lord Igyeom treated him
like his real brother.
They were very close.
But he coveted his older brother's woman.
Lord Igyeom must be miserable inside.
Haven't you noticed?
Sometimes he is not himself.
Come to think of it, you may be right.
Anyway, I feel very reassured
about having you with us.
The thought of being alone with him
gives me the chills.
Thank you so, so much.
There's no need to thank her.
Sir, don't be like that.
Aren't you happy that
Lady Dain is coming with us?
Do not make a fuss.
I do not want her company.
What?
I thought you wanted to bring her with us.
Isn't that why you taught her to shoot
and gave her a gift?
That...
Maybe I fell for her seduction.
Seduction?
Who seduced whom?
Someone told me
that you are good at seducing people.
Compared to you, I have much to learn.
Your tongue must be as sweet as honey
for the Chief State Councilor's daughter
to visit you at home.
You should teach me your secrets.
Behave yourself.
Who's next?
Will you seduce a princess?
How dare you!
Oh, I was mad to bring you along.
What's wrong with you guys?
Have you forgotten already?
We saved each other's life!
Sir, she saved your life.
Lady Dain, if Lord Igyeom hadn't saved you
at the cliff, you'd be dead!
Have you forgotten?
We are on the same side!
I was too harsh.
I apologize.
I didn't mean what I said.
You look good dressed as a man,
and it suits your character.
Maybe you should consider living as a man.
How about that?
Is that so?
It seems the word "petty"
suits you much better than "scoundrel."
A petty person.
What? Petty?
Yes, petty.
Are you in love with each other?
- What?
How dare you!
Are you mad?
Stop it! Stop!
After this secret mission,
you two will never see each other again.
Do you understand?
Being stuck in the middle of you two
will kill me before my time. Ugh!
Welcome.
You must have traveled far.
Sit here.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
They are impressive.
How can they only rob
the bad noblemen's houses?
It looks like the gang of bandits
haven't struck this town.
It's very quiet here.
Have you seen the gang of bandits?
How could we, when they are so elusive?
We came from the neighboring town,
and the bandits left a big mess there.
Hostess, do you have rooms available?
I'm sorry.
I don't have a room. You must share.
Share?
Are you still interested?
We have no choice.
Roommates.
Go in.
May we join you?
Sleep over there.
Roommates!
Oh, no, it will be a long night.
Can we join you?
Find a spot.
Wait!
Hey.
Get away from me.
I would love to.
Stop pushing.
I am being pushed.
Why did you get up so early?
I couldn't sleep.
Is something on your mind?
Someone next to me was snoring away,
so how could I sleep?
M-Me? I snored?
You also grind your teeth.
I never...
I couldn't sleep either.
Why did you keep
gently stroking my head?
You weren't asleep?
I was, but I was awakened.
Because you kept doing it.
But you didn't move.
I guess you didn't hate it.
Gosh.
Oh! I don't know who,
but the woman who has to share
a bed with you will be miserable!
That means you will be miserable.
What? Me?
We still have a long journey ahead of us.
And we will spend many nights together.
Oh, th-that's right.
I will be miserable.
Dain.
Yes?
What is it now?
I don't mind
if you snore or grind your teeth.
But you said earlier that you couldn't
sleep because of my teeth grinding.
You can grind your teeth
all the way down to your gums.
I was harsh earlier.
I apologize.
I apologize too.
Don't worry.
We are risking our lives for this job
without knowing much about each other.
If you have any questions for me,
you can ask me directly from now on.
May I really?
Yes.
So, do you still have those dreams?
I heard you lost your beloved
because of your younger brother.
Did Chunsam tell you?
Yes.
He talks too much.
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have asked.
Ibeom and Sunae
were the most important people to me.
I went looking for them after that day,
but I couldn't find any trace.
Time passed, and I consoled myself
by telling me that no news is good news.
But...
After all this time...
He appeared but as the leader of robbers.
Do not blame so much.
I don't blame him.
No.
Do not blame yourself.
You two are early risers.
I got up because I must be somewhere
very early.
Go back to your business.
Goodbye.
You should get some sleep.
You go ahead.
Pardon me.
Lord Seong!
Our money is gone.
Who would take it?
It was him.
What? Sir, what's wrong?
Let's split apart and look for him.
Yes, sir.
Yes, Lord Seong.
That way.
Madam, ma...
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
Madam!
Lord Seong, who is this woman?
Lord Seong!
I will check inside the house.
You check to see if anyone is alive.
What? Me?
Madam.
Sir.
They all look dead.
Anyone there? Is anyone inside?
- Everyone looks dead.
- Lady Dain.
Why is everyone lying on the ground?
Chunsam.
What's this?
Blood, blood!
Chunsam, check to see if anyone is alive.
M-Me?
Yes.
But why should I?
Hurry.
Sir!
From noblemen to slaves,
everyone got murdered.
This can't be one man's doing.
Sir, c-could it be Lord Ibeom?
The sun will come up soon, so let us
report this to the government office.
The patrolmen arrived long ago,
so where is the magistrate?
Make way!
Make way! Make way.
What's wrong? Do you know him?
I do.
He is very evil.
He was a secretary
with the Ministry of Justice.
He lied about getting punishments reduced
and took bribes from the family members
of the criminals.
Shame on him.
How do you know so well?
I surveilled him under the order
of the Chief Royal Secretary.
You exposed him.
Yes. He was exiled,
but it seems he was reinstated
as a sheriff.
He wouldn't recognize you, would he?
I looked just like this.
What?
You have enemies everywhere.
I know.
If he was in the Ministry of Justice,
he must at least be a good investigator.
Let's keep an eye on him.
Get rid of them.
Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir.
Their money is missing,
so it must be a robbery.
A gang of robbers attacked
a nobleman's house
in the neighboring town.
Yes, I also heard that.
They call those robbers
a gang of bandits, I heard.
Yes, that is correct.
Even people in Hanyang know about them.
It must be them.
Search for the gang of bandits.
This will justify my excuse
to leave this tiny town.
Make way!
It's already over?
I knew it. People don't change.
Listen!
It was the bandits who murdered
Lord Lee and his family!
- Bandits?
- Bandits!
If you have seen them or have information,
report to the government office!
Do you really think it was Lord Ibeom?
What's going on?
Lord Lee was murdered by the bandits
last night.
He was robbed by the bandits?
You reap what you sow.
What do you mean by that?
So many people of this town held grudges
against Lord Lee.
Is that true?
He was an infamous usurer.
I wonder why the bandits don't attack
the gambling house.
What gambling house?
You, it's you!
Oh!
It's you!
Dang it.
Stop right there!
You!
Hey!
You stop right there!
Oh, my heart.
You couldn't catch a snail at that speed!
What? What did you say?
That prick.
Where is our money?
Lady Dain.
You lost all of it?
Yes.
Where?
Tell us, before I...
I lost it at the gambling house.
Gambling house?
There is a gambling house in this town?
Earlier, you said you wondered why
the bandits haven't attacked
the gambling house.
Did I?
Be honest with me!
Is there a reason why the bandits
might be interested?
The gambling house here
is of no average scale.
At least a thousand brass coins
collect there a day.
A thousand?
The gambling house is where
all the troublemakers gather.
Lead us there.
Listen carefully.
The guard inside the gambling house
is not heavy,
but there are ruffians so be cautious.
Wait for my signal before you move.
We only want the safe.
Understand?
- Yes, sir!
That's the place.
The sheriff hasn't done anything
about a place like that?
Chunsam, take this man
to the government office.
Can I take a look around?
What did you say?
You want to gamble again?
You want to die?
Please spare me.
Serving time is the only way
for you to live, understand?
We'll go.
Come!
You come with me.
Yes, Lord Seong.
They must charge money to enter.
What should we do?
If you have a money pouch, let me have it.
A money pouch?
But it's empty. What will you do?
Good job.
This is too much.
Don't be too grateful.
Darn it.
Go and check the inside.
Yes, sir.
If the bandits know about this place,
they wouldn't pass by it.
I agree with you.
Welcome.
You guys are new.
Oh, you are so handsome.
I bet you hear that often.
Such a handsome man would have
caused a stir in town.
Why haven't I heard about you?
I know.
Come this way.
Have a seat here.
Enjoy yourselves.
I didn't know such place existed.
I've seen many gambling houses,
but none as big as this one.
Sit down.
What's wrong?
If we only watch, they will suspect us.
We should at least try this.
Do you know how to gamble?
Do I know?
I became a royal agent thanks to this.
What?
Never mind.
Do you know how to play?
I picked up a few tricks
at the courtesan house.
What will you bet?
Are you being serious?
Let's make it more exciting while at it.
In that case, doing what the winner asks.
How about that?
Sure.
Pick first.
When I stand up
and throw the strips down, we begin.
Subdue the armed ruffians first.
Afterward, you and you will
gather people into one place,
and the rest of you will collect money.
Do you understand?
- Yes, sir.
Come.
Two eights.
I'm sorry.
Two tens.
What?
You always lost, didn't you?
How did you know?
May I tell you what I want?
Yes, go ahead.
After the mission is completed,
there is someone I must meet.
The governor of Jeolla Province, you mean?
How did you know?
The Chief Royal Secretary
gave me a mission.
Meeting him is my second mission.
You knew that had something to do with me,
so why didn't you ask me for the reason?
I don't care what the reason is.
Everyone has a past
they want to keep hidden.
Well, I will tell you my wish.
Until the mission is complete,
stay with me.
Is that what you want?
Yes.
Why are you laughing?
That is no big deal.
I was planning on doing that anyway.
Welcome, sir.
Do you have a nice table for us?
Of course. Come this way.
Let us play one more round.
What?
Lord Seong, we are not here to gamble.
Yes, you are right.
Gambling is highly addictive.
Fine. Let us play one final round.
This has to be
the final round.
What is that place?
It is a gambling house.
What? A gambling house?
Yes.
How brazen of them.
Go straight to Hanyang and tell Lord Kim
that the royal agent is neck deep
in gambling and hedonism.
Yes, sir.
Things are getting interesting.
Hurry up and come.
Come right now.
What is your business?
Is the Sheriff inside?
He is out.
He is always out.
Oh, he went there.
There where?
To gamble.
I bet he went to the gambling house.
The Sheriff went to the gambling house?
Hey,
how dare you run your mouth here?
Get lost!
I brought a criminal.
Hey!
Out of my way!
Hey! Wait, wait.
If the Sheriff went to the gambling house,
Lady Dain.
Lady Dain, Lady Dain!
Sir!
What took you so long?
I had things to take care of.
I will take you to a nice table.
You!
Ill-fated ties are never easily broken,
so we meet again.
You owe me something.
Owe you?
Have you not realized your mistakes?
What?
I told you I will kill you
if we ever meet again.
I guess today is that day.
I will take your life for it.
Grab this girl.
Yes, sir.
We are here to gamble.
Let her go.
Let her go?
You must be in this together.
Lord Seong!
This is nothing so don't mind us,
and keep enjoying yourselves.
Bring her!
Yes, sir.
Let her go!
Let me see your hand.
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Show me your hand!
I fold.
Lord Seong.
I am fine.
I'm impressed.
Put the swords away.
You have spirit.
If you want to fight that bad,
why not play a round against me?
If you win, you can take her.
If I win, on top of her life,
I will take yours too.
What do you say?
No, Lord Seong. Don't do it.
This is a trick.
Do you think I will lose?
Yes.
If I win, will you grant my wish?
What?
How could you say such a thing
at a moment like this?
Answer me.
You were so bold before,
but you must be scared now.
I will.
Fine.
Good.
Set the table.
Maehyang, watch them
and make sure they don't flee.
Yes, sir.
I knew it.
No man can be this beautiful.
This is so exciting.
Come and place your bets!
This is not your ordinary game!
A match where a young man's life
is on the line is about to begin!
Place your bets!
Sixty coins on the young man.
Pick.
Lord Seong, how is it going?
Oh no.
Show me your hand.
Two nines.
- Two nines!
Two tens?
- Two tens!
What?
Two tens?
We're done for today.
Yes, sir.
Thank you for a great game.
Stop.
How dare you try to deceive me?
Sir!
Get him!
Sir! Lady Dain!
Why? What's wrong?
That way!
Darn it!
Gather the patrolmen!
- Yes, sir!
Wait, wait.
What happened?
Did you already meet the Sheriff?
Yes.
He holds a deep grudge against Dain.
But good for you for making it out alive.
Thanks to me.
I used the skills I developed in gambling
and saved our lives.
I knew it.
I want to ask you what happened.
What I saw was a one and a ten.
You did.
So?
How did they become two tens?
Actually...
One final round.
This is the final round.
When I was playing against you,
I hid one so I can beat you.
What?
Was that why you asked me to play
one more round?
Yes, because I knew I would win.
Would I bet my life in vain?
Wow, you are really...
No one can compete with you
when it comes to nerves.
You haven't forgotten the promise
you made, have you?
What promise?
If I win, you said you would
grant my wish.
But you did not win fairly.
A win is a win.
Fine. Tell me what it is.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Did you hand that man
over to the government office?
Yes.
Good.
I need to look into something.
Dain, go to the post station with Chunsam
and have the men get ready.
Are you going to make your appearance?
Yes, I am making my appearance
tomorrow at the government office.
Yes, Lord Seong.
- Come.
- Yes, Lady Dain.
What is it?
You gambled, which is illegal by law.
Out of my way.
Lady Dain, come.
Hey, you two, stop right there.
Lady Dain, you go ahead.
Chunsam.
I will deal with them.
Chunsam,
thank you.
Where are you going?
Lady Dain!
I am fine!
Please go!
- It's fine.
- I don't mind dying,
so please live happily ever after
all by yourself!
But please remember Park Chunsam!
Darn it.
Stop it! You will kill him.
Chunsam, Chunsam!
Lady Dain, why have you returned?
I said I am fine.
You don't look fine at all.
But I am.
This isn't the path
to the government office.
You! Where are you taking me?
You sure are chatty. You'll find out.
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Don't you know why you were brought here?
Oh,
gambling is just for entertainment.
I will show you what happens
when you cheat at gambling.
Who are you accusing of cheating?
After you left, I counted the strips.
Here.
Do you still deny it?
Oh, that?
Everyone does that in Hanyang.
It must be a regional difference.
Regional difference is nonsense.
Enough of this absurdity!
Lord Seong!
Sir!
Dain.
Are you all right?
How about you? Are you hurt?
What do you think you're doing?
Get that girl up.
Come.
You were once a secretary
of the Ministry of Justice,
but now you've become a worthless gambler.
Yes, you are as insolent as ever.
Bring her to me.
Lady Dain, Lady Dain!
I will cut out your tongue first.
No!
Sir!
Stop!
I will teach you a lesson!
Dain!
Who are you?
They are the bandits.
Bandits?
What are you waiting for?
Apprehend them!
Put down your weapons.
You idiots.
So you were all in this together.
You will never leave this town alive.
I will kill every one of you
by tearing your limbs apart.
Just you wait.
We finally meet.
It's been a long time, Brother.
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Must you go inside?
Every crime scene holds clues.
This is odd.
I've noticed too.
Everything is in order,
as if someone cleaned it.
I heard of carts going into that house.
Are they moving the profit
from the gambling house to here?
I heard the ledger is in there.
What about the ledger?
Did you kill Lord Lee and his family?
No matter what I say,
you won't believe me.
Are the rumors true?
I only returned what they have lost!
Then make me believe you.