EPISODE 10
Take off her mask,
and I will raise it to 300.
We will start again at 300 coins.
What are you doing?
Keep her as your concubine
or just get rid of her
after playing with her.
I will buy her for 500 coins.
Anyone else?
One, two, three!
Sold!
Will you come with me?
No.
I paid a handsome price for you,
so you better be worth it.
What are you doing? Let go of me!
I heard a royal secret agent is in town.
A royal agent?
So what? Who cares?
Rumor has it that
if you just feed him a hearty meal,
he'll become grateful
and even hand over his horse tablet.
What are you waiting for?
Pour me a drink.
Where are you going?
Who are you?
Me?
I am the royal secret agent!
Stop him!
Lord Seong!
Where are you going?
Let go of me!
Sir!
Chunsam! Now!
Get them!
Here comes the royal secret agent!
Apprehend them!
Take the guards and apprehend
those still inside.
Yes. This way.
I must find Sunae.
What?
Sir!
What is it?
The royal secret agent is here.
You must leave.
What? The royal secret agent?
My Lady! Lady Sunae!
Sir! Over there! Over there!
Stop right there!
You stopped.
My Lady.
I will knock you down and rescue her.
Chunsam, are you all right?
That way.
Lady Sunae went that way!
My heart.
Lord Ibeom.
What are you doing here?
Lady Sunae...
Did you see her?
Yes, but...
Ibeom.
Igyeom.
Why was Sunae here?
Why did you fail to protect her?
Where is she right now?
If you want to find her,
come with me.
This is the one who tried
to have his way with me.
That hurt.
You were hiding here.
You know, don't you?
Who was that with a dokkebi mask?
Where is he right now?
I do not understand
a word you are saying, sir.
Send a message to my house.
My father will be enraged.
Do you even know who these people are?
Tell him to stop!
I cannot do that.
Help!
Tell me.
Stop.
I have an idea.
The man who is always with him
is not here.
It's Kim Daegwang.
Darn it. You should've said it sooner.
Dain and Chunsam, take these men
to the government office.
Yes, sir.
And you, come with me.
Open the door!
Who is it?
- What are you doing?
- What is this about?
Where is Kim Daegwang?
What is this about?
I am fine.
You are...
I am here for your son.
Daegwang?
For what reason?
Your son is responsible for all the women
who were killed in this town.
Did you come to my house
to accuse my son of murder again?
Kim Daegwang, Park Wumin, and Jeong Munho
did it together.
What?
If it is difficult to believe,
go to the government office.
His accomplices have been apprehended.
Now will you tell me where your son is?
He said he was going to the lecture hall.
My son is not capable of such acts.
The others must have tempted him,
so please show him mercy.
Kim Daegwang may come back,
so I will stay close and keep watch.
Good. I will go to the government office.
Igyeom.
I am sorry I failed to protect Sunae.
I failed to protect you.
Twist their legs!
- Yes, sir!
Stop!
Where is the leader of your group?
How could we possibly know that?
We know nothing.
How dare you!
You are still resisting.
Guards!
Magistrate!
What is it?
I think something happened.
Is that true?
Yes.
Kim Daegwang is dead.
What?
What did you say?
I thought he was a good man,
but he practiced lustful acts.
Take his body to the government office.
Yes, sir. Take down the body.
- Yes, sir.
Search this area.
He took a woman with him.
Yes, Lord Seong.
Search this area thoroughly
and report when you find traces of a person.
- Yes, sir.
What is that?
Let us go.
Yes.
Lady Dain, this was on the ground
just over there.
Wait.
What is it?
I need to check the body.
What?
What is it?
How odd.
What is?
Look. If he had committed suicide,
the ligature mark would be diagonal,
across the center of the neck
going up toward the earlobe.
But for this man, it is horizontal.
That was probably because
he was struggling hard.
It's blood.
Lord Seong!
Lord Seong.
What is it?
Something bothers me.
Bothers you?
I found evidence of murder.
Murder? is that true?
Yes, his head has a scar
from a blunt force trauma.
Someone knocked him out
with a blunt object,
made him defenseless, and killed him
by strangling him with a rope.
Who would do such a thing?
We will find out when we investigate.
Lord Seong, I found the suicide note.
And we also found this.
I regret all my crimes.
I will take my own life.
There is no mention of a woman.
Lord Seong, I will take the suicide note
and compare it with his handwriting.
There is no need.
I have sent a man to Lord Kim's house.
Where did you find this?
Over there.
Let's go see.
Oh, my heart!
Lady Dain, did I scare you?
How dare you!
Wait.
I have a plan.
Chunsam, I owe it all to you.
To me?
Come. I have something I want to check.
Again?
Lady Dain.
Is this the place?
Yes, it is.
Keep searching.
I must go back to the government office.
I keep thinking
about the evidence of murder,
so I want to go and check the body.
Yes, Lord Seong.
What brings you here?
I am here under the order
of the royal agent.
Bring the tortured prisoners
to Bugeundang.
Prisoners Jeong Munho and Park Wumin,
come out.
I knew it.
I was wondering why he ignored us.
We brought them.
What happened to the royal agent?
Is he leaving soon?
Will you let us go once he leaves,
as you promised?
If only that royal agent
hadn't come to this town...
I expected you to just pretend
when you tortured us,
but it was unbearable.
Are you going to let
that royal agent run wild?
We will get rid of him
without anyone's knowledge,
so make your decision, Magistrate.
I will make my decision.
You.
Was this the magistrate's doing?
Chunsam.
Yes.
Report this to the royal agent.
What is this?
What are you doing?
If you had left quietly,
you could have stayed alive.
Where is the royal agent?
Lord Igyeom!
Sunae? Is that you, Sunae?
I've finally found you.
Are you all right?
What happened?
Keep searching.
I must go back to the government office.
It was him.
What are you waiting for? Shoot them!
Stop!
Who are you?
Listen carefully.
The government office is surrounded
by the royal agent's men.
Why do you want to go down for the crimes
your corrupt sheriff committed?
Those who put down their bow will live,
but if you fail to do so,
you will be punished for treason
for killing the royal agent's entourage
who receive orders from His Majesty.
What are you waiting for?
I said, shoot them!
No use.
You...
Get him!
You need to come with me.
He went in there so call the guards.
There are no guards.
They went home after they transported
the prisoners to the government office.
What?
What are you doing?
You!
Let go of me.
Lord Igyeom!
I just said it, hoping to save you.
Sir!
Out of my way!
Or the royal agent dies!
I am fine so apprehend him.
Be quiet!
Lady Dain.
Put the bow down!
Lady Dain, what are you doing?
Didn't you hear his order?
Do not try anything foolish.
No.
Dain, don't shoot.
Lord Seong, Trust me.
Don't shoot!
This is the last one.
If you have a clear idea of what
you want to hit, you can do better.
What you are trying to hit
is not that tree.
Imagine about what you want to hit.
Imagine about what I...
Want to hit.
What is she doing?
No!
Sir!
Lord Seong, are you all right?
Your terrible archery skills saved me.
Never again,
never again shoot an arrow.
I will remember that.
But I saved your life.
Sunae.
Lord Ibeom.
You're okay?
Yes.
Answer me.
Do you admit killing
the women in this town?
I know nothing about them.
You know nothing?
Do you admit to gathering young scholars
and taking opium poppies?
And entertaining yourselves
with prostitutes?
The prostitutes brought the opium poppy,
so I had no knowledge of it.
And what is so wrong with enjoying
a bit of entertainment
with the young scholars who study hard?
Are you saying you did not kill
the women and Kim Daegwang?
I did not.
Is he telling the truth?
Tell me.
It is true.
I watched you sell opium poppy
to a courtesan,
so how dare you lie to me?
Well...
It was Gwiseon who produced
the opium poppy and gave it to you.
Does that mean you killed Gwiseon?
No!
It was not me.
Does that mean it was you?
No! It was not me!
They are lying.
Beat them!
Lord Seong!
We only did what we were told.
It was Magistrate who killed Gwiseon.
That is correct.
You!
Gwiseon threatened to tell you everything,
so he killed her.
Is that true?
- That is true.
Do you still deny it?
You!
You ruined everything.
Kill me.
Killing you is not difficult.
I will report your crimes to His Majesty,
so you can be punished.
Until the royal order arrives, you will be
held at the provincial office prison.
You will not be able
to avoid decapitation,
so beg the Heavens for mercy
until you take your final breath.
Take this man away.
You have become a royal secret agent
who saves people.
I am very proud of you.
I became successful but lost you.
My fault is grave for leaving you behind.
If only I had not gone
to take the state exam,
you would not have suffered such ordeals.
There is no need to feel guilty.
What happened that day was my choice.
Why won't either of you tell me?
Tell me what happened.
I will.
After you left,
I
became Lord Ibeom's woman.
Is that true?
To you, I belong in the past.
You...
Must keep going
and become even more successful.
Put your past behind you
and keep walking toward your dream.
You are unyielding.
Very unyielding.
Do you still refuse to change your mind?
Magistrate, I may be a peasant,
but I am betrothed to a man.
How could you demand me to betray him?
A retired courtesan's daughter
talking about chastity?
If you say so, what can I do?
I found this at your house.
You must be a Catholic.
There must be others like you.
If you continue to refuse
to join me in my bed,
I will frame everyone you know
of being a Catholic
and behead them.
No!
I am the only one,
so please leave others alone.
That depends on you.
I will give you one day.
Think about it.
Lock her up!
- Yes, sir!
The magistrate wants the prisoner.
Yes, sir.
I must save you.
What do you mean?
If you do as the magistrate says,
you will die,
and if you do not, your friends will die.
Lord Igyeom will come for me.
No one in Joseon can protect
or save a Catholic.
Please leave.
I would rather die.
Do you not care about losing your life?
I will leave it all to Heaven.
Then let us leave it to Heaven.
Get them!
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
Lord Seong, are you all right?
Lady Dain, how could he be?
His beloved had an affair with his brother
and went far away.
And when he saved her life,
she told him to never seek her again.
What is this?
What? What now?
If it were me, Park Chunsam,
I could not let them be.
Lord Ibeom is much better at martial arts,
much more muscular,
much taller, and for appearance?
Well, I guess you win that category.
Still, how could she dump him?
- Stop it.
- Don't you agree, sir?
What's with your eyes?
- No, Lord Seong.
- Those eyes.
Please calm yourself.
I understand why people commit murder.
What?
I am just concerned about you.
Pardon me.
Lord Seong, try to focus
on the journey ahead.
We are almost at Jeonju.
We will go to Seongmunsan first.
Why?
You will know soon enough.
Your Majesty, I am beside myself
with shame for causing you concern
with the recent discovery of the greed
and tyranny of the corrupt officials.
It is not your fault
so do not blame yourself.
That means the royal secret agent
is doing his part.
Your Majesty, I am afraid to say
that there is something that may cause
more concerns for you.
Concerns?
What is it?
This is an okro.
OKRO: AN ORNAMENT
THAT GOES ON TOP OF A GAT
Your Majesty,
that is an okro that was owned
by Prince Hwiyeong who attempted to steal
Your Majesty's throne.
Prince Hwiyeong.
The records said it was Dobongam
in Seongmunsan,
so it must be around here
where Prince Hwiyeong died.
Father!
I will return soon.
Give me a few nights, would you?
Sir, who is Prince Hwiyeong?
He was a traitor.
A traitor?
Then why did he die here instead of being
punished at the palace?
While he was being transported to Hanyang
for the crime of treason,
he took his own life.
Lady Dain, are you all right?
You look pale.
I am fine.
Jeonju is near.
You can do this.
There is one last mission left.
Learning the truth
behind Prince Hwiyeong's death.
We will go ahead. Take your time.
We came together,
so we should go together.
Father.
It is I.
Why are you alone?
I sent Chunsam ahead.
Why did you want to stop here?
I thought you might want to.
I do not understand your intentions.
You know I am connected
with Prince Hwiyeong,
so why won't you ask me anything?
I thought you might need time.
Prince Hwiyeong is known to be a traitor.
It might put you in danger,
so how can you be so composed?
It was your tenacity that made me want
to find out for myself
the truth behind Prince Hwiyeong's death.
Lord Seong.
You are my attendant.
And you will be with me through the end.
So trust me.
Your Majesty, I am here.
I summoned you despite the time
because I have an important question for you.
Take a close look.
When my father was alive,
he had that specially made for someone.
Do you know the owner of that okro?
I am embarrassed to say I do not know.
That is the traitor
Prince Hwiyeong's jade heron.
That traitor's belonging was found
in your home.
I do not know anything about this.
Maybe you do not know.
But that girl must know.
What girl?
The girl named Hong Dain,
who is staying at your house.
I heard that was found in her room.
Why does that girl have something
that belonged to a traitor?
If you do not know, summon that girl.
Right now!
Your Majesty,
he cannot summon her right now.
What do you mean?
She is with the royal agent.
Your Majesty, that girl must have a motive
for accompanying the royal agent.
The traitor's followers
must be conspiring.
What traitor?
Do not speak in haste.
Your Majesty, allow them time.
Everything will be cleared once
the royal agent returns from his mission.
Your Majesty!
Traitors might be plotting something
this very moment!
Please summon the royal agent!
Summon that girl
and the royal secret agent.
Stop!
Go and check him.
Yes, sir.
Hello!
If you want to stay alive,
drop your weapons!
You!
Who dares to threaten the government army?
Guards! Get him!
- Yes, sir.
Lord Seong, over there.
Sir! Sir!
Over there, over there.
Don't go. Sir, don't go, don't!
Oh, geez.
Take cover.
Don't do it, don't do it.
Don't do it, don't shoot.
Brother!
- Brother!
It's an ambush!
Retreat.
Are you all right?
Thank you for helping us.
We could have lost everything.
Where are you going with that much rice?
We are headed for Hyemisa.
Hyemisa.
To a Buddhist temple?
Many are injured.
We must return to the provincial office.
Pardon me for asking when we've just met,
but would you be willing to help us
return to the provincial office?
We will.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I will never forget this.
I will report this to the governor
and give you a reward,
so please return tomorrow.
Government army taking rice to a temple.
What do you think that is about?
It was the governor who sent them,
so there must be a reason.
Geumgangsan has beautiful peaks
and the mountain ranges
th-that stand tall among clouds
and the peak that appears
to be covered in snow
stand tall toward the sky,
so people have c-called it a scenic spot.
My Lord, the head of propriety is here.
He may enter.
My Lord, I am ashamed to say,
the rice offered to Buddha
that was headed for Hyemisa
has returned to the government office.
What?
Well, they were attacked by bandits
on their way.
Did you capture the bandits?
I am sorry.
Apprehend those men!
I will show them what happens
when they come after
the rice offered to Buddha.
Yes, My Lord.
What are you staring at?
I-I have committed a grave sin!
I have an imbecile for a book reader.
What are you so afraid of?
Wow, is this the famous Jeonju bibimbap?
How much is it?
Six coins.
Six coins?
Are you ripping us off
because we are from out of town?
Ripping you off?
If you don't like it, go somewhere else.
You think we won't?
Talk about being unkind.
Sir, let us go.
Chunsam.
Hostess, why is the meal price so high?
Because it is for food.
Do you know how rare rice is these days?
I understand so calm yourself.
Sir.
Thank you.
Sit down.
As long as it is delicious.
This is some expensive rice.
Lady Dain, count every grain of rice
and chew thoroughly.
The price of rice must have gone up
because of bad harvest.
That must be why those bandits
went after the rice.
Is it good?
Lord Seong, what are your plans?
I will visit the government office
tomorrow afternoon.
I may be able to meet the governor
because I helped his soldiers today.
If you want to meet the governor,
you can appear as the royal agent.
If the answer was that easy to find,
they would not have sent a royal agent.
I must approach it in a meticulous manner.
Then how...
Dain,
let me eat.
What is taking him so long?
Lord Seong, let us hurry.
Dain, you stay here.
What? What do you mean?
Even if I do meet the governor,
I will go in alone.
Lord Seong, I am sure
I can be of assistance.
You must have forgotten,
but this is a mission I received
as a royal secret agent.
You need to follow my orders.
This is the royal agent's mission,
but it is also mine.
That is precisely the reason.
I cannot work with someone who is ruled
by personal feelings.
So if you wish to help me, stay here.
Come.
What about Lady Dain?
I told her to stay here.
What?
Did something happen between you two?
Nothing happened.
But we always go together.
You want Lady Dain to stay here?
I am doing this for her.
What? Why?
Come.
Yes, sir.
What brings you here?
I am here to meet the captain.
Welcome.
This is the head of propriety
of this government office.
He is the man who saved us.
If it hadn't been for him,
we would have been in serious trouble.
You have delicate features,
but you must be strong.
I hear that often.
I am known to surprise people.
Well, he does appear to be better
than your men who let
the bandits beat them.
I will leave this up to you.
Yes, sir.
Oh, and since you experienced trouble,
I will repay you for that.
Do not brag about it and make it last.
What is this?
It is the Jeolla Province rice,
which is more valuable than gold.
Remember you promised
to mention me to the governor?
I would like to meet him.
Really?
Do you think the governor
has a lot of time on his hands?
How dare you mention him?
Wait here.
Sir, what is his deal?
When the tiger is gone,
the fox plays king.
I am sorry.
Actually, I have an offer for you.
How about working with us?
What? Work with you?
I noticed yesterday
that you are an excellent archer.
We desperately need archers like you.
I will consider it.
Are you really considering joining
the provincial army?
It is a chance to observe the governor.
Oh, now we have to join the army?
My heart! What was that?
Hey! Little boy!
You stop right there!
You! Darn it!
Hey!
There is never a peaceful day!
How odd. I'm sure he came this way.
Sir, where could he have gone?
The road is...
Sir!
Sir, what is this?
I am not going there again.
I will not!
Why would you say that so suddenly?
Please reconsider.
Where else could you find a job
that pays as well as reading books
for the governor?
I should have listened to my friends.
Why did I say yes to that job?
Calm down.
If you quit too,
how am I supposed to do business?
How would I know?
Anyway, I cannot do it anymore.
Wait!
Hey, Gannan!
Gannan, Miss Gannan!
Hey, leave the books!
Oh, darn it.
Pardon me.
Are you looking for book readers?
Yes, I sure am.
Come in and have a seat.
I told you not to steal!
Give that to me!
Give it!
I am sorry.
I should have taught my son better.
You look like you need this.
Take it.
What?
I don't know how to repay you.
Pardon me for asking,
but where is your husband?
Is there a reason?
We weren't living like this in the past.
When my husband was alive,
we owned a small piece of land
and a house.
But we could not pay back
the high interest loan,
so the government office took our land
and house,
and the stress killed my husband.
The government office lent money
on high interest?
Yes, they did.
The governor provides high-interest loans
through grain exchange
and charges interest
that is two times higher.
I could not get rice.
Take him away.
- Please forgive me.
- Come.
Bad harvest was not the only reason
why rice is as expensive as gold.
I heard the governor is suffering
from a dreadful skin disease
and has been offering rice to Buddha
to cure his illness.
And that rice is the rice he took from us.
Sir, the rice from yesterday
must be the rice the governor
was offering to Buddha.
You're back. Come in.
You're back.
Lady Dain,
we learned something very important.
What is it?
The reason why that bibimbap
was six coins.
What?
The governor has been taking rice
from people and offering it to the temple.
How can a governor steal food
from his people?
So, did you meet the governor?
He is suffering from a skin disease,
so he never leaves the government office.
Skin disease?
That must be why he said
I should never look at his face.
We are going back to the government office
tomorrow and meet the captain once more.
What were you doing by yourself?
A book.
I was reading a book.
You were reading a book?
Yes.
What?
Do I need your permission to read a book?
I can read if I want.
Let me go and read this book.
Sir, about Lady Dain,
I am worried about her.
I doubt she will stay at the tavern.
What do you need?
I am the new book reader.
My Lord, the book reader is here.
Let her in!
I am here to serve you.
I am Hong Dain.
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Tell me the truth, My Lord.
Who sent you?
I am sure someone sent you with a motive.
What?
What is Lady Dain doing over there?
Chunsam, go and bring the station guards
as soon as possible.
Are you going to announce yourself?
I will make the governor tell me the truth
about what happened to Prince Hwiyeong.
They are going to behead Dain.
What? Behead her?
I must go to the government office now.