Seong Igyeom.
EPISODE 8
Who are you?
You.
I should've killed you then and there.
Chunsam.
Yes?
Take them and go to the temple.
Sir.
Now!
Yes, sir.
Come.
Get them.
Lady Dain,
I will stall them,
so you run and don't look back!
No, it's too dangerous for you.
Lady Dain, I am Park Chunsam.
Please remember me, Park Chunsam!
Chunsam.
You will regret meeting me today.
I will lead you to hell.
You stay right there.
Stay! Don't move!
Move when I tell you to!
I am thinking about how to beat you up.
Just wait. I'm coming.
I'm coming! I am!
I am!
Lord Choi?
Lord Choi, what are you doing here?
I brought His Majesty's order.
I am glad to see you.
Where is Lord Seong?
I will take you to him.
Chunsam, look after Lady Sunae.
Yes, Lady Dain.
I will join you soon.
This way.
Yes.
I know you are just an underling.
Does the man
who received the gold from you
want my life now?
You should have died long ago.
Tell me.
Who's trying to control if I live or die?
Do you want to know who that is?
Tell me.
Fine, I will tell you.
Lord Seong.
Lord Seong. are you all right?
I am fine.
Where is Sunae?
Chunsam took her to the temple.
How are things in Hanyang?
Appeals claiming you are neglecting
your duty, using your position
to gamble and seek pleasure
have been submitted, one after another.
His Majesty sent me here to find out
if that is true.
That is ridiculous.
Lord Seong went undercover
to catch corrupt officials.
He never got addicted to gambling.
And by the way, do you have any idea
what kind of ordeal he's suffering here?
I am only doing what I was told.
You have no idea.
Did I do something wrong?
Try to understand.
You know how she is.
I travelled a long way to come here too
because of the Chief Royal Secretary.
I know. I really do.
Lord Seong,
we still have work to do.
I know. I think it is time to end it.
Magistrate! Magistrate!
Magistrate, there is someone
who wants to see you.
No. Tell him to go home.
I think you should see him.
It's that man.
Magistrate,
I met the man you've been searching for.
What? How did you meet him?
He said he was giving out
the money he stole from you to people.
He gave me some too.
What? That loathsome man!
How dare he steal my money
and give it out as charity?
Where is he now?
He said he has been staying
at Lord Lee's house.
Lord Lee's house?
Yes.
So, he was right under my nose.
I had no idea.
Lady Sunae, please come inside.
I feel better waiting out here.
You go inside and don't worry about me.
But...
Yes, I will.
Lady Sunae,
Lord Seong still says your name sometimes.
Lord Seong and I both thought
you were dead.
Has he been well?
Of course. If only he hadn't become
a royal secret agent...
A royal secret agent?
Is Lord Seong a royal secret agent?
Yes.
So he has done it.
They are gone.
That bastard.
Guards, search every corner of the house
and find him!
- Yes, sir!
Here comes the royal secret agent!
What nonsense is that?
- Here comes the royal secret agent!
Drop your weapons!
What are you doing?
I am the royal secret agent!
You are the royal secret agent?
Yes.
It's over.
Kneel.
Don't forget that the promise I made
of killing you is still valid.
Even if my arms and legs are cut off,
I will roll to you and kill you.
That will never happen.
You will be beheaded
for the crimes you have committed.
Is beheading the punishment
for dabbling in gambling?
Did you think no one would find out
about what you've done?
You probably thought you had killed
everyone in this household that night.
What do you mean?
You were mistaken.
Aeran, are you there?
She is the daughter of a concubine,
and she was here that night.
Mom.
Do as I say, do you understand?
Magistrate.
Here is one more!
No, no!
Please spare me! Please!
Where were you that night?
I was in there.
That is nonsense!
Come with me.
Take a look.
It was too small,
so my mother could not climb in.
Only I could hide in there.
She is lying!
Really? Do you still believe
you can hide the truth?
Aeran.
Yes.
Tell me what you saw that night.
Nonsense!
Do you expect me to believe
the words of that lowborn?
Why shouldn't we believe the words
of someone of a low social position?
Tell me the truth.
That night...
She is trying to frame me!
Lord Lee deserved to die.
He corrupted this town
with his gambling house
and lent money at high interest
to the poor, making enormous profit.
I killed an evil man
as the magistrate of this town,
so why is that a problem?
For this town, on behalf of the people,
I killed that man!
The evil spirit that possessed Lord Lee
has possessed you too.
Aeran, what did you see that night?
That night I...
Did not see anything.
She was going to say that
she did not see anything that night.
However, you have admitted your guilt
with your own words,
so you won't object
to me apprehending you, will you?
What? How dare you toy with me?
Apprehend him and his men
and take them to the government office!
Yes, Lord Seong.
I am innocent. I am innocent!
The money you earned by taking advantage
of the people will go back to the people.
Do you admit your crimes?
I do.
However, what would you do
to the high officials in Hanyang
who demands money for promotions?
All I tried to do was to get out
of this tiny town.
Were you planning on using
all that money to bribe someone?
To go to Hanyang,
I needed all that money.
Who hates money?
Open the storage and give all the food
he has stolen to the people of this town.
- Yes, sir!
Come this way!
I am sorry for your hardships.
Thank you.
You evil man! Heaven will punish you!
I am sorry for your hardships.
Take your time.
It is over now.
Yes.
You could have earned
the respect from everyone.
You are finally going to Hanyang,
the place you have been dreaming of going.
Transport the criminals to Hanyang.
Join us.
I still have work to do.
Can you tell His Majesty
that I will return after my mission?
I will.
Come with me.
Now!
Sir! Sir!
Chunsam, why have you come here?
Lady Sunae has left.
She left? What do you mean?
I am sorry, sir.
I told her
you are a royal secret agent by mistake.
She asked me to give this to you.
I really wanted to stop her,
but she did not want to be a burden.
Please forgive me
for saying goodbye through a letter.
Being able to see your face
even if by passing
makes me feel
I have resolved my biggest regret.
Everything that had happened
in the past was by my choice,
so please forgive your younger brother.
Isn't that the royal secret agent?
He is the royal agent?
- Royal Agent.
- He is.
Royal Agent, Royal Agent!
- Thank you.
I am sorry to say
this is all we can offer you.
What is that?
They are rice balls.
Please take them for your journey.
You don't have to do this.
Please take them.
In that case, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Hooray!
I believe your dream of making a world
where noblemen and peasants can live
in harmony will reach the heavens.
I sincerely respected you
and loved you with all my heart.
I will keep you close to my heart
for the rest of my life.
- Ta-da.
Here.
Thank you.
Chunsam.
Oh, yes, Lord Igyeom.
Sir, try this.
No, I am not hungry. You eat.
Yes, sir.
How much longer will it take?
You are not acting like yourself.
What do you mean?
Why do you look like you are miles away?
Miles away?
Your eyes have lost focus,
and your shoulders are dropped.
I was thinking about something.
About a woman?
Wo...
What?
You've been like this
since Lady Sunae left.
Am I wrong?
You are.
If not about a woman,
what were you thinking about?
Relationships.
I was thinking about relationships.
Relationships?
Yes.
I thought about the faces of many people
I have met and said goodbye to
until now, one by one.
And all those people
have become a part of me.
Do you understand what I am saying?
I do not.
Yes, of course.
Lady Dain, what did he say?
He said he was thinking
about relationships.
The three of us meeting like this
formed a relationship, don't you agree?
He can be so silly.
We will find out after this mission,
whether or not this was
a good relationship.
I can't believe them.
Why wait to find out whether or not
if this is a good relationship?
Wait for me!
Do you only live in the moment?
You're not eating or sleeping.
Is there no tomorrow for you?
I lost my appetite, and I am not sleepy.
Do you know why?
It is because your head is somewhere else.
How much longer will you
let your personal feelings guide you?
You are a royal agent.
Do not forget your mission.
Personal feelings.
Neither you nor I would be here
without personal feelings.
Yes, I know.
You became a royal agent as a punishment
at first and for your brother next.
And now,
now for what?
As for my request of letting me
be with you until the end of the mission,
you don't have to worry about it.
Whichever choice you make,
be it your younger brother and beloved
or your mission as the royal secret agent,
I will not blame you.
You make the choice.
Dain.
I have already chosen.
I will not forget
the promise I made to you.
Sir.
I am hungry and weak.
Chunsam, build a fire.
I will go and catch some fish.
Sir, are you all right?
I have to be.
If I feel down, someone gets angry.
Who?
I will go and see
if I can find something to eat.
Look what I've caught.
Yes, you caught some.
I found these.
Good job.
Lord Seong.
Yes?
Stay still and don't move.
Why? What's wrong?
You better stay still.
Why? Why?
You may get bitten,
so please stand still...
Sir? Sir?
Are you that afraid of snakes?
I never said I was afraid!
Is it gone?
No, it is still there.
It is a big snake.
It is on your leg.
I am joking.
Joking?
Yes.
How could you joke at a time like this?
Sir!
Sir! Sir!
Did you scream just now? Did you?
What happened? What is it?
- Something...
- It was nothing.
Wait, something?
Let us go. I am hungry.
Sir, what happened
between you two?
What was that something?
What do you mean?
I am hungry. Let us go and eat.
Bring the fish.
Something?
The royal secret agent ate this too.
It is the royal agent soup and rice
the royal secret agent ate.
Come and try.
Here is the soup and rice filled
with the royal secret agent energy.
Did the royal secret agent really eat
soup and rice here?
He sure did. He ate in that bowl.
He did?
This will be my lucky day.
What is the name
of the royal secret agent?
It is Lord Seong Igyeom.
Why do you want to know his name?
Who knows?
He might buy something from me
if I tell him we ate from the same bowl.
Enjoy your food.
- Sure.
Hostess.
Yes?
Is the name of the royal agent
Seong Igyeom?
Yes, that is right.
Do you know which direction he went?
Lord Seong, are you all right?
I am.
We will reach a town soon.
So just hold on a bit longer.
Yes, let us go.
Sir!
Lord Seong!
Are you all right?
He is burning up.
Chunsam, go get some water.
What? Where can I find water here?
Go dig a well if you have to.
Yes. Sir, hold on.
No, I am fine.
Let us go.
I think you've caught a cold.
Did I?
I've never caught a cold
in my entire life.
We should go.
Are you sure?
I am fine. Let us go.
Sir.
- Sir! Sir!
- Lord Seong!
Sir. Sir.
Sir, what do we do?
Sir!
Sir. Sir.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
Your Majesty,
I have returned from inspecting
the royal secret agent.
Yes, good work.
Tell His Majesty what you saw
of the royal agent's conduct.
Yes. I was ordered by Your Majesty
and inspected the royal agent
on his secret mission
and learned he was carrying out
his duties faithfully.
As for the appeals on his corruption,
they originated from a misunderstanding.
Is that so?
Are you sure it was a misunderstanding?
I saw with my own eyes.
If it was not a misunderstanding,
it must be a lie.
A lie?
Someone is trying
to frame the royal agent.
Who would do such a thing?
Your Majesty, some local government
officials are evil enough to use
their position to drain the people dry
to line their pockets.
What they fear most
is the royal secret agent.
So they will do anything they can
to soil the royal agent's name
and frame him to hide their own crimes.
Do not let them deceive you.
You are correct.
Royal agents are my eyes and ears,
so if I cannot trust them,
who could I trust?
Your Majesty,
this is what the royal agent asked me
to deliver directly to you.
What is this?
That is the ledger Lord Lee Cheolyong kept
of all the bribes he gave
with the profit from his gambling house.
Second Minister Jeong Chilseong,
Left Associate State Councilor Jo Hoyeong,
Director Lee Sunsu.
Chief Royal Secretary Jang.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Give an order to apprehend
everyone mentioned in this ledger!
Yes, Your Majesty.
What are you doing here?
They have committed a grave crime
of taking bribes for special favors!
Apprehend them all!
- Yes, sir!
What is going on?
Let go of me!
Let go!
- Let go of me!
- Let go!
Do you know who I am?
Let go!
Lord Kim, what do we do?
I believe they are coming after us.
Watch what you say.
From this moment on,
they have nothing to do with us.
This is the royal secret agent's fault.
That royal agent has turned
this government upside down.
Their names will be recorded
in the book of corrupt officials,
preventing their descendants
from ever becoming government officials.
Doesn't it look like the government
is finally becoming righteous?
Pardon me.
Please step aside.
Good work.
How is Dain doing?
She is the same.
Of course.
I feel sorry for the royal agent.
Yes.
Where are they headed?
They are headed for Jeolla Province.
Are they going there for a special reason?
Shh.
You should rest for the day.
Yes.
Lord Jang, I do not have to
go down there again, do I?
Don't worry.
You won't have to go down again.
However, if His Majesty orders you to,
you would have no choice.
Do you not agree?
I do.
Miss, pardon me.
Yes? Is there a problem?
This is a dangerous area,
so why are you traveling alone?
What are you doing?
I would like you to take your clothes off.
Come here.
You are pretty.
Who are you?
I am her husband.
Out of my way.
This will teach him a lesson.
Men like him should be made eunuchs.
Sir! M'lord, please, not that.
Go.
Thank you for letting me keep my manhood!
Did you see my older brother?
Yes, but it was too brief.
You were desperate to see him, so why?
Lord Igyeom has become
a royal secret agent.
So I could not tell him the truth.
I see.
I was foolish.
I knew I could not go back
to the way things were,
but I went to see him,
as if I was possessed by something.
He is a royal secret agent.
He realized his dream.
I am afraid one day you and Lord Igyeom
will meet as enemies
with swords pointed at each other.
That will not happen.
Let us go to the town you mentioned once.
Do you mean that?
Let us stop wandering around the country
and settle down there.
Lord Ibeom.
Sir, do you feel better now?
Are you all right?
Where are we?
We were carrying you
because you were unconscious,
and we spotted
Miss Gwiseon's house and got her help.
Thank you.
We are in great debt.
Don't mention it.
I had an empty room and offered it.
By the way, are you living here alone?
My siblings got married, and my father
passed away while digging for herbs.
Oh, no.
I am sorry.
We cannot burden her this way,
so let us leave.
I am fine.
Lord Seong.
It is too late.
My house is humble,
but I think you better stay here tonight.
We should.
I will be with Miss Gwiseon.
Do get some rest.
You are a very kind person.
Chunsam, bring me some water.
Yes, sir.
Forget it.
Oh, I can breathe now.
What is wrong with me?
I have been waiting.
But how...
What is wrong with him?
Chunsam, what is wrong with Lord Seong?
I have no idea.
Just a moment.
Sir. Sir.
Sir, what are you doing?
Sir?
- Sir, it's me, Chunsam!
- You.
Sir, wait!
Sir, it's me, Chunsam!
Sir, sir.
Chunsam, are you all right?
This is bad. He drank poppy seed tea.
What? What is that?
It is the opium poppy seed tea.
It is used as painkiller,
but he drank too much of it,
and it made him hallucinate.
Hallucinate?
Chunsam, let us move him inside.
Yes, Lady Dain.
Did I really do that?
Yes.
If it hadn't been for Lady Dain,
I would be dead by now.
How odd. I have no memory of it.
Of course.
I devoted my life to serving you,
and look where it got me.
If I really did that, it was not
my intention so forgive me.
But...
It happened because he mistook
poppy seed tea for water.
Chunsam,
let us get ready to leave.
We must, don't we?
Yes.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Don't mention it.
Lord Seong, I have a favor to ask of you.
What is it?
I have a cousin in town.
She lost her husband and lives alone,
and she makes a living by selling herbs.
Could you please give this to her?
I will.
I have marked her house on the map.
Yes.
Take care of yourselves.
I will never forget you.
Me neither.
Sir, about Miss Gwiseon,
isn't she a nice woman
the more you look at her?
She is.
You looked like
you were about to propose to her.
If it hadn't been for our mission,
I would've done it.
That is your problem.
You fall in love too quickly.
Do you really think you can win
a woman's heart that way?
Women are attracted
to men who patiently wait
and care for them.
Don't you know?
- Sir.
- Patiently?
So you're just going to wait?
With women,
you must steal their hearts
at first sight.
The way Miss Gwiseon looked at me earlier.
Didn't you see?
Well, I saw your eyes filled with lust.
My heart.
What is it?
A man who patiently waits and cares?
Yes.
Steal her heart at first sight?
Steal.
Women are...
Forget it.
You two would not understand.
Hey, how can you stop in the middle?
Lady Dain, women are what?
Whatever. I don't know.
- Finish your sentence.
- You would not understand.
Sir, I think it is this house.
Let us go inside.
Yes, sir.
Is anyone inside?
No one seems to be home,
so why not just leave it here?
Can't you see the shoes?
She must still be sleeping.
What?
It's midday, so what kind of woman
would still be asleep?
Let us wait.
We should check inside.
What are you doing?
We don't have the owner's permission.
In there, in there.
What is wrong?
Did you see something improper?
Why? What is it?
What is it, sir?
What happened?
Who reported this?
They did.
Tell me what happened.
Yes.
We spent last night
at an herb gatherer's house.
And she asked us
to deliver some herbs to her cousin.
When we arrived, we found her dead.
Herbs?
Where are they?
They are here.
Good work.
Give each of them some rice
and send them away.
Yes, sir.
What should we do about the body?
Throw it outside the town.
No one will care about a dead peasant.
When an innocent person is murdered,
an autopsy must follow.
Insolence.
How dare you order me around?
Guards, get this man out of here!
Yes, sir.
What is that?
Horse requisition tablet!
Horse requisition tablet?
Horse requisition tablet.
Royal secret agent?
Yes, I am a royal secret agent.
Oh, My Lord!
My Lord!
- Sir.
Prepare for an autopsy.
I will attend.
I found traces of rape.
Assault and rape.
He took his time to torture her to death.
It must be from a personal grudge.
It is getting more vicious.
What do you mean?
It is getting more vicious?
No, I mean...
You mean there are more victims?
Oh...
Sheriff, you answer.
Is there another victim?
Actually...
I cannot believe this.
I am deeply ashamed.
Two women were found dead,
and one woman disappeared and is missing.
Are you even trying
to capture the culprit?
We are doing our best to investigate,
but it has not been easy to find clues.
Three women are either dead or missing,
but you haven't found any evidence?
I apologize.
While you were taking your time,
another woman got killed.
Lord Seong, the sheriff must have
his own difficulties,
so do calm down.
As the royal agent,
I will investigate this case myself.
Oh, it's you.
He is the royal secret agent.
This way.
Introduce yourselves.
He is the royal secret agent.
It is a great honor to meet you.
I am Kim Daegwang.
These are my friends.
I am Jeong Munho.
I am Park Wumin.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I am Royal Agent Seong Igyeom.
Lord Seong, they are the pride
of this town.
These young men have even
studied abroad in China.
That is great.
Use your knowledge
for this country and the people.
We will.
You came all the way to our town,
so we must hold a banquet for you.
Yes, that is a great idea.
There is no need.
I dare not seek pleasure
while I am on a secret mission.
Of course.
That was thoughtless of me.
Please forgive me.
That is fine. I appreciate the thought.
We will leave.
Please excuse me.
Come.
Who are they?
From Sheriff's reaction,
I can tell they are no ordinary men.
They're probably sons of rich noblemen.
They owe everything to their ancestors,
but they act like they are so special.
But they sure are handsome.
I almost felt offended just now.
Handsome? Who's handsome?
When it comes to appearance, no man
in Joseon could compare to Lord Igyeom.
Am I wrong, sir?
If being handsome is a crime,
I deserve the death penalty.
Yes! You deserve to have
your limbs torn apart.
I wish he gets his limbs torn apart.
This is our guest house.
I had my clerks clean the rooms.
Thank you.
You can take that room.
Yes, sir.
And you can take that room
with Lord Seong.
What?
You should get some rest.
Excuse me.
Hey, where are you going?
Chunsam, go to Miss Gwiseon
and tell her what happened.
She will be in shock,
so try to console her as best as you can.
Must I really?
It's not even good news.
Should we turn our backs on her then?
I will go.
I will be back.
Lady Dain, take this, please.
He is becoming more and more like you.
Then he is on the right path.
I will take that room for myself.
Miss.
What brings you back here?
Take this.
Why did you bring this back?
What?
Calm yourself, Miss Gwiseon.
The royal agent will catch the culprit
and console your cousin's spirit.
Royal agent?
Yes.
The man who was with me
is a royal secret agent.
This is all my fault.
How could it be your fault?
I will make sure the man
who made you cry pay for what he did.
Twenty-year-old Kim Joi's autopsy.
The body is covered in bruises,
and there are burn marks on the chest,
stomach, and buttocks.
Twenty-six-year-old An-geum's body
showed similar injuries.
She must had been tortured to death too.
The methods are similar,
so it must be the same killer.
Sir,
you must catch the culprit!
If you can't,
I will catch him!
Do you understand?
Yes, I do.
I think it happened again.
What happened again?
He fell in love again.
Again?
He did not say anything,
so how do you know?
Oh, Lord Seong,
must I spell it out for you?
I will leave this place.
Do not follow me.
If you come any closer,
I will go and
tell the royal secret agent everything.
Heaven will punish you.
What is it?
What happened?
It's nothing.
Did you have a bad dream?
Where is Dain?
Where is she?
She must be in her room.
I am getting a bad feeling.
Gwiseon! Gwiseon!
Why aren't you answering?
Oh, darn it.
Gwiseon?
Did she go to gather herbs?
Oh.
Gwiseon! Gwiseon!
There are people lined up
to buy herbs, so where is she?
What's this?
Lord Seong.
Did you sleep well?
Yes, thanks to you.
Where are you going?
I am going to interview
the dead woman's neighbors.
I might find something.
Lord Seong, you should leave that to us.
Magistrate!
What is it?
A body was found.
What?
Wait, she is...
Miss Gwiseon.
Yes, do you know Gwiseon?
She helped us a few days ago.
How far is her house from here?
It is just over that hill.
Another innocent life was lost.
I am deeply ashamed.
I need to visit her house.
We might be able to find clues.
Yes.
Lord Seong, we will go.
Just make sure to collect
the body properly.
Let me borrow your weapon.
Are you all right?
Yes.
We must catch the culprit and punish him.
Move over, move.
There are rocks here.
Move over.
I said there are rock here.
Chunsam!
Darn it.
Hello.
Am I at the wrong house?
I am indebted to a woman
who lives around here.
I must repay her.
But this is not the right house.
A bow.
Oh, this bow.
I heard there is a tiger around here.
This is to scare the tiger away.
Get him! Get him!
Where?
Get him!
ROYAL SECRETAGENT
I am going visit the herb shop owner.
He is the only one who knew Miss Gwiseon,
so he may know something.
There was something odd.
She came to me and asked
if I could get her poppy seeds.
Poppy seeds?
You can leave
and get us the head courtesan.
Sit, sit. I've been wanting to sit.
Park Chunsam.
Go and get the head courtesan!
I said to get her. I did not say leave.
They left.
I heard you send courtesans to banquets.
Igyeom has the patience of a child,
so you better talk.
You can enjoy poppy seeds there,
so everyone is eager to go.
What do you have to do to go there?
Something smells fishy.