Where are you going?
FINAL EPISODE
Step aside.
Do you know who he is?
I do, Royal Agent Seong.
Are you here to summon the station guards?
Apprehend the royal secret agent?
Did we not come here
to apprehend the robbers?
We only need to follow the orders.
Do you dare to stop a royal agent
from appearing?
Do you not know that it's a crime
against the government to stop one?
Stop?
I only came to show hospitality
to the royal agent.
You only need to appear to punish
corrupt officials, am I wrong?
There are no corrupt officials here.
You are beyond brazen.
Using robbers as an excuse,
you oppressed innocent people,
and moreover,
you turned commoners into slaves.
As the governor,
it is my duty to apprehend robbers
using any means possible.
And with the matter of slaves,
the commoners volunteered
to become slaves,
so who am I to stop them?
Then you have no reason to stop me
from appearing.
Step aside this instant.
Come with us to the provincial office.
I have a rather interesting story
to tell you.
It is about two brothers
who fell apart because of a girl.
Are you not interested in the details?
If this is a ruse to stop me...
If you feel suspicious,
you can ask the person involved.
Her name is Kang Sunae.
Apprehend them!
Stop!
Anyone who dares to stop me
will face grave punishment!
Is this insubordination?
He is a robber impersonating
a royal agent!
There is no need for fear.
Apprehend him!
Sir, what do we do?
The station is near,
so you bring the station guards.
What about you?
I will do my best to buy time.
Run like how you always run from me.
Yes, sir.
Your Majesty!
Fooled you.
Out of my way!
Get him!
Here comes the royal secret...
Chunsam!
Stop.
Move, and he dies.
What good is a soldier
who cannot even defend himself?
Just kill him.
Lord Byeon!
Get him!
Stop!
Or he dies.
I am sorry, sir.
Take them to the provincial office!
Take them.
Oh, it is a fine day.
Oh, it is a clear, beautiful day.
Hey, what are you doing?
Go to the back of the line.
Let me go in front of you.
Can't you see the people behind me?
Where? Where?
Get lost before I get mad.
Oh, for a wild boar, you are petty.
Wild boar?
- Wild boar?
- Oh, geez!
You idiot!
Let go of him!
What are you doing?
Wait here.
You idiot!
What are you waiting for? Take them away!
Look here!
The dead is waiting.
How much longer must we wait?
Let go of me!
What is that?
Can't you tell?
A person died in there,
so we are bringing a coffin.
Oh, I am dying!
Help me!
Go in.
I'm dying!
Help me!
Let them in!
That is enough.
Let go of me! Let go!
Get him off of me!
You!
Let go of me!
Help me!
Help me, please!
- Let go of me!
- Let go, you! Help!
Do come again.
Sure.
Where are you going?
It is not your concern.
Sit down.
Do you expect me to relieve myself
where I was eating?
Please hurry.
I will not.
Geez.
How could he be so relaxed?
It is tonight.
Will you join us or not?
Who here does not owe Jeon Gyesu?
- Jeon Gyesu?
- We must go and do our part.
I agree with you.
Let us hurry.
Oh, I apologize.
Come.
"I plan to punish the governor,
so those who wish to join my cause
shall gather on the last day
of this month."
It is tonight.
We must inform the royal agent.
If this letter is real,
it is not something we can stop.
I have seen countless bad officials
while on secret missions.
Their crimes varied quite much,
but every one of them said the same thing.
"I am not responsible.
I only did what I was told."
Can you truly call them loyal?
Please think about whom His Majesty needs
in a moment like this.
Do you wish to help the royal agent?
Yes.
Helping the royal agent
is helping His Majesty.
You are fearless.
Sometimes you must do what your heart says
in order to leave no regrets.
Come.
Where?
To the royal agent.
Chunsam.
Where is Sunae?
How impatient of you.
You can see her after I finish my story.
That jerk.
I would like our relationship
to be amicable.
We have history, do we not?
Stop the ambiguity.
What do you want?
I only need you to write a few words
saying everything here
is running smoothly and peacefully.
What would that get me in return?
I will not report
that you have been protecting
the robbers.
When did I begin protecting you?
What?
The only robbers I have seen here
are you and your men
who beat innocent people
and steal their status and wealth.
So you can talk.
But once you see this,
you might change your mind.
Bring her!
Lady Sunae.
Sunae.
Sunae!
You! What did you do?
I only delivered the punishment
the criminal deserved.
Criminal?
Whom do you think
should tell him the truth?
Lord Igyeom.
Looking at you this way
brings back memories.
I should have executed you back then.
Execute?
What do you mean?
Did you not know?
She is a Catholic.
Catholic?
I was generous enough to take her in,
but she refused to sleep with me,
so I had no reason to keep her alive.
Tell me.
Do you still think your Catholic god
will save your life?
Just kill me.
You have not changed.
You! Take your hand off her!
You should be angry
at your younger brother and not me.
Because he took her and fled,
I could not execute the criminal.
Ibeom, she is my woman.
Look after her for me until I return.
I will. Do not worry.
Because of the promise he made with me...
Lord Igyeom.
Now you see?
If I open my mouth,
you will become a traitor who protected
a robber and a Catholic.
So take your time
and consider my offer.
Lock them up!
- Yes, my lord!
Your stipend comes from the tax money
collected from the people.
Are you not ashamed
of the regimentals you are wearing?
Take them!
- Yes, my lord!
Let go of me!
Bring me my horse.
I must visit someone.
Yes, Lord Byeon.
Lord Byeon, I apologize.
You are pathetic.
Get out of my sight.
Tsk, tsk.
You should have done a better job.
You should be ashamed.
You fool.
Are you all right?
Yes.
Why did you not tell me?
I am sorry.
Was it for my sake?
Were you afraid for my safety?
I did not intend to deceive you.
For you...
Did you think I would abandon you
for my success?
After you two disappeared,
everything in my life became meaningless.
You must abandon me.
I cannot be a burden for you any longer.
We must escape from here.
Sir, I have an idea.
I will pretend to have a seizure
as if I'm diabetic.
I can make it realistic.
That will not work.
How would you know without trying?
Like so.
I just know.
Chunsam.
Yes?
Do you have the compass
Lady Yeongsin gave you?
Compass?
Yes, I have it inside my pocket.
Why do you ask?
What? Why? What now?
No, not this.
Make it sound good.
I am relying on you.
But it is mine.
Hey, over here.
What is it?
What could this be?
This is a limited edition compass
made by the best compass craftsman
in Hanyang using the rare wood
that is offered as tribute
to the royal family.
There are only three of these in Joseon,
and I have one right here.
Did you steal it?
Did I steal it? How could you say that?
Please take this,
and bring us a bowl of water.
You dropped it.
Open the door.
What do you need?
I was ordered to send the prisoners
to the slave market.
Yes, sir.
Wait, wait.
Get it out.
Let us go.
What happened?
Tie them up, and bring them out!
- Yes, sir!
Lord Kim, I have apprehended
the royal secret agent.
Did you?
What happened to the robber
named Seong Ibeom?
Many people have received rice from them.
So it is not easy to find them.
But now that we have his girl
and his older brother,
with a little rumor,
I believe he will show himself.
It is too early to celebrate.
Don't be fooled
by the royal agent's pretty face.
This letter says that the royal agent
has been colluding with the robbers.
Send it to Hanyang to prepare
for the unexpected.
You are very thorough.
Seong Igyeom.
I must see him with my own eyes.
Let's go.
Yes, Lord.
Where are you taking us?
What are you doing?
I will side with the royal agent.
Rather than dying like a beast
under the governor,
I choose to die with honor, however brief,
by the royal agent's side.
I will not force this on you.
It is your choice.
Thank you.
Why are you helping us?
You asked if we were not ashamed
of the regimentals we are wearing.
I do not possess the power
to stand against injustice, but you do.
And most of all,
the governor annoys me.
Good decision.
Lord Igyeom,
prepare to make your appearance.
You should get to safety.
Do not worry about me.
There is a temple nearby
called Boeunsa.
You should go there.
I will take you.
Thank you.
Go, Lord Igyeom.
Yes.
Come.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
That man is...
He should be in exile,
so what is he doing here?
Something must have gone wrong
with the royal agent's plan.
Where are you going?
I must find Lord Igyeom.
Yes.
Boss, what if not a lot of people show up?
We will learn soon enough.
Did you pass this out?
We did.
This is the place!
We are here to see the prisoners.
Open the door.
What? The prisoners were sent
to the slave market.
What? What do you mean?
I was told you gave the order.
Who gave such an order?
Captain told us.
The horse requisition tablet!
What is it?
Lord Kim, the royal agent
and his horse requisition tablet are gone.
This is why I told you to take caution!
Gather your soldiers.
The royal agent will soon arrive.
Countless government officials have been
stealing rice from us
and have been threatening our lives.
We are supposed to be
the root of the country.
How much longer
must we just watch those who threaten us?
Now we must attack the provincial office,
and take down the corrupt officials.
Let us show once and for all
whom they must fear!
- Hurrah!
There are no guards.
Go and free those in prison.
Go and find the guards and subdue them.
Let us go and apprehend Byeon Haksu.
Yes.
- Let's go!
Oh, look who it is!
You are Seong Ibeom!
This provincial office
belongs to the people!
According to whom?
Men!
Are you Seong Igyeom's younger brother?
I set this trap for the older brother,
but the younger brother has been caught.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN
Is everyone here?
We will now attack the provincial office.
I will apprehend the governor
and interrogate him for further crimes.
The provincial guards may resist,
so you must be prepared.
- Yes, sir!
Lord Igyeom!
What...
Lady Yeongsin.
What are you doing here?
That is what I would like to ask you.
Was there a problem with your plan?
Something did happen.
But, Assistant Royal Guard Choi,
you were to take Lady Yeongsin to Hanyang.
Why did you return?
We saw the governor and Kim Byeonggeun
enter the provincial office.
Kim Byeonggeun?
He was exiled, so why is he here?
They must be plotting something.
This is good.
I was about to take the station guards
to the provincial office.
Lord Igyeom, I found this.
What is this?
It says there will be a revolt.
If men gathered last night
after reading this,
the provincial office
must have been attacked already.
Revolt? As if apprehending
corrupt officials isn't hard enough?
Why do you think the revolt happened?
People who lost
their possessions and status
and are angry at the governor's tyranny
must have participated.
Their rage probably reached its limit
from losing their loved ones.
Lord Igyeom, before you head
to the provincial office,
stop by the slave market first.
You must rescue the people there.
Yes. Let us hurry.
Lord Jang, what brings you here?
The governor ordered me
to get rid of all the slaves.
Kill them all, and leave no trace.
Bring them out!
What are you waiting for?
Come out!
Kill them all.
Stop!
Here comes the royal secret agent!
Apprehend everyone!
I told you I was no ordinary servant!
I only did what I was told.
That is your crime.
Kneel in front of them and not me.
Lord Igyeom, leave this place to us,
and head for the provincial office.
I will.
I will leave the station guards,
so sort things out
and come to the provincial office.
Yes, Lord Igyeom.
Chunsam, come.
Yes, sir.
You men come with me!
Step aside!
Lord Seong!
Stop.
I was waiting for you.
I will come with you.
Good. Come.
Sir, what is it?
There are no guards at the gate.
What?
You are right. This is strange.
Search inside!
- Yes, sir!
Sir, over there.
Sir.
- Ibeom.
- Lord Ibeom!
Ibeom.
What happened?
Igyeom.
Untie them, and take them to the doctor's.
Yes, sir.
Stop right there!
They have revolted, so they are criminals.
Anyone who lays a hand on them
shall be considered one of them
no matter who they are!
You have finally revealed
your true colors.
Guards! Apprehend the station guards!
As you said,
the royal agent was colluding
with the robbers.
Yes, that is how it looks.
What?
Station guards, listen!
As you can see, the royal secret agent
has forgotten his duty
and colluded with the robbers!
The royal agent is working
with the robbers!
So he must be removed from his position!
Anyone who dares to follow
the royal agent's words
will be punished for the same crime.
Everything he said is a lie!
What right do you have
to punish the royal agent?
I could not punish a royal agent,
but I could punish a criminal.
You must know very well
which of us the real criminal is.
Are you saying that criminal
is not your younger brother?
His Majesty has been informed,
so when you return to Hanyang,
you will be interrogated.
You are a criminal in exile,
so how dare you mention His Majesty?
You!
Lord Kim has assisted me in apprehending
those who conspired to revolt,
so His Majesty will give him credit.
Fine.
He will surely be executed,
so if you are truly innocent,
cut his head off,
and prove to us of your innocence.
Then everyone here will believe you.
If you cannot do so,
you would be admitting your own guilt.
How about it?
Can you cut his head off?
Igyeom,
kill me.
How could I ever kill you?
I would rather die by your hand...
Than anyone else's hand.
Only then will this be over.
Sir.
Sir, sir.
You and I...
Have been handed the most brutal fate.
Igyeom.
I was correct.
Guards! Apprehend the criminals!
Step aside!
What is happening?
They are...
Lady Yeongsin.
These men established
the notorious slave market,
turned innocent commoners into slaves,
and sold them illegally.
Governor Byeon Haksu
knows about this better than anyone,
since he is the man who turned
commoners into slaves.
That is ridiculous.
What kind of trickery is this?
There are dozens of forged self sales
documents and witness accounts.
Do you still refuse to admit it?
Answer me.
Who provides slaves to you?
All the slaves came from this place.
Apprehend them all,
and lock them up in prison!
Kill all those who resist!
Stop!
You must protect the people.
So how can you kill them
after listening to their pain?
What is this?
What are you waiting for?
Apprehend them!
This is enough!
Are you not ashamed?
How much longer will you blame yourselves,
following unjust orders?
We have seen their evil deeds,
and we know what happened.
What makes us
any different from those scoundrels?
That man is a deserter!
He will be beheaded!
Apprehend them this instant!
Anyone who wishes to work for the people
and not the corrupt officials,
put down the weapons and join us!
Anyone who puts down their weapon
will be punished!
I will follow the royal agent's order.
How dare you!
Do you wish to die?
What is happening?
Stop acting like fools,
and return to Hanyang
to receive punishment for your crimes.
Station guards, apprehend these men!
What?
No!
No, let go of me!
Let go of me!
- Let go!
This is what happens to the treacherous.
Let go of me, let go.
Ibeom.
Igyeom.
Let go!
You! You!
Lord Ibeom!
No!
You!
Ibeom.
Igyeom.
I am sorry.
Ibeom.
Ibeom!
- Boss!
Take his body.
Sunae is at Boeunsa.
Let him rest there.
- Yes, sir.
Take the criminals away!
- Yes, sir!
Seong Igyeom, you!
How dare you! Seong Igyeom!
Let go of me!
Seong Igyeom!
How dare you!
No!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Everyone listen!
The man who led the revolt has died,
so I will not punish
those who participated.
Therefore everyone who was imprisoned
will be pardoned,
and those who were forced into slavery
will be reinstated.
And...
Those two officials and who follow them
will receive just punishment!
Lord Igyeom.
Let us return to Hanyang.
I will catch up so go ahead.
Yes, Lord Igyeom.
Come.
Let's go.
Lord Igyeom.
Sunae.
Ibeom.
Igyeom.
You are dead.
That is how you and I can both survive.
Sunae is waiting for you.
Survive, and go to her.
Thank you.
Look after yourself.
There was a world we have dreamed of.
I will strive to make that happen.
You should do your part as well.
Then one day, we might meet again.
Yes, Igyeom.
Royal Secret Agent Seong Igyeom
has revealed Governor Byeon Haksu's
greed and tyranny
and the related crimes
of the traitor Kim Byeonggeun.
Your accomplishment is great,
however, I have questions I must ask.
According to Byeon Haksu's appeal,
the man who attempted to kill him
was your younger brother.
Is that true?
Yes, he is my half-brother.
Does that mean you admit
you are the man behind the revolt?
People revolted because of
Governor Byeon Haksu's tyranny.
The governor stole
people's status and possessions.
Their lives were threatened,
so they had no choice but to fight.
The royal secret agent only stopped
a bigger revolt from taking place.
Your Majesty, the reason why they revolted
was because they wished
their voices to be heard.
Unless the world they dream of comes,
the revolt will not cease
and continue to spread like bushfire.
What is the world they dream of?
It is the world
where people live with dignity.
Your Majesty,
please answer to their voices.
The man who led the revolt
in Jeonju has died,
and the royal agent consoled the people,
appeasing the uproar.
Therefore no one who was involved
in the Jeonju revolt will be punished,
and from this moment on,
no one shall mention it.
Jeolla Governor Byeon Haksu will be exiled
in a faraway island,
and his family will be relocated
to the border area.
Traitor Kim Byeonggeun
is sentenced to execution.
What did you wish for?
I prayed that no more people in this world
suffer from injustice.
How about you?
I made a similar wish.
I prayed for a world
where a royal secret agent is not needed.
We made the same wish.
Since my wish will come true
thanks to your wish,
I should make a different wish.
What will that be?
I will pray for a life with you
and for things to be as good as now.
How do you like that wish?
I feel like it will come true.
Lord Igyeom, it is snowing.
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Chief State Councilor Jang,
I was about to pay you a visit.
You must come with me.
I summoned you
because of the recent appeals.
"Royal Secret Agent Seong Igyeom
demanded 100 silver coins as a bribe..."
What does this mean?
I demanded a bribe?
I have not been outside Hanyang recently.
I know.
I assume due to the work
you did in the countryside,
there are men
who are taking advantage of your fame.
Pardon me?
They are deceiving the people,
impersonating you.
Those trashy insects!
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
These things are occurring
because you are outstanding.
You have demanded bribes
in several places.
The sheriffs must have
squeezed their people dry
to get the amount you demanded.
My name cannot be...
No.
The honor of the royal secret agent
cannot be tarnished.
Send a real royal secret agent,
and resolve this issue.
You and I agree.
However...
Who could apprehend the man
who is impersonating Seong Igyeom?
You are correct.
It will not be easy to find the right man.
Yes! No one is as good as you.
But you have suffered enough,
so I cannot ask you to go again.
What am I to do?
Lord Igyeom,
how was it with Chief Royal Council Jang?
Lady Yeongsin,
I am sorry.
Pardon me? You are sorry?
No, no.
No, it cannot be.
You cannot say you are going
on a secret mission again.
No, no.
I am.
What?
Aren't there other men in the government?
Why must you go again?
I will go and speak to His Majesty and...
Men who are impersonating
a royal secret agent are torturing people,
so how could I just do nothing?
Are you asking me
to wait for you until you return?
Lady Yeongsin.
Fine. Where are you going this time?
Are you going to some island?
I'm going to Gyeongsang-do.
Gyeongsang-do?
Yes.
You know how I am, do you not?
I am not good at waiting.
Lady Yeongsin.
What are you waiting for?
Go and prepare,
and have a nice long journey by yourself.
L-Lady...
Sir, the air is cold.
What if you catch a cold?
Do go inside.
The moon is very bright.
What?
I agree.
Women are so difficult to understand.
Lady Yeongsin...
She even followed you
on your secret mission.
Why would she abandon you now
when all there is left to do is
to live in happiness?
Chunsam,
I am to go on a secret mission.
What?
Lady Yeongsin is a wise woman.
Take it.
What is that?
What is this?
It is a document to free you.
What?
Chunsam,
you are no longer a slave.
Sir.
You told me once
that you wish to escape
from this dreadful life as a slave
and live a new life.
You are free now.
So live the life you've always wanted.
I am forever indebted to you,
even after I die.
- Chunsam.
- Good luck on your secret mission.
I will leave to realize my dream now.
Please look after yourself.
Chunsam.
Let me have a hug.
Sir.
Sir!
By the way,
you said you were forever indebted to me.
How do you plan on repaying me?
- My secret mission...
- What?
I will think about it later.
I must go and realize my dream.
I am Hong Dain...
The scoundrel?
Sir, hurry up.
OPEN WHEN YOU GET TO NAMDAEMUN
You come empty handed,
you leave empty handed.
Being alone is not so bad.
It is I,
Park Chunsam.
Chunsam?
Is that my clothing?
Yes, it is.
But clothing is not important.
I am no longer a slave,
so I must dress accordingly.
Why did you come?
I told you to go and live your life.
I was going to realize my dream, but...
Over there.
Lady Yeongsin,
why are you dressed like that?
Have I not told you?
That I am not good at waiting.
So I've decided to go with you.
And who would look after you
if not I?
Yes, you are the only one.
Don't forget about me.
But Lord Igyeom,
this is the last time,
and I really mean it.
Do you understand?
I do.
Let us go and apprehend
all corrupt officials.
Yes, let us go.
What is the mission?
There are men who are impersonating me.
What?
Of all people,
why would they impersonate you?
How strange.
What could we do?
Corrupt officials tremble in fear
when they hear his name.
Tremble?
That cannot be.
Why did you bring this fool?
I do not know.
Wait, I am not a slave anymore,
so do not call me fool.
You fool!
Again?
Lord Igyeom, calm yourself.
Three is better than one, is it not?
Just the two of us might have been better.
Then you two be
the royal agent's entourage.
I will leave.
Leave, leave!
You think I'm joking? I am leaving!
I am!
Hey!
You fool!
So childish!
Wait for me!
I am not going to do this!
It is no fun!
Get him!
You got me again!
Oh, you two!