EPISODE 5
Lord Seong!
No!
If you don't want to lose your head,
put that sword down.
Lady Dain.
Chunsam.
Are you all right?
Yes, I am.
Sir!
Take Dain to safety.
Yes, sir.
I still have work to do.
Lord Seong!
On your knees!
Tie them up!
- Don't move.
- Stay still.
Lady Dain, what's wrong?
Maybe something happened to Lord Seong.
I should go and see.
No, Lady Dain.
Lord Seong ordered me to protect you.
If something bad happens to him,
I would be miserable.
Then you stay here.
I will go.
Over there.
That is...
Lord Seong?
Sir!
Sir.
What are you doing?
Come here.
Are you all right?
I am fine.
But...
But let me have a moment.
Lord Seong.
Lord Seong?
Are you all right?
You should rest more.
I should ask you that.
I told you to go to Hanyang,
so why did you come here?
To rescue you.
You never listen to me.
Lord Seong,
you saved all those men.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Why are you crying?
I don't know.
Sir! Lord Seong!
Sir!
What? What happened?
Sir, my lord,
are you all right?
Let us all go home!
There is a baby that was born
from a courtesan.
Which is it?
- Please spare us, Sheriff.
- This is my baby. Spare us!
Shut up!
Confess now or I will kill
every one of them.
Please spare my baby.
- Please!
- Spare us!
This is my baby.
Please spare us!
She is a widow!
How can a widow give birth?
Where is your husband?
Answer me.
He was sent to labor camp
and died there.
If he was sent to labor camp,
how did you have that baby?
You are either unchaste or lying,
and both are unforgivable.
Kill the baby.
- Yes, sir.
No!
Spare his life!
Please spare his life!
No! No!
Please spare him!
Sir! Sir!
We're in big trouble!
What is it?
- Here comes the royal secret agent!
Why, you! How dare you!
Here comes the royal secret agent.
Apprehend everyone!
No! Not me!
Stay still.
That hurts!
You collected tax from dead people
and forced children to submit hemp cloth
to be exempt from military duty.
Your position was given to you
to look after your people,
so how dare you use it to steal from them?
And you must know what you've done.
You used your position
as the sheriff's son and harassed people,
and moreover, used them as game.
Am I wrong?
Bring it!
Now, tell me.
You dared to kill a royal secret agent
and framed innocent people
for illegal mining...
All for these rocks?
Do you know how many men
lost their lives for these rocks?
There was a man
who collected gold from Hwaeomsan.
Who is he?
Where does he bring the gold?
If I told you the truth,
would you be able to handle it?
What?
Tell me the truth.
Whose gold is this?
Stop!
There he is.
Who is he?
He's the seonjeonkwan sent by His Majesty.
I bring His Majesty's order.
It is the royal order!
Transfer the criminals Kang Inchung
and his son Kang Jonggil to Hanyang.
Punish those who collaborated with them
appropriate to the gravity of their crimes
according to the royal agent's decision.
Collect the royal subject
Park Cheolgyu's body,
console his spirit
and prepare it for a burial in Hanyang.
Everyone listen!
Those who were wrongfully forced
to the life of hard labor at the mine,
and those who became criminals
because of heavy taxes,
you will be cleared of all crimes
and never be charged again,
so return home!
- Hooray for the royal secret agent!
Hooray!
- Hooray!
Lord Seong,
how does it feel to become
a true royal agent?
A true royal agent.
It is not half bad.
You have returned.
I am actually...
Have you decided on the boy's name?
Oh, his name.
His name is Yunsu, Jeong Yunsu.
So that baby is...
He is Sawol's baby.
Raise your sister's baby well.
Yes, sir.
I will never forget your kindness.
We are returning to Hanyang.
Thank you for everything.
Uh, sure.
What are you waiting for? Come.
What?
Sir, am I not fired
from the royal agent's entourage?
Oh, I'm not sure.
If she believed Chunsam
was a royal agent and trusted him,
that means he conducted himself
like a royal agent.
Why not forgive him this once?
Should I or not?
Fine. I will forgive you for Dain.
Sir!
Let go of me!
That hurts!
- I love you.
- Let go of me! You're heavy!
All the gold is gone.
Burn this place down and leave no trace.
What's wrong?
We should say goodbye here.
What do you mean? Say goodbye?
The palace is nearby.
My role ends here.
We shall meet again, so you should go.
Lady Dain, if you leave now,
all the glory will go to Lord Seong.
If it hadn't been for the two of us,
he couldn't have returned
to Hanyang alive.
Hey.
Chunsam, thank you.
Goodbye.
Lady Dain, are you really leaving?
Lady Dain!
Come.
Your Majesty, Royal Agent Seong Igyeom
has returned from the secret mission.
Stand.
I can see from your face
the hardship you have suffered.
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
I worry your dragon gown will be soiled.
I am very proud of having
a subject as you.
Come.
I want to hear your story.
Isn't he?
Wasn't he an assistant advisor?
That moron was the royal secret agent?
Come.
Tell me the truth of this case.
Sheriff Kang Inchung
and his son Kang Jonggil
built vast wealth with the gold
they mined illegally.
In that process, numerous men
were forced into hard labor
and lost their lives.
Royal Secret Agent Park Cheolgyu
discovered this
and lost his life to them.
And we discovered something peculiar.
Peculiar?
They were sending
some of the gold to someone.
Who were they sending them to?
I interrogated, but they refused to speak.
However, the man who received the gold
must be the owner of the gold mine.
He had private soldiers
manage his illegal mine,
so he must be a powerful man.
Only the sheriff and his son
know the identity of that man.
Where are they now?
They have been taken
to the Royal Investigation Bureau.
Prepare a royal interrogation.
We must find out who he is.
Yes, Your Majesty.
What do you want to do the most now?
You have worked hard,
so you may ask anything of me.
I am immensely grateful
of Your Majesty's kindness.
Your words are enough of a reward.
Are you being honest?
However, if I may ask of one thing...
Yes, speak.
I would like to eat as much as I could.
What?
This is His Majesty's reward
so enjoy yourselves.
Lord Jang, where are you going?
This is not my reward to enjoy.
What will happen to Dain?
She will be a guest at my house for now.
Dain deserves great credit.
I am aware.
Enjoy the feast and rest well.
Thank you.
Sir, can I really eat that?
It is a royal order. Let us eat.
Let me pour you a drink.
Come to think of it,
I never had the chance to thank you.
We are of same age,
why not be friends?
When we are not on duty, we can relax.
Yes, Lord Seong.
Don't be like that. Relax.
This is me being relaxed.
Anyway, thank you.
You could have just returned to Hanyang.
I was about to.
But?
Dain stopped me.
She insisted on rescuing you.
I asked Dain about you once.
What did she say?
She said you treat
your subordinates as your friends
and protect the weak despite danger.
Oh,
Dain is good at reading people.
Don't you agree, Chunsam?
She must be. She saw the side of you
I never saw my entire life.
You.
You haven't forgotten the promise
you made me, have you?
No. Do you still believe
your father was innocent?
Yes.
When I was the sheriff of Okgu
ten years ago,
your father Prince Hwiyeong
retired to his hometown.
Governor Jang,
I was told that foreign vessels have been
seen often in the coastal waters of Okgu,
and that robbers have been
wreaking havoc on land.
We are making every effort to rebuild,
but as you well know,
the militia has been long dissolved,
so we are desperately short of soldiers
to focus on defense.
We cannot let this be.
Do you have a solution?
Instead of waiting for someone's help,
should we not grow our own strength?
Prince Hwiyeong used his own wealth
to provide military training
for the people.
That was the seed of his own ruin.
A vile rumor began spreading in Hanyang.
It said Prince Hwiyeong was headed
for Hanyang
with his army to begin a rebellion.
My father would have never done that.
But the world does not say that.
Those are the words of people
who wish to forget and bury his death.
If I can find the truth,
I will do anything.
I learned who escorted Prince Hwiyeong.
He witnessed the death
of your father firsthand.
His name is Kim Myeongse.
He is the governor of Jeolla Province.
Kim Myeongse.
Governor of Jeolla Province.
Send me there.
Do you think
you can get the answer you want there?
You stay put.
I have a plan.
What is that plan?
A new royal secret agent will
take this mission.
A new royal agent?
Who is that?
Is he trustworthy?
That is none of your concern.
It is late.
Let's go in.
As a royal secret agent, Assistant Advisor
Seong Igyeom of
the Office of Special Advisors
discovered the truth behind
the missing royal agent, Park Cheolgyu,
and corrected the crimes of the corrupt
official Kang Inchung
and his son Kang Jonggil who stole
from people and violated the law.
Seong Igyeom will be appointed
as a special advisor
as a reward for his service.
Additionally, Royal Agent Park Cheolgyu
will get a posthumous promotion
and his son,
even if he has not reached adulthood,
will be appointed to a position
after the mourning period.
- We are immensely grateful, Your Majesty.
I heard you have refused food or water.
Are you regretting your past?
Regret?
Yes, I should regret
not killing you when I had the chance.
Everyone who is born must die.
However, one must die
with an honor as a man,
not as a creature lower than a beast.
If I tell you the truth,
do you have the power to spare our lives?
If you reveal the man behind you,
you will escape death.
Do you expect me to believe that?
You are naive.
I do not know who is behind you.
But do you not see?
You have been abandoned.
Reconsider.
You are running out of time.
Father,
are you just going to
let them torture you to your demise?
Wait.
He will not let us die.
You were careless. That's unlike you.
I apologize.
There will be a royal interrogation.
They will not be able to endure it.
Pay them a visit.
I will, Lord Kim.
PART 2 WILL SHORTLY BEGIN.
Come! I have miracle salves from China!
Magical salves to turn old woman's skin
into baby skin!
Don't miss this once in a lifetime chance!
Come and see.
What is that?
If I may tell you about this,
if you put this salve on your skin,
it will become soft and smooth
as a baby's bottom.
Try it.
How do you like it?
Sir!
You're home.
I'm hungry. Let us eat.
Sure. Go inside.
Someone has already made dinner.
Who?
Lord Seong!
Lord Seong, congratulations.
Chunsam told me
you are now a special advisor.
Yes, but why were you in there?
You must be hungry. Let us go inside.
What are you waiting for? Eat.
What is going on?
What do you think? It's a happy occasion.
You have been promoted.
Eat. It is getting cold.
I cannot eat with your staring.
Oh, enjoy your meal.
I thought I would never see you again.
Were you disappointed?
In that case, would you like me to stay
with you forever?
Are you all right?
You sure are Honglang the courtesan.
What are you saying?
Tell me.
What are you trying to gain
by winning my favor?
Actually,
Royal Secretary Jang is searching for
a royal agent to send to Jeolla Province.
I thought it could help you,
so I wanted to tell you about it.
I am not interested
in being a royal agent.
But he said an even higher position
will be awarded.
An even higher position?
Yes.
And if you go on that mission,
I would like to join you.
You don't want me?
You did play a key role
in the last secret mission,
so having you will not be a hindrance,
but you already know
how dangerous it can be.
I do.
But I have trained in martial arts
since I was a child,
so I can protect myself.
How about archery?
I will learn.
That can't be so hard.
How will you learn?
You must teach me.
Me?
Yes. You killed that giant wild boar
with a single arrow.
If I need to learn it, I must learn it
from the best archer in Joseon.
True.
Fine. I will teach you.
Lady Dain, where are you going?
Chunsam, you should eat up.
What?
Sir, what is Lady Dain up to?
How odd.
She wants to join me on my secret mission.
What? You are going on a secret mission?
No, I did not...
If I am to go on a secret mission,
she will join me.
What has gotten into her?
I know.
You do? What is it?
You don't understand women at all.
You must understand the hidden meaning.
The hidden meaning?
She will follow you to the end,
even if it means death.
She's into you.
Wait, Into me?
Lady Dain is deep into you.
That's it.
No!
It can't be.
As you've ordered,
I looked into Seong Igyeom.
Seong Yongjae?
Is he Seong Yongjae's son?
Do you know him, Father?
I do, of course I do.
He was the chief censor of the Office
of Censors with the late king.
Now I can see he takes after his father.
He has the trust of the king, so he will
become a problem for us in the future.
How about framing him for a crime
to nip him in the bud, Father?
Do you know the easiest method
of beating your enemy?
It's having that enemy be on my side.
Take the bow and arrow.
If you hold it too close to your body,
the string will hit your sleeve.
But if you hold it too far away,
your wrist will suffer,
making it difficult to pull the string.
I am ready.
Stand with your feet spread apart.
And straighten your entire body.
Press against the ground with your toes
and concentrate your strength
on your calves, thighs, and rear.
You must have
a strong lower body to shoot arrows.
Yes.
Lift your left hand up to your forehead,
and pull the string with your right hand
back to your shoulder, behind the ear.
Inhale and hold.
Hold and squeeze your anus.
Pardon me?
Focus.
Do you see that target?
Yes, I do.
Do not let your arms sway
because you're tired.
Hold that position.
Aim the tip of the arrowhead
at the target.
And shoot.
Did you shoot with your eyes closed?
Do you really think so?
I did everything you said.
You must focus. Focus!
I am focusing.
Again.
Shoot.
Again, again.
Again.
This is the last one.
If you have a clear idea of what
you want to hit, you can do better.
What you are trying to hit
is not that tree.
Imagine about what you want to hit.
I hit it!
You missed the target,
but that is good.
Yes.
What did you imagine?
You.
How dare she!
Does it hurt?
Your hand
is as rough as your personality.
It is not your concern.
Take it.
What is it?
It is a salve.
If you put it on, your skin
will be as smooth as a baby's bottom.
What?
I'm sure if you apply it,
your hand will get better.
It smells wonderful.
Thank you, Lord Seong.
I thought about it,
and I am not going
on the secret mission with you.
But why?
Why won't you go?
I just don't want to.
Now that you have been promoted,
you have a bright future ahead of you.
So you want to stay in the government,
get involved in verbal disputes,
and enjoy a life of luxury?
But you've seen
how many people
outside Hanyang are suffering.
I meant even if I do
go on a secret mission,
I cannot go with you.
But you said you were
able to do your job because of me.
You said I deserve credit.
Yes, I did.
So why not?
Why can't I go with you?
I do not wish to put you
in that kind of danger again.
And...
Because I said so!
Lord Seong, why won't you finish
what you were saying?
Oh, this is why I am not going.
If I go with you, there will be
so many things for me to pay attention to.
Look what just happened.
You are making me very uncomfortable!
Lord Seong!
Lord Jang!
What is it?
Kang Inchung and his son
took their own lives.
What?
Lord Kim!
It is you.
Have you heard of the news
of the prisoners taking their own lives?
That is why we are here
having a discussion.
Have a seat.
We must run autopsies
to learn how they died.
The investigation has finished.
It's finished?
They took their own lives,
afraid of the royal interrogation.
So why the uproar?
They were bound to die.
What would you do if they were murdered?
Who would kill them?
The man who does not wish
for the truth to be revealed.
I will tell His Majesty
and check the bodies.
There is no use for that.
The bodies have been torn apart
and discarded.
If you want to see their heads,
go out to the market.
Lord Seong, I will do anything you ask.
I will practice my archery and...
What's wrong?
They are...
Something is wrong.
Dain, return home.
Will you let this be?
They were not the kind of men
who would take their own lives.
Enough.
The Chief State Councilor is behind this.
If you raise an issue,
he will take it as a personal attack.
You are no longer a royal agent.
Focus on your new position.
Royal agent.
Will becoming a royal agent change things?
I heard you are looking for a royal agent.
I am looking for a royal agent
to send to the south.
Who told you that?
Dain told me.
She said that His Majesty promised
an even higher position as a reward.
Dain said that?
What else did she say?
Did she tell you she will join you?
What? How did you know?
Dain took advantage of you.
What?
She has a personal goal
so turn her down.
What is that personal goal?
Do not concern yourself with that.
I will deal with Dain.
You may return home.
She tried to take advantage of me?
Assistant Advisor Seong.
I guess I should call you
Special Advisor Seong.
My father wishes to see you very much.
The Chief State Councilor?
Father, I brought
Special Advisor Seong Igyeom with me.
Enter.
Did you ask for me?
Sit down.
You've become a different man
after your secret mission.
I am pleased to say that I see ambition
in your eyes that wasn't there before.
Why have you summoned me?
I will tell you.
You may not know yet,
but a man needs great power
to accomplish great deeds.
Do you know where that power comes from?
I haven't given it much thought yet.
It comes from connections.
Join my side.
Miok, are you out there?
Yes, Father.
Come in.
Introduce yourself to him.
I am Kim Miok.
She is my youngest daughter.
She has reached the marriageable age,
but finding the right man for her
has not been easy.
Pardon me?
Becoming my son-in-law
will ensure a bright future for you.
Be all you can under my wing.
I...
Father, don't you think it's too sudden
for him to give you an answer?
Was I too haste?
I will give you two days.
There is no need to ponder over it
so decide quickly.
You're back.
Lord Seong.
Have you looked into it?
Why were they beheaded?
What is wrong?
I had forgotten
what kind of person you are.
You have a knack for mesmerizing people.
Pardon me?
Why did you say you wanted to join me
on a secret mission?
That is because I want to be of help.
You are a pathological liar.
I will not be going
on a secret mission with you.
Lord Seong, wait.
Actually...
Is anyone home?
Is this Lord Seong Igyeom's home?
It is. What brings you here?
What's happening?
Lady Miok.
What brings you here?
Did your father send you?
No. I wanted to pay you a visit.
I guess you must move first.
Do not worry.
My father will find a place for you.
But I...
Will you have me stand here?
Pardon my rudeness. Do come in.
Sit down.
What brings you here?
I wanted to see
what kind of a person you are.
Me?
As you can see, I am not much.
That is fine.
As you may have guessed,
there are many men who wish to marry me.
They came not for me but for my father.
But you were different.
How was I different?
When my father offered his own daughter,
you hesitated, without any signs of joy.
I did?
Take your time and decide.
But I wanted to tell you
that I have made up my mind.
What are you doing?
I shall go.
With marriage, swifter the better.
I shall wait for your answer.
Sir, marriage?
Who is she?
She is the Chief State Councilor's
youngest daughter,
so why would I refuse to marry her?
What? Just like that?
That's great news.
You got promoted,
and now you're getting married.
Congratulations.
Anyone can be a royal agent.
But I didn't need a royal agent.
I needed you.
Sir?
What is going on right now?
I couldn't have done it without you.
I have questions
about the prisoners' deaths.
They took their own lives,
and they were beheaded.
Who found the bodies?
The guard who was on duty.
I would like to speak to him.
He took a sick day.
Tell me where he lives.
I will go and visit him.
What are you staring at?
Doesn't he look familiar?
That is the leader of the gang of bandits
who is wanted.
A gang of bandits?
Yes, they only rob rich noblemen
in the countryside.
And they give out a portion
of the properties they steal
and win people's favor.
He is clever.
Yes, I thought so too.
Some even help them hide.
What is his name?
The noblemen call him Docheok.
Docheok?
Please excuse me.
I will visit the guard who was on duty.
Thank you.
Doesn't he look familiar?
You are thinking of the same man,
aren't you?
It's Ibeom.
While I am away in Hanyang,
prepare yourself.
What?
When I return after I pass the state exam,
I will persuade Father
and bring you with me to Hanyang.
You can study there
and take the state exam.
I wouldn't dare.
The world is changing.
There will come a day when anyone,
even if your mother is a peasant,
can have an opportunity to accomplish
anything they want.
Do you really think so?
Of course, it won't come on its own.
We must work toward it.
Don't you agree?
Lord Seong!
Ibeom, she is my woman.
Look after her for me until I return.
I will. Do not worry.
His age is over twenty,
and his height is six and a half feet.
He has dark eyebrows with sharp eyes.
He robbed noblemen
in Chungcheong and Jeolla Provinces.
Should you see him, report
to the government office with haste.
Sir, I think it is Lord Ibeom.
What should we do?
Make things right.
Robbery cannot change the world.
Lord Jang, Lord Seong Igyeom is here.
Let him in.
Is someone here?
Yes, a young man.
His name is Seong something.
Lord Seong Igyeom?
What brings you here at this hour?
I have something urgent
to discuss with you.
Okay, go ahead.
Appoint me as a royal agent again.
Royal agent?
What is the reason?
I heard His Majesty
is searching for a royal agent.
Wouldn't a man with experience
be better for the job than a novice?
That is true, but you have been promoted,
and you've won His Majesty's trust,
so why do you want to be a royal agent?
Have you heard of a man called Docheok?
Docheock? Of course I have.
He is wanted in the entire country.
He is my younger brother.
What? Younger brother?
How can he be your younger brother?
Is there anyone else who knows of this?
No.
You must never speak of it.
There will be those who will use
your flaw to destroy you.
Most of all, it is because
you have won His Majesty's trust.
I will not forget.
I will tell His Majesty
and set an appointment,
so you should return home for now.
Thank you, Lord Jang.
Sir, you are going to work already?
Did you sleep well last night?
Pack your things.
We will be gone for a long time
so check around the house too.
Yes. What?
Sir, it's not that, is it?
What do you mean?
You're not
going on a secret mission, are you?
What secret mission?
Secret mission.
I must have lost my mind.
We barely came back alive,
so what secret mission?
We can't do that.
You are correct.
So hurry up and get ready.
Sir!
What do you mean by that?
We are going on a secret mission.
If you want to go, go by yourself.
I can't go.
No, I won't.
What?
It's not a secret mission.
It's a death trap.
Would you like to try the death trap?
I'm not going!
You!
I'll see you later.
Do you still have
some unfinished business with me?
I came to negotiate with you.
Negotiate?
ROYAL SECRET AGENT
Royal Secret Agent Seong Igyeom, go down
to Chungcheong and Jeolla Provinces
where robbers are raising havoc
and console the people.
What is it you want?
There is someone I must meet.
Take me with you.
I do not want her companionship.
I thought you wanted to bring her.
Maybe I wasn't myself.
Compared to you, I have much to learn.
Who's next?
Will you seduce a princess?
How dare you!
I received a report of a robbery
of a nobleman's house in Chungju.
Start your investigation there.
From those of noble blood to their slaves,
everyone was murdered.
The murderers are a gang of bandits!
Sir, do you really think Lord Ibeom
is responsible?