[English subtitles are available]
Reiner!
Eren!
We have to stop now.
I don't have any strength left.
I don’t think Reiner…will come to kill us.
Let's go back.
Back to our home.
Reiner...
See you around.
Protect the airship from the enemy below!
All the ammunitions should be used against the enemy!
Finally...
They're retreating.
...’Are we safe now?
They escaped?
Gabi!
Eren Yeager!
I won't let you get away!
I will definitely kill you!
♫ Let's start a new life from the darkness ♫
♫ Until the light reveals the end ♫
♫ Sinister faces, growing curses ♫
♫ This is my last war ♫
♫ Angels playing disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Angels planning disguised
with devil's faces ♫
♫ Children cling to their coins
squeezing out their wisdom ♫
♫ Destruction and regeneration ♫
♫ You are the real enemy ♫
(#68 Assassin's Bullet)
I can't believe how messy you are.
You look like you just fell
in a pile of shit.
Eren.
Captain...
It's been a while, Eren.
You're as easy to kick as always.
I’ll put you under arrest.
Then we can talk.
I don't mind.
But everything is like
what I wrote in my letter.
You should’ve agreed by now.
You’ve got the same look
as those jerks whom
I'm sick of seeing in the underground city.
I didn’t expect you’d end up like this.
You, too.
Are you happy?
Everything went according to your plan.
Don't let them escape!
Shoot them down as many as you can!
Get in! Hurry!
Let them know that none of their
weapons can shoot down this airship!
Jean!
You should get in now!
I'll cover for you!
I'm counting on you,
Commander Lobov!
I told you, I'm just a new recruit!
We no longer need Garrison!
Neither do we need those old money-suckers!
Jean!
Hold on!
Called the roll yet?
We're still waiting for
Squad Lima in the front.
We've currently confirmed six deaths.
I see...
Shit!
Just compare it to the losses
we caused to the enemy.
It's a huge victory!
The new Eldian empire's first battle
has ended with a huge victory!
Let’s cheer for it!
That's how we pay tribute to
our six fallen heroes!
First battle, huh...
Just how long will it last?
Just... how many more do we need to kill?
For now, once again, we survived this one,
though it’s not fair to our lost friends...
But you guys are special to me.
That's how I feel.
That hurts, idiot.
Don't hug people with that
lump of iron on.
What's that, Jean?
The real idiot is the guy who tries
to groom a fresh beard.
I’m referring to you! Idiot!
Huh?
He's right, you know?
It's not like you can eat
a beard or anything.
Huh?!
Anyway, when will we eat?
Wait until we get to the island, okay?
What a useless commander officer!
Gabi!
Gabi! Wait!
Let’s stop.
The enemies can fly;
it's pointless to run after them.
You understand, right?
But Zofia...
Her torso got crushed by falling rubble.
I was sitting right next to her.
Udo tried to save Zofia.
But he got stomped by the panicking crowd.
He got stomped over and over
until his head got crushed completely.
The two gate guards scolded me.
It's all because I tried to go back
to the plaza.
They were so desperate to warn me,
an Eldian, about how dangerous it is.
And then...
They got shot by the woman
on the rooftop and died.
I'm an Eldian born in this internment zone.
People would spit at me when
they see me walking around town.
I had a lot of awful
experience here, but...
That's exactly why I must work hard.
I wanted to prove to the world
that Eldians were good people.
I believed that the time would come
when I could be proud of this Eldian armband.
That's why I was able to work
so hard until now.
But it's all destroyed now.
This internment zone...
This place is my home, and
it's the home of people I love.
How am I supposed to forgive
those who trample over it?
Will you still ask me to stop
running after them despite that?
Mr. Zeke was killed in front of us.
We couldn't do anything.
We don't even know
why we had to go through that…
Why, Reiner?
Why did my mom have to be
eaten by a Titan that day?
It's because they were trampled.
Our enemies got attacked by Marley
Warriors and many died.
And this must be their revenge.
Did you see that?
No... I didn’t.
Neither did I.
Our enemy were originally the island
devils threatening world peace, right?
Didn't you study?
They're savage devils who deserve
to die, as they always have had.
They're different from us.
I'm just like you, Reiner.
Be it on the other side of the sea
or inside the wall,
we're the same.
Squad Lima?
Alright, all on board now.
Tell the control room that
it's time to rise and withdraw!
Yes, sir!
A child?!
I hit him...
It's still... connected.
Gabi!
What are you planning to do?!
It's this trigger...
If I pull this hard...
Gabi... are you going...
...to get on that ship?
I'm going to kill all of those island devils.
You will just get yourself killed, idiot!
Tell my parents,
Reiner and everyone else,
that I fought until the end.
Even if we can't win now...
those who are still alive will surely
carry on my will.
Falco!
Gabi!
What are you two doing?!
Brother...
See you, Falco.
You are... a good guy.
You must save Gabi
from our bleak future.
Falco!
Falco?!
Why?!
The one who inherits the Armored Titan...
is me!
I just heard something.
Hey, quiet down!
Raise your voice!
It's our huge victory!
Hey!
By the way, have
you seen Lobov yet?
No, but he should’ve been here by now.
Sasha!
You bitch!
Sasha! Hey!
Stay with us!
Hey!
You're so loud...
Is the food... ready yet?
Get a tourniquet! We must
cover her wound! Hurry!
Okay!
Sasha! Hang in there! We’ll reach the island soon!
Meat...
Jean.
These two got up here using Lobov's
vertical maneuver gear.
I'm going to throw them out.
No objections, right?
Can throwing some kids out of an airship...
... stop all this bloodshed?
What happened to Braun and Grice?
Well...
They ran off on their own and
haven't returned since then.
Pieck...
Commander...
Now I remember.
That Marleyan soldier who led the Warrior
unit and trapped me and Galliard in that hole.
I saw her
three years ago.
After Reiner and the Warrior unit
retreat from the island...
She was a member of the first survey
fleet that was sent to Paradis island.
From the missing survey ship?
Yes.
And moreover...
That beard didn’t fit her.
Hey, how long are you going to wear it?
Really?
People seem to like it, though.
They're still yelling there?
Don't touch me, you devils!
We haven't lost yet!
Our folks will carry on
War Chief Zeke's will!
Gabi, stop it!
What are you planning to do with her, Jean?
We, the true Eldian, will wish you a horrible death.
Tell that to your ring-leader
once you kill me!
I will bring you to him.
Just try to say the same thing to him.
How did you figure out it was her?
That's because...
I was quite interested in her.
Because she...
...was one of Zeke's followers.
Gabi...? Falco?
Why are you here?
...What do you mean, why?
...Why are you here, Mr. Zeke?
So you are alive!
But, to think that you got
captured by these devils...
Who are these brats?
They killed Lobov and got here
using his equipment.
And then this girl shot Sasha.
It doesn't seem like she can make it...
I'm leaving the rest to you, Onyankopon.
Roger that, Ms. Hange!
So, did everything really go
according to your plan?
Zeke Yeager.
It was good for the most part.
But we made some mistakes.
Mr. Zeke...?
Who are these kids?
Mistakes.
Yelena!
Weren't you supposed to restrain
the Jaw and the Cart?!
Some of our friends died
because of you!
I'm sorry.
I've certainly trapped those two
down the hole, but...
That was my fault.
And the Beast threw more pellets
at us also because of them, huh?
That was quite of an improv act
for a clown.
Don't you agree, Beardy?
Don't glare at me like that, Levi.
What would you do if I wet my pants?
You're quite an actor yourself.
Considering you must've wanted
to kill me right there when you could.
I'm the type who likes to save
the best for last.
I want to savor the taste well, after all.
We killed the Marleyan army officers and
destroyed its primary naval fleets and ports.
We should be able to buy time for now.
You mean the time until the rest
of the world attack Paradis island?
We risked our lives to get you back every
time you get captured by the enemy.
No matter how many of us
died because of it.
But despite that, you went ahead to
go with a plan to make yourself a hostage.
As you wish, we have no
choice but to follow along.
You trust us, but unfortunately,
We’ve lost our trust in you.
But now that we have both
the Founding Titan and a Titan of royal blood,
all of those precious sacrifices will surely
bear fruit and bring freedom to Eldia.
Sasha...
She's dead.
Connie.
Sasha...
...what were...
...her final words?
She said... meat.
I brought meat from
the officers' storehouse.
It's fine!
Once we retake the land, we can
raise cows and sheep again.
Eren...
Sasha died because you got
the Survey Corps involved, you know?
♫ In an instant ♫
♫ In an abandoned world ♫
♫ If you can fly, please tell him ♫
♫ Many birds with burnt wings ♫
♫ Scattering ashes and smiling ♫
♫ I wish someone ♫
♫ Spreading the proof of my existence ♫
♫ Even if my body turns into ashes
I will be immortal ♫
Maybe there was another way.
However, we can't change the past.
We have no choice but to continue
to move forward on this path.
Next Episode: Volunteer