#ROMANTIC
#FREE-SPIRITED
#GIRLCRUSH
#VOLUNTARILY SINGLE
#IN A LONG-TERM RELATIONSHIP
HOW IS YOUR LOVE?
LOVESTRUCK IN THE CITY
We're drinking hard liquor today,
so we'll keep this wine.
Hey.
That bottle looks familiar.
How does it feel not to be an alcoholic?
When was I an alcoholic, you rascal?
What would they think of me?
-Let's enjoy the barbecue.
-Okay.
You must be upset
because of that camera thief.
I'll pour you a glass.
Hey, don't you dare drink.
You can't.
Not until you forget about her.
Not even one sip.
Put that down.
All right, then. Exclude the alcoholic.
-Bottoms up!
-Give him some water at least.
Here.
I'm sorry.
All right.
FF!
-Friends forever!
IPG!
-Interact! Prosper! Good luck!
HER!
-Hopeful, energetic, rich!
Do it.
YHUD!
-Youth has ups and downs!
-Hey!
-Cheers.
"Hey"?
By the way, what did you mean?
When did you take off your ring?
Why bother asking?
He threw it out after taking
that thief to the police.
"You're as good as dead to me.
I'll throw you out with this ring."
Good job.
Jae-won.
To be honest,
I can't even imagine how you feel.
-So let's give him a drink.
-No, don't.
Will you pick him up from the police?
I said no.
Don't you do that again.
What do you think, Ms. Lee?
You seem to enjoy
sharing stories about your love life.
You seem to enjoy keeping yours secret.
Yes, I tend to be careful.
I don't tell anyone about it.
I see. I was wrong.
I should've bled to death
without anyone knowing.
Instead, I caused a huge scene
and bawled in front of everyone.
I'm sorry.
I'm…
I was wrong.
What's wrong?
I think he has anger issues.
-I--
-That's not it.
He's just sick. Be considerate.
Eun-o, he's very shook up
because of the camera thief.
Please understand.
Jae-won, you'll find a better woman soon.
Right, your necklace.
-Right.
-What?
-Right, your necklace.
-What are the rings for?
-A new boyfriend?
-Why didn't you tell us?
Let me see.
Mind your own business.
Even if I get a boyfriend,
I'll never tell you guys.
You see,
unlike someone,
I will keep my private life private.
-Where are you going?
-The bathroom.
Come on, we're friends.
Why can't you tell us about it?
-She's so secretive.
-Even strangers will tell us.
-I bet.
-What's wrong with her?
How did he know I lived here?
He didn't look shocked to see me.
He must know everything.
But how much does he know?
Right.
I brought Eun-o's proposal
and the bidding request.
I should give them to her.
I'll do it.
I need to use the bathroom anyway.
-Will you?
-Yes.
What is that?
-Password, please.
-It's 0660 and an asterisk.
Remember the proposals you gave me?
Everyone liked it.
Kyeong-jun thinks I'm here
because of this.
You seem to be close to my cousin.
I had no idea.
How fascinating.
I can't believe I've come to O3
with these request papers.
Ms. Lee Eun-o must be a marketer.
I can't work with you.
Of course. Me neither.
Then why are you here?
I wanted to see if this Lee Eun-o was
the one I met at the police station.
If you're done, leave.
By the way,
is that all you got to say?
What do you want to hear?
What should I hear to soothe my anger?
I don't think anything can soothe me,
but say something.
Explain to me at least
why you can't tell your friends about us,
why we broke up like that,
and why you hid from me
even when you heard from Kyeong-jun
I'd been looking for you. Explain.
This is driving me crazy.
So this is what Lee Eun-o's like.
Seon-a wasn't like that.
You…
Everything was fake.
If you were Seon-a,
you would have forced yourself to speak.
Seon-a would've been honest with me.
And that's what I liked about her.
That's why I didn't understand
the way you chose to break up with me.
Seon-a wouldn't have just disappeared.
She wouldn't have left an absurd message
about stealing my cameras.
If Seon-a wanted to break up with me,
she would've at least
said it to my face.
She's not a coward like you.
Everything about you was fake
from the start.
You were a liar.
-How did it go?
-I gave her all the materials.
You can explain the details. I'm leaving.
-Bye.
-Already?
-See you next time.
-Okay.
Bye.
-I'll call you.
-Go home safely.
He's so cool.
He's totally my style.
Rin-i, let's go.
-We can see Eun-o tomorrow.
-Okay.
Hold on.
Do I have to clean this up on my own?
Fine. Ready or not, rock-paper-scissors!
Let's go! Let's hurry!
Have fun cleaning and good night.
Good night, Pushover.
Who the hell are you?
-You little…
-He always plays rock.
I know. That fool always does.
Hey. They all left.
You gave Kyeong-jun my proposals,
didn't you?
He has many connections
and is the most successful one here.
I asked him to introduce some companies.
It's all because you're good.
If you were incompetent,
he wouldn't have done so.
See? Mr. Park came here right away.
I can only bid for it
when I'm competent enough.
Whatever. I feel so miserable.
Why do you feel miserable?
It's not what you think.
You just downed a million won.
If you're done, leave.
What do you want to hear?
-Take that!
-Stop it.
When will we finish cleaning up?
Eun-o, let's do the dishes.
You can't leave everything here…
Eun-o!
Don't you know how expensive this is?
How could you finish this precious…
Where did she go?
Don't.
Come on.
Long time no see, Eun-o.
Hello.
-Where are you going?
-To see Geon.
-Why?
-Because I was kicked out.
Why?
Imagine if you're my dad.
Would you like me
when I drink every day?
But why would you go to Geon
after getting kicked out?
Because there's nowhere else to go.
He lives at my house.
I know. That's why I'm going there.
Goodbye, then.
Hey.
You think I'm crazy, don't you?
What?
No, not at all.
I always thought you were cool.
I'm obviously a crazy woman.
Do you think I'm cool?
All right.
But
this cool woman didn't get over Geon yet.
Why?
Because he told me a long time ago
that even if we break up,
if I ever miss my mom terribly,
I could visit him anytime.
Isn't he amazing?
He's a decent guy.
You like him, don't you?
What?
Let me tell you right now.
If you ever marry Geon,
you're dead meat.
Why would I marry him?
Don't say such disgusting things.
Do you think Geon is disgusting?
He's not disgusting.
Geon is
very sexy.
You must be crazy. Why did you hit me?
To be honest, I've always hated your guts.
What in the world are you saying?
Why do you hate me?
Because Geon likes you.
I like him too.
We're close friends. It's obvious.
Hey.
Just go.
I'm going to do a palm blast,
so leave.
Here I go.
Palm…
Blast!
Are my hands frozen from the cold?
Then…
Hold on. One more time.
Palm
blast!
You're hammered.
You won't be able to find my house.
What? Why isn't it working?
What? Hey.
Hey, where do you live?
Why isn't she answering me?
Why am I still here?
Is that the right way?
Did Eun-o go to take a bus again?
Why does she ride the bus
whenever she's drunk?
Everything was fake.
If you were Seon-a,
you would have forced yourself to speak.
Seon-a would've been honest with me.
And that's what I liked about her.
She's not a coward like you.
Everything about you was fake
from the start.
You were a liar.
-Isn't this too small for me?
-It looks fine.
-Who could that be?
-Door opening.
Baby, I'm home. Are you surprised to see…
It's not like you didn't know
that I fell out of love.
No, you never told me that.
I kept sending signals
that you were annoying.
You're too boring and ordinary.
I feel suffocated when I'm with you.
Did you really not know,
or did you just want to deny it?
I'm starting work in a week.
What am I supposed to do?
DAESEONG MOTEL
What should we do?
Ms. Lee,
did you not get the notice
that we canceled your employment?
Sorry?
What do you mean?
The HR Team couldn't reach you.
They texted you
and even sent you an e-mail.
Hello, everyone.
I'll be working with you from today.
My name is Yoon Seon-a.
Did you hear about my interview?
I'll keep that energy up
and always try to help
relieve your stress.
-Nice to meet you.
-Thank you.
What? Fellow newcomer?
We were interviewed together, right?
I hope we get along.
One of the employees'
job transfer to Dubai got canceled,
so she'll be remaining here.
That's why we decided to hire
just one more marketer.
Why…
Why didn't you hire me?
You picked both of us.
Ms. Yoon was in
the same interview group, right?
Both of your applications were excellent.
But her interview score
was higher than yours.
We wanted a new employee
who was full of vigor, determination,
and new energy.
Your answers
were too ordinary.
I'm sorry.
Okay, thank you.
Hello?
Mom, it's me.
Sorry, my phone broke.
Min-su?
Yes, he's doing well. He is.
I know he can't pick up.
Yes.
Mom, Min-su had to go abroad for training.
No.
I'll be fine without him. I'm doing well.
The new job is nice.
Everything is nice.
I'm having so much fun. I love Busan.
Mom.
I have so much to tell you,
but not over the phone.
Yes.
I'll explain everything in person later.
Okay.
What do you mean? I'm not crying.
It's just that hearing your voice
makes me miss you so much.
That day, I rode the bus just like today.
And that bus led me to Jae-won.
I sometimes wonder
what would've happened to me
if I didn't go to that beach.
BIN'S SURFING & RA-RA'S RAMYEON
LOOKING FOR A PART-TIMER
NO HONORIFICS
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS
If you want to eat, sit here.
We have a customer.
What do you want?
Where's the menu?
KALGUKSU
RAMYEON
Ramyeon?
Sure.
Most ordinary people get that.
Ramyeon?
No, hold on.
-I'm not ordinary.
-What?
I…
WONTON MEIN
Hong Kong wonton mein.
Wonton…
-Yuntun mian.
Enjoy.
Do you want more?
Eat slowly.
She's loving it.
Okay.
RA-RA'S RAMYEON
Did you have breakfast?
I haven't eaten much for a week.
Have some more.
Here.
Here are the leftovers.
You finished an entire pot.
That's all we have.
Can I work here?
What?
LOOKING FOR A PART-TIMER
-No.
-Yes.
-Yes. What?
One, two, three.
-Yes.
-We click so well.
-I love you.
I love you too.
All right.
We should know your name then.
What's your name?
Do I
have to tell you?
You don't have to,
but what should we call you?
Pick whatever name you want.
Pick a name you want to be called.
That's when
I thought of Yoon Seon-a.
You're looking very casual today.
Yes. The Marketing Team
doesn't need to meet customers.
If I get the job,
I'll be receiving a uniform.
And I can dye and straighten my hair.
I thought it was most important
to represent myself in this interview.
-Doesn't this look suit me?
-Yes, it does.
-What do you do for fun?
-I dance.
But how can we verify that?
Should I show you, then?
I can show you.
It will be boring without any music.
Mr. Red Tie,
could you turn on some music?
I'll liven up this room.
Let's see.
My playlist is a bit old-fashioned.
It's okay. Any will do.
All right.
This is good.
Could you clap for me, please?
You can call me Yoon Seon-a.
Yoon-seon?
No. Yoon Seon-a.
That's how I became Yoon Seon-a.
And then, I met Jae-won.
A healthy breakup?
Sure.
If it's possible,
I'd like to break up that way.
I didn't mean to leave him like that.
Do you think I enjoyed that breakup?
He was someone I loved.
But I stripped and hit him
and yelled at him to return
everything I gave him.
I didn't want to do that.
The day Jae-won and I agreed to meet here,
I came here with his camera bag.
He left for Seoul in a hurry,
and I wanted to give him back
the cameras he'd left behind.
I was going to come clean.
I just wanted him to say,
"Seon-yeong, don't do this.
I love you."
That's what I wanted to hear.
However,
when I saw him waiting,
I couldn't walk over to him.
I was too scared.
That's why I left that message
that I stole his cameras.
I wanted him to hate me.
I wanted him to curse me.
I wanted him
to forget me.
But I've never heard those words before.
Every time I requested a breakup,
they didn't hesitate
as if they were waiting for that moment.
I didn't want to break up like that.
I didn't want to end it like that.
I just
wanted confirmation
that I was being loved.
I've been betrayed before,
so I know how Jae-won must feel.
I don't know how to confirm their love
or how to break up.
I have no idea.
I still don't know
how I should've broken up with him.
I think I'll never know.
I just
regret it.
I just keep thinking
I shouldn't have done that.
I'm lonely.
Where am I?
Where is the house? I'm exhausted.
I found it!
Kang Geon, let's play!
Isn't it the right place?
Am I wrong?
Then I should keep searching.
It's freezing.
Geon.
Why are you still here?
Palm blast!
That rascal's strong.
You have my respect.
You're incredible. Thank you.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
Ripped by TTEOKBOKKIsubs