♪I can't help but feel a little bit happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little bit nervous♪
♪The earth is spinning because of you♪
♪Without you, the earth will stop♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaves clover♪
♪I dreamt about white-horse carriage
and you became my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Are you the happiness that I'm looking for?♪
♪The doe inside me is lost♪
♪I'll hold your hand and let's count down
to our happiness♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit fragile♪
♪I can't help but be a little bit gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who took away
all of my loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 28=
Director Xu.
(Work Report of the Administration Department)
What's the matter, Mr. Xu?
Who is in charge of the Marketing Department?
Wei Zi Zhao.
What kind of report is this?
Call the Marketing Department to
have a meeting right now.
Yes.
The Marketing Department?
Mr. Xu.
I'm the manager,
Wei Zi Zhao.
Well, the name is just a title.
Call me Brother-in-law.
You look familiar.
Do I?
Mr. Xu, I have one of those faces
that you can randomly see on the streets.
Sorry, I'm late.
Mr. Xu.
Wei...
Zi Zhao.
Wei Zi Zhao.
What kind of report the Marketing Department
has made?
I read no more than three pages
and I have found a few errors
that do not match with the time.
How careless. And it's so messy.
Who made this?
I think it was...
I made it.
No matter who made it.
As a manager,
shouldn't you go through it first?
There is a lot of staff.
I can't keep tabs on everyone.
Yes.
As the department leaders,
you should learn to take responsibility.
Redo it.
Do it yourself.
Don't get others to do your work.
Got it?
Yes.
You're right, Mr. Xu.
Go on.
It's weekend.
Although you're my boyfriend,
you still have to pay me
for overtime work.
Here. Take a look.
You're invited to participate in
the reconstruction of your alma mater's library.
This is awesome!
They sent me the invitation.
But after all,
I've graduated for quite some time.
Shouldn't I give this opportunity
to my fellow juniors
who have
just graduated?
That's very generous of you.
But
you can't miss
this opportunity.
Think about it.
You can go back to your alma mater
and leave your mark there.
That's one way
to set an example to the juniors.
That's what I thought.
Well, what's with that idea
of giving your spot to others?
I just wanted to know what you think.
Does it matter?
Of course.
After I won the Jin An Award,
I once thought
about ending my own life.
You changed my mind.
So
I don't need to tell you
how big of an influence you have on me.
All my previous designs were made
with winning the Jin An Award as my goal.
So I was under
a lot of pressure.
This time,
I want to regain
my original intention
of studying architectural design.
No strings attached.
Not seeking anything in return.
Simply
designing for the sake of passion.
♪Ah~♪
♪We can start again from here♪
Be sure
to follow your heart.
Show them
all of your talents.
♪I got a feeling♪
Well, I'll get everyone
to come back and work overtime.
All right.
♪Should I go or should I let you know♪
♪For you, I let myself go♪
Xiao Ning.
What
is so urgent
that you had to call us back on a weekend?
You'll find out very soon.
Everyone is here, right?
Well, I'll just get right
to the point then.
I'm going to accept the invitation
from University College London
to participate
in the new library construction proposal.
Although this is a charity project,
our design
and the names
of everyone in our team
will forever be engraved
on the walls of the new library.
This is a dreamlike honor
to all designers.
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Help me find
the library project materials
of the National University of Singapore.
Okay, I'm on it.
Man...
She always quarrels with me.
Now that she's gone all of a sudden,
it makes me kind of miss her.
Here.
Okay. Thank you.
Brother Dong.
♪I'm at a loss for words♪
This is the architectural style
that we want.
Jeez.
Replace this light with this.
Okay.
♪Woo~♪
♪My heart beats because you are by my side♪
Manager Wei, you asked for me?
Zhao Yan, come on in.
Come in.
Here's the thing.
Pack your stuff
and move to the top floor.
Why?
Mr. Xu wants you
to move upstairs to be an executive assistant.
Zhao Yan.
During this period of time,
my work...
She's really champing at the bit.
Xu...
Manager Zhao.
Mr. Xu.
Get back to your work.
What is it, darling? Miss me?
Did you have me transferred
to work as an assistant?
I just want
to see you every day.
Did you ask for my opinion?
Isn't it great to work together?
Do you know what is respect?
Come on.
Well, Jiang Xiao Ning
is Gu Chuan's assistant too.
Re...
(Resign)
Resign.
Darling,
get ahold of yourself.
Type the resignation letter yourself.
I'm leaving.
Wait.
I just want
to be able to see you every day.
Was I wrong?
It's all because of Xu Cheng Ran?
No.
Don't deny it.
I've resigned.
Why must you resign?
If I don't,
we'll get a divorce certificate.
Sister Yan Yan.
You don't have to.
Our relationship
is very complicated, you know that?
If he was just my boss,
I'd have no comments
on the job transfer.
But he's now my husband.
He got me transferred
not because
he appreciates my ability
but because he wants to see me often.
Besides,
he didn't even discuss it with me.
Both my life and work.
Double kill.
You
should take a shower
and lie in bed comfortably.
If you can't fall asleep,
think of his goodness.
I think you've
made things too complicated.
I don't think so.
I think
when I got carried away,
I started to take things easy.
Are you really not going to let him come back?
I've changed the passcode of the door.
Stay here for a few more days with me.
Why would this happen?
Cheng Ran
has worked in the company
for sometime.
I think
his performance
didn't go unnoticed.
Today,
we'll do a vote.
Please raise your hand
if you agree that Xu Cheng Ran
will serve as the executive director
and the CEO of the group.
Please raise your hands.
It's unanimously passed.
Really?
It looks like there's no objection.
Since there's no objection,
that speaks a lot
to Xu Cheng Ran's capability.
All right.
It's passed unanimously.
(Statement of Assets and Liabilities
of Reindeer Group)
Mr. Tang.
Mr...
What's the matter?
I have no idea.
Sun.
Are you going out?
Yes.
Director Xu asked to see me.
Anything?
Is he...
Is he going to check the accounts?
That's right.
He wants a thorough check.
I think
it's going to take a while.
I heard
there'll be external audits.
By the way,
do you remember
the funds
I asked you to transfer last month?
What about it?
I transferred out based on the contract.
Can you do me a favor?
Don't bother about the contract.
I'll settle the legal issue.
Can it be processed
as my personal loan?
How is it possible to process such a huge amount
as a personal loan?
Besides,
the Financial Department
doesn't get a say
in the audit.
It's handled by external auditors.
We're only working with them.
Sun.
We're old acquaintances.
Look.
This has nothing to do with that.
All right now.
I'm busy. I have to go now.
How about this, Sun?
Buy me some time
and handle those funds
last.
I'll make up for the amount.
Please, I'm begging you.
Why do you need to do that?
Don't worry about this.
I'll make up for the funds
and rescind the contracts.
Just pretend none of this
ever happened.
Sun.
All right then.
One to two days, tops.
Not for long.
All right.
Thank you, Sun.
I'll return the favor next time.
There's no need for that.
All right now.
Wait for me.
I need to go over now.
All right.
Take care.
Boss said
we'll be able to rest
after pulling a couple of all-nighters.
Thank you.
I knew I'd be put through hell
when I chose to be in this line of work.
What did you say?
It's for our company's performance.
Here.
For the sake of our company,
we...
Don't mind working hard!
That's enough, Wang Kai.
Boss.
I'm just trying to boost morale.
All right.
What happened?
Damn, I was halfway through it.
What's going on?
It's rendered halfway.
Calm down.
Stay calm, guys.
I'll check it out.
What happened?
You don't look good.
I'm fine.
Maybe because the progress is a bit slow.
So I'm feeling a little anxious.
Are you mad?
No.
Was the power outage because of you?
Don't get me wrong.
This time,
it has nothing to do with me.
Thank God.
Although it's slower than expected,
everyone is working hard.
Be patient, all right?
Okay.
What do you want?
(Marriage Certificate)
Please fulfill your obligations.
You can't kick me out of the house.
I reserve all the right for final explanation.
Darling, I'm sorry.
It hurts!
Are you alright?
My foot's hurt.
Slow down.
Let me take a look.
Darling.
I was wrong.
Forgive me.
I promise I won't do it next time.
Next time?
No more next time.
Does it hurt?
A little.
Here.
I bought pizza and fruits.
I thought you don't eat these.
I'm trying now.
After all, I've done things
that are way more dangerous.
What is it?
Loving you.
Ever since I'm with you,
my heart
tends to beat faster.
I couldn't even feel your heartbeat.
Which baby formula
is your baby having?
Baby!
Gu Chuan!
Are you all right?
-Gu Chuan!
-Are you all right?
Gu Chuan!
Are you okay?
Gu Chuan, wake up!
Is he hurt?
Please call 120!
Hello?
Gu Chuan!
Is this 120?
There's been an accident.
It's at the park by the street.
-Please come at once!
-Gu Chuan.
Hurry up.
-Thank you.
Don't fall asleep, all right?
The ambulance will be here soon.
You'll be fine.
You'll be fine, Gu Chuan.
It'll be all right, Gu Chuan.
Yes, a motorcycle.
A motorcycle.
You'll be fine.
Injured patients?
There are two.
How are you feeling?
Don't fall asleep.
Darling, I'm going out.
There's an emergency.
Go faster.
All right.
Where are you?
Gu Chuan got into a car accident.
We're on the way to the hospital.
I'll be right there.
Gu Chuan.
(Emergency)
The surgery went well.
The patient is awake now.
The only thing we can treat
is his physical injuries.
But there are things
that we aren't able to treat.
For his heart problem,
we have to contact Dr. Peer
from the Institute of Science.
I just called.
But no one answered.
You need to get in touch with
this doctor as soon as possible.
Otherwise, he'll be in grave danger.
You may see the patient now.
But don't disturb his rest.
Make sure that the patient
has a calm and stable emotional state.
All right?
Thank you, Doctor.
You're welcome.
Get more rest.
Thank you.
Chuan.
Are you feeling better?
Much better.
You must be very scared.
A little.
Go home and rest.
Xu Cheng Ran
can keep me company.
I want to stay.
Go home.
You can bring over
some stuff I need tomorrow.
Be a good girl.
Go home.
Don't worry.
This has happened
a few times before.
My heart aches all of a sudden.
I have no idea why.
Does it require
an update or something?
What did the doctor say?
Lately,
I haven't been able to reach him.
I've been calling him
just now.
But there was no answer.
Didn't he still say
that your heart problem
can be completely solved
soon enough?
Why the sudden loss of communication?
I've booked
the earliest flight tomorrow
to bring the doctor over.
All right.
Miss Qing Zi.
Mr. Xu.
Sorry to disturb you.
I'm here to see Dr. Peer.
Ms. Qing Zi.
Did something happen?
Dr. Peer
has passed away.
(Intracerebral hemorrhage.)
(He didn't even leave)
(any last words.)
(Miss Qing Zi.)
(I know)
(it's not the right time to say this.)
But this is really urgent.
What about the problems I'm having?
Who will take over
the laboratory?
As far as I know,
the lab funding has been terminated.
I can think of ways
to help with funding.
Everything is open for discussion.
But the lab cannot be shut down.
It's not just for Gu Chuan.
It's the hope of many people.
The core of the lab isn't the funding.
It's Dr. Peer.
The mechanical heart is Dr. Peer's patent.
(It's way ahead)
(of any research institute.)
(So far,)
(no one has been able to come close to his level.)
You're shirking responsibility.
It was you
who replaced Gu Chuan's heart.
You can't just install it
and leave it just like that.
We feel sorry too.
(But it's legal for us)
(to help replace Mr. Gu's heart.)
(Even broad-spectrum drugs)
(may have side effects.)
(Mr. Gu's current situation)
(is the side effect of it.)
(Tell me.)
How long can Gu Chuan's heart last
if there's no upgrade?
According to Dr. Peer,
each time there's a glitch,
it causes damage to the master copy.
So the best way so far
is to live
according to the lifestyle
that the doctor
had previously advised.
That way,
it can maximize its lifespan.
Perhaps, it can last a long time.
(But it may also)
(stop working all of a sudden.)
Banana?
Sure.
Apple?
That's fine too.
We'll go with the tangerine.
Mr. Xu.
Since he's here, you can go back now.
You can change shifts now.
It pains my heart if you get too tired.
All right.
I'll visit you again tomorrow.
Bye, Mr. Xu.
Bye.
You didn't find Dr. Peer?
What is it? Tell me.
Dr. Peer
has passed away.
It was very sudden.
Chuan.
There'll be some other ways.
Really, don't give up.
God must be kidding me.
I couldn't die when I wanted to.
Now that I want to live and he won't let me.
Chuan.
You won't abandon yourself to despair.
No one can tell me
what kind of life
I'm supposed to live.
Does it mean
you're giving up?
I might leave this world
at any time.
Don't do anything stupid.
It's been 10 years.
In the past 10 years,
how many things,
big and small,
have happened?
There were so many times
I thought I wouldn't survive.
I have fought death
so many times.
This time,
I thought
I would be calm like how I was.
But I realized
I couldn't.
Because of Jiang Xiao Ning?
I'm afraid I might just drop dead
and it might happen right in front of her.
I really couldn't imagine
how big of a blow and impact
would this do on her.
She was already
unfortunate enough when she was a kid.
She had to witness
her parents died.
And now,
she finally got over it.
If I...
If I leave quietly,
she'll get anxious looking for me.
It's better not to prolong the agony.
Perhaps,
ending our relationship now
is the best thing to do.
That way,
even when she
learns about my death,
she won't be too sad.
There will be a way.
(That mechanical heart)
(can give you a second life.)
(But you have to understand.)
(It will also bring you the pain)
(you have to endure.)
It's a kind of happiness
when one's heart beats for another person.
But in your case,
that signals danger.
(So in the days to come,)
(you can't let yourself be filled with emotions.)
Gu Chuan.
Ten years ago,
you went your own way
and pushed me away.
Ten years later,
are you still going
to do the same to another girl?
Is that you, Big Brother?
Yes.
♪The destined one♪
From now on,
we'll never be apart again.
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
(Xiao Ning, I'm sorry.)
♪Why does my heart beat so fiercely♪
(Sorry.)
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Who is it♪
(Outpatient)
Where are you?
I brought the dumplings
my aunt made for you.
Come and eat.
I'm at the studio.
How can you be discharged?
Did the doctor allow you?
I can be discharged already.
I'm busy. I'm hanging up.
Boss, please sign this.
The person in charge of each project.
Go to the conference room in five minutes
to report the progress of the project.
Report the progress of the project?
Didn't he say in the previous meeting
that we should all focus
on the library project?
Shoot.
I haven't started working on it.
Do you know what's wrong with our boss?
Why is he a different person all of a sudden?
All of a sudden?
That's because you don't know.
Before you came,
our boss acted like the King of Hell
for a really long time.
His friendliness can only last for so long.
Dong.
Get moving.
You have only five minutes.
It's four and a half minutes.
Four and a half minutes?
Hurry up.
Here's the design.
Give me the design.
Let's begin.
What's the matter?
Should I call your names?
Boss.
The sketch
of the library project
has been revised.
I'll need
your confirmation.
Why are you only asking it now?
You weren't around in the past few days.
Don't you have my WeChat?
I didn't want to disturb you.
I said this before.
The library project is our main project.
We're already behind schedule.
You know there's a problem
and you didn't communicate it at once.
Cheng Dong.
You're not new here.
Do you need me to teach you how to do your job?
Sit down.
I'm going to say this again.
The library project is our top priority.
It has to
be completed on schedule.
Got it?
-Yes.
All right.
Who's next?
Well...
Mr. Gu.
This...
This is my architectural
design plan.
Are you sure you're okay?
I know the status
of my own health.
We can talk about personal matters after work.
Okay, Boss.
Hello.
Need help?
No, you can go.
Cheng Dong, are you done with the work?
Not yet.
You really don't need my help?
Boss said it upsets him to see
too many people around.
But...
I'm going to get the sketches.
(I'll wait for you downstairs.)
(I'll drive you home after you're
done with your work.)
Boss.
It's getting late.
You can go first.
Cheng Dong.
Those comments I made today...
It's all my mistake.
I was too harsh.
You can lead the team
to this project proposal meeting.
Me?
What?
You have no confidence?
It's not that.
Boss, isn't that your project?
It's everyone's work.
Thank you, Boss.
I'll do my best.
I won't let you down.
By the way,
Xiao Ning is still waiting for you outside.
Did you...
I should be having late-night
snacks with friends now.
I'm late already.
Well, I'll get going.
Lock the door and windows
on your way out.
Brother Dong.
Xiao Ning.
You've finished working?
Where's Boss?
He just left.
Left?
Boss told me
that he's having late-night snacks
with friends and left in a hurry.
I see.
It's getting late.
Why don't you go home?
What about I drive you home?
It's fine.
I can call a cab.
Bye, Brother Dong.
Stay safe then.
♪My eyes are tearing up♪
♪I have so much to tell♪
♪The secrets will remain untold♪
♪Make it last forever♪
♪No one walks me home anymore♪
♪Now, there's someone who ties me down♪
♪If you miss it too, it won't feel as lonely♪
♪We'll not forget♪
♪The box will be full of memories♪
♪The meaning will withstand the passage of time♪
♪The lively boy passes by on the car♪
♪The belief when we made our promise♪
♪I was so in love with the silhouette♪
♪We'll meet again if there is no farewell♪
(Boss.)
(You were just discharged.)
(Don't stay up late.)
(Get more rest.)
♪You, who are in my heart♪
♪The person I miss♪
♪Tears drop every morning♪
♪Is there someone♪
♪That you miss so badly late at night♪
♪I was so in love with the silhouette♪
(You don't need to pick me up tomorrow.)
♪I was not brave enough♪
♪I'll stay here, waiting for you♪
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off Guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪