♪I can't help but feel a little happy♪
♪I can't help but feel a little nervous♪
♪The Earth is turning because of you♪
♪Without you, the Earth stops♪
♪You are the rainbow that fills up
the black and white♪
♪I was once obsessed with the legend
of the four-leaf clover♪
♪I dreamt of a white-horse carriage
and you becoming my prince♪
♪Your gaze is too seducing, please save me♪
♪I'm turning into a moth, flying towards the fire♪
♪Your smile is dancing on your lips♪
♪Am I the happiness you're looking for?♪
♪The deerlet inside me is lost♪
♪Holding your hand, let's count down to happiness♪
♪I can't help but feel a little fragile♪
♪I can't help but feel a little gloomy♪
♪The sky is bright because of you♪
♪Without you, the sky is grey♪
♪You are the angel who takes away all loneliness♪
=Miss Crow With Mr. Lizard=
=Episode 27=
Coming.
Why didn't you bring...
Wasn't the meeting for business?
Why did you drink this much?
I'll get you a glass of water.
Drink some water first.
I'm telling you.
Don't play drunk on me.
Yan Yan,
I have something to tell you.
I don't want to listen.
You have to.
Xu Cheng Ran,
you'll regret this tomorrow.
I have to tell you
even if I'll regret it.
I want to ask you,
when will I be able to
get closer to you?
When will I be able to
hold a place in your heart?
Don't you know
clearly about what type of person
I, Xu Cheng Ran, am
and how I treat you?
I've never treated any relationship
as seriously as this one.
I have never treated
any girls like how I treat you.
I'm asking you.
Do you dare to
try this with me?
Do you dare?
Xu Cheng Ran,
say it one more time.
how dare you lying on my bed?
And your clothes...
♪You're the haze in my sky♪
♪A disaster for my clear blue sky♪
♪But you're my most gentle cover♪
♪Blocking out the blinding sunlight♪
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who asked me to love♪
♪I love this bad guy♪
♪I want to rely on you♪
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who asked me to love♪
♪I have no idea♪
♪I won't let go♪
♪You're the villain in my story♪
♪Added funny things to my boring plot♪
♪And the story becomes wonderful all of a sudden♪
♪We're not destined lovers but we
keep getting closer♪
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who asked me to love♪
♪I love this bad guy♪
If you can't drink, don't drink.
♪But who asked me to love♪
♪Who asked me to love♪
♪I have no idea♪
♪I won't let go♪
♪Let go♪
Get up, Ran Ran.
Let me sleep a little longer.
Wake up and look at me.
There's nothing to look at.
Sleep!
Good morning.
Why am I here?
Stop acting.
No...
I think I drank too much last night.
How come I can't
remember anything?
Do you remember
what you said?
Yan Yan,
no matter what I said yesterday,
it was all nonsense,
definitely not telling the truth when drunk.
Don't take it to heart.
Xu Cheng Ran.
Are you making a fool of me?
I really don't remember.
Do I look that easy to fool?
Xu Cheng Ran.
Yan Yan, I really...
I really don't remember
what I said.
Yan Yan.
I dare to.
What do you dare to do?
I dare to try it with you.
What do you want to try?
Whatever you say.
Yan Yan.
Yan Yan, what do you want to try?
I can't recall
what I said yesterday.
Dumb.
An unusual person
has shown up.
A rare sight.
I think you already know
in your heart.
But I still think that
I should tell you myself.
I won.
You came here
for
the sole purpose of
showing me your presence?
It seems you still look down on me.
I'm still
not as good as your godson.
You like him better.
I shouldn't have come.
You can't
talk like that, brat.
Let me tell you.
You have to show me that
you can do it by going back to Reindeer Group.
And you have to show me that you're better than me.
That way you win.
Wait for it.
Do you understand?
Let me
think about it.
Just tell me straight up if you need me.
No need to beat around the bush.
Gu Chuan.
(Hello.)
(The number you have dialed cannot be reached.)
Yan Yan, are you asleep?
(How should I tell Yan Yan)
(that I'm going back to Reindeer Group?)
(Yang Chun Alley)
Brother Xu.
Why did you come here all of a sudden?
You're drinking?
Xiao Ning,
nothing.
I'm just feeling down
and wanted to talk to someone.
Because of the bidding?
Not only that.
I have something
to tell you
about this bidding.
I've always respected you
and treated you like a brother.
I've always felt that we're close.
But
you didn't have to do
that kind of thing
to win over Mr. Xu and Mr. Gu.
If Mr. Xu investigates this,
you'll probably...
Sue me, right?
Let him sue.
The reason that I've been
deliberately planning all these years
is to win over them.
I won't be able to establish a place for myself
in this industry
unless I win over them.
I can only help you
become a top-tier architect designer
when I obtain
enough money
and power.
That's the only way I can help you to make
all your dreams come true.
But
I never asked you
to do that for me.
And I would never let you
do all that.
I was too impatient.
I should have done it
when I've better established myself.
You're drunk.
Come upstairs with me.
I'll ask Aunty
to cook you some hangover soup.
Xiao Ning, I'm not going.
Xiao Ning, I'm not going anywhere.
Xiao Ning.
You must
wait till I finish.
I've kept it to myself
for too long.
I never had a chance
to tell you about it.
It's like a needle
hurting me every day.
If I don't say it,
it might destroy me.
What... what are you going to say?
Xiao Ning,
I like you.
Brother Xu,
you're drunk.
I'm not drunk.
Xiao Ning.
I'm sober.
So listen to me.
Xiao Ning, I like you.
I've always treated you like a little sister.
I thought that it would be enough
to just take care of you and protect you.
But it's not
what I imagined.
I realized that my feelings for you
are changing day by day.
I have fallen in love with you.
I want to give you the best life possible.
That's why I suffered in silence
in that house.
I just hope that one day,
after helping you
achieve all of your dreams,
I can tell you
that I like you
uprightly.
Brother Xu,
I already have someone that I love.
Why Gu Chuan?
I'm just as good as him.
We grew up together.
We experienced the accident together.
I've protected you with my life.
You warmed my heart
with your smile.
Xiao Ning,
our story together is irreplaceable.
No one can take that away from us.
Brother Xu,
we grew up together.
I treat you as my family and real brother.
I told you I don't want to be your brother.
Brother Xu, you're drunk.
Let's talk again when you're sober.
Xiao Ning.
Brother Xu.
Brother Xu, wake up, Brother Xu.
I asked the doctor.
The doctor said that you're fine.
You'll be discharged after having a little rest.
What you said today
surprised me.
We grew up together.
But it was just
true friendship.
We're good friends.
It's even sibling love.
I know.
But you've hurt this love today.
Xiao Ning.
I really didn't
control my emotions well.
I said hurtful things.
Xiao Ning, don't take it to heart.
Xiao Ning.
We should avoid seeing each other from now on.
Take care.
Xiao Ning.
Hello,
the person you are calling is currently unavailable.
(Dr. P)
Hello,
the person you are calling is
currently unavailable.
What's wrong?
I missed you.
So I'm here.
Feeling wronged?
No.
I just want to hug you.
Okay.
Let's hug.
What happened?
Chuan, save me.
If I keep doing this,
I'll have to go get another heart.
Help me.
I can't do anything.
No,
I'm just afraid that
when the whole truth is revealed,
Zhao Yan will...
kick me out of this house
without any hesitation.
Then confess.
Confess?
If I confess, she definitely will abandon me.
No, I would die faster if I confess.
Can I just
have it both ways?
He's busy.
Hello?
Irresponsible.
Who's this?
So weird.
That looks familiar.
Isn't this Mr. Xu Junior?
Right.
Mr. Xu.
I'm your secretary, Zhang Xiao Mi.
Hi.
Secretary?
Yes.
Were you Tang Xu's secretary?
No.
I just got transferred here
from another department.
Then I'm good.
Okay.
I'll head out then.
Let me know if you need me.
Okay.
Brother.
You're in the wrong place.
This floor is for the senior executives.
The Administration Department is downstairs.
Also,
call me Mr. Xu here.
I'm just here to hand over things.
Also to congratulate you.
I'm going to leave if you don't have anything else.
Wait.
You forgot something.
Take your drinkware away.
Baby.
Are you busy?
No, no. What's up?
I'm just calling to tell you that
I have to work overtime tonight.
You don't have to wait for me for dinner.
You're working overtime.
Overtime?
Work isn't that important.
Don't overwork yourself.
Don't take it too seriously
when you work overtime.
I'll let you do your work.
Working overtime.
Hmm...
Secretary.
Mr. Xu.
I'm Zhang Xiao Mi.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Xiao Mi,
tell everyone my order.
No.
It's a mandatory rule.
No other department's personnel
is allowed to randomly
visit our floor for any reason.
Of course, Mr. Xu.
Also,
replace everything
that I don't like
in this room.
Okay.
So,
which ones do you not like?
Let me look around
and get back to you.
Okay, you can take your time.
I'll leave first.
You're the one I don't like the most.
You're so childish.
Playing hide-and-seek in the same building.
How long do you think
you can hide?
As long as I can.
Don't you tell
Jiang Xiao Ning.
Think about it.
When the whole truth is revealed,
what are you going to do?
I'll...
die in a really bad way.
Glad you know it.
Good luck.
I can do it.
I'll work hard
for my happiness.
Why are you here?
Xu Cheng Ran.
How can you recognize me when I'm like this?
I can recognize you with one glimpse.
Here for your dad?
No way.
I'm not that lame.
I'm here
to pick you up from work.
So you came from upstairs.
I went to the wrong floor.
It's not important.
What do you want to eat?
Don't rush it. You can take your time.
With our current progress,
we should be almost done.
Wait a second.
Put this on.
Turn around.
♪Cicada chirping at the end of the street♪
Sister,
I'm going to take you to a place.
♪Two sleeping cats♪
♪Coolness after the rain♪
♪Endless dreams♪
Look, Sister.
Is my drawing pretty?
♪Pink roses, Diana♪
And over there.
♪Heart wavering like green grass blades♪
♪Time passing by gently♪
♪Our eyes meet inadvertently♪
♪Do you feel it in your heart♪
♪Open the doors and windows of the new moon♪
♪Embrace the longing for pouring rain♪
♪You smile and say hello♪
Boss,
this is so real!
Step back a little.
♪Clouds and fog gather♪
Okay, stand here.
Look up.
♪Suddenly dark clouds fill the sky♪
♪Just like, gradually♪
♪Forgetting about your kindness♪
♪Pink roses, Diana♪
♪Gradually withering away♪
♪Time flies away♪
♪The flashback of our conversations
and the time♪
♪Loved one is no longer here♪
♪Close the doors and windows of the full moon♪
♪Push away the longing for pouring rain♪
♪Summer is over♪
It's so gorgeous.
I can't believe I took part in this
gorgeous building.
I'm impressed by myself.
Are you laughing at me?
You always look down on me.
I'm not laughing at you.
I didn't have you
join this project
with Reindeer Group as an assistant.
Will you be unhappy about it?
Of course not.
The best help I can give
is to not help at all.
I know my place.
Don't worry.
Okay.
But
no matter how busy you are,
you must take care of your health.
I don't want anything else
to go wrong.
What?
Are you afraid that,
one day,
I'll say goodbye to this world?
I hate the way
you talk about it.
Actually,
I'm scared every day.
I'm afraid that some random day,
I'll just
lose everything I have now.
No way.
You protected ten years ago.
Now I'll protect you.
♪Caught off-guard by our first encounter♪
Kissing here won't trigger electric discharge.
♪And the corner of your mouth is lifting♪
This is a little over.
♪Am I abnormal or are you shining♪
♪Woo~~♪
♪Falling in love is having you by my side♪
(Dr. P)
Morning.
Yan Yan,
let's go on a date.
We aren't
coming back tonight.
Check and see if you have your ID.
It's in my bag.
Check it.
It won't be good
if you forget to bring it.
It's in here every day.
Let me go look for it.
Don't waste any time.
How about
bringing your household register booklet.
As long as you can prove your identity.
I'll wait for you in the car.
(Marriage Registration Center)
(Jiang Dong Civil Affairs Bureau)
So you took me here for a date?
To get married.
Did you
take my ID?
Yes.
Xu Cheng Ran,
I agreed to date you.
Did I say I would marry you?
I know.
Zhao Yan, if you say yes,
we'll go in right now.
If you don't,
we'll just take a day tour
of the marriage registration office.
We'll come here sooner or later anyway.
I'm going to go now.
Mess around on your own.
Yan Yan.
I didn't prepare a
fancy marriage proposal ceremony
because I know that
you don't like those.
I apologize that
you won't enjoy more time
of me chasing after you.
I'm really afraid that
you'll change your mind one day.
So I want to ask you now.
Will you marry me?
Xu Cheng Ran,
I do like you.
But if you're talking about getting married,
there are a lot of external conditions
that prove we're not a good fit.
I've never asked
about your past.
But I know that you really don't like
rich second generation.
I've never relied on my family
after I graduated from university.
I started my business with Gu Chuan
and worked my way here.
You know about all this.
I've told you about this.
Yes, I'm born rich.
But whether it's my family
or Reindeer Group,
none of them is up to me.
I've never thought that
my family
can give me any convenience.
I think of it
as a responsibility.
The reason that
I'm still not back at Reindeer Group
is because I'm trying to avoid it.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid that I won't be able to
take on the responsibility.
I'm afraid that I'll destroy everything.
Hundreds of people
rely on that for a living.
So are you trying to tell me that
you're going back to Reindeer Group?
I'm already back.
♪You're the haze in my sky♪
So you lied to me in the elevator.
You liar.
Wifey, I'm sorry.
Who...
Who is your wife?
Yes, I went back.
I went back to take on the responsibility
I'm supposed to take on.
I went back to give,
not to take.
That's my family.
You don't want to
marry a man
who isn't responsible for his family, right?
So you're a sweet talker.
I know
you must be so moved now.
Kneel.
♪I want to rely on you♪
Yan Yan,
I've never been this serious
about a person
or any relationship.
But I met you.
I'm serious about us.
Very serious.
So serious that I want to
do marriage registration and marry you.
I can't wait to
take you in there
and force you to do
the marriage registration with me.
I want to keep you tied to me
and not let leave me at all.
Zhao Yan.
I'm so serious that
I want to spend my whole life with you.
I love you.
♪We're not destined lovers but we
keep getting closer♪
♪But who asked me to love♪
I really don't know
how I can prove myself to you.
No matter what impressions
you have of me from our previous encounters.
I'm willing to change for you.
To start over
♪Who asked me to love♪
from the beginning.
[*Literally means "head"]
What's this for?
I really didn't know
how to show you my determination.
So I came up with this
dumb idea.
You...
Zhao Yan,
I'm going to ask you again.
Will you marry me?
Are you dumb or something?
I actually regret it a little too.
This is a little impulsive.
But
you won't dislike me, right?
No...
You...
What would other people think of me
if we go on a date in the future?
We... we can...
I can wear a hat.
You wear a hat now.
When we go inside to take a picture
and you take your hat off,
you think the photographer won't see it?
When we go in...
So you said yes!
My skirt.
We'll go inside now.
Excuse me.
(Legal Representative of First Party: Xu Guo Xiang)
Here.
Mr. Gu,
since you're long-time friends
with Cheng Ran,
(Legal Representative of Second Party: Gu Chuan)
I think that
the relationship between us
should be closer.
So, you're welcome
to visit us anytime.
Of course,
I'll be there often.
Alright,
let's get a picture taken together
to celebrate this moment.
Sure.
Come.
Come, Cheng Ran.
Mr. Gu,
although Cheng Ran worked with you before,
the only reason
that you won the bid
is because your design plan
impressed the experts.
We decided to
use your design
because of the experts' opinions.
So, Mr. Gu,
you're an excellent architectural designer.
Congratulations.
I didn't complete this design
entirely on my own.
My assistant, Jiang Xiao Ning, also took part.
She proposed
the big idea.
No, no.
It was just a random idea.
Dad,
Jiang Xiao Ning and you
have some connections.
Really?
Her dad is Jiang Guang Da.
He was your co-worker.
Jiang Guang Da.
You're Jiang Guang Da's daughter.
His daughter
is this grown-up now!
That's nice.
Oh, right.
I made a reservation at a restaurant.
Let's celebrate it together.
Let's go.
(Marriage Certificate)
Have you seen one before?
Chuan,
you won't be able to catch me this time
even if you were to ride a rocket.
You're going to be my best man for sure.
But
who's going to be your best man?
Xu Cheng Ran,
you should stick it on your face.
Show it off to anyone and anywhere.
This is the first time I got married.
So excited.
So how many times are you planning to get married?
Slip of the tongue.
Just once is enough.
I want to be with my wife
until we turn old, grey, and wrinkly.
Can a wig turn grey?
Does this feel good?
Here.
Do you need help?
No.
Everything will be ready soon.
Thanks for your hard work.
Not at all.
Let's eat.
Mr. Xu, Sister Yan Yan, time to eat.
Coming.
I'm starving.
Jiang Xiao Ning, you're a good cook.
Looks great, smells great.
Let me have a taste.
How is it?
Delicious.
Chuan,
you're a lucky guy.
Our Xiao Ning
excels at work
and in the kitchen.
Who will be so lucky
to marry her in the future?
So what are your plans?
Wifey,
I also excel at work and in the kitchen.
Aren't I great?
Why do you have to be a part of everything?
Gu Chuan, I'm serious.
Xiao Ning is someone
who always thinks about others,
but never
thinks about herself.
So you...
I know what you mean.
Don't worry.
Stop worrying.
Gu Chuan is very responsible.
-I…
-Sister Yan Yan.
Sister Yan Yan, time to eat.
Try out my cooking.
We were the ones who got married,
but you're the one who cooked all this.
Although I feel kind of bad,
I'm really happy.
Our meal today is
to celebrate you two getting married,
to celebrate
signing a contract with Reindeer Group,
and to
thank you for taking care
of Xiao Ning all this time.
Xiao Ning,
I also want to thank you.
If it weren't for you,
I might not have gotten
Yan Yan to be with me.
Come on.
Happy Wedding Day
to Mr. Xu and Sister Yan Yan!
Thank you.
Cheers.
My dream has finally come true.
Wifey,
please take good care of me from now on.
Please take good care of me.
But your hair...
When will it grow back?
Sister Yan Yan.
Mr. Xu is so sincere.
He shaved his head
in order to propose to you.
This is being stupid.
Look at Gu Chuan.
What a romantic confession.
Alright, alright. Stop.
The second toast.
Wish Xiao Ning and Gu Chuan happiness.
Wish all the best
to the four of us.
Right.
All the best.
Hold on.
Let me get this out now.
If you don't
treat Jiang Xiao Ning well
and I find out about it,
you will be held responsible.
Why do I have to be held responsible
if Gu Chuan doesn't treat Jiang Xiao Ning well?
Inadequate supervision on your part.
Fine. Let's finish our toast.
Once we do, we can eat.
Cheers.
Give my cooking a try.
♪Destiny is a little annoying♪
♪It takes those I care about♪
♪Away from me♪
♪If memory is bright♪
♪It would hold up a lamp in my heart♪
♪And light up the night~~♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪Sunshine alternates with moonlight♪
♪Returning to life in time♪
♪Gift me with a dream♪
♪A dream with you in it♪
♪Ah~ah~ah~ah~♪
♪The one who caught me off guard♪
♪Steps foot into my life~♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪Is it you~♪
♪If it weren't for parting♪
♪How can we meet again♪
♪Ah~ah~♪
♪It's you~♪
♪Exchanging sunshine for moonlight♪
♪Exchanging fortune for the past♪
♪Exchanging my heartbeat for you♪