VINCENZO
The heinous Babel Chemicals
must repent!
-Repent!
OUT WITH BABEL CHEMICALS
BABEL CHEMICALS MUST BE HELD RESPONSIBLE
I can't live my life coughing up blood.
Babel Chemicals must repent!
This performance shows
the painful struggle of the victims,
everyone!
MURDEROUS BABEL CHEMICALS MUST BE GONE
THE TRUTH WILL BE REVEALED
What are those assholes doing?
Let's go.
Unbelievable.
LIFE
Their dishes don't taste as good
as they once did.
Their broth is terrible.
-Let's go elsewhere, okay?
-Yes, sir.
This is tasty. My gosh!
Goodness! I'm so sorry!
-Come on!
-You're all drenched!
I lost my contact lenses.
-Damn it!
-Hold on. You got some here.
Watch where you're going!
I'm truly sorry.
Let me pay for the laundry.
-Forget it!
-Okay.
-Damn it.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm truly sorry. Did you leave?
You can't see the judge before trial.
I still had to say hi to you, sir.
Did you quit so you could work with him?
He said he'd treat me well.
You should do the same for me.
I always clean up after
Babel Group's trials.
I promise to repay you
and our association handsomely.
Do that under the table, okay?
Do it secretly.
Yes, sir. Please help us out today,
as always.
Secretly, that is.
Well, I don't think today's trial will be
that hard.
The plaintiff's evidence
is not concrete at all.
Anyway, I hope your first trial
as a lawyer goes well.
I hope so too.
Thank you, sir.
What? What's going on?
Water has been leaking from the ceiling
and the walls.
We're looking into it.
Then move us to another room.
All the rooms are occupied.
I'm sorry, sir.
I guess this building was
poorly constructed.
-Who the hell built it anyway?
-Babel E&C.
What?
To be exact, it's Haemun E&C.
It's their former name.
They have it engraved out there.
This is nothing.
Every six months, the toilets leak too.
Damn Haemun. It's a government facility.
How could they do such a poor job?
Tell me about it. They should've done
a proper job, right?
I bet Babel E&C is
much better than Haemun E&C.
-Are you excited, you fool?
-Yes.
-Having fun? Happy?
Are you here to have fun?
Go inside. You little…
Sorry, Boss.
PLAINTIFF'S TABLE
B**** C******* INDUSTRIAL ACCIDENT CASE
IN PROGRESS
EPISODE 6
Mr. Nam.
-I have a question.
-Sure. What is it?
We're told to rise when the judge enters.
-Yes.
-But
what happens if you don't?
Right. I've been quite curious about that
as well.
A maximum of 5 years in jail
or a fine of 50 million won.
Really?
They charge you that much
for simply not standing?
I was kidding.
Nothing happens if you don't rise.
-Damn it. I fell for it.
-Goodness.
Anyway, why do they tell you to rise?
It's not like we know the judge.
It's not for the judge, but…
How do I put it? To show respect
for the law and his ruling.
-"Respect"?
-Yes.
They always give such ridiculous rulings.
-Right?
-Yes.
They always side with the wealthy.
-How absurd.
-Right.
I won't stand up.
I'll show them my determination
as a martial artist.
Me too.
I'll show them my conscience
and resistance as an artist.
With the spirits of all the former monks,
we won't stand up either.
Let's all not stand up
as a show of defiance.
-Okay.
-It's okay to do so, right?
Of course. They won't arrest you.
-Okay.
-Let's show our solidarity by doing this.
-Sure.
-All right, then.
Here comes the judge. All rise.
So much for solidarity. Salute.
-Goodness.
-Oh, dear.
-Are you okay?
-Goodness.
Goodness.
Why did you cover the floor
with plastic wraps?
Water was leaking from the walls as well.
How could water leak
in the sacred court of law?
-Goodness, my back.
-Are you okay?
Goodness.
Based on the submitted materials,
the researchers neglected
the safety regulations
that were written on the manual
and were exposed to toxic agents.
However, they decided to blame
the company for it
and are arguing
that it was an industrial accident.
Will the plaintiff's attorney refute
this claim?
Yes, Your Honor.
We have enough evidence…
-What's wrong with her?
-What is going on?
…to refute.
-What's wrong?
-Your Honor.
Lately,
I've been suffering from a panic disorder.
-Goodness.
-Panic disorder?
-Oh, no.
-Did you know?
I had no idea.
Your Honor.
May I take some medication?
Yes, hurry up. Go on.
You may continue.
Your Honor…
-Goodness!
-Ms. Hong!
Are you okay?
-Oh, dear!
-What should we do?
-Hey, call 911 right now!
-Help her!
At this one gambling joint,
the Mafia does this first when
someone is about to win big.
They remove the dealer from the table.
The dealer?
The "dealer" at the court is…
-Are you okay?
-What's going on?
-What should we do?
Cha-young!
Open your eyes.
Someone call 911!
Oh, no! I heard a loud thump!
You heard it, right?
-Oh, dear.
-I heard it.
Call 911.
Did you hear the loud thump?
Silence!
Goodness. Lieutenant.
-Call 911 right now.
-Yes, Your Honor.
Cha-young.
Generally speaking, in the absence
of the plaintiff's lawyer,
it is impossible to go on with the trial.
However, due to the gravity
of today's issue,
we cannot postpone this trial.
During recess, we will ask the doctor
to check up on the lawyer's condition.
After that, we will resume the trial
later in the day.
What if it doesn't work?
What do you think? Get up right away.
Goodness.
-Gosh.
-She's up.
-Goodness.
-She got up.
-She's okay.
-Really?
-She just took a nap.
-I see.
You're up. Are you all right?
Yes, Your Honor. I feel better
once I regain consciousness.
DEFENDANT'S TABLE
Why did you rush over there?
She was obviously putting on a show.
I see.
Then let's resume.
The plaintiff's lawyer may refute.
Since the materials weren't submitted,
I will explain them in words.
The evidence is…
Goodness.
-What's going on?
-Gosh.
-My goodness.
-Oh, dear.
-Goodness.
-What should we do?
Goodness. What's going on?
What if the game resumes
without the dealer?
If that happens,
they black out the entire gambling house
so no one can play.
-Come on.
-Silence!
Oh, my.
Why is there a blackout?
Your Honor.
We cannot continue without stenography.
One minute. Let me evaluate the situation.
-What did you say?
-Right.
Your Honor.
We can't hear you
because your microphone is off.
-Me neither.
-I can't hear you.
Gosh, I'm so embarrassed for them.
You can use your laptop, right?
Yes, Your Honor. One minute.
It's impossible to record quickly
or accurately on a laptop.
It doesn't matter. She just needs
to record the core matters.
Goodness. This isn't right.
This won't do.
-She should jot down everything.
-That's right.
-Can they do that?
-Come on.
-Shouldn't she record everything?
-She should.
Are they allowed to do that?
-Does that even make sense?
-I don't know either.
-If she forgets the details…
-What if the player insists
on gambling no matter what?
Then as a last resort,
they kick out everyone else
and create chaos.
SEOUL NAMDONGBU DISTRICT COURT
WITNESS STAND
-She's back.
-I can see that.
Not yet.
Calm down.
The plaintiff's lawyer may continue!
The defense lawyer's claim
that the researchers neglected
the safety regulations
is shameless, cunning, and evil.
It's a big, fat lie!
Your Honor.
That remark is unrelated to this case.
It's meaningless and a personal attack
at that.
Acknowledged. Please be careful.
-Yes, Your Honor.
-Now!
-Yes!
What is that?
What's this sound?
-What's going on?
-Where's this sound coming from?
-It's so noisy.
-What's happening?
My gosh.
What is this sound?
Is someone flying a drone in here?
Who is it?
Which reporter is secretly flying a drone?
-Look at that!
-What?
-What is that?
-Goodness!
It's a giant hornet!
You'll certainly die
if you get stung by it!
Everyone, run!
Get out, everyone!
Get out of here! Go! Hurry!
You should get out of here.
Those hornets are notorious
even in the States.
Why should I get out?
I can't believe this!
My goodness!
Oh, no!
Move out of the way!
Silence, everyone!
If you keep this up, I'll have to
ask you all to leave the court!
How can we cause a scene
and teach the judge a lesson?
We'll have to think about that a bit more.
Ma'am.
-Hello, Mr. Lee.
-Hello.
My uncle made this hornet drink himself.
You should try it.
Hornet drink? Goodness!
-Here.
-Thank you.
Be careful.
They're unconscious right now.
Be careful when you take them out.
They can be deadly.
We should add the honey first.
-No. Water first.
-No, water.
-It's honey first.
-No, it's water.
-The honey should float on top.
-Right.
-Great idea.
-Pour it in.
-Now, the honey.
Silence, everyone!
-Goodness!
-Your Honor!
That hurts! What was that?
Goodness!
Did you get stung here?
I'm sorry.
-You won't die.
-I won't?
-You'll be fine.
-That's right.
-It hurts a lot, doesn't it?
-Goodness.
All rise.
-Oh, my.
-Unbelievable.
Goodness.
-Oh, dear.
-His mouth is swollen.
That's even better than
any special effects.
That's so terrifying.
What the...
Sit down, please.
It's just marvelous.
Help us, merciful Buddha.
I can…
no longer go on with this trial today.
Due to the gravity of this case,
we will…
What is he saying?
We will continue…
-What?
-I can't understand him.
…the trial
a week from now.
-Your Honor!
-Are you okay?
Your Honor! Wake up!
-Your Honor!
Be careful.
-Can we go now?
-Be careful.
-Goodness.
-We should leave.
Let's go.
-Good work, everyone.
-I can't believe this.
-Goodness.
-Can we leave now?
You should be ashamed.
How could you insult the sacred court
just to buy a week?
Insult what?
You also practice the law.
But this is too cheap, immature,
and lowly!
What are you talking about?
Wasn't it like a musical?
It had a well-organized narrative,
and the climax was just wonderful.
And what did you say?
I insulted the sacred court?
The judge who was bribed
by the Babel Group,
Wusang who colluded with him,
and us, who planned this scheme,
are all in the same boat.
Since when did you become
a hero of justice?
How can you be so cheesy?
I don't care about justice.
Then why are you fighting back?
Because you're despicable.
Both Wusang and the Babel Group
are despicable.
What did you say?
Isn't it just human instinct
to have the urge to slap those
who are despicable?
See you in a week.
That damn girl really must
have a few loose screws.
Are you okay?
-Only I can take this.
-It stung your butt.
-I was touched.
-Me too.
-She's here?
-Where?
Goodness!
My gosh.
-You were awesome!
-Let's go.
-Goodbye.
-I'm famished.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Zumba Snake is more furious
than I expected.
"Zumba Snake"?
Choi Myung-hee.
She's a snake that dances to Zumba.
She went on about how cheap, immature,
and lowly we were.
This is one of the Mafia families' motto.
"The strongest punch comes from behind."
That's right. You need to fight dirty
if you want to win.
And if you win, it's more effective
because your opponent is humiliated.
I'll make sure I'm well-prepared
for next week's trial.
Wonderful!
Before anything, let's go eat.
I'm famished. My blood sugar levels
have dropped.
Go without me. I have to be somewhere.
-Why don't you come eat first?
-No, I need to go right now.
Where is he going?
Right. Today is…
Tuesday.
Is he going there?
Where?
Since the day the Korean constitution was
established on July 17, 1948,
giant hornets
have never appeared in court.
Okay? Not even once.
Gosh. In my 25 years as a lawyer,
I've never experienced
such chaos in court before.
It's my first time. Okay?
That hurts.
-Does it hurt?
-Yes.
Well, suck it up! Suck it up!
Yes, sir.
On top of that,
my first trial as a lawyer was a flop.
God, those dirty bastards.
Of all things, how could they think
of bringing in those hornets?
What should we do?
Aren't we the best in the country
when it comes to playing dirty?
We don't play dirty. We're…
What's it called again?
Strategic? Yes, we're strategic.
Shut up.
We're all dirty here.
You have such a double standard.
But since the trial has been postponed,
there is no winner just yet.
Of course, there is. They beat us.
Yes, they did.
You damn assholes!
I will gouge every single
one of your eyes!
HANJU PRISON FOR WOMEN
What should I do?
What?
-What's the matter?
-Well…
Mr. Hong was a public defender
for a woman named Ms. Oh Gyeong-ja.
She's currently incarcerated.
He took such great care of her.
He'd visit her the last Tuesday
of every month.
But now that he's gone,
that won't happen anymore.
Hello.
Please sit down.
How are you feeling?
I'm doing okay.
The pain has subsided.
Since Mr. Hong passed away,
I thought no one would come
see me anymore.
Thank you so much for coming.
Don't thank me.
I only came to tell you that
no one will be visiting anymore.
You should ask your friends
or family members for help instead.
I have no one.
What about your husband?
What about your children?
I have none.
I see.
You don't have any family.
I get that you were wrongly accused,
but how did you live your life that
you have no one who could help you?
Life…
isn't always rosy for everyone.
No matter how hard you try,
you rarely get it your way.
It's probably because you're…
so full of excuses.
Yes.
My life was full of excuses.
I'm sorry for living this way, sir.
Don't apologize to me.
Spend the rest of your life
thinking about the ones
who deserve it the most.
Goodbye, then.
We won't…
ever meet again, will we?
I'm leaving Korea.
This isn't my country.
Sir.
Goodbye.
Are you Ju-hyeong?
Ju-hyeong, we are going to be a family.
Ma'am.
My mom.
My mom said she'd come for me.
She said to wait
and that she'd come back for me.
I need to wait
for her to come back.
Here's your pepperoni pizza.
Once I post about your restaurant
on my blog,
it'll flourish in just three days.
Thank you in advance.
In that party photo,
people complimented your pizza.
-But it's not that special.
-Sorry?
-Well--
-If you want us to put in a good word,
you can just give us this food for free.
I see. For free.
That puts me in a pickle.
Try to savor it,
and you'll be able to see
how our pizza is different from the rest.
Try this one.
It's too strong.
Hey, if they ask for some jalapeños,
say we're out of them. Okay?
And don't give them any freebies.
-They're terrible customers.
-Yes, sir.
Why are you teary-eyed by the way?
DIRECTOR TAE
Hello?
-Are you crying?
-No, I'm not, sir.
Are you drunk and feeling sorry
for yourself?
No, sir.
Where are you?
I'm running errands.
Come back right now.
-It's an emergency.
-Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
-Sir.
-Hello, sir.
Thank you for today.
My pleasure.
I'd like to thank you as well.
Why are you carrying this cross?
Oh, this? There's an abandoned church
that Babel E&C's men took over.
And for over a month, this cross
has been lying on the ground.
But what will you do with it?
I'm going to donate it to Geumga Church.
They will value this cross.
Goodbye, then.
Sir.
Would you like to help me?
Sure.
Goodness. Thank you for helping me
carry the cross.
Sir, I have a question.
Ask away.
If I go live somewhere far away
like in the middle of the ocean,
will the anger inside me disappear?
It doesn't matter where you live.
What matters is whether you still
have the anger inside you or not.
Does that mean
that I need to achieve enlightenment?
The only way to get rid of your anger
is by fighting it.
Stand your ground and fight back.
Enlightenment is what you get
when you win that battle.
Should I hire someone
to tail Vincenzo and Cha-young?
There's no need.
No matter what they do,
they can never outwit me.
What is this?
Did you make your move already
without telling me?
Goodness. You're just amazing.
-Call the tech team.
-The tech team?
The tech team.
Get me the tech team.
LAW FIRM WUSANG
It's done.
REP. ATTORNEY HAN SEUNG-HYUK
Over there. That plant is from me.
Raise the volume.
It's a live broadcast.
But if people catch us doing this,
we'll be in big trouble.
Didn't you hire me to do big things?
That's exactly why
we shouldn't get caught.
-All right.
-I don't get them.
Two days ago, all I heard
were footsteps and music.
We're bound to get something
if we keep listening.
SPEAKER
What is that sound?
LAWYER HONG CHA-YOUNG,
I HOPE YOU LEARN TO BE HUMBLE
What is it? You're scaring me.
Stop it! You're giving me goosebumps!
How did you know the plant was tapped?
Stuckyis grow well
even when they're not watered for a month.
It's the perfect spot
for electrical devices such as wiretaps.
In the past, intelligence services
often used them for wiretapping.
My gosh. Even her dirty tricks
are old-fashioned.
By the way,
you sound like an expert in this area.
Isn't this just common sense?
I see. "Common sense."
Then I must seriously lack common sense.
Ignorance isn't a sin,
but refusing to learn is.
I choose to sin and remain ignorant.
I can't be bothered.
Right. I asked Mr. Nam
to look for a good shopping district
in Sangchi-dong.
Are you really going to get them
a new place?
Yes.
I'm planning to pay for everything
as well.
But…
is that really necessary?
I want to wrap everything up quickly
and leave.
Then you should hurry.
Thanks to that,
the people here have hit the jackpot.
I have to study for the hearing.
I'll get going first.
Wait.
What is this? Are you a wizard?
Did you just get back from Hogwarts?
My blind date wants to see me again.
That's great, but this is wrong.
She'll want to flee.
"Flee"?
She can flee into my heart.
Well, then…
Are you fleeing too?
Mr. Cassano.
If you're not too busy,
we should have a few drinks.
Something more proper than beer.
Do you have something to tell me?
Do you only drink
when you have something to say?
It'll help us work better together.
It'll be nice.
You don't have drinking habits, do you?
Hey!
I told you not to look
into that consigliere!
How dare you ignore my orders and
disguise yourself as an assistant chef?
How did you know, sir?
Do you think this is
some ordinary company?
Ten minutes is all I need
to find out what you're doing!
Right, that's true.
You have no respect for your boss. Gosh.
My blood pressure is rising.
-I'm sorry, sir.
-Damn it.
DIRECTOR TAE JONG-GU
Take a look.
Two parties have requested
a background check on Vincenzo Cassano.
One is Law Firm Wusang,
and the other one is the Babel Group.
What the hell is he doing
for them to take interest in him?
Is he really forming his own gang?
Or is he gathering some money?
I haven't found anything strange so far.
Then what's going on?
I'll write up a report and submit it.
And as for these requests…
I'll reply to them myself.
Okay.
And don't use money from your own pocket.
Charge the company.
You're dirt poor.
-No, I'm not.
-As if.
I know you still haven't
paid off your loan
due to your mother's hospital bills.
Okay, then.
-Thank you, sir.
-You may leave.
I…
Gosh, that crybaby.
I burst out laughing
when I saw the judge's face.
It looked like there was playdough
on his face.
And his speech was muffled like this.
Right.
You visited Ms. Oh Gyeong-ja
this afternoon, didn't you?
-How did you know?
-Mr. Nam told me.
Isn't she the one
who was falsely accused of murder?
I read it in my dad's files.
He even flagged it as important.
I see.
Thank you
for visiting her on his behalf.
I should've gone instead.
You're better than his own daughter.
I just told her
that nobody would be coming anymore.
What?
You don't need to take over
all of his duties.
You should focus on your own work now.
-I thought she was ill.
-Enough about her.
Now, help me get Geumga Plaza back.
How can I when you're refusing
to tell me why?
Do you have to know that?
Of course.
Only then can I come up with a plan.
Promise me you'll keep this secret.
You must never tell anyone.
What is it?
Do you want drumrolls?
Underneath Geumga Plaza,
there are 1,5 tons of gold.
Really? 1,5 tons?
How much is that exactly?
That's about 110 million in euros,
and 150 billion in Korean won.
A hundred fifty billion won?
But there's a problem.
The gold is--
Underneath my house,
there are 100 golden calves.
That's hilarious.
You know how to toy with people.
Do you think I'm lying?
So this is your drinking habit.
-You bluff with a straight face.
-"Bluff"?
-It's about time we left.
-Let's go.
-"Bluff"? Wait.
What does "bluffing" mean?
It's a good thing!
You even sound like you're really upset.
I'll get this.
Let's go, Mr. Mansour Cassano.
Monsieur Mansour, Monsieur Mansour
I'm not lying.
Yes, Mr. Cho. It's me.
I left the equipment you requested
at your house.
We need to hurry
and also think of another way
to retrieve the gold.
I'll hire some more experts
and look into it again.
Right. Just in case,
check if the explosion system
is still working.
It uses electricity,
so you'll be able to detect it.
But why do you want to know that?
If the system has malfunctioned
and been turned off,
then we could just dig in the ground
without demolishing it.
All right.
I'll seek the advice of some experts
and get you a detector.
Damn it.
NANYAK TEMPLE
Why is it so hot in here?
Why do they keep these on?
Why is an Italian mobster
bowing so respectfully?
He's crying.
Could those be tears of repentance?
The consigliere of the Mafia
is bowing and shedding tears
in front of Buddha.
What is going on?
Does this mean he flew in
to repent?
The system is doing just fine.
It's perfect.
It is.
-The mission was a success.
-It really was.
-It was absolutely perfect.
-It was.
-"It's a giant hornet!"
I'd like to say something.
Thank you very much for helping
U-yeong out so willingly.
Gosh, it's nothing.
He's pretty much our family. Right?
Your compassion and willingness
to help others
remind me of Buddha.
-Goodness.
-Don't mention it.
Who in the world could possibly sneak
a giant hornet into a courtroom?
-Right.
-Even James Bond wouldn't be able to.
Gosh, your butt is still swollen, honey.
I can withstand the venom
because of my background in martial arts.
Remember that judge? He was knocked out.
Goodness.
-I don't think I can sit yet.
-Be careful.
By the way, how is U-yeong doing?
He needs to receive chemotherapy first,
and then we'll see how things go.
-He still has hope.
-Yes.
U-yeong will pull through just fine.
-Of course.
-You bet.
By the way, you truly put on
a marvelous show today.
The empathy I had for the victims
helped me do a great job.
Your salami, cheese,
and spaghetti vongole are here.
Enjoy.
-It looks scrumptious.
-Eat up.
-Isn't this expensive?
-It is.
I'm truly sorry
that I couldn't go to the trial today.
I had to serve food
to some popular influencers.
You totally missed out.
By the way, what should we do?
Do we need to move out or not?
Oh, right. Mr. Nam told me this.
Mr. Cassano asked him to look
for a shopping district in Sangchi-dong
-where we could move into.
-Is that true?
Not only that,
but he's also going to pay for everything.
Then we should ask him to build
our temple over the ground.
You know what?
I felt the sincerity in his gaze
from the very beginning.
I'm still a bit dubious.
Okay. What's your plan?
It's obvious. Whether it's here,
there, or anywhere else…
Gosh, that was a killer line.
We should definitely move.
Yes. We must.
I'd love to continue my fight
with Park Seok-do,
but we need to put bread on the table.
Is this a unanimous decision? I'm down.
-Me too.
Me…
-Have mercy, Buddha.
-I'm down too.
-Me too.
Fine. I'm down.
-What is it?
-What's going on?
Isn't he that homeless man by the station?
You're right. He rambles on
when it's about to rain.
I think his name is Gilbert.
Why is his name Gilbert?
I don't know. That's what he said.
Why did he come inside? Goodness.
I'd like a bottle of beer
and one of those.
-Get out.
-Come on.
Okay. It's a good day.
We can share some food.
-He's right.
-Yes. He must be famished.
No, hold on.
You're not allowed to sit anywhere.
Wait.
You look very familiar.
Am I wrong?
If you give me food,
I'll tell you something important.
It could totally change your life.
Sure. Let's hear it.
It's never too late to change my life.
You're all extremely lucky.
REPORT ON VINCENZO CASSANO
CONSIGLIERE TO THE CASSANO FAMILY
It's a secret agent's duty
to deliver accurate information.
HANDSOME, DOE-EYED
However…
Yes. I need more time to observe him.
It's not time yet.
Not yet.
Hello! Good morning…
Let us go inside if you're all at peace.
What? What's gotten into them
so early in the morning?
VINCENZO CASSANO
ATTORNEY JANG JOON-WOO
ACTIVITIES AND AWARDS
VOLUNTEERED AS A TEACHER
IN TANZANIA, AFRICA
MILAN PHILANTHROPISTS' CLUB
YEAR-END CEREMONY
POPE BERNARDO AND VINCENZO CASSANO
ATTENDED THE FASHION MAGAZINE
VOGO'S CHARITY EVENT
What a perfect guy.
He's a famous human rights lawyer
in Milano,
a celebrity, and a philanthropist.
He also defended the Mafia's victims
and has received numerous death threats.
Is this really true?
That was from the one in charge
of Italia's mob crimes.
I'm a bit dubious.
Hello, Mr. Jang.
Yes.
Chairman Jang of Babel.
No, sir.
Sorry? Today?
We need you to testify
during our second trial.
You also need to be prepared for
questioning from the defense and myself.
-Do you think we can manage?
-Don't worry.
We'll tell you our questions in advance
and share
the defense's expected questions.
Mr. Nam.
You should brace yourselves.
Our opponent's lawyers
are extremely malicious.
I'm so busy as it is. Why does he
want me to brief him all of a sudden?
Why does he need me?
All the Babel companies
must know how things are going.
I'm sure he called you over for a reason.
We'll find out soon.
Joon-woo, you better do a proper job.
Don't you stutter.
Sorry?
Right. Okay.
See? He's already stuttering.
"Sorry? Right. Okay." You little…
-Is this all fun and games to you?
-No.
What should I do
about this foolish partner of mine?
"Foolish partner"? Okay.
Is it funny? It is, isn't it?
Be quiet.
He doesn't take his job seriously.
Enough, already.
What is our chance of winning this trial?
If our witnesses testify well,
then I'd say it's 40 percent.
It's much higher
than that of the first trial.
Have you filed in the request?
Yes, I have. They're probably
looking over them right now.
If Director Gil of Haemun Medical Center
testifies, it'll be difficult for us.
We also need a reliable doctor
on our side.
-Any news?
-Until last night,
we were rejected by a total of 56 doctors.
It's always difficult to find a medical
adviser for industrial accident cases.
They won't buy off our witnesses, right?
It's highly unlikely since they're
very hostile toward Babel.
-However…
-However?
…they may provoke them in other ways.
Then we should do the same.
At times like this, we must find out
who their enemies are.
Because the enemy of my enemy is a friend.
I'm having butterflies.
Never in my wildest dreams did I consider
provoking Babel's witnesses.
Then let's find out who their enemies are.
Begin.
I said, start.
All right, then.
I will begin the briefing.
THE SECRET OF BABEL
I will now reveal
the secret of the Babel Group.
The Secret of Babel.
We came up with a fun briefing.
51 YEARS AGO FROM NOW
Chairman Jang Guk-han,
the founder of Haemun Group,
now known as the Babel Group,
had two sons.
He and his wife, Hwang Suk-jin,
had their eldest son.
As for his second son,
he was birthed by Seo Min-hui,
a young secretary.
Instead of focusing on the company,
he cheated.
Hey, Joon-woo! What are you saying?
Joon-woo! Come back here.
-Stop that.
-Stop?
-Sit.
-Sit?
-Quickly.
-Quickly?
First…
who is this second son?
It's none other than
Chairman Jang Han-seo!
JANG HAN-SEO
What a surprise!
Now, who is the eldest son?
He was always smart and active.
He was always the top student.
He didn't graduate
from Stanford Law School as
the top student, but he got good grades.
On top of that, God has made him
perfect and charismatic.
So who is it?
Who?
WHO IS THE TRUE KING OF BABEL?
It's me.
-Jang Joon-woo.
-What's going on?
The real owner of the Babel Group is
Jang Joon-woo!
Han-seo, are you ready?
-Tonight, the star is me
-The star is me
Babel Group is actually mine
It's his
-It's mine!
-Surprise!
-Babel Group is actually mine
-It's actually mine
It's mine
-It's mine
-You didn't know that, did you?
-You had no idea!
-It's mine
I fooled you all!
Babel Group is actually mine!
-It's mine!
It's mine!
I'm sorry, sir.
Please forgive me for my transgressions.
It's okay. I had fun.
Didn't you?
Of course. It felt like
I was on a rollercoaster every day.
-Sit down.
-Okay.
Aren't we
like robot vacuums?
We do our best, but we always fall short.
Not at all, sir.
I'm proud of both of…
No. I'm amazed by your wisdom.
I mean, you both have endless talents.
Come on. Just be yourself.
My foolish boss.
"Foolish"? Right.
I can be quite the fool.
I have so much room for improvement.
It's a shame.
From now on, give him the respect
he deserves as the chairman.
And keep it a secret.
-Yes, sir.
-Don't be like that.
It doesn't matter who the chairman is.
No, sir. Now that we know,
we should treat you with proper respect.
Right, Ms. Choi.
I heard you wanted
the prosecution service.
Yes, sir.
Give me a list
of people I need to buy off
and how much they will cost me.
I'll purchase them for you
after reviewing it.
Yes, sir. I'll submit it to you.
Enough about that.
Yesterday's trial was disappointing.
You barely did anything.
You guys at Wusang aren't doing
a proper job these days.
Can't you see how patient he is?
I'm sorry, sir.
We won't let them have their way again.
I heard you were dubbed "the butcher"
at your former workplace.
But in my eyes, Vincenzo seemed
to be the one wielding the sword.
Do you know about him?
How could I not?
He was the one who blew up my warehouse.
He's the one who put 50 syringes
in my pillow, isn't he?
If you can't beat him,
just get rid of him
like you did with Mr. Hong
and the researchers.
Nice and simple.
Please have trust in us, sir.
Okay.
All right.
Fine.
Take good care of my brother as well.
-Don't ignore him just because he's fake.
-Yes, sir.
-Right?
-Right.
Goodbye, sir.
I heard you were dubbed "the butcher."
But in my eyes, Vincenzo seemed
to be the one wielding the sword.
In the next five hours,
we'll come up with an entirely new plan.
Excuse me.
-Yes?
-Hello.
Are you the treasurer
of the Babel E&C victims' group?
Yes, I am. Why?
PATIENT: LEE U-YEONG
DAECHANG DAILY
And lastly,
report it on the 6 a.m. morning news.
Mr. Nam, why are you calling me
so early in the morning?
Ms. Hong! Turn on the news right now!
According to an exclusive
by Daechang Daily,
the delegate of Babel E&C victims' group
had been embezzling donations
for the past two years.
What the hell is that?
SECURITY AREA
RESTRICTED ACCESS
Detective, if you look closely…
-Detective.
-Ms. Hong.
Ms. Hong, what should we do? Help us.
What's going on?
-Are you their lawyer?
-Yes.
Did you arrest them
because you had solid proof?
Proof?
We've been bombarded with too much.
We found cash everywhere
from their cars and houses
to the ceiling of their office.
They embezzled the donations.
Do you have proof of that?
Him.
The treasurer of the group confessed.
He said he was coerced into tampering
with the book and had no choice.
That's not true.
We're being falsely accused.
We have nothing to do with this, okay?
We're innocent.
We have absolutely nothing to do
with this.
You know us. We're innocent.
Please help us. Please.
We're being falsely accused.
We're truly innocent.
Choi Myung-hee should work
in the movie industry.
She's an excellent screenwriter
and a director.
And how could they blindly believe
her lies?
Because the power of their lies grow
with how powerful the person lying is.
They need to testify,
but they won't be allowed to now.
Even if they're allowed to testify,
she'll just prey on them.
That'll do us no good.
I guess the last witness we have is
Mr. Lee U-yeong who's hospitalized.
Yes, Mr. Nam.
The court called just now.
Our witnesses were denied?
Yes, that too.
And Mr. Lee U-yeong was denied as well.
Mr. Lee? Why?
MR. NAM JU-SUNG
They tested him for drugs
and found small traces of meth.
They need to investigate him.
Methamphetamines?
Talk to you later, Mr. Nam.
Unbelievable.
She made sure to put an end to everything.
She must be a part
of the Mafia or something.
Even the Mafia don't do
things like this these days.
Cha-young.
What? Are you here to gloat?
Come on. Don't be so harsh.
I'm here to prepare for my briefing.
-Then go do your job.
-Cha-young.
Come back to Wusang.
-Are you the boss?
-I'm just relaying his message.
He said you'll be given
the same treatment as Ms. Choi.
I guess those giant hornets
made him want me back.
Tell him no thanks.
Why do you waste your talents
on such grueling cases?
-Why is Babel so important?
-Why are you serious?
Why are you suddenly so serious?
Watching you suffer for no good reason
is making me upset.
And…
I don't appreciate the way you do things
after you two joined hands.
Joon-woo.
Remember what I told you before
about crossing the line?
I'm just worried. Can't I do that?
No, you can't. Just focus on your job.
Let's go back and look for a solution.
Sir.
I'd like to share
this one memorable saying.
"Don't dig
your own grave."
I don't want her to be six feet under.
And I don't appreciate you
digging it for her.
I believe you're a very smart person.
And those who are smart
know when to give up.
Two things.
First, we are digging a grave.
But it's not for us.
Second, it's not about knowing
when to give up.
A smart person knows
when their opponent is weak.
Wusang is teaching you well.
You'll become a promising lawyer.
I'll see you next time.
They murdered my dad, and now what?
They want me back?
Those brazen bastards.
One is easily humiliated when cornered.
Hey.
Can't you share some encouraging
or hopeful words
at times like this?
Hopeful words?
Right.
"Giving up on a hopeless war
will give you a new opportunity."
How is that hopeful?
Damn it. I'm so annoyed.
Whatever.
I won't summon any witnesses.
That's right. Everyone is alone in life.
I'm going to walk back and blow off steam.
Get a cab or something.
All I need to do now
is ramble by myself in court!
What should I wear?
5 DAYS LATER
SECOND HEARING
Thanks, Boss.
This can open both ways.
Hi, Cha-young.
DEFENDANT'S TABLE
Are they summoning any witnesses?
Of course not.
They were all denied.
Okay.
My God. What's that fishnet?
Is it see-through?
The judge called in a bee expert
just in case.
He's been traumatized.
Chairman Jang. Hello, sir.
-Go.
-I'll sit here.
Okay.
Once again, thank you in advance.
Well, Director Gil from Haemun
will put an end to the hearing today…
Sir.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
All rise.
You may be seated.
WITNESS STAND
Therefore, the claims made
by the plaintiff are absurd.
None of them were healthy.
They enjoyed smoking and drinking.
And the other workers at Babel Chemicals
were no different.
That'll be all.
All of your witnesses were denied.
You don't have any additional witnesses
to summon, do you?
Your Honor.
I'd like to summon a surprise witness.
A surprise witness?
What is going on?
Well…
Do they have any information
regarding the case?
Yes, Your Honor.
He has concrete information.
Then…
First…
Bring them in then.
Come inside,
my surprise witness.
This is Vincenzo Cassano,
VINCENZO
There's a card I can't help but play.
It's the most common method.
Creativity is something you're born with,
just like Vincenzo Cassano!
Take her for everything she has.
Then do something.
Just shut up and demolish it.
The business owners may get hurt.
They're bound to leave traces even if
they're invisible. That's our chance.
I present to you this critical evidence.
You'll dive head-first into hell.
You have to pay the price
for your actions.
I will make them pay no matter what.
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
Ripped and synced by
TTEOKBOKKIsubs