Get in the car!
(Episode 7, The Unbreakable Tie)
Hwang Jung Tae,
do you not want to eat?
Pardon?
It's not that.
Why? He's eating.
It's because he just woke up.
It's all because
he's never had to starve...
and gets a hot meal served to him
three times a day.
If we just give him water
and nothing to eat for a few days,
he'll never pick at his food again.
Mr. Hwang,
what brings you by so early?
Oh, I found a book
Jin A should read.
- Here.
- My gosh, this is precious.
("The Principles of Mathematics")
Can she read this though?
Yes, of course.
She's improving by the day.
- My gosh, thank you.
- No problem.
Oh, my.
Jin A has her midterm exam today,
so she'll come home early.
Why don't you eat with me
and wait for her?
Oh, then...
Then Myeong Hee should join us too.
- Myeong Hee?
- Yes.
She's not home at the moment.
I guess her overnight shift
isn't over yet.
- Overnight shift?
- Yes.
She didn't work last night.
She didn't come home last night,
so I assumed she was working.
She didn't come home?
No.
Maybe she came home
after the curfew began...
and left early this morning
before I woke up.
After the curfew began?
(Emergency Room)
How can we help you?
Are you a guardian?
No, I'm sorry.
Hey, In Young.
Can't you tidy up right away...
- Clean this up, will you?
- Yes, ma'am.
By the way,
I thought you were off today.
Don't get me started.
This is all Myeong Hee's fault.
(Ethanol)
Oh, I got this. My goodness.
In Young, right?
- Do I know you?
- Well...
Is Ms. Kim Myeong Hee here today?
She didn't come in today
and didn't even call.
She's never even taken
a half-day off,
but she didn't even call.
I wonder what's going on.
What?
What do you mean Myeong Hee is gone?
She's not at home.
She missed work without calling in.
Did you hear from her at all?
No, I didn't.
Maybe something urgent came up
last night.
Then she would've called
the hospital.
Do you know where she could be?
Why are you asking me?
Now, you know more about her
than I do.
You've known her longer than I have.
You said she's your best friend.
Hello?
Soo Chan.
Don't answer
Hwang Hee Tae's calls...
until things get sorted out.
But if I hang up on him like that...
Don't answer his calls.
Do you want to keep this job or not?
- Get your job done properly.
- I'm sorry, sir.
Goodness, what should I do with you?
Just do what your predecessors did.
You can't even do that?
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Excuse me.
I'd like to report a missing person.
Oh, no. Is your child missing?
How old?
No, it's an adult.
She's 26 years old.
What's your relationship with her?
I'm her boyfriend.
How long has she been missing?
It's been...
About 15 hours, I think.
15 hours?
So you saw her last night...
but haven't heard from her since.
That's right.
We parted ways
in front of her place last night,
but I can't reach her.
- Go on. Go.
- No, wait.
Why won't you listen to me?
Has it ever occurred to you
that she might be avoiding you?
She's not at home,
and she didn't go to work today.
What if she got into an accident
on the way to work...
Goodness. People don't go missing...
that easily, okay?
- Hey.
- Hello, sir.
And we can't say she's missing
if it's only been 15 hours.
It looks like she went somewhere.
Wait. She'd never go anywhere
without telling me.
Come on. How do you know?
How can you be so sure?
Well, for example...
Maybe she saw
her late grandparents...
in her dream
and went to visit their graves.
Or maybe she went to see her parents
because one of them collapsed.
Who knows?
Hello.
You need a haircut, punk.
First, check all the places
where she could be.
Wait another day...
No, come back in three days.
Then I'll open a case for you.
I'm already so busy.
Where she could be...
Oh, I need to go to Naju.
It's been a while since I went home.
All I did was call.
Go away! That hurts.
Hey, Digestive Drink!
Your big brother is here.
Big brother? I don't have a brother.
I think they unplugged the phone.
Why?
They do it from time to time
because of my grandma.
But...
is Myeong Hee in Naju now?
I wanted to call them and ask,
but you're saying
they unplugged the phone.
Do you know
when they'll plug it back in?
That will depend on
my grandma's condition.
It could be for half a day?
The whole day?
It's different each time.
Myeong Soo,
can you give me the address?
(190 Maeseong-ri, Sanpo-myeon,
Naju, South Jeolla Province)
Hold on.
Visiting her parents
when it's only been a few hours...
That's creepy.
Okay, I'll just check from afar
and see if she's there...
That's creepier.
I should pick up some gifts
on the way...
and properly introduce myself
to them...
That will creep them out even more.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Young man.
Listen, can you...
Can you call a doctor?
What?
My son is about to die right now.
I took him to a local hospital...
and they said I need to prepare
to say goodbye.
Oh, what's wrong with your son?
Oh, my.
Are you a doctor?
Oh, well, no...
I am...
Then why don't I call
an ambulance for you?
Why are you up already?
You should lie down
and get some more rest.
I'm sick of lying down.
It's just a cold.
Gosh, you must be fine now,
hearing you say that.
- Drink this.
- Okay.
Where's Mother?
She got up
in the middle of the night...
and stayed by your bedside...
She's not in the room.
She was here just a minute ago.
My goodness.
Gosh, I was busy brewing
your herbal tonic.
I'll go take a look around
the neighborhood...
so call the village foreman
and ask him to make an announcement.
Okay. Where's the phone?
I can't believe this.
Is anyone home?
- Hyun Chul.
- Gosh, Mother!
- Mother!
- Goodness.
Where have you been?
You scared me to death.
Where is her son?
Oh, yes.
I'm her son.
Oh, she said you were my age.
Can you tell me
what's troubling you?
Sorry?
Oh, did she say her son was
about to die...
and drag you here?
The thing is, my mother loses
her memory from time to time.
Gosh, I'm sorry about this.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I'm glad you're okay.
Then...
- Thank you.
- Have a good day.
Mother, let's go inside.
Oh, by the way...
Can you tell me which direction
this is?
- It's my first time here.
- Oh, sure.
(190 Maeseong-ri, Sanpo-myeon,
Naju, South Jeolla Province)
Sorry we don't have
many side dishes.
I should've fried some eggs.
I'm sorry you came
all the way here...
but couldn't meet Myeong Hee.
Seeing you're here on a weekday
instead of at work,
I guess you're a college student.
Well, yes... So...
I'm about to graduate
from college soon.
You're the same age as Myeong Hee
but haven't graduated yet?
You must've taken a few years off.
Actually, I didn't take time off...
It takes six years to graduate
from my department.
Six years?
Then does that mean...
you're a medical student?
Where? Chonnam National University?
Chosun University?
No. It's...
Don't tell me...
Seoul National University?
Yes.
Cut it out.
Mother, what are you smiling about?
So, do your parents know...
that you're seeing Myeong Hee?
Why are you asking that?
How silly of you.
Kids these days
aren't like us anymore.
Don't mind him and eat.
Sorry he keeps interrupting
your meal.
Go on.
- Go on and eat.
- Okay.
Stop talking to him
when he's eating.
Thank you so much for today.
I came so abruptly,
but you even cooked for me.
Gosh, I'm sorry I couldn't make you
a proper meal.
If you tell me in advance next time,
I'll show you how good a cook I am.
So come with Myeong Hee
next time, okay?
Okay. I look forward
to seeing you again.
Ma'am, I'll see you next time.
We should repair this darn door.
Take care!
She's not here either.
Where on earth is she?
No, it'll be okay.
Her mom told me not to worry.
She'll be fine. I'm sure she's fine.
Myeong Hee!
Where did you go
without even telling me?
Do you know how...
Do you know what I was thinking?
What brings you here?
Do you think I came all the way here
to have fun?
You weren't at home or at work...
so I thought
you might've come here...
I know it may creep you out. I know,
but put yourself in my shoes.
How could I remain calm...
How did you find out my address?
I asked Myeong Soo.
I know this may creep you out too.
I know, but...
Myeong Hee, what's wrong?
Is something wrong?
What's wrong, Myeong Hee?
You seem like a different person.
Myeong Hee.
Stay still, you brat.
Who are you people?
Why are you doing this to me?
Well, who do you think we are?
Why don't you make a guess?
Is this because of money?
If it is,
I'll give you everything I have.
Man, are you treating us
like some petty thieves?
We don't need your money.
Your body will do fine.
I wonder how much we'll get for you.
It's a waste to sell you off
to an island.
Hey. Who would buy her?
I did nothing wrong.
Gosh, what a surprise.
You caught on faster than I thought.
Let me go.
I did nothing wrong
to be dragged here like this.
Hey, you brat. Hey.
That's for us to decide.
How can a government organization
abduct a civilian like this...
without even telling me
what I did wrong?
Why do all of you
blabber on so annoyingly?
Shall I make you shut your mouth?
Go on and try it.
I'll tell the press...
and the Catholic Church
about what you did to me...
The parents of the couple
will thank the guests.
Please give them a big hand.
(End the martial law!)
(End the Martial Law!)
I heard you're preparing
to go study in Germany.
Why Germany, of all countries?
You see,
compared to other countries,
Germany's visa screening process is
a lot stricter.
There are communists
who try to defect to North Korea...
through East Germany.
That's why...
we must look closely into...
whether the applicants
have participated in any protests...
and what kind of ideology
they believe in.
Are you doing this...
because of Hee Tae?
Defeat the Yushin remnants!
- Defeat the Yushin remnants!
End the martial law!
- End the martial law!
- We say no...
- to martial law!
- To martial law!
End the martial law!
- End the martial law!
Defeat...
Step down!
Why are they protesting
in broad daylight?
- We say no to martial law!
End the martial law!
- End the martial law!
Defeat the Yushin remnants!
- Defeat the Yushin remnants!
- Myeong Hee.
- End the martial law!
- We say no...
- to martial law!
- To martial law!
Soo Chan. I don't mean to be rude,
but I need to ask you something.
I understand. Thanks.
I won't get a passport, will I?
Apparently, the process
has been put on hold.
It's almost done,
but they need
another institution's approval.
It's the Defense Security Command.
What?
It's Hee Tae's father.
Well... You see,
I'm sure they're just trying
to scare you.
Not even the Defense Security
can randomly stop...
an individual from studying abroad.
It's not like you violated
the National Security Act.
Myeong Hee,
don't worry and just wait.
I'll find a way somehow.
You'll be only wasting your time.
I'll be going now.
You should go back.
You're making me feel pressured
and uncomfortable.
- Myeong Hee, I just...
- Please just...
Please just go back.
Fine.
I'll be waiting for you in Gwangju.
Let's talk later.
See you at the terminal!
I'll be waiting, Myeong Hee!
I wondered why...
Myeong Hee was always stuck
in the hospital like a nun.
Who would've known
she was dating a doctor?
What a pleasant young man.
He even looks like a movie star.
- You're getting ahead of yourself.
- Goodness.
Gosh. You're one to talk.
Weren't you asking about his parents
when we just met him?
I wasn't getting ahead of myself.
I just...
Whatever.
Goodness, Myeong Hee!
Welcome home, sweetie.
It's been so long.
Did you see him on your way here?
He was waiting here for you
until a moment ago.
Oh, dear.
They must've missed each other.
Anyway, have you eaten?
Why are you so out of it?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
Myeong Hee, is everything okay?
What happened?
It doesn't matter why.
You can't leave the country anyway.
(Kim Hyun Chul)
(Daughter, Kim Myeong Hee)
(Convicted of violating
the National Security Act in 1954)
There's no way...
a commie's daughter will be allowed
to go to Germany.
No way.
My father can't...
Have you ever wondered...
why your father can't even open
his own shop...
and has to go from market to market
for decades?
When all the other protesters
were released,
your father made a confession.
Didn't you find that strange?
(Convicted of violating
the National Security Act in 1954)
Is that because...
Yes.
Your father...
is a commie.
That means...
Is it true
that I'm a commie's daughter?
I'm not sure...
what you've heard and from whom...
Father, you tell me.
Is that true or not?
Why did you never tell me?
I had no idea.
I've blamed myself for everything
all my life.
I've regretted everything
I've ever done.
You could've...
You could've told me
it wasn't my fault at least once.
- Myeong Hee.
- If only you'd told me...
If you'd only told me...
why I must live in silence once.
Then I wouldn't have gotten
my hopes up for nothing.
Why did you have to make a fool
out of me?
Why do I have to get shoved
into the ground without knowing why?
Answer me!
Answer me, Father!
You little...
You despicable little wench!
Were you sent by Hwang Ki Nam too?
- Go away!
- Mother, please calm down.
- Let go!
- Hurry up and unplug the phone.
Take Mother away.
- Mother, calm down.
- How dare you show up here?
- That's enough.
- Take me instead!
- Mother!
- Get lost!
Mother!
My goodness. My son is innocent.
Why are you taking him?
Sir, just a second, please.
Mother, they're just going to ask me
a few questions.
Like you said, I'm innocent.
You don't have to worry.
Honey, see you later.
See you.
- Be careful.
- Hyun Chul.
- My goodness.
- Wait.
Ki Nam.
You're Hwang Ki Nam, right?
It's been a while, Hyun Chul.
Goodness. Ki Nam.
My leg hurts so much.
I'm didn't do anything wrong.
You know that.
My father passed away.
My brother has been
out of reach for years...
Your father defected to North Korea
during the war.
Your communist partisan brother...
talks to you regularly.
That's what I heard.
- What?
- That's what you said.
You told me that yourself.
Hwang Ki Nam, you scumbag!
(Statement, Kim Hyun Chul)
Just admit it already.
If you end up with more injuries,
your mother will be so worried
that she'll fall ill again.
Your poor mother.
(Statement, Kim Hyun Chul)
Gosh, Mother...
That's all.
But that's how things were
back then.
So that was all...
Hwang Ki Nam's doing?
I was going to tell you
when you were leaving for Germany.
Who told you about it?
Don't tell me...
you can't study abroad
because of your father.
I should get going.
Myeong Hee!
I thought it would end
if I just stayed quiet.
I didn't want you...
to have to worry about such stigma.
I wanted to break it off
so you wouldn't be affected.
But it didn't stop with you.
Myeong Hee...
She still hasn't come home yet?
She must be working overtime.
I called the hospital,
and they said she wasn't there.
And I can't reach
her family in Naju.
She must be on a trip or something.
Myeong Hee isn't a kid.
Why is everyone making a fuss
looking for her?
Goodness gracious. Go on home, okay?
If you give me a chance,
I'll take responsibility
and sort everything out.
Then how long will the process take?
Several months?
I see. Then please call me
as soon as you find out...
about the part
I asked about earlier.
Soo Chan. What's going on here?
Soo Ryeon.
I'm a little busy right now.
Let's talk at home.
What's this?
Passport... Visa...
Is this about Myeong Hee?
What is it?
Soo Chan.
The Defense Security blocked
her passport and visa applications.
What?
It's all my fault.
You don't have to worry about it,
so just go home.
Hey.
I have something to tell you.
It's about Myeong Hee
and Hwang Hee Tae.
I don't know how you found out
they're seeing each other, but...
I lied...
from the beginning.
Are you saying...
it was all a lie,
even the blind date?
Then when Mr. Hwang asked,
why did you tell him
you didn't know anything?
I was scared.
I didn't know things would get
this out of hand.
Lee Soo Ryeon.
Do you realize...
what you have done?
Soo Chan, I was just scared...
that something bad would happen
to our family because of me...
Look what happened
because of your immature behavior!
- End the martial law!
Expedite the political process!
- Expedite the political process!
Guarantee workers' rights!
- Go home, you punks.
- Guarantee workers' rights!
- I'm sorry.
- Go home.
Yushin remnants, step down!
- Yushin remnants, step down!
End the martial law!
- End the martial law!
Myeong Hee.
Myeong Hee!
- Yushin remnants, step down!
- End the martial law!
Myeong Hee!
- Yushin remnants, step down!
Myeong Hee,
can we talk for a second?
- Yushin remnants, step down!
Myeong Hee!
- End the martial law!
What are you doing?
You saw me. Why did you run away?
You were following me, that's why.
Tell me what happened.
If I've suddenly become someone
you have to avoid overnight,
there must be a reason.
Must I tell you the reason?
Yes, I need to hear it.
I kept racking my brain,
but I can't figure out...
why you're suddenly treating me
like this.
I don't want to be by your side.
I hate it.
I don't want to be called a minx
who stole someone's fiance,
and I don't want to hurt those
around me...
I can't do this anymore.
Did something happen
between you and Soo Ryeon?
Or is it because of Soo Chan?
I just...
I just don't want to
do this anymore.
There, you heard it.
Are we good now?
Do you seriously expect me
to believe that?
You said you wouldn't regret it.
You said we should tell each other
everything.
You said that yourself yesterday.
Then you suddenly disappeared
and had me worried sick.
What is going on?
What are you trying to hide?
Go ask your father.
My father?
I can no longer study abroad...
because I dated you.
Why am I running away?
It's because I'm scared.
I don't know what could happen
if I stayed with you.
My life could get a lot worse
than it already is.
I ran away from you
because I was scared.
Hee Tae, I am...
scared of you now.
Father, you're home.
You didn't have to do that,
you know.
I heard you met that girl.
It was just a fling.
You didn't have to waste your time
like that.
You told me...
that men should date a lot
before settling down.
What's your point?
I just wanted to have some fun
before she left the country.
But now that she knows
you disapprove of her,
she thinks this is like
the love story of the century...
as if she's in
some kind of tragic love story.
My goodness.
I'm worried
she'd cling to me forever.
Just let her leave the country,
Father.
I never thought I'd see you...
pull such a dumb trick on me,
Hee Tae.
Seeing how desperate you are...
makes me think I should uproot
the foreseeable problem for good.
Wait.
Please let her leave.
Wouldn't you be relieved
if she left the country?
There are many things I could do
to be relieved.
I... I insisted that
we keep seeing each other.
She kept saying no,
but I made her...
She just...
Her only fault is
that she got involved with me.
You really don't need to do this!
I'll get married.
I'll get married right away
if that's what you want.
Of course,
you'll get married as planned.
Did you think you could use it
to strike a deal with me?
Hee Tae.
This is why
you shouldn't kneel down often.
Okay?
It'll look too cheap...
when you actually need to do it.
I told you.
The only thing you can block...
is this hand, nothing more.
And you're in the palm of my hand.
It's too early to get scared.
I haven't even begun yet.
What is it that you want?
I'll do anything you want.
I'll behave myself...
and live my life the way you want.
I'll do anything you say,
so please...
Please let her...
Please just let her live her life.
Get ready to go to Seoul at once.
And...
don't come back until I tell you to.
As for that girl...
I'll decide what to do depending
on how you behave yourself.
What do you mean?
You want to send them to Seoul?
They should get a place to live
near the hospital in Seoul anyway.
Let's have them move there
and get a place first.
The wedding can happen
as soon as we decide on the date.
You talked big that
you'd get everything sorted out.
But were you actually planning
to just push forward with it?
Well, the woman problem
has been taken care of.
You don't need to worry anymore.
How do I believe you
that it's been taken care of?
Their marriage...
isn't a business merger.
You can't force it.
Let's take some time
and see how the situation unfolds...
Are you hoping...
the wedding will be called off?
We should put the broken pieces
back together...
for both families' sakes.
Those broken pieces...
could become weapons.
Is this...
a threat?
No, I'm offering you
a word of advice...
to help you make a wise decision.
Seoul?
So?
I said, no way.
Gosh, I must've been out of my mind.
I practically walked
into the tiger's den to keep warm.
I'm grateful to the girl
he cheated on you with.
At least we had that
to protect us...
from being eaten up.
Don't give him iced water.
Hey, it's just one glass.
Don't make such a fuss.
Father.
There's something I must tell you.
What is it? Is it about work?
It's something you should know.
Are you saying...
you planned the whole thing
from the get-go?
Why, you...
Lee Soo Ryeon! You little...
Father, no!
Father, please.
Forget it.
Talking about who's at fault...
will only upset me more.
It may be a blessing in disguise.
The situation has worked out
in our favor.
Father.
We should tell them the truth.
What do you mean?
Are you saying we should tell
Hwang Ki Nam about this?
I told you.
If we don't do anything,
Myeong Hee will be made
the scapegoat.
Listen, Soo Chan. Myeong Hee...
I know it's unfortunate.
But we must save our family first...
and compensate her somehow later.
That's what Soo Ryeon was thinking
when she started this.
This all happened
in order to save our family...
so we must make things right.
No, we can never do that.
If we suddenly reveal that,
it's practically throwing our family
at Hwang Ki Nam as prey.
So do you mean you want to
throw Myeong Hee instead...
and put an end to this?
What's wrong with that?
To be frank, she's not even family.
Father!
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid
I can't obey you this time.
What?
Hey, Lee Soo Chan! You...
Father!
- Father.
- Father!
Open your eyes.
He was lucky this time.
Like I've always told you,
stress is the most deadly disease
for patients with angina.
He may suffer a cardiac infarction,
so you must make sure
he gets absolute rest.
How long has Father been like that?
Why didn't you tell me?
If I did,
would it have made a difference?
Don't tell...
Hwang Ki Nam.
Lee Soo Ryeon.
How could you still...
I will...
I will go to Seoul.
Since I started all of this,
I'll take responsibility.
Both Myeong Hee and Father...
did nothing wrong.
Yes, you made the right choice.
My son has a house in Seoul,
so they can stay there
until they find a new home.
Yes.
Then I'll make the preparations
for them to leave immediately.
Yes, okay.
"It's nothing?"
So I canceled my plans
on my day off and covered for you...
over nothing?
Hey, Kim Myeong Hee.
Are you acting up
since you'll be quitting soon?
No.
Why do you even come to work?
It seems like your heart
is already in Germany.
If you're going to skip work,
just stop coming at all.
I'm sorry.
Are you sure
nothing happened yesterday?
I'm sorry.
You must've had a tough time.
It's okay.
By the way,
did you talk to Mr. Hwang Hee Tae?
He came to the hospital yesterday
looking for you.
I think I said something
that must've worried him.
He seemed awfully concerned.
(Hee Tae's Song Writing Notebook)
It's a Teacher's Day present.
Write a song that will win
the University Song Festival.
I have a present for you too.
You do?
Here you go.
This is for the upcoming finals.
And these are for next year.
And...
This is a math concept notebook
that I organized myself.
It'll be more useful
than your reference books.
Why are you giving me a book
for next year already?
You can just give it to me
next year.
I can't give it to you next year.
Today is our last lesson.
You can just listen from there.
I just came to say goodbye.
I'm going to Seoul tomorrow.
I probably...
won't ever be coming back.
Okay.
I wanted to thank you before I left.
The few weeks we spent together...
were the happiest moments...
in my entire life.
Thank you.
Can I come closer for a moment?
I'm sorry.
I tried my best to be careful,
but I broke it.
That's how I am.
Anything that comes close to me...
keeps getting broken.
I hope you continue...
to bravely go down the path...
that you wanted to take.
You are...
a strong person
that no one can break.
You too.
I hope you stay strong...
and live bravely.
Look back.
Look back...
You'll ruin everything.
Just like your father
ruined your life,
you'll end up ruining...
Hee Tae's life
if you stay next to him.
He's your son.
If you're curious,
stay right next to him and watch...
how far...
I can go.
Please...
leave Hee Tae alone.
I'll break up with him.
(Youth of May)