Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Your breathing grazes my cheek  ♫
♫ With you warming up the stage, happiness never comes to a close ♫
♫ Boring jokes add some sweetness to the dinner ♫
♫ Daily life is even more like a comic than comics themselves ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫
♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up someone pitiful off the street ♫
♫ No matter when and where, you always appear ♫
♫ Holding me tightly and spinning in circles ♫
♫ Rainy days make me so nostalgic because of you ♫
♫ Becoming some part of the memories ♫
♫ Walking down a street with lights lighting up one after another ♫
♫ Warming up the whole world ♫
[Please Feel at Ease Mr.Ling]
[Episode 4]
After all, seeing you like in Angry Birds (a video game), you look very cute.
Blockhead!
Like this, you'll always be by my side.
What's up, what's up, what's up?
The electricity was out a moment ago.
You scared me!
I had thought some big thing happened. This isn't the first time.
The picture I just painted has gone! I haven't saved it.
Here! Wait a moment.
I finally got a chance to give this to you.
- This is...
- Open it!
Xin'er!
Mom.
Xin'er, you are back.
Who is this?
Auntie, I'm Ling Sheng. Don't you remember me?
Ling Sheng?
You've grown! It's so hard to recognize.
Auntie, wait a minute!
Auntie, I have a little gift for you.
You shouldn't be!
Please accept it.
Then I won't be too polite.
Thank you.
Please come in.
Auntie, today I came in a hurry.
So I won't come in but maybe another day.
Alright, alright. Please come when you have time.
Okay.
Xin'er, I'm leaving now.
Have a safe trip!
- Auntie, see you again!
- See you.
Bye-bye.
This Ling Sheng, is he the one who kept on talking about marrying you all the time when you were both little?
Mom, that was just a joke when we were young.
As I see, he still has you in mind.
Mom, please don't mistakenly pair us up.
Little girl, think no more about
someone whom you aren't sure of his survival.
Don't you want to achieve something in your life?
It isn't enough to rely only on yourself.
A man create his own world.
But for a woman, one should take control of a man's heart.
That Ling Sheng has all his mind on you.
It's the best choice now.
Understand?
There are so many of these cards, when can we collect all of them?
I'm sick of collecting these. Can we change to something else?
No way! Brother Yue likes these Water Margin cards.
Let's get in.
[Express Delivery Service]
(TN: lit. Arriving fast delivery - the same as the previous segment.)
- Anxin, we're leaving.
- Okay.
- Bye-bye.
- What are we going to have?
- Can't think of anything.
Manager, which way will you go? Can you give me a lift?
Okay. No problem.
Anxin, let's go together.
No need. My house is very close by.
You guys, go ahead!
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Anxin.
Why are you here?
I came out for a troll.
Your leg isn't good and you still want to take a troll?
Let's go home.
Accompany me to the property management office to pick up some packages then.
Okay. You'll lead me.
Let me push you. It'd be faster.
Sure.
I'm tired. It'd be better if I just get them myself.
Every time you get a package, do you always have to go that far?
That's right.
I got off work too late today so I have to leave all these packages at the management office.
However, I can only keep them there for a bit but not too long.
You think, it would be great if picking these packages is like going to a bank.
You can do it any time.
Aren't you buying too many?
Big discount! Spending 300¥ and get 300¥ back.
It's almost free.
It's a business strategy.
You aren't a shop-owner, what do you know about business strategy?
Moving all these stuff is tiring
but opening them is so joyous.
For you.
Don't you complain that this phone is too old!
But... but it has everything that a phone should have.
I'm asking you to enter the phone number.
Okay. You see? This tree is me.
This tree is ugly.
Don't say that! This is a fortune tree.
I'm hungry. Prepare something for me.
Exactly! I happen to be hungry, too.
- Spicy or sea—
- Just instant noodle?
Let me cook it.
There is no money for me to buy a pot.
Don't you worry! I learn a dish from a TV show.
Art and real-life aren't the same.
Turn around.
Th-that's enough. If you add more I'll be fat. It's alright.
Shouldn't girls be chubby?
Chubby? Do you think we are pigs?
Take your chopsticks.
It's all yours.
It's enough.
Can you cook more tasty food from now on?
Then we can eat this more often so we don't have to eat instant ramen.
- In the past, did you eat instant ramen every day?
-Yes
It's cheap, so I ate ramen.
Then in the future I'll make ramen for you every day.
Okay.
Don't waste food.
Hello?
Lend me $300,000
Why do you want money again? Is money the only thing between us?
Ai Li will personally pay you back.
Then I'll send it over right away.
Kisses and hugs.
Doctor Xiao, you treat your girlfriend so well.
Your room, too.
Did you win something?
I just randomly chose some scratch cards.
Randomly?
And you won the lottery? You won big?
I'm lucky. I can't help it.
How is this lucky?
This is as if you saved the Milky Way in your past life.
There's still $200,000 in here. You take it.
I can't take this money. I didn't win it.
Anyways, I won't receive payment for doing nothing.
I don't want it.
Take it. The password is 888888.
I've received it.
I'll help you save it.
Xiao Ba, when I took you in -
Let me tell you, in the future I'll do anything you say.
You'll agree to anything?
Only serious things.
I'm not just giving you this money for nothing.
It's so that you can serve me better.
I understand. Don't worry.
Anxin, I'll help you.
Look.
Manager Du sure takes extra care of Anxin.
Don't you know? Gu Anxin has a boyfriend.
And she's still clinging onto Du Ming.
Is this news legit?
There was one time he got drunk and it slipped his mouth.
No way.
She said herself, "My boyfriend is out of the country. He doesn't come back often."
Isn't that hinting at Du Ming that he has a chance?
You can't really say that.
If Manager Du knows she has a boyfriend why is he like that?
If you don't believe it, why don't we personally check it out?
Sure!
- Anxin
- Yes?
After work, can we come over to your place?
I can make a hot pot for you all.
I can be an assistant.
How about another day? We can do anything on another day.
Are we not welcome?
That's not what I meant.
Then it's settled.
Manager Du, come with us.
Okay.
Anxin your home is quite far away.
Yeah, I have never came here before.
Yeah, I have also never come here before. There is also no traffic right now.
My coworkers are coming over. Leave!
Anxin
Who are you talking to?
No, I was just checking the time.
Don't play with your phone anymore, let's chat together.
Okay.
My coworkers are coming over. Leave!
We've arrived.
We've arrived?
Here?
Sir has been waiting for you
for a long time.
Surprise.
Bonjour, Madam.
Thank you...
How shall I address you?
- Ba.
- Ba?
Mr. Ba, what is your relationship with Anxin?
We live together.
What relationship do you think we have?
It's over, the gods are fighting.
We'll be fine right? We're just watching the show?
Fight what? You have to be evenly matched to fight each other. But look at this.
Manager Du and this Mr. Ba are on complete different levels.
Anxin, didn't you say that your boyfriend is usually out of country?
Yeah
I just came back from out of the country.
But didn't think that friends would come over,
so I arranged seats for everyone last minute.
Also, we don't have to share all of our private matters
with coworkers. Right?
Right, yes.
Get the present for me, will you?
Just a small gift.
Please watch over Anxin a little more at work.
She's a little oblivious. She won't even know when she's being tricked.
What are you thinking about?
Be careful.
Alright.
Anxin, does your boyfriend have any single friends?
When I go back I'll ask for you.
Sadly I got married early so I don't have a chance.
Caring and romantic.
The key is that he's handsome.
Where did you find such a great boyfriend?
It's just that he's a bit arrogant.
We're leaving and he didn't even come see us out.
He is probably tired from the long flight.
Anxin go back quickly
to take good care of him.
- Then we're not going to take more of your time.
- Drive safe!
Bye!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Didn't I tell you to hide?
Then what?
You hide until after they leave and then come back.
Even if you get away with it this time, then what happens next time?
These coworkers were clearly trying to make you look bad.
What could I do.
We all work in the same building and will see each other everywhere.
The wintermelon-looking guy,
is he the one that gave you flowers?
Wintermelon?
His name is Du Ming.
Then what's up with this "foreign boyfriend?"
I don't have a foreign boyfriend.
It was just a way to avoid situations.
If I had one why would I let you stay here.
Now you can use my to avoid situations.
How about that? Isn't that easy?
It is.
Oh right.
How do you know so much?
Also, you bought perfume and prepared a Western meal.
Where did you get the money?
Did you win money again?
How much?
There's still $200,000. Take it.
How much is left?
$200.
$200?
There's only $200 left?
You're angry?
No.
This card was yours to begin with, the money was yours. What does that have to do with me?
I'm not angry.
I'm going to bed.
The money has already been spent. Furthermore, it wasn't yours.
Why do you care so much?
You can't really say that.
In any case, it was a huge sum of money.
It's just too wasteful.
Yeah.
Is it that fun?
It's alright. You want to try?
No need.
You don't look so good. Are you still mad at me?
Of course not. Of course I'm not mad at you.
If you aren't then come try this program.
[Big Bad Wolf and Little Sheep]
Here.
That's you?
Wow.
You like it?
Yes I do.
In the future you can use this to draw.
Even if there's an accident you won't have to worry about losing the drawing.
It will automatically save.
I suddenly know what you're doing.
Then you tell me. What am I doing?
You have a fun computer,
and you're normally so secretive.
You're a hacker.
You're overthinking it.
Are you still mad at me?
Still mad?
No I'm not.
I'm sleepy. I'm going to bed.
Good night.
You You?
Why are you tied up?
Who tied you up?
Anxin
Are you sure that handsome guy is not your boyfriend?
He's really not.
Then what happened to his leg?
Does he have a girlfriend?
It's a long story.
Wait, I wanted to ask you
Didn't you tell me before
that you were gonna be away for a bit longer?
It's also a long story for me! It's all because of my parents.
In order to force me to go home, they stopped all my cards.
I have nowhere to go because of this cold war with my parents.
Anxin!
Please let me stay here for a few days!
K.O.!
Sure!
Gu Anxin, help me take a shower.
Wait!
You two?
Are going to shower together?
No, it's not like that.
-Can we not shower today?
-No!
No way...
I'm telling you guys—
-What are you doing?
I... wanted to use the bathroom.
Why can't you use it later,
he still showering
Okay.
I'm sorry!
No way...
That is so interesting that you just took him home like that.
Even TV shows wouldn't plot like that.
What else can I do, I was the one that crashed into him.
I can't just leave him outside.
That is true.
But he is very good looking
and has a good figure. He can just debut now!
If I was the one that took him in...
Don't even dream about it.
Also,
what happens if he has a girlfriend.
Maybe not only is he single,
but he is a rich single batchelor!
Just like the main character in your manga!
You should wash up and go to bed. You're already dreaming.
Hey Anxin.
I see that he listens to you. Can you help me?
What?
I don't think that's a good idea.
Please Anxin! Please help me!
Okay, go to sleep.
I will try tomorrow.
Can you help me with something?
What?
Can you pretend to be You You's boyfriend for a day, and then
escape from her parent's questioning?
Okay.
Really?
That's great!
What do I need to do?
You don't need to do anything besides sit there.
Then Anxin should also go.
Why do I need to go? It's not necessary for me to.
No way, I already told my parents
that you were the one who introduced us both together.
Then of course need to see you.
Dad. Mom.
At first, I thought that brat was lying to us.
I didn't think it would be real.
You sure are good looking.
What's the point of being good looking?
The most important thing is to have good health.
Such a young age and already in a wheelchair.
Your mom and I are older and we aren't even sitting in a wheelchair.
Okay, Mom and Dad. Let's not argue. Since you already saw him, you can rest assure.
How is he, Mom? Are you satisified with him?
I am satisfied.
What do you do?
What does your family do? What are your plans for the future?
When do you plan on getting married to You You?
As long as she is willing, we can get married whenever she wants.
I'm currently preparing a tech company. In the future,
the company, including me,
belongs to her.
Let's eat!
Here Anxin
Eat, eat!
Okay, Anxin! Stop drinking!
Why are you drinking so much?
-There's no more?
-There's no more.
Boss! Can you give us...
5 more bottles?
What are you sitting there for? Help me out.
Oh.
Ah! You can't sleep there, that's not your bed!
That's not your bed, that's my bed.
He is also mine.
Dear Anxin,
Thank you for taking me in for the past few days.
Also! Let me tell you some good news.
After so many years, I've finally had the chance to become a koi.*(experience good luck)
I have been chosen to go to London to attend Mike's fan meeting!
I also hope that your love with Xiao Ba is sweet.
Coming back this time, I was very happy to see your changes.
Treasure that man.
Love you always, You You.
M-Monday?
-Good morning.
-Eat some breakfast.
-I'm in a rush to get to work.
I already asked for half a day off for you.
Why?
Do you remember what happened last night?
What happened?
He is also mine.
Anxin.
Manager Du, you didn't leave yet?
I like you.
You are drunk.
I am sober.
Y-You stand there. We can talk from there.
I like you sincerely.
Wait a second! Don't come over here!
Listen to me. You should give me a chance.
I- I don't come
-Don't cover over here!
-Anxin.
-Listen to me!
-Don't come over here!
-Give me a chance, please!
-Anxin!
Anxin!
Listen to me. Give me a chance!
I really like you. Anxin!
You hit me? Anxin!
Anxin! Anxin!
Timing and subtitles brought to you by The Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Clearly, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up ♫