Hello, You You?
Anxin! I have good news! I saw Mike!
He's so much more handsome than in TV!
Then did you take a photo with him?
Of course! I'll be back in a few days.
Can you let me live at your place for a few days?
I don't want to go home, or else my parent's will remind me about marriage again.
No. These few days don't work out.
Why not? Could you have
hidden a man in your home?
Its-No, no, the company held a training session and chose me.
They want me to go train outside of the city for a few days.
So you can't live here.
I'm scaring you! Alright.
Then I'll play a few more days before coming back! Bye!
Bye...
I noticed you're pretty good at coming up with stories.
I can also not make them up.
You move out and make some space.
It's alright.
I think the way you speak nonsense is pretty cute.
Oh, right. Remember to help me buy a wheelchair.
Imported from Germany.
Imported from Germany?
Then isn't that several thousand...
Aren't you about to receive money?
H-How do you know?
You talk about it everyday. "I'm getting paid on Wednesday."
You scared me...
Huh? Why does my right eyelid keep twitching?
Grandpa Liu.
-Grandpa Liu, your grandson sent you some good food!
-Hey Anxin.
Here.
There's a new one today?
The joy of getting a package is no longer what's in it,
But it's to see what your new manga is about.
-I'm glad you like it. I'm going to leave first.
-Okay. Walk safely!
I'm leaving.
What is the new perfume you're using? It smells really good.
Layered Fragrance. This perfume is not bad.
You can try it too.
Isn't it Gu Anxin?
Anxin? Is it really you?
What a coincidence.
-Gu Anxin, it's been so long since we have last seen each other.
You are still the same.
Nancy, you know her?
Of course. We went to the same school.
Did you guys know, this delivery girl
was the adopted daughter that was abandoned by the Gu family.
Adopted daughter? The one who was kicked out of school?
-Ya!
-Nancy.
Stop talking.
Give me President Wei's namecard.
Anxin, this is the business my friend opened.
You can go look for him,
he will give you a good job.
No need. The job I have now is pretty good.
-Just take it.
I really don't need it. Thank you.
You are already in dire straits and you are still so arrogant.
She's helping you because she finds you pitiful.
You are really uneducated.
There's really no upbringing at all.
What are you doing?
People like me without any upbringing won't know what actions I would take.
Please watch what you say.
I'm leaving.
Take this.
Oh yeah, Nancy. About your boyfriend's project
our company won't be investing in it.
This decision is from top management. Please relay this message to him.
Wait, Xin'er.
Gu Xin'er!
How can they do that?
You bastard, get out of this family.
Why did you tattletale to Dad?
I- I didn't.
It was you. After you came everything has changed.
It's because of you!
It's because of you, you bastard.
It signifies wealth when the left eyelid twitches.
What are you trying to do?
I'm asking you. What are you trying to do?
I'm talking to you.
I am the victim, why are you acting like that?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you shaking?
Are you scared of water?
Wait here.
♫ Look at me, don't avoid me.  ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Let me try to touch your hard shell  ♫
Wait here. I'll go close the water.
♫ Hug me lightly  ♫
♫ give me the last of yourself  ♫
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Without walking it before  ♫
♫ how would you understand ♫
♫ Look at me, don't avoid me.  ♫
♫ Give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Let me try to touch your hard shell  ♫
♫ The fragility of hugging  ♫
♫ Hug me lightly ♫
♫ give me the last of yourself ♫
♫ Memories are like heavy rain. Without walking it before  ♫
♫ how would you understand ♫
Why are you looking at me?
Nothing.
Your holding the magazine backwards.
Let me calculate this with you.
Based on today, you are responsible for everything.
Maintenance: $490.
Spanner, ¥$30.
Thread seal tape, ¥$10.
Tee pipe, ¥$20.
Faucet: $35
Water pipe: $53.23
Pliers: $15
In total it is...
$653.23
I understand.
Oh ya, we can clean these things tomorrow.
But you need to help too.
Even if your hurt, you need to help.
What's wrong.
Aren't you cold?
The weather forecast says today is 30 degrees.
There's a big difference between indoor and outdoor room temperature.
So weird...
You have something here.
Just-let me help.
Do you know how many germs are on a bottlecap?
How many?
1.59 million.
Wow.
And it's easy to hurt your teeth resulting in gum infection and enamel buildup.
It does sound pretty scary.
Hurry and eat. We still need to go to the hospital afterwards.
Doctor, are you really sure everything's normal?
Of course it's normal. It's not like he's hurt anywhere else.
Was I too rough?
No. Is the doctor married?
Doctor Liu? He doesn't even have a girlfriend, so who could he be married to.
Everyone's too busy working in the hospital. No one has time to date.
Sometimes, I'll walk around at home.
What about you?
No.
Then do you have a girlfriend?
Right there.
Aren't you brother and sister?
Isn't it the trend right now to call each other brother and sister?
I still have something to ask you.
His leg is healing well,
but right now I think his head has some problems.
Just...he often
says and does some very odd things.
I don't know what's wrong with him.
The CT scan of his head is perfectly fine.
What you're saying must be after the patient is injured, his mental health is impacted as well.
The patient's family must slowly make sure he recovers.
Can you keep walking?
I'm alright.
Watch out!
So accurate?
Oh my...
You aren't hurt?
How could I be hurt? I've trained before.
Trained?
I catch quick delivery.
Wait.
The skin's broken.
What's wrong with that? It's a small problem.
What are you doing?
It doesn't hurt?
It doesn't hurt...it's just a small injury.
I-It's a small injury. I'll do it myself.
Alright.
Thank you.
♫ No longer panicking on the night of the blackout ♫
♫ You're by my side, illuminating light for me ♫
♫ Heartbeat increasing, oxygen decreasing as our eyes meet ♫
♫ Happiness and sadness ♫♫ Make up the moments of life ♫
♫ Rainy days become very special because of you ♫
♫ Picked up someone pitiful off the street ♫
Hurry! Hurry! The rain's getting heavier! Hurry!
The rain's so heavy. Let's call a car.
[Confirm service]
Let's keep waiting. Bus 23 will be arriving soon.
It's here! It's here! Let's go, let's go!
I'm sorry. It's 25, but I thought it was 23. So it was 25...
Call a car! I'll pay.
W-Why are you taking off your clothes?
What? You don't need to shower after getting rained on?
Y-You shower but you don't need to take your clothes off in front of me. Go inside and take them off.
Oh, right. I forgot to tell you.
The showerhead is broken, so you can only use the bath tub.
Go and shower first. I'll shower after you shower.
I need you to help me.
Help you do what?
Help me shower.
What are you thinking about?
What am I thinking of?
Or are you expecting something?
W-What's there to expect?
Y-Your foot's hurt, not your hand.
You can shower normally before, but you can't today?
But I need to bathe today.
What's the difference?
The difference is that I, an injured person, cannot sit into that bathtub.
Figure it out yourself.
100 a time.
200.
Your good?
Then I'll leave.
Wait.
I can't reach the shampoo.
Gu Anxin!
Hand.
Timing and subtitles brought to you by Rabbit and Wolf Team@ Viki.com
♫ Let's start the story from the rainy day where we met ♫
♫ Memories are soaked in rain ♫
♫ Fate works bizarrely ♫
♫ The past that cannot be forgotten has received a response ♫
♫ My heart suddenly beats abnormally ♫
♫ Borrowing the hands of friendship to hug you ♫
♫ Clearly, I am starting to mind more and more ♫
♫ Abandoning the token of happiness, for it has always been you ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Yet the longing has never been able to stop ♫
♫ Searching for the route to return to your side ♫
♫ Our story has only just begun ♫
♫ Using all of my most beautiful adjectives ♫
♫ Is still not enough to describe your name ♫
♫ Our story is exclusively ours ♫
♫ Our palms hold onto the key to the future ♫
♫ Using love to slowly open up ♫