♪ Waking up in a nightmare ♪
♪ Facing this cruel world ♪
♪ Whose heart is flipped ♪
♪ Missed farewell to lover ♪
♪ If the ending is tragic ♪
♪ Fearlessness is born in adversity ♪
♪ Even if the wings are torn ♪
♪ And fall back to the abyss ♪
♪ Hold your hands and move forward ♪
♪ Never stopping day or night ♪
♪ Transcending time and distance ♪
♪ I may be hurt and heartbroken ♪
♪ Yet be brave to fight on ♪
♪ As a hero ♪
♪ Looking beyond,
conflicts and war never stops ♪
♪ Turning behind, you are always there ♪
♪ Lash out the curse in life ♪
♪ Let the story be eternal ♪
♪ Martial Soul surges aggressively ♪
♪ To embrace your lone wolf braveness ♪
♪ Even if the future is harsh ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
♪ When there is no way out in reality ♪
♪ Hope is vexed by desolation ♪
♪ Yet smiling freely ♪
♪ Hammer protects Blue Silver Plant ♪
♪ The power of twin souls illuminates ♪
♪ Surviving in every plight ♪
♪ I will never give up ♪
[This animation is based on the novel Soul Land]
[written by Tangjia Sanshao]
[Previous episode]
Send my orders.
Assemble all of the Martial Soul Hall's troops,
and destroy the power
of the Tian Dou royal family.
You really are cruel, Qian Ren Xue.
My suggestion
is for you to go to an extremely dangerous place
where you can quickly improve your skills.
From today onward,
Fourth Prince Xue Beng
will be the crown prince
of Tian Dou Empire!
The battle between Tian Dou Empire
and the Martial Soul Hall
has officially begun.
How should I protect their peace?
[Episode 157]
We won the fight at the Tian Dou Palace
all thanks to the power
of Tang's clan.
Emperor Xue Ye
also complimented you as well.
Little Freak.
Count me in Tang's clan as well.
Just give me an honorary elder title.
Of course.
Can I stop you?
But
aren't you used to freedom,
and don't want to be in any clan?
Isn't this your clan?
I mean,
are you going to judge me?
I do like freedom.
But that was when I was young.
Now that I'm older,
I'll spend my retirement
in Tang's clan,
as long as you take care
of my food and living space.
Call me when there's a fight
or things get busy.
Old Freak.
Why make it sound so sad?
As long as you're willing,
I will take care of your retirement.
Teacher.
You want me to train on Haishen Island?
Then the Seven Clans
Re-selection Contest...
If I go,
I likely won't be able to participate in it.
Do you think
that with the power we have right now,
we can stop the Martial Soul Hall
from finishing the Contest?
As long as we have the support
of the Tian Dou and Xing Luo Empires,
even the Martial Soul Hall
won't make any risky moves.
Choosing
to leave now
to improve your skills
and hone your power
is the best move.
Teacher.
I will listen to you
and train on Haishen Island.
You are not the only one
that needs training.
The others in the Shrek Seven Devils
are all at a similar bottleneck.
Also,
if you go together,
you can take care of each other.
Seven Devils?
How could I not be worried
unless the seven of you
took on this challenge together?
Teacher thought through all of this for me?
Once you return from the Hao Tian tribe,
Mu Bai and the others should be here too.
The seven of you
are our trump cards in the battle
against the Martial Soul Hall.
I believe that all of you
will receive great results
after going to Haishen Island.
[Tang's Clan]
Brother San.
Are you being serious?
Why don't you bring Xiang
to train with you?
She also needs to improve her skills.
Granduncle.
Don't worry.
As long as I'm here,
Xiang will return safely.
Great!
Fatty.
Remember.
You can't force
a relationship to happen.
Brother San, don't worry.
I will win Xiang over
with my love and sincerity.
After I take care of the matters
at the Hao Tian tribe,
I will return quickly
to meet up with everyone.
For the next few days,
you will be in charge
of Tang's clan.
Brother San.
No problem!
[Tang's Clan]
[Hao Tian Tribe]
Uncle.
Thank you
for allowing Senior Lou Gao
into the Hao Tian tribe.
No.
You helped yourself.
You completed one of the three requests
from the elders
in such a short time after you left
and now have a Century Millennium Soul Ring
at the Soul Emperor level.
Did you forget their expressions
when they saw your red soul ring?
Uncle.
I'll entrust Senior Lou Gao
with you.
Only your Hao Tian Hammer
can help his forging.
I understand.
You must keep Tang's clan a secret
to prevent unnecessary misunderstandings.
Speaking of which,
Hao Tian tribe did mistreat
the four single attribute tribes.
If Tang's clan develops well,
that will be
a good outcome for them.
Uncle.
Once I return,
I will go to see my parents first.
After that,
my friends and I
will go to a place full of pressure for training.
We won't be back
in a few years probably.
Where are you going to train?
Haishen Island.
I don't know
if you've heard of it before.
What?
You're going to Haishen Island?
You know about it?
How would I not know?
Your father and I went there before.
San.
That place is no joke.
Your great-grandfather, Tang Chen,
and Qian Dao Liu
were both defeated there back then.
Great-grandfather?
Qian Dao Liu?
Uncle.
What actually happened?
Your great-grandfather, Tang Chen,
was a level 99 Grand Soul Land Master.
Back then,
he and the Martial Soul Hall's Head Flamen
and also
the Judicial Elder, Qian Dao Liu,
were known as the two leaders
of the soul master world.
[Star Forest]
Your great-grandfather was
a bit more powerful than Qian Dao Liu,
but the gap was very small.
Level 99?
Then who defeated
my great-grandfather and Qian Dao Liu?
Grand Ocean Master from Haishen Island,
Bo Sai Xi.
Her power is equal to Qian Dao Liu's,
but on Haishen Island,
she can harness the power of the ocean
Unless it's someone of level 100 or higher,
no one can defeat her.
A level 100 soul master is just a legend
on the continent.
No wonder Great-grandfather
and Qian Dao Liu failed.
San.
When outsiders set foot on the Haishen Island,
even if they pass the challenge,
they still won't be able to leave.
Have you really decided to go?
Since we're going,
we will definitely pass the challenges
and think of a way to return safely.
Alright.
You young people
are really confident.
Your father and I didn't expect this.
Since the elders
have acknowledged you,
then
I should pass some of our clan's secret skills
to you.
Thank you, Uncle.
[Soul Land]
First Skill, Phoenix Firing Line!
Ao.
Be careful of Chen Xiang.
Second Skill, Flying Swallow!
Sixth Skill, Cloning Sausage!
Jiubao Boosts.
You Fatty,
get out of my way!
You knew I was fast,
but you still blocked me.
Did you do that on purpose?
I was afraid you would get hurt.
If you just rush over,
you might fall into a trap.
Xiang.
Fatty is right.
Brother San's martial soul is focused on control.
Your speed is fast,
but if you get caught
in the Constraint of Spider Web,
you won't be able to escape.
I think he
just wanted to show off.
Xiang,
we...
How many times did I tell you?
Don't call me Xiang!
Fatty has really met his match this time.
It seems like
Master's suggestion was right.
When we're together,
we're very happy every day.
Without pressure,
we won't have the motivation to train.
Ever since we came back,
to be honest,
I haven't been focused on training at all.
I just want to be with you.
Me, too.
Hey,
Ao!
You're actually willing to come back?
Zhu Qing!
I'm begging you!
Let me hug you for a bit longer.
Boss Dai.
Can't you be more gentle?
It's a good thing you came back alive.
You got a scar?
I'm finally more handsome than you.
But you're still not the most handsome.
Don't forget about San.
San?
Who will compare with him who is not even human?
Senior Qin.
Boss Dai!
Come here.
Let me ask you.
Fatty.
You have good taste.
Who is this...
Boss Dai.
Please don't say anything bad about me.
I'm serious this time.
Are you actually serious this time?
Let's go,
Boss Dai.
Let's talk on the side.
Ao and I have a lot to tell you.
Where are San and Wu?
The Shrek Seven Devils
is now only without San and Wu.
Yin.
Do you feel it too?
Dad!
Your mom is very happy that you're back.
She is welcoming you.
I know.
Why are you crying?
You should be happy.
Dad.
Mom is growing much faster
than I expected.
I believe
that she will definitely recover.
I believe so as well.
San.
Did you know?
Watching your mom's body grow everyday
is my biggest satisfaction.
Coming back this time,
I want to ask you both for a favor.
[Since the commencement of
animating Soul Land on April 1st, 2017,]
[episode 157 has been completed
and broadcast for nearly 1480 days.]
[Total minute of the animation: 2371]
[Total scene: 58480]
[Total CGI: 27605]
[Total plan of action scene: 12219]
[Total scene model: nearly 554]
[Total character model: nearly 999]
[Total props model: 13377]
[We appreciate your continuous support and love.]
[We will definitely keep on striving.]
[Dream of Soul Land illuminates our martial soul,]
[vibrant youth with your presence.]
♪ We still have to part from each other ♪
♪ I'm faint-hearted to stop you from leaving ♪
♪ Amidst the grieving woods ♪
♪ Who is crying out there ♪
♪ I still relentlessly hold on ♪
♪ I refuse to accept this destiny ♪
♪ Desperately searching ♪
♪ Any signs of you ♪
♪ The bleak Star Forest,
illuminating in the moonlight ♪
♪ In your eyes, the world never changes ♪
♪ Yearning grows and interweaves with the past ♪
♪ Aside from promise,
I have much that I haven't told you ♪
♪ You are the memory I refuse to let go ♪
♪ And the craziness of my desperation ♪
♪ Can you hear ♪
♪ My calls ♪
♪ Breaking through extreme dolours ♪
♪ Rushing towards your embrace ♪
♪ You are the only one
I dreamt to comb my hair ♪
♪ And the wish I made upon a star ♪
♪ One day ♪
♪ You will turn up gorgeously ♪
♪ And hold my hands ♪
♪ To envisage our future ♪
[Next episode]
Wu.
Will you marry me?
Yes, I will.
[Two souls meet under the moonlight,
love is San and Wu's affection for each other.]
[Time passes by,
we travel the world hand in hand together]
[520 - An invitation to this romantic moment]
[Soul Land]
[10 AM every Saturday]