[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 36]
We're still in the Ling Town.
It's just an illusion you created
that feels like ten thousand years ago.
Good job.
Clever.
I worry that I might not be able to hate you again.
What exactly do you want?
Yushi.
You think this is the best we can get?
What do I want?
Why do you have so many questions?
You really don't care about Qin Lie
out there, do you?
You won't hurt him, will you?
Those people are slayers from the Surah Realm.
If this is just an illusion,
could slayers be real?
Of course not.
They are the illusions
created by the Supreme Voodoo Insects.
They take orders from me.
They won't hurt Qin Lie
without my command.
It's just
you've made me sleep now.
They can be brutal
without my instructions.
I see. Qin Lie is protected by the Spirit Pillar.
But they're the Supreme Voodoo Insects.
The Spirit Pillar is only a tiny object.
How could it protect him
from the Supreme Voodoo Insects?
This is my divine sense.
I'm the Master here.
You will obey me
even if you are the Mother of Earth.
Go! Leave!
I won't. Let's go together.
Yushi is still trapped in there. I can't leave.
Don't you want to be human?
Go, then!
You pretended to give yourself away
so that you could lure me in.
That's right.
I know.
You're better at playing it cool than Qin Lie.
When I was feeling cold
and found out you were going to
use the strength of the earth,
I knew you would see through my plot at any point.
So,
I lied to you that Du Shaoyang was a spirit artifact.
I made a slip of the tongue
on purpose to lure you in.
Then you made me talk to
to buy you more time.
What are you playing at?
Take it easy.
All in good time.
It's done!
What exactly do you want?
I want to awaken Du's bloodline.
I want him to be a spirit artifact and
go back to where he belongs.
Gongmu Lie will wake up this way.
Weren't you trying
to stop him from waking up?
I didn't expect that
your love for Qin Lie
could let him break the
Forbidden Curse Wuchun had cast on him
and love you back.
That's why you want him to wake up
and change back to Gongmu Lie.
The Forbidden Curse works better on the latter.
Yes. He won't
miss you a bit by then.
Night Fairy, stop it.
Shut up.
Gongmu Lie will hate you for this.
You're just my substitute.
You don't deserve to mention his name.
Get out of here!
I can't allow you to do this.
You can't hurt Qin Lie.
Song Tingyu.
The man you love
will never love you again.
Don't!
Gongmu Lie, this is just an illusion.
The Night Fairy created it all.
Please don't.
Gongmu Lie, you're finally back.
Leave!
Do you know how much I missed you?
If you had listened to me
not to go to the Deserted Spirits Realm,
you wouldn't have to sleep for ten thousand years.
It's none of your business
where I went.
You.
Tell me
what's going on.
Where is he?
At least we need to find his body if he dies.
Damn it.
Could he be abducted by the Night Fairy?
Hang on.
The spatial energy is unusual here.
La Fei. La Er.
Here it is.
How did you get the
Supreme Voodoo Insects from Jiang Yan?
I was trapped in the Graveyard of Gods
for ten thousand years.
I didn't know the Insects were buried
beneath until
I sensed the Voodoo Master.
Then I tried to control Du Shaoyang with them.
I didn't expect to be hurt by Sheng Xie
when I was recovering the first spirit artifact.
I pretended to repent
and stayed inside the Spirit Pillar to recover.
I was waiting for my time.
I didn't expect Du Shaoyang
to plot against me with the Voodoo Insects.
I took this opportunity
to send the fire diagram into their bodies.
I'll kill them.
I'll kill them all.
You know who your real master is?
Yes, we know.
Too right!
You will all obey me.
Otherwise,
the fire diagram inside you
will burn you out.
Of course.
The Night Fairy is controlling
the Supreme Voodoo Insects.
Qin Lie is trapped in the illusion with others.
What do we do now?
Hang on.
Let me think.
Have you done with it?
No. No. No.
Have you finished?
I found out that you were in the Ling Town
through the Ghost Eye Race.
So, I tricked Du into meeting you there
to prevent the last spirit artifact
from returning to its master.
I didn't expect that Qin Lie
would rather let Du leave
than awaken himself.
My plan failed.
So, I had to create an illusion
that the Voodoo Master was killed
ten thousand years ago.
They were forced to wake up
when faced with danger.
You were a badass.
You almost killed Qin Lie.
No, I didn't. That was nothing
as long as you can wake up.
What if I did not?
You would rather let me die
than see me
with another woman.
That's right.
No.
Stop there.
Gongmu Lie.
I am always your mentor and friend.
I've always stayed with you.
I've been waiting for you for ten thousand years
while you were sleeping.
You should even want to kill me
after all this time?
You stopped me ten thousand years ago.
You plot against me after all this time.
Shouldn't I kill you?
Yes, you should.
You should.
Since you do not want to live with me,
why don't you die with me?
How about this?
Have you made up your mind?
I'm still thinking!
Still thinking?
What the hell are you thinking about?
They're fighting inside!
You're so useless. I'll do it myself.
Damn.
They can't hold it anymore.
It's going to explode!
Chu Li, do something!
Chu Li?
What are you doing with this turtle shell?
Shut up.
You know nothing, do you?
You lot from the Scarlet Tide Continent.
Our sect are the maters of bombs.
You are only good at
setting them off like firecrackers.
We're different.
We practise using our spirit energy.
The more skilled we get,
the more likely we are to
make it an integral part of us.
Hang on.
You want to crack the illusion
with a human bomb?
Would you die of it?
No.
That's impossible.
But my skill is not yet perfect.
I still need your help when I throw the Bomb.
You need me to throw you then?
Many thanks in advance.
You have the Illusory Demon Sect to thank!
They're in grave danger. Come on.
Step aside, guys.
Chu Li.
Gongmu Lie.
You gave me a body.
However,
I've suffered a lot as a human.
Since you wish so,
have it your way then.
Kneel.
I don't want to give in.
You were a gun owned by the God Race.
You were born to kill your own master.
I despise
my own fate.
I hate what it means to be natural.
You killed him
to defend the dignity of the God Race.
Won't give in?
That's why you're Du Shaoyang.
You have the bloodline of the God Race.
I am the only one that connects with you.
You will only become my spirit artifact
if you are willing to obey me.
Don't you worry that I might kill you
if I am born to kill my master?
No spirit artifact wants
a reputation like that.
You're so loyal to me
that you don't even mind your reputation.
I understand you.
Only you
are able to change my fate.
This is
your only opportunity.
Who dares to stop me?
How dare you.
I know you. In the Deserted Spirits Realm,
you refused to tell me the whereabouts
of my father.
Sister. Sister. Sister.
Sister.
I knew.
Once Qin Lie wakes up,
I will lose him forever.
I don't know him.
I know you always don't mean what you say.
You can never make me forgive the Surah Realm.
Never!
I...
Let go of her! Let go of her!
Let go of her! Let her go!
I've been holding these grudges
for ten thousand years.
I can only calm myself
if I kill all its people.
I won't let you leave
till my last breath.
Don't hurt her!
Why I still remember you
when you already forget me?
Was it because I cursed you
but forget to curse myself?
I didn't forget to curse myself.
It's just I don't want to forget you.
I don't want to forget the joy of love.
I want to remember you.
Remember what you look like,
no matter it's been a thousand,
or ten thousand years,
no matter whether you still remember me or not.
You've cast a Forbidden Curse on Gongmu Lie.
Yes.
What else?
Nothing.
You should have forgotten each other.
But only he got the curse.
You forgot to cast it on yourself.
You worried that if he ever woke up,
no one would be able to
see him through difficult times.
You would rather suffer
the bitter love on your own.
Your love for Gongmu Lie
will go beyond time.
You aren't even aware
of that yourself.
One day,
when you understand it
and still don't
regret it,
that's when you can truly wake up.
Sister Wuchun.
The Mother of Earth.
Don‘t cry.
I'm still your sister.
Sister.
Do you know how to save him?
He will be fine.
Where is Gongmu Lie?
He's left for the Surah Realm for revenge.
He's gone too far.
You can't get him back.
I need him to come back.
Gongmu Lie.
Follow the stars and come back.
Does it mean...
The universe is turned upside down?
I've never seen this before.
Before the universe was created,
the world had been chaos.
The Mother of Earth had been able to
get the spirit energy from the sky
and control the space and dimension.
However, this could only be done
if she sacrifices herself.
Wanna stop me?
Can you?
Gongmu Lie.
Don't go there.
Why do you stop me?
Ten thousand years ago,
you refused to tell me where my father was.
Now,
you want to stop me from going wherever I like.
I hate you so much.
I've been hating you since ten thousand years ago.
No!
I hate you!
Don't!
I'm now casting the Forbidden Curse on you,
using my blood, as the Queen of the Nether Race.
I forbid you, Gongmu Lie
from ever falling in love with Wuchun.
Ridiculous.
How could a tiny curse
stop Gongmu Lie from loving Wuchun?
If it fails,
I am willing to pay you back with my life.
You're ruthless.
I have to.
How do I
break this curse?
Unless
you hate me.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
I don't want to see you die.
So, I asked you to hate me.
The curse broke because of hatred.
That's why you saw
yourself killing the person you love.
It would hurt you to the core.
It's all because you were so ruthless.
And that's why
you hurt me to the core.
The deeper the love, the deeper the hate.
We will go down in history
because of hatred.
There isn't hatred
without love.
Back at that time,
we met for one moment
after missing each other for ten years.
Now,
we finally get to meet
after ten thousand years.
Gongmu Lie,
can you promise me something?
Never enter the Surah Realm
until the time has come
and you are ready.
You know me as well as
Qin Lie knows Ling Yushi.
I am always slower
on this.
I know you less than you know me.
It's alright.
You still have ten thousand years.
I only need to say one thing to you
in ten thousand years.
You don't have to say it.
You don't have to prove it.
But you can forget it.
I will prove it with my whole life,
with my life as Gongmu Lie and Qin Lie.
Because
you are my wife.
This is what I can give you.
The last leaf of heart.
I'll keep your soul here.
It stays with me forever.
If you ever meet someone
throw it away.
I only
need you
in my life.
Chu Li.
Yu...
Wu...
Look after Xuanxuan.
Don't worry.
I will always be with her.
If she dies,
I will die with her.
Gongmu Lie,
ask Tong Xin to save Sister.
Don't.
He...He...
He...He can save Yushi.
He is with that...
That...
Old bastard Hua.
He is with him.
Master Hua?
Can you save my sister?
They can.
Us?
You can't bring people back to life.
But you can borrow the strength of the earth.
How?
Let the Mother of Earth return to the earth.
She might be able to come to life.
Are we there yet?
She can't make it any longer.
You need to leave her even if you can't.
Close it.
The Ghost Eye Race is asking the Earth for help.
Please resurrect the Mother of Earth.
Show yourself.
I need to go looking for my father
and my grandfather.
Go with me
if you want to.
I won't stop you
if you want to leave.
I'll be back
by the time you wake up.
Let's go.
Take me with you.
I don't take kids.
How about this?
Not bad.
They've all gone. I know you miss them.
I would rather you died forever.
You just want to make me cry.
I make you cry?
I only want to make you laugh.
Besides,
you never cried for me.
You only cried for Yiyuan,
for Hua Yuxin,
and Tong Xin. Right?
I will blow you up with my Bomb!
They never mean what they say,
that's what grown-ups are like.
Teasing each other.
Never gets to the point.
You lot,
wanna go with us?
We need to stay here,
waiting for the regeneration
of the Mother of Earth.
We need spirit stones, as many as possible.
You can take these.
I'll have my people bring you the rest.
Xuanxuan,
one can change their mind.
One can always fall in love again.
We're never going to starve again. Never.
Will you go or not?
Always so slow.
Bye-bye.
Gongmu Lie has woken up.
The four spirit artifacts have been restored.
However,
there's still a long way to go
to overthrow the tyranny of
the Heaven Fighting Race.
Under the leadership of Gongmu Lie,
they are heading to the Surah Realm.
A new journey has begun.
They will fight for justice.
They will fight for the Spirit Realm.