[English subtitles are available]
[The World of Fantasy]
[Episode 35]
I think,
I should say it to the forehead of Qin Lie.
But will he be
willing to lend his forehead to me?
What are you doing here?
I am worried about you.
Worried about what?
I can't be better.
You are sad deep in your heart
but why don't you cry it out?
Then you can go sleep after crying.
You kept nagging last night
and Yushi had to stay up for you.
She is my big sister.
Of course, she had to keep me company.
What does it have to do with you?
Who are you?
Who do you like?
If I have to say a person who I like,
then I like
Tong Xin.
He is adorable and he saved my sister.
But if you are asking about who I love,
then...
I love Yuxin.
In front of you is Yi Yuan.
Why didn't you choose me?
If you don't like or love me, then what is it?
No feeling for me at all?
It is you.
You stupid.
The person I like and love
is you.
Promise me,
find someone who treats you nicely,
has fun banter with you,
and always stays with you, okay?
Of course, I will find someone.
And the one I find
must be better than you.
Xuanxuan, I... I'm...
I told you, you should never apologize to me.
I am leaving.
Then leave.
Why are you looking at me
as if you don't wanna leave me?
Xuanxuan,
the human heart can change.
You can fall in love with someone again.
I know.
Du Shaoyang,
if I tell you that
you are one of the four spirit artifacts...
I am my own person.
Don't you dare think that
I would be less than you forever.
I told you to go home.
I...
I am going home.
Is this the way home?
It isn't?
Then maybe I got lost.
Look how scatterbrained I am.
Are you?
Alright.
Fine, I lied to you.
I knew it.
You old man. Tell you what,
I value loyalty more than my own life.
I am persistent and sentimental.
Now that I regard Qin Lie as my big brother
and he is in trouble,
I will not run for my own life
and leave him in danger.
Are you throwing your own life away?
That's called dying in my prime.
I'd like to sacrifice for our brotherhood.
I don't even want to live to your old age.
Always nagging and gabbling.
Pretending to be gallant but actually a coward.
How rude!
You can go now.
Why? What is your game here?
I also wish to find a friend
who is willing to die for me
or someone
I am willing to sacrifice my life for.
Really?
You do think this way?
It is the right thing to do.
That's why they say...
- Are you leaving or not?
- Life...
I am leaving, I am leaving.
Where are they now?
They're at the Ling Town.
So far away.
Thanks a lot.
Get back here.
Father.
What's going on?
Gongmu Shan is in danger now.
He is trapped in the Six Heaven Fire Formation.
Didn't he go to find Chongming to
ask about Gongmu Hao's whereabouts?
Maybe it's Chongming.
Maybe it's Gongmu Hao.
They are all trapped in the Six Heaven Fire Formation.
I need to go save them.
Don't, father.
The Six Heaven Fire Formation
can only be broken by
the original Scripture of the Nine Hells.
If you go to save them,
you are seeking your own demise.
What demise?
Told you it's sacrificing for my loyalty.
Otherwise,
wouldn't I be less than that brat?
Go watch Du Shaoyang closely.
Don't fight him unless necessary.
Let them settle their
grudge by themselves.
Understood.
Three of the four artifacts are now in their place.
The one who gained something
is Gongmu Lie.
But the one who lost something
is me,
Qin Lie.
As we are getting closer
to the day Gongmu Lie awakens,
it feels that on that day
Qin Lie would be replaced by him.
But I hate to leave those around me,
you in particular.
That's 'cause you care about
loyalty and relationships.
What you are afraid of
is never heavy responsibilities,
but losing people you care about.
I am afraid of losing you the most.
No matter you are Qin Lie or Gongmu Lie,
I will always stand by your side.
- Where do you think you are running to?
- Mom.
- Mom, stop it.
- Run, keep running.
You stop right there.
Alright, fine, mom.
Get out of my way.
- Mom.
- I'll slap you on the butt.
After three more months,
the moon will come out.
Then we'll come back here
three months later.
Why bother waiting for three months?
Even if the moon doesn't come out,
it's still there.
It still knows about what's on our minds.
The moon already knows about
what I am thinking.
Did it tell you?
No, it didn't.
What is on your mind?
Here come the newlyweds.
The first kowtow is for the Ancient Masters.
They will be happy
if we are happy.
Every year,
to the moon,
I would make the same wish.
I wish to grow old with you
and stay together forever.
Now the wish has come true.
Even if I am punished for breaking the ban,
I won't regret it.
When all the spirit artifacts are in place,
I will be able to awaken.
Then, we can lift the curse.
Unless you hate me,
otherwise, the curse will never break.
But I would rather die
than let you hate me.
You shouldn't have been so cruel to cast it.
But it saved your life,
so I don't regret anything.
Then today,
we need to do another thing
that we will never regret.
Are you willing to do it?
Yes, I am.
Witnessed by the snow and ice,
matched by the cloud and wind,
Qin Lie and Ling Yushi
of the Ling Town in the far north
will take each other as husband and wife.
We got to know each other.
We made our promises for life.
We will grow old together
and be with each other through everything
with no regret.
I know about the wind, the sea
and most importantly, you.
I devote to you my heart, my affection
and my everything.
With water as wine,
we hereby take the vow today.
Against a background of violence,
disciples of any sect
are able to swagger
boldly in the open.
Except you,
who are forced to hide in the dark.
It's been ten thousand years.
Do you want to keep living in shadows,
or devote your body
to the Supreme Voodoo Insect left by our ancients
to bring glory to the Black Voodoo Cult again
so you can walk in broad daylight?
We pledge our allegiance to you, Master.
Where is Qin Lie now?
In the snowfield.
The Scarlet Tide Continent.
Ling Town.
It's Chu Li.
Don't pull a long face.
I only got beaten up 'cause I let my guard down.
I'll be fine after resting for a while.
I am so sorry, Yushi.
I occupied your new house.
It's fine.
What should we do now?
Go and find Du Shaoyang.
Go where to find him?
The only lead we have is
the Graveyard of Gods.
Alright.
Let's go now.
If we really find Du Shaoyang later,
don't fight him and leave it to me.
What do you want to do?
Don't worry, he already has a plan.
But Xuanxuan...
I am fine.
You stay here in the Ling Town.
Don't go and risk your life with us.
No.
Every time I left you, I ended up regretting it.
I don't care.
I will go wherever you go.
But I can still see the tears on your face.
Obviously, you are very vulnerable right now.
I am afraid you might hinder us later.
How about you go back and cry for a while?
Shut your mouth.
Let's go.
Such a tough girl.
Master,
I am back.
Master?
When we first met,
it happened to be that time of a year
when the moon was in its zenith.
First met?
You mean ten thousand years ago?
Guess ten thousand years ago,
something happened between us.
You know it better than me.
My master,
there are things I know about
and things I don't know about.
Tell me about it.
I am
a dagger you forged before.
You are the dagger?
I am the first spirit artifact you ever made.
My master,
aren't you happy to see me again?
I am neither happy
or unhappy to see you.
Is that so?
I remember
you were so happy at that time.
But I was not.
If you wanted to make an artifact,
why didn't you make
a blade that slays in the battlefield,
or a strong armor that protects you from enemies?
Instead, you made this insignificant dagger.
You hold a grudge against me.
You were a powerful magic weapon
that killed countless enemies
in the battle with the Human Race.
You fought until the last minute,
but eventually you were broken
and the only part left was the edge.
I hated to see you rust or become scraps,
so, I forged you into a dagger.
You thought you were insignificant,
but you didn't know how valiant you were in battle.
You thought I made you like this willfully
but you didn't know that was the best I could do.
If you pledge allegiance to me,
I promise you that
I will take you with me to the battlefield
and lead the armies.
You pledged allegiance to me,
but why do you still hate me?
Because you're full of lies.
You actually think of me as nothing
even after ten thousand years,
when I woke up from the sleep
and we met in the Ling Town.
At that time, the moon was in its zenith.
I asked you
if you were willing to fight by my side,
you said that
you didn't see eye to eye with me.
But you never asked why
or reflected on what you did back then.
You harbor evil intentions and play dirty tricks.
Your hatred from ten thousand years ago
never stopped.
Then why don't you ask me
why I followed you but still held a grudge?
If you wanna say it, then tell me.
After you forged the dagger,
have you ever drawn it from its sheath?
Yes.
Only once.
You...
You never heard my sobbing.
You failed me.
I huddled in the cold,
dark sheath.
I ate ice and snow,
only waiting to be drawn from the sheath.
You said you'd bring me to the battlefield,
but all you did was to let a woman hold me
and stab me into your own body.
You used me on the battlefield of love.
That's enough.
I know everything
that you just said.
But a spirit artifact is still an artifact.
You won't be blamed. Just come back.
Why would I choose to be your servant
instead of the master of the Black Voodoo Cult?
I haven't paid you back for your kindness,
how can I go back now?
How will you pay me back?
Ten thousand years ago,
because of her,
you broke your promise to me.
Today, I will use your blood
to compensate all my hatred and grievance.
That's enough.
You are getting more and more absurd.
Let's just fight.
Such a long speech!
You want to fight or not?
Charge!
Don't kill them.
Xuanxuan, go bring them back.
Understood.
Qin Lie,
what are you doing?
I knew that you are my spirit artifact.
What did you say?
I didn't tell you
because I had so many doubts and questions.
I wondered why you betrayed me again and again.
I also wondered
why I could never fully trust you.
I didn't dare to tell you everything
but I didn't want to let you go either.
Now I finally know.
I forged you as my first spirit artifact.
And I also failed you.
Ten thousand years ago
and ten thousand years later,
I am the one who owes you.
So, the only thing I can do
is use my blood to wash away
your grievance and anger.
What would I want your blood?
Are you alright?
I am fine.
I won't die for a moment.
Thank you for letting me do this.
You always know what I want.
If you don't want to be the dagger,
then just be Du Shaoyang.
But then,
you won't be able to go back to be Gongmu Lie.
If I had a choice,
I would rather be Qin Lie.
You are willing to let me go?
What's the point of forcing you to stay?
Everyone has the right to choose
their own path in life.
I want more than being a dagger.
I want to be Du Shaoyang.
I want to be human.
I want to have all the emotions of a man
with their joys and happiness.
I don't care if you are
genuine or not this time,
but from this moment,
we don't owe each other anymore.
We'll go our separate ways.
And I hope we'll never see
each other ever again.
Who are you?
Jiang Yan,
the residual power of the voodoo insects
can no longer save you. Die.
Jiang Yan.
How is it possible?
Who is it?
People from ten thousand years later.
[Su Mie, slayer of the Surah Realm]
Ten thousand years later?
We traveled back to ten thousand years ago.
Just now, I knew I was doomed
so I buried the remaining power of
the Supreme Voodoo Insect
deep underground in the Spirit Realm.
I just waited
for people to take the power
so I can bring them back
to help me escape and change my fate.
Turns out,
you never wanted me to bring glory to the Cult,
you were just using me!
You need to kill them.
Otherwise, don't even think about going back.
Alright.
I'll kill you with them then.
Is this far away enough?
I think so.
What do you wanna do?
Then I'll start it.
No, no, no.
I'm gonna use the bomb to help you repent.
No.
Don't.
Let go!
It will blow you up.
I can't.
We agreed to save them.
Weird.
I can't wield the Power of Earth.
The sand feels unusually cold too.
Something is wrong.
The Power of Earth is not working.
Du Shaoyang,
you are a spirit artifact!
You should go to your master when there's danger.
Your only way out is to help your master awaken.
Qin Lie, help me.
She must have a good reason.
Let's hold it until she wakes up.
I'll try my best.
Are you dead?
No.
Don't bomb us. Please.
Don't bomb us. Don't.
You...
Are you okay now?
Your Terminator Profound Bomb is indeed powerful.
It killed the voodoo insects in us.
Pay for our medical bills!
You bombed us so badly,
you need to compensate us with lots of money.
They are definitely okay now.
Let's go. Let's bomb Du Shaoyang.
Wait.
It wasn't Du Shaoyang.
What are you saying?
If it weren't him,
then who did this?
It's the Night Fairy.
The Night Fairy?
You saw it through.
You are so annoying, woman.
I knew it was you.
Now I don't have to worry.
Worry about what?
No matter if what's happening outside is real or not,
as long as you are behind it,
you will never hurt Qin Lie,
not under any circumstance.
It's Gongmu Lie.
The name doesn't matter.
You won't hurt him anyway.
Now that I saw it through,
why don't we be honest with each other
and leave here together?
Now that you know he's not in danger,
why hurry to leave?
Why not sit down and have a chat
so we can know more about each other?
Maybe,
you will find out that my resentment towards you
is merely a misunderstanding.
Maybe,
I will stop this.
How did you know it's fake?
I tried to use the Power of the Earth,
but it didn't work.
And I felt this chill in my body.
I tried to gather sand into a sword,
but my wrist felt numb.
How can sand make you feel cold?
Only ice and snow can do that.
Right.
That's what I thought.
Then I remembered that,
we were in the Ling Town.
The far north,
where snow and wind never stops.
Such a miserable life.
So I began to think,
maybe this is not sand
but ice and snow.
Maybe we didn't go back to ten thousand years ago,
but we're still in the Ling Town,
and we never left there.
So observant.
When you have doubts,
you just pay extra attention.
I wasn't sure until you said...
Du Shaoyang,
you're a spirit artifact.
You should go to your master when there's danger.
Your only way out is to help him awaken.
How would Jiang Yan know
Du is a spirit artifact?
He's the voodoo master.
He sees everything through.
What's so strange about it?
But the most important thing is that
you can't hide your resentment towards me,
no matter how hard you try.
I'm afraid the only person that hates me
this much in the world,
is you, the Night Fairy.
We are still in the Ling Town.
This so-called ten thousand years ago,
is just an illusion you created.
Great!
So brilliant!
I'm so scared. I won't hate you anymore.
What are you after?