Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
The Long Ballad
This is a work of fiction.
Episode 14
Hurry and gather the Bear Army!
Quick!
But Mu Jin discovered me.
This is from him.
- Go. - Yes.
Anyone who acts rashly will be killed.
As ordered by Great Khan.
Don't try to use Great Khan to pressure me!
But Your Highness,
if this is truly Great Khan's instruction,
won't we be messing up Great Khan's plan...
if we send out our troops now?
- I'm afraid... - Afraid of what?
If you don't send the troops now,
we'll always be at the Eagle Army's feet.
Send out the troops and gather the Bear Army now!
Your Highness.
Why are you laughing?
Do you want to die?
I'm laughing at the fact that the mighty prince...
of the Eagle Army is actually such a coward.
Is that so?
Your Highness, you'll choke him to death.
That's what I want to do!
Calm down, Your Highness.
If you kill me,
you'll lose your last chance...
to bring down the Eagle Army.
You'd better behave.
Just say what you want to say.
Don't waste His Highness's time.
Commandant Li, the one who is protecting the city,
is my brother.
I'm the best bargaining chip you have to negotiate with him.
How much are you worth?
To my brother,
I'm worth at least half of Shuozhou City.
You're not lying, are you?
If I'm not worth it,
you can kill me anytime you want.
Stop.
Didn't we agree to meet at the city wall?
We just received news...
that Tu Ka She and Yi Bu Kan are heading towards Shuozhou...
with someone from the Central Plain.
We must move as fast as we can...
and get there before they do something stupid.
Otherwise, all our plans will go to waste.
Bring the disguise to His Highness!
Yes.
Commandant Li, the Bear Army is here.
How dare they still come here?
There aren't many of them, but the strange thing is...
there's someone from the Central Plain with them.
Auspicious clouds in the sky
Shuozhou
Mr. Li.
Look who's here.
Shuozhou
Dou.
Speak! Ask them to open the gate!
I told you to speak!
Ask them to open the gate!
I said talk!
Ask them to open the city gate.
If you touch him again,
I'll break your bones.
Mr. Li.
As long as you open the gate...
and come out to talk to us,
I'll let him go.
Or else,
I'll beat him to death right in front of you.
Commandant Li.
- Commandant Li! - Let go of me!
Let me go!
The Bear Army is too close to the gate.
If we open the gate even just a crack,
they can barge right in.
The consequences would be unthinkable.
That's right, Commandant Li.
You're a monster.
You're even hitting a kid.
Auspicious clouds in the sky
Shuozhou
I'm going...
to be a general.
Dou.
No.
Hold on, I'm coming to save you.
Commandant Li!
Commandant Li.
- You can't. - Let go!
- You can't go. - Commandant!
- Commandant Li. - Let go!
We can't put...
the entire Shuozhou in jeopardy just for Dou.
Auspicious clouds in the sky
Shuozhou
I am...
going to be...
a general.
I think Dou is saying something.
I am...
going to be...
a general.
Dou isn't kneeling...
because he's begging us to open the gate to save him.
He's saying...
Auspicious clouds in the sky
Don't be silly.
Dou.
Don't be silly, Dou.
Get up.
Hurry and get up.
Get up, Dou.
Master.
I...
I can finally be a general.
I can finally become your subordinate.
Dou, you can be a general after you've grown up.
I'll take you away.
You can't die here, Dou.
Master.
I can do it.
No.
Dou, you can't.
Dou, get up!
Daizhou has been occupied.
There are no reinforcements!
You little liar!
I'll kill you.
Dou!
I thought he said there are no reinforcements.
What's this then?
They're the Ashina Tribe disguised as reinforcements.
Send a signal with the flag!
Dispatch 10,000 soldiers!
We can't let these Ashina Tribe people...
disguised as reinforcements...
take even a step closer to Shuozhou City!
- Commandant Li! - Commandant Li!
Send a signal with the flag! Now!
Quick!
Reinforce Commandant Li!
Your Highness.
Ashina Sun's plans...
have all been ruined by that boy.
What should we do?
Why don't we seize the opportunity and lead the attack?
You killed our most valuable hostage.
You sure arranged this well.
Attack?
How are we supposed to attack with such a few people?
Let's step back first.
We'll see how things are when they get here.
Yes.
Retreat!
Stop.
- Kill! - Kill!
Bear Army, retreat!
- Retreat! - Retreat!
Retreat!
Tu Ka She, that dirtbag!
He chickened out at the last minute.
Ashina Sun, they're determined to fight to the death.
At this rate, things won't look good for us.
This stab...
is for Dou.
Don't kill me.
This kick...
is for the people of Shuozhou.
An army burning with indignation is bound to win.
Tu Ka She has already caused us to lose our advantage.
Let's retreat for now.
Come on.
This last slash...
is for the warriors who died in battle.
It's not my fault.
No! Don't kill me!
General Dou's Tomb
I don't know who you are,
but I'm sure you're not a lowly person.
I live a hard life.
I'm afraid no one would even know...
if I died in a canal.
If I can follow you and live a spectacular life,
it would be worth it even if I die.
Master, you're my future.
I'll follow you, no matter if I'll live or die.
Since I'm going to be your master,
of course we must have a formal ceremony.
From now on,
you're my disciple.
The two of us won't fail each other.
When I return with glory,
you'll have to call me...
General Dou.
I am going to be a general.
General Dou's Tomb
Congratulations on your triumphant return, General Dou.
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
General Dou's Tomb
Prefectural Governor's Manor
Send this letter to Ashina Sun.
Only to be opened by Prince Sun
Master, our two armies are at battle right now.
Ashina Sun is their prince.
Why did you write this letter?
What's the matter?
Are you worried that I might collude with the enemy?
I wouldn't dare.
I was only joking.
You've been with me for years.
When have I ever done anything I have no confidence in?
I have a plan for everything.
Everything is under my control.
You just need to make sure...
to hand this letter to him.
Yes.
Governor Gongsun.
Governor Gongsun, I have a plan.
- Tell me. - Governor Gongsun.
When the weather turns cold in the seventh month,
the north wind will rise.
We can pretend to retreat...
and give up Shuozhou City to the Eagle Army.
Then, we can set up potassium nitrate...
and dry wood in the city.
Once Ashina Sun's army enters the city,
we'll start a fire.
With the advantage of the north wind,
we'll surely burn every single one of them.
What if Ashina Sun's army continues to besiege the city?
The provisions in the city...
can only feed our people for three days.
But if we go with your plan,
both the evil and the innocent will be destroyed together.
All the civilians of Shuozhou will become refugees.
Commandant Li.
Between these two difficult choices,
do you think the price we have to pay for the latter...
is more worthwhile?
I...
Why do you think...
I want to protect Shuozhou?
What I want to protect...
is not a fortress...
but the thriving city of Shuozhou...
where tens of thousands of citizens are settled.
If it weren't for this,
I wouldn't have surrendered to the Li family...
after the rise of the Tang Dynasty in Jinyang.
Thinking about it now,
fighting or surrendering...
is merely a means to an end.
Keeping the people in peace and away from war...
is the most important thing.
These are also the principles I've been holding onto it...
in my heart.
Governor Gongsun.
You're not thinking...
of surrendering to the Ashina Tribe, are you?
Did Dou and all the warriors that sacrificed in battle...
all die in vain?
Commandant Li.
Calm down.
I was just drawing an analogy.
Sorry for being rude.
All right, Commandant Li.
It's late.
I've already secured a plan...
to repulse the enemy.
Let's discuss the rest tomorrow.
Yes.
Your Highness really came here alone.
I'm impressed.
I've heard a lot about you.
Since you invited me here,
you wouldn't set up an ambush.
Besides,
aren't you the same?
What do you want to discuss with me?
You can just cut to the chase.
If Shuozhou surrenders to you,
can you guarantee...
not to take the lives of the civilians?
What if...
I take advantage of this north wind and incinerate the city?
Although I don't expect the Eagle Army to die with me,
all you'll end up getting are the ashes of Shuozhou City.
I'm sure...
this isn't the ending Your Highness would want.
If that is your plan,
you wouldn't have put it off until now,
nor would you threaten me with it.
It's not a threat.
I'm asking you a favor.
I'm curious.
Why are you asking me this?
I've been attacking the city with my troops for days.
Shuozhou's defending troops suffered heavy casualties.
In your eyes,
am I the type of person who is soft-hearted?
When the troops of the Eagle Army...
burned down the granary,
you could've also burned...
the civilians nearby along with it.
Then I would've been forced to do anything to save the people.
But you didn't do that.
Instead, you let them live...
and informed me to come quickly.
This proves...
you don't want to do any unnecessary killing.
All these years,
you've been leading the Eagle Army to fight battles everywhere.
I've long heard about your way of doing things.
I believe...
you have the capability...
and the will...
to save their lives.
However,
all these years,
I've fought...
with the Ashina Tribe many times.
All of the Ashina Tribe people...
have a lot of resentment towards me and Shuozhou City.
Now,
if I'm going to give away my city,
then I should be very sincere.
I will give you...
a gift that will satisfy,
relieve, and appease...
all of the soldiers in the Ashina army.
I won't put Your Highness in a difficult position.
Have you thought it through?
Is it really worth it to give everything up like this?
When it comes to certain things,
there's no turning back.
It's just a gift.
Compared to the safety of the people in Shuozhou,
this is nothing.
I have...
no regrets.
I finally know...
how you got the name "the protector of the people".
Don't worry, Governor Gongsun.
I agree...
with your proposal.
I will surely keep my promise.
Okay.
Right here,
on behalf of the people of Shuozhou,
I thank you.
Prefectural Governor's Manor
We've been in battle after battle recently.
You've all worked hard guarding the city day and night.
Don't say that, Governor Gongsun.
You've been doing everything you can...
for all the civilians. It's even harder on you.
Yes.
You are our backbone.
It's all thanks to you...
that all the people of Shuozhou are united and protecting the city,
with no fear of death.
This battle has been tragic.
We must appropriately arrange...
the bereavement compensation for the soldiers who sacrificed.
When it's the right timing,
we must also send someone to Chang'an...
to report the situation here in Shuozhou...
and ask for help.
Over the recent years,
Shuozhou has been suffering from poor harvests.
Now, the granary has been burnt down...
and our military colony fields are destroyed.
This makes our situation even worse.
How are we going to get through this winter?
What will we do about the livelihood of our people in the coming year?
You'll need to think about these problems carefully.
In the future, there will be a lot to take care of in Shuozhou.
I hope all of you will do your best.
I hereby...
thank everyone in advance...
on behalf of the soldiers and civilians of Shuozhou.
There's no need for that, Governor Gongsun.
It's our duty.
You don't need to thank us.
I am thanking you...
for your deep kindness...
on behalf of the Shuozhou soldiers and citizens.
Commandant Li.
It's difficult to turn down such gratitude.
Just accept it...
and drink this cup of wine.
Here.
Madam's millet wine is indeed the best.
It's so sweet and rich.
It's been a while since you've had a break.
Drink more if you like it.
This is a family meal.
Just relax yourselves.
Be good, Yuan Er.
Put the wooden sword down first.
We'll play after dinner, okay?
Okay.
Yuan Er got this wooden sword today...
and wouldn't let go of it.
I asked her why.
She said she wants to protect the people and help the weak,
just like Shi Si, Dou, and her father.
You must grow up quickly then, Yuan Er.
When you grow up,
we'll eliminate evil together.
That's great.
Yuan Niang,
hurry and say thank you to Shi Si.
If that's really what you aspire to do,
then learn some martial arts to protect yourself.
If one day,
Father isn't with you anymore,
you'll be able to protect yourself...
and you won't be bullied by bad people.
Why won't Father be here?
Silly girl.
Are you never going to get married?
Are you going to stay by my side...
until you become an old lady?
Honey, let me drink to you too.
All these years,
I put all my focus on fighting on the frontlines.
I have to thank you...
for giving me support,
looking after the wounded,
taking care of the logistics,
and pacifying the people.
You had to take on all those burdens alone.
You even took care...
and taught our Yuan Er...
by yourself.
I really don't know...
how I can repay you for everything you've done for me.
We complement each other...
and understand one another.
You don't need to repay me.
You have your principles.
This is also my choice.
I told you this before.
If there's something you want to do, just do it.
Even though I'm just the madam of this back courtyard,
I'll keep up with you...
and walk your path with you.
Honey.
You have to take care of your health.
It's autumn now.
You need to nourish your health.
Otherwise, when the winter comes,
you'll feel the cold...
and have trouble sleeping again.
You don't have to worry about me.
The winter is rough,
but spring will eventually come.
Spring will eventually come.
Here.
We need another drink.
This drink...
is a toast to Shuozhou.
After experiencing this calamity, I hope Shuozhou will be blessed...
with good weather,
have good harvests, just like things used to be.
With you here, it will definitely happen.
Come on.
Protect the frontier to bring peace to the people
Governor Gongsun, did you ask me to stay behind...
because you have other orders?
Commandant Li, please have a seat.
Please.
Inside is Shuozhou City's defense map.
All our supplies,
grain depots, and the treasury...
are all clearly marked on it.
As for this command token...
With this,
you can mobilize Shuozhou's defending troops...
and the people in this manor.
Why are you giving me these?
All the troops of Shuozhou listen to your orders.
Why are you giving me the command token?
Shuozhou's defending troops only listened to my orders...
because I've always been here.
Governor Gongsun.
What do you mean?
I've made up my mind.
Tomorrow, we'll open the city gates and surrender.
Ashina Sun has also already promised me...
that he'll make sure all the civilians will live.
At what cost?
What's the price we have to pay?
The price?
The price is...
my life.
Governor Gongsun.
Please give me a little more time.
I'll definitely come up with a foolproof plan.
This is already the best option we have.
Governor Gongsun.
All these years,
the Ashina Tribe has never occupied Shuozhou City.
So to the troops of Shuozhou,
as long as I'm still alive,
they'll never surrender...
even if they're down to their last stand.
But to the Ashina Tribe,
I've guarded the frontier for years.
Their Great Khan has lost countless battles against me.
He hates me to the core.
Now, I can only offer up my life...
in order to dispel his doubts and resentment.
This is also the only way...
to get the people in the city a chance of survival.
No, I won't allow it.
There must be another way.
Being able to entrust the lives of the civilians in Shuozhou City...
to a Tang princess...
and commit an act of benevolence...
is considered a happy ending for me.
Princess Yongning is very smart.
You still have a lot to do in the future...
and a long journey ahead of you.
You can't break down here.
You know who I am.
The man who chased you that day...
called you Princess Yongning.
Princess Yongning,
do you have any last words?
I fought him before.
Based on his martial arts techniques,
I deduced that he must be an imperial guard in the palace.
He chased you all the way to Shuozhou to kill you,
yet he didn't have an official arrest warrant on him.
Other than the former Crown Prince's old subordinate,
who else could it be?
Actually,
to me,
it doesn't matter who you really are.
Ever since the first time you pulled that little trick...
and saved my wife and Yuan Er,
I knew you were no ordinary person.
No matter what intentions you had at the start,
I knew one thing for sure.
You had no ill intentions towards me or Shuozhou City.
That's why I was willing...
to keep you by my side.
Unfortunately,
I won't be able to see the day...
you walk to the end of the path in your heart.
Governor Gongsun, my name is Li Chang Ge.
I'm the daughter of Crown Prince Li Jian Cheng.
I'm not Princess Yongning anymore.
Now,
I just want to fight the enemy with you.
Please revoke your command.
I'll definitely do all I can to protect Shuozhou.
Your Highness.
Your Highness, don't do this.
I have been loyal and righteous all my life.
Especially at a time like this,
I cannot overstep my bounds.
I'm the one who should be on my knees right now.
Your Highness,
you have such kind affection for the civilians of Shuozhou City.
Please accept my gratitude.
Governor Gongsun.
Please rise, Governor Gongsun.
I don't deserve this.
Please get up.
Your Highness.
I have one more favor to ask.
At this point,
this is the only thing I can't let go of.
My dear Yuan Er...
hasn't grown up yet.
I know...
that after my death,
my wife won't be willing to remarry.
So I'd like to ask Your Highness...
to take care of her...
and my daughter, when possible.
I hereby...
thank you...
on behalf of the two of them.
Governor Gongsun.
You should be watching Yuan Er grow up.
Please take back your command.
Please, Governor Gongsun.
I'll watch over them...
and pray for their safety from up above.
Elder Qin.
Take Her Highness to get some rest.
Governor Gongsun.
Governor Gongsun!
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
The Long Ballad