Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
The Long Ballad
This is a work of fiction.
Episode 13
Governor Gongsun.
This is all because of my negligence.
Because of our geographical advantage,
I moved the men from the east to the west.
I'm willing to redeem myself.
Please send me to the east to face the enemy.
That's enough.
When two armies fight,
it's a battle of wits.
It's not entirely your fault.
I just didn't expect that...
the elite troops of Ashina Tribe...
are so tricky.
Xu Feng.
Gather everyone.
Get them to come with me and Commandant Li...
to face the enemy together at the East Gate.
Yes.
But Governor Gongsun,
they worked tirelessly...
to steal from the granary.
The East Gate and the granary are miles apart.
How did they do that?
They're so fast.
Shi Si Lang.
You need to be clear about it.
From now on,
you're dealing with Ashina Tribe.
They're the fiercest cavalry.
On my mark.
Fire!
Shuo
Master!
- Governor Gongsun! - Master!
- Governor Gongsun! - Governor Gongsun!
It's all right.
I just need to wrap it up.
Governor Gongsun.
Governor Gongsun, you should go back first.
Leave it to me.
Lead everyone.
Guard the east side of the city!
Yes, sir!
Send Governor Gongsun back!
Yes.
This is bad! They brought reinforcements!
As you have planned,
Ya Luo took our men and destroyed the farms.
Gongsun Heng will find out about it soon.
Put it on.
I'm such a handsome man.
Why should I put on a mask?
Fine.
I should have chosen a nice mask.
Auspicious clouds in the sky
What do you think? Do I look good?
Shuozhou
Isn't that Shi Si Lang?
So you're worried that he might recognize us.
You hid your real identity before.
Shut up.
Since both of you are not true friends,
things are way easier.
Just kill him.
Let's catch the leader first.
I told you to shut up!
Relay my orders.
Attack the city in full force!
Attention, Eagle Army.
Kill them!
- Kill them! - Kill them!
Chief Registrar Li, the defense...
at the East Gate has always been the weakest.
I've sent people to get the watchtower and catapult.
Do we have knife rests?
We only have less than 100kg barbed wires.
We could only set up...
at most a line of defense with what we have.
Eagle Army will most likely avoid it.
Use all the barbed wires.
Yes, sir!
Be it the Eagle Army or the reinforcements,
they must have been riding all night.
They didn't have time to prepare...
food and water for the horses.
- Don't eat it! - Don't eat it!
Don't eat it!
Stop the horses!
All right.
It's Shi Si Lang again.
Ashina Sun.
We have to kill him!
If we lose the war,
it'd be difficult to explain to the Great Khan!
- Stop! - Stop!
Ashina Sun!
Why are you hesitating?
Prince Sun!
Auspicious clouds in the sky
Shuozhou
- Chief Registrar Li! - Master!
Master.
- Master! - Chief Registrar Li!
Help!
Master!
Auspicious clouds in the sky
Since your commander is dead,
just come out and surrender!
We promise not to kill anyone if you surrender now!
- We accept surrender! - We accept surrender!
Shuozhou
Auspicious clouds in the sky
- Chief Registrar Li stood up! - Chief Registrar Li is not dead!
- Chief Registrar Li is not dead! - Chief Registrar Li stood up!
That's impossible.
Ashina Sun.
You're the best warrior on the grasslands.
You've never missed your target!
- How great. - Yes!
- How great! - How great!
No way, Ashina Sun.
The commander of Shuozhou is still alive.
The morale of the Tang Army is soaring high.
This is not the right time to attack the city.
- This... - This...
Retreat.
We'll camp outside the city.
- Retreat! - Hurry up!
- Retreat! - Retreat!
We won!
- We won! - We won!
Master!
Why do you get up?
How is Governor Gongsun doing?
Master, you're badly injured.
You shouldn't be worrying about others.
I'm fine.
It's just a minor injury.
Furthermore, the military doctor has changed my dressing.
At the moment,
the battle with Ashina Tribe is more important.
Governor Gongsun is injured.
How can I rest?
The new wound has triggered Governor Gongsun's old disease.
He's in his bedroom now.
Dou.
Go to bed early.
I need to talk to Governor Gongsun...
Master, don't forget...
that your target is not Shuozhou,
but Chang'an!
Your health is of the utmost importance.
Dou.
In comparison to the calamity in Shuozhou,
the resentment between Li Shi Min and I...
is merely a personal affair.
But now,
Shuozhou is in great danger.
I can't just sit back and watch.
Besides,
you can change the dressing for me in time, right?
I'm worried about your health, Master.
Look.
I'm fine.
Wolf Army is attacking Yunzhou and Daizhou.
The Great Khan demanded you to conquer Shuozhou in 10 days.
Otherwise, His Majesty will do it himself.
If we continue camping outside the city,
can we take down Shuozhou in 10 days?
When the Great Khan gets here,
Eagle Army will become the laughingstock.
A beast at bay will put up a desperate fight.
But for how long?
You're right.
The granary was burnt to the ground.
The farm was destroyed.
Let's starve them to death.
Mu Jin.
How are my archery skills?
You've never missed your target.
Ashina Sun.
Don't tell me...
you plan to sneak into Shuozhou?
No way. Absolutely not.
I was wrong.
You are quite the archer.
Shi Si Lang is fine for sure.
I mean it.
Bring the report.
Let's meet up with Tu Ka She.
I'll get rid of him.
Shuozhou...
will be taken over by the Eagle Army.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
In order to win against the Eagle Army,
I still have an idea.
What are you doing here?
The Bear Army is down and out.
How do you plan to explain this?
Your Highness!
Your Highness, please spare my life!
I promise...
I'll make sure to kill Chief Registrar Li!
Please give me another chance, Your Highness!
A missed opportunity is a lost opportunity!
Because of your one move,
half of the Bear Army could never come back to the grasslands.
If I give you another chance,
I'm afraid even the Eagle Army can't save you.
Your Highness.
I have the heart to contribute to the Bear Army!
Heaven and Earth will be my witnesses!
Do you plan to explain to the Great Khan...
with this man's life?
The Bear Army is being held back by the treacherous official.
Regarding that...
I'll explain it to the Great Khan myself.
There's no need for that.
I've received the order from the Great Khan.
Why do you bring it to me now?
Do you still want to humiliate me?
We only hope that you can stop acting impulsively.
I don't expect you to contribute.
Just don't hold the Eagle Army back again.
You're trying to grind the Bear Army...
beneath your heel.
You're being overly impatient.
We've no choice...
but to report everything to the Great Khan.
Tu Ka She blatantly disobeys His Majesty's order.
Prince Sun.
The Prince of Bear Army has received your order.
Please leave.
Yi Bu Kan.
Yi Bu Kan!
Can't someone watch the door?
This is the battalion of the Bear Army,
yet everyone just barges in as they like!
The Eagle Army has just changed the venue of their battalion.
They will do something for sure.
Watch him closely. Keep an eye on him!
Do you understand?
Yes, sir!
Watch the door!
Just say what you want to say.
We could have bought off that strategist...
for our own use.
Why did you let Tu Ka She kill him?
I don't like traitors.
But he's right.
Gongsun Heng had wings on him.
If we get rid of Shi Si Lang,
things will be a lot easier.
If the Great Khan takes action himself,
you know the consequences better than anyone else.
Why are we just procrastinating?
She Er's Wolf Army will conquer Daizhou soon.
Great Khan demanded that we assist him.
When the time comes,
I'll send you.
Me?
Ashina Sun.
I just talk too much.
You don't have to push me into the pit of fire.
Once this battle is over, you'll set off.
Remember.
When you reach Daizhou,
keep some defender's clothes with you.
Don't make things difficult for the common people.
You don't have to tell the Great Khan...
what I just said.
Is that all?
Tell me what's going on!
- Attack! - Attack!
Come on!
Run!
- Run! - Hurry up!
Run for your life!
- Come on. - Run!
- Help! - Help!
What's happening?
- What are you doing? - Help!
- You can't go in! - Help!
- Open the door! - Help!
- What happened? - They have invaded the city!
Close the door.
- I'm begging you. - What are you waiting for?
- Come and help! - Please let my child in!
I'm begging you!
Open the door! Open up!
Please let my child hide!
I'm begging you!
I'm begging you.
Let the kid hide.
I'm begging you!
- What are you doing? - Please!
Let them in.
How dare you!
Who do you think you are?
How dare you point scissors at me?
Do you want to die?
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Help me.
Where is she?
Hey!
What are you doing?
The Great Khan demanded us to chase after...
Daizhou's army that escaped from the city.
Let's go!
Hurry up!
Master, where are we going?
Let's check the east part of the city.
The east of the city is besieged by the Eagle Army right now.
However, the area outside the east of the city is full of forests.
We never took strict precautions in that area.
The Eagle Army may not be that vigilant too.
Even if they keep a close watch,
there are so many mountains, so I'm sure we can avoid them.
Dou.
You're all grown up.
Pawnshop
- Run. - Master, let's go together.
Call for help!
You followed me here.
It seems that not only you want Crown Prince's seal,
but you also want my life.
So what?
Governor Gongsun has been gravely wounded.
Shuozhou is surrounded by enemies.
Do you really have to kill me during this time?
Cut the nonsense.
My job is to kill you now.
Princess Yongning,
do you have any last words?
Even if I die,
I won't die...
in a lackey's hand.
Master, are you all right?
Do you know who she is?
If you help her,
you'll regret it later.
I only know that...
he's the Commandant of Light Chariot of Shuozhou...
who is fighting hard to resist foreign enemies.
Sir.
I guess you came into Shuozhou...
before it is besieged by the Eagle Army.
You should know...
the situation in Shuozhou, right?
Governor Gongsun is injured.
Everyone in Shuozhou...
is relying on Chief Registrar Li.
So...
I can't let you hurt him.
If you insist on helping her,
we'll just wait and see.
Thank you, Elder Qin.
Elder Qin.
I have an idea.
We can get out.
Back then, when we drown Tu Ka She in water,
we drained all the water...
from the drainage that connects to Wuding River.
Master, let me go.
Your injuries...
I'll do it.
I'm more familiar with it.
Chief Registrar Li.
Governor Gongsun?
- Please help Elder Qin. - Governor Gongsun.
- Chief Registrar Li. - Why are you here?
Elder Qin told me...
you found a stone canal...
that leads outside the city.
Judging by your outfit,
are you going to notify others on your own?
The canal in the city leads to the Wuding River.
The city is besieged by the Eagle Army.
Wuding River is the only place that is not heavily guarded.
If I don't go now,
I'm afraid there will be no time.
I plan to get out when it's dark...
to inform everyone.
You're already severely injured.
Today, you're attacked again.
It's like rubbing salt to the injury.
How could I...
put you in danger again?
That's right, Chief Registrar Li.
That man was merciless.
Chief Registrar Li.
Let me go.
Shuozhou needs you and Master.
Only when both of you are around, people in Shuozhou can survive.
Furthermore, I'm Governor Gongsun's guard.
It's my duty.
No.
The canal was used to drain water.
It's narrow. You're not going to make it through.
Governor Gongsun, I can do it.
I can go through it.
Dou!
Master, I know you're worried about me.
You don't want to put me in danger.
But you're injured.
If you don't get well soon,
you won't make it through.
What if you pass out on the journey...
and delay in seeking help?
That's why I'm the best candidate to do it.
Please trust me, Governor Gongsun.
I won't let you down.
Stop messing around.
You're just a kid.
How can I put you in danger?
It's precisely because I'm young...
that I won't draw their attention.
Besides,
why did my master take me as his disciple?
It's because I'm smart.
I've been with my master for so long.
I've learned many tricks from him.
But when I'm back,
please let me have a title in the military camp.
Master.
Don't hesitate.
We've been through so much together.
Don't you think that I can handle it?
All right.
Make sure you take care of the bag.
There are an escape route map and a wrist crossbow in the bag.
You can use it against the pursuers.
Master, you are very insightful.
When I return with glory,
you'll have to call me...
General Dou.
Dou.
Take care of yourself.
Yes, Master.
Tell everyone to hang in there.
Wait for me!
Chief Registrar Li.
You took in such a great disciple.
I didn't teach him much.
I, on the other hand,
am so blessed...
to have met him.
Your Highness.
Our men followed Mu Jin...
but he shook them off halfway.
He was heading towards Daizhou.
Daizhou?
What does that mean?
Has the Great Khan conquered Daizhou?
What's wrong?
Why?
Why don't I know anything?
No one takes the Bear Army seriously!
Calm down, Your Highness.
I'll keep a wary eye on Ashina Sun.
I'll never let him deceive the Great Khan...
and take all the credit for conquering Shuozhou.
That's enough!
That's nonsense!
Get lost!
Prefectural Governor's Manor
Broad-minded and knowledgeable
Yuan Niang.
You're finally back.
People in the city sent us food.
They said that even if they could only afford husks,
they had to make sure that Governor Gongsun...
and the soldiers have enough to eat.
I sent them all back.
Those are all the grains people have been saving.
I don't have the heart to take it.
My dear wife,
you did the right thing.
Father.
They said it was all thanks to you...
Shuozhou is not conquered.
Yuan Niang, you're praising me again.
However, I think...
Shuozhou...
is still surviving...
because of them.
It has nothing to do with me.
I can't take the credit.
Count the rations...
and the grains that we own.
Distribute them to the people.
Yes.
We must survive until Dou is back.
Go!
Minister Yi, as per the Great Khan's demand,
we've annihilated all the soldiers in Daizhou.
How about those who escaped from the city?
They were killed too.
Well done. The Prince of Eagle Army...
send someone from Shuozhou.
Great Khan instructed us to take him in.
Go back to the city.
Don't make the representative of Eagle Army wait.
Yes, sir!
We're doomed.
The bridle-road is blocked.
The news can't reach Chang'an.
Daizhou has been conquered too.
We can't get reinforcements.
What should I do?
I have to hurry back...
to inform my master.
- Stop. - Stop.
All of you.
Take Tang Army's military uniform.
After leaving Daizhou,
change into Tang Army's military uniform.
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
- Go! - Go!
Come on.
Get up.
- Spare our life. - Spare our life.
- Please spare our life. - Please spare our life.
- Please. - Please.
Kneel. Hurry up!
Why should we kneel?
It's because of them that we're suffering now.
Kneel down!
- Please spare our life. - Please spare our life.
Stop.
Stop it!
Who are you?
It doesn't matter if you don't recognize me.
Can't you recognize Wolf Fang Arrow?
Since when the Eagle Army has control over the Wolf Army?
Know your place and get lost.
You should know...
how powerful the Eagle Army is.
If you lose your life because of the refugees,
it's not worth it.
Retreat!
- Go! - Go!
Go!
You should go now.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
It's urgent. We need to hurry.
- Yes. - Yes.
Go!
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Let's go home.
- That's great. - Father.
- Go! - Go!
Isn't he...
the baby monkey that was on that person's side?
Yes.
I know you.
Kill him.
Hold on!
My king!
I have something to tell you.
"My king"? It's His Highness.
Yes, Your Highness.
You greeted me wrongly.
Kill him!
Your Highness must be curious about the situation in Shuozhou.
Spare me.
I may be useful to Your Highness.
Tell me what is so great about you.
Otherwise, I'll chop you into pieces.
I bet you know that...
Chief Registrar Li trusts me.
I know all his moves...
better than anyone.
During the battle at Wuding River,
Your Highness lost so many soldiers.
It's impossible for Your Highness to continue the battle.
I heard that the Eagle Army is taking the lead...
Darn you!
Nothing you say is pleasant to the ears!
Are you trying to make me mad?
Kill him!
If Your Highness had any control over the situation,
Your Highness should have known that Chief Registrar Li...
has been promoted to Commandant of Light Chariot!
Your Highness, you should keep me...
and let me negotiate with Shuozhou.
I can make Chief Registrar Li...
hand Shuozhou on a silver platter.
Now,
even this little monkey...
has the guts to deceive me.
Do I look so gullible?
Do I?
That rascal, Sima Jian, lied to you!
Your Highness,
Chief Registrar Li and Governor Gongsun are dying.
They were both seriously injured by the Eagle Army.
It's the perfect time to make peace.
I know them really well.
No one is more suitable for peace negotiations than me.
The Eagle Army has been fighting for so long.
However, everyone in Shuozhou still works together with high spirits.
At worst,
even if I can't persuade him,
we can crush the morale of the people in Shuozhou.
That's something...
the Eagle Army can't do.
Let's trust him for this once.
Tie him up to my horse.
Bring him to the battle.
Make sure he lives.
Yes, sir.
It's the Great Khan's order.
Intrusive maneuvers will be executed.
Go!
- Hang in there. - I can't walk anymore.
Young lady.
You mustn't do that.
Put it on.
You're so kind.
Young lady, you were kind enough to save me.
If only my daughter...
was as lucky as I am.
You must stay alive.
You'll be able to see your daughter soon.
Your Highness, the Eagle Army...
obtained a lot of clothes belonging to soldiers of Daizhou.
In the journey, Mu Jin instructed the Eagle Army...
to change into Tang Army's military uniform.
The Eagle Army wants to take the lead!
Gather the Bear Army!
Hurry up!
Sub by VIU & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
The Long Ballad