Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♫  Nowhere to escape  ♫
♫  No one to rely on  ♫
♫  Withdrawing smiles  ♫
♫  Never give in  ♫
♫  Forget about one's youth  ♫
♫  I've never been afraid of loneliness when
embarking on this journey  ♫
♫  Tears and regrets go hand in hand  ♫
♫ But my heart is still fiery-hot ♫
♫ To the distance ♫
♫ The miserable past is like a dagger ♫
♫ Though my wings are broken ♫
♫ I will keep flying ♫
♫ Following the direction of the light ♫
♫ I'll forget you ♫
♫ The memory shaped my stubbornness ♫
♫ By virtue of the light in the dark night ♫
♫ I'll return it with a long ballad ♫
♫ The river of life is under my feet ♫
♫ I don't regret my craziness ♫
The Long Ballad
Episode 13
Governor, this is all my fault.
I capitalize on terrain too much, moving our troops from east to west.
I want to atone for my faults.
Please let me handle them.
Fine.
The war is all about the wit and moral courage.
It's not entirely your fault.
I just didn't know
the elite squad of Ashile Tribe could be this cunning.
Xu Feng, summon all our people
to meet me and Commandant Li
at the East Gate and confront the enemies.
Yes.
But Governor, they were constantly on the run
before they attacked our barn.
Now they're at the east gate, miles apart from the barn.
How could they be so quick?
Shisi,
you should know that
from now on,
you're facing the most elite and powerful cavalry of Ashile Tribe.
On my order.
Shoot!
Master!
Governor!
I'm fine.
Put a bandage on it and it'll do.
Governor!
Governor, you should go back.
I'll be here.
You need to lead the troops
and defend the east side.
Yes!
Take Governor back, now!
Yes.
This isn't good. They've got reinforcements.
Yaro has destroyed all the state owned land
according to your plan.
Gongsun Heng shall find out about it soon.
Wear this.
Come on, I'm so handsome.
Why would I wear this?
Alright, then.
I should've picked a prettier one.
How about it?
Do I look good?
Shuozhou
Isn't that Shisi?
You're afraid that he'll recognize us.
So you've both hidden your real identites.
Shut up.
So you're not real friends.
Well, that just makes everything fine.
I'll kill him.
Destroy the leader and the gang will collapse.
Shut up!
Give out my order.
Go all the way to attack the city.
Attention, Eagle Division!
Kill!
Registrar, the east gate has always been the least defended area.
I've sent people to get lookout towers and catapults from elsewhere.
Do we have any more javelins?
The remaining iron caltrops are less than 50 kilos.
We can only lay one line of defense
with the iron caltrops now available.
And the Eagle Division can easily avoid it.
We should do whatever we can
to make the best use of the existing iron caltrops.
Yes!
Whoever they are, Eagle Divison or reinforcements.
They must've been on the run the entire night.
They wouldn't have enough time
to feed their horses with food and water.
Don't eat that!
Stop eating!
Stop it!
Rein up!
Nice!
It's him again!
Sun, we must kill him.
If we get defeated,
Great Khan would be so mad at us!
Sun!
What are you hesitating about?
Tegin Sun!
Registrar!
Master!
Help!
Your commander is now dead.
Surrender now, get disarmed
and we won't kill you.
Surrender! Surrender!
Surrender! Surrender! Surrender!
Surrender!
Commandant Li stood up!
Commandant Li didn't die!
How could it be?
Sun.
You're the best warrior on the plains.
You never miss the targets!
Great!
Great! Great!
No way, Sun.
The chief commander of Shuozhou didn't die.
It boosted their morale.
It's not a great time for us to launch an attack.
Well...
Withdraw.
Encamp outside the walls.
Withdraw now!
We won!
We won! We won! We won!
Master!
Master.
Why are you up?
How's Governor doing?
Master, you're seriously injured.
I can't believe you're still worring about others.
I'm fine.
It's just minor bruising.
Not to mention that the doctor has changed my dressing.
Right now,
what really matters is our war against Ashile Tribe.
Governor is also wounded.
How could I rest?
Governor's new injury triggered his old wounds.
He's at his bedroom now.
A'Dou, You should go to bed now.
I'll go talk to Governor
- and see what we can do.
- Master!
Don't forget that your target is not Shuozhou,
but Changan.
Your health is everything.
A'Dou,
compared to this war in Shuozhou,
the personal hatred between me and Li Shimin is nothing.
Right now,
the situation in Shuozhou is grim.
I can't just sit by and do nothing.
Well,
you'll change my dressing on time, right?
I'm just worried about your health.
Look,
I'm fine.
Wolf Division is targeting Yunzhou and Daizhou.
Great Khan ordered you
to take Shuozhou in ten days.
Or, he'll lead the troops himself.
If we just camp outside the city like this,
I doubt if we can take Shuozhou in 10 days.
By that time,
Eagle Division will be an object of universal derision.
A trapped beast will still struggle.
But it won't last long.
Fair enough.
We've burned their barns,
and destroyed their lands.
They'll be starved to death.
Mu Jin,
what do you think of my archery?
You never miss a target.
Sun, don't tell me you're sneaking into Shuozhou
at a time like this.
No way.
I won't permit that.
I was wrong.
Your archery is just great.
Li Shisi must be alright.
Really.
Take the reports.
Let's go to see Tu Kashe.
I need to get rid of him.
Eagle Division must be the one
to take over Shuozhou.
Tegin, there's no need to be angry.
If you want to surpass Eagle Division,
I have another plan.
What are you doing here?
Bear Division was badly injured.
What are you going to do?
Tegin.
Tegin, have mercy on me.
I swear, I promise!
I will kill Registrar Li.
Please, Tegin, give me another chance.
You missed your chance
and that's it. You lost it forever.
It was your trick
that rendered half of the Bear Division dead.
If we give you another chance,
maybe even Eagle Division couldn't save you.
Tegin, god knows how eager I am
to serve Bear Division.
You think you can just kill him
and get things over with Great Khan?
Bear Division was misled by a treacherous minister.
I will explain it to Great Khan myself.
No need.
I have received Khan's order.
Now you're taking it to me.
What?
Are you trying to humiliate me?
We just want you to stop being reckless.
We don't want to take credit for occupying Shuozhou.
We just want you to stop holding us Eagle Division back.
You just can't wait to tread Bear Division underfoot, right?
Why the rush?
Then you leave us no choice but to report the truth to Great Khan.
That Tu Kashe defied his intructions openly.
Tegin Sun,
Tegin of Bear Division has received your order.
Now please.
Ibukan.
Ibukan!
Isn't there anyone who'd guard the entrance for me?
This is the camp of Bear Division.
Do your job and guard the damn door!
Eagle Division changed their camp site.
They must be up to something.
Keep an eye on him.
Keep an eye on him!
Understand?
Yes!
And guard the damn door!
Just say it.
You could've just bought over that counsellor.
Why did you provoke Tu Kashe into killing him?
I don't like traitors.
But he was right.
Gongsun Heng got a brave general all of a sudden.
Things would be much easier
if we kill Li Shisi first.
You know it better than anyone that
what will happen if Great Khan leads the troops himself.
Why are you just laying siege to this city?
Sher's Wolf Division will soon take Daizhou.
Great Khan ordered us to assist them.
I'll send you there.
Me?
Ashile Sun, yes, I am a bit talktive.
But that doesn't mean you've got to throw me to the wolves.
Once this war ends, you'll leave.
Remember, when you're in Daizhou,
save some clothes of Tang defenders,
and don't hassle common people.
You don't have to tell these to Great Khan.
That's it?
Shouldn't you set things straight before you go?
Hurry!
Run!
Run! Run!
Hurry! Hurry!
Run!
Hurry! Run!
Hurry!
Run!
Help!
What's going on?
What are you doing?
- Help!
- You can't come in.
Help!
Open the door.
Open the door! Help!
What happened?
The enemies are breaking in.
Close the door.
Please, I'm begging you.
Come on.
Help me close the door.
Just take my kid in, okay?
I'm begging you!
Please!
Open the door! Open it!
Just let my kid in!
Please help us!
I'm begging you!
Let my kid in!
Please!
What are you doing?
Let them in.
Are you nuts?
Who the hell do you think you are?
How dare you point the scissors at me?
You're seeking your doom.
Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Help me!
Where did she go?
What are you doing here?
Great Khan sent us to chase after
the Daizhou Force that has fled from the city.
Hurry up!
Come on!
Master, where are we going now?
Let's go and take a look at the east side.
Right now, the east side is under siege by the Eagle Division.
But outside the east gate, there're towering and forested mountains.
We don't have our forces garrisoned there.
So might the Eagle Division.
However tight their defense might be,
I don't think they can find us
among so many mountains.
A'Dou,
you've really grown up.
Go now!
Master, let's go together!
Get someone here!
You followed me the whole way here.
I guess you want more than the Seal of Crown Prince.
You also want to kill me.
So what?
Right now, Governor Gongsun is seriously wounded.
Shuozhou is surrounded by enemies.
Do you really have to kill me right now?
Cut the nonsense.
It's my duty to execute you here.
Princess Yongning, any last words?
Even if I were to die,
I wouldn't be killed by a pawn.
Master, are you okay?
Do you know who she is?
If you help her,
you'll regret it later, for sure.
All I know is that she's the commandant
who's protecting Shuozhou.
Young man, you must've sneaked into Shuozhou
before the siege by Eagle Division, right?
Then you must be clear
about what's going on here.
Governor is wounded.
Everyone in Shuozhou rely on Commandant Li.
So I won't let you hurt her.
If you insist on helping her,
we'll wait and see.
Senior Qin, thank you.
Senior Qin,
I have an idea.
We can get out of here.
Back then when we flooded Tu Kashe,
we pumped the stone canal dry
that once drained into Wuding River.
Master, just leave it to me.
You're still injured...
I'll go.
I might be a bit more familiar
with this place than you.
Commandant Li.
Governor?
Help Senior Qin out.
Governor.
- Commandant Li.
- Why are you here?
Senior Qin told me that you found a stone canal
that might lead out of Shuozhou.
Seeing you dressed like this,
are you going to deliver the message yourself?
The stone canal in the city leads straight to Wuding River.
Shuozhou is now under siege by the Eagle Division.
Wuding River is the only area with no garrison.
If we don't spread the message now,
I'm afraid we're running out of time.
I plan to get out of here
and deliver the message while it's still dark.
You've already been seriously injured.
And today you were almost assassinated,
which just made things even worse.
How could I let you risk your life?
Yeah, Commandant Li.
That guy hit you real hard.
Commandant Li, let me do it.
Shuozhou need you and Master.
You're the hope of Shuozhou.
Also, I'm Master's bodyguard.
This is my duty.
No.
The stone canal was built for drainage.
It's too small for you to get through.
Governor, Iet me do it.
I can get through it.
A'Dou!
Master, I know you're worried about me.
You don't want to put me at risk.
But you're already badly injured.
If you don't get a good rest,
you wouldn't be able to carry on.
You don't want to pass out halfway
and cause delay in reinforcement request, right?
So I'm the best choice for this task.
Governor, please place your trust in me.
I won't let you down.
Enough of this nonsense.
You're just a kid.
How could I put you at risk?
Yes, I'm too young,
and that's why I won't attract their attention.
Besides, Master accepted me as a disciple
because I'm smart.
I've been learning from Master for a long time.
I've commanded so many tricks.
But, when I'm back,
Governor, would you award me some titles?
Master, stop hesitating.
We've been through so much.
You don't think I can handle it, do you?
Fine.
Take this baggage with you and don't lose it.
You'll find an escape route map in it
and some pocket crossbows
with which you can beat off the enemies.
Master, nice choice.
And when I'm back in glory,
you'll all call me General Dou.
A'Dou,
take care of yourself.
I will, Master.
Tell everyone to hang in there
and wait for me.
Commandant Li,
you have a great disciple.
I didn't teach him anything.
In fact, I'm the lucky one to meet him.
Tegin.
I sent people to spy on Mu Jin.
But he managed to get rid of them halfway.
He seemed to be leaving for Daizhou.
Daizhou?
What does that mean?
Great Khan has taken Daizhou?
What's happening?
Why?
I know nothing at all!
What? Do they take our Bear Division seriously?
Tegin, don't be anxious.
I will lead a team to keep an eye on Ashile Sun.
I won't let him fool Great Khan
and take all the credit for occupying Shuozhou.
Enough.
Cut that nonsense.
Get lost!
Now!
Yuan.
You're finally back.
People sent food here just now.
They said they'd eat chaff and herbs
as long as you and the soldiers are well fed.
And I had people to send it back.
They saved their own food.
I couldn't accept it, really.
Madam, you are right.
Father.
Everyone is saying that
you're the one who's defending Shuozhou.
Your mom must have praised me again, right?
But I think, they're the reason Shuozhou exists,
not me.
I can't take the credit.
Check all the food provisions
and the grains we have.
Distribute it to the common people.
We must hold out till A'Dou comes back.
Yes.
Tegin,
we've killed all the Tang soldiers around Daizhou
on Great Khan's command.
What about those who fled Daizhou?
They were all killed.
Good.
Tegin of Eagle Division has sent someone here from Shuozhou.
Great Khan ordered us to meet him.
Let's go back to Daizhou.
Don't keep that messenger waiting.
Yes.
Damn it.
The post road was blocked.
I can't send message to Changan.
And Daizhou fell to the enemies, too.
We won't be able to get any reinforcements.
What should I do now?
I must go back
and inform Master of this.
Stop.
You guys.
Find some clothes of Tang soldiers
and get changed on our way out of Daizhou.
Yes!
Come on.
Get up.
Have mercy on us.
Don't kill us!
Please spare us!
Come on, kneel down.
Why should I?
They are the real culprits, the offenders.
Just kneel down.
Have mercy on us! Don't kill us! Please!
Please don't kill us!
Stop.
Stop it.
Who are you?
You don't know me. That's fine.
But I'm sure you can recognize this spike arrow.
Since when does Eagle Division get to tell us what to do?
If you're smart, you'd get lost now.
You know well what Eagle Division is capable of.
I suppose you wouldn't want to die
for these refugees.
Let's go!
Go!
You should go now.
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
We must get back to Shuozhou as soon as possible.
- Yes!
Go!
Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you!
Let's go home.
Great!
Father.
Isn't he that... That...
That guy's apprentice?
Yes!
I know you.
Kill him. Just kill him. Now.
Wait!
My lord! Lord!
I've got an update for you.
Lord?
He's our Tegin.
Yeah, okay. Tegin! Tegin!
You got my title wrong.
Kill him. Kill him. Just kill him.
Tegin, right now you must be desperate
to know what's going on in Shuozhou.
Spare my life and I'll prove myself useful to you.
Then tell me how you might be helpful to us.
Or, I will kill you myself.
Tegin, you know that
I'm Registrar Li's trusted follower.
I know his tricks better than anyone.
During the battle around Wuding River,
you lost so many soldiers.
The situation for you is grim.
I also heard that
now it's the Eagle Division that's leading the attack.
Screw you.
I don't want to hear any of these.
Did you take him to me just to piss me off?
Kill him. Just kill him. Kill him.
If you were still able to manage the battle,
how come you know nothing
about Li's promotion to Commandant?
Tegin, spare my life.
Let me talk to the generals in Shuozhou.
I'll make Commandant Li
to offer up Shuozhou submissively.
Now even a cute little cub dares to cheat me.
Do I look like a fool to you?
Do I?
Sima Jian, that liar, he cheated you.
Tegin, you don't know it.
Commandant Li and Governor Gongsun are dying at this moment.
The Eagle Division hit them real hard.
This is the best time for negotiation.
I know them quite well.
I'd be the best one for this task.
It's been so long since the Eagle Division laid siege to Shuozhou
and people there are still closely united with high morale.
Even if I fail, which is highly unlikely,
it'll demoralize them greatly.
That's something Eagle Division can never do.
Let's take his words for the moment.
Tie him to my horse.
He'll be going into a battle with me.
Don't kill him yet.
Yes.
Great Khan ordered that
any one who makes a rash act will be executed.
Come on!
- Hang on.
- I'm too tired.
Miss, I can't take it, Miss.
Wear these.
Miss, you're so kind.
Thank you for saving my life.
I wish someone could save my daughter.
You must survive.
Maybe you'll get to see your daughter one day.
Tegin, the Eagle Division collected many clothes of the soldiers
defending Daizhou while cleaning up the battlefield.
And later on their way back,
Mu Jin ordered the Eagle Division to change into Tang uniforms.
They want to grab the credit from us.
Gather Bear Division now!
Hurry! Come on!
Sub by Viki & Ripped by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
♫ The heart gradually responds, ♫
♫ gradually revives, ♫
♫ gradually swims towards you ♫
♫ Before bidding farewell, ♫
♫ we expect an encounter ♫
♫ As your silhouette weaves ♫
♫ and locks in my nostalgic dream ♫
♫ Before the daybreak, ♫
♫ through the obsession of love, ♫
♫ the yearning flowing through thoughts ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ where the wilderness burns in my heart ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into an eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
♫ There's always a moment ♫
♫ where the wilderness burns in my heart ♫
♫ There's always solicitude ♫
♫ which froze everything between you and me ♫
♫ Meet each other in different time ♫
♫ Encourage each other in different worlds ♫
♫ My longings become a cocoon ♫
♫ Layer after layer ♫
♫ It turns into eternity ♫
♫ The cocoon in the dark night ♫
♫ It is sleepless ♫
The Long Ballad