♪I’d taste all the bitterness and pain♪
♪Just to be with you♪
♪Yet we could never be inseparable♪
♪As you and your shadow♪
♪Warmth aside♪
♪Deep down inside♪
♪What I felt♪
♪Was nothing but pain♪
♪My only wish was♪
♪Our souls could connect♪
♪Now we’ve stopped dreaming♪
♪Or longing for warmth
After darkness♪
♪The dawn would break out♪
♪Bringing bitter warmth♪
♪And glaring sunlight♪
♪When we gave up waiting alone♪
♪And went back to our original promise♪
♪Someone would endure pain for love♪
♪Someone would be♪
♪The love of our life♪
=The Blessed Girl=
=Episode 2=
(A few months ago
Zhaodu, the capital)
All good.
Summon Fei Tian.
Your Majesty.
Did you activate the Calculator again?
I’m ready
to receive the nobility
coming to the capital to pay respects.
They’ve left.
Left?
I asked them to leave
to protect Your Majesty.
I’m old enough
to deal with them.
Your Majesty, do you remember
when was the last time
they came
to pay respects to you?
When was that?
I barely
remember their looks.
Why did they flood in
all of a sudden?
They came to check
if I could still keep the throne.
What are you going to do?
They’ll see
I carry the Yuan’s bloodline.
I am the chosen one.
No one can replace me.
Your Majesty,
are you
going to play tricks on them
with the Calculator?
Tricks?
It’s Immortals’ legacy!
You said it yourself
it’s a legacy.
God’s gone for 100 years
without any trace.
Back in the ancient Suchuan,
God
only existed in stories.
Your Majesty,
a state’s prosperity
lies in humans
instead of Gods.
It’s true!
Our ancestor and God
used to fight side by side
to seal the Evil Soul underground
and bring peace and unification
to this once
uncivilized and blood-stained land.
They drove out
enemies over and over.
Because of them,
Suchuan has been in peace
for a thousand years.
That’s all the more reasons for you
to work harder as the emperor
to not lose your state
to others.
Work harder?
The nobility has risen to power
over the last hundred years.
My decrees couldn’t
even get out of the capital.
Right now, what Suchuan needs
isn’t a diligent
but weak emperor
but the one blessed by God.
You’re the last descendant
of the Yuans.
I, Fei Tian,
and the Moon Tribe
will safeguard you and Zhaodu
as long as we can breathe.
Good day, Your Majesty.
You don’t believe in God?
He’s not here
at the moment!
It’s true that Goddess
has never left.
They’re back.
What happened?
Don’t know.
What’s wrong? Is she alright?
Is something wrong?
No idea.
Go get the physician.
No need.
Look, they’re back.
Don’t say a word to Linglong
about what happened earlier.
Leader,
is that monster
the Fire Demon?
Shut your mouth!
Would you still be on your feet
if it was a monster?
Chi Fang,
go with him.
Yes.
Take this.
Leader,
what about him?
Sweetie,
don’t scare me.
I promised your mother
that I’d take good care of you.
You...
Huotu Xin,
open up.
You aren’t alone.
We’re here to help.
Open the door,
Huotu Xin!
What?
How’s Linglong?
She’s fine.
About that thing...
What thing?
What are you talking about?
Linglong needs to rest.
Leave her alone.
Huotu Xin!
Hey,
who are you?
You...
You aren’t a member of our tribe, right?
I’ve got lost.
Miss,
where are you from?
Pingting.
Pingting?
Linglong!
Father.
How do you feel?
I think
I had a dream,
a bad one.
In the dream,
I hurt you.
Silly girl.
Look at me.
I’m strong as an ox.
It was
like a dream,
but
too real to be one.
I’m sorry, Jin’er.
I wasn’t there with you
when Linglong was born.
Huotu Xin!
There you are!
Your wife is giving birth.
She’s in labor. Go home quickly!
Hurry up, Huotu Xin!
The midwife is already there.
Run faster!
Why are you leaving?
Monster!
You have a monster at home!
Why must we go there?
The Earth Fire
behind the Flame Chilling Wall
can kill people.
Besides,
outsiders
aren’t allowed to be there.
Ancestors made that rule
when the Wall was built.
No one has ever broken it.
You’ve already broken the rule once
by marrying me, right?
They aren’t the same things.
Jin’er,
why do you
insist on going there?
You can tell me.
I’ll explain it to others.
Don’t worry.
I’ll let you know
when we get to the Palace of Flames.
No entry is allowed there.
It’s a deathtrap inside.
Why must we take such a risk
with our baby?
It’s for me
and her.
Trust me.
I’ll tell you everything there.
Let’s go.
Be careful.
Jin’er,
the entrance is right ahead.
We must be more careful.
This way.
Slowly.
Be careful!
My baby!
No!
This is for her.
She’s going to need it someday.
Jin’er!
You are...
This is for her.
She’s going to need it someday.
You knew what would happen,
didn’t you?
Come on.
I know you’re awake.
Stop pretending.
Finish this bowl of noodles first.
You do this every time
when you’re in trouble.
Aren’t you hungry?
Doesn’t it smell good?
Do you want it?
You can’t hold it.
Father.
Go on.
Why did you stop?
Go back to sleep.
Father,
you won’t punish me
while I’m still weak, will you?
Fill yourself up.
Once you’re done,
think carefully
about what you should say to me.
Isn’t this mother’s necklace?
Eat up.
Who are you?
What are you doing over there?
All done.
Bring it on.
I’m at your disposal.
Your chin almost touches the floor.
You can’t even look at me?
Look up.
What were you thinking?
You almost made my heart stop.
Thank goodness, you’re safe.
This necklace
had been with your mother
the whole time
until she left it to you
before she passed away.
You didn’t get to see her inside,
but her necklace
will protect you instead.
I knew
-you wouldn’t punish me.
-Oh, stop it.
Knock it off.
Just save it.
You do this every time.
So do you, right?
What about me?
Seriously, are you not going to tell me
about last night?
Are you
avoiding it again
just like how you avoid
what happened to mother?
Are you going to
keep that to yourself forever
without telling anyone?
Linglong!
you’re still young.
I’m not, father.
I can tell
the strange glance
they shot at me
as if
I were
a public enemy
without knowing it.
Linglong...
The longer you keep me in the dark,
the more I’m eager to know the truth
and put myself in grave danger.
Would you rather
see me risk my life
and get injured again?
Of course not.
Then tell me
what happened last night
after I got burned
by the Earth Fire.
How come there isn’t even a scratch
on me?
Are you sure
you don’t remember anything?
Yes.
I might have
seen a boy.
Who is he?
You
don’t know him?
Good. Great.
I was about to
ask you about your relationship.
So he’s a stranger to you.
That’s a relief.
I was worrying for nothing.
Your Majesty.
Chief Priest,
were God here,
would the Pillar of Eternity shine?
In ancient times,
every year at the Ritual of Eternity,
God
would follow Heavenly Immortals’ will
and spread out
their grace through the Pillar.
Then
it would shoot its light up to the sky.
Pillars all over Suchuan
would resonate with it
and bestow such light
on every corner of the land.
At that time,
the sky
became incredibly magnificent.
Would Immortals
receive my prayers?
How come God no longer descends
to guard the Yuans?
The Yuans are the royals
of the Immortal Blood.
Your reign
is the proof of God’s existence.
Royals of the Immortal Blood?
Maybe
God is expecting
a great emperor.
Your Majesty,
16 years ago,
one Pillar of Eternity somewhere
did shine.
Really?
Scouts didn’t return
with any information,
but I believe
that was
God’s message to us.
I’ll find you!
So,
who are you?
What do you know?
How’s
that girl?
You know Linglong?
Yes.
We’ve known each other
since ancient times.
Utter nonsense!
You...
Be specific.
You mean that monster
or Linglong?
Monster?
It’s understandable
that you don’t recognize her.
Goddess has been away
from you for so long
that you no longer remember her.
Are you saying
that monster
is Linglong?
If Huotu Xin
hears that baloney,
he’d whack him for sure!
Chi Fang,
what do you think?
It’s kind of ridiculous.
But given what happened back then...
Haven’t Huotu Xin
done enough ridiculous things?
I guess
only he
can tell us the truth.
This time,
he can’t get away from it.
He didn’t say it 16 years ago.
Would he
do it now?
Look,
we can’t keep him here.
I agree.
Leader!
Calm down.
Tell me everything bit by bit.
Shizi...
He... He’s dead.
Linglong.
Xin.
Is Linglong alright?
She’s fine.
That’s good.
Come with me.
Did you see them
bringing back
an outsider?
I didn’t.
But my father said
there was a stranger in the dungeon.
Tanmiao,
could you do me a small favor?
No problem.
I need to
ask that stranger a few questions.
Could you distract
your father for a while?
It’s all for Linglong.
Fine.
Are you expecting questions from me?
Don’t you have any?
Kids these days
are so cunning!
My daughter wants to know
who you are,
but I
have no interest in that,
let alone
what you’re up to
or what you know.
On the contrary,
people with such information
should disappear for good.
I don’t want anyone
to know about that.
What are you doing?
Hold on.
You saved my daughter,
so I owe you one.
But our Leader
doesn’t think so.
I know him well.
It’s just a matter of time
before you’re burned to death.
Follow me
if you want to live.
Wait.
Hang on.
This is it.
Go back to where you belong.
Don’t you want to know the truth?
Didn’t you
call Linglong Goddess?
Do you know what that means?
All I know is she’s my daughter.
She has nothing to do with other things.
Listen,
keep your mouth shut.
Or I won’t be easy on you.
You don’t need to tell me that.
I’ll leave
only if you join me.
Join you?
On what ground?
I saved you
and Linglong.
If she transforms herself again,
only I can protect her in Suchuan.
Your tribesmen
have known
that she’s that monster.
Do you think your Leader
will allow you to stay here any longer?
You told them?
It’s the first time in 500 years
that God has descended to Suchuan again
in your daughter’s body.
Nothing is better than that.
Whatever happens
to my daughter
stays in my family.
You’d better leave.
Don’t ever come back again.
Understand?
She should go with me.
She doesn’t belong here.
She doesn’t belong to you alone.
Brat,
I’m warning you
that if you harass Linglong again,
I’ll burn your whole family to ashes!
Not before you know who I am first.
As a Fire Tribesman,
you’ve never
gone out yourself or with Linglong
in your entire life, right?
Yes. So what?
Please hear me out.
You think
by living in seclusion in the mountains
with your tribesmen,
Linglong can live a peaceful life
despite all those secrets about her?
Last night,
the Pillar of Eternity
outside the Palace of Flames was lit up.
You saw that, didn’t you?
It already
happened once
16 years ago
when Linglong
was born, right?
You’ve tried so hard
to bury that.
Zhaodu took that one
as a mistake
but that very Pillar of Eternity
has shone again.
How long can you keep that secret?
Pillar of Eternity.
What is that?
What’s that ray of light
got to do with Linglong?
Now, you want to know?
Cut to the chase.
Answer me!
I’ll tell you
but you have to believe me.
She should leave with me
because she could be in danger anytime.
What danger?
Do you see that twinkle?
It comes from the Flying Crystal
outsiders use to send messages.
I bet
I’m not the only one
knowing that secret.
Linglong!
Leave us alone,
or I’ll kill you!
Think hard.
What would
the great Emperor Yuan Tu do?
Hey.
I knew my father was unable to change.
He said he’d ask you about the truth
but he didn’t follow through.
You must’ve known
that I’m Linglong,
and
what’s your name?
Yuan Yi.
That’s my name.
Yuan Yi,
thanks for saving me.
It’s done by a saber.
Saber?
Not that monster?
It’s not our saber?
No.
It’s been over 500 years.
The storm
is coming.
Linglong!
Ling...
Who are you?
Where’s Linglong?
Father,
it’s me, Linglong.
I’m asking you.
Where’s Linglong?
Father,
how could you not believe me?
I can change my look
however I please
like I did yesterday.
Do you like my new look?
You were there yesterday?
Was that thing
in the sky yours?
You aren’t that stupid
and you aren’t too blind.
You...
You... You... You...
Your daughter
is in danger.
Is this hers?
Linglong!
Follow me
if you want to see her.
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪All the more reason to be a flower♪
♪Next life in spring♪
♪I’d blossom near you♪
♪I’m not sure if I’m strong enough♪
♪I’m not sure if I can make you smile♪
♪Happily every day♪
♪Just like sometimes♪
♪I get caught up in fear for no reason♪
♪Sunlight we take granted for♪
♪Might disappear one day♪
♪In this world♪
♪If there was no such thing as eternity♪
♪I’d be more grateful♪
♪For the moment we met♪
♪Right at that moment and place♪
♪You cast a spell♪
♪It’d always turn out♪
♪To be something new♪
♪Other than love what else♪
♪Could toughen me up♪
♪Without faith♪
♪I’d still feel lost♪
♪Everything you left♪
♪Lit up the bottom of my heart♪
♪Even to this day♪
♪I can still see light♪
♪How lucky I am♪
♪To have met you in this life♪
♪To have put a smile back on my face♪
♪Feeling loved♪
♪I wish to do something in return♪
♪So I choose to start over♪
♪My life♪
♪Once withered like a falling flower♪
♪Until the day♪
♪We met as if it were a dream♪
♪We were close♪
♪We were distant♪
♪Looking back♪
♪At all that we’ve been through♪
♪I’d be a flower in the next life♪
♪So that I could be with you♪
♪Life ebbs and flows♪
♪Flowers bloom and wither
People meet and part♪
♪All that is fate♪
♪That’s how the world works♪
♪You gave me♪
♪This moment♪
♪You gave me treasure♪
♪To make life warm♪
♪So I won’t give up♪
♪I’ll live my life to the fullest♪
♪To be your flower♪